- We're making three different dishes.
The winner gets $10,000.
But, this cook off has a huge twist so let's go.
You challenged us to make a pizza, but here's the twist.
We're not allowed to use a rolling pin,
a pan, a knife, or a can opener.
So, let's go. I've got a whole bunch of
dough cause I'm making a - Whoa!
Chicago deep dish pizza man. - Nice.
I have to cook my eggs but I can't use a hotplate
or a pan.
So, I'm using dry ice.
- Oh my gosh! That's gonna freeze an egg.
There's no way it's gonna cook the egg though.
- I guess we'll find out.
- Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oh!
Dude, it's sizzling, bro. - Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- If you do that I'm gonna create
my Chicago deep dish, but the issue is
I'm not allowed to use a pan. So, I'm just gonna
have to kinda - Let's just
mold it with my hands, - get that out of the way.
here like this. - This is pretty cool man.
- Look at it right there man, just kind of like
bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh.
- Oh, dude! I'm gonna try to cook the egg
in this thing here.
- Yo, it's like bubbling up! - That is so cool!
- I gotta say, that's probably the coolest way
I've ever seen eggs cooked, man.
- This reminds me of a stress ball.
- The deep dish crust is done.
Next up I gotta make some rotisserie chicken right now.
- It totally worked! Oh!
- Look at this!
- Wait, just pick it up is it stuck on there though?
- It's a little stuck.
What? - Oh my gosh!
- Dude! - It looks like a saucer!
And because I'm not allowed to use a knife to slice up the
chicken I brought along some
wolverine claws, - Whoa!
out of my private collection, so.
- Wait a second, what? Yup!
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(yelling) - Oh! Oh!
and don't try this at home!
- Yeah, do not try this at home.
- Do not! - Here we go! Let's send
this off. I didn't know - Whoa!
I needed chicken, - Woo, Iron Chef!
- but now I do! Alright, here we go.
- I have a lot of chicken. - Oh my gosh!
(growling)
- Kind of blacked out there for a second.
What just happened? - That was crazy!
- You got chicken in your hair,
now look to the side. - Do I?
- And since I can't use a hot pan or a grill,
or anything, I gotta use two irons.
- Wait for what? - That's right
I'm cooking the hot dogs just like this.
- Oh my- oh geez!
That isn't really cool man. - This is totally working.
- You lost a dog.
Next up, time to slice up an onion.
(grunting and heavy breathing)
- Alright, my hot dogs are cooked.
- Alright, well you know,
I think it's time to retire the wolverine claws
and man, I gotta say these things were a ton of fun.
(growling)
- (yells)
- (growls)
To cook my steak, I have a brand new way of doing this.
We are using Gallium,
or should I say, liquid metal. - Wait.
And I've heated it up - what!
where the Gallium is now molten
It's extremely hot and we're gonna be pouring it
on here to see if it sears it, and cooks it.
- You're not gonna eat that right?
- No, you can not eat it once the Gallium has touched it,
we're just doing it to see if it'll actually work.
Do not try this at home!
Put some safety goggles on.
We got a cutting board right here.
We are taking this very
seriously. - Whoa! Gonna get out of the
- way a little bit.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1,
Ohhhh!
- No way!
- Listen to that, oh my gosh!
- Great job! - Yo,
I can smell it sizzling.
It's literally molten metal right now guys
on the inside of this thing. - Eww!
- Look at the metal's like still liquid
and everything dude. - Wow!
- This is definitely gonna win me the $10,000.
- Alright, next up I gotta roll out my dough,
but unfortunately, I can't use a rolling pin,
so I gotta use these things.
- Hold on, why do you have blue dough?
- Dude, this thing is very difficult.
What is going on?
- Alright, here we go, we're just gonna lather
some of this cheese on, just like this.
What are you doing?
- I'm trying to roll this thing out.
- Here we go, I've now lathered up my cheese.
It's time to shave it.
So let's see here, here we go.
Just gonna shave it like this.
- This is actually working out.
- Ohhh! Look at that man.
Cheese shaving out the wazoo bro.
- I'm putting the hot dog in the crust,
and now I'm attaching it to the crust.
- You're encrusting a hot dog. - Yes (drums)
Alright, my crust is done
and now it's time to cut up some pepperoni.
What are you doing?
- I'm brickening my cheese man.
Yeah I can't figure - You're what?
out how to cut it. - That's not a term!
- That absolutely is man.
That's like really clean.
- I hope you sanitized that brick Collins.
- I did man, I always clean my bricks before I use them
in my cooking. - Alright, time to
cut up this pepperoni.
- Wait, how you gonna, again see, how you gonna cut that up
without a knife. - Oh.
- You're probably gonna need to use a brick!
- Oh no, no, no.
- Uh huh - I got the best way.
Alright Collins, I got the saw!
- Yo what! You brought a full saw you'd use to
chop down a tree? - Yes.
- This does not belong in a kitchen, Devan.
- Here ya go. - Do not try this at home.
- Three, two, one
- [Both] Ooooh!
- Yes! - [Both] Yooooooo!
- $10,000 here I come. Time to get rid of the saw,
I think I did what I needed to do.
- Wait, wait, wait, what about my cheese though?
Okay, fine. You know what,
back to the brick bro, back to the brick.
- It's almost time to assemble our pizzas,
but first, I need the most important ingredient,
tomato sauce.
- while you do that, I'm gonna make some squiggly potatoes
with some squiggly scissors here.
- Oh wait! - It broke my
squiggly scissors.
- Oh, yes!
Yes! - Oh My Gosh!
- It's opening, I need something to put it in.
- Oh yes! - What!
- Squiggly potato number one.
It's such a little amount of tomato sauce
for the amount you're having to squeeze that thing dude.
- I know. - And the finishing touch,
I grab my mom's hair crimper like this,
and no we're gonna put this thing inside like this
and then we're gonna cook the potato
just like this. - What!
- Here we go! - Alright!
- I've got all the sauce I need
and now it's time to assemble our pizzas.
- This is like ketchup, right?
- Dude, that's like half of my sauce!
- Oh man, double dip.
- What're you doing?
- Alright well now let's assemble the pizzas.
We've got all the pizza ingredients,
and now it's time to assemble it.
So I'm gonna kick it off right here with a whole bunch of
tomato sauce man! - Same dude!
- Alright here we go. Three! Two! One!
(yells) - Whoa
- Dude this thing splattered it man!
- (yells) - What?
- I lost concentration for a sec.
- My pizza was so great. - But it got on me bro.
Next up, we got some of this cheese,
so here we go, let's just splat down the cheese like this
Oh yeah man! - Whoa!
- First layer is all done,
time for the second layer.
- Alright next up, I'm laying down
a base of cheddar cheese
- I'm putting a whole bunch of chicken
and onion for this layer.
Alright here we go man, just gonna keep pullin it in,
pullin it in, uh oh.
- I hope it tastes good, because
it doesn't look so great
- This is food, Devan,
it's not about how it looks, it's about how it tastes.
- Alright time to put the finishing touches on these things
and find out who wins the $10,000.
- Got the completed pizza's
and I have never seen a pizza that looks like that before.
Here's the big reveal, you ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one, ta-da!
- Bro! And when I slice this thing open,
man it's gonna be incredible on the inside.
You get to comment down below and vote.
Who's pizza do you think is gonna taste better?
We'll be trying them
as well as choosing the $10,000 winner
at the end of the video.
You challenged us to make a taco,
but we're not allowed to use a tortilla press, a knife,
or a griddle. So let's go!
Because I'm not allowed to use a griddle,
I'm kicking off by turning my watermelon
into a functioning grill right now.
- Wow!
- And since I can't make a normal tortilla,
I'm making a rice tortilla
- [Both] Oh! - Okay, here we go, let's go.
- Dude! (yells)
- It's in my eye, it's in my face.
- Alright here we go. - Well I'm going to continue
- over here. - I am drenched off the bat.
- Instead of making normal white rice,
I'm making purple rice!
- That is brand new bro!
I've never seen a purple rice taco before.
That seems like it's be a lot more convenient, man.
- I'm really excited to see if it works.
- I'm confused.
- Whoa, is this cause you - Three, two
can't use a knife? - One. Oh my gosh, I feel like
- One. Oh my gosh, I feel like I'm using a sword right now
okay, (grunts)
- I hear it goin' - Oh snap!
- [Both] Dude!
- No! - Nice!
- But a perfect slice
off the top! - Good job!
- Come at me bro! Give me a high five! Yeah!
- The rice is cooked and it's cooled,
and now it's time to make the patty.
- This is called juicing from the bottom
- Careful!
- (yells) - Oh man!
- I regret nothing.
- Alright well now, I'm taking out my rice from the top
and I'm gonna lay it down on this very hot skillet thing.
- Wait, why? - 'Cause this is gonna
cook the patty dude.
- It's like sizzlin bro,
you're gonna like crisp rice though man.
- Exactly.
- (yells)
- What? - It ran into my armpit.
- Final step is to make the grilling top
here on the melon, so we're bringing back the drill, baby.
- It totally worked!
- Oh my, dude that's super crispy.
- Wait, dude what are you drilling on your watermelon?
- I'm gonna be grilling a whole bunch of meat for my taco.
- I think my purple rice is finally ready
to be formed into the perfect tortilla shape.
- Time to finish up the watermelon grill,
this thing is coming along amazing.
- My purple rice taco shell is done,
now it's time to slice up my pepper.
- Wait, so how you gonna slice that without a knife?
- [Both] Oh! - Liquid Nitrogen!
- Dude, this is so cool! - I know right!
- Oh my gosh! Do not try this at home,
we have a trained professional here.
- It's time to dunk in my pepper.
- Oh my gosh! - This is food grade
liquid nitrogen,
so you can actually eat whatever you put in it.
- [Both] Three, two, oh wait,
- Three second like-challenge,
we wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds,
you ready? Here we go,
- [Both] Three! Two! One! Done!
Three! Two! One! Ohhhhhhhh!
- It's like bubbling up - Oh! Oh, oh, oh!
- It's bubbling up
- Alright I gotta get it out!
- I'm gonna use the pineapple to protect myself
- Dude, this is definitely gonna win me the $10,000.
- And the steam is like all by my legs right now,
it's so cold!
- This is insane! - Oh my! It's like a hot bath
except it's freezing cold! - Whoa!
Look at that, it's working!
- Dude! This is the most amount of liquid nitrogen
we've ever had before.
I kinda wanna freeze my pineapple now.
Can I freeze some pineapple?
- No, no, no, this is for me Collins.
- I just wanna freeze some pineapple.
- This is for me. You can actually knock on it right now.
- I have never heard a pepper that sounds like this before.
Man, this is- - I haven't either.
- so cool!
- [Both] Whoa!
- Oh my gosh! - It's already starting
- to crack,
alright it's ready to go. - Oh my gosh!
- I'm setting it down.
- It looks like it's been stuck in cryo sleep
for years, man. It's like coming out right now.
Again, do not
try this at home. You ready? - Yes.
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
(smashes pepper)
Ohhhhhh!
- Oh my gosh! - No Way!
(replay in slow motion)
- And this is all I need, that's perfect.
- That sounded like a piece of glass dude!
That is the best alternative to a knife I have ever seen!
Holy cow! - This is insane!
- Alright my first ingredient of my salsa is done.
Next ingredient is this mango and a drill.
- Wait, you're gonna put a drill in a taco?
- No, no, no, I'm drilling the mango.
- Why are you drilling the mango, bro?
- I gotta drill the mango to get the mango out
to put it into my salsa.
Now I hit reverse and we reverse outta there
and look at that! A little bit of mango at a time.
- If you can't tell, this is my not impressed face.
- Dude, I'm working without a knife.
- I'm not impressed. - Have you ever tried to make
salsa with just a bunch of diced up fruits and vegetables
without a knife?
- We're not impressed.
Next, I'm gonna pickup some piece of pork right here alright
let's just drop 'em in. So here we go, splash.
- And now I'm cracking these crab legs.
- I put a whole bunch of hot coals
inside the watermelon grill,
so hopefully this is gonna work.
- And do not try this at home.
Bro, this looks so good.
Three! - [Both] Two! One!
- Oh!
- Dude, listen to it sizzle bro!
- Dude! I didn't think this would work man.
A watermelon grill?
- Well what might not actually work is cracking these
with some bolt cutters!
- Wait! Bolt cutters?
- An employee at target told me it was a life-hack.
- Alright that's enough pieces of pork for right now.
Perfect, so now I'm gonna let those
cook and roast - Whoa!
- It fits! Oh yes!
- Oh my gosh!
It actually works man! - Dude!
- Here, how about this bro, I'll help
you out a little bit Devan.
You don't need any help I guess, okay.
- No help needed.
- Oh snap!
Dude mine are cooking so perfectly, bro, look at this!
- Oh! - It's starting to come along!
- Yes! Look at that!
- Alright here we go, gonna press my tortilla,
got a tortilla pressing contraption.
- Dude, that is way too elaborate!
- You can never get too elaborate
when trying to press a tortilla.
First, I'm gonna put the two pieces of glass together
like this, what are you doing?
You got a frog man, - I got a frog.
- You're supposed to make music with that.
Separate the two, just like this and then plop it down.
- Ooh! Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep! Yeah!
- We have a little pump here,
so this pump is gonna be integral to the plans.
- This does not come out dude.
- Oh my gosh are you seeing this!
- Whoa!
- Look at this! - Dude!
- Why is it not perfectly circular though?
- That is amazing.
- I'm a little concerned.
Alright man! - Nice!
- There is my taco shell.
- That is the most impressive way
I have ever seen a tortilla made.
- To cook my tortilla,
since we're not allowed to use a grill, I made a hot rock.
- Basically I stuck it in the oven, and got it super hot.
Do not try this at home.
So, let's see if it's actually able to cook my tortilla.
Three!
- [Both] Two! One! Ohhh!
- Oh no, I forgot to PAM the rock.
I gotta PAM the rock, hold on.
- Alright! Here we go! - Here we go!
- You ready? - Yup! Three! Two! One!
Teamwork man! - Yeah!
- Oh dude! It's gotten crispy!
- To cook my tuna, I'm actually using beeswax.
- Wait, beeswax?
- Yes. - You can cook something
with beeswax? - I guess we'll find out!
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
- Are you pouring it directly on the fish?
- Yeah! - Oh my gosh!
- Yo! It hardens instantly. Keep going, keep going!
Oh my gosh! - This is amazing!
- Alright the wax is all hardened
and now it's time to break out my fish.
- [Both] Ohhhh!
- Wait a minute, it looks like congealed bologna
with some weird some stuff in the middle man.
- This doesn't look so good.
I gotta break it open somehow. - Yeah how you gonna do this?
- I don't know. Three, two, one.
- [Both] Ohhhhh!
- Oh my gosh!
- Dude! - It breaks away so easily.
- It's working out perfectly.
- You gotta be careful,
you're getting wax all on my hot rock bro.
You gotta be gentle with your fish man.
- Look it, it cooked all the way through.
This is the final stretch right here.
- Oh! Oh my gosh!
- Whoa! - Yo!
- That is amazing!
- I did not think that would work at all.
Got our tacos and now it's time to assemble them,
but first we gotta add
some seasoning to it. - Yes!
- So check this out. So here we go.
(light saber sound effect)
- [Both] Ohhhh!
- Touch sabers, here we go.
- [Both] Oh!
- Flips off. Let's deactivate, there we go.
Seasoning time, see if you hold it down,
- What!
- I gotta go with the wasabi next.
You makin' like a like a sushi taco.
- Oh my gosh dude,
I still can't believe that the watermelon
was able to fully cook the meat.
Next up I'm adding this ahi tuna.
- Aw man! - There we go.
It's very nice and pink on the inside though.
- I know! - Alright! Just gonna add
this on top.
- Wax cooked fish man, how it that gonna taste?
Alright. - Look at this though.
Alright now it's time to put the finishing touches on these
and find out who wins.
- Got the finished tacos.
- And you added a whole new element,
man competition is tough.
- We're going for $10,000 man so here's the big reveal.
- [Both] Three! Two! Oh yeah!
- Five second subscribe challenge!
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
You ready? Here we go!
- [Both] Five! Four! Three! Two! One! Done!
- If you can do that comment down below Keyper Squad,
right now and let's see how these look.
- [Both] Three, two, one, ta-da!
- Oh my gosh,
I made a little extra thingy and everything!
You get to comment down below - Man!
who's taco do you think is gonna taste better?
We'll be trying them and choosing
the $10,000 winner at the end of the video.
- You challenged us to make a burger
but we are not allowed to use a knife, a hotplate, or a pan,
so let's go!
To kick mine off I gotta crack some eggs,
- And I gotta slice up some tomatoes. Three!
- [Both] Two! One!
Ohhh!
- No way!
- What are you making? - I'm making the breading
for my chicken. Next up is for me to slice up this beef,
but I can't use a knife,
so I've got the next best thing, a paper shredder!
- Wait, that makes no sense
that's the office paper - Really?
shredder Devan. Wait, okay I don't
even think it's gonna be able to
grind up that meat to be honest bro.
Next up, we gotta melt the cheese,
So we got my moms wax melter over here,
just gonna place some cheese in
and I'm sorry mom, from now on whenever you melt wax
you're gonna smell like a little bit of cheese.
- Alright my beef is tenderized
and Collins it's time for you to hold the shredder.
- This is raw meat, do not touch raw meat
and do not try this at home!
- [Both] Ready? Set! Go! Oh!
- Snap! - Dude, it worked!
- It does sound kinda broken though.
- It's stuck, I want it back, I want my meat back.
- Why you can't get it! Ah, my cheese fell!
Look, it's starting to overflow on the top Devan.
I gotta say, man I did not think that this would work bro,
but I'm actually shocked.
- I'm actually kinda surprised this worked too.
- If this was featured in an infomercial,
it would be the next billion dollar product for sure!
You ever find yourself at 3 p.m.
thousands of feet above the earth in a Goodyear blimp
with nothing but raw meat and a paper shredder?
- No. - But if you did,
what would you wanna do with it Devan?
You got raw meat, - Beef basher!
- No that's not the design yet.
You got raw meat and you got a - Beef basher!
- Devan, you've got raw meat and a paper shredder
- Beef basher 2000!
- There we go! Ours!
Order today by calling my personal cellphone number 555
34 - you can't give that!
We're on air!
Got my garlic minced up,
I think I'm gonna make some aioli
and I'm gonna use this mustard next.
- As you make your aioli,
bro I'm gonna be filling my patties with cheese.
Alright here we go, so let's see if I can
suck up some of this cheese,
Three! Two! One!
- [Both] Oh!
- It's working! It's working! - Nice! Nice!
Gotta overpower this garlic with all the other ingredients.
- Oh my gosh! I'm gonna go on the side like this,
here we go, three, two, one,
just gonna inject the cheeese - What are you-
- [Both] Oh! - It's dripping out the sides!
- Oh boy! Okay.
- Time to mix my stuff up! next up gotta cook my shrimp.
- We don't have a hot plate though,
how you gonna cook that thing dude?
- I'm gonna use an electric fly swatter.
- What if it like combusts the shrimp?
- I guess we'll find out - It's an electric
fly swatter, bro! If it touches it might just go, boof!
(electricity crackles) - [Both] Ohhh!
- That was definitely a piece of shrimp.
- Alright, here we go, three!
- Oh my gosh! Oh boy! - Two! One!
- [Both] Ohhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
- I did not think that would work bro.
- I didn't either. - Next up I gotta chop my
onions, but since I have no knife,
I'm gonna use a figure skate!
- A what? How are you gonna slice it?
It doesn't seem that sharp man.
- Three! Two! One!
Oh yeah! - Oh my gosh!
If you do that, here we go!
I'm gonna pop my potato on the top here like this.
- Got in my eye!
- You shoot onion juice in your eye man?
- (yells) - Are you alright?
- So how bout this, I'm just gonna borrow
your skate real quick.
This was a much better method so here we go.
Just gonna slice up like this,
give us a second, we gotta finish this up real quick.
- Dude, this no knife thing is so tough,
I'm gonna have to use pencil sharpeners to cut my onion.
- I'm having an issue with no hot plate,
but I think I've got a great solution,
a curling iron to cook my bacon.
And remember, do not try this at home.
- Oh! You hear the sizzle? This works!
Oh my gosh just gonna take it off,
and just gonna place it down here, you ready
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
(mumbling)
- Oh, gonna curl up a few more of those
and then it's time to assemble the burger.
- Time to dredge my chicken. - Dredge it?
- So, I'm just gonna dip it in here first
- That's called dredging?
- And then they go right in to here.
- Wait, ew my gosh .
- What do you mean, "Ew my gosh"?
This is gonna be amazing!
- I don't know man, it's kinda questionable.
- Alright this is my last piece of chicken.
- I've got my cheese-filled burger patties,
and now it's time to cook these in a very unique way.
You ready Devan? - I'm so ready.
- I'm sure this is gonna blow your minds,
so right now let's hop outside.
We have a Lamborghini here,
which was lent to us by our friend Chris.
We're gonna be cooking the meat in two different ways.
Number one, is on the engine
and number two is on the tailpipes.
- Here we go. Three! Two! One! - Oh man!
(car engine revs) - Dude!
- Oh my gosh! - What!
I've got the burger meat and now it's time
to see if it will actually cook. Do not try this at home.
So here we go, lemme get 'em in position.
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
(car engine revs) Oh!!!!
- Oh my gosh! Dude! it is so hot right now,
I can feel the heat coming off.
(elevator music)
Alright that's enough right now for the burgers, Devan.
So, next up we're gonna see
the tailpipe can cook your chicken.
Alright. Three! Two! One!
(car engine revs) - Dude! What?
This is insane!
(elevator music)
- Done! Alright!
- Alright. My chicken's looking super crispy dude.
- And the burgers are almost done,
so we're just gonna be cookin 'em a little bit more
and then we'll be adding these to our burgers.
Now surprisingly, this didn't work,
so we actually had to put it in the oven.
It's now time to assemble the burgers,
so I gotta say, off the bat bro,
my bun - What?
turned out so good!
- Mine looks so boring in comparison.
- It truly is,
I really hope these unconventional cooking techniques work
'cause I wanna win the $10,000 so bad man
- Dude, same.
- For my burger patty,
remember this thing is filled with cheese.
Yo, dude yours actually turned out really good.
Next up, we're gonna get some pickles on there,
'cause you gotta get some salty, crispy, crunchiness on it,
then of course we've got the spirally bacon.
Time to put the finishing touches on out burger
and I'm really excited to see who's looks better,
but more importantly, who's tastes better.
So right now let's finish these things up.
We've got the burgers
and I say mine is definitely worth the $10,000.
- I don't know man, I think mine is.
- So here's the big reveal!
- [Both] Three! Two! Oh wait!
- If you wanna win a 15 minute video call with Devan and I,
text the word "eat" to 81800 right now,
so pause the video, text the word "eat" to 81800,
you'll automatically be entered in to win,
and lets see how these turned out.
- [Both] Three! Two! One! Ta-da!
- You get to comment down below,
who's burger do you think is gonna taste better,
We'll be tasting them,
and choosing the $10,000 winner at the end of the video.
It's time to find out, which pizza tastes better.
We have two very different pizzas,
mine you got a whole bunch of layers to it.
It's extremely heavy,
dude, feel it. It's like, - Yeah. That looks
really heavy, okay - Oh my god
it's like 20 pounds bro.
- It's not that, yeah that's really heavy.
- Are you kidding me bro?
That's extremely heavy and you've got a blue pizza
so it's gonna be really interesting to see
which one tastes better.
Devan, which pizza should we taste first?
- Let's taste yours dude,
I really wanna see what's on the inside of that.
- Here we go, do not try this at home.
Here we go time to slice this open, three! Two! One!
- Not too quick. Not too quick - Yeah, okay
here we go, okay.
- Now open it. Open it up. I wanna see what's inside.
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
Ohhhhh! - Oh my gosh!
- That looks so good!
- Dude, you can see the layers man, it's perfect.
- Dude! - Alright, here you go Devan.
Here is your piece.
- Oh, thank you.
- That's your piece right there.
- I didn't know I wanted such a big piece.
- It's a two slice pizza guys,
it's kind of a Chicago deep dish tradition
wait, so seriously that's all you're gonna do,
just a forkful?
- Yes, what are you doing here?
- I'm just trying to turn it around
so I can get a bite of it.
- It's gonna fall out. - Okay, here we go.
- (screams) It's coming out!
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
- Mmm! - Whoa!
- Mmm! - Mmm!
- That is super good!
- Oh my gosh, two thumbs up!
(mumbles) the barbecue sauce.
- Dude, I did not wanna like that,
but that was so good! Nicely done!
- It's like a smurf pizza man. - What do you mean dude?
- You're breaking the middle,
oh my gosh Devan come on, clean slice!
I got mine perfectly clean, Devan
you're being judged on this man.
- This is a little bit more difficult than I expected.
- A dry ice egg man, you put an egg on a pizza once before
which I questioned but it actually tased really good,
but a dry ice egg?
- It looks like it turned out though didn't it?
- It has a weird like texture and quality to it,
I can't quite put my finger on it,
but it's not quite the most appetizing look.
- I don't know if you're looking at the
same thing I'm looking at.
- Oh, I definitely am man.
- Here's the first slice. Collins you can have the honors.
- Oh, see you missed the egg!
Your blue crust is um-
- Is what? Fantastic? Amazing? Like the ocean?
Reminds you of everything good in the world?
- Suspicious.
- Here you go Collins.
- Yep, be very careful
- Here is your, yep, there ya go.
Time for my slice.
- Wait, why do you get a bigger slice than
I do man? - I did?
- If you look at the exact, okay they're the same.
- I tried to make it pretty equal.
- They're the same, they're the same, okay I take it back.
- I did a good job on this.
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
- (coughs) - Whoa! Whoa!
- It's so bad it makes you wanna do kung fu.
Wow! hat's like a weird combo man.
(mumbles)
- Why?
- [Both] (laugh)
- That was like some really good elements,
like the pepperoni,
- Yeah! - the cheese,
I gotta say man, the crust, the blue crust
- Yeah - No!
You get to comment down below
and vote who's pizza do you think won this round.
We'll be announcing the $10,000 winner
at the end of the video. We've got the completed burgers,
and now it's time to find out
which one is worthy of the $10,000 prize.
How bout we start with yours first
- I'm super ready!
- What really makes these burgers interesting
is that they were cooked using
a Lamborghini, so it might - I know!
change the whole taste of 'em.
The chicken was right by the tailpipes man,
just taking a whole bunch of heat from the car.
- Alright I think I'm gonna cut it in half first.
- With a fork and,
I've never seen someone just cut a burger just...
- Alright here we go, going down the center.
- Dude, the shrimp, I forgot, with the electric fly swatter.
Man, just zappin it, I don't know if it cooked it or not.
- Yeah - Oh, there goes a shrimp,
You lost one. - This is a tough one man.
- Alright here we go, gonna try and sink my slice. Ready?
All right. - Yeah
- What are you pushing it into mine for?
- Three, two,
- Hold up, what are you three, two, one-ing?
- I'm revealing your burger!
You have a lot of full onions in here, man.
- Yeah, it was more for aesthetics.
- Oh my gosh, it's all sliding apart Devan.
I gotta say in terms of construction,
this burger gets a B minus.
Can I order this burger without onions?
Can I just take the onions off please?
- I'm the chef and I think you should eat it
the way the chef prepared.
- Here we go
- what are you doing?
- I'm not taking off the onions, it just fell off.
- Uh-huh, really?
Yeah - on purpose.
Oh wait, now I lost the bottom bun, hold on Devan.
- Really? You're so much drama man! Just eat it.
- [Both] Three! Two! One!
- Once you get all the flavors, it's not so bad.
- It made me do a little "Hmm".
- Yeah, I like that.
Got some cheese, you know, got some burger.
- I gotta say that was really good,
once you get past the initial onion man,
it was delicious - Yeah. That was actually,
really, really good. - Here we go.
- Time to slice down from the top man,
but do not try this at home.
- Oh man, the cheese!
- Three,
- [Both] Two, one.
Ohhhh!
- Look at the cheese!
- Whoa!
Bro, it's all wet and slimy.
- I'm just doing my best to make a great burger, man.
Right now let's see how this cheese-filled,
Lamborghini-grilled burger tastes. Three!
- [Both] Two! One!
- Oh - What?
- It's so dry, it's like a saltine cracker.
- The pickles taste really good.
You get to comment down below
and vote who's burger won this round,
and we'll be finding out who wins the $10,000
at the end of the video.
We've got the completed tacos,
and now it's time to find out which one is worthy of $10,000
and just remember,
we grilled the meat on a watermelon,
so it might change the whole flavor
of this thing - Oh, yeah!
- This thing's in a taco bowl that was made by a hot rock.
Alright I don't know how we do this, do we just,
I've never eaten a taco bowl whole before.
- I'll grab my fork and knife
- Oh, yeah you wanna split it in half?
You did do a good job of cutting these things man.
- Thank you, wait cutting what?
- Of cutting these!
- Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's right, thank you.
My art on the side is definitely (kissing sound)
You're opening this thing up and not in the best way, man.
It started off as a taco bowl,
and it's turned into a regular taco.
Alright so I guess on the count of three
we'll see how this thing tastes, you ready? Three!
- [Both] Two! One!
- Oh yeah!
- You know what, I didn't think the flavors blended,
but they really do!
I think that watermelon actually really helped
with the fruity flavor.
- Yours is gonna have a tall mountain to climb
if it looks to beat this one here.
Yeah, the pomegranate seeds
like tied the whole dish together.
So now Devan, time to find out how yours tastes.
- Yeah, mines got a rice taco shell,
prepared in a coffeemaker.
- That's not even the craziest thing bro,
you have fish that's been cooked in hot wax.
- I think this is gonna taste great.
- I don't know man.
- [Both] Three! Two! Oh wait!
- We just launched our brand new Keyper club,
and if you become a member you will get exclusive access to
live streams, merch discount codes, custom emojis,
loyalty badges and exclusive content
you can't see anywhere else.
So click the top link in the description to join,
it's only $4.99 a month and let's see how this tastes.
Here we go.
- Three! Two! One!
- Alright oh, that doesn't look good.
- (mumbles)
- The wasabi! - Ohhhhh!
- Oh my gosh, automatic disqualification, trash!
- It just overpowered the whole thing.
- You get to comment down below, who's taco won this round.
Now it's time to find out who won the $10,000.
There were three different dishes,
and I gotta say Devan, you definitely won the burger dish.
- Oh yeah, definitely.
- That was all yours, but the taco dish,
that was mine right there - Yes, unfortunately
- And what it all comes down to is the pizza dish,
so mine, I gotta say, a lot of really unique flavors,
but all-in-all it had multiple different layers
of all it's goodness within - yeah, but presentation
was super weak.
- Okay yeah, I gotta say the blue crust
was definitely a nice touch on yours, egg in the middle
- Yeah, mine looked the part.
It looked like $10,000
- But ultimately it comes down to taste, Devan.
- Yeah
- And if we're jusdging based on taste,
I think you know the answer.
- Unfortunately, I don't think mine was the greatest.
- Therefore - so I think, you won!
- Yes! I won the $10,000! - Nicely done!
- So comment down below, what would you buy with $10,000
and click over here if you wanna see another video.
You got five seconds, here we go,
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done!
- This is going directly to my savings account, we love you!
- [Both] Bye!