(glass shattering) (long beep)
- What's up? It's Collins Key
and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now for today's video I'm really excited
because as you guys saw from the title
I'm going to be recreating popular GIFs.
And to start things off
I know you guys are gonna be going it's Jif, it's Gif.
I did a ton of research on this
and definitively there is no answer.
So I've made the executive decision
for this video I'm gonna be calling them GIFs.
If you don't agree with me, I apologize.
And now it's time to find some GIFs to recreate.
Now my friends they've all been telling me about
this brand new streaming service, it's called fullscreen.
And they have a whole bunch of original series,
popular TV shows, they have feature films.
And what I love about it is that
you can actually make your own GIFs.
Like they have a custom GIF creation tool.
So as you're watching your favorite show,
you can pick a little part of it
and then make it in to a GIF.
So today's I'm just gonna be havin' fun
like goin' through the app,
trying to find just my favorite GIFs
and then I'm gonna recreate them.
Without any further ado, let's jump right in right now.
And let's create some JIFs.
Or GIFs, oh that was close.
(laughing) Let's create some GIFs.
Okay, let's get started.
I'm just gonna open up my phone right now.
Going to head over to the fullscreen app,
and all the GIFs are located right here in the app.
So I'm gonna scroll through, let's take a look.
They have a lot of GIFs.
Okay, let's see what this one is here.
(funky music)
Yes, okay this one's awesome.
Alright, I'm definitely gonna try this one right now.
(funky music)
Okay, that was fun, let's try another one right now.
Let's see, yes, Adele.
Hello from the other side, with a banana.
Alright, cool, let's give this a shot.
(funky music)
Let's look for the next one here.
Wait what was that?
When you're waiting for a text from bae.
Yup, I've been there, done that, let's try it.
(funky music)
Before we try this next one,
if you guys wanna create your own custom GIFs
from TV shows and movies
I would love to see them.
And all you gotta do is just download the fullscreen app.
Boom! Link is right there.
I'm also gonna put the link down in the description below.
And when you download the app, you automatically get
a 30-day free trial.
And also you get access to your favorite stars playlists,
you can edit them, you can create your own,
you can share 'em, do whatever you guys want.
It's a lot of fun.
Check it out at fullscreen.com
but right now let's get in,
and let's try to recreate some more GIFs.
Now let's try something a little bit more active.
What is, what is carting? Is that a thing?
Let's see it's about to be a thing, let's see.
Alright cool, about to grab Devon
and we're gonna go try this.
(funky music)
(cart rattling)
Alright, this one here's gonna be the last one
so I wanna find something crazy.
Let's see what this one is.
(funky music)
Yup, alright cool.
It's gonna be a lot of glass, it's gonna be nuts,
but let's give it a shot.
(dramatic music)
(glass shattering)
Thank you guys so much for watching.
And also be sure you guys go check out the fullscreen app.
Again, the link is down in the description below.
Sign up, I would love to see you guys on there.
I'll be liking your guys' stuff,
commenting, interacting with you guys on the platform.
I'll see you guys again next week.
Love you, bye. (fingers snap)