- It's 4:00 AM in the morning. Devan's still asleep.
And for the next 24 hours,
I'm going to be pranking my friends nonstop.
Oh snap!
- What? Bro! Bro! Bro!
- Good morning Devan
(techno music)
Devan wake up it's time to go man, let's go.
- Wait why are you doing this, oh my god.
- [Collins Key] It's 6:00 AM in the morning,
we are outside of Bella's house
and it's time to prank her.
Devan's dressed up like a giant Teddy bear he's going to
scare her, and I'm going to do a slime dump but right now
let's get into position before she leaves quick.
So here we go. Let's go over here.
I've got the slime bucket.
I'm going to be hopping upstairs like this.
And remember for the next 24 hours,
I'm pranking my friends nonstop, and first up, is Bella.
- I'm coming towards ya.
- Devan that's not me
- And I'm going to give you a big bear hug.
- That's not me I want a hug.
Dude over here. I'm over here. Yes
- Where are you? I was hugging a palm tree?
- I couldn't stop you.
Okay dude. Come on over here, dude seriously.
Watch your step.
- Watch my step. What do you mean?
- Dude Devan, there are literally steps right behind you
- Oh, okay, okay
- I feel like I'm dealing with a massive child right now.
Like a huge Toddler. You want to take a seat?
- Okay where?
- No, no, no, Devan oh my gosh, you're so heavy.
Holy cow. Dude are you good?
- Yeah I'm good.
- I pulled a muscle in my neck. You got it?
- I might rip it. I might rip it. Oh no.
- Okay
And there
That looks pretty good to me
Okay. Well one second.
Alright here we go to the finishing touch right here.
We got the package. So here we go Devan
you just want to hold this package here.
It's right there. Yeah. Perfect. Just chill there.
Yo, so I think I hear Bella coming.
I gotta get upstairs really quick, here we go.
- All right, go quick, go quick go.
- I'm over here, good, I'm over here.
(bouncy piano music)
(tense orchestral music)
- What is this, is there like a name on it?
All right well what's up with this?
(Devan screams)
(Bella screams)
- Hey, it's me Devan.
Bear hug! What's up?
- Oh my god!
- I've got slime dump coming up man let's go.
- We're just delivering our brand new toys,
games and challenges available at Walmart to our friends.
I'm so sorry for scaring you.
- [Bella] No it's okay, I'm just glad
- I know right.
(Bella screams)
- Whoa, whoa dude. Yes!
- All right well have fun going for your run
see you later, Bella.
- Wait guys um.
- I can't. I'm sorry. I gotta go
- I'll just play it by myself then.
- [Collins] For this next prank.
I've invited some friends over it's about 10:30 in the
morning right now. So let's get them.
All right so here's the thing none of them knows
there's actually a massive prank going on
right now.
We're wrapping all of their cars in saran wrap,
wrapping paper, filling with ballpit balls at the warehouse
literally as we speak with the whole team.
So, shh don't say anything.
(Collins' friends talking)
- Alright. Everyone's back there.
And now it's time to pull the craziest pranks yet.
Cause they just think they're here to play with our new line
of toys, games, and challenges,
but really it's only a set up so we can pull back to back
nonstop, pranks on them.
So right now, let's go get them.
Yo, alright guys. Let's do it.
- [Devan] Welcome back!
- We brought you guys over here.
Basically we're going to do like a
little video for our brand new product line
that's just launched, actually like today.
So we're super excited about it.
So here's what we'll do, we'll do like a little
intro and then we'll get to the gameplay. Sounds good.
- [Friends] Yeah.
- Yo, what's up.
It's Collins Key
- And Devan Key.
- We're here with our friends.
And it's time to show you our brand new toys, games
and challenges that just launched exclusively at Walmart.
Now Nina. You want to open up.
This here is the mystery wheel challenge.
Yeah you want to open it up, and take it out. Let's see
(Box exploding)
(everyone screams)
- Whoa, oh snap.
Holy cow, are you all right?
- It got on me!
- It got on you!
- Oh no!
- Are you good?
- Holy cow!
- It got everywhere.
- Let's get you cleaned off real quick.
Then we'll play the product. Right? cool
- Alright guys I'm in the cupboard for my final,
greatest jump scare.
waiting for somebody to finally come by so I can finally
scare someone. If I was inside the cupboard,
I would be doing math problems
like crazy. Four times four, 16.
(cool music)
- All right are you all cleaned off.
- Yeah
- I'm so sorry. Okay.
- Let's reveal the mystery wheel. You're ready.
- Yes, okay here we go.
Three, two, one. Taadaa!
- Yes. It comes with some playing cards here.
I'll put those right there.
- Oh dude, look at that.
(girls scream)
- I got an idea
You get a bucket, and you fill the bucket with water.
Can you grab that broom, that's over there.
It's a little life hack. If you want to catch a cockroach,
put the bucket up here.
- Yep, exactly.
- Push it up, push it up.
And then Bella do you want to come over here?
You want to just hold this, real quick?
You just grab that.
You just want to hold that.
Perfect. All right guys we're all set
- Wait wait wait wait
- What? You're just going to hold it.
- It's part of a life hack.
All right girls so what else we got in here?
- So this is a container that all the mystery compounds and
add ins comes in, we'll reveal those in a second.
But first, let's load up the mystery wheel.
- It's basically going to decide
which fake food it is we're making
with all these crazy compounds in here.
- Here we go three, two, one spin!
Here we go a donut
- Yes!
- Hey! Yes.
All right so it landed on blue,
that means I get the blue compartment to open,
and get my mystery compounds
- You guys get to spin next to find out what compounds you
guys get? All right, here we go.
Three, two, one, spin it! Nice
- All right so you guys are a team.
You guys get the yellow.
Collin, why don't you and Tibbles be a team.
- Yeah!
- Bella and I could be a team over here. Okay.
- I don't know if I can this is getting heavy
(shouting and screaming)
- I tried to save it
- You got it on me more.
- The big reveal, the bug is still there
- [Devan] It didn't even work?
- Okay great.
- So my biceps are sore for nothing?
- Sore? I'm soaked fam.
All right Ben so now it's time for us to spin
- Yo I just noticed Lauren doesn't have a teammate.
- Oh yeah, you're right.
- We got like this mannequin, like dummy looking dude.
- He's in the media room. If you just go upstairs,
you can use him as your teammate.
- All right, Ben. Here we go. We're going to spin it.
What color do you think we should get?
- Green's my favorite.
- Green's your favorite color? Here we go three, two, one.
We learned things about Ben today.
(Victory music)
(everyone screaming)
- We got green.
- Dude, okay
(Suspenseful music)
(Mannequin screams)
(Lauren screams)
- It was alive
- What happened? What?
- Oh my goodness. Are you okay
- I feel kind of bad for Lauren, how about you
join our team all right?
- Oh, good idea. Join the losing team.
- It's Day three in the cupboard.
I just want somebody to hold me sometimes.
- All right, guys.
The competition begins in three, two, one, go.
- [Bella] Here we go!
- Bella is a pro look at this
- [Girl] Okay, we're going for the twist.
Now we put it together.
- [Devan] I'll just roll it out a little bit here.
- [Everyone] And done!
- [Collins] How did you get that so perfect.
- What do you mean?
- You cheated bro
- What are you going to do about it bro?
What are you gonna do about it?
- This Devan!
- What? No! Oh no!
(everyone screaming)
- Guys, it's a prank video
this here is actually sugar glass. So it's not real glass.
So do not try that at home
why don't we spin right now to find out who
wins and whoever wins gets a big surprise.
- Here we go.
Three, two, one. Let's see.
- Let's see what it's gonna be.
- Previous winners!
- No!
- Yes!
(screaming noises)
- Okay guys I think I hear them.
I'm going to turn off this light,
so that way I can get ready to scare them.
Put on my angry face.
- I don't know that that's the prettiest.
Have you seen this down here?
- Oh!
- Plot twist
But here's the thing guys, it's about creativity.
And they got creative with their donuts.
Your guys just kinda got, kinda like eh.
- Is it a tie?
- Well you knew what Devan, let's do it'
let's give it to our guests. Lindsey and Nina.
They won, so everyone give it up.
(cheering)
Since you won we have a massive surprise for you
in that cabinet, back over there.
All right, you guys can go grab your prize but
first we want to let you guys know that these toys,
games and challenges literally just launched and this game
we just played here the mystery wheel fake food challenge
you can literally play at home, right now
and the best part is you can literally reset everything
to play again and again and again.
Click the top link in the description,
it's exclusively available at Walmart,
and now let's check out that prize.
- Go for it yay
(Nina and Lauren screaming)
- [Collin] Are you guys all right?
Left you one more awesome prize for you guys,
where you all parked today.
if you guys want to come with me right now.
We'll head over there
All right guys let's do this.
- Let's get you out of the cupboard, here you go.
I'll take this.
- [Devan] Collins is out pranking our friends,
but little does he know
I have the biggest prank to pull on him
That's right I ordered over 1,000,000 packing peanuts
and now it's time to put them in his room.
All right now that we got all the bags inside,
and I actually brought one of my friends
Ben here, where'd he go
There's Ben. He's gonna help me get it into Collins room
Let's do this thing. Here we go. Yeet!
All right we got it. Success.
All right it's time to get a little crazy.
You ready for this? Here we go!
Dude I did not think that through.
- [Collins] Initial thoughts,
what do you guys think the surprise is?
- Um, bugs
- Bugs
(Collins laughs)
- [Collins] Okay , so let's do this,
so if you guys want to line up
and right about there turn and
then turn your face this way right now.
- All right so now that we have all the bags up here
it is time to remove the stuff out of Collins' room.
Cause I think it might get broken.
All right all right let's move this over.
Here we go, three, two.
(grunting)
- We should probably leave that maybe move the lamp
- I think we're both one-trip kind of guys
whoo, I'm going to break this stuff on my way out
Where'd James go. James we're ready for yah.
You're going so slow Collins is about to be here
bro let's go, let's go' let's go
- [Collins] All right here's the reveal ready in
three, two, one check it out
- [Girls] Oh my goodness
- How did they do this?
- How am I going to get in?
- This is insane
- Help me get mine off
- Teamwork makes the dream work
- Let's sumo it out
- Oh yes.
Three, two, one
Whoa, whoa, whoa, guys, guys, guys.
- What, what, what!
- Guys, I got to go.
- What happened with the prank
wait dude where are you going?
You're actually just leaving?
- I'll be back
- Pass me a bag, pass me a bag.
We got to finish this thing up real quick.
- What about my car?
- Oh yeah
- I can't get in
- [Collins] Let's do this, maybe everyone gets a door
and we all just open it up on the count of three.
Here we go three, two, one, go for it.
(screaming)
- Looks like a wonderland
- Okay now that we've filled up the rest of the room
Niko is going to hide in a gorilla costume
and then bury himself in these packing peanuts
and then scare Collins, it's gonna be great.
(House electro music)
- Yo, this is crazy
Okay so let's uh, let's check out Ben's car now,
let's see what's going on over here.
- I don't think I wanna change it actually it's grown on me.
- Nice little color addition to it over here
all right we're gonna start peeling
- No, no it's perfect
- Broom power
Peanut in my mouth
All right, so I filled up half of Collins' room,
now it's time to hide some of his prize possessions.
So the first thing I'm going to hide in here is Collins'
most prized possession. Can you guess what it is?
It's his sunscreen. This boy's pale.
Alright, there we go.
Boom! It's gone
- All right, let me do this,
we're going to head back to the house.
Grab Devan, so we can help you guys clean this up.
So I'll be, I'll be right back.
- Yo dude, I think Collins is almost here.
I'm just going to leave you in here. You got this?
- Got it
- Anyone have a large vacuum?
- Yo Cons, where are you at?
- [Cons] Yo so I'm on my way home right now actually
- No, no, no, no, no, wait, don't come over here Cons.
Cons you should go to Alexis's house first and prank her.
Cause I think you've got a couple hours left in the day and
then you should go prank the twins again.
Cause they said that they're going to be suntanning later
- Oh dude that would be hilarious.
- Yeah, yeah. So go, go, go, go
(Horns)
- Alright. As Devin suggested I'm at Alexa's house right now
and this next prank is going to get pretty messy because
my friend Alexis back there, she's actually one of
the top 20 tennis players in the entire state of California,
and this is a normal tennis ball and this is a pigment
popper. Basically when you hit this thing,
pigment goes everywhere.
It's like a hundred degrees outside.
I'm sweating let's go play some tennis.
All right what's up, Alexis?
How are you doing? All right.
Cool. So I've come over here.
I want to test your tennis skills.
- Oh, okay.
I heard your like freshman year,
you went like 31 to zero, right?
- Yeah, I know, kinda crazy.
That's impressive. But you haven't faced me yet.
A true tennis champ.
- Oof
- Here we go. We'll go with the first one.
(Collins laughing)
That was close!
Okay. That was a little bit too close for comfort.
Okay, cool.
How about this I got one more ball. And Let's try this.
So basically I want to see how your serve is.
I'm gonna lob it to you, so kinda like mess it up.
How about this want to take it?
Yep. Yep.
Go for it. I'm just going to hop over here.
Yep. Yeah.
Go for it yeah. Nice, nice big serve on it.
Oh!
Yes!
Yo come on over here.
We're doing a pranks video man.
- My outfit!
- I'm sorry.
- Oh my God. It kinda looks good though
- I thought, you got a get a pink shirt.
It might match.
Exactly.
So thank you for being a part of it.
Well basically today. I'm just going to prank
all my friends.
It is so hot. I'm sweating.
- I know. You want me to go grab you a drink?
- Yeah that'd be great.
- Yeah, I, I got you, I got you.
- Alright, so we'll get everything
wrapped up right now and cleaned up.
- All right. So Collins thinks I'm getting him a Gatorade,
but I'll pull a fake Gatorade prank on him.
I am going to dump out the real Gatorade and fill it with
Mac and cheese powder and water.
- Dude. This is a mess.
- All right, I'm gonna fill this up with some water.
Now it is time to add the Mac and cheese powder. Ooh, Ooh.
This is going to be nice.
Okay guys, the fake Gatorade is ready.
Let's go take it out and see his reaction.
- It is hot today, man.
I think it's literally over a hundred degrees right now.
- Okay Collins, here you go.
- Thank you
- It's a drink.
- How long have you been playing tennis for?
- Well I've been playing tennis for like 12 years.
Oh!
And you just got pranked.
- That was you? What no way!
- I had to get you back.
- Is there like actual Gatorade anywhere?
- Yeah, here you go.
- [Collins] It's 03:45 in the afternoon.
And just as Devin suggested it's time for our next prank
because our friends, Lindsey, Nina are currently tanning.
So we're going to hit them with a ton of big bird goop.
Plus we've got Nico in a ghillie suit over here.
He's going to swim through the pool, super sneaky,
and then jump out and scare them real bad.
So right now let's get into position
Three, two, one, go, go, go, go.
I think they're like sleeping.
(Suspenseful music)
We're in position.
Niko go get ready to get in the pool right now. Go, go, go.
He's going to be scaring them.
We also have the yeet cannons,
blast a whole bunch of bird poop
here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to fire this thing off
and you're going to jump out of the water
You got it. Let's do this thing.
So hop back in let's fire off the heat cannon and do not
try this at home. Twist out on the count of three.
Here we go. Three, two .
Wait five second subscribe challenge
We want to see if you can subscribe to the channel and turn
on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
You ready? Here we go.
In Five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you were able to do that like comment down below,
keyper squad right now and let's go for it.
Three
Two
One
(Gunshot)
- Oh my gosh, eww that's disgusting
(girls scream)
- Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry.
That's Niko dressed up as a swamp thing.
Sorry again for pranking you
I'll let you guys get back to tanning.
See you guys later.
- [Devan] Bro, I can't believe you got here
before Collins did.
We gotta finish this thing up. Dude I think
Collins is going to smell like packing peanuts for a week.
Dude I feel like I could sleep in this room.
Just like on the top here, man.
It's like the best bed ever.
- You're going to have plenty of cushion.
- I do. I cannot wait to see Collins' reaction.
- This place is packed.
- Oh man, I think I can hear him pulling up.
We got to get this stuff inside really quickly.
I feel like if I'm making no progress,
I'm just getting really tired.
I'm going to be so out of breath when he gets here,
I hope I don't give it away.
Oh man. Oh man. Oh man, man, I spent so much money on this.
I can't ruin it now.
I got to figure out how to close this door. Get it in.
Get in!
Oh I think he's here. I think Collins is here.
Oh, hey Collins, how'd it go?
- Why are the cameras here?
- What do you mean?
We're just shooting a vlog.
- I thought the video was over
- It is. It's a vlog bro
- No it is not. It's a pranks video. Like seriously.
- What are you doing? Don't attack our plants bro.
- It could've the bushman guy. He's like, Niko.
why would you spill a blog at like the end of like the day?
- Because we want to show like behind the scenes
our lives, what we do.
- This is definitely a prank.
- It's 24 hours of pranks. Your pranks are over.
You've got no more pranks. There's nothing there.
- All right, let me do this.
So if we're going to like vlog.
I'm going to like change into something else now.
- But where are you going?
- I tripped on the stairs.
- Why are you going upstairs?
- Cause I know there's a prank man.
- There's no prank
- There's definitely a prank.
I feel like you're extra interested in my room.
- I'm not, I'm not interested in your room at all.
Look, I'm not interested, just going to.
- Alright. Well let me open up the door then
look at that look.
- What look?
- The look on the way back,
Dude, you better not have done anything to my room.
- What do you mean what could I do to your room?
- You know, I love my room bro.
I sleep in my room. I do work in here.
- You do
- There's a dirty fingerprint.
- Dirty fingerprint? I don't have dirty fingers.
I wash my hands on the daily.
- My door is usually very clean
and there are literally dirty fingerprints all over.
What did you do to my room?
- I don't know what you're talking about, bro.
I think you're just paranoid.
There's not any, I didn't say that.
What are you listening for?
(Suspenseful music)
There's nothing there bro.
- If someone's in there. Leave!
- You think that something's going on,
but nothing's going on?
- Devan, there're two cameras.
- I know we're shooting a vlog.
- That's not how you vlog, a vlog is like this.
This is different.
Someone is hiding here.
I think I'm just going to have go for it.
Let's go into the room. Here we go.
Three, two, one.
What the heck?
- What? You can't open your own room.
- What'd you do to the room?
- You're just messing with me bro.
I didn't do anything to your room
Wait dude you can't actually open it.
- No, you want to?
What did you? You smack your head on the door?
- Yeah.
- Is that a prank?
- No, that's a welt
- Alright. I think I'll give it a shot.
We'll see if I can open this thing up.
For your sake. Let's hope there's no prank in here now.
- Seriously.
What does that mean?
Is that a threat?
- All right here we go, three, two, one.
What! No, no, no.
You filled my room with packing peanuts.
- I did
- Yo you get back back here bro, get back here.
- Dude, I'm the best man.
- Are you kidding me?
You know what, I gotta give it to you bro
I think it's the best prank that we've ever done on the
channel.
I'm very mad, but yet very impressed at the same time.
How much did you spend on this prank?
- Too much.
- I literally can't even open my door, man.
- Don't forget, the gorilla's about to scare him.
You're about to break that door bro.
Just jump in Bro.
- Holy cow. This is insane.
Dude, this is like a winter wonderland man. Like Holy cow.
- I want to jump in
- Come on in
- Three, two, one, yeet!
What did you actually leave in here?
Like what's been actually taken out?
- You'll have to find out.
- Dude I have some very fragile stuff in here
I do not want broken.
- Yeah. You had like the weird monkey in here too.
- Yo if you did something to the laughing monkey bro,
you are gone.
(Monkey screaming)
- I want to submerge myself,
give myself a little wiggle down.
Woo let's go man.
Let's go man, let's go!
It's absolutely insane.
(Collins screaming)
- Holy cow! You were in here the whole time?
- Whole time
- You must be sweating dude. Is that Niko?
- All right Niko let's bounce, Collins has to clean up.
- I seriously have to clean this whole thing up?
- Oh yeah all by yourself.
- I thought you were just Joking bro.
Well got to say this was the
most insane 24 hours of pranking ever.
So if you want to see another video, click right over here.
You've got five seconds. Here we go.
Five
Four
Three
Two
One, done.
Love you. Bye.
(Rock music)