- You challenged us to pull the most insane DIY pranks
of all time on our unsuspecting friends.
(loud pop) (surprised shouting)
Oh my God!
- That's prank number one!
- Holy cow!
Alright, our friends are arriving right now
and they think they're just coming over
for a normal house tour,
but really it's going to be a nonstop prank war!
And the first prank is with the front door.
We call it the boom stick! Enjoy!
(knocking on door)
Yeah, come on in!
(loud pop) (surprised shouting)
Before all the chaos begins, it is time to teach
you how to make these super crazy DIY pranks,
But let's rewind it before our friends got here.
It is one hour before our friends get here,
so it's time to setup all the pranks.
The first one is
the boom stick right here! - Boom!
We're going to be putting it on the front door
to really start off the tour with a bang!
The first prank we are working on is
the mannequin jump scare prank.
So basically a friend of ours is gonna get
in a zombie costume, stand super still,
and at the right moment jump out!
(screaming)
- Was that a good reaction?
- No, that wasn't good at all.
- That was a nice little run. - It was a little extra.
- So we're also going to have an edible brain.
Some snakes kinda scattered around our friend
in the zombie costume.
I'm making the edible brain.
- And I'm making the snakes.
- But right now I'm going to add in some pecans over here,
like this.
- I've got my string here,
and this is outlining where the snakes are gonna go.
And this is the, the.
(suspenseful music)
(laughs)
- Gotta be careful where you point that thing.
- This is for gaps and cracks.
- Next thing I need for the edible brain
there's a whole bunch of peanut butter here.
So Devan you've got some gloves on
can you open that for me?
- I do, I will help.
(both screaming)
- Also, I forgot to mention - Dude
- We're going to be pranking each other
as we go through this.
- Yeah
- Definitely found my first prank.
- All right.
- The war is on bro! - It is on!
- So here we go, I got some real peanut butter over here.
So, just gonna add this in.
- Jeez dude.
- So here it goes,
squeeze it in.
- (high pitched voice) Squeeze!
- We got the ambiguous chihuahua cat-dog.
(cultural festive music)
- Still can't tell whether or not it's a cat or a dog.
- Hoooo!
(chuckles)
- Powdered sugar.
We're gonna add this in right now.
So there we go, okay boom!
- Smack that!
Sorry!
- Was that a prank too, man?
- I don't know, I meant to smack it but
I forgot it was in a hinge and its flung.
- [Devan] Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
- [Collins] Oh, man!
- [Devan] So I'm gonna coil it around the string here.
- I gotta say man, you do not have a steady hand.
But me!
(smacks)
Yeah, I gotta steady hand.
- [Collins] All right, well here we are,
we're gonna get in here and just kinda,
mix all this up.
- So, the shape of the snake is done.
Now, I just have to clear this away,
and make the skin of the snake.
- [Collins] Dude, I nailed it!
- [Devan] Wow! - [Collins] That's the perfect like,
play dough consistency.
I gotta get the brain mold.
- Oh wait. - Where you going?
- We're both leaving?
- No, no, no, no, no!
Gimme the brain (stumbles)
- Goodbye!
- Right there. All right, now that Devan's gone,
I've got some extra pranks for him,
so (shushes) don't say anything.
- [Devan] Are you talking to me, Collins?
- Nope, no you're good Devan!
- [Devan] I got the clay.
- Wait, from upstair- wait, wait,
you just left to the, what?
I'm super confused.
Aye! My brain mold!
- Whoa, what, what, what do you mean?
- [Collins] It's clear, it's a clear brain mold.
- I can see it.
- So here we go, just gonna plop and drop.
(whistle) (boom) - [Devan] Plop and drop!
- [Collins] Bam! Gonna add in a little bit more
peanut butter. But, time to pop this thing in the fridge.
I'm gonna add a beautiful glaze.
- I'm gonna start rolling out this clay here.
(chuckles) What're doing dude?
Just leave dude! (stumbles)
What's your issue? You got problems leaving bro?
All right, now that Collins is gone.
I'm actually gonna prank him with this rubber brick.
(chicken clucks)
Whoa! Dude, what! - [Collins] I'm back!
I'm back!
- How did you get there?
- I'm a ninja!
- And you heard nothing, right?
- Yeah, yeah, no what's up?
- I just got a brick here.
(screams)
- That actually hurt! What was the prank?
- It's a rubber brick
- Okay, so it hurt less than a real brick.
But you still smacked me.
- All right, just gotta roll this stuff out.
- Yup, and for this time,
I'm for real gonna go grab my brain out of the fridge.
All right, so my brain is all frozen down. - Oh!
- I have a serious brain freeze right now.
As you can tell.
(chuckles)
It's got very cold.
- Oh yeah, (sizzles)
Whoa! Wow!
- Here we're going to take our frozen brain,
plop and drop. And then we're gonna start to make a-
- A lot more drop.
- Here we go, this is-
- Well, before you do that, I have the clay rolled out
and I'm gonna add the scales with this mesh stuff here.
- Actually, can you hand me that pan down over there, Devan?
- Oh yeah, sure. -That would be perfect.
So here we go, pick up my brain,
pop the brain in the pan like that. - Here you go.
- What are you up to?
- I didn't know which way I wanted to do.
- That was a last minute change.
- [Collins] Ready, three,
- [Both] two, one.
- [Collins] Let's go for the pour.
- [Both] Ooooooo.
- [Devan] That looked cool!
- [Collins] Here we go.
- [Devan] That looked really cool!
- But don't pour it too much. - Ooooooo! What?
- All right, we got all the pranks set in room number one.
(struggling)
- [Collins] What! Holy cow!
He's having a little bit of trouble man.
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Collins] Okay, that was actually very close to my face.
Right now, let's get to the pranks.
(loud pop) (surprised shouting)
- Welcome to the house! Yes! Okay! - Dude!
- We haven't actually officially done a house tour,
as you can tell.
- Yes. - We got the camera too, if you guys wanna wave!
- Hey! - What's up!
- But, as you guys can tell,
this isn't a normal house tour.
We got a whole bunch of fun things we wanna show you.
So, the first one, is actually over here.
- Yeah.
- This is our pre-Halloween decoration. (laughs)
So as you can tell, we got a whole bunch of fun stuff.
We got some snakes. Devan actually made the snakes.
- I did! Yeah, yeah. -Yup
- [Devan] These actually are made out of
cardboard and stuff. And they kinda slither.
- Wow! - Yeah. - They look so real.
- Yeah, exactly. So this here is the edible gummy brain.
We actually just made this in the video.
Wanna touch it?
(scaring sound) (shrieks)
(laughter)
- [Collins] And of course, last but not least,
we have the mannequin. (amazement)
Don't worry we're not trying to scare you guys.
- Argh! (screaming)
(laughter)
- [Devan] I am so sorry!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
- [Devan] Are you good dude? Are you okay?
- [Collins] Okay. I don't know what to say.
- On the ground, man. Yes! - Holy cow! All right,
well, that's our friend Conrad!
- [Devan] You okay? - That got me. That was a lot.
All right well.
(chuckles) You're checking your pulse.
So, no more surprises, normal house tour from here on out.
- Wait, Collins, I forgot to clean out the boxes.
- Yep, let's get those out of here, all right. - Let me just
grab these.
- So, the next thing that we're going to be doing
is that we're going to be hopping into...
(screaming) (laughter)
- I forgot about that one.
- No more surprises, ah. - No more surprises going on.
- Yeah, right?
(stumbles)
- It's a prank house tour, so da da!
All right, we got a couple rooms we're
going into for this prank tour right now.
All right guys, follow me into the kitchen.
- [Devan] Oh! Looks like he found my bonus prank.
Let's go back to before our friends arrived to show you
how to make the next set of pranks.
- Next up in the kitchen,
we are doing the prank food roulette challenge. - Yup.
- So basically, we've got twelve different foods
and half of them are normal delicious foods.
(screaming) - No whoa! What! - The other half of them
are prank foods.
- Are you kidding me?
- And are guests have no idea which are which.
And here's the twist, they get to choose what they eat
and what we eat. So they'll be getting pranked,
we'll be getting pranked. There's gonna be lots of pranks.
- Get out of here with these pranks!
- That actually kinda hurts a little bit.
All right, so right now let's make some prank food.
- Hiya! - No!
- So, for my first prank,
I'm making Lil' Debbie birthday cakes.
- Lil' Debbie birthday cakes!
How can you make Little Debbie birthday cakes without me!
Little Debbie!
- You're definitely not Little Debbie.
- What talking about man! Totally Lil' (stumbles)
full on Deb!
- [Devan] There's just no way man. - I'm Debra!
- Collins, what is this?
- I don't think you should look at that.
- Are you trying to prank me here?
- Don't pay attention to the tape.
It has nothing to do with anything. (sparkle noises)
- See, I would grab a new package,
but this is the only one we have and I need this.
- Mhm, yes. That's, yes. Look, aw wait, wait, wait.
- What're you doing? What're you? What're you? (smacks)
- Pick that up! Pick it up real quick. - Fine, fine.
(thuds)
- Cool, all righst so we're good here.
- What did you do?
- Totally nothing at all. - Really?
- I'm glad we have your only box
of Lil' Debbie birthday cakes.
- They're over there! We have more boxes!
- All right, while you do that, I'm gonna add in some
sriracha into my agar agar over here. (suspenseful music)
- Whoa! Okay, wait. No, there's nothing in here.
- Might've been one of these. I might've mixed it up.
We'll save it for when our friends
get here later and then prank! - Deet!
- What's that? - It's a Lil' deet!
- All right, so add in the sriracha sauce into the
agar agar and now it's time to mix it all up.
So, gotta boil this, cook it up right now, and then
make the little sriracha balls.
- [Devan] Wait, aren't sponges normally wet when they
come out of the packaging man?
- What? They're all this way?
- Its been a while since I've- No! These are mine.
- Three, two, one! (squeeze)
- [Both] Whoa!
- We made it back, oh, we're crossing!
- [Devan] I just got to cut these sponges
in the shape of the Little Debbie birthday cakes.
- All right, well, I've got this jar right here.
So, now its time to strain out the sriracha caviar.
So, we have some cold vegetable oil over here.
Stand right there... its cold.
- Ah. - Ha ha, pranked!
- There we go, there we go. - My number one pet peeve
is oily fingers so, yeah.
- Oh.
Gonna suck up some little sriracha goblets....
droplets, what?
- Gotta figure out how many Little Debbie birthday cakes
come in one package, so I can make that amount.
- Can you please say that, like a tiny-
- Lil' Debbie birthday cakes!
- Cause' it's not like birthday, its like bird day!
- [Collins] Now it's time to harvest my sriracha caviar,
so here we go.
- Wait, harvest it? What the- - Yup, I gotta-
- What?
- [Collins] Well it's in there you gotta get it out.
That's not gonna fit, okay.
- [Collins] All right, let's see if we can just,
scoop down into it. Oh! There we go! Boom! Look at that!
- [Devan] And it looks so convincing!
- [Collins] Yo! This is baller!
- [Devan] So, I'm actually putting edible frosting
on the inside of these sponges.
- Next prank is silly string in the fridge!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! - Oh sorry!
That was pointed the wrong way! - What was that?
- Or was it a prank!
(screaming)
- Got you bro! - No, no why!
- So basically, I'm going to be putting these
silly string things in the fridge. So that way when our
guests open up the fridge, gonna blast em'!
- Where are you gonna put them in the- Agh!
- Sorry.
- Where are you gonna put them in the fridge dude!
- Oh well, see that's the thing is that I'll-
I'll take it out, I'll take it out, I'll take it out!
Let's see, I don't know,
maybe top shelf would be good or something-
(screams)
- [Devan] Yes! - Oh my gosh!
Two snakes? - Yes dude!
- Was that necessary, Devan? - Oh yeah!
- One wouldn't do the job? - Nope.
- [Devan] I got some white chocolate here
that I'm dipping these Lil' Debbie birthday cakes into.
- Bird day cakes.
So, to make this silly string prank,
what I'm basically gonna do is take a thumbtack
and stick it right in the hole that the silly string
comes out of.
I don't know the technical term for it.
Press it down like, there we go, okay, and then here we go,
tape it on the sides like this.
All right, next up it is time for the
mayonnaise and ice cream prank so basically-
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's in your pocket! Dude!
(screaming) It's on fire, it's on fire!
- Oh my gosh! Dude, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Ooooh! - You put something in the lemon bag?
- It's a prank!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, you put a smoker in the lemon bag.
- I did. This is a bigger prank as well,
that involves our oven.
- Wait, we're pranking our oven now?
How is mom gonna make her delicious banana bread
if we're pranking the oven?
- Are you kidding? We have multiple ovens.
You got, one, two, three, four ovens.
- That's an impressive quantity of ovens.
Next up is the ice cream and mayonnaise prank.
Basically, you replace a whole mayonnaise jar
with delicious ice cream.
- Nice, wait dude, I wanna try this thing. - Mmm
- Mm hmm - Hold up.
- Wahoo! (suspenseful music) - Whoa! What was that?
- That's the real stuff. - No!
- Pranked!
(Both mumbling)
- Raugh!
- My prank is-
- Ha! - Excuse me.
That was a prank. Ha ha, gotcha.
I'm using this fog machine, putting it in the oven.
So, you'll see. I got one of the trays locked in here man.
- Maybe, we turn the oven on. - No! No, n-
You actually press the button. (chuckles)
First tray is out man.
- I thought they were racks.
(cool music)
- [Devan] Next up, I'm taking this big speaker here.
- Holy cow! - And I'm puttin' this in the oven as well.
- Feel like a block party with that thing. -Yes.
- Are we gonna have like a- is this like a-
- You'll see, you'll see. -Oh!
Is it like a broken oven prank.
It's gonna scare me. - No dude, it's not that scary.
(boom) Oh my gosh! Holy cow!
- For my next food prank, I'm making garlic Almond Joy's
- All right, well, I'm gonna keep filling up
the mayonnaise in here.
All right, next thing I'm gonna have to do is freeze
this whole container righ-
- Garlic! (sparkly noises) - What?
- Ha! It's like a movie man. Your like, what!
- What?
- All right, Collins take a whiff.
- No, no, no, no. All right, here we go,
gonna pop this in the freezer right now.
(elevator music)
- [Collins] All right, while he's doing that I think that
my ice cream is finally frozen so, here we go,
gonna pull it out. Ta da!
- Wow! Whoa! No way! - That looks just like ice cream bro.
- Wanna take a taste of it real quick. - No!
- Cause' you know what the real stuff tastes like
- Ah no! - All right, so I'm gonna pull this mold off and
ta da! Oh, oh! I'm gonna top it off, instead of an almond,
use garlic cloves.
- My eyes are watering and that's not even an onion.
- But I do have some onions, just wait.
- Oh god. I'm out, I'm out. (laughs) I quit.
(sad music) - Come back!
All right, the last thing I gotta do for my garlic joy
is add some chocolate on the top.
- I've got some chicken gravy over here.
Which I'm playing with off as butterscotch gravy, but
its actually made out of chicken.
- Ugh! - [Collins] Here we got some Crisco.
- It's like melting it. - Yeah it's kinda coagulating.
Here we go, we use this Crisco as kinda like the
whipped cream on the top. I'm gonna have to clean it up
a little bit but I think this is a pretty
convincing ice cream dessert. - Yeah.
- So I'm gonna pop this in the fridge.
- This next one is a very tricky one
and we'll definitely get our unsuspecting guests.
- Yeah very tricky. Why'd you drop all my pickles over here.
All right, cool, pickles are fully washed so-
- Wait a second, isn't a pickled cucumber just a pickle?
(crickets)
- Yeah but I'm going for the gusto on the name.
- Begin crying in three, two, one, yeah.
(crying)
- Oh my gosh! My pickles!
(laughing)
I don't know. If your gonna cry over something,
mind as well crying over your pickles.
All right so, here we go, got a pickle on a stick.
Hohoo! That's cool.
Oooooo. - It's very, very satisfying.
Now I just gotta stick it in the caramel
and we have a fake caramel apple.
- All right, well, it's... done!
- Ha, it is?
- It is!
We're just gonna have to hope that it passes as a banana.
- It's definitely not a banana.
All right, so I've added some sprinkles but
to add some more I need this egg.
- That doesn't make any sense - What do you mean?
- How's an egg gonna add sprinkles - I'm gonna use this egg
to crack it on head. - You're gonna- No, no, no, no, no!
No! no, no, no, no! Devan, Devan! - Oh! Look at that.
- What? What on Earth? - I'm adding the sprinkles.
What did you think was gonna happen?
- You have an egg, what did you think, I think would happen?
- You're crazy, dude. And I think I actually
need some more sprinkles, so I got another egg right here.
You ready? - Yup, yeah, go for it. (cracks)
- Oh! - That was a real one! That was a real one!
All right, well now it's time to set everything up
and get this room ready for our friends.
We got fridge pranks, oven pranks,
and a whole bunch of real fake foods.
So, right now let's get it all ready
and I gotta take a shower, bro. - Sorry about that bro.
- Are you kidding me?
- Follow me into the kitchen.
- Oh, dude yes! - Holy cow!
- That's right bro. -Tape?
- I pranked ya! - Are you kidding me? - Yup I'm sorry dude.
I had to do it.
- Okay well, watch out for that
there's more in the kitchen. What the heck?
All right guys, so this is the next room right here,
the kitchen. So this is the prank food roulette challenge.
So basically, you guys get to choose which foods you
wanna eat and which foods you want Devan and I to eat.
- Yeah so, choose wisely. - Yes.
On the count of three point to the food you wanna eat.
- [Both] Three, two, one, go!
(ding)
- [Collins] Oh caviar, ice cream, and oreo.
Bella, you get to choose my food,
Ava, you get to choose Devan's
Three, two, one, go! (ding)
- [Devan] Agh! Oh no. - [Collins] Wait so, wait, I'm going
for the- Oh! We'll start with Devan, make our way down
to me. So Devan, you get to eat yours first.
- [Devan] All right, well, it already smells and kinda
makes me wanna cry so, here we go.
- [Bella, Collins, and Devan] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Go for it!
Oh! Why was it so squishy? - [Ava] What is that?
- It was an onion!
(disgusted exclaims)
- Wait a second, it actually made the onion kinda sweet.
- No way! - Awww. - Boo!
- [Collins] All right Bella,
so you've got the next one here, you've got this sundae.
- Oh, what if it's a tomato!
- She hates tomatoes by the way.
- [Bella] I hate tomatoes.
- You ready here we go.
- [Everyone] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Let's see.
- [Devan] What it taste like?
- [Collins] Is it ice cream?
- Is it? - Is it? Oh! That's not ice cream.
- What is it?
- It's a tomato. (laughter)
- Yeah!
- Fun fact, its tomato, mayo, Crisco, and I think there's
like some chicken broth in there. - Oh my god!
- Yeah, so- (laughs)
So, unfortunately, we're two for two right now with
the prank foods. So hopefully this next one, Christian.
- [Collins] Do you think that's a prank food or not?
- [Christian] I think these are packaged Oreos,
that's why I picked them.
(laughter)
- All right, lets take a bite. (explosion)
(shocked screams)
- The oven broke! So like, I take that, yeah.
I totally actually forgot about this prank.
So yeah, this is the broken oven prank.
- [Devan] Lets see how it tastes go for it.
(crunch)
- [Collins] What's it taste like - [Devan] What is it?
- It's just an Oreo.
(celebration music) (exclaims)
- I was about to say, wait a second,
I didn't do anything to that.
- And just like that we're onto Ava. So, Ava, you got these
nice little lovely looking caviar chips.
- [Ava] I'm slowly getting more and more nervous.
- [Collins] Here we go.
- [Everyone] Three, two.
(mumbles)
- We wanna see if you could like this video
in three seconds, you ready?
Here we go, three, two, one, done.
All right, here we go, you ready?
- [Collins And Devan] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Go for it. We wait.
- Not good?
- Ugh! And its spicy.
(laughter)
- It's spicy? - It's spicy.
- It's actually sriracha caviar. (panicking)
- Oh my god!
- [Devan] Well, now its on to Collins, man.
- Do you guys think this is, I mean like look, it's-
- It looks pretty legit.
- [Collins] It's in packages. - [Ava] Yeah.
- [Collins] It's fully packaged.
You ready, here we go.
- [Everyone] Three, two, one.
- [Devan] Aye! It's normal. - Aww.
- Oh! I thought it was a prank!
- Haha, no, it's just a normal one.
(celebrates)
- Now it's time for us to eat
the next prank food roulette's.
I'm gonna clear off the ones we've already eaten.
- Wait Bella, can you actually grab the pickles out
of the fridge, we need those real quick for the next one.
As Collins is clearing out these, (suspenseful music)
why don't you grab that out of the fridge.
There you go and I'll grab- (glass shattering)
- [Collins And Devan] Oh!
- [Devan] What! - [Collins] You just broke some sauce!
- [Devan] There we go! (chuckles)
- Are you trying to kill me?
- I'm sorry, we had some snakes that were supposed
to pop out and some silly string but I guess it just,
shot out a jar, yeah we should get that cleaned up.
Prank backfired, lost our sauce.
Time to choose the next prank food.
Let's do this again, Ava, Bella, Chris, you guys wanna
raise a finger.
- [Collins And Devan] Three, two, one, point
- [Devan] Oh my gosh! You went for the- Wow!
- Christian, this time you get to choose which foods
Devan and I have to eat.
So, point to which food's Devan gonna eat.
- Devan's having the chicken wing.
- [Collins] Oooo! - [Devan] All right.
- I think there's one left, it's these lil' cake pops.
Again let's start with Devan.
Let's start all the way down on that side.
All right Devan, we believe in you.
- [Everyone] Three, two, one.
- Tastes great! I don't think I got pranked!
- All right, Devan got a normal chicken wing .
(cheering)
- [Collins] All right Bella, you're next,
with your chocolate delights.
- Please be a banana, please be a banana.
- Here we go, just a- big bite, big bite.
(encouraging)
- [Collins] What is it? That ain't a banana!
(laughing)
- Yeah! (high fives) - Yeah
- No banana!
- Why are your high fives so hard?
- [Collins] What is it?
- [Devan] Is it good?
- It's a cucumber.
- Okay, are you not pranked?
- It's really good!
- [Christian] Really?
- Wait, have we like discovered a new delicious recipe?
All right, so Christian, my man.
- Okay - It's up to you, you got your packaged good.
Your Almond joy. Ta da!
- [Devan] Yay! - [Collins] Lovely little- it looks I mean-
- [Bella] It looks promising.
- [Collins] It looks promising.
- That actually looks pretty real.
- I think it looks shady.
(laughter)
- No!
(more laughter)
- [Christian] It's not an Almond Joy!
- All right here we go, three.
- [Everyon] Two, one.
- [Collins] Yup, and then chew it. - [Devan] All right.
What's it taste like? What's it taste like?
- [Girls] What is it?
- [Christian] Oh my god! Oh my god! (laughter)
- What is it? What is it?
(laughter)
- Would it be like, garlic maybe?
- [Collins] It's basically all garlic with a garlic clove
instead of the almond.
- [Devan] He's got garlic breath now!
- That's gonna last for about a week.
- I want another Oreo.
(laughter)
- [Collins] So, Ava, next up we have your birthday cake.
- All right, well, I picked something packaged because
I thought that maybe a good idea.
But now, my confidence is taken.
- [Collins] Wait did you take another bite of the cucumber?
- Yes.
- Being all sneaky over there.
- [Devan] Are you- Wow! - What is wrong with you?
- All right Ava, we believe in you,
just go for it, take a big bite, go for it.
Is it workin'?
- [Devan] Oh, what do you taste?
- It's a sponge! - It's a sponge!
(laughter)
- That's not even food!
- I just, like, pushed chocolate up into my gums (mumbles)
- She's like what is this substance?
- [Collins] Okay so now it's time for my final prank food.
These lil' cake pops. - [Devan] Yup.
- I'm looking at Devan, I'm trying to like sus' him out,
like he might've added this in like
an extra little prank one.
- Who knows man, who knows?
- [Everyone] Three, two, one.
- [Devan] Whoa! That was all of it.
- Oh yeah! (disappointed responses)
- Dude, I can't believe you got the normal one.
- Hey man, in my defense, they choose the foods I got to eat
so, not my fault.
- That makes it even worse.
- All right, so those are the prank food roulette's
but we still have one more prank room,
with a crazy big prank that we're gonna end it all with.
Gonna hop out right now. Yeah, let's do it.
So over here, this is the last area we're going to be doing
pranks, but there's a twist for this one.
Instead, us pulling pranks on you guys,
you guys actually get to pull a prank on us.
(excited) - Yes, finally! - [Collins] Yes, exactly!
Okay so, here's the only twist though,
you gotta open up the trash can.
- Oh come on!
- So trust me, no more pranks, just a trash can.
- Nothing suspicious!
(commotion)
- What could go wrong, it's just a trash can?
- Do it.
- Yeah, if you guys wanna get closer to the trash can.
- Yeah, yeah, just get a lot- Yeah.
- Just ah, we're just gonna chill back here.
If you just wanna just- - [Devan] Tell us what's inside.
- [Collins] Yeah, yeah, yeah,
just tell us what's inside the trash can.
(suspenseful music)
- There's nothing in it.
(screams)
- Time for us to make our final DIY prank and
this is the ultimate slime dump.
I'm making a jiggly water slime.
- [Devan] And I'm making a Fanta slime.
- [Collins] We're just gonna add some food coloring
like that, yo! Dude, the little like droplets kinda like,
skidded out on all of it bro.
All right, time to mix in the coloring.
So, here we go, just gonna go, ooh! Dude!
Its little like cyclone!
- And I added all the glue so now I'm adding the activator.
- Your moving along quickly.
- I sure am. Its almost like I've made slime before.
If you could just leave it like that, that would be awesome.
- Oh, like an ombre effect.
- Yeah, exac- What? I don't know.
Its got a little marbling in there too.
- Oooo, look at all these art words!
All right, so next up to make my slime,
I gotta add some activator! Oop! I almost spilled it all.
(words drown out each others)
- Here's the activator for you, yes.
- Awesome man. So, here we go-
- Whoa! - What! Come on! - Yes!
- How many of these things have we hidden around the house?
- A lot.
- This has become the staple prank of this video, man.
Like snack attack. They're everywhere.
I don't wanna open that one.
- Why it's just activator. - Are you kidding me?
W-why? Why would I possibly not wanna open that one?
I have no idea! Forget it dog!
- It's for you. (sighs)
- Unfortunately, to make my slime I need activator.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh. What. - Oh aye, okay.
- There you go!
- High five!
(zapping)
- There we go, whoa. - Oh whoa.
- Secret ice cube. My hands they're electric.
- Is the rest of you- (zaps)
- Yeah, it's pretty much all of it.
Mind as well pour over the top, here we go.
(singing) - Bleh!
- Well I gotta dd some floam beads next so.
- Some what?
- Some floam ble- beads.
- [Both] Three, two, one. (pop) Oh! (exclaiming)
- [Collins] Are you kidding me? It got in mine!
I think these should be rebranded man, floam beads, uh uh,
wack beads! Wha wackness, dem beads, they wack!
- You just offended all the people who love floam beads.
- Yeah, well I don't like them.
- You don't want that army attacking you.
- I am so sorry to the floam bead community,
I didn't mean to upset you at all.
Floam beads are indeed legit,
but I feel like they're wack. I stand by sa-
- More floam beads!
- Yeah well you got more floam beads,
I got a balloon over here. Pranks on you!
- Whoa! (both screaming)
- Are you kidding me? That is all over the floor!
- Yeah. - Dude, we gotta clean this up.
(panicking)
The last time this happened, it stained the floor,
we gotta get this up! Okay! Agh!
- Oh my gosh! Oh boy!
This is not good!
- [Collins] We're probably gonna need some help.
- [Devan] My socks are wet!
- [Collins] Paper towls!
- [Devan] I know!
(elevator music)
- That was close.
- All that cleaning has got me a
little bit thirsty, dude so.
- Okay, yeah, okay wait. - Gonna grab a drink real quick.
- All right, you wanna take a swig of- Yes! Yes!
Boom, soy sauce. -Mmm!
- Yep! It's soy sauce also added in a
little bit of Canada Dry
as well for the carbonation so, how's it taste?
- Nope, he doesn't like.
- That was so salty and savory.
I feel like I need somethings sweet to eat now, so.
- I gotchu. Zebra cakes! - Really?
- [Collins] It's like raining Orbeez from above.
- [Devan] Those are really cool.
- [Collins] Yeah so, we got that.
You know, we'll add some rubber duckies in here as well.
So go, ya! Yeet! Okay, there we go.
- This looks okay.
- [Collins] Time for me to start mixing up my slime.
It looks like rubber duckies in the tub.
- The package seems to be untampered with.
- Yeah, but they're normal zebra cakes, okay, just enjoy-
- Testing the buoyancy. Three, two, one.
- You don't have to three, two, one
your own zebra cake bite.
- Oh! - Good right. - Wait, agh!
(screams)
- It's a spider!
- Oh! No! (laughs)
- What? - No! - What it's just a spider.
- No! How'd you hid a spider in my zebra cakes.
- It was hard. - I didn't appreciate the jiggle towards me.
I don't like that I do not like that.
- All right, the slime is all ready for the
ultimate slime dump prank. (sneeze) Bless you Devan.
- Ah, thank you. And I got the contraption right here,
that's gonna dump on us, so let's fill this thing up!
- All right, here we go,
so I'm gonna pick up my slime like this, you ready?
- Yup, yup, yup, go for it, go for it.
- Three, two, one. Yo! - Whoa!
There you go. - There we go, slimes going in.
- How're your arms doing?
- Not too good!
- And I think we're gonna need to make a lot more slime so,
let's get too it.
- So, this the first batch of it so, there we go.
- [Collins] All right, now we're just gonna make a whole
bunch more slime, fill this thing all the way to the top,
and it's time for the ultimate slime dump prank.
So right now, let's go.
(screams)
- Oh my god! - Yes! -Yes! -Again?
- Good job! (laughter)
- See you later!
- All right, thank you Con- the doors. (stumbles)
Yeah, that way.
(everyone says goodbye to Conrad)
- [Collins] That was the last prank I promise.
- [Devan] The last, last.
- You said that five minutes ago!
- This now is the official last prank,
you guys get to pull on us.
Basically, you get to dump us in a whole bunch of slime.
We've been kinda been pulling pranks on you this whole time.
We feel kinda bad and so,
it's time for you guys to get your revenge on us.
Yeah, please go easy on us.
- No. - But right now let's- (laughter)
- Oh gosh. Let's uh, it's time to get slimed.
All right, so the time has come for the final pranks.
Are you guys ready to get us back?
- [Ava. Bella, And Christian] Yes!
- You guys seem way too excited about this. - I know.
- Way too excited. As you guys have seen,
we made some slime contraptions, pretty awesome.
So, you guys get to pull the rope and dump the slime so.
- Here's a rope for you
- Ava, if you wanna take the rope for me.
- We're gonna stand in the middle you guys stand over there.
- Stand directly underneath it.
- Don't pull it! Don't pull it, don't pull it.
- No false pulls.
It will get you as well if you guys false pull it.
- Are we in the right- I think we're in the right spot.
- Directly underneath it, first lets take our shoes off.
Cause' we do not want to get our shoes ruined.
We have matching shoes by the way. - Yeah, ha, ha.
- Brother goals.
- Our dad has the same pair too. - Yeet!
- All right, shoes are gone.
Christian you wanna take your shoes.
Those are pretty nice.
- [Devan] Yeah, those are nice and crispy man.
(laughter)
- Might not wanna put them. Yup.
- I would- I would just throw them.
There's a pool over there!
- I'm not gonna throw them.
- You don't acre about your shoes?
- All right, #DEYGONE. This is the moment
we've been waiting for, time for the slime dump.
Are you guys ready?
- [Ava And Christian] Yes!
- All right, here we go, I mean it's only right
we pulled so many pranks and now they get to prank us
with a final one, so here we go.
- [Collins And Devan] Three, two.
- Five second subscribe challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready? Here we go.
- [Collins And Devan] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you were able to do that comment down below,
"KEYPER SQUAD" right now. And it's time to get slime dumped.
- [Collins And Devan] Three, two, one.
- Pull!
- [Devan] Pause! You thought it was over.
But no, I have one more prank to pull on Collins.
- Help! Devan, get me down! Get me down!
- [Devan] What no the prank is not taping to the ceiling,
I've already done that. This one involves slime. Enjoy!
- [Devan] Yeah! Dude! (screaming)
(laughing)
- Yeah! Dude! (screaming)
- Yes! - It keeps coming what's going on?
- It keeps on going! - Why is it going! Why!
- Yes! (laughing)
- So I forgot to tell you there's one last prank Collins
and it's that you get slimed and I get no slime!
- Yeah, I don't like this prank, Devan. We'll done.
- And big thank you to Ava, Christian, and Bella.
Thank you very much! They went through a lot for this.
We put their links down below so, make sure you go
follow them and show them some love.
- If you want another video, click right over here.
You have five seconds, you guys ready?
- Here we go.
- [Everyone] Five, four, three, two, one.
- [Collins And Devan] Done! Love you! Bye!