- You challenged us to turn our house into a real
life Candyland and were kicking it off with
makin a candy garden. We've got a whole bunch of
melted down Gummy Bears in here that we're going
to be coating, here this one is you ready?
- You ready? Here we go
- [Both] 3,2,1
(glass shattering)
- You blew it bro, are you kidding me?
- This is a college moment
- You got it on my face! It's gonna stain my nose.
- I know, we've got to get this off!
- That took forever to clean up and it has
literally stained everything.
Got a new uh, a new gummy bear
- I do man
- What happened to your old one?
- It kind of popped in the process unfortunately
so now I've got the melted down Gummy bears
and I'm gonna fill in this giant Gummy bear.
- So now I'm gonna be making some soda soaked watermelon
so basically you take a soda thing like this,
open up... no! No!
- Whoa, whoa!
- No! Get in there
- Wow!
- Basically the goal here is you want the soda
to soak all through the watermelon, really
permeate the juices.
- Wait, is this how we make a purple watermelon kong?
- Get it deep in there!
- Dude, you have to warn me!
- I don't have to warn you, Devan, it's not in
the contract.
- Well then, I don't have to make this really
cool Gummy bear tree.
- See this is different,
you don't make a cool gummy bear tree
you will get flamed in the comments.
So light this man up.
- I would not say that.
You might actually light me up in the comments.
- All right so don't light him up in the comments.
- All right so Collins I'm gonna need your help
to hold this gummy bear.
- Got up into the goop on my hands
so I can't quite put my gloves on properly.
Wanna drop it in?
- Yeah I'm ready man.
- Drop a load.
- Here we go.
(laughs)
- Yup! Yup there we go I'm doing a great job Devan.
Oh! Come on! Come on!
Think thin streams.
- I can't see it.
- It just drenched me dude.
I'm not doing as good a job.
- I think we got it man.
- All right.
- I'll help, I'll help.
All right well I just have to fill this thing up entirely,
and next up I'm making a strawberry but with an apple.
So let me do that and then I'll be right back.
- All right next we're gonna empty out the watermelon
and turn it sour.
- [Devan] All right I have everything I need
to turn these apples into strawberries.
I'm coating it in this nice melted chocolate here,
so I can attach these jolly ranchers.
- We're gonna use a drill here to
chop up the inside of the watermelon.
So here- this thing really scares me man.
Okay so here we go...
(laughs)
- I feel like a rockstar in a way.
Wait what? What rockstar does that?
Oh! We blasted the ceiling bro look at that.
- We? We? We?
You and I?
- As a duo. As a dynamic duo.
- All right, so now, I have to attach
these jolly ranchers on the top.
- All right here we go,
so we're gonna take the chunks out
and just drop them in here.
Basically hollowing out the watermelon, (grunts)
it's not working.
- Whoa!
- Dude, look! It actually looks pretty cool. (light bang)
There we go!
It's going in here, flippin' scooping it out.
Scoop-da-da-doop
doo-doo-poo-poo-pa!
I gotta say I love being outside.
I am fully uninhibited to be my greatness. (splash)
- Wow!
This literally feels no different than inside to me.
- Next up, it's time for me to make
the sour insides of the watermelon.
So, I melted down a whole bunch of
sour patch watermelon over here.
So now, I'm going to drench all the actual watermelon
in the sour patch watermelon.
- All right, so, I finally have half of it coated.
I separated some yellow "Nerds" here, and
these are gonna be the seeds of the strawberry.
- If you could just hold the actual watermelon for me
I'm gonna dump this in.
- I can.
- So if you wanna grab the actual watermelon, it's
right over the-
- Yeah, okay. What?
- You checking your nails?
- This just in, YouTube star,
Devan Key checks his nails.
So lift up that water- holy cow, this is heavy.
- Ugh, this is heavy.
- All right, lot of heavy stuff.
- Is it going in?
- Yup! Oh, yup yup yup!
- It's splashing a little bit but it's going in.
It's very chunky are you supposed- th-th-that's it!
- Is it going in? Is it full?
- Pull back, pull back.
- It's full?
- Yes it's very full.
- Oh wow, that is very full.
The last thing you gotta do is
add a beautiful mirror glaze
to the exterior of my watermelon.
Let me grab that real quick.
(splatter)
- Ugh! Whoa whoa!
- I'm sorry I didn't mean that.
- Its all good.
- For the strawberry stem, I'm actually gonna use
these fruit roll-ups.
- Time to add a mirror glaze
it's gonna look so satisfying.
All right here we go,
- [Both] 3,2,1... Whoa!
- [Collins] Man!
- [Devan] Nice!
- [Collins] Dude!
- [Devan] It looks so cool coming out of the container too.
- [Collins] It looks so beautiful!
All right, gloves are coming off.
So this thing now, just has to set here.
It's time to head back inside
to make the rest of the candy garden.
- Lets do it!
- We got all the elements for the edible garden.
Bro, that gummy bear, like, what happened?
It's very interesting.
- Bro, it's like 40 pounds.
- All right well here is the big reveal.
- [Both] 3,2,1.. TA DA!
- [Collins] Look at these, man!
These are just a few examples, of all the things
we're gonna be adding into the candy garden
for the massive candy room
and we'll be eating that at the end of the video.
For the next part of Candyland
it's time for us to make a real life edible candy circus.
We got the yeet hammer and a carnival game.
Let's give this a shot.
(bell dings)
- Ah!
- And that is why I don't go to circuses man.
All right, right now, let's get into it.
To start off, I'm making a jello slushy.
Collins what is that? What is that?
No, no, no.
- I'm battering you up, Devan. You look great!
To be clear, I am making a funnel cake ice cream sandwich
so I put the batter here in this squirt gun.
- That wasn't clear at all. - That wasn't clear?
- No.
- All right. So right now, it is time
to make some funnel cakes for real though
so we're gonna place the safety glasses on.
- I got my hot jello here, I got some dry ice in here
so now I'm gonna pour that in here the goal is to freeze it
and make it look awesome.
- [Collins] That does look pretty awesome
the way it's just steaming up.
- And you're probably thinking
how on earth are you gonna make a jello slushy?
- Actually, Devan I was thinking
- Oh my gosh, I'm glad you asked!
- Don't touch me.
(laughs)
- Let's keep it cordial.
- 6 feet distance.
- 6 feet apart.
Not because of the quarantine,
there was another incident that happened.
- Yeah, it was that.
- Devan, get me down.
- Yeah.
- All right so here we go, I've got
a whole bunch of batter here in this
lovely cooking thing.
I don't know what the thing's called I don't garden.
So here we go, let's just do a little pour.
- [Both] Oh!
- That's hot!
- You're deep frying it.
- Yeah we're deep frying it!
That's how we make a funnel cake.
Just step back a little bit, and then just..
Ahhh, that's not good.
This is not good!
Turn this off real quick.
Also wanna mention
do not try this at home!
We are trained professionals.
- Well we're not trained. We're professionals.
- Yeah!
How's your jello slushy coming along?
- It's not going great
but it's gonna work, you know?
It's gonna work.
- So I'm actually just gonna pull it out
I'm not even gonna flip it
cause that would be a terrible idea.
Then underneath it that thing's resilient, BOOM!
- Wow! That's cool!
- Funnel cake!
- Whoa, look at this dude, it's bubbling up!
- [Collins] It's just a couple bubbles man.
- It was cool! I mean, come on.
It had no bubbles before, and then it had bubbles.
That's cool.
(applause)
- [Collins] Next up, gonna make some colorful funnel cake.
Whoa yeah!
- Whoa yeah!
- Okay well there we go we've got color number 1.
We're gonna go two colors simultaneously, BOOM!
- [Devan] You've got it too high again bro.
- Yeah I got it just a smidge high.
- I think that's too much, bro.
I think that is way too much.
- Purple protestants.
- No dude! I think that's too much!
- Yeah I guess you're right, here I go.
Purple from a distance, BOOM!
- Yeah I guess you're right,
let me just do it anyway.
- All right that's definitely a great band name.
Purple... from a distance.
- They only sell back row seats.
- Fun fact, they're actually back there.
You zoom in, at a distance.
Time to get out my second funnel cake
I don't know if you can call this, like, a funnel cake.
It looks more like, just like a patty almost.
Oh! Yeah it's crumbling.
- [Devan] That is a little bit weird.
- Gonna move it down over here like this.
Let's see it does a little plop, okay,
there we go!
Funnel crumble.
The first part of my ice cream sandwich is done.
So funnel cake. And now it's time to make some
delicious popcorn, that's gonna go around
the outside of the ice cream.
All right so we've got the funnel cake right here
I've got the popcorn which will be kind of like
the topper on top of it.
I filled up the super soaker
with a whole bunch of ice cream.
You wanna feel it, to confirm it's cold?
- It is cold.
- All right so here's the deal
we're gonna add the ice cream on here
because that's how they do it
at all circuses and carnivals.
So here we go
- [Both] 3,2-
- Wait 3 second like challenge
we want you to like this video
in 3 seconds, you ready?
Here we go
- [Both] 3,2,1, done!
3, 2, 1
(spits)
- Holy cow, it got the squeaks!
- Oh, oh there's something hanging out of it.
Oh jeez.
- Think if it was chocolate ice cream
that would be uh, that would be a little bit bad.
- Well I need to pour this cereal
into the liquid nitrogen here.
The reason this is called dragon's breath
cereal is because when you put it in your mouth-
- Whoa!
(buzzer)
(laughs)
- Let me try it again, let me try it again.
- [Both] 3,2,1
(suspenseful music)
- Oh! There you go!
Yeah! There you go!
All right well I've got the actual tub
of ice cream here so now its time to add
all the actual ice cream.
Oh man this is a weak little thing.
- So this was my topper to my slushy so I'm gonna-
what are you doing?
- I'm doing it with my hands.
- Well I'm gonna take this here
and I'm gonna pour this
- Ow! Finger freeze!
- [Devan] Just look at this though.
- My hands so cold!
I look at that and it kind of triggers me
because my hands are so cold at the same time
that that's so cold.
- This is definitely colder than your hand, Collins.
I can tell you that.
(groans)
- You wanna feel my hand?
- I don't.
It is time to deep fry some twinkies
and some snickers.
- All right so speaking of stuff that's been fried
I've got my funnel cakes over here.
I'm gonna pop this on top of the ice cream.
- Dude, that got soggy.
- Yeah it did. - That got a little soggy.
- I don't need you to rub it in Devan.
So here's the thing, I've also got my popcorn.
- That got soggy.
- This cuts me at a very deep level it hurts.
All right so gonna add some popcorn down over here.
All right here we go gonna pick it up like this
and then,
(chuckles)
Those weren't even any words.
So we're gonna take this we're gonna pack it
on the outside over here like this
and again this is gonna be for my freak shake
because Devan's making his own freak shake.
My freak shakes gonna be even freakier than Devan's.
- Nah no chance.
- Yeah man got the freakiest of the freak shakes
it's gonna be freaky fresh.
- Well mine's gonna be freaky!
- Mine's gonna be FREAKY!
- Well mine's gonna be FREAKY!
- Mine's gonna be
(screeching)
- Now that I've got my twinkies
and my snickers all skewered
I'm gonna dip it into this colored batter here
so, BOOM!
- And now, I deep fry it!
Look at that, man! Look at that!
Where'd you go?
- I just got a little scared cause like
you stuck it in the oil right when I arrived.
I've got a large chunk of ice here
we're gonna be setting this down.
I've also got some dry ice
using some shaved ice as the base of my freak shake.
So I've gotta shave up some ice now.
Are those the twinkies?
- These are the snickers in the funfetti.
- Oh, dude, that's gonna like melt the chocolate.
Oh! that actually sounds lowkey really delicious.
- Uh huh.
- [Devan] Turn the ice upside down
it looks like he has hair now.
- I think its the dry ice it, like,
froze all the water around it.
So now let's get some shaved ice.
3,2,1. I've been waiting to use this thing
- Oh yeah!
- All right here we go, 3, 2, 1 OH!
- My feet are cold, it got on my feet.
- Well that definitely got us some shaved ice man.
I even looked away, I couldn't look.
I was like it's gonna be too crazy.
- Look at this bro, it's totally different
than what you're doing.
But its very cool stuff.
- Is it a glaze?
- Yes, here we go.
- [Both] 3,2,1.. OH!
- Awe man!
- Yeah!
- Maybe go back over it a little bit.
You probably shouldn't actually listen to me
cause I'm terrible at this kind of stuff but-
- [Devan] Whoa!
- [Collins] Whoa! That looks awesome dude that's sweet!
- I am very proud of myself, this looks awesome.
- I did have a small suggestion that could've helped out
- Good job.
- Thank you very much.
- All I gotta do is just collect
a bunch of the shaved ice I made
with my giant yeet hammer and then
that'll be the base of my freak shake.
Then I gotta add some flavoring to it.
All right time to make the flavor for my shaved ice.
- [Devan] My trusty steed has arrived.
- You're your own trusty steed?
- These are my trusty steeds Collins.
- Ah, yes. Very reliable.
- These legs don't need any steed.
- I'm making a straw man barbell
and I'm using these for the weights on either end.
What are you doing?
- I'm making the flavor for my freak shake, man.
My freaky shake.
- [Devan] So I have some royal icing here
that I'm gonna fill, oh, that's cool!
And this is gonna get really hard and solid,
sorry Collins were you trying to say something?
- Yep!
The blueberries are n the cloth right now
and not it's time to get the juice out
and this is gonna be the flavoring.
So here we go.
(grunts)
- You're leaking so much of it, man!
- I know!
- All right now time to smash the berries
let's go: 3,2,1, AH!
There we go!
- [Devan] Look at that!
- [Collins] This is totally failing.
That's actually really awesome dude!
I'm actually very much into this right now
that's gonna be absolutely delicious.
- Well I need to make one more of these
and this is totally not working so I'll be right back.
- All right while he does that we're gonna add
the raspberries in here cause the show don't stop.
Just squeeze these in here, oh man!
All right for the topping I have some
condensed milk here which should freeze on impact.
- [Devan] Oh yeah!
- Oh!
- [Devan] That was like one of your greatest creations.
- How is it, that right when I'm about to
get something that looks cool
I screw it up.
- Well I made two of these things
and then I also made this nice taffy
candy cane right here.
- Taffy?
- Yeah and if you look at it
it's like a barbell.
Next up I have to glaze it. You ready?
You ready? Here we go, 3, 2, 1
- Oh that's gonna look so nice!
- Oh it's like a hydro-dip, an edible hydro-dip.
Spin it, lift it, OH!
- I'm out! I'm done!
- Look at that thing.
- I'm outta here.
- Are you actually leaving?
- Well we have to take a- AH COME ON!
Come on!
- I'm so sorry for you.
- It just squeezed out all the pulpiness.
I'm gonna find a way to fix this but I think
we've got everything we need
for a candy circus.
We've got all the circus candy and these
turned out absolutely amazing.
- Oh yeah.
- These look so delicious, dude.
- Your freak shake looks incredible I have to say.
- It's freaky for sure, and so is yours man
plus the barbell.
Everything is on point so here is the big reveal.
- [Both] 3,2-
- 5 second subscribe challenge
we want to see if you can subscribe to the channel
and turn on the post notifications in 5 seconds.
Ready? Here we go
- [Both] 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
done!
- If you were able to do that
comment right now Keyper Squad and let's see
how these look.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1.. TA DA!
- [Collins] Yeah these freaky shakes!
We're gonna be adding these
to the massive candy room
and eating it all at the end of the video.
- Next up I am making the flower to my lily pad
but first I need some strawberries.
- Fresh back from the market
with a cart full of strawberries.
- Are you kidding?
Those were over there!
Why did you grab this?
- And scene.
Here's what we're gonna do Devan.
We're gonna get a close up shot of the cart,
it's moving at lightning speed.
It hits a bump, oh no! Strawberries flying!
Smeared on the ground! Who's in the cart?
Tiny Devan!
- No! Not me!
- First thing I've gotta do for my edible rock
is use these 3 musketeers bars.
Three. Musket. Tears.
The goal here is to separate the chocolate
from the moo-sket.
(record scratch)
Nougat.
And that's again for the edible rock
so here we go. Oh, that's actually kinda-
- Wait, you're making edible rocks with a koi pond?
- Yeah. - Nice, all right.
- Why'd you start off laughing at me man?
- Well I just didn't think you were serious.
- Does this face look not serious to you?
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
- [Devan] All right I've got my strawberries cut up
and now I have to mash them.
- All right guys time to separate the nougat.
I've gotta say, it doesn't- hey.
Don't be touching my nougat.
If you take away the squareness of it-
- Order!
Order in the court!
- You're smashing some berries!
- I am, but I'm also calling order in the court.
- This is for your ice cream?
- Yes, I'm adding this in here.
It's actually for my lily pad-
- [Collins] Whoa! -[Devan] What?
- Strawberry juice. What-t-t-t
are you planning on doing with that strawberry juice?
- Putting it in here.
- No give it to me.
- No.
- Devan give it to me.
Devan look at this, if I take this one nougat
- Why are you so amazed by this?
- Oh no. - Yes.
- Oh don't tell me.
- You know where it's going.
- I do.
It's a massive log.
- You can't deny the logness of this log.
- I can't. Nor do I want to.
- Exactly, so here the deal, with this log
you can do things like poke Devan in the ear
- No!
- It made slight contact.
- First I need to add some milk
so I'm gonna do that.
I need to turn this blender thingy on, the mixer.
Collins be careful, we have real liquid nitrogen right here.
- Oh snap! You gonna make ice cream!
- Yes!
- Don't try this at home by the way.
- Do you have anything else to say Collins?
(laughs)
- Carole Baskins.
- Okay.
- [Collins] I'm very scared. No! That's not working!
- [Devan] Yes it is.
- What are you talking about Devan?
- Leave bro.
- I don't.
- Hey! That's starting to look
real weird.
- Don't look at it right now.
- [Collins] I'm looking at it and it scared me.
- Give me like 2 hours and I'll get it right.
- I've seen some things.
- Oh yes bro, look at this!
- I mean it is kind of cool
you used liquid nitrogen to make ice cream from scratch
but now, it's time for me to turn
this little ball into a rock.
Here we go.
Reverse wand!
- I have some marshmallow fluff
and I'm making the bowls that the ice cream
is gonna go in, for the bulb of the flower, of the lily pad.
- I'm pretty sure I misheard you there, you're doing what?
- So I'm making the bulb of the flower,
for the lily pad, and I'm making a bowl
that this ice cream goes in.
- Yeah I'm thoroughly lost.
- Now I combine the marshmallow fluff
with these fruity pebbles right here.
- Hold up the fruity pebbles man.
Batter up!
(laughs)
- You lost it it's over there.
- I lost my rock. Truce, bam.
- Its a little...
- Is it the marshmallow fluff?
- It is.
- You just gotta do a magic trick.
- I don't do magic tricks anymore.
- What do you mean?
- I'm a youtuber now.
All right here we go so we're gonna charge up,
3, 2, 1,
(crashing)
- Hey it worked! We're detached.
- (groans) but at what cost?
- Don't worry I saw it in a marvel movie so it
can't be that bad right?
- What is this doing here?
- That's just my log. Probably shouldn't touch that.
- Are you sure that's not mine.
- You might've lost it in flight.
- [Devan] So now I've got the fruity pebbles here.
- [Collins] And its time for me to coat this again
in chocolate.
We're gonna pop this into the fridge
it's gonna mold it a little bit better
and then it's on to the next part of the koi pond.
- Lots of dough! What were you about to say?
- I was gonna say the first thing I'm making
for my giant oreo is the filling on the inside.
Got some dry ice here as well as a slab of marble.
While I've got the filling contained
in this here siphon.
So this time I'm gonna do this
suspended, mission impossible style.
(hums mission impossible)
- You have socks on dude! What are you doing?
- Whoa! If I wasn't here it would've been all over me.
- Yeah like me.
- Yeah. Surprise innovation! I'm just ahead of my time.
All right so here we go we're just gonna get- oh!
Look at that ice cream bro look at that!
- That's awesome.
- Game changing, man.
Oh this is gonna be so delicious.
- Well I've got this all rolled out and now
I've made some stencils here for the lily pad.
Just gonna kinda cut this out here. Oh!
- [Collins] That looks really good man.
- [Devan] Yes! And for the next part of the lily pad
I made a smaller outline here, cut it out, then
gonna fill it with these jolly ranchers.
- Next up time to make the cookie part of the oreo.
So we've got the dough over here
we've got some 7-up as a rolling pin.
- Wait what? What's the oreo for?
- Sorry I should've mentioned
the oreos actually gonna be like stepping stones
leading up to the koi.
So when we fill up the whole room-
- Whoops, you need some flour.
- Yeah you're very right
- Here you go, I just did this.
- Here we go, let's see if we just did this.
- That's not some flour.
- That's a little bit of flour.
- Not some flour!
- Yeah!
- You just gotta roll it out. Calmly! Calmly!
- This is calm! - No it's not!
(glass breaks)
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm sorry.
Here we go, gonna plop this down in here like that.
Hey look, we're twins!
- We're doing the same exact thing, we're not twins though.
What are you doing?
- Double high-fiving.
- This is a lot of status here.
- A lot of status?
- Yeah, this is how you achieve clout.
So I'm just gonna pop these things into the oven.
- Yeah okay hold on, hold on!
- I wait for no one!
- Hold on! We're gonna do it together.
- Okay here we go, why did you, you went in first?
How rude!
- Perfect!
- Gonna pop these in.
- All right so we got these things out of the oven.
- There we go, fully got them
and they are now exposed.
- And these are actually two halves of one lily pad.
- What are you doing?
- I'm using a ouija that you usually use
to clean your window.
I'm repurposing it to use it for my oreos.
- Squeegee bro not ouija.
- It's not a ouija?
- I don't think so.
- I think its a ouija.
- I'm pretty sure it's a squeegee.
- We got all the elements let's see how this looks.
Here is the big room reveal, let's see,
- [Both] 3, 2, 1... TA DA!
- [Collins] Look at this!
Hands down the craziest thing we have ever done.
- I feel like I'm in a dream right now, dude, holy cow.
- Dude its all edible like literally we can eat everything
from the rocks to the grass.
- I know.
- Next we have time to harvest the fruits
of our labor from our candy garden.
- Oh yes!
These strawberries need to be freed,
these carrots are in captivity.
- [Devan] What do you mean?
- In this cage so...
- This is a fence.
- Sweet tricks.
- No. No collins! Stop!
- That's on you man I was doing sweet tricks.
First lets pop this little rose right outta here
so, Devan.
- Wait I need mine.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm the bachelor, you're the lady on the show.
Do you accept my final rose?
- I think they do it on the bachelor
and the bachelorette.
- I'm the bachelor I'm not the bachelorette clearly.
- Well in that case I'm also the bachelor.
- Do you accept my final rose?
- No will you accept MY final rose?
- Do you accept MY final rose?
- I think you wanna choose mine.
- Think you want this rose right here.
This rose. Will you accept my rose?
All right lets just take a bite of it 3, 2, 1
- Oh!
- [Both] Mmm!
- Wow!
- What would've happened?
- I need some sprinkles.
- Wow. 10/10 phenomenal man, I accept this rose.
- You gotta try the rock.
- Oh yeah, this is kinda like take it and break it so,
(glass breaks)
I forgot that's glass!
- That's our table bro!
- I'm an idiot.
- Just eat it I wanna try this.
- Did you just take a bite of that thing?
- Mhmm.
- Your teeth are stronger than glass.
- There you go.
- Yeah see there's layers to this on the inside
so here we go,
I'm gonna take my bite over here from this wack lump.
(laughs)
- I mean this is actually very good.
- He next thing we gotta eat of course
are these delicious edible strawberries.
- Here's the thing, I appreciate the attention to detail
we put in it, it looks like its growing from the ground.
- We? We?
- Well you kinda helped with some of the stuff.
- What? I made this entirely.
Rewriting history, see how it is.
- It is what it is.
- So here we go, take a- pluck a strawberry.
- [ Both] 3, 2, 1
- That's what I thought would happen.
- Soft ground Collins, soft ground.
- Okay there we go!
- Mmm! That's so good!
(chokes)
- I'm good.
I don't think we've done enough damage
here at the candy gardens so now
we're onto the next part.
Sorry man.
Let's put this worm back in the dirt
and let's eat some more candy.
- I've had my eye on this giant gummy bear
from the very beginning.
It looks so good man!
- He looks good to you collins?
- Yeah well I- he looks a little funky.
- He is a little messed up, his face is all like,
squished in.
Okay hold on, here, here , here.
- [Collins] He's heavy!
- [Both] Oh! Whoa!
- Mission disaster, we lost an arm!
- This thing is so heavy.
- I'm telling you bro it's super heavy.
- All right you gotta just go for it. Ready?
- 3, 2, 1...
- Oh!
- Okay you gotta give me a little warning.
- I don't know what to say, tastes like a gummy bear.
- Lets not put the slo-mo. No slo-mo, no slo-mo!
(distorted voices) Will you accept my rose?
Are we married now?
- Guys its time to try the sour watermelon
so I think we go in with a hand
and just scoop it out.
- Wait for real?
- Kinda like Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
- [Both] Oh!
- All right I got my handful you wanna go in?
- [Devan] Uh kind of.
- [Collins] Go for it! Ready?
- [Both] 3, 2, 1... OH!
- It's sour!
- That is sour! Ugh!
We've got way too many good things in this room
so let's move on.
- Yeah let's move on quickly.
Time to eat the freak shakes. Freaky little
freaky shakes, man. Freaky shakes!
- Is this edible?
- I don't know, did we make that part of it edible?
Lets see, here we go. 3, 2, 1...
- [Both] Plastic.
- Definitely plastic.
- Now its time for the deep fried twinkie.
- Oh I'm gonna go for the snickers. Can I get- please?
- What?
Fine, fine.
You get to try one of mine.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1...
- Wow. Its very different than the candies I just had.
- Whoooo!
- What? Is that one really good?
You ate like all of it.
- I took a big bite man.
- I said like, take some of it.
- I know (laughs)
- I gotta try some of the top.
- Whoo! That's all I can say is whoo! You know what?
- What?
The time has come.
HAND MODE!
- [Devan] Ugh this lollipop I really wanna eat that.
- Whoo makes my hand very cold.
My hand is getting a brain freeze.
- Are you just going for it man? Holy cow.
- Um here we go.
Ah! Brain freeze!
- It's so cold!
(both grunting)
- So the final thing here in this circus section
is of course, Devan's little curly thing over here
the barbell.
Here we go, ready?
This takes concentration.
- Did you say little curly?
- Ah!
- No give me that.
- Mine!
Its a bird its a plane,
nah fam it's a barbell.
- [Devan] All right I'm gonna set the barbell here
and now its time to break open one of these-
- All right you're gonna have to help me out
you're gonna have to tap my arm
- Okay.
- No on the count of 3. I need to be ready.
- Is that a bruise there?
- Yeah its gonna be a TikTok.
- 3, 2, 1
(shatters)
- Ah!
(laughs)
- Got em!
You good?
- All right note to self, don't do that again.
Are we just gonna take a bite?
- Yeah let's do it.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1
- Mmm. Oh, that's the best one yet!
- Dude! Holy cow it's so soft!
- It's like a cake pop.
- Literally just imagine a cake pop, and then
multiply it by 10.
That is so good!
- Its delicious! Man great job!
- Now its time to eat the candy coconut
but first there's a butterfly that had the audacity
to land on my beautiful coconut.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1
- Mmm very delicate just like a butterfly.
- Very light and airy.
All right enough of the butterfly
it's time for the main attraction
it is time for the coconut.
- What? The main attraction bro?
- Everyone wants to know, what's it like
to have a candy coconut.
You've gotta crack and smash this open.
- You're right, you're right.
- I'll do it on this planter over here.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1
(crack)
- [Both] Oh!
- No way! Look at that!
Blown away!
- Nicely done!
- [Both] 3, 2, 1
- Wow. - Mmm!
- Bro it's like a giant almond joy!
- All right so let's move on to the next candy.
All right it's time to try the candy pond
but the first thing I wanna try is
the actual soda pend.
- Soda pend.
- Pend, pond.
- Go for it.
- Going for a scoop of the pond like this,
So here we go, ohp it's splashing around like this!
- [Devan] 3, 2, 1
- Mmm!
- Is it good?
Delicious pond water!
- Mmm! - See isn't that good?
This froggy man is an absolute gem
a true masterpiece man.
- He really turned out good.
- We should probably eat him very quickly man.
- Lets do it. So I'm gonna try to take him off the lily pad
if I can.
- He might be attached to it.
- [Devan] Oh! I broke the lily pad!
- [Both] No! Oh!
- Man, all right, well do you wanna take his head?
- I don't really feel comfortable with that.
- Why?
- The head just fell off
I don't want that happening to me.
- Hold the lily pad.
- Okay what am I doing with this?
- What do you mean? Just hold it.
- Okay.
- Ready? Here we go, 3, 2, 1
- [Both] Oh!
- It tastes so good.
It's so fruity and fresh.
- The way you ate that, I'm gonna let you enjoy this one.
- I don't know if there's a clean way of me getting any.
- Dude! This is so good!
- Do you wanna take a bite of your cupcake bro?
Your homemade ice cream is lowkey delicious.
- Okay hold up, hold up. Gotta put this to the side here.
- I got some of the lily pad as well.
- I wanna try that after. Here we go
- Losing a bit of it, all right,
- [Both] 3, 2, 1... whoa!
- That tastes so good!
- You gotta try some of the lily pad.
- [Both] No!
- Are you kidding me?
- I guess the lily pad was a once in a lifetime experience.
- It is now the moment we've all been waiting for,
time to eat.
These wonderfully, massively oversized oreos.
So here we go just gonna slice down this oreo just like this
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Collins] Check this out!
We'll just go back over here and do the review.
- [Both] 3, 2, 1... whoa!
- Look at that! Holy cow!
- Our dad has been eyeballing this all day.
- Time to take a bite of this insane delicious oreo. Ready?
- Yeah here we go. 3, 2, 1... oh!
- That oreo is absolutely incredible.
And all of this is absolutely insane.
We went all out. This is one of the greatest things
we've ever done.
So comment down below in 5 seconds, here we go,
5, 4,-
- [Both] Oh!
- That's our cookie!
Love you guys! Bye!
- Bye!