- [Both] Oh!
- My gosh.
You challenged us to test
a whole bunch of Instagram famous slimes
and we're kicking it off with the most requested one.
- [Both] Butter slime.
- Oh no, no.
No, no no you don't.
- I was so close.
- You will not be doing that.
(laughing)
Ew okay, okay stop it, stop it.
Okay lesson learned.
If you're inside, this is not a messy challenge.
Truce?
- And truce.
- Take my hand.
Truce.
- Truce. - All right.
Now that we're all cleaned off,
Devan you have officially lost your shaving cream privileges
and step number one for the butter slime needs,
where'd you get that?
Okay so step number one you got to add the glue to,
are you kidding me?
- You never know when,
might, might go.
You never know.
- So guys step number one you're going to add the glue.
- Some glooby glue.
- Gloop gloop gloop gloob.
- Whoop whoop whoop try saying
that 10 times fast.
- Glooby glue, glooby glue, glooby glue,
gloob gloob gloob gloob.
(hollering)
- All right next up, baking soda.
- No shaving cream.
- Oh. - Tips of these.
- All right.
(pounding)
- [Announcer] Two hours later.
- How's that working out for ya?
- Not too good.
Boom.
Add it in, sha boinks, okay.
Next up.
Oh my gosh.
Baking soda, he got baking soda.
- No, that joke's from like 2015.
- Yeah but you got it on your shirt
so it's, that's still funny.
All right so let's see we're just going to grab
a little teaspoon out.
Ha.
My mouth is like foaming bro.
(pounding)
Baking soda, I taste baking soda.
We have to do one more. - Taking it back in.
- That's not sanitary. - No it's not.
- Okay next up, two tablespoons of contact solution.
- Next up we have to mix it til it's marshmallowy.
(moan)
(trilling)
- Getting nice and marshamllowy, whoa ha ha.
Nice dude.
The thing about these slimes,
like I've seen these things blowing up
all over Instagram and I really want
to test to see whether they're actually legit.
Yo this is some crazy feeling slime.
It feels like a sh'more.
- Really?
- Like a marshmallow. - Like a sh'more.
- A sh'more, we're creating our own vocabulary.
We're like Shakespeare.
- Slight deviation from the normal vocabulary.
(laughing)
- [Blonde] It feels super bizarre.
- [Devan] Oh it does, it feels like a marshmallow actually.
- It's not slimy but like it looks
like you would want to bite into it.
Okay so next step Devan is to add the clay
and that's how we turn this
from mush mallows into booter slyme.
Now put it in the center.
- Okay.
- [Blonde] Okay and then yes nice, smoosh it it.
- Oh.
- I can hear it popping inside, that's crazy.
- Oh this feels so good.
- Let's do this, let's split it in half
that way we can go double time on it.
I'll take half, whoa.
We've got two different strats right now.
I'm going to go for adding a bigger mound of clay,
he's going for smaller amount.
- And I'm going for a more modest amount.
Let's go.
- There you go he's going to push it in.
(old time piano music)
Oh that look he worked out so well.
When you kind of spread to begin with
'cause it doesn't get all clumpy then in the middle.
It just like really mixes right into it.
- That's a good idea.
- Oh.
So my butter slime is all ready
and Devan's didn't
quite turn out. - No it's not so great.
It just crumbles apart.
- Oh my gosh this looks so cool.
- Oh you nailed it.
It looks so good.
- It looks crazy.
So now we're going to add the yellow dye to it
and that way it's going to now look like butter
and then we're going to try to do
the ultimate butter slime test
which is like
spread it with a knife.
There we go, for for it.
All right that's enough, that's enough that's enough.
- Your whole hands are all yellow.
Oh my gosh. - I fail all across the board.
- This slime is crazy how much is actually resembles butter.
- [Devan] Whoa.
- You can see it's starting
to like come through a little bit.
- Mine looks like cheese.
- [Blonde] Yo.
- [Devan] Oh that looks...
- This looks seriously like butter.
- It looks just like butter.
- Oh my gosh.
This is insane.
- [Both] Whoa oh.
(cracking)
- Oh.
Darn it.
All I want is for my slime to be just
like yours Collin.
- Devan crushes me at like the pancake challenge
which is all art,
but then when it actually comes to the hands on
craft stuff this is the first time
I've ever like done it better than he has.
I'm shocked.
Flabbergasted.
- Are you going to try and flip it around.
- What, why would you do that my butter slime.
Now for the ultimate test.
Will it butter?
- I think it'll spread.
Hold on I just I want to cut it first.
- [Collin] Oh that went well.
- And then I'm just going to put this on there
and then see if it will spread, no.
Unh unh.
Nope, that did not really work at all.
- I dare you to take a bite
out of the toast with it.
With the butter on it.
- You do? - Yeah.
- Well after you smacking me in the face
with shaving cream, I don't think so.
Hold up where mine really excels
is bounciness.
See look at it.
- Mine does the same thing dude.
Yeah mine does the same thing.
- No it's just not like mine.
- Oops I lost my butter.
- See mine just has this extra spring
to it that-- - Ow.
Just a nice little thing of butter here.
Let me see if I can just...
- Spread it?
- [Collin] Yeah we'll go from like right around here.
- [Devan] Oh.
- [Collin] The satisfaction.
- That's nice.
Where did mine go so wrong?
- This is like so satisfying.
Like I literally I did not think that slime
would actually be able to spread like butter
but oh my gosh this just looks so cool.
It looks just like butter.
Like this is crazy.
Okay okay okay okay.
We just made the most satisfying butter slime
of all time, what are you doing?
The next one we are doing is called crunchy slime
and it's kind of on the opposite end
of the spectrum but still just as satisfying.
Glue me Devan.
- I got,
chu bro.
Yo this is so cool, there's so many crunchy balls.
- And this was actually suggested
by the Instagram keyper of the week,
so shout out to you and if you want to be featured
as the Instagram keyper of the week,
check the description down below to find out how
but all of you commented and let us know
that you wanted us to make this slime pink
so we got the pink dye
and let's add it in right now.
The spoon of destiny is going to mix it all around.
(old time piano music)
This looks like strawberry yogurt.
- Oh it does.
- It's crazy how one color
can make glue look like the most delicious food
in the entire world.
I low key want to eat glue right now.
- I don't.
Next up is this Sta-Flo. - Sta-Flo.
- And this one you just eyeball it
and then pray for the best.
- If you ever wondered how to make slime,
we don't know.
So we eyeball it.
Oh my gosh. - Oh, no.
- This does not look good.
It went from looking so delicious
to like expired.
Devan hit me with some more Sta-Flo.
- [Devan] There you go.
- That's perfect.
- [Devan] Yeah it's getting pretty solid.
- Oh. - It looks so cool.
- Making slime is so much fun.
Like it's truly a passion of mine.
(raspberry)
(laughing)
That was the best attempt we've had yet.
- It was like bubblegum.
- So I think next it's time
to add the crunchy elements to it.
- All right.
(slapping)
Air drop. - Oh.
Just sticks to it.
Give him some more.
Oh, wow.
- Oh. - Hey.
They just stick.
Ah that's so funny.
This is so much fun.
I'm just going to chuck all of these.
- No, no no no. - All right you ready.
Oh the mess is so worth it.
- [Collin] I think we're just going to close him up.
- [Devan] Trying to make his head.
- Here we go.
Oh, this is so cool.
Bloop, bloop bloop, blue la loop.
I got to admit like this is cool,
but it's not like crunchy.
- I feel like we should add this one.
- All right here we go.
Oh, ah ho ho.
Oh that looks so cool.
All right don't drop any Collins.
It's you know I'm over here being really clean
and neat and tidy.
- Oh I can tell.
This reminds me of the candy slime we made,
it's just you can't eat this one,
but like just with all the little things in there
looks like you could eat it.
- [Devan] Oh that sounds so cool.
- [Both] Oh my gosh.
- [Devan] This stuff is so cool.
(popping)
- All right let's stretch it out.
Wait wait wait, but first,
we've got a challenge.
I want to see if you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on your channel post notifications
and give us a thumbs up.
- [Both] In seven seconds.
- You ready for this?
- Yup. - Here we go.
- [Both] Seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one, done.
If you can do that comment down below,
keyper squad right now
and let's see how this looks.
- All right you ready.
- Yo this turned out so cool.
- Pow. - Whoa.
Devan, have you ever felt like
a fish bowl in a bowl of fish?
- No.
- Well we're about to make some slime
that resembles it.
- All right.
- This one sounds really confusing
but it's called fish bowl slime.
- Like which part of the fish bowl
are we making?
- I have no idea.
We're using clear glue for this one
and then we're also going to use some glitter.
Can you grab the baking soda Devan?
- Did you just say glitter?
- I did.
- We're using glitter?
- Yeah.
- Can we skip that step?
- I didn't want to tell you about it
but that's what we're doing.
Devan and I are terrified of glitter
if you guys didn't know.
Two pinches now.
- Two, no.
- Devan's like that was a pinch.
- Nicely done.
- What a perfect pinch.
- Baking soda bae.
- Yeah.
This ain't just regular glitter bro,
this glitter's extra fine.
- Just do a teeny little bit, please.
That's perfect.
That's it, that's it.
No that's it.
- [Collin] We got to just add both of it.
- No, really,
that's way too much.
- Way too much okay.
- You're mixing this one.
- Now one more step before we actually turn
this into slime is these things called filler beads.
- I don't think that's how you're supposed
to open it bro.
- [Both] Oh.
- They're even like stuck to my shirt.
How does that happen?
- [Devan] That's it, that's it that's it.
- We're going to add a little bit
of contact solution at a time.
Time to mix it up and to see how this goes.
- [Devan] Oh you're making little bubbles.
But it looks so cool.
- Yo. - Whoa.
That looks like so cool. - Crazy.
- I'm not a fan of glitter,
but I got to admit glitter is,
it's kind of essential for this one.
This is actually, yeah this is actually really good.
Oh my gosh and the glitter's not coming off.
It's a holy miracle.
The texture of this is so crazy.
Like you can just, you can see all
the little sparkles in it and everything.
Plus the beads.
This is really crazy.
We're about to stretch it out
but if you want to be shouted out
in the next video, comment down below
and let us know that type of video
should we do next.
Literally whatever you want us to do,
comment down below right now.
You ready for this, let's do it.
Three, two, one go for it.
- [Both] Whoa.
- My gosh.
(exhaling)
It's so resilient, oh my gosh.
- So cool.
- This stuff is crazy.
Listen to this.
(popping)
- [Devan] All the little beads are making these air pockets.
- I want to stick my hand through it, you ready.
- All right try it, try. - Three,
two, one.
- Oh, what.
What is going on.
- [Collin] It looks so trippy.
- It's like Saran wrap or something.
Show the back of your hand too.
- Yo this looks crazy. - Whoa.
- Oh my gosh.
If you want to see us fill up a pool
with 10,00 pounds of slime,
oh my gosh, click right over here.
And if you want to see us make edible candy slime,
click right over here.
Love you guys, bye.
- Bye.
- [Both] Oh.
- My gosh.