- What's up?
It's Collins Key.
Welcome to the Thursday vlog.
For today's video,
I'm going to be doing something informative.
You are going to learn something
after you are done watching this video
which for the most part,
it doesn't really happen on my channel.
This is a super special video.
I'm going to be teaching you guys
some of my favorite Snapchat tips,
tricks, and hacks
'cause you guys know I love Snapchat.
I'm always on it.
You guys always ask me how I do
all these different crazy things.
Today, I thought I'd let you guys know
how it all works.
Also, I wanna let you guys know
I'm doing a huge giveaway on my channel right now.
I'm giving away a GoPro,
Instax camera,
and also a Mac.
If you guys wanna win all that stuff,
let me know by liking (bell rings) this video.
(bell rings) Comment down below
what is your favorite video
that I've ever posted.
Of course, you must be subscribed to this channel.
Without any further ado,
let's get it in.
These are my five favorite tips,
tricks, and hacks for Snapchat.
Also, stick around 'til the very end of the video
'cause I've got a couple of bonus ones
at the very end.
Right now, let's jump in to number one.
This is hands down one of my favorite ones
to do on Snapchat.
This is how you really freak out your friends
because people think you only have
four basic filters you can use.
With this one, you're able to create
as many filters as you could ever imagine.
This is how you do it.
For this, select your favorite emoji.
I'm going with the flame emoji
because it's lit.
(chuckles) Now you just gonna wanna zoom in on the emoji
and you'll see a fuzz being created.
Using this fuzz,
you can now create your own custom filters.
Have you ever wanted to write in white or black on Snapchat
but you just couldn't figure out how to do it?
Well now you can thanks to this next tip.
Also, you can make even more specific colors.
(chuckles)Yeah, let's just get into it.
To start just tap the icon that looks like a pencil thingy.
Go to the color wheel
and drag all the way to the top left corner.
That's gonna allow you to write in white.
Now if you wanna do this in black,
just go back to the color wheel,
drag to the bottom left.
From there, you'll be able to draw in black.
If you want to get in even more specific color,
go back to the color wheel,
go somewhere in the middle.
Right here, I've got like a pink kind of salmon color.
That is how you do it.
I just wanted to throw this one in
as a little bonus, (bell rings)
and that's how you can add people super quick on Snapchat.
Pull down and a custom Snap code will appear.
From there, if you hold your phone over it,
tap and hold on that icon,
their profile will automatically appear,
and you can add them as a friend.
If you want to try this out right now,
just go watch this video on a desktop,
pause it.
At this point right here,
you'll see the little icon right over there.
Scan it.
That way you can add me immediately on Snapchat.
Also, if you haven't already,
you might as well add me on Snapchat.
My username is CollinsKey.
I've always got some fun stuff going on there.
I might even post a little bit of magic
from time to time on Snapchat.
Go check it out.
Normally, Snapchat restricts the amount of text
you're able to put into a Snapchat
which is kind of frustrating.
With this one,
you're gonna be able to bypass it
and put in as much text as you want.
First, take a snap you like,
then go into notes,
hit return a whole bunch of times,
select it, copy it,
then go back into Snapchat,
paste it.
I know it's a lot of stuff going on,
but now you can do literally unlimited text.
This one is for those of you who are
very specific and like to get very, very detailed
about each letter having a very different color.
Yeah, let's get into it.
We'll start off easy.
If you want to change the color of a word,
all you have to do is just select that word
and using the color wheel,
you can change it.
Now if you want to change the color of each letter,
again, just select each letter
and using the color wheel, you can change it.
If you do this to all of the different letters,
you're gonna be left with a really cool effect.
This one is hands down the sneakiest one of them all.
This is how you can screenshot someone's Snapchat
without them knowing about it.
With great power, comes great responsibility on this one.
First, turn on Airplane Mode
and that's it.
Now you just have to go to their Snapchat,
screenshot it,
and they will have no idea what just happened.
(funky music) (audience cheers and applauds)
To use multiple filters at once,
just find the one you like,
tap and hold on it.
From there, you can select another filter over it.
To turn the camera around super fast,
just double-tap on it.
If you want to zoom in,
instead of pinching,
you can actually use your finger
to go up and down.
That will do the same thing.
(bell ringing) Snapchat, Snapchat, Snapchat,
(bell ringing) Snapchat, Snapchat, Snapchat.