- You challenged us to try a whole bunch
of crazy school hacks.
One of them is a giant edible glue stick.
The winner gets $10,000.
So right now, let's go. - Oh yeah.
- You challenged us to do the ultimate egg drop test,
but we're using ostrich eggs.
These things are massive,
so right now let's figure out
how we protect these eggs.
I'm using a giant squishie
as the first layer of protection
for my egg right here.
- [Devan] I thought I'd use a watermelon
as like an extra layer of protection.
- Now it's time to take a look at the inside, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- It melts so perfectly. - That's so satisfying
- [Collins] Dude, if you add too many rubber bands
you'll make the watermelon blow up.
- [Devan] Nope, don't think so.
- So here we go, gonna take the egg,
gonna see if it fits.
Yes!
Like a glove.
- Like a glove.
- All right so here we go.
(watermelon popping) (both screaming)
- What just happened?
- I told that was what's gonna happen!
(watermelon popping) (slow motion screaming)
- Dude!
- It's like dripping bro!
I warned you Devan.
Now it's time to turn this thing over.
And I'm gonna be coating this in gallium,
which is liquid metal, it's gonna add a metal coating to it.
Alright, time to put on the safety glasses.
Do not try this at home!
Three,
- [Both] Two, one.
Ohh!
- [Collins] You can hear it sizzling!
- [Devan] What?
- [Collins] This looks nuts!
- [Devan] That's insane.
- [Collins] Let's listen to it, man.
- [Devan] It's like a chromed-out Mario.
- I think it's gonna add a really nice protective layer
to my squishie.
- [Devan] So for this next step I'm gonna be using oobleck.
- [Collin] Oh that's, hey, nah, nah, nah, not in my gallium!
- I am so sorry!
- Yo, dude!
- Wait, what?
- [Collins] This split my pan!
- Whoa, put it down, put it down, put it down, put it down!
- [Collins} No, but dude look at that man!
That is absolutely insane, bro!
- That is not good!
- The heat must've like, cracked it open.
- [Devan] Oh, yeah.
I can feel it turning into oobleck already.
- Got my metal squishie,
and now it's time to put an instant glue shell around it.
- [Devan] All right, so I gotta add my chia seeds next,
so I'm gonna add these.
- Devan, this about to smell real bad,
so we're gonna pop these masks on.
All right, here we go, stay still Devan here we go.
Just gonna pop this on, just like this.
I'm sorry I'm trying to figure this out.
- You're kind of yelling in my ear though.
- All right, there we go, boom!
All right, yours is on.
- Yep, that's really tight and secure.
- [Collins] All right, here we go.
Three, two, one!
- [Both] Ooooh!
- [Devan] Look at that!
No way!
- [Collins] What on earth?
- [Devan] This is insane!
- [Collins] This is nuts!
- [Devan] This is crazy!
- [Collins] That's awesome!
(Collins cheers)
I'm making some indestructible slime,
we're starting off with
the indestructible shaving cream mound.
- What are you doing, making a shaving cream fortress?
- [Collins] Yes, exactly Devan.
I'm making slime in a brand new way.
- [Devan] I'm lining the inside of my melon with cement.
- Next up we're gonna add some Sta-Flo,
and I really hope that the shaving cream's
gonna stop this stuff.
- What exactly are you trying to do?
- [Collins] I'm trying to make some slime, Devan.
So here we go, just gonna mix it all in like this.
I really hope it starts coming together.
Uh oh, Sta-Flo.
No, oh, oh.
(both yelling)
- Sta-Flo, stop!
- Stop-Flo.
- [Devan] This is really messy.
- [Collins] Yo, look at this!
Whoa!
- [Devan] Dude, I gotta set it down.
- [Collins] It got red so fast!
Dude, oh my gosh!
- [Devan] All right the concrete watermelons are done,
now it's time to make a nest.
(Collins screams)
And you're surprised by this?
- [Collins] I'm just trying to do my best!
I've learned from my mistakes!
Oh my gosh and now I've got a bucket of slime.
- Hold on, 'cause this next part takes
a lot of concentration.
I need you to contain yourself.
All right, so you take the ice mold just like this,
and you wanna just go across very quickly like this.
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
Next up we're gonna get some Orbeez in here,
so let's see, we're just gonna pick up a whole bunch
of Orbeez like this.
And then just, uh, sprinkle them in like that.
- All right so I spun a couple more webs.
What?
- I'm sorry?
- [Devan] And I made a pretty nice nest.
- [Collins] Yeah, that nest looks really good actually.
- [Devan] Yeah, it really does.
- [Collins] Now as you do that, it's time for me to
lift out my egg here and coat this thing in slime.
(Collins yells)
It's soggy!
So here we go we're gonna put it in like this.
And then we're just gonna kinda like cover it from the front
so everyone say goodbye to my very well protected egg.
Let is just fall down and perfectly coat my egg,
just like this.
What're you, what is that?
- [Devan] I'm using Flex Tape.
- It's time to seal it in a bag.
- Why?
- You'll see.
Here we go, we're gonna lift this up,
and on the count of three we're gonna drop it in.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
Devan!
- I got you!
- I can feel it cracking!
You're breaking the structure of it!
- I got you, I got you.
- No you are not!
- You're overflowing!
- That's because you didn't hold it right!
- Why are you overflowing?
- You did this to yourself.
- What do you mean?
- And to me!
- [Devan] I need more Flex Tape bro.
- I need more help!
Help me!
So here we go, just gonna put the pump on here.
(Devan grunts)
(Collin mumbles)
Oh, dude, it's working!
- [Devan] That looks terrible!
Yeah, that looks pretty funky, man.
I gotta say, I don't think it's your, uh,
not your most pleasing work, I'll give you that.
Here we go, screw this on, and, all right.
I got a few finishing touches to add to mine,
and then it's time to find out if this can
really protect my egg and win the $10,000.
These things turned out crazy, man!
Like yours, very interesting.
Yeah, there's a lotta elements on it, mine though,
I think definitely has a big chance to win this,
so here's the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Tada!
- [Collins] Man!
What is that, bro?
- [Devan] How the tables have turned.
- [Collins] I know.
You get to comment down below,
whose egg do you think will survive the drop.
We'll be testing it and finding out the winner
of the $10,000 at the end of the video.
You challenged us to do the ultimate art challenge,
but with a whole bunch of school hacks, so let's go.
For my art piece, I'm making an insane item from Fortnite.
- [Devan] And for mine I'm making an Angry Birds mosaic.
- [Collins] I'm using acetone to melt
a whole bunch of styrofoam in a very sticky paste.
- [Devan] And I'm using liquid nitrogen
to freeze some rubber duckies, and then explode them.
(both screaming)
- What on earth?
I'm almost scared right now.
- [Devan] This hasn't happened before.
- [Collins] Let's do this, here we go,
we're gonna dump the whole bucket into mine.
We'll melt this down from the top as well.
Here we go.
Boom, like that, check it out.
- [Devan] Whoa.
All right now it's time to dump 'em all.
- [Collins] Do not try this at home!
- [Both] Three, two, one!
(both yelling)
- That is the worst rubber ducky bath I have ever seen!
(both screaming)
- [Collins] Holy cow!
They're popping off!
What is going on?
- [Devan] They're like fireworks on Fourth of July!
I've never seen this before, man!
(both screaming)
The goo is starting to come together,
so right now I'm gonna use a styrofoam cup to add even more.
I'm gonna use a styrofoam cup to add even more.
and check this out.
- Look at that.
- What?
- You gonna see it like decomposing,
and deconstructing right in front of your eyes, man.
it can deconstruct in front of your eyes, man.
Now the moment of truth,
time to see if the goo is actually working, so here we go.
- [Both] Yo!
- [Collins] Look at that!
- Now it's time to smash these things up.
- Dude if they were already like, popping off and bursting,
what's gonna happen when you smash it?
Yo, the goo is all done!
This stuff is wild!
- All right just gonna scoop a couple out.
Just like this.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(hammer pounding) (duck squeaking)
- [Both] Oh!
Oh!
- [Collins] I heard the squeak!
(rubber ducks squeaking)
- All right, yo, listen to them.
- [Collins] All right, yo, listen to them.
- [Devan] Why are they squeaking?
that's what duckies do Devan.
it's what they do.
- I know but they're frozen.
All right, go for another one.
- Here we go.
I'm sorry guys!
(hammer pounding) (glass shattering)
(screaming)
(glass shattering)
(glass shattering sound plays)
Wait a minute!
I have no idea what this has to do with art,
but I really hope it's gonna help you make a great piece.
- Oh you'll see.
Next up I have a life hack with this iron and pastel.
- While you do that I've got a roller blade here,
this is uh, not mine.
Uh oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, bigger chunks coming down.
- All right, I've got the sketch out
outta my mosaic right here.
- Yo, that looks awesome.
- [Devan] Just gonna place it down like this.
- [Both] Oh!
- [Devan] Yes!
- [Collins] Dude, that is awesome.
- This would've taken so long without this.
- [Collins] All right, well the rollerskate is done,
again this is gonna act as the base of my Fortnite item.
- [Devan] Next up I'm making squishy paint for my pigs.
- [Collins] I am making a crazy unicorn horn.
- [Both] Ready, set, go!
- [Collins] Just gonna use some support here,
gotta be very careful with it.
- [Devan] I have no clue what's about to happen.
Whoa!
- [Collins] It's working dude!
I gotta stay so still right now.
- [Devan] It's like the instant water, dude.
- [Collins] Holy cow!
It's building up, bro!
- [Devan] It's like you're making a candle from scratch.
- [Collins] It's turning into a real unicorn horn, bro!
This literally looks like magic right now.
There you have it!
A literal unicorn horn made with actual magic.
(jazzy music)
(jazzy music plays)
- [Collins] Well as you do that,
I've got a whole bunch of Styrofoam here,
and it's time for me to carve out the main piece of my art,
Devan, yeah.
- Are you distracted at all?
- Yeah, if you could stop doing that
in the background that'll be nice.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Whoa!
- [Collins] Oh, snap.
Boom, art, there we go.
- [Devan] Time for bowl number three.
Okay I got it, I got it, I got it.
Put bowl number one off to the side.
- I mean, that pretty much worked.
- [Devan] All right,
now it's finally time to mix up the colors.
- I wanna see if I can remove this piece right here.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Oh!
- Whoa!
- Dude, it's starting to come together, man!
You're super good with that tool.
- Thank you man, yeah, I've found my true art passion.
- All right I've got my place mat cleared,
just gonna, kinda, just gonna pop that in right over here.
- I am out of room!
I got some clay here to fill out the head.
- [Devan] Now I got a couple more colors to fill in.
- [Collins] To extract the color from a crayon,
we're gonna do it in a very unique way.
We're gonna use a hair straightener right here,
or curler, I dunno, this does something to your hair.
So here we go, we're just gonna melt a crayon
on and drip it on to the little sponge.
Oh, man, look at that, it just melts down, so here we go.
- [Devan] First step for me though, is laying down the glue.
- [Collins] Dude, it melts so quickly on this thing, man.
You can just line the whole thing like this.
I've got the melted crayons,
so right now time to do a little swipe on here.
You ready, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Oh!
- Wait, wait, where are you doing that?
- I'm swiping it right here, man.
There we go, a rainbow, Devan.
Isn't it clear, it's a rainbow?
- Yeah.
This is my electric lawn applicator.
So I'm gonna pour some of this lawn into here.
There's an electrical current that runs through this.
You can think of this nail as a lightning pole,
What?
(thunder booming)
- I thought like, lightning was gonna strike us.
- No no no.
It conducts the electricity through the glue here.
I just have to, kinda shake it around.
- [Collins] So you're just like adding grass to it.
- Now it's time to create the electrical reaction.
- I don't know what to do with my hands, man,
I'm kinda scared.
Are you sure this isn't gonna create like,
electricity everywhere or anything?
- No, I'm not.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Oh!
- [Devan] Man!
- [Collins] Whoa, look at that!
- [Devan] It's like hopping around!
- [Collins] Dude, I know, the little piece are like
jumping all up in the air.
It's like an alien attack, man, it's like a
spaceship just dragging up a whole bunch of the grass.
Right now it's time for us to put
the finishing touches on our art piece.
The art pieces are done,
and these things look absolutely crazy,
so here is the big reveal.
absolutely crazy, so here is the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Tada!
- [Collins] Look at this thing, man!
And look at that!
- [Devan] These are crazy!
- [Collins] Yeah, so you get to
comment down below whose art piece is better,
we'll be choosing the $10,000 winner
at the end of the video.
You challenged us to make the ultimate school lunch hack,
with macaroni and cheese and pizza.
The winner gets $10,000 so let's go.
I'm kicking it off with the cheese for my pizza.
So here we're just gonna suck it up like this.
- [Devan] And I'm making the cheese for my mac and cheese.
I'm turning it into a cheese powder.
- [Collins] Whoa, dude, look at it, it's like,
it's kinda like undulating on here, man.
Yo, this is insane!
Dude, you're not doing it right.
This, is how you do it.
You just go like this.
See, look at that.
You wanna powder rise in midair.
That's how you do it, Devan.
Yo, wait a minute dude, look at this.
My cheese is coming together.
From the front it looks like delicious cheese,
but from the back, it looks like a frosty paradise.
For layer number two,
we're gonna be using this thing over here.
So let's just, ah, whoa.
So let's see, we're just gonna pour some of this in,
three, two, one.
Ohh!
- [Devan] It looks like a shower of cheese.
- Oh, could you imagine?
A world with a shower of cheese.
Eh, eh, it's dripping, it's dripping, it's dripping.
No no no, no no no, no no no!
Suck it up!
Suck it up, and shoot it out!
Suck it up, and oh, my gosh.
- [Devan] All right, goldfish are done,
now I'm gonna add it to this bowl.
So I think it'd be super cool to spray my cheese
onto my noodles.
I'm gonna use some water to test it out.
Three, two, one.
- Do it on my dry ice to see if it works.
(both cheering)
- That, it totally works!
- Dev, that's water, that is water, that is water.
- I feel like this is like my broom-broom machine.
- You're gonna soak our whole room.
- [Devan] It's like when you're in space
and you need to get propelled and you're like.
(Devan makes spraying sounds)
- A broom-broom machine?
I can see the astronauts be like.
This is uh, Houston Roger,
I can't find my broom-broom machine.
- Oh Houston, it's right here.
- Gonna place this right over here,
hopefully it does not melt.
And next up, we've got my quesadilla.
I mean, pizza crust.
- Wait, that's a paper towel, Collins.
- I forgot what I'm doing.
Wait, you're actually filling it up with cheese?
- [Devan] Well yeah, it's gonna be the best way
to add it to my macaroni.
- [Collins] All right, here we go, just gonna use this
right here to suck up some pasta juice like this,
and then just kinda like sprinkle on the inside like that.
This is squeet pizza, here we go.
- Okay then.
- Didn't think that through.
- I got my cheese prepared,
and now it's time to spray it on my noodles.
All right, here we go.
- Three second Like Challenge.
- Three second like challenge.
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds.
You ready?
Here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, done.
Three, two, one, oh!
- Absolutely blasting it, dude.
- I'm gonna use this to protect me, man.
- [Devan] Dude, it's actually working, though.
- [Collins] It is?
- [Devan] Now I'm making my next cheese filling,
but I'm gonna do it in a really rapid fashion.
I'm using sodium citrate to speed up the process.
- All right, I'm making my own relish
with some pickles here.
Dude, if you put your hand in here you get a pickle hand.
Pickle hands, Devan, legitimate pickle hands!
Awww!
- Ah, it's falling apart.
You really do love pickles, don't you.
- I love pickles.
- [Devan] All right, you know this is done when
it turns into a slime consistency.
- [Collins] It looks like an alien carcass right here man,
Area 51 watch out,
this is what you're gonna find in it, man.
- Dude, the cheese filling is done,
now it's time to make the ravioli.
All right, take this dough,
put it over the top of the ice cube maker.
- [Collins] All right here we go,
just gonna add a little bit of onions right here.
And last up we got some cornstarch.
Three, two, one, here we go.
Okay, yeah!
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
And there we go, okay yep.
And, done.
Okay, there we go, my relish is all finished up, and now,
it's time to add it to my pizza.
That's right, I'm gonna have a relish stuffed pizza crust.
- [Devan] I've got the covering to my ravioli right here.
Just gonna lay it on top.
- [Collins] All right, here we go,
gonna take some relish here like this.
Aw, man, dude, look at this.
You know when the lunch lady asks what you want,
always say you want relish stuffed pizza crust
and she'll be very confused.
Next up we gotta skin these potatoes,
so I got the drill right here,
but I realized, I've been going on mode one.
There's actually a second more powerful mode.
- Oh no.
You were not supposed to find that.
- Mode two!
Three, two, one.
- Why did you dump it in first?
Oh, jeez.
What is the point of this?
- To be honest, I um.
I thought a lot more would've happened.
Doesn't appear to have um, had any impact whatsoever.
- Are you just trying to get everything messy dude?
- On my potatoes.
Let's go for a little gentler approach.
- [Devan] Dude, maybe turn it on one.
It's on two.
- It's gonna work, Devan.
Progress, there we go, you can see it's a little peeled.
I don't know if it was totally worth it.
- [Devan] Look at this!
- [Collins] Dude!
(elevator music)
- All right, done, the potatoes are actually peeled, dude,
look at this, man.
- [Devan] For my next life hack I'm turning pizza sauce
into an edible glue stick.
- [Collins] Time for me to shred up
some of my potatoes here,
and this is gonna be a huge part of mine.
- [Devan] For the rest of this life hack,
I just gotta pour this stuff into the straws.
All right my straws are filled,
now it's time to pop 'em in the fridge.
- All right, I just gotta keep shredding my potatoes.
- [Devan] All right the glue sticks are back,
now it's time to take 'em out of the straws.
- [Both] Oh!
- That looks insane.
- It's like a little worm!
All right, got the glue sticks out,
now it's time to pop 'em in the freezer.
All right so while that's in the freezer,
I'm gonna roll out some dough.
- [Collins] Next up we're making a
tater tot grilled cheese sandwich.
It's a crazy life hack,
but first we gotta slice up some cheese right here.
So here we go, just gonna use this butter knife right here.
- I've got something that's gonna be even cooler.
So I got the glue sticks out of the freezer.
And now, I'm gonna put them onto my pizza.
- [Collins] That's not a glue stick though,
that's pizza sauce, right?
- [Devan] Yes.
- [Collins] Yo, this reminds me of like
melted cheese and create a grilled cheese
without having to cook it at all, man.
- [Devan] Yeah, I wasn't really sure
this was gonna work, and it did.
- All right I'm gonna make a panini here
with my tater tots and cheese.
So here we go, just gonna place some uh, some layers.
Oh my gosh.
- [Devan] All right, last thing on my pizza
is some pepper slices.
- [Collins] All right, well as you're doing that,
I gotta get my next layer of tots right here.
So here we go,
just gonna layer these things like this on top't.
- [Devan] All right this pizza's ready to pop in the oven,
and now I'm gonna make a pasta bowl, out of pasta.
All right the first step is to grab this balloon here.
- [Collins] All right well as you do that,
it's time for me to smash this thing down
and turn it into an actual panini made out of tots.
Three, two, one.
- [Devan] You don't think that's too much?
- [Collins] No!
Here we go, just gonna smash it down like this.
We dislodged a couple pieces of cheese!
- Oh!
Dude!
- Well!
- Do not try this at home!
- Do not try this at home.
All right, let's give this another shot.
Three, two, one, just gonna squish it down.
- [Both] Oh!
- [Collins] Man.
- [Devan] This is some edible glue here
I'm gonna put on the outside of my balloon,
to make these noodles stick.
- Let's see how this turned out, here we go.
Three, two, one.
(both yelling)
It's an actual waffle.
- Three, two, one.
(balloon pops)
(Collins screams)
Look at that, it's my pasta bowl made of pasta.
- All right, well we've got all the ingredients
and now it's time to make our final school hack lunches.
The school hack lunches are all done,
and my mouth is watering right now.
- [Both] These look amazing.
- So here is the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, oh!
- Five second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
You ready?
Here we go.
[Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you can do that,
comment down below Keyper Squad right now.
- [Both] Three, two, one, tada!
- [Collins] These both look amazing.
You get to comment down below
whose school lunch hack is going to taste better.
We'll be finding out the $10,000 winner
at the end of the video.
We've got all the school hacks,
and now it's time to test them
to find out who's gonna win the $10,000.
It is time for the egg drop test, and I gotta say man,
looking at both of these, I do not know
which one's gonna successfully be able to do it man.
- I know, this did not quite fulfill my vision for it.
- [Collins] But right now it's time for us to hop outside
and see which one is able
to better protect its egg from cracking.
We've got our eggs,
and now it's time to drop them to see
if they'll actually be able to withstand the impact.
I think, did a pretty good job on the construction here,
what about you?
- I don't know about mine, mine's falling apart already.
- This is a pretty high drop, man,
we're gonna be trying to hit the bullseye.
For the baseline test,
we're gonna drop a real unprotected ostrich egg
to see if that cracks on the ground.
And here is the unprotected ostrich egg.
Three.
- [Both] Two, one.
(egg splattering)
- [Both] Oh!
- [Devan] Did that crack the cement?
- [Collins] I don't know, man, that was quick.
- How bout this, Collins?
I'm gonna hop down there, you chuck it down,
and we'll assess the damage.
- The way that that egg broke,
I don't know if this'll be able
to fully withstand the impact.
- I don't know, dude,
I think you have a huge chance of success.
- The thing about mine is,
I've got a giant squishie,
that was the first thing I cut open,
then I covered it in a whole bunch of gallium,
we've got slime in here, and the baking soda and water.
That reaction that happened coated it
in an unbreakable substance, man.
In a scale of one to ten, Devan,
where do you think this one falls, in terms of uh,
ten being it has full chance of making it, one, it's done.
- I think you've got like a solid eight and a half.
- An eight and a half.
I don't know.
Should I just kinda like, hold it out,
and then just drop it?
- No, you've gotta give it a nice throw, or maybe a lob up.
- Three.
- [Both] Two, one.
(egg splatters on the ground)
- [Both] Oh!
- [Collins] Oh, no.
- [Devan] Orbeez everywhere!
- [Collins] Oh no.
- I don't know if that was so good for you, man.
- [Collins] I think the bottom of the bag,
I think burst open.
- [Devan] Oh my goodness.
- We're gonna take the bag apart afterwards to see,
if it stayed intact.
Devan, you wanna, you wanna trade,
so you wanna come up here?
- Yeah, I'll go up there.
- [Collins] All right so we do a little switch right now.
- This is gonna be super interesting,
because I coated my egg in a watermelon
I popped with rubber bands.
Cement on the inside.
Oh yeah, not to mention oobleck
on the outside for safe measure.
I can hear the egg moving around in mine.
- That's not good.
- That is not a good sign.
- [Collins] The nest on the inside.
That's what really blows my mind, because like,
I think that that might be your saving, what?
- I almost just dropped it.
Here we go.
- [Both] Three, two.
- Wait up, wait.
If you wanna win a fifteen minute video call
with Devan and I, text the word school to 81800 right now.
So pause the video, text the word school to 81800,
you'll automatically be entered in to win,
and let's see how this goes.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
(egg thudding)
- [Collins] No way!
- [Devan] No way!
- [Collins] That was a solid thud,
like it did not crack at all.
- Dude, I think I just won.
- Ah, yeah, let's grab these eggs, let's hop back inside.
Now it's time for the moment we've all been waiting for,
time to find out which egg was able to withstand the drop.
So how 'bout this,
we'll start with yours first.
- [Devan] Yeah, I think this Flex Seal Tape
is gonna be a lot to get through, so I brought a saw
to get into mine.
- Yeah, do not try this at home.
Oh!
There's a crack, wait wait wait wait wait.
- [Devan] I can see it, all right.
- Here we go, the big reveal, let's see if it worked, ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
No!
- I thought this would work.
- It's not even like cracked, it's obliterated.
If that's what happened to yours, what happened to mine?
All right, well, let's take the bag open here,
we've got all the squishies, we got the toast.
Don't forget about the toast.
So the first bag got breached,
but did the second bag pop open?
Here we go, let's, oh, yes, it did!
Look at that.
- Orbeez everywhere!
- Look at that!
- [Devan] Oh, jeez.
- [Collins] Here's the egg.
- [Devan] The slime is like fully coating it, man.
- [Collins] All right here we go,
we got the egg here, so let's see if we can just
pull off some chunks of slime, like this.
The real question though, man, is did it survive?
I am so concerned right now.
Come on.
All right, well, uh, fun fact,
it's very difficult to find out where,
how I closed this thing.
- Oh dear.
- Yo, here we go, let's see if we can just tear it open.
- [Both] Ohh!
- What?
What, what, what, what, what?
- I just saw something.
You ready for the big reveal?
- I'm ready.
- All right, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Let's give it a tear.
- [Devan] What, what, I can't see it yet.
- Look at it, it's perfect! - No!
- Not even a scratch.
- No way!
One hundred percent intact.
You get to comment down below,
what is one ingredient you would use
to save Devan's egg from not cracking.
Got the ultimate school hack lunches,
and now it's time to find out which one tastes better.
My delicious infused crust pizza, or your whack bowl.
- [Devan] Yeah, I think we should try
your bland dish over here.
- Whoa.
Let's start off with my grilled cheese tater tots,
I gotta say, oh boy, it's a little um, crumbly.
You want the bigger one or the smaller one?
- I'll take the smaller one.
It smells really good.
- Whoa.
- I'm actually really excited for this.
- Yeah, I'm pretty thrilled for this.
- I hope this works.
(Collins whoops)
- Let's uh, let's touch tots.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Whoa!
Whoa!
- I wouldn't say it's quite a whoa, or a whoa,
but you know, I think it's pretty solid.
- What?
Yours has a pretty high bar to climb
if it really wants to reach it man.
Did you put peppers on there?
- Yes.
Were you watching what I was doing?
- Not really.
- [Devan] I will offer you the choice,
which slice do you want.
These are your only two choices.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Mmm.
- Whoa.
Is there anymore of that?
- I wish I did, but no, I already ate it.
- [Collins] Wow.
I didn't think it was possible,
but that was better than the tater tots man.
- Way better.
Like, million times better.
- [Collins] It comes down to the main dish, Devan.
I'll take this slice over here.
Oh, there we go.
Look at that, you see the relish in there.
I'm folding it over like this,
and I'm gonna take a bite over here,
so I get the sauce, the cheese, the relish and the crust,
all in one, bam.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Whoa. - Wow.
I wasn't totally sure on this combo.
- That is interesting.
Yours, I don't think is gonna be able to top that.
- [Devan] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Why is it a brick?
These should be individual pieces.
- It formed to the bowl.
Here you go.
- Wait, so I get a whole, I get a whole slice of this.
- Right, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two.
- We just launched our brand new Keyper Club,
and if you become a member,
you will get exclusive access to live streams,
merch discount codes, custom emojis, loyalty badges,
and exclusive content you can't see anywhere else.
Click the top link in the description to join.
It's only $4.99 a month.
Now let's see how these things taste.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh.
- Whoa, huh, okay.
- The textures.
- This is not good.
- [Collins] You get to comment down below,
whose school lunch do you think tasted better,
and we'll be finding out the $10,000 winner
at the end of the video.
We got the edible glue stick,
we've tested all the school hacks,
and now it's time to find out
who is truly worthy of the $10,000.
So for the egg drop,
I think I was definitely the clear winner.
I mean, my egg actually stayed intact.
Whereas yours, just shattered everywhere.
So there we go, one point to me.
Now for the art project,
I gotta give that one to you Devan,
I think you had some cool stuff.
You made electric grass, you smashed up little duckies.
It was pretty wild, so there we go, point for you.
But now what it comes down to is the school hack lunches,
and this one, is a bit of a toss up, man.
There's a lot of crazy things that we did in this,
and I gotta say although you won the appetizers,
I won the main dish, but that being said.
- [Devan] Uh huh.
My appetizer was pretty good.
- [Collins] And I think if we compare your appetizer
to my main dish, Devan wins the video.
- [Devan] Yes!
- [Collins] So that means you win the $10,000
and the giant edible glue stick.
But now it's time to find out
what this edible glue stick actually tastes like.
- [Devan] I know right?
- Can I feel how heavy this thing is?
- It is really, really, heavy.
- Oh my gosh.
- You gotta hold onto it.
- You got it, you got it, you got it?
- I'm super strong.
Holy cow, that's heavy.
- Stand up, stand up, I got you.
- You should just take it back.
- I will take it, I will take it.
I don't even know how I'm gonna eat this.
- I think I gotta hold it for you.
- Oh, okay yeah, sure.
You got it?
- I got it.
- You 100% got it?
- I 100% got it, Devan.
- Three, two, one.
Ah.
Ow.
- I can't see, is it working?
- No.
It's way harder than I expected.
- It's gotten on your teeth.
Wait, smile Devan, smile forward.
Does it taste good?
- It's definitely edible, and it tastes delicious.
- Well this is getting super heavy,
so if you wanna see another video
you gotta click right over here.
You got give seconds, here we go.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- We love you, no!
Bye!
- Bye!
- Have you not seen this, it's literally rolling.
- I see it, but you've ruined a rollerskate.
- I did not ruin this, Devan,
it is made better by what I've done.
- You're getting feathers everywhere.
- It's shedding season for my rainbow smash over here.