- We're known for making crazy life hacks,
and you're always asking us,
"Do they really work in real life?"
So today, we built The 'ULTIMATE ORBEEZ OBSTACLE COURSE'
to test these life hacks under the most extreme conditions.
Like this one for example,
A watermelon stuffed full with a whole bunch of matches.
- Yeah, I don't get how this is a life hack.
- Just wait until you see how it's actually used
in the obstacle course.
It's gonna blow your mind, it'll make perfect sense.
The first obstacle we're gonna be tackling
and creating life hacks for is the balance race.
Where if we fall off,
we'll be landing on a painful bed of Legos,
or into a massive vat of slime.
So right now, let's go make the life hacks,
that'll make sure we don't fall off as we race across.
I'm making a balancing pole
with squishy pineapples on either end.
So right now, here's a crazy life hack
to make some homemade squishies.
Here we go three, two, one.
Whoa! (both squealing)
- You broke it, bro! - I broke it, bro!
- Wow! - Holy cow, I broke it!
- So, as you're making your nonsense over there,
I am gonna make my balancing apparatus.
- Nonsense? - Well, yes, seriously.
- Bro, squishies are where it's at, man.
How's that gonna help you balance?
You're gonna look like a giant, like, floating rag.
- I'm making some wings.
- All right, well, I'm dumping the water in there.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! (splash)
- See, you get a little extra of soap sud in there,
you gotta dual wield these (laughs)
I can't say the name of these
cause we will get in trouble.
- Why will we get in trouble?
- Don't ask.
All right, so here we go. - Oh yes, oh yes.
I got you.
- Okay, so here's the deal, we're gonna to put
all this in and this it's gonna help
to create the pineapple.
I guess it's like a life hack as well,
except my hands are getting very tired.
- All right, one wing is done.
Now it's time to make the frame for it.
So, I'm going to start with this long PVC pipe
here and then bend it around the boogie board.
- Gotta get the silicone and get all nice, here we go.
Soapy water! (splash)
(laughs)
Yeah, that's unfortunate.
Oh my goodness this is in my eye.
Holy cow, this side of my face looks shut down.
I can't hear anything and I can't see anything.
- Useless life hack alert!
I have some hot sand here if you ever wanna bend a PVC pipe,
pour some hot sand down it.
- While you do that, time for me to coat my pineapple
in the silicone over here.
NFL, if you're watching this you might consider drafting me.
42, set, pineapple
(crash) Oh, geez, oh.
Dude (laughs)
- Well that wasn't coat it.
- It's giving me beach vibes right now.
- Exactly - There's sand and water.
(upbeat music)
I bet you we could go ice skating on this stuff.
- Wow - Key Olympics
- Ta-da! - Figure skate
(crash)
(gong) (bang)
- Whoa - Karate kicks
- Geez
- Now unfortunately making a squishy pineapple
has distracted from your life hacks.
The question is, does this useless life hack
actually bend the pole?
- Absolutely not at all.
- Let me try, let me try. - Look, look, look.
Oh what are you - What are you, what are you?
Oh! That's hot sand. That is hot sand.
- It just broke off.
- All right, so we got a pineapple,
we got a silicone, you know what's 'bout to happen.
- No. No. (bang)
Oh (laughs) I see that now.
- (growls) - Whoa, it's working!
- Bend down for one second.
- Yes! Look at that, man. That is my wing structure.
- I was aiming for the Legos.
- That went really far. - Whoops.
- NFL, give him a call
(laughter)
- So, if you're wondering how this relates
to making a squishy, basically this will create
the mold that'll fill with the squishy material
and that's going to help me cross a tight rope race.
Whoa, ho, ho. Glad I found that.
- I honestly can't believe that this worked.
- Wait - This is insane.
- And this is for your wing?
- This is for my wing, so it's going to be like that.
- I still can't believe Devan about to look like a bird.
(laughter) - No. Like a dragon, bro.
- No. You're going to look - No.
- Like a sparrow.
- Sparrows are pretty cool too. I'll take it.
- You look like a pigeon.
- Okay, I don't take that. We have a useless
life hack that actually works.
- So congratulations, you found the first one
coz' I don't know if this silicone one
is quite working man. You could have just like
bought a pineapple mold. All right.
So, I've got to go let this thing dry.
(screams) Oh my god!
It went under my nail. Fudge! That was not fun.
All right. Sick, so let's, let's go let this
thing dry now and tend to my nail.
All right, so I've got the mold,
I've taken the pineapple out and now
it's time to create the squishy on the inside.
All right, here we go. Time to poor it in.
Here we go. Three, two, one. Let's go for it.
(screams)
- Man - No!
- Holy cow, okay.
- So, this is foam, not elephant toothpaste?
- This is foam right here, so we're going
to have to like clear off the top, let it set.
- And I just have to attach a couple more
of these PVC pipes and then the frame will be done.
- Oh and we have partnered with Adobe
to bring you a massive giveaway so stick around
to find out how you can enter in for a chance to win.
The DIYs are done and bro, those wings are insane.
- Yeah, they might be a bit overkill.
- Yeah, for this race, whoever makes it backwards
across the balance beams all the way first wins
and if we fall off we're going to be landing
on a painful bed of legos or in a massive pool of slime
and you know to make it even more fun
we've actually brought along our friends
who've got water balloons, squirt guns
and a whole bunch
of other stuff. - [Devan] Exactly.
- They will be throwing at us to try to knock us off
as we go across these balance beams.
All right, Devan. You ready? - I'm ready.
- All right, here we go.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2 - Oh wait.
- Five second subscribe challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, you ready? Here we go.
- [Devan and Collins] 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Done.
- If you were able to do that, comment down below,
Key Bros squad, right now and let's go for it.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2, 1, Go!.
- Whoa
(screaming) (confetti pops)
- Here we go, all right, you got your balance?
(screams)
- You're shaking me. We shouldn't have connected these.
- Ugh, my back is terrible. How is you working, dude?
- These wings are actually kind of working.
- Pineapples for the lose. Are you like already making it?
(laughter)
Oh no. - No
- Are you in the slime? I have a chance.
I have a chance. I'm getting soaked.
(screams) Oh that was not fun.
All right so I fell off and now I've got to get back up.
- Oh, the slime is all over my feet.
- Is it slippery? - Yes.
- Your wing is hitting me.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Take the wing out - No. Sorry.
- I fell off again. This pineapple sucks.
This life hack is a bust. Here we go. 3, 2, 1, Yeet.
- I just want to make it to the Orbeez Pool.
That's all I want
(screaming)
- Why are you on my side? - I don't know. I think
- Oh my kidney. (chuckle) - Dude.
- How have you not fallen in the Legos yet?
Oh my other kidney. Do I have two kidneys?
Yeah, they both hurt.
- Extend the wings. - Oh yeah, balancing.
- I got it.
- I've got good vibe about this one man.
(screaming)
No. No. Oh no. - Yes!
- I can still make it though. I'm just going
to have to cross the Legos, (screams) it's all for the win.
- I'm so close! Yes, I won.
- Oh my gosh. Devan won the first one,
but that doesn't matter because it really
comes down to the Orbeez Obstacle Course
and then I'm thinking we turn ourselves
into human boats so right now, let's go.
Oh this is so hurting me.
To make it across the pool, you challenged us
to turn ourselves into real life human boats
using a whole bunch of ridiculous life hacks
and the first ridiculous life hack is
opening up a soda bottle with an ax. Here we go.
3, 2, - What? What? What? What?
- One! (explosion)
- Oh! - My eye!
- I ran away and it still got me.
- It's in my eye. Dude we blasted the ceiling, bro.
- It's raining. So as you're making a whack boat
over there I'm making a balloon helmet
for my first bit of inflatable boat.
- Don't flip!
(clank)
- Oh! - Come on!
- Call me dude perfect. - No. Me. I did that.
- Well, we're both on the channel, so you know.
- Exactly, team work, dynamic duo.
- All right, so I have to blow up some balloons
for this balloon helmet.
- Why is there a fire extinguisher though?
- Because I'm doing it with a completely
unrealistic, unnecessary life hack.
- Sound like our channel.
- All you need to know is that I'm making dry ice.
3, 2, 1
(spraying) (screaming)
- I wonder what our neighbors are thinking right now.
(spurting)
- So I got some dry ice, it's as simple as that.
- There's nothing.
- You know what man, this is a life hack
that's very important stuff.
- For like less than a dollar you can get
way more dry ice than that.
- Collins, life hacks.
- Time for me to make the floaty stuff that's
gonna go inside of my little ski pole buoy
over here. So, right now I'm just going to add
in some shaving cream over here.
- All right so I'm going to put this
into the hot water here.
- The dry ice? - Yeah.
And boom! - Yo!
- It's gonna blow of the balloon. Yeah!
- All right, well, I gotta say, it's
a useless life hack because its
- No, no, no, no. It does granted take a
little bit longer, but it works.
- Want to see another life hack. It's called.
(air blowing)
- See, doesn't work.
- The next thing I gotta add in over here
is some corn starch and that's going to let me
add the fluffiness to the substance.
Wait, wait, what are you doing?
- Well, it just took too long.
- What happened to your life hack?
- I don't got time for that.
- You aint got time for this life hack?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- This life hack is over.
- I knew you were going to throw it
on the ground to be honest.
- No. No. I don't break stuff. That's not who I am.
Ya. Yeet. Oh! (splat)
- Well, now that I got all my balloons blown up,
its time to make a waterproof glue.
- Wait, now what?
- So I got this mixture here,
which is sugar, water and flour.
- It looks like yogurt.
- So, I'm gonna put this vinegar in here
(crash)
- Here we go. I got the no mess corn starch.
- That's like a Frisbee, bro. See, look at this, dude.
It's a Frisbee. - Here
- Okay. - Here we go.
Go long. - I'm open.
- Go long. - I am.
- Let's test his speed. - You kidding?
(laughter) Collins, I'm over here.
- Yeah, I was testing your speed.
- I thought you were testing the speed of the Frisbee.
- No. That was a test of you Devan.
- All right, so I gotta put this vinegar
in here and just stir it up real quick.
All right, so I got this here, this nice glue,
I'm just gonna put it on my helmet.
- Here we go. Just gonna.
- Wait, Collins, you're doing what?
- I'm gonna add the corn starch.
- What are you? - All right here we go.
- You don't need to do that. Why are you doing that?
- All right here we go. 3, 2, 1. Face protected.
Here we go. Gotta rethink it like this.
Oh yeah, that's very nice. Holy cow.
Some of the remnant of what's is called
the corn starch got my eyeball.
- Are you saying croissants?
- (laughs) I want croissants.
Can you please take my goggles off?
I can't really talk or see anything.
- There you go. - Okay.
- Next, I need some webbed hands.
I have to be able to swim around like a fish.
- Swim around.
- I sound like Sid from the 'Ice Age'
(inaudible)
To make my webbed hands, I need The Glovenator.
- What in tarnation?
- Bow to its majesty.
- What kind of mid evil contraption is this?
- The first thing you need is a glove. That's right.
If you never want to touch gloves again,
we've got The Glovenator for ya.
- But you're touching a glove.
- But just ignore this part.
- Okay. It didn't happen. - Yeah, it did not happen.
All right, so I'm gonna turn on the vacuum seel here
and it should just do its thing now.
- Well here we go, I got my ski pole
and I'm gonna stab this in over here and this here
is going to be a flotation buoy.
- How am I supposed to remove it?
- Just put the (mumbles).
- I thought I never had to touch a glove again.
This is falsely advertised.
- Falsely advertised by whom?
(cynical laugh)
All right we're gonna let this thing set
in time for me to make the next part of my human boat.
Here we go. We got these life guard buoys.
(bang) - What?
- Saving lives and making them look good in the process.
These are gonna act as the flotation devices on my feet
in addition to a whole bunch of them boogie boards.
All right, my ski pole flotation devices are all set
and now the last thing I've got to do is hydro-dip them
in a whole bunch of Flex Seal. Here we go. 3, 2, 1.
(squish)
- You're going to Flex Seal them to the table. Holy cow.
- Aw man. Now we just pull it out, ta-da!
- That stuff looks so cool.
- Yep. What are you doing though?
- I am Velcro-ing these pool noodles
to this jacket so I can float.
- I'm gonna dip this one in here.
Here we go 3, 2, 1. Boom.
- Got it on my jacket. Oh my eye!
(squealing)
- No! No! I'm going to get this off real quick,
finish all this up and it's time
for the reveal of these suits.
We are all suited up in our human boats and bro,
you look absolutely insane.
- Thank you.
- Looking at these now, compared to the Orbeez Pool,
I think it's gonna be complete overkill,
so I've got an idea. Let's incorporate
our actual pool into the obstacle course.
Right now, let's head over to the pool,
then we'll jump back into the Orbeez,
but we are going over to the pool now.
- Let's do it.
- Now it's time for us to test these life hacks
against our first obstacle, the pool of treatury.
- Dun, dun. Dun.
- Basically, we have to make it all the way
across the pool take off our human boats
and finally jump in the hot tub, hit the buzzer
and the first person to do that wins.
I also forgot to mention, there's gonna be
a whole bunch of people throwing water balloons,
giant exercise balls to make it even more interesting.
So, now, here's a reveal of our human boats.
- [Daven and Collins] 3, 2,
- It's finally time to share how you can enter
for a chance to win insane prize and even appear
in a video with us. So we partnered with Adobe
to bring you the Influencer Summer Camp Contest.
There's gonna be multiple challenges
and each challenge will give you the chance
to win some insane prizes and the first challenge:
Create your best meme is kicking off right now.
- Yep. So go to CollinsKeyXAdobe.com,
download the Creative Cloud
and remember students always get 60 percent off.
Then use one of the Adobe apps like Photoshop
to create your best meme.
- And once you've created the meme, post it Instagram,
Twitter or Facebook with #AdobeMemesForPrizes
and #CollinsXAdobeContest and boom you've been
entered to win and bonus prize alert: If you go to
CollinsKeyXAdobe.com and vote on your favorite meme,
you can win even more prizes. So what are you waiting for?
Click the top link in the description and come join us
on our Influencer Summer Camp Contest.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2, 1, ta-da!
- [Collins] Look at these man.
- [Devan] Dude!
- Now this is what I'm talking about.
Don't touch me with those weird little noodles.
- I can't even hug you man.
- Yeah, I don't want to be hugged by your weird, little
noodle-y arms. All right the race is about to begin.
You ready Devan?
- Here we go.
(intense music)
[Devan And Collins] 3, 2, 1
(air horn) (splash)
- Oh man. No. No. Okay. I got this. What's happening?
Screw it. I'm blasting off (inaudible). Oh snap! Ow!
(splashing)
I'm going backwards. (inaudible)
(screams)
- [Devan] This is genius.
- Mine is not genius. Okay.
- Water balloons are making it ...
How much ammo do you guys have? Geez.
- I'm gonna make it.
(screaming) (laughter)
Ah, ow.
(intense music)
- Now for the next part, we gotta get these things off
(splash) (laughter)
(grunting)
- I gotta get these things off. Darn it. Oh man. Aw, shit.
Okay, here we go, this is for the victory. Here we go.
- [Devan] No. No, no, no.
(splash) (victory music)
- All right, so I'm the winner of the challenge, except we
(splash)
You just got everything soaked.
- What do you mean? So clearly I lost
(splat) Oh man.
- So now it's on to the next one.
All right, we have taken off our human boats,
gotten all dried off and it is finally time to tackle
the Orbeez Obstacle Course.
- What? - in all of its glory, man.
- Yes!
- So the first thing here is the Wipe Out balls.
We're going to have to bounce our way across these
then we're gonna make it to the punching wall over there,
have to throw balloons at a target.
Once you hit the target you can move on to the next part,
which is the teeter totter wall.
Once you make it over that, you gotta cross
the boogie boards, climb up on the scaffolding
and finally pop all the balloons as you look
for the final end buzzer.
Oh I also forgot to mention, there's gonna be
a whole bunch of people throwing water balloons,
and maybe even more interesting things.
Whoever hits that buzzer first, they win.
- It's gonna be me.
- I don't know about that.
Now, in my opinion, the most difficult part
of this entire obstacle course is going to be trying
to throw those water balloons at a target
while getting punched a whole bunch of times.
- Oh, so that's where we light the watermelon?
- No, no, no. Not yet, Devan.
- No? Not Yet?
- We're just wait on the watermelon, trust me,
it's gonna be used at the perfect moment.
The life hack that I'm focusing on is making sure
that I don't get punched once.
- Oo. Okay, well I think the hardest part of this course
is gonna be that teeter totter,
so I'm gonna make a life hack to help me get over that.
- All right, right now, let's go make our life hacks
and then its time to jump in to the
Orbeez Obstacle Course, so let's go.
- Yes!
- In preparation for the Ultimate Wipe Out Course,
we're making some DIY shields.
- And I'm making some sticky gloves.
- Yes, we are. Oh, no. That was not called for Devan.
- Sorry. Whoa!
(cynical laugh) - Fear
So the first life hack I'm doing is basically this tube
right here, you see this thing that's filled with water?
Well, this is gonna be the strap that I use
across satchel side. If you can just cut
right there for me.
- I'm with it. I'm with it. All right. Sure. 3, 2, 1,
(water spraying)
- (screams) There we go.
(laughter) (squealing)
(indistinct)
- That was not what I expected. Okay, here we go.
3, 2, 1 (splash)
Oh there we go.
- First DIY is done and I gotta say,
I think it was a complete win across the board,
couldn't have gone better.
- Bam. Are you kidding me?
- I'm not kidding Devan. I'm for reals.
- We did all of that, for that?
- Exactly, because now it's stretched.
- For my sticky glove, I'm making a rowing glove,
which is a life hack apparently, so we'll find out.
You ready? - Wait.
- [Devan and Collins] What?
- Yo are you all right dude, are you okay?
- I think I might be stuck.
- Holy, yeah, I think it is stuck man, what is going on?
- So this is gonna be the mold for my glove
and I have no idea how I'm gonna get my hand out.
- You seemed to use some sorcery magic to get it end there,
so maybe you need some sorcery magic to get it out, Devan.
Lucky for you, I have a very industrial magic wand.
Here we go now I gotta send a magic words.
Ready Devan, I'm gonna aim for your heart.
- What? Why?
- It's the only way to make this work
so stand like this so I can see you.
- Okay - Here we go 3, 2, 1
Abra-crowbar-dabra
- Ugh, my spleen - Oh sorry about that.
Here we go, here we go.
(screams)
- My full intestine! Ow.
- This thing is not accurate, but the real question:
How did it help the thing?
- Ta-da!
- A dab for the the Crowbar-dabra. Respectfully.
- [Devan] So, nicely done.
- [Collins] That's going to be the mold?
- Yes. This will be the mold for my sticky glove.
- All right and this is going to be the base
of my shield cause here's the thing.
As we go across this Wipe Out obstacle course
there's gonna be a whole bunch of objects flying at us
that we got to like dodge and protect to make sure
we don't get knocked off the course.
So, first thing I gotta do when you're trying
to hold the shield what don't you want? A handle.
I'm making my own custom handle because this handle,
not reliable. I need something that I know
is battle tested and can take, I don't know shrimps.
Cause who knows what they're going
to be throwing at us man. Like shrimps could be
coming flying. You'd be like a shrimp cocktail.
- That's what you're most concerned about? Shrimp?
- Dude, flying shrimps are crazy bro?
- Are they? - Oh yeah.
- All right. - A lot of legs.
I'm gonna pop the handle off.
- You're bending the shield, dude.
- Okay, I think we are going to revert to the other way.
- Wow. All right, so now that my mold is made
I have this silicone here
(crash) - I'll figure out how to get
this handle off, don't you worry.
- I'm gonna pour into here for my sticky glove.
You ready for this? - Yes.
- All right.
- Dude, this handle is not coming off.
- [Devan] 3, 2, 1. Oh, dude look at the colors
in this thing it looks so good.
(elevator music)
(rock music) (banging)
- Hey! I got it!
- Now that the silicone is on the inside,
I'm gonna let this solidify off to the side here
and now I'm gonna melt down some of these sticky hands.
- While you do that, time for me to get my shield
to be a little bit more flat cause right now
it looks like what it is, which is a trash can lid.
Do you mind holding this for one second?
- Whoa
- I'll place it like this, a little hat for ya.
Here we go, old fashioned, it's one of Devan's passions.
I'm just going to pick this up over here.
Ah, it's very heavy.
- Collins, you see what I'm doing over here?
It's pretty genius.
(grunting)
I'm gonna move my heavy equipment over here.
This stuff is great.
- I'm melting down sticky hands for my sticky gloves, bro.
- Where did my trash can lid go? Hold on.
- What do you mean, it's on my head.
- Oh, well alrighty. Let's, let's see,
I'm just gonna take it like this.
I don't know how to use this to be completely honest.
- [Devan] Dude, this isn't actually working very well.
- You and me both Devan. You and me both.
So therefore Captain America Shield the background.
(crash)
I'm just saying, I could be in the movies.
- Yeah, no, Collins, it has to come back.
- The only unfortunate thing is that
this isn't quite Vibranium. I think it's called
Aluminum and it is bent quite out of shape.
- If you're having trouble bending Aluminum, bro,
I cannot imagine you as a superhero.
- Oh, you came at me. - Aluminum.
- That was uncalled for.
- That's aluminum not Vibranium, bro.
- Nice.
- You know, instead of doing this, I think I'm just gonna
put it in the oven to heat it up. This is terrible.
Dude, look at the hand that I got out of the mold.
- Wait a minute, couldn't you have just used a regular
glove instead of filling that.
- No. This is useless life hacks, bro.
- I forgot. This is a useless life hack here.
Our next step (crash) oh! No.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- A lot of paint! These things are filled with paint.
This was, again, another terrible life hack
because they didn't stay on here, so here's the deal
I got to paint my shield for no other reason
than aesthetically its gotta look beautiful
as I'm on the Wipe Out course because you guys
know me, aesthetic beauty is my main thing.
It's what I'm known for. So here we go.
I'm just gonna empty out the stuff like this.
- Dude, we're actually doing something similar,
but this is actually the melted down sticky hands.
- Happy to hear that Devan.
We got a little paint on here and this is a life hack
I saw on TikTok, so I don't know if it's actually
gonna work or not, but this way,
I'm making it look really cool.
So usually I'm not the artsy one, but this time
I think I am. Here we go, 3, 2, 1.
- Whoa
(crash)
Nice slip.
- That got paint everywhere man, look at this.
On the top of it ta-da!
- It looks like trash.
Dude, I can't believe these melted down sticky hands
actually worked, now all I gotta do is just peel
it off of this mold and then I'm done.
- So we just got to finish these things up
and then its time to tackle tie Wipe Out obstacle course.
All right, we finished up our life hacks
and these are gonna be so important to make sure
we make it across the obstacle course.
Mine's a shield to make sure not one
punches me on that punch wall.
- And man these gloves are sticky, dude.
- All right so now it's time to go place these
exactly where they need to be on the obstacle course.
- So, I'm gonna put my gloves over here
so that they're ready for the wall.
- I almost just tripped man, that's not a good sign
for this obstacle course if I'm already tripping.
- It's hot. - It is hot.
- Holy cow. Oh geez. Okay. I'm gonna put it.
- Put it down, put it down, put it down.
- Shield's there, good to go.
- All right, let's hop back over.
- Whew. It's hot.
- For the first leg here is the Wipe Out balls.
We have to bounce our way across these
then we're gonna make it to the punching wall
over there, have to throw balloons at a target.
Once you hit the target, you move on to the next part
which is the teeter totter wall.
Once you make it over that you gotta
cross the boogie boards, climb up on the scaffolding,
and finally pop all the balloons
as you look for the final end buzzer.
Oh, I also forgot to mention,
there's gonna be a whole bunch of people
throwing water balloons
and maybe even more interesting things.
Whoever hits that buzzer first, they win.
- It's gonna be me.
- I don't know about that.
We'll decide who goes first with a classic game
of rock, paper, scissors.
- Let's do it. Here we go.
- [Devan and Collins] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot. Oo!
- Nice to meet you.
- [Devan and Collins] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- Aye! - Man!
- So I get to start first.
So, right now, let's run the course. Here we go.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2, Wait.
- If you want access to exclusive content,
special events and a whole bunch more,
click the link in the description and join our Keyper Club.
It's completely free to join.
We cannot wait to see you there. It is a ton of fun.
So right now, let's run the course.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2, 1 - Oh!
- Oh dude, holy cow! I took a ball to the face.
I gotta get back on, I gotta get back on.
- Wait. No, no, no.
- Do it, do it.
(screaming) (laughing)
(splashing)
- [Collins] Okay. Here we go. Come on (inaudible).
Spoiler alert: Attack
(whistle) (splash)
- [Devan] No. No. No.
- It got me. Not me. Give me your hand,
I want to get you through this. Here we go.
(splash)
Dude, that was right on his shins (laughter)
Quick pause. We need to give Devan some CPR here.
(inaudible) go like this. Is it working?
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Come on across.
- Here we go. Here we go. Okay. There we go.
We're gonna pretend like that worked.
- All right we made it through obstacle number one
and now it's time to throw water balloons,
hit the target without getting punched.
Where' my life hack? (splash)
All right so I got my shield here.
The issue with this is like an anti-life hack.
I'm not left handed, but I've gotta be left handed.
Here we go. (grunts)
(splash) Oh geez. That was (inaudible)
- Ow. - Oh my god.
(screaming) (splash)
(inaudible)
- This is super tough.
- [Man] Heads up there.
- I got a shield man. The shield's not working.
- It feels like were going on.
(grunting) (splashing)
- Ouch. That was to my head.
- I think this is good.
- Here we go.
- I think it's good.
(splash) (cheering)
- All right. All right. Come on. Do it.
- I got to get this. Here we go.
Guys, here we go, here we go.
- Lose!
(cheering)
- No, no, no, no.
- [Group] 3, 2, 1, Oh!
- You made it. What? He's like Spider Man.
- Whoa. Okay. All right.
- You want me to push you over?
- Oh yes. Wow!
- Devan. Flip it my way.
- There's no way you're getting around this, bro.
- Whoa. Man that's not right.
- No. You ain't getting around this.
(grunting)
- Oh, my shins! Holy cow!
- It's back. There you go, I've had it.
- Oh! That was close.
- All right, here we go.
It's gonna go forward,
but I'm not really fully committed.
Oh, that was a weird place to get hit.
No. No, no, no, no, no. No. No. No. No.
(splashing)
(laughter)
I just got clocked by a mystery ball.
- Come on bro, it's--
- What Devan?
- Yes. - Aw, what? Holy cow!
(laughter)
You know what, that was actually very close.
- No.
(splashing)
- Oh, that's concrete on my knee.
- Thank you for not hitting me at point blank range,
I appreciate it.
(water spraying) (screaming)
- Okay. All right.
- Oh, no way!
- Yeah! Yes!
- All right, you know what, the boogie boards
have just submerged, so just imagine
I'm stepping on the boogie boards right now.
- Wait. Wait. How do we pop them?
- With my hands.
(nylon squeaking)
- Nope. Not there.
- All right, good. I got to find this button
to make it before you do.
(screaming) (balloons popping)
- Ew, I got hit in the chest. (splash)
(laughter) - Brutal, man.
Holy cow, I don't know how many more hits I can take.
- Dude, my eye!
- Don't try this at home, all right guys.
We are a little bit high up right now.
There's only a few balloons left
to try to get here (inaudible).
There's the buzzer! It went into the Orbeez.
Holy cow, we got to get there.
We got to get that person down.
- [Devan] My eye!
- Here we go.
- No! Man.
- Yes, and I won the Orbeez Obstacle Course.
You know what that means. I get to light
the matches watermelon, man.
- I wanted to do that so bad.
- The ultimate prize, so right now, let's go light it up.
It is finally time to reveal what's up
with this life hack here, and since I won
the majority of the obstacles,
that means I get to demonstrate it's awesome power.
- I'm so bummed. I don't even know what this is for.
- If you were to take a guess,
what do you think this life hack is for, Devan?
- Uh, haircuts? I don't know.
- Haircuts? No, no, no, Think about it.
- A bowl cut, you know?
It's like in a watermelon bowl.
- Basically I took a watermelon
stuffed with a whole bunch of matches
and are you ready for the big reveal
of what this life hack is?
(drum roll) 3, 2, 1.
The ultimate pool light! - Are you kidding?
- As you can tell, the pool light 3000.
- That's what it is?
- Imagine it just glistening and glowing in the light, man.
- Does it actually float though?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no.
- It doesn't really float.
- Yeah, get it out.
- You're gonna mess up my matches, Devan.
- Kind of floats, but not really.
- Holy cow. All right, so, grab the lighter
and we gotta say do not try this at home.
- Yeah, don't.
- [Devan and Collins] 3, 2,
- Oh wait, if you want to win some insane prizes,
click the top link in the description
and join our Influencer Summer Camp Contest.
The first challenge: Create your best meme
kicks off right now, so click the link, literally right now.
You might even appear in one of our YouTube videos.
- Yep
- Now, let's light this thing up.
- [Devan and Collins] All right. Here we go.
- 3, 2, You know what, - What?
- Since I won the majority of the obstacles,
how about I get to light it. - What?
- So here we go, ready? All right. No!
- No! - No!
- Dude, I didn't have it.
- Are you kidding me? That was you.
- I only have one hand. - Butterfingers.
- I was handing you the lighter.
- Dude, its ruined, bro.
We're gonna have to swim in the darkness now, Devan.
- I was so ready to light this thing.
- Come on. I think it still works.
Try to light it. (inaudible)
- I'm so hoping it still works.
- All right, hold it away from my face.
- [Collins] Oh, please, please.
Nothing.
Yo, I spent hours on this.
- Are you kidding?
- You know what, I'm gonna have to retry this
for TikTok, but if you want to see that video
click right over here. You've got five seconds. Here we go.
- [Devan and Collins] 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, done.
- Love you. - [Devan and Collins] Bye.