- Yo, we got watermelon!
You want some?
- Yeah, of course.
- Alright, here we go just gonna crack it open like this.
Yo! - Oh, wait, what?
- Check it out! - How did you do that?
- How'd you make it orange?
- Orange, wait, you want an orange?
Alright, here we go. - Wait, an orange?
- An orange!
So I just gotta smooth it off a little bit and there you go.
There's your orange. - I asked how did you
- make it orange, not get me an orange.
- Alright, well right now we're gonna show you
how to peel a watermelon.
So right now, let's go.
For this kitchen hack, the secret is
you don't need one watermelon, you need
two watermelons! - Two watermelons!
- And so here's what we're going to do.
First step, we gotta peel one of the watermelons.
So we're going to place one of them off
to the side right now.
And now, we have to peel the melon.
If you do this at home and if you're using
a knife, you must be very careful.
Even if you need to ask for someone else who's very
experienced with knives to help you out on this.
Fun fact, watermelons actually have micro-hairs on them.
- Wait, what?
I've never seen hair on a watermelon.
- Look at this.
- [Devon] What?
- Deny that, boom - You just
put a mustache on it. - Proof, no!
- [Collins] So here we go.
So, it's gonna some shaving cream on it.
Oh! - Oh!
- Bro!
- Don't touch, hey, hey, hey, stop, stop!
Devon.
- What?
- Shave the melon.
- [Devon] You didn't even take off the hair, bro.
(Collins yells)
- What?
Now, I noticed that Devon used a knife to carve off
the top layer of it, but I think
that he did it the wrong way, per usual.
So, - I did not.
- I gotta use super sped up, super awesome sandpaper.
Let's go!
- Wait, what?
Whoa, whoa.
- Oh, no! - Whoa!
- [Devon] Hey now!
- No dude, it broke in half!
- [Devon] Dude, you broke it.
- We're going to use this right over here
and we're just gonna relax him.
Now that he's relaxed into a very subdued
and quiet state, it's time to wake him up.
- Oh, oh poor watermelon.
- Dude. Dude. Dude.
Most watermelons are uptight, they're always in a circle.
They're always like, (grunts)
but when you relax them they're like ahhh.
- [Watermelon] Ahhh.
- Alright, mine is all peeled and now it's time
to move on to the next step.
Step one is to cut it in half.
Step two is you scoop out what is inside of the watermelon.
- Just like this.
- [Devon] It's harder than you would expect.
- (tongue clicking) Oh, oh, oh!
Devon, if you could just put your finger on my forehead.
(Grunts)
Three, two, one.
Yes!
- Ay! - It worked!
- Waiting on slowpoke Devon over here.
- I'm ready to go. - Alright, Devon gonna
- go into hyper-speed right now.
Activate it.
(upbeat carinval music)
- And done.
- Alright, hyper-speed is out.
Here's the big reveal.
Three, two, one, ta-dah! - Three, two, one, ta-dah!
- So I'm just gotta crack mine open like that.
Ta-dah!
And you get to comment down below who made a better
peeled watermelon and right now we're on to the next round.
For this round, you challenged us
to make orange jack-o-lanterns.
So right now, let's go. - Wait.
Dude, all jack-o-lanterns are orange bro.
- No, see this time we're literally
making them out of oranges.
And now with my supersonic hands, I can crush 'em.
These actually makes it harder to grip things.
Alright well, right now, let's go!
First step, we gotta tenderize these oranges.
- Jack-o-lanterns are supposed
to be round, not oval shaped, bro.
- We gotta give it the second once over tenderizer.
So, this is it here.
(Grunting)
Okay, there we go, perfect, done.
And next up, we gotta add some little
magic genie juice on this thing, bro.
(magic music)
And done. - Wow.
- Alright, the genie juice is on it.
- Alright well, while you're doing that,
you're actually supposed to cut off the top of it
and then take out the inside with a spoon.
- Oh!
Alright, so now I'm just gonna remove the top.
So, here we go.
- It's empty now so the next step is
to draw out how my jack-o-lantern is gonna look.
- Alright, the designs are on
and now it's time to carve 'em out.
Alright. eyeball number one has been completed.
- Well, this is actually way easier than I expected.
First eye done.
Final step is to add the candle.
- These jack-o-lanterns turned out so cool
and bro, yours looks absolutely insane.
So here's the big reveal.
Three, two - Three, two
- Wait, wait, first, five seconds to subscribe to challenge!
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Five, four, three, - Five, four, three,
- Two, one, done. - Two, one, done.
If you can do that, comment down below
Keyper squad right now.
Ta-dah! - Ta-dah!
- Bro!
- Dude! - These are awesome.
So you get to comment down below who you think won.
My jack-o-lantern--
- Wait, is yours throwing up?
- So right now guys, we're on to the next one.
So this round you challenged us to make
a whole bunch of aquatic snacks.
- Collins, what are you wearing?
- Bro, I'm a dolphin.
Or should I say (dolphin calls)
- Uh, wow.
- Now it's time to swim into the round and we dive.
- Dude, you're not even swimming,
you're trawling and clapping.
Do some dives.
What?
Okay.
- Next up, we got the bananas.
So right now we just gonna need one banana.
So there we go, perfect.
I got my one banana.
Only thing left is for this to be blessed by the holy llama.
So here we go.
Holy llama, holy llama, uh, uh.
Holy llama, holy llama. - Is this necessary?
- And now, for the final blessing process!
There we go!
(Trilling)
Woohoo! - Creepy eyed monster.
- Guys, if you do this, be very careful.
- I'm crying a little bit.
- Alright, so first step is you cut off this top part
and then you move it off to the side
'cause we're going to use it later.
- Next step, you cut the banana at an angle like that.
- Ay! - Ay!
- And this you have to be very, very careful.
We're gonna chop down the center of it.
Boom, nailed it.
Now it kind of looks like a little dolphin.
Yo, it's like (dolphin calls)
So next up,
- Yes!
- we're going to use this little bit over here.
So you're gonna cut it in half, being very careful.
We're gotta add the little eye holes;
a little, little area right over here.
And then we're going to put this little bit
of like rotten stuff in there, or not rotten,
but the top of the (gasps)
(laughs) It looks like a little eye.
Next up, we gotta make sure our dolphins can
swim in the great blue ocean of the world.
We're just gonna do this, we're gonna, like that.
You make little triangles on it like that.
We're gonna pull up the little fin.
Look at him, he's like yo, what's up?
How you doin' bro?
- Alright, now we add a grape to it.
- Look it's so cute and now all we have
to do is make the ocean habitat in which
it lives and this part is super easy.
Whelp, we got a little bit carried away here.
We made a whole bunch of dolphin friends.
We actually made a whole super pod.
So now, we gotta make the ocean.
So we're gonna take out this little tree
'cause there ain't no trees in the ocean.
Yeet!
Alright, so we just need some--
- Yeet!
- It's very rare that you out-yeet me,
but today you have out-yeeted me.
Congratulations, Devon.
- You're welcome.
(trumpet playing)
- Fleet!
Doesn't even work.
I think mine is all mixed up enough so
I'm just gonna start populating it
with my dolphin breed or squad.
Squad, no pod?
Pod.
Let's get this little dude in here.
Oh, they're all kind of like falling on over, oof.
That's so cute, they're like sharing this little grape,
but naw fam, star-crossed lovers.
You gonna have to sit at opposite sides, bam!
Now I got my saucer paucer of apple sauces and dolphins.
Well, you know what you guys get to comment down below
who made a better pod of dolphins.
Mine's a super pod, his is a regular pod.
We'll be eating these at the end of the video,
but right now we are on to the next round.
You challenged us to the pancake art challenge,
but with eggs.
- Oh, oh jeez.
Oh, I caught it! - That was a good catch.
- But right now, here we go, - Dude, what?
- we're gonna do a--
Oh, you're good at it. - You're gonna
crack the eggs, bro. - That was another good catch.
- Here we go, another one.
Oh! - Oh, I got it!
- You got it!
- Alright Collins, now it's time
to test your net catching skills.
You ready? - Alright, yeah.
- Here we go! (screaming)
- What! - Oh, it cracked, no!
- [Collins] I got this. - Here you go.
Okay, there we go, you got another one.
- Oh!
Now it's time to crack open some eggs.
So, this is our first egg cracking contraption.
- [Devon] How does this even work?
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
- Oh! - Oh!
- What?
- (screams) Mind blown!
But you know what, since I accidentally put my yolk
in there, here's the way I'm going to fix it.
We got a stealth cactus.
And then it goes (slurping), and then sucks it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Whoops, sorry.
Okay, okay. - Oh no, did you break it?
- Now this contraption is incredible.
The goal is you place it on top here,
and it will cut out a perfect circle at the top of the egg.
Three, two, one.
- Oh, no way!
No, it just made a little mark on it.
Three, two, one.
- Mine worked.
Oh! - Oh!
- What?
- What!
- Like look at this little hat.
What, I'm stylin' now!
Next up is the very challenging task of
transferring all of these egg whites and egg yolks
into these pancake art bottles.
- But luckily, we have this egg holder
slash funnel-looking thing.
Alright, you ready for this?
- Sure!
- It's working!
- Oh, man I filled it up too fast!
- It's not your fault, it's the funnel's fault.
- Oh, oh!
- Okay, that was partly your fault.
- So we got the egg whites,
and now it's time for the egg yolks.
- Hopefully you've learned, Collins.
- Learned what?
I was gonna straight freestyle this thing.
If 50% of it makes it in,
that's better than my normal average.
(gasps) Yo!
Haha!
The moment has come.
It is time to make the egg art.
So first, we gotta Pam it up a little bit.
You know, get a little bit of Pam on--
No, ooh, ooh.
Alright, so I don't know what Devon's going for here.
I have a little bit of an idea of what I'm gonna make.
So, here we go.
Step one, done!
Gonna give him a little ooh!
- This stuff does not cooperate.
Now it's time for the eye.
Oh, no!
This is so difficult, bro!
- Like work with me!
- [Devon] Mine is not turning out, dude.
Here we go, I'm just gonna add a little bit more around it.
- I can't work with this.
- I got the touch for this thing!
- Oh, I'm messing it up further!
Alright, it's time for me to flip mine.
- Oh, man!
This might me the first art challenge that I'm gonna win!
- You ready for this?
- Yeah! - Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Oh!
- It doesn't even flip like a pancake!
- Wait, so what is that?
- It got folded in half.
It was supposed to be a chicken, dude.
- Here's the big flip.
You ready?
Three, two, wait, wait, - Two
- first, three second like challenge!
We want to see if you can like this video in three seconds.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Three, two, one, done. - Three, two, one, done.
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
- Oh! - Oh!
Aye, I think you did that
good. - I recovered it fully!
We're gonna try this one more time, here we go.
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
Oh, oh! - Oh, oh!
- You just took it out of the pan.
- [Collins] Oh, oh no.
Well this was a complete fail, but you get
to comment down below, even after they both got wrecked,
who made a better one?
And right now, we are on to the next one.
For this round you challenged us to turn
an ordinary apple into a terrifying monster.
So right now, the game is 86 to 89 love
and let's just get lit!
(laughing)
Jesus, sorry!
- It snapped on my finger!
- I'm sorry.
First step, you're gonna take an apple,
drop it on your cutting board,
and then we're gonna use these paddles.
We use the dog squat of poppin-ness.
- [Devon] Do you take the-- (porcelain crashing)
- Oh, I didn't know.
Next up we're gonna use a dinosaur head
to split this thing in half and fun fact,
T-Rex's heads are 6 times stronger than an actual banana.
- Only 6 times?
- Yeah, that's it.
- That's surprisingly little.
- Yeah, a couple little dinisaurs. (yells)
- Oh, dude, oh!
Next up, cut up the strawberries.
- Oh, yeah!
- Just wanna put that out there.
- Wait, you already started?
What?
- Like half way through.
- That's crazy.
I got a focus up real quick.
- Almost done.
- Wait, What?
Okay, gotta use these to give me a vision into the future.
Here we go.
Whoa.
Whoa, dude. - Are you okay?
- The future is too crazy, bro.
You don't even wanna know what happened.
The dinisaurs came back.
It was absolute may-
- Next up we take two grapes, a toothpick,
break the toothpick in half, stick the toothpick
in the grape, just like this,
and you attach it to the top as eyes.
- So alright, here we go.
Just gonna feed him some raisins.
Nom, nom, nom, nom!
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom!
- So, the last step is you take some raisins,
you take small pieces off of the toothpick,
and you attach the to the grapes as little pupils.
- My dude has strawberry eyebrows.
Alright, here's the big reveal of our terrifying monsters.
Three, two, one, ta-dah! - Three, two, one, ta-dah!
So you get to comment down below
and let us know which monster is scarier.
For this round you challenged us
to turn a pineapple, oh my gosh, into a parrot.
First step you gotta grab a pineapple.
Ooh. - Watch that snack.
See Devon, we're making a pineapple parrot
and this is gonna be the feathers of the parrot.
First step's first, you're--
- You have a dusty pineapple, bro.
- I know, I'm just gonna get rid of all the dust.
Be very careful with the knives
and maybe ask someone else to help you.
But now we're just gonna cut, I'd say about,
(high pitched beep) like right here.
You now have the bird!
I know it doesn't look like it, but trust me this is it.
You gotta carve this into the head.
- So how do you do that?
- Well you could either carve it or
you can just take a beak like this,
and just pop it on over the top and then you're finished.
- Seems kind of like cheating bro.
- Yeah, we're not gonna do that so fleet!
Oops.
- I think it would be easier to get this stuff off first.
- You're not supposed to take that stuff off.
- Yeah you are!
- It's the plume-age.
This is the feather of the bird.
- No, it doesn't have that much plume-age.
- I'm making a peacock, bro.
A peacock parrot.
Why can't we make a p-carrot?
- Next up after, - Keep it clamped down.
- what you do is you use scissors
and you cut off some of these leaves near the bottom.
- Again, unless you're making a p-carrot.
Man, this thing is not holding in place.
Alright, there we go, nice.
- This reminds me of trimming my bonsai tree.
- Fun fact, Devon has a bonsai tree
and I must say it's in phenomenal condition.
Alright, now here we go.
So I think that that is the top of my p-carrot.
- Can I just say, I had no idea
how dusty pineapples were, bro.
- Well I can help out cleaning it.
- No, no, no, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That would make it dirtier, bro!
- What, this is super clean.
- No, you have a dirty duster
Just sayin'. - Excuse me?
Now I just gotta scoop out the interior of this here.
(groaning)
It's just not working, man.
(hammering)
Alright, there we go, perfect.
And now just, I don't actually know if that helped at all.
Let's just use a carrot pick.
(hammering)
- [Devon] A carrot pick?
- Slinky solutions, let's slink.
- Slinky solutions?
- Yeah, that's gonna be the name
of my company, Slinky Solutions.
- Next step is shaping the head.
- I'm just gonna have to go into the top
of the pineapple here and just (groans)
Here we go, the carrot's still in there.
- Alright, mine is shaped now.
It's time for me to carve it out.
- Done!
Alright so I had to use the pineapple
of destiny to finish it off and you know what,
to celebrate we're going to use the trumpet of triumph.
(saxophone playing)
- Wow dude, that's quite an impressive
lung capacity you have there.
- Yeah, and that's why they call me
the clairvoyant clarineter.
- It's a saxophone.
- Actually, it's a snorkel.
(whistle blowing)
Everything else is ready except now we gotta finish up
the head of my p-carrot and your regular parrot.
So right now, let's turn these into a masterpiece.
- Dude, yours looks crazy, bro!
- Yeah, I don't know what happened there,
but here's the big reveal!
Three, two, wait, - Two, one
- first if you wanna win 15 minute video call
with Devon and I, text the word FOOD to 81800 right now!
So pause the video and text the word FOOD to 81800,
you will automatically be entered in to win it
and right now, here's the big reveal.
You ready?
Three, two, one, ta-dah! - Three, two, one, ta-dah!
- [Devon] Yours is terrifying!
- Well I added some extra eyes!
So now it's also spider as well.
So now it's called a sp-carrot.
A spider, parrot, carrot.
So you guys comment down below who made a better one
and right now we are on to the next one.
This round is crazy!
I'm literally going to teleport to New York
with special guests for this next one!
- Wait, what?
That's awesome, bro!
- Yeah, so just gotta grab one thing and here we go!
I'm gonna miss you, bro!
- Alright, see you later!
Have fun! - Alright, here we go!
Three, two, one.
- Wait, why did he take my watermelon?
- Yo, what's up guys!
It's Collins Key and I'm here with Kelly and Ryan.
I just finished filming their live show
and now they're here on the channel.
So we're gonna be making a watermelon shark.
You guys ready?
- We're ready!
Let's go! - A shark that bites back!
- Exactly!
Alright, so right now, let's go!
- Good news for me, Kelly is a master crafter!
- Move your fingers, move your fingers.
- She looks super good at this.
- Alright, so now my dude.
Oh yeah I forgot, we gotta scoop out little balls.
Those are very important.
See, they're already ahead of me on this one.
I'm just kinda going for it at this point.
You guys got the Keyper Squad shirts on so it's all good.
It's meant to get a little messy, you know.
Dude, I'm going for the win, bro!
Uh oh. - I like it.
- Okay now. - Weez good!
These guys are pros!
What?
- Snap, crackle!
- Yo, yo, yo, oh!
- I mean, I really will say that this looks like
something prehistoric and really bad happened to this.
- How?
I really gotta step my game up, man.
This is not good.
- No, we need a fin so I'm gonna festoon a fin.
- Festoon?
Is that a cooking term?
- It's a carving term. - Yeah, it's a carving term.
- If you're not careful, she'll festoon us, alright?
- He looks so sad! (laughs)
- What, that looks so cool! - It looks vicious!
- The whole operation is falling apart over here, guys.
- What's happening with you?
- You know, just (laughs)
- Have you ever done this before? (laughs)
- No, I have never the craft.
I mean, that's like, it's there, but like barely.
Okay, well that's good.
I guess we'll just pour it back in now.
- I'm going to take a couple of teeth out.
- Yours vomited!
- Yeah it's looking definitely like it vomited.
- So now you fill it back in.
- Look at that.
Martha Stewart, eat your heart out!
- Yo, this thing is not turning out.
There's no way that I can win.
Hey bro, can you hear me?
- (yells) Go for Dev.
- I need you to make me a watermelon shark right now.
- Already on it.
(intense music)
- Bro, do you have it?
- Almost there.
- Dude, hurry up!
- Dude, these things take time!
It's ready.
- Alright, so I guess they're working on
their shark over there and I guess we'll give this a shot.
Here we go, three, two, one, bam!
Alright, cool!
So I think I'll just add a couple of finishing touches here.
- Wait, hang on, hang on! - Hold on, hold on, time,
- Calling time out.
- This is what we ended up with so,
I guess these are the watermelon sharks that
you guys get to comment down below,
who made a better watermelon shark.
- Yeah, who made it? - Wait, no, wait!
- Who made it? - That's illegal.
- Thank you guys so much for being here!
- Thank you!
- Alright, you guys I gotta teleport back to LA.
So here we go, three, two, one.
- What just happened here?
(upbeat music)
- And then finally we're just gonna stick it
in the cactus cup for a second.
Just let it sit there as it continues to tenderize.
- Did you break the cactus cup?
- Not broken, just altered it and improved it.
Pick it up from, oh!
- Hey, you grab a pineapple, bro.
- Oh no, we got a little bit of uh oh,
we got some spiky things sticking to the pineapple.
- Oh no.
- There we go, get that one out.
So now let's test out how one of these things flies off.
So here we go, we're gonna get--
- What, flies off of what?
Remove one of these little pieces here
and place it on the top and then...
- You dropped it!
What was that for?
- So I had to see how it's gonna react
in its aerodynamic ability to fly through the air.
Why does a pirate wanna join the X-Men?
'Cause he wants to become a mutiny.
Comment down below what is your favorite food
you would love to see us make a kitchen hack out of!
And if you want wanna get your own merch,
click the top link in the description
or you go to ShopCollinsKey.com right now
to get your merch before it's all sold out!
And if you wanna see another video, click right over here.
You have five seconds, here we go!
Five, four, three, - Five, four, three,
- two, one, done! - two, one, done!
Love you!
Bye!