- [Collins] Dragon fruit ink!
- Oh my God! - Oh my God!
- You challenged us to make giant edible markers,
rockets using a whole bunch of life hacks, so let's go!
- [Collins] This is the perfect life hack
for peeling apples, I'll be using these
as the eraser for my pencil.
- [Devan] This is the edible ink that's gonna go
inside my Sharpie, you ready?
Three, two, one!
- Ooh! - Oh!
- All right, now I just gotta grab a balloon.
- [Collins] Wait, you going for another one?
- [Devan] Yes, I'm going for another one.
- Three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- Aah, no! - Aah, no!
- That was insane! - Wow!
These are gonna be perfect ink capsules
for the inside of my sharpie.
All right Collins, I have a grand strategy for my sharpie.
This is an inflatable sharpie,
and it's not what I'm gonna be using.
- Okay but we're trying to make edible ones,
not just inflatable, that'd be - No.
- cheating. - So I have to make
a mold for the cap of my Sharpie,
so I have to fill this thing up with a normal,
boring garden hose.
- Oh so for mine, it's a much simpler process,
I've got an apple, time to freeze it,
and this will be the eraser for my pencils.
- [Devan] I ended up filling up the Sharpie
with a normal, boring garden hose.
- [Collins] Oh, gotta get a couple of these apples out,
here we go.
- Now, I've got my hot isomalt, do not try this at home!
- Yep, do not try this at home!
- I don't even know how you would.
- [Collins] Do you need any help with this, Devan?
- I got it! - Your hand
looks mighty shaky.
- Oh! - Oh, wait a minute!
The plastic appears to be
bubbling up!
- No, no, no, no! - Devan, Devan!
- No, no, this is gonna be the greatest cap ever, bro!
- [Collins] I can already see the structural integrity
is waning, Devan.
- I can already see your faith waning!
- You didn't have to come at me like that, Devan.
Time to smash some apples for my erasers, so here we go!
- Oh yes!
- Snag my favorite hammer. (godly light beaming)
How is this not gonna pop, Devan?
- I don't know, but we're working through it, just like
any relationship, you know?
- You're in a relationship with this giant Sharpie?
- No, no, just like, you know it's a metaphor.
- This just in! YouTube star, Devan Key rumored
to be in a relationship with a giant Sharpie marker!
- Rumored by one source!
- Himself!
- No, no!
- Back to you, Patricia!
All right, here we go, time for the smash, ready?
Three, two, one! - Two, one!
- Oh! - Oh my gosh!
- [Devan] I think it's leaking out of the bottom.
- [Collins] You hear that sound?
- It's like an ice glacier cracking, dude!
- [Collins] All right, now to make the applesauce
I just gotta gather up all the pieces of the apple
for the eraser over here.
- [Devan] I'm just gonna let this dry, then cover
the other side, and then I got my Sharpie cap!
- To make the lead of my pencil, I've got some
liquid nitrogen, and also a bath bomb!
And here's the thing.
What are you doing?
- I have rigged up an old fidget spinner here
to crack some eggs with the tip of my pen!
- I can't even get close to it
right now, man, - Yes!
- it's going so crazy! - It is--
- Oh! - Oh!
- You can crack it into the bowl.
- Oh, you've launched another.
- Hey! I got one, that ain't bad, 1 out of 2 ain't bad!
- Yeah it's one out of three. - Wait it's one out of three.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. - That's a pretty poor
percentage, Devan.
- [Devan] Look at that, Boom!
- [Collins] I'm not really sure how this is a life hack,
it seems to make everything more complicated.
All right, well I've got my bath bomb here, and I have
a question, Devan. What do you think is gonna happen
when I drop
- No questions allowed!
- [Collins] Well, what happens when I drop a bath bomb
into liquid nitrogen, Devan?
Three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- [Devan] Whoa!
- I'm out! I'm out!
It appears as though it's, um...
- [Devan] It seems fine.
- Got a container of water right here, now it's time
to grab the bath bomb out.
- Here we go, three, two. - Here we go, three, two.
Oh wait! - Three second like challenge!
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds,
You ready? Here we go.
- Three, two, one, done! - Three, two, one, done!
- You ready, three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- Oh man! - Oh what?
(slow motion zooming sound)
(water splashing) - Look at that!
- [Devan] Did you hear the sound?
- I know, it was like whomp-whomp!
Dude, it's not dissolving the bath bomb at all,
look at this!
The bath bomb is untouched!
- Whoa! I'm gonna add some coloring to this dough here.
- Unfortunately, these are not edible, so right now
it's time for me to make a DIY edible bath bomb
that'll hopefully react in the exact same way.
- All right, well as you do that, I'm gonna add
a lot more food coloring.
- [Collins] we'll get some dry ice here, do not
try this at home, I'm gonna drop it in like this,
gonna add in a whole bunch of berries right now like that!
- [Devan] Wait, why?
- [Collins] I'm adding berries because I have to
get a little bit of extra color for the lead tip of
my pencil right here, so here we go gonna add all those in.
I've got a whole bunch of frozen berries
- Nice! - and you know what time
it is, right, smashing time!
- It is! And you know what time it is for me?
To make the inside felt bit of the pen!
- Wait, what is this?
- I'm gonna pour it in and it's gonna do stuff!
- What a great description!
- There's a reaction to it. - Now, one to 10, where we at?
- Nuts!
- That's not even on the scale!
Now, before you drop that in, Devan, we gotta add
a little bit of magic to it.
- Oh okay. - So, here we go.
Bruh, like this! - Whoa!
- All right here we go, three, two, one, ah!
(blasting sound)
Okay, there we go! - Okay.
Three, two, one, ah! - Three, two, one, ah!
- You got it all over me! - Yes!
- You got it on me, bro! - I think I did it.
Well, I just need to stir it up a little bit.
- All right, well you know as you're doing that,
it's time for me to smash some berries, here we go.
- Three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- Oh! - Oh!
I think that works.
- I think so, finally got all the pomegranate juice,
now I gotta add this agar agar.
- All right, well as you do that,
I'm moving over your little triangle
of Illuminati-ness over here. (mysterious chiming sound)
We gotta really move that over.
Here we go, gonna flip it over,
make sure I don't spill any of it.
And here's the-- - You got a pan, I got a pan.
- Pan bros! - Yeah!
- You want some pans, we got some pans!
- All here we go, gonna take this, we're gonna flip
it over, and see if I can not spill any of it.
Here we go, three, two, one, yay!
On the count of three, I'm gonna lift this up
and this is a hack to make sure you get beautiful
colored dough every single time.
Three, two, one! - Two, one!
- Yay, whoa! - Whoa, man!
- That turned murky!
You know what, if I just mix all this together,
it'll turn back into normal lead color,
and then I won't have a colored pencil.
- [Devan] Well, I just gotta add this in here,
let it heat up, and then let it sit.
[smooth piano music]
- I've got some compressed air and now it's time
to freeze some bananas!
- [Devan] Yup, I've got my agar agar and now it's time
to roll it up, this looks delicious!
- [Collins] That's the inner lining for your Sharpie?
- [Devan] Yeah!
- [Collins] Life hack, always peel your bananas
from the bottom, this is for another layer of my pencil.
Yeet! - Yes, I think I got it!
All right, now this is definitely a life hack!
- All right, the bananas are right over here
- Whoa! - So, here we go,
it is time to freeze them up. - Okay, all right, hold up.
What, what, what? - Redemption yeet!
Yeet! - Whoa, that was close!
- [Devan] It's payback for how many times this thing
has been hit by you.
- Since when are you on this dude's team and
not my team?
All right, time to freeze some bananas, here we go.
- Three, two, one! - Let's see them go
like this here. - All right,
well I have to make another batch
of this, cause this isn't long enough, what?
I'm making another batch, by the way.
- [Collins] I feel like a mad scientist over
here, man, just frosting bananas.
(laughing) You never know!
To make our giant edible Sharpie and pencil,
I think we got everything we need.
So now, let's put it all together.
We finished up the edible
marker and pencil. - Yup!
- Here is the big reveal!
Three, two! - Three, two!
- Oh and this video is sponsored by the makers of
Invisalign Clear Aligners, and we are so excited
because we both use Invisalign Clear Aligners
every single day.
- And you probably couldn't tell, but we're both
wearing ours right now!
- We've seen an amazing transformation in our smiles
and this is crazy, but the Invisalign brand
is giving away five free treatments to you.
Our Keyper Squad, so keep watching
to find out how you can win that
and a video call (victorious tune)
with Devan and I!
- Three, two, one, ta-da! - three, two, one, ta-da!
- Bro! - Look at these, bro!
- [Devan] I know!
- [Collins] Unbelievable, but the real question,
will they write and how will they taste?
And we'll be testing it and eating them
at the end of the video!
Rocket launch test!
- Whoa, man! - Whoa, dude!
- You've challenged us to make edible rocketships
that will literally fly!
[excited yelling]
As you can tell here, I have a mini bottle rocket
basically gonna add in a whole bunch of baking soda,
cork it, turn it upside down, and we're gonna see
how high it flies up, so do not try this at home!
Putting the baking soda in, you ready?
Three, two, one, let's get all the baking soda in!
- Is it capped? (excited yelling)
- Four, three, two!
No!
(laughing)
Are you all right?
It flew off and hit Devan! - Man down!
- Man down! - Holy cow I'm sorry.
Yeah Devan's done, man. - Oh!
- I gotta say though. - My stomach!
- In all fairness, it was you who flipped it over.
- [Devan] I failed us, Collins!
- [Collins] You did, dude, I think we've gonna have to
try that again.
Devan, are you prepared to do the flip?
- I am ready, Are you ready?
- [Collins] Yeah, I'm gonna do it tightly, dude.
Three, two, one, go, go, go, go, go!
(rocket whooshing) (triumphant cheering)
- Yes! - That's crazy!
- Dude, nice! Dude look there
it flew right up and left the cork!
- [Devan] Look at that! I don't know why I should
be so excited 'cause that's your rocket and not mine.
- Exactly! I think that that's a pretty strong case that
mine is going to work!
- My rocket fuel, I have big block of wax and honey.
Ooh, look at this!
- [Collins] Very bizarre!
But I've got some eggs right here, some hot oil,
do not try this at home!
- Oh! - Oh!
- [Collins] Look at that!
- [Devan] Whoa, holy cow!
- But this is the insulation on
the inside of my rocket, to be honest,
I'm actually really surprised this life hack worked!
- Gonna extract some of the honey here.
- [Collins] I don't think it's gonna work, Devan.
You've gotten like 0.00% honey.
- That did not work, yeet!
- For a yeet, Devan, you didn't quite achieve
a lot of distance.
- I didn't fully commit, you know?
- Yeah, well see, when you yeet, you gotta fully commit!
Yeet! - All right, now I gotta
get this chunk into the inside of this.
All right, I've gotta say, I really
hope this turns out to be a life hack!
- Yo! - Yo!
- [Collins] Fluffy eggs!
- [Devan] It's like a balloon egg!
- Oh! - There you go!
Oh, oh, oh, that smell! - Yeah I gotta pop it.
- What you don't like the smell of eggs?
- No, I don't!
- [Collins] I'm just gonna kinda start
to just pull them apart.
This is gonna be the perfect insulation for my rocket!
We've got some liquid nitrogen
and now it's time to make a little bit more insulation
for my rocket, gonna add in some dots,
so let's see how this goes.
Ready, three, two, one! - Two, one, whoa, whoa!
That's too much, I'm guessing?
- I think I was supposed to like little driplets,
little drops, and I kinda wanna ham.
I wanna Ham FM radio on it, so let's uh.
(sting percussion)
All right, should we open it up a little bit?
- What? - I don't know.
- What was that joke? (laughing)
Was that supposed to be a joke?
- [Collins] Okay, it looks like the life-hack
might've worked, it's very fragile, so let's,
Oh! - Oh!
- [Devan] That is really cool.
- [Collins] Look at that!
It's like a Christmas wreath!
- [Devan] It's like a bagel!
- Can I hold it, without?
Ah, oh man! - Ah, oh boy!
- Yeah, that definitely, in hindsight,
it was too fragile for me to hold it.
I really doubt that's what you're supposed to do.
- Exactly, let's see if I just crush it,
let's see like this.
- Oh! - Oh!
- [Devan] That is really cool.
Now's the time to find out
if my technique actually worked.
Three, two, one, yeah! (triumphant tune)
It separated it, look at it.
- Not as much as just buying
a regular thing of honey. - Hey man!
- I'm just saying!
I'm gonna try to get a much thinner layer
going around, like this.
Ugh!
- [Devan] What?
- I made an oopsie!
- [Devan] Look at this, man.
I am definitely hoping that this honey works
as my rocket fuel.
- I call it the smack-a-whack-em technique.
You gotta smacka mack em (whacking noises)
and then you whack'n, whack'n, whack'n.
You know what, forget it.
Yayeet!
We're just gonna pour all that's in there like that.
- Look at this! - Bam!
- Whoa! - And let's see what happens.
- All right, what? (disastrous trumpet blast)
- What happened? - The bottle went in,
I dropped the bottle. - Was that on purpose?
This tofu thing was not the greatest idea.
I think there's a chance that they didn't
design this for honey.
All right, now I just gotta let this thing cook .
- I've got an anvil, some dry ice,
and now it's time to smash it, so here we go,
do not try this at home.
- Three, two, one! - Two, one!
- Oh, look at that! - Wow!
(crashing and breaking sound)
There ya go!
- That was perfect, look at it man!
It perfectly powderized! - That was crazy.
- As you can see these are cool bowl tricks.
Bam, like this and then, (swishing sound)
Bowl tricks. (swishing sounds)
Bowl! (metal clanging) - Are you still
on the bowl tricks?
- Ah, bowl tricks!
- That's what you get.
- Woo! - Now it's time to see
if this will turn into rocket fuel, you ready?
All right - Should I like get in, taking
cover or anything? - The goal is for this
to be able to propel a rocket
into space. - All right well I'm gonna
step back a little bit, so.
- Did you hear that, into space?
- Yeah I heard that - Yeah, yeah, or atmosphere.
- I don't believe him.
- Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
- Gaborg! - Go mix, mix, mix, mix!
- Did I get it, did I do it?
- I don't know is it going anywhere?
- Aey! - Okay well that.
- Look at that! - Devan!
That will not propel a rocket anywhere bro!
- I know.
- [Collins] That's not even gonna get it off the ground!
- [Devan] I think I messed up.
- But in the meantime,
time for me to add this dry ice in.
So here we go. - Yes.
- It's time for me to drop some of this in here
and this is gonna be able to create
a cryofreeze mixture in here so here we go.
Three, two, one. - Okay.
- Oh, yeah! - Oh, man!
Well now it's time to drop in my vermicelli noodles!
- All right well here we go - Look at this!
- Go for it, three, two, one, go for it!
Yo! - Yes!
Dude this is gonna be perfect to create
the protective layer for my rocket.
Oh, it is overflowing!
- That's good it's like a magic trick bro,
the way it just like puffs up! - I know.
- It never gets old.
- All right, now it's time to coat the cacti.
- Oh, what was that? - Oh, look at that!
This is gonna be the body of my rocket.
- All right as you you coat that, I've got a shovel here,
time to slice off the top of the jackfruit.
Urg. (thumping sound)
Oh man! - Oh.
Look at this!
- [Collins] That's super crazy bro!
- [Devan] Whoa dude that's so satisfying.
- Three, two, one.
Oh my gosh! - Wow!
That was close, that was really close.
- There we go bam, all right one side chopped off.
You know what man, I'm actually going for more off
a "Star Wars" ship design for mine.
- [Devan] All right now it's time to reinforce
the outside with this indestructible ramen noodle mix.
- Is that the fuselage of your rocket?
- It is Collins.
- [Collins] Those noodles don't look too aerodynamic
I gotta say.
- [Devan] They won't be yet, but they will be
when they're in the air.
- Now it's time to put the rockets all together
so first of all I'm gonna add my stuffing here.
Oh these eggs feel weird what?
- This turned out great!
- I know you really nailed it on that one, so here we go,
the egg is gonna drop, what? - Dude you gotta look at this.
This is mushroom foam.
- [Collins] No way, 'cause off camera Devan blended up
a ton of mushrooms and can't believe
this is what it came into! - I know right!
- I'm gonna add the eggs and they've definitely discolored
a bit which is kinda gross but luckily they're fluffy
so this is gonna be the insulation
for the inside of the rocket.
Next I'm gonna pick up some of these frozen dots
and just sprinkle em in like this.
- We got a ton of work to do, I got some painting on mine,
I gotta figure out how to attach these to this.
- I'm gonna get iceable coating to the outside of it
to make it smooth and probably have to reshape it
a whole bunch and yeah, it's gonna be a lotta work.
We got the edible rocket and these things turned out
absolutely incredible. - I know right.
- I was kinda worried there for a moment,
I didn't know if they'll be able to turn out
but the real question is not how they'll taste
but will they actually fly?
So here's the reveal.
Three, two. - Three two.
- Oh it's finally time to share how you can enter
for a chance to win free Invisalign treatment
and for us Invisalign aligners are really
the ultimate life hack because it improves your smile
without disrupting your life, like you can literally
eat whatever you want without having to worry about
the hassle of metal wires and brackets.
- Yeah and I've actually been using Invisalign aligners
for two years and you probably didn't know this
but I was always a little bit insecure
about my smile before.
So I did a ton of research and found that
the Invisalign brand has the most advanced
clear aligner system in the world by far.
And they've transformed over seven million people's smiles.
- And when it comes to our smiles and yours
we only wanna give you the best,
which is why we are so hyped that the Invisalign brand
is giving away free treatments to five lucky Keypers
and we'll be announcing the rules to enter very soon
on our Instagram.
- But in the meantime, we wanna make sure
that these five free treatments go to the Keypers
that really, really want them.
- So click the top link in the description
and fill out the smile quiz right now and as an added bonus
we are calling one lucky Keyper, who filled out
the entire smile quiz and then send us a screen shot
of this confirmation page right here and again,
we wanna see which Keypers really want
the free Invisalign treatment and the video call
with Devan and I.
So sign up for the smile quiz right now
and let's see how these rockets look.
Three, two, one, ta-da! - Three, two, one, ta-da!
- What on earth? - Wow!
- We got the edible rockets and now it's finally time
to test to see if they can actually fly in the air
and reach the moon. - Oh boy.
- Yeah, reach the moon.
- That is the goal. - Exactly.
- If it doesn't reach the moon
it is a massive failure. - Exactly.
- We're setting the bar really high.
- Can you admire this custom yeet blaster here?
- Yeah Devon was doing a lot of research
on how we could launch these rockets.
And Devon feels this will be the best way to do it
With how heavy this thing is,
if this gets any flight whatsoever,
if it just gets of the ground one inch, I will be happy.
Which rocket should we launch first Devan.
- You know I think let's launch mine.
- Devan your pretzel's a little off
which means it's gonna traject that way,
it's not gonna go straight up, it's gonna be like that.
The more the moment comes, - yes.
- The less confident I am that these
are actually gonna be able to fly Devan.
- The more confident I am though,
this looks amazing - What, I don't know!
It looks pretty professional compared to mine
but on its own it looks pretty janky man.
- What are you talking about bro?
- On a scale from one to 10. - Yes.
- How confident are you, I want you
to put down your prediction right now.
10, meaning it's gonna reach the moon.
One meaning it will not achieve lift-off
and potentially combust.
I'm about a nine.
- What? - Yes.
- I gotta give it a four man, I'm not that optimistic.
I'm looking at it. - Yours is a four.
- No mine is not man.
- Yours is a four - It's squat
it is stout. - If I've ever seen one.
- And it is ready to make some action upwards bro.
- Are you kidding me?
- I am not kidding.
- All right now it's time to see this thing fly.
- But here's my major concern Devon.
My concern is that it actually flies, it goes
straight up in the air. - Exactly!
- And lands on my rocket.
- What are you kidding me? - Which would not be good.
So here's the thing.
- The chances of that are so low.
- It doesn't matter Devon, I will not allow your rocket
to destroy mine so I'm gonna have to protect my baby.
- All right. - So I'm just gonna go
over here. - Well here we go
and remember do not try this at home.
- Oh my gosh are you ready?
- Here we go!
- But before we launch the rocket
it's time to see how the Sharpie and pencil taste.
What do you think we're gonna go with first?
We go with mine first or yours first?
- [Devan] Let's eat yours first.
- All right so here we go, let's test it out
and see how it tastes, here we go.
Three, two, one - Three, two, one.
- Wah.
- Is it good?
(smacking lips)
- One moment. (laughing)
- [Devan] My arms are getting tired.
- Yeah here we go, - here we go, there we go
- yourself under it. - There we go, okay.
- [Collins] Time to eat the tip of my pencil.
All right here we go three, two, one just gonna get
a slice down like this. - Yeah okay.
- All right bam! - Oh wow!
- [Collins] I'm gonna go for this piece here.
- I like the blue one, I'm going for it.
- Now it's time to see how this tastes.
There we go, three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
(upbeat music)
- Hmm, hmm, mm!
- You did a good one!
- Wow. - This is amazing!
You did a really good job.
- Oh! - Yeah!
- Wow!
- That was really, really good.
- It got the whole banana. (laughing)
It's time to see if yours even holds a candle.
- The main event.
- What on here is edible?
- The innards! - I'm looking at it.
- Collins the innards.
- That's it? - All right, here we go
Three, two, one.
(popping sound) Yup, okay. - Just ripped it off?
What on earth? - I know right!
So I'm gonna go in with these tweezers here.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait! - What?
- That's like, I feel you're gonna pop
a membrane or something in there.
- Yep, pretty much!
It's the edible ink of the marker.
I'm gonna put these tweezers in here
and just hopefully pop the thing.
- Go for it! - I'm trying!
(surprised trumpet blast)
No, no, no, no - Holy cow!
- No catch it, catch it! - I'm catching, I'm catching!
- Yes, it's edible! - Lift it up, lift it up!
- Okay, okay, okay. - That was.
I have an idea Devon - Whoa, whoa!
- I know how we can get more out of it
Here we go. - No, no, no
Why here we go, yeah, yeah, - No, no!
- Yeah, yeah! - Oh, Oh, no, no, no!
- There we go that's pretty awesome!
- Oh no I'm trying to catch it.
- Oh yeah you're doing a good job of catching it Devon
I believe in you.
- Dude put it down!
I'll try to hold this side of the marker, here we go.
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Go for it, urg!
Oh man! - Yeah!
- Is it? - Yup, yup, that's it.
- What?
- It's the pomegranate agar agar that I made.
- I'm gonna dump this out real quick,
here we go, watch. - Oh yeah, yup, yup, yup.
- Oh! - Oh man!
- [Collins] You put paper towel in there?
- I did, I did.
- What to insulate it?
- Exactly.
- All right here we go.
Let's just unroll this - Oh, oh, oh, unroll it.
- Here we go, three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- Ha!
- Whoa!
A second bite for approval.
- Redemption bro, I think that this balances out
the badness of this mam.
- Devan, think about--
Sorry.
Remember, this deliciousness we both thoroughly enjoyed.
Remember the reactions we had man.
- Yeah. - It was like, it was a lot.
- My memory's fading a little bit though.
- Yes I guess we'll just kind of like drink it?
- Yeah! - You drink it.
- It's ink dude. - All right.
- It's not like some dough stuff.
- Three, two. - Three, two.
- Oh and remember the Invisalign brand is giving away
five free treatments to you, our Keyper squad
so stay tuned for the giveaway rules
and if you want to win a video call with Devan and I,
go fill out the smile quiz right now and then send us
a screenshot of this confirmation page
once you've completed it, so literally right now,
- Right now. - Go fill out the smile quiz,
click the top link in the description
and let's see how this stuff tastes.
Three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
(upbeat music)
[Devan] Mm, mm.
(gagging) Mm, mm.
- Arg! (fist hitting metal)
Arg! - Mm-mm, mm-mm.
- Oh man! - Mm-mm, mm-mm.
- All right that's enough eating,
it's time to test the rocket.
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
(hissing sound)
- [All] Oh! (thump)
(laughing) - Man!
Oh and it
explodes the bottle. - I mean, what is this?
- I couldn't make it work with all edible elements
so the coating is all edible but the inside unfortunately
is a plastic bottle.
- Are you kidding me this looks like styrofoam bro.
- And I used some styrofoam, so.
- What? - Dude you have
a bit of a plastic base.
- Yeah just a plastic base, that's not gonna--
- Yeah that's like essentially what I did.
(laughing)
It's not my proudest moment all right,
I just wanted it to work.
It even got like a foot of air.
- I gave her a four, that was way too generous bro
that was like a two man.
- Yeah I agree, that was really, really bad.
- And I gotta say I think it was some bad luck
'cause it flew right up and down onto the pipe,
which is like the worst place
it could have possibly fallen onto.
- Yeah, yeah, but at least it's edible.
After seeing how mine went,
I don't have a lot of faith in yours.
- Are you kidding? - Look I just don't
have a lot of faith.
- More weight means more trajectory Devon.
- Yes. - So here we go.
Next up, we gotta place it down over here.
- What are you doing? - Here we go I gotta find
the right point here.
- Your hands are all weird!
- See the thing is Devan, I'm more focused on the result,
not so much focused on my hand grip position, here we go!
- Did you get it, did you actually get it?
- What does it look like?
- I don't know.
- Yes, I got it - I don't know the inner
workings of yours. - There we go that's uh.
- Are you sure that's high enough?
'cause the other thingy.
- Oh yeah, yeah, I guess it--
(disastrous trumpet blast)
- Oh, it went down - What?
- Okay well I'm trying, I'm doing my best.
I'll figure all this out before it goes
but here's the question Devon.
Scale one and 10, what do you think my rocket's
gonna be bale to achieve?
- After seeing mine, I don't think
I can go above a one, - What?
- So a zero.
- What, come on!
- Yeah I mean I just had to be honest.
- Honestly, I think I can get a three.
- One.
- Which would be a win, 'cause yours got a two.
- I only need three to win. - Wait, wait, wait.
Who actually set the two. - Me.
- So I set this one then.
- Okay fine, yes. - You ready?
- I think it's gonna be below a two.
- See the thing is you know it's not fair when the judge
is already prejudging your work before it's even happened.
The one thing I will say, I'm a little bit insecure about
is the lack of a point on my rocket.
As you can tell, I've ruined the cone.
- Hey but it was all in good fun because we ate it.
- Yeah but see the thing is, it's now no longer aerodynamic
and it might capture extra air instead of being able
to slice through it. - Uh huh,
well it served a greater purpose.
- Exactly - It made me full.
- And it tasted good.
So uh. - Well not really.
- See the judge is already biased man he doesn't look
at my apple to begin with.
This is not fair.
Comment down below on a scale of one to 10,
how high you think this rocket will be able to go.
A 10! - Two.
So uh, less than a two, a one.
- I wanna see a lot of 10's in the comments guys,
comment a lot of 10's so I know you're with me.
So lets uh. - It's not gonna work.
Let's see how it goes.
All right here we go man,
- Do it! - I can hear it sizzling,
it bodes not good! - It's making sounds.
- All right here we go you ready?
Get behind me dude, get back - Yeah.
- over here, all right here we go.
And you know why yours failed Devon,
'cause you forgot to reet.
- Oh man! - So for mine,
I'm gonna give it the reet, here we go.
- Three, two, one! - Two, one!
- Reet! - Reet!
- Oh!
- I gotta catch it, I gotta get it.
- Dude, yours didn't go anywhere!
- What do you mean that this, this went to the moon.
- I'm sorry Collins, was that a bottle?
- Yeah well you know I had to put something in the middle
so it didn't blow up.
- Was this a bottle?
- It was!
- Did you cheat too?
- Just like you, I realized there was no way
this was actually gonna be able to fly
so we needed one inedible part so I chose a bottle,
I did not also go for styrofoam.
- That is hilarious. - Like you did
- You should also get points removed Devon.
You did a styrofoam, mine was all edible
besides with the bottle okay.
- I can't believe we both thought
we would get away with this.
- I know. - The only thing
that flew out was the bottle,
the rest of the thing didn't even fly.
- And the apple!
Here's the thing Devon, I wanna see how difficult
it would be to make this actually fly.
- All right. - I'm just gonna yeet it,
in this case give it a reet.
So I guess I'm just gonna throw it up in the air.
Three, two, one! - Three, two, one!
- Yareet!
- Uh-oh.
- Uh-oh! - Uh-oh!
- Oh! - Oh!
- Well I gotta say those definitely did not work
as well as we would've hoped. - No.
- And if you want to see the video click right over here,
five seconds here we go.
- Five, four, three, - Five, four, three,
- two, one, done. - two, one, done.
Love you, bye!