- What's up, it's Collins Key and welcome--
- Wait, dude why am I in it don't I have to
start from out there? - Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
You should get out for a second.
- Okay.
What's up it's Collins Key and welcome
to the Thursday vlog and today I have a special guest.
You have no idea who it could possibly be, so uh
without further ado, Devin!
- Heyyy what's up? - I wasn't ready
Okay, heyyy!
Okay now he's here bro I just looked like
an idiot there for like a second.
- I know (laughing) - Oh my gosh
We did not coordinate that and today we are
going to be doing an Ask the Key Bros cuz you guys
had a ton of questions you wanna ask us,
so you guys took to Twitter,
you used the hashtag Ask the Key Bros
and we actually trended worldwide.
I think let's just jump into these questions
what do you think Devin? - I'm ready.
- No I don't care what you think,
we're jumpin' in on these questions, let's go.
First question, what color underwear are you wearing?
Okay we're going zero to a hundred real quick.
And what are you wearin'? - Black underwear
- I'm wearin' black underwear as well.
Who has the longer left ear?
Let's find out, I think we're goin' from the bottom
the voluptuous lobe to the tippity top of the elf ear
and yours are three inches.
From the bottom of the slightly voluptuous lobe
- Bro
- Not quite as voluptuous as mine
- Yeah, no.
- And he is at two and a half inches.
- Alright so Devin is the winner,
I guess you call the winner
he is the winner of the Left Ear Challenge!
- Do you have a crush on someone right now?
Yes I do, do you? - No, I do not.
- Really? (Laughing)
What do you think about Justin Bieber?
What do you mean?
Who is better at the Chubby Bunny challenge?
Well, let's find out.
So this is the Chubby Bunny challenge
and we have to figure out how many of these
we can fit in our-- okay.
- Chubby bunny! - Chubby bunny.
- Chubby bunny. - Chubby bunny.
- Chubby bunny. (laughing)
- Chu'y bunny. - Chubby bunny.
(fastforwarding noise)
- Chubby bunny. - Chu'y bu'y.
- Chubby bunny.
- Chu'y ...
(laughing)
- Have you ever told Devin any of your magic secrets?
Okay Devin is the only person in the entire world
who knows every single one of my secrets for
every single magic trick I've ever done, ever.
- Do you guys wanna know how he did it?
- No, dude chill, chill! - Full list of all--
- No, no, no!
Boxers or briefs?
Oh gosh, briefs - Briefs definitely
I don't like boxers.
They're like another pair of shorts under your,
well I don't wear shorts, but under your pants.
- Well I like pull up my pants and when that happens
the boxers just go with it, so
- It's like you have a giant cloud sitting
around your waist region.
Show us the most embarrassing pictures
you have of each other so here's Devin's picture, boom.
That's it right there - And here's Collin's!
- Oh, there it is, enjoy.
- I dare you guys to hug each other right now
[Both] Eyyy!
- Mmm yes - Yes, mmm.
- Good quality hug - Such a beautiful, hey!
- Ohh okay we're back in it - Where you goin' bro?
- Help me!!!
Help me!!!
Unexpected! (laughing)
- You got the edge!
The rim! - The rim (laughing)
- Which one of you takes longest to get ready?
Hmm, I don't know. - I don't know on that one, hm
- Maybe this guy, I don't know - I guess we'll never know.
- What is nine plus ten?
- Twenty one - Nineteen, dude it's nineteen
I almost said tw-- - He almost said twenty one
Who can run and eat the fastest at the same time?
- How am I supposed to know this?
- We're about to do it right now so let's find out.
Let the banana games begin!
(electronic music)
(yelping)
(victorious cry)
(laughing)
(snorting)
- Oh! - Das whip!
(laughing)
(spitting)
- What's your favorite dinosaur?
I know for me its the bambiraptor, what's yours?
- Uh, for me it's the tricerabronchosaurus t-rex
(laughing)
- He named like three of 'em.
Have you ever liked the same girl?
- The answer to that is a big whopping yes, many times
- Many times
Do you annoy each other? - Ohh dude chill!
Okay the answer to this one is yes
and I know just how to push Devin's buttons.
Like for instance, if I were to say like if we're in an
argument or something and if I'm like,
"Devin, are you getting mad right now? Devin are you angry?
"Are you feeling upset right now?"
- When I'm obviously not angry
- And it just like makes him angry
- What is the best impression of each other?
- I'll let you go first, ladies first.
- Oh gosh... - Impersonate me, bro
- Impersonate me, bro.
Should I laugh like you?
- Haha! Ah hahaha!
(high pitched laughing)
- That is not at all how I laugh, Devin.
- What's up guys, it is Collins Key and
welcome to the Thursday vlog.
- Alright, I have to say that's kinda spot on
- I don't, I mean I don't, shoot it off?!
When have I ever said it, "Let's shoot it off?"
I have never used that in any of my videos!
(laughing) Who said "Let's shoot it off?"
Whaaaat, seriously?
- A supreme marksman would say that.
(laughing)
- Whaaat??
What???
That makes... (laughing)
Okay. (laughing)
- See you do kinda laugh like that!
- I don't-- - Hahahaha (impersonating)
- On the real.
- On the real, dude?? (laughing)
You never say any of these things in real life ever.
I have never heard you say "On the real",
"let's shoot it off", who are you dude?
You've changed! (laughing)
I literally, I'm crying right now.
- Ready for this one?
That was a hoot and a half
No?
(laughing)
- Whaaat?!
- Dude okay, you're done alright now it's my turn
to impersonate Devin - Alright.
Featuring a chair now. - What?!?!
- I'm sorry, I'm crying like Collins when I laugh
- Okay that is a really good impersonation
- This is probably the best impersonation I could do.
- I'm Devin Key, I never smile in my selfies
- That was pretty accurate, actually.
- Yeah that's Devin right there,
there should be one more thing.
Hey so basically I'm really, no (laughing)
That's not at all like you, sorry.
Are we both single?
- And - Yo
(laughing) [Both] Yeah.
- Pretty much yeah, we're very single.
Netflix and chill by ourselves, eh!
Not like with each other, but like in separate
nevermind, let's move on.
What's up with your sleeping habits?
(snoring)
Can you say something in French?
French toast, okay there we go.
This question is a personal favorite of mine
Who can peel and orange the fastest?
I think it was supposed to be 'and orange' the fastest,
but I like that you said 'and orange' the fastest
so let's have a little competition right now.
I have a different strategy. (laughing)
Okay that did not work.
- Oh god, ahh
Ants are gonna love this area. - Yep okay great there we go
and, peeled!
That's a very unconventional peeling.
I'm gonna go more traditional now.
- Hey!
- This was much more effective, I don't know
why I didn't do this the first time.
- Ugh. - Smack cam
I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win!
- I think you are, I think you are!
No!
- I peeled a grapefruit the fastest.
(grunting)
- Obviously I am the better magician here, right?
(gasping)
What, he's gone that's right I'm the best magician here.
No!
Put ketchup in your hands and then slap each other.
Oh my god dude you have, ah!
Got him!
- Oh, you actually got it this time!
- I know (laughing)
and now it's time for the ketchup cam!
Really gotta load him up.
Alright there we go.
Okay, okay, okay, okay eh, what are you doing?
(spitting noise)
- Ohhhhh god!
I can't hear, I can't hear anything!
- Yeahhh! - Oh my god
- Dude chill, chill, chill chill okay alright cool!
Can you lift up the ref--RIGERATOR!
(laughing) Yeah you got me good.
You got me really good, that was a direct hit!
Battleship down, the answer is no.
- I think --
Like do you really think that I can lift up the refrige?
Oh god, it hurt I'm crying it hurt.
- Especially not now
- Yeah no I can't lift up a refrigerator.
- Do you know how hard it is to laugh and lift something?
(laughing)
When was the last time you and your brother wore shorts?
[Both] Never, we've actually never worn shorts, ever.
- Ever.
- Can you make this your last question?
OW dude you missed it and yes, that is it
for this week's Thursday vlog, so if you guys
enjoyed this video please share with your friends
right now and also give me the big thumbs up.
Yeah, oh... DUDE!
Also comment down below
- Eyyy!
Some other questions that you guys have for us.
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel
there are new videos coming out each and
every single Thursday and make sure you guys go
check out and follow Devin on all his social media sites.
All the links are down below so you should go do it
and yeah - Do it, do it!
But yeah make sure you turn on all of his notifications
and yeah, show him some love.
And the Keyper of the Week is Bryan Johnson
so shout out to you Bryan you are hands down
one of the most active Keyper's of all time,
Bryan you are such a huge, huge part of our Keyper family
and if you wanna the Keyper of the week, all that you
have to do is be super active on all my different platforms,
make sure you have my Instagram notifications,
Twitter notifications on, YouTube notifications on,
liking, commenting, sharing, the more active you are,
the better chance you have of being featured
as a Keyper of the Week, but again congratulations Bryan
you are the Keyper of the Week, I love you bro.
Thank you for watching and I'll see you
guys again next week, bye.
Alright, cool good video, good video.