- What's up, it's Collins Key, and for today's video,
I have something very special planned.
(Collins whooshing)
(Jessie snapping)
- Whoa!
Yo, guys this is crazy.
I've never actually been teleported to someone else's video
for a collab, 'cause as you guys can tell,
this is not my background, right here.
- Very Jessie Paege.
- This is my friend Jessie.
So, first of all, if you guys haven't already subscribed
to her channel, go do that right now.
We put her links down in the description.
And also, we did a video over on her channel.
We're gonna put the link right over there.
So, after this video, go check that out.
But for today's video, since it's that time of year,
it's getting close to back to school, we are doing guys
versus girls back to school challenge.
Whoever wins the majority of the rounds,
that person wins this challenge.
They get to make the loser do something very embarrassing
on their SnapChat.
We're gonna have the video of that at the end of this,
so make sure you guys stick around to the very end.
- Oh, my gosh, really?
I'm scared.
(both laughing)
Squad, all right.
We are going to kill the like button and just, you know.
- Yeah, annihilate it.
The way she said it was so soft and gentle, like,
we're gonna kill the like button.
- Kill it.
- While I'm like, "Yo, we're gonna go at this like button!"
No, yeah.
But if you guys want us to do a messy challenge video
together, let us know by liking this video,
and if this video gets enough thumbs up,
then we will do a video where we get super, super,
have you ever done a messy video before?
- No, but I will ruin the pink hair,
and that's saying a lot, 'cause this is my everything.
- Oh, my god.
And I also wanted to let you guys know,
I'm doin' a giveaway, and we're actually doing
a giveaway together, so for my channel, right now,
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So, if you guys wanna win a MacBook, all you have
to do is like this video, comment down below
what's you favorite video I've ever posted,
and you must be subscribed to the channel.
But to enter the giveaway that we are both doing together,
we are giving a way an Instax Mini 8.
This is a Polaroid camera.
We're giving away this Polaroid camera,
and also we're giving away Polaroid film, as well.
The winner not only will get the camera, the Polaroids,
but also some signed Polaroids of just us.
- Our faces. - Chillin', our faces.
See, if you guys wanna enter into that,
all you have to do is just follow us on Twitter,
Instagram and SnapChat.
Our Snap codes are right over here on the screen.
I'm gonna put all of our links down
in the description below.
That's all you have to do to enter into this giveaway.
And now, without any further ado,
let's jump in, and this is the boys versus girls
back to school challenge.
I'mma juggle these things to start this off,
'cause we need energy.
- Oh, my gosh, you're so good.
- Let's get this started.
Round number one, a friend of ours put a whole bunch
of random stuff in these backpacks,
and hidden amongst them are three things
that we have to find.
Scissors, a pencil sharpener, and a glue stick,
and whoever can find all these items first,
they win round one.
Three, two, one, go!
I shouldn't a zipped them closed, okay here we go.
- Hey, hey, hey!
(Jessie clapping and laughing)
- What?
Yo, I'm not gonna say my friend rigged this
or anything, but my friend has rigged this.
What just happened?
- Actually, I have a secret power,
no I'm kidding.
- Hey, I'll take the loss.
I'll take it, I lose round one, so.
- Sorry.
- Congratulations, you win round one.
And a fun thing to add is that every round you win,
you get to put on one of these apple stickers.
'Cause, I guess, you give a teacher apples.
- If only I was healthy enough to eat one of these.
(Collins laughing)
- So, you get your first official apple sticker.
Awe, so cute.
That is round number one.
Let me actually find my freaking pencil sharpener now.
It's got be here somewhere.
Oh, there we go, at the bottom of all the pen's
the sharpener.
So, for round, we've made such a mess.
For round number two, whoever can sharpen their pencil
the most in 30 seconds, they win that round, so.
Set timer for 30--
- [Siri] What was that again?
- I didn't even start yet.
Set timer for 30 seconds.
- [Siri] Okay, your timer is set--
- Oh, gee, it's going.
(Jessie yells)
I need to figure out a system for this.
- Oh, gees.
- I feel like I'm breaking mine, okay.
Whoo.
Oh, we only have 10 seconds left.
This like a wrist workout, man, ow.
Three, two, one, and stop.
(Jessie laughing)
Okay, what happened?
(both laughing)
I think it's kinda clear who won this,
no there's no technical difficulty.
- Me, obviously, yeah.
This is clearly a great, oh gosh, help me.
(Jessie laughing)
- So now we are tied, and now I get my very own
apple sticker, and I'm going for the--
- Put it on your cheek.
- For you.
I don't know if I can do it.
Upon further reconsideration, I don't think,
it doesn't work for me.
So, I'm gonna be baller with it.
- Wear it like a man.
- Come at me, bro, come at me.
For round number three, we have to put as many loose
leaf papers in these paper protectors as possible
in 45 seconds.
Whoever can do that wins round three
and will take the lead, so here we go.
Hey, Siri, put 45 seconds on the clock for me,
will ya, fam.
- [Siri] Okay, I found this on the web
for put 45 seconds on the clock for me will ya fam.
- [Both] Will ya fam.
- Will ya fam, no. - Isn't that...
- Okay, let me do it again.
Hey, Siri--
- [Siri] Sorry Collins, I didn't get that.
- Oh, shady.
Hey, Siri, 45 seconds on the clock.
Do it.
- [Siri] 22.5.
(Collins laughing)
- Hey, Siri, 45 second timer.
- [Siri] Done, I love a good countdown.
- All right, let's go, let's go.
- Oh, my gosh.
I feel like I'm gonna fail at this miserably.
- It's stressful to do.
I'm assuming you don't do a lot of--
- In, in!
Okay, there we go, boom, one.
- Oh, wait, you have to go one in each?
- Yeah, one in each.
- Oh.
- Oh, you're trying to put 'em all.
Oh, I see how it is.
Where's the opening of this, there we go.
- Okay, I'm not winning this at all.
- Here we go.
(Collins panting)
I need one more!
- Wait, ah, where's the opening?
Okay.
(Collins exhaling)
Just go, no!
Kay, how many did you do?
- One.
- One, okay.
I got two.
So, I'll take round three.
I get one more apple.
That was the most stressful thing of all time.
Trying to get them open was so--
- Right?
It was like something about it was cringey.
Like something about putting it in there was like
eh, like nails on a chalkboard.
- Cringey is the best word to use to describe this.
I'm going green apple for this one, and I'm
gonna do matching, bam.
Round four, let's get it.
And we're going on to round number four,
and this one here involves locks, because you guys know
you have locks on your locker.
So, for this challenge, whoever can unlock their lock
the fastest wins.
So, here's what we're gonna do.
Locks on the table.
- Here, we'll mix it up first.
- Oh, okay, okay.
You good?
- We're all good.
- Hands on the table.
Here we go, three, hands on the table.
Two.
- Sorry, I had to flip my hair.
- Two, one, begin.
Um, it is--
- This is my workout for today.
- 14.
What was the last one?
Eight.
- Bam!
- No!
- Oh, yeah.
- That's 'cause--
- Wait, mine didn't even...
- You were homeschooled.
(Jessie laughing)
- Ho, ho!
We are tied now, going into round number five.
The tie-breaker round.
Whoever wins this round gets to have the loser do
something super embarrassing on SnapChat.
So, first of all, pick an apple.
- I wanna keep it consistent.
- Awe.
(Jessie mumbles)
This really is boys versus girls.
- Game time.
- Girls like, on the cheek, it's so cute.
I'm like, "Man patches with my apples."
All right, here we go.
This is the tie-breaker round,
and for this last one, we have to make a sandwich.
Fully complete the sandwich.
We don't have Ziploc bags, so we're gonna put it
in one of the page protectors.
And then, you have to seal it, oh why is there lettuce
in here?
(Jessie laughing)
And then you have to put it inside of your lunch box.
Zip it all the way up, and whoever does that first
wins the final round.
Loser has to do some embarrassing things on SnapChat.
We'll put the video of that at the end of this challenge.
- Oh, my god.
- Three, two, one, go!
But that tear, doe.
- Oh, I would do anything for the carbs.
- This is making me hungry, too, 'cause I haven't
eaten all day, yet.
- Oh, really?
- All right, there we go.
Tasteful amount of mustard, not too much.
- Um.
(Collins groans)
Whoa, my tomatoes.
(both laughing)
Just squeezing it?
There we go, bam, tomato.
Ah, what else do I need on there?
Lettuce, okay.
No, no.
So, I'm good, okay, here we go, boom.
- No, no, no, no.
- Yes.
- Ah, ah, ah!
He's missing cheese.
- No!
- And guess who has the cheese?
- No, give me the cheese.
Give me the cheese!
This is unfair, okay.
- That's my slice.
- Ah, no.
(Jessie laughing)
And you threw it so far, too.
All right, here we, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
I lost my tomato.
Bam, I won!
Yes!
- No, you have to zip it!
You gotta zip it!
- Wait you can't zip it.
- Yes, you can.
- Wait, zip, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait.
- Yes, whoo!
- No, that was not zipped up.
That was the exact same time.
- Wow.
Well, that went zero to 100 real quick.
So, I think.
- That was a tie.
- 'Cause that was a tie--
- Look what I did.
- We're both, for this, gonna do embarrassing things
on our SnapChat.
- You said you didn't eat all day.
Do you want this?
- I'm good.
I'm good.
So, right now, we're 'bout to do some embarrassing things
on our SnapChat.
But, yeah.
- Should we say what we're both gonna do?
- Oh, I tried the mustard, that was gross.
(Jessie laughing)
- I believe in mermaids!
And you should, too!
- If you haven't already added us on SnapChat,
you are missing out on fun things just like that.
So, make sure you guys go add us right now.
- This now on us embarrassing ourselves.
- Yeah, so go add us on SnapChat,
'cause you do not wanna miss that.
Make sure you guys go check out the video
that we did on her channel.
I'm gonna put the link right over there.
Also down in the description.
Subscribe to her.
Right now, I have to go teleport back
to my home, so bye!
(Collins snapping)
- Well, this is awkward.
Hi, welcome to Collins' channel,
and Jessie Paege is taking over, dun, dun, dun.
(high energy music)