- What's up?
it's Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now for today's video, before I go any further,
please welcome my little brother, Devan Key.
- [Both] Hey!
- What's up?
- Dude, how does it feel to be on my channel
for the very first time?
- I'm actually honored to be on this channel
for the very first time.
- This is Devin. - Thank you
so much for having me here.
- Making his YouTube debut.
- Yeah, this is my YouTube debut.
- Right now, he has never been
in any other YouTube videos before.
- Never been in a video ever.
I'm actually kind of nervous.
- You're a little bit nervous. - Not really.
- Well you should be nervous
because we are doing a challenge today
and we are doing the backwards word challenge.
And actually Devan, since this is your first time
on my channel, I'll let you do the honors
and describe the rules of this challenge.
- Okay, so basically we get a word
and we have to say it backwards.
This app will reverse that, so saying it forwards.
And whoever is the closest, wins.
- That was actually very good.
Wow. - Thank you.
- I'm impressed for-- (chuckles)
Let's try that again, take two.
For the first time on my channel,
Devan did a great job right there.
And now I'm also-- (laughing)
- Well this is the first time on.
- Yeah no, this really is the first time
he's on my channel. - Yeah.
- I'm also doing a big New Year's giveaway
where I'm giving away a MacBook, Instax camera, Go Pros.
So if you guys want to enter into that,
all you gotta do is give this video a thumbs up,
comment down below what your favorite video of mine is,
and also subscribe to this channel.
And then of course click the little video link
right up there.
You guys can check out all the rules, all the details,
'cause this giveaway is happening on YouTube,
on Twitter, and on Instagram.
Different prizes all across the board.
Without further ado, let's jump.
- [Both] Into the backwards word challenge.
♫ If you love pina coladas
♫ Dun dun
♫ When you're caught in the rain
- So we're gonna be starting it off easy
because this is Devan's first time ever
doing a YouTube challenge
and so we're gonna be starting off with the word banana.
So guests gets to go first.
- Ana-Na-ba.
- You can't redo it, you can't redo it.
Ana-na-buh.
(laughs) That one's probably gonna be wrong.
Alright, well let's play, you go first.
- [Phone] Huh-ba-nay-nay.
- Ba-nay-nay, it sounds like the nae-nae, ah-ba-nay-nay.
- [Phone] Huh-banana.
- Ahh, no! - Oooh, ooh.
Steph Curry with the words.
- [Phone] Huh-banana.
- This next one is ding ding ding, Drake.
- Do we have to add the ding ding ding in? (laughs)
Er-idged.
- Eder-dee.
(laughs)
- Dee.
- [Phone] Drake.
- Oh!
- [Phone] Nik-drake.
- Yeah.
- [Phone] Drake.
- Yeah yeah,
that was way closer. - A little closer.
Okay. - Nicely done, bro.
- Thank you. - Killin' it.
- Next one is peacock.
- Cocka-Peap.
(laughing)
- Cocka-Peep?
(laughs)
Cock-peep.
- You forgot the P at the beginning.
- Aw, poop no man.
Let me say it one more time.
- No you can't. (Collin groans)
- [Phone] Peap-coh.
- Yeah, that's kinda close.
- What?
- [Phone] Pea-cock.
- That actually is in, bro.
- Have it, that's fine. - Alright cool.
Yay, turn up!
Alright, next one.
Your turn.
- This one's right up your alley.
Wizardry.
- Up at Diagon Alley.
- Badum, tss.
- Wizard--
- Wizardry.
Yeah, I know.
- You (mumbles) to just put like wizard.
Can we just do wizard?
(Devan laughs) Please!
Wizardry is really hard.
No, I'm doing wizard.
Wizard, I'm keepin' it to wizard I'm overruling you here.
Do-wiz-woop.
(laughs)
- Yeah, about that one. - Yeah, right.
- Since you did wizard, I'm gonna do wizardry.
You know, to make it harder.
- Great, yeah.
- Wizard, what?
- I don't know. (mumbles)
- Yer-Boogar-Zaw.
- [Phone] Op-zi-wiz.
- I forgot the R.
- Yeah, it's not even there.
- [Phone] Wa-zid-ri.
- You need to try it again 'cause I did mess you up.
- Yer-Dri-Zaw.
- It sounds like a Snoop Dogg video.
My Yer-Dri-Zaw.
- Scrr.
- [Phone] Waz-idwish-dri.
- Way closer than mine. - Yes.
- And I'm just going for the biggest of wizards.
Next one is faceplant.
- Tuh-Nalp-Saf.
- [Phone] Fas-plant.
- Oh!
- Wow, that was really close.
Let's see.
- [Phone] Fas-planus.
- You still got it--
- I think we should call it a tie.
Moving on-- - That was very kind.
Thank you. - You're welcome.
Iridescent.
- Are you kidding me?
Iridescent?
- I've got harder ones so--
- Harder ones?
- Don't worry.
- No seriously bro, iridescent?
- Don't you worry.
I've got harder ones.
- Even me trying to say iridescent regularly
is probably not going to go into this right.
Tiri-nis-sen-duri-de-I.
No, did not even close. - Great job, bro.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, that's perf--
Spot on.
- I'm sure it was.
- Tenes-Siridi.
- [Phone] He-nes-derun-nes-senerus.
- I don't even know what is that.
- Yeah, pretty ba--
- You said, nese-sit.
- Okay, fine.
- [Phone] He-deris-sen-et.
- That's still closer than mine.
- Yeah.
- Literally anything you do
is probably way closer than mine.
Next up is the wonderful buoyant animal, the kangaroo.
- Oo-Ra-Gek.
- Oo-Ag-Kenu-Kuh.
It's got the "kuh" in the end
so that was like a little hit some--
You just go for it.
(laughs)
- [Phone] Keg-na-roo.
- Hey, that's pretty close.
- [Phone] Hus-bun-nek-ga-oo.
(laughs)
- Nailed it.
(laughing)
- At the end it was like--
- [Phone] Ooo!
(laughing)
Ooo!
- And next, you're up. - Repugnant.
- Are you kidding?
Repugnant?
Dude, how are we even supposed to get repugnant?
- I don't know dude.
- Ti-Nig-Yur-Burp.
(laughs)
Ti-nig-yur-burp.
Let's see how it is. - Ti-nig-yur-burp.
- Ti-Nig-Yur-Burp, let's see what it is.
- Hi, my name is Ti-Nig-Yur-Burp.
- [Phone] Prub-Yur-Gin-nished.
- It did just sounds like even more (mumbles) backwards.
(laughing)
Listen to it, it literally sounds like--
- [Phone] Prub-Yur-Gin-nished.
(gibberish)
(singing gibberish)
- Alright, cool.
We're good. - Alright.
- Alright, so we're gonna be moving on
since neither of us can successfully say this word at all.
Yeah, next is single.
For bonus points, you can add the word Pringle after it.
A single Pringle.
(laughs)
- I'll let you add that bonus word.
I'm just gonna try to get it right.
Guh-nis.
- Yo-Gu-Ings.
- [Phone] Sin-ik.
- [Phone] Snug-goy.
- Sounds like snuggley.
- Yeah, it sounds like snuggley.
Okay.
- [Phone] Snug-goy.
- Something that does not happen when you're single at all.
So that's kind of ironic.
We were both pretty far off.
Negative one point from each.
- Yeah, wow okay.
Phobia is my next word.
- Are you kidding me bro?
You should know like, phobia.
- Yeah.
- You say it first.
- Okay. - Then I'll copy what you say.
- Alright.
(clears throat)
We did that in sync.
- Yeah. (clears throat)
(laughs)
- Ayi-Boaf.
- Ayi-Bofu.
Nailed it. - That actually might--
- Hold up.
I got (mumbles).
- [Phone] Uh-pho-bia.
- Oh!
- It's a come up baby, don't you ever forget--
Well let's hear how your sound first.
- [Phone] Pho-bia.
(laughs) (sighs)
- I literally thought I won this one and then Devan--
- It can cause a tie but we're pretty close.
- No, Devan.
You distinctly one that.
My next word is redonkulous.
Which I don't think is even a real word.
- His favorite word.
- I used to say redonkulous to just
about everything. - Bro that's redonkulous dude.
- So we're gonna get it a try right now.
- Redonk--
- Redonkulous!
- Jeez.
- Sorry.
- That's my phobia.
(laughs)
- Donk is what gets it.
The donk and--
(laughs)
- I feel like you just picked this word to say and--
- Redonkulous!
- Point proven.
Okay.
Ulous.
Redonk-ulous.
- Redonkulous!
(laughs)
- It's back.
This one's a difficult one.
Redonkulous. - I think your word is,
redonkulous!
(laughs)
- Distracting me man.
Sulos-kar-daw-er.
- That sounds redonkulous.
Se-ri-do-di-yur.
Redonkulous!
Alright, so let's give it a test shot right now
and let's see. - Alright, let's do it.
- [Phone] Re-do-yu-ris.
- That's pretty close.
- That is actually very close.
- Yes.
You go for yours.
- [Phone] Yer-hud-rak-sa-lus.
- That round was redonkulous!
- It's not redonkulous.
It's re--
- [Both] Donkulous!
- So that donk.
- Donk. (laughs)
- This next word is yek.
You'll see why.
- Okay, go. - Do it.
- Ka-I.
I don't know, try it.
(laughs)
- What?
What?
- Alright, well.
Key.
(laughs)
- Good one.
- [Phone] I-yak.
- [Phone] Yek.
- You's a fool.
You's a fool.
You are a fool bro.
Our final one.
- Yeah?
- Is Netflix and chill.
- Nosh-Kan-I-Eat-Still-Fin.
- [Phone] Netflix and chill.
- Ooh! - Oh!
- Ooh! - Ooh!
- But like--
- [Phone] Netflix and chill.
- Ooh. - Yeah.
- Killed. (mumbles)
- Brought it home on the end so.
- Mine was more of a "chuk" and your's like,
chill. - Chill.
So make sure you guys leave this video a big thumbs up
if you guys enjoyed it.
And also comment down below if you guys want to enter
to the giveaway that I'm doing here on my Youtube channel.
I'm givin' away a MacBook, Go Pro, Instax.
Subscribe to this channel
for new videos every single Thursday.
Go follow little Devan over here.
Oh my gosh.
All of his links are going to be down in the description--
- [Both] Below.
- So go check him out.
And the keyper of the week is Emma.
So congratulations Emma.
Yay!
Round of applause.
A round of applause.
I love you guys so much.
I will see you all again next week.
Bye, Felicia.