- You challenged us to make three crazy pranks.
The winner gets $10,000,
and by the way--
(both men yelling)
- What did you you do to me?
(men yelling)
- [Collin] You challenged us to make an edible volcano
and castle prank so let's go.
- [Devan] To kick it off I'm boiling honey
to make a manmade honeycomb.
- And I'll be using a pineapple as the base of my volcano.
- All right, you said the pineapple, here you go.
- Yup, wait that's not a pineapple bro, oh my gosh.
All right Devan this is all fun and games,
but like how do I get my pineapple out of here bro?
Oh man!
- Did it work?
(groaning)
- Wow. - Okay here we go.
- Wow, that like actually totally worked.
- Wow. - There we go!
The pineapple's out, look at that man, that's so cool.
Look at the imprint it left man.
Prank's on you Devan, I'm actually enjoying it.
How are you gonna make a manmade honeycomb?
- With some magic bro.
And my secret sauce is in the baking soda.
- [Collin And Devan] Three, two, one, whoa!
[Collin] Dude its like totally bubbling over the edge!
- [Devan] It looks like the moon.
All right, gotta pour it into the pan first, just like this.
- [Collin] Oh my gosh.
- [Devan] Wow, it's so fluffy bro.
- It looks kind of funky though, I'm not gonna lie.
Dude my honey settled so well.
- Oh wait what? - Now it's time
to break it up into sand bits.
You ready for it? - Do not try this at home!
- [Both] Three, two, one, oh!
- [Colin] That is perfect sand, dude oh my.
- This is gonna taste so good.
Nope, nope, nope.
- Are you sure, I just want I.
- No no no, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Gonna mix up a whole bunch of peanut butter and jelly
to make the base of my volcano.
It's not coming out though, hold on let's see if we can,
oh boy!
- Oh dude, what did you do?
- Have you? - Is this?
Is that bad? - I think
this peanut butter might be expired.
So here we go, we've got the jelly.
It's very bubbly on the top.
Wait a minute bro, this isn't jelly!
This is slime, wait was this a prank?
- Yes it is!
All right, I've got a ball of Isomalt here to
- A ba, what?
- Of Isomalt, I'm using it to make sea glass.
- Is that related to a seagull?
I don't know, like a sea glass
is just like glass.
- [Devan] Now I poke a little hole in it.
Just like this. - Okay.
- [Devan] And fill it up with air.
- Oh. - It's totally working.
- It's like a radish. - A radish?
- [Colin] This is one of the coolest things we've done.
Of course we can't use this right here
because it's actual slime, it is not edible at all.
So we gotta get some actual peanut butter
and jelly right now.
All right here we go, it's gonna take the peanut butter
and let it drop.
- [Devan] That looks more like peanut butter, man.
- Yeah, oh yeah, just a lot of girth to it.
There we go.
- What did you just say? - Oh!
- Got my sea glass bubbles done
and not it's time to smash'em up into the glass jewels.
(chuckling)
And remember, do not try this at home.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Oh!
- [Devan] That was insane.
- That was beautiful man, that was absolutely beautiful.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Oh!
- Look at that! - That's so cool!
- It looks so much like.
(upbeat music)
- I was gonna hit it again.
Now I'm gonna be smashing my coconnut
to make some edible moss out of it.
Wait what is that ?
- [Devan] I'm making coral with water, flour, and oil.
- You really want to crack open coconut,
what you gotta do is look for the little face on the bottom.
Then occasionally it'll make funny faces at you.
- Balala!
- What you wanna do is find the mouth
and then trace your line right up here
and you'll see there's actually a seam.
So right here, look at this, if I take it like this
I was smacking it pretty hard, no crack.
But this time--
- Still nothing.
Oh wait it actually worked.
- Ouw!
- I mean--
- Oh yes, yes, yes! - Whoa whoa whoa!
You're not getting any of juice.
- Dude it's perfect!
- No, don't you need the juice?
- [Collin] Look at this!
Oh no no no, I don't actually need the juice.
I just need the inside of the coconut.
- Got it. - Just the husk.
- Uh oh, it's coming up,
it's coming up. - Okay okay okay.
- Duude! - Yooo.
- This is so cool! - That looks nuts!
- I gotta put my coral down over here,
but for some reason there's coconut juice
all over it.
I don't know why.
- Yeah I don't either, that's very confusing.
- Who would do that?
- Let's find him and kick'em off the channel.
- No, that's a little drastic.
Next up I'm making some edible kelp.
So I've got some calcium lactate
and some sodium algenate over here.
So just gotta suck up some of this good juice here.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Go for it!
(screaming)
- [Devan] Dude!
It totally worked.
- [Collin] That is so cool.
- [Devan] Instant kelp noodles!
- Oh my gosh, that is insane.
Last thing I need to do to complete my moss,
is put all my coconut meat in here,
blend it up with some spinach powder
and its gonna be perfect.
- [Devan] Now I'm cracking up some eggs to make the base
for my castle.
- And I'm making some hot lava slime right now.
So I've got some cilium husk. - Oh nice.
- Add this in like this.
Oh dude, it's already orange which is perfect!
It's just like lava, man.
- [Devan] Next up I grabbed this meat.
Just add this in here.
- [Collin] Yoo dude, it's coming together.
Bro that is gonna be perfect slime.
To cool down the cilium husk lava slime,
I'm gonna pour it on the dry ice.
Three,
- [Both] Two. - Oh wait wait!
- Oh yeah, three second like challenge.
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds.
Ready?
Here we go, - Three, two, one, done!
- Three, two, one, oh, whoa!
- Its like bubbling up. - That is so cool!
- Whoa, look at the bubbles! - No way!
- [Collin] Look at the bubbles, look at the bubbles.
- What! - What!
Its expelling so much dry ice right now.
Yo!
Look at that!
- [Devan] It's going crazy.
- [Collin] It looks like something out of a movie man.
- [Devan] All right now we gotta add in
some of these sliced up vegetables here.
- Oh my gosh. - Just like this.
My last step is to add some of this Agar agar,
and then pop it in the oven.
- We have the base of my volcano all done.
We've got a pineapple coated with the peanut butter
and jelly granola around it.
(thunder and lightening) - Thou shall not pass!
- Where?
I'm not trying to go anywhere.
- You shall not pass this challenge.
- What? - That's what I meant to say,
you're not gonna win. - No,
I'm gonna win the $10,000.
- No you're not. - I will totally win.
- You're not.
Make the pile on here, yup!
- [Collin] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Just gotta nail it down just like this!
- [Collin] Right up here I got a whole bunch
of peanut butter and carob right here.
So this is gonna be the outside of the volcano.
- Now it's time to pop out this watermelon tube.
Tower done.
All right I'm starting with my towers here.
Just putting these down like this.
And then grabbing these hot dogs.
- [Collin] And just imagine man, as a science project
for back to school this would be perfect.
- All right I'm gonna finish these in a second.
But first I have to get out the agar agar solution.
- Oh my gosh, is it your jelly meatloaf?
- This is nasty!
(screaming)
No, no, it fell apart!
- [Collin] Well I'm gonna be mashing some potatoes here.
To act as the ocean here around my volcano.
That's probably the worst smelling
ingredient we've used so far, man
- Now it's time to add some sea foam around the sides.
- What?
That looks light an evil goblin, wait--
- [Devan] When you dip this bottle in here
with this rag on it.
- Wait I am so confused.
Wait what's gonna happen? - You'll see, you'll see.
Can you grab me some red?
- Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
- I just need some red. - Some red?
Well I have red over here.
- Oh yeah yeah yeah. - Oh wait wait.
- Oh yeah that's good.
- Pink, pink is fine. - Pink, pink is fine.
All right well here you go, here's pink,
want me to open it for you? - Thank you.
Now you just blow on this end here.
- Wait what's gonna happen though?
Oh,
that is nuts. - Yup!
Just gonna put it on the sides just like this.
- I did not see that coming at all man.
That was awesome.
- Got a little sea foam moat right here.
Oh and by the way these are specialty made edible bubbles.
- All right time for us to complete the pranks
and these things are gonna look insane.
We've got our finished pranks
and these are the best ones we have ever made.
- These are insane!
- On another level, so here's the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one, tada, yes !
- [Collin] And you get to comment down below
whose prank looks better!
Well be tasting them and finding out who wins the $10,000
at the end of the video.
- You challenged us to a candle and soap prank
so let's go.
I'm using dry ice as the first ingredient in my prank.
- [Collin] And I've got this little soap bar right here
I'm gonna use it to create corn in a very satisfying way.
- Looks like my wax is ready and now its time to dump it.
- Wax on dry ice?
Is that even allowed?
- What do you mean is it allowed?
- [Both] Three, two, one, Oh!
- That is cool man! - That is so awesome!
Gotta grab the mint leaf.
Gonna create an imprint of the leaf.
This is so cool, I think this totally gonna fool people.
Whooaaaa.
- Oh my gosh! - That looks so good!
- It is perfect.
For my egg I need a push pin, Devan.
So do you know where my push pins are at?
- Oh yup, its in this box right here.
- Thank you, okay here
(screams)
oh my gosh!
That scared me so much.
- Dude I got you so good.
- Best prank so far.
- For sure.
(screaming)
- [Collin] First I'm gonna poke some holes here in my egg.
- [Devan] Just gonna juice this lemon into here.
- [Collin] Oh my gosh it smells super zesty.
- Whoa! - whoa!
Yes !
- Once the holes are poked there's basically a magic trick
you can do with the egg.
You can empty it super fast, just like this.
Here we go, three, two, one
- Oh yeah, I love doing that-- - Ah, I broke it no.
My lips, they're just too strong
time to inject the egg with some jelly soap.
Oh wait a minute its coming out the bottom
I oh, ah, its hot its a little hot
- All right got my extra blueberries
now its time to squish it.
All right, I'm just gonna squeeze it like this
- Wait what are you doing its like a bench bite
- Gotta reopen it, man.
- Man, you can't even open it.
- I pranked myself
(laughing)
But I mean look at this
so I'm using these blueberries just for the coloring,
gonna add it into my pan.
What are you doing?
- [Collin] I'm adding some yellow in here
to create the egg yoke.
Trust me its gonna be incredible, man.
It's gonna look just like an egg,
except it's made completely out of soap.
- [Devan] Next up I'm hollowing out this lemon.
- Oh! - Oh!
Is it working?
- Perfectly dude, look at that.
Now, to do it properly, the outside is perfectly coated
and this will at as the yoke in the center.
- [Devan] All right, its time to fill up my lemon
with this jelly wax
its gonna be a fake lemon, dude.
- [Collin] While you do that I'm gonna try
and remove my silk hard boil egg.
You hear that bro?
Here we go the shell's now getting all cracked
- Next up I gotta grab this vegetable shortening.
- Wow looks pretty big for a shortener.
- Yeah it is. - Ah oh my god
- Collins
(laughing)
- I forgot I did that
- Well I'm hoping that this one is not another prank.
- [Collins] That was good.
- [Devan] Time to get some scoops of this stuff.
- Dude I fully peeled the egg. - Wow.
- [Collins] This is insane,
it's literally a soap egg right here.
- [Devan] Whoa, it look exactly like the real thing
- This is a perfect prank right here
because you would never know
that this is actually a candle, man,
you'd think that looks delicious.
- It even kinda feels like it too.
- Is it cold? - No, its not cold at all,
but it kinda has the same sorta creamy feel.
- [Collins] So this time I'm making a fishcake,
just gotta plop it on just like this.
- You ready I'm gonna drizzle some cherry sauce on the top.
Three, two, one.
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Collins] Yo, that looks just like a delicious toping man.
All right, here we go,
were just gonna put this down.
Oh I missed it with the pink, man!
- Oh no! - I'm sorry,
I'm doing my best.
I'm gonna put this flavor on top.
Oh amazing, smells like soap in here,
wooh, I need to see that, man.
- I mean, that's not the worst smell in the world
- Its smells nice and clean, fresh, and a little burnt.
(breathing heavily)
- I got some hot wax here that I'm gonna use
and make sure you do not try this at home.
As you can see its already starting to conjeal.
- Hot, hot, hot and I did it!
- [Devan] All right, my topping is done!
- [Collins] And I'm gonna slice this thing open right here.
Do not try this at home.
- Oh that's so cool.
- This is the cutes soap ever, man.
- [Devan] This looks so good.
- [Both] Three, two, one ahhh!
- My mind is thoroughly blown right now.
to make my ramen noodles
I got a whole bunch up hot soap right here.
Three, two, one oh my gosh I'm making one long noodle!
- What is that?
- Its my noodles, man.
- [Devan] Its a good thing
those noodles are gonna be covered, man.
- What do you mean covered bro, I think they look awesome.
- They look what? - Awesome!
- I'm gonna start making my blueberries here
putting them in, whoa, gotta grab it out, yeah.
- That's a huge blueberry
- I just gotta mold it into a sphere,
I got a blueberry here for reference, nope too big.
- Well, dude, I'm gonna try to push this down,
there we go, it's coming out, okay, there we go.
- Ew, ew.
Look at that! - That looks so perfect, man.
- [Devan] This looks like a blueberry!
- It looks like a perfect blueberry.
I wanna feel my noodles now, here we go let's see, whoa!
(both squirming)
Its like weirdly slimy,
these definitely don't act like noodles
but in my ramen I think they'll look perfectly in place.
I've got all the ingredients
and no its time to assemble our prank.
- [Devan] I'm starting it off
by slicing open my candle lemon.
Oh that looks awesome!
- Oh my God!
for my ramen bowl here,
I've actually made the bowl out of soap
the second part right here is my soap noodles
and these things turned out so cool.
- [Devan] Wow, those look good, wait, can I touch them?
- [Collins] Yeah you can touch my ramen noodles, dude,
they're awesome.
- They feel kinda creamy actually, like hard cream.
Dude, look at this I got some awesome ice cubes
that aren't actually ice cubes.
- Wait, what they're squishy. - I know
- [Collins] Next I've got some jelly soap
and this is gonna act as the broth for my ramen.
Yo, I hope this doesn't melt my wax bowl.
- [Devan] I got my ice cubes in,
now I'm gonna add some blueberries
just like this
- It looks so real. - And one lemon.
- Oh my gosh.
- Now its time to add the liquid.
- What is that?
- Its my jelly wax three, two, one!
Oh, this is remarkable.
- Well here we go I'm gonna some corn onto mine right now.
This little old some some battering
and corn on the top like that,
next I'm gonna add some green unions on the top of mine
I totally forgot about the soap eggs.
I'm gonna slice this thing open right now.
Oh, man.
- Wow. - Wow, dude.
- No way. - What?
Oh well, right now its time
to add the finishing touches to these, man.
These are gonna look insane.
Pranks are done and these look so edible
but we are not allowed to eat them.
But here's the reveal.
Three, two-- - Oh.
- Oh, yeah 5 second subscribe challenge!
We wanna see if you can can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
You ready?
Here we go!
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done!
- If you can do that, comment down below
keyper squad right now.
- [Both]] Three two one ta da yeah!
- [Collins] Oh my gosh, you can comment down below
which one looks more edible.
We we'll be testing them at the end of the video.
You challenged us to do an extreme pizza prank so let's go
and instead of using cheese I'm gonna be using egg whites
to make a meringue.
So where are my eggs at?
- Actually its kinda perfect you mention it
'cause I prepared your eggs for you right here.
- No in an block of ice, dude?
This is not even a prank, it's an inconvenience
and the only way to get these out is with a hammer,
three, two, one!
- [Both] Oh!
- I am soaked!
There's a whole bunch or water, that's the issue,
all right, well let's see, let's just--
(banging)
(Yelling) the eggs are broken, I broke the eggs!
- [Devan] Now you may have heard of cheese filled crust
but instead I want people to make this ugh face
when they bite into my crust.
So I'm filling it with Greek yogurt
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
I got the egg out now it time to separate the whites
and the yoke and turn it into some cheese.
- I got my meat grinder here and now its time
to make some terrible meat balls.
- Nice I'm just whipping up my egg whites over here
its gonna look just like cheese when its done, man.
- You want any of these cherries by any chance?
- Those don't look like cherries, man.
- Oh, trust me they're just from a different part
of the world, they're actually really tasty.
- Are you sure?
- To prove to you it's not a prank I'll eat one with you.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(yelling)
- [Devan] So good.
- Ah wow what is that?
- So delicious.
- Wait, is it fine for you?
- Yeah, it's great.
- Oh my ugh!
- How did you eat it and have no reaction to it?
- I didn't actually eat it, Collins.
- [Collins] Next I'm gonna blend it up with this,
here we go.
Okay, oh yeah.
Well, the cheese is done,
this is probably gonna taste really funky.
- Yo!
- Oh my gosh someone's gonna bite into this
and think its a meat ball,
but it's literally just gonna make them go ugh,
'cause it's raw.
For my meat I've got some prosciutto here
and I've actually got a very unique way of cooking it.
I'll be using a plasma globe.
But first I need to redirect
all available power to this globe.
So, here we go, three, two, one go!
- [Both] Yo!
- Oh my gosh, dude, that is crazy.
- That's so cool.
I'm gonna see if we can cook the meat,
If it works it might leave an electric after taste
to the meat.
Three,
- [Both] Two, one, oh!
- Oh oh, my gosh
I'm gonna use this prickly pear
to see if I can create a spark in between the two.
Here we go.
- Wait what? - Three, two, one.
- [Evan] Is that even possible?
What no!
- Oh my gosh! - Oh my gosh!
- [Collins] Get the lights back on!
and see if this actually worked.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Oh!
- Dude, did it cook?
Dude, smell that.
Right, that definitely smells very electrocuted.
- [Evan] And instead of pepperoni I got a sweet surprise
for anybody who bites into my pizza.
- Wait strawberry's for pepperoni?
- Yes and the secret ingredient is dried ice.
- What?
Oh my gosh! - Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oh!
Yo.
- [Collins] It becomes a witch's cauldron again.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Oh! - Ah
Oh my gosh! - I think it's working.
- Next up, time to cook the shrimp
but instead of using olive oil,
I've got some ketchup right here.
Just gonna add it down.
- Is it clogged or something, dude?
- Does that look clogged to you?
- Oh yeah, ah.
- Dude, it's just the string.
I would never put ketchup on shrimp, that's a big no no.
- But you would squirt it in my face.
- Exactly.
- All right, now its time to see if my strawberry froze.
Three, two, one,
- [Both] Oh, no!
- Now its time to see if it's gonna smash.
Safety glasses on!
- Do not try this at home.
- Oh, it's hard to put on with one hand.
- [Both] Three, two, one, oh!
- It's still on you.
- [Collins] I got hit with a whole bunch of pieces,
strawberry in the throat.
Why are you even doing this?
- Remember this is my pepperoni substitute, Collins.
- These are perfectly cooked
Ah it's gettin' hot, retreat.
Retreat!
- [Devan] Right, now it's time to lather this stuff
onto my pan.
- [Collins] When this stuff hardens it's gonna look
just like pepperoni, man.
You won't be able to tell the difference at all.
- Next step, I gotta dehydrate this stuff
so, I'm gonna pop it in the oven,
then I'm gonna take it out
and cut out the pepperoni slices.
All right, it's out of the oven.
- Instead of tomato sauce I'm using kimchi
for my pizza sauce. - Wait, no!
- [Collins] So here we go, I'm gonna crack it open.
- O wait, wait, wait,
I heard you actually open it upside down.
- Okay got ya, here we go, open up like this,
you ready?
- [Boh] Three, two, one,
- Here we go. - Go quick,
You're supposed to go really, really fast.
- [Both] Oh!
- Yes yes!
- What, my hand is covered in kimchi now, Devan.
All right, here we go, now time
to get it all and to strain it up
the sauces is almost done.
We got all the ingredients
and now it's time to assemble the pizza prank.
So, Devan, what are you gonna start with?
- [Devan] Instead of tomato sauce
I'm gonna start with Sriracha sauce.
- Oh my God. - No, no, we have to eat this.
- Next step, time for my cheesy meringues, so here we go,
oh man, egg whites are gonna be all over this thing.
Oh, it's coming out the top.
- Why is it coming out at the top?
- I don't know, Devan, I broke it.
are you ready for this stuff - What is that?
- [Devan] This looks like jerky than bacon.
- All right, next up, we got these boba balls here
they're very slimy,
reaching into the bowl is unpleasant.
- Now it's time for my unsuspecting prey
to take a whiff and a bite
- Ah-ah.
- You're not gonna do it?
- No I won't eat an uncompleted pizza
all right, next I'm gonna line the thing with okra, dude.
Oh. - Oh
- Look how slimy it is.
Right now, time to put the finishing touches on the pizza.
- Both pizzas are out of the oven
and these did not turn out how I expected
so, here's the big reveal,
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Tada, yeah! - What is this dude?
- Mine is gonna be so spicy! - Oh my gosh!
you can comment down below
whose pizza do you think will taste worse
we'll be eating them at the end of the video
and choosing the 10,000 dollar winner.
- [Devan] Got all the pranks and now it's time to test them
and find out who's gonna win the $10,000.
- [Collins] Remember mine is an active volcano
that might go off at any second
- Wait what really?
- Yeah it might literally erupt, don't even get close, man,
you never know what's gonna happen.
- My sand castle's pretty legit
because it's just as fragile as a real sand castle
So, I think we should eat mine first.
I think I'm gonna go for the center bit.
This is a meat in the agar agar
you can have some of the tower as well.
- No no no no-- - What?
- I want the whole tower.
- All right, it's like a little treat for you.
- This doesn't, no,
I'm gonna say no.
- Three, two, one
- Ah the coral is so, oh my gosh, hold on.
- [Devan] The orange doesn't really help it.
- Ah, it's so cold.
- You know what the taste kinds gets better,
'cause remember this isn't a prank
on the person eating the sand castle,
it's a prank on the person watching
the other person eating the sand castle.
- What?
- I've got something to tell you, Devan about my volcano.
Its not currently active.
But it will be active when we add hot vinegar into it.
I got the vinegar, you can tell it's red,
'cause I wanted to make sure it looks really like lava.
We're gonna be very careful, we're gonna pour it in
just like this.
Next thing is, we got some baking soda here.
So, I'm gonna be dumping this in
and it's gonna set it all off, it's gonna go crazy.
You might wanna step back a little.
- Three, two--
- Wait wait!
- If you wanna win a 15 minute video call with Devan and I,
text the word fun to 81800 right now,
so pause the video, text the word fun to 81800
to automatically be entered in to win.
Now, let's see what happens.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Oh!
(whooshing)
- That shot right up at me! - My sand castle's falling!
- [Collins] Oh no, now it's time to slice all the pieces
of volcano, it's gotten soggy.
- I actually wanna eat one of these edible bath bombs
and I'll eat some of that.
- Gotta pick up some of the mash potato lotion right here.
Ooh, boy, this smells good!
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- Whoa, whoa. - Oh yeah!
You get to comment down below
whose you think would taste better.
We'll be finding out the 10,000 dollar winner
at the end of the video
We got the finish pizzas
and these things are gonna taste funky, man.
Mine's got kimchi, yours has got hot sauce,
literal sriracha sauce,
but the first thing we're looking for is,
do they look like a normal pizza?
And the answer is no.
They look like fancy pizzas,
'cause at a fancy restaurant they put anything on pizza
and charge a lot of money for them, they're like,
oh, you have cactus on your pizza, sir.
We have shrimp, so right now,
which pizza are we going to try first?
- I think, let's try mine.
I think I made a diabolical masterpiece.
Hot sauce in the middle, the wasabi, the cactus, ooh.
- And we're judging it based on which pizza tastes worse.
- I don't know where I should cut it from.
I think I gotta get some of this.
- [Collins] You can give it an angle.
- [Devan] Gotta get the cactus on there.
- [Collins] I don't wanna eat a piece of cactus.
- [Devan] Now it's time for my slice.
- [Collins] Oh, oh no, the yogurt.
I did not think about the effect
that cooking yogurt would have and it is not good.
- Got my slice right here,
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Wooh!
(both yelling)
- It's really spicy, but it's so cold at the same time.
(Collins grunting) (Devan yelling)
- It's so hot, dude.
- All the flavors were so contradictory,
we had the sweet strawberry pepperoni,
mixed with the tart flan, hot wasabi and the hot sauce.
- Hopefully mine tastes just as bad,
better as in bad.
- No, no, it's gotta be really good,
I hope it's tasty.
- [Collins] I gotta say, mine, all things considered,
looks pretty good.
Let's see, we're gonna lift this off.
- [Devan] This crust is ridiculous.
- [Collins] Yeah, I know, so here we go, Devan.
I'm gonna balance a slice of pizza as I do this.
- I like how you move your whole body
when you cut something too.
- Its a sea saw motion that really cuts it.
Learned it from a professional chef.
- [Devan] I think this is perfect.
- [Collins] Oh, you're a folder when you eat your pizza.
- Oh, I have to, man.
- Just in Devan folds his pizza when he eats it.
- [Devan] I gotta pull of the front off this, dude.
I'm pulling out the front of your pizza.
- You're mangling my creation.
Enough talk, it's time for action.
- [Both] Three, two,
- Oh, wait wait,
we just launched our brand new keyper club
and if you become a member,
you'll get exclusive access to live streams,
merch discounts codes, custom emojis,, loyalty badges
and exclusive content you can't see anywhere else,
so click the top link in the description
to join, for four, 99 a month,
now let's see how these taste.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- Oh!
- Ah!
- Oh, oh!
- Ah! - Uh-uh!
This is bad.
- I don't like that.
- That was the weirdest combo of foods I've ever tasted
- I gotta say the shrimp was just like a whoopoo,
it came out of nowhere, just at us!
Comment down below,
whose pizza do you think would taste worse
and we'll be choosing the 10,000 dollar winner
at the end of the video.
We've got our soap and candle pranks
and now it's time to test 'em to see
which one is truly worthy of $10,000,
yours looks so amazing, man.
- I know right?
- I could totally see myself picking this up
and taking a drink of this
and being very confused why nothings comes out.
Can I try it? - Go for it.
All right, let's see, here we go,
three, two, one its just a whole bunch of candle wax.
What I like about this one,
the wick is very hidden on the inside,
you can't really see it.
- I really like yours too
except the Irish Spring, the smell is a dead give away.
That is some pungent stuff.
- This dirt, to make sure this stuff actually works
and remember, its all made out of soap,
got my hands a little dirty right now.
- [Devan] Oh, we're going for it right now.
- Oh boy, this is some good dirty dirt.
Oh my gosh.
These are hands that have been in the garden
making mud balls and not doing any actual work.
Gonna try to get the soap out right now.
Oh, I can feel its almost ready to come out
the soap is out.
- Covered in dirt but it's out
- Let's see if it works,
rub it all around like this,
seems to be working
- Whoa whoa whoa
your splashing it everywhere
that actually totally worked!
- Yo, look at it sudding up.
you can put this in your bathroom sink,
could be very confusing, like, nope, that's my soap,
it's not a bowl of ramen, my soap.
- I think yours is good,
but I'm not sure if it's gonna stand up
to my dry ice mint leaves, bro.
- Excuse me sir.
- Why'd you call me sir?
- I'm feeling very fancy
now that my hands are all washed up.
- Now I think its time to light these candles.
- Oh, yeah, that's the real test
to see if this actually works.
- And this involves fire
so remember do not try this at home.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- [Devan] All right, it's lit.
- [Collins] Oh, it's so small.
- It's lit, here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I can see it melting a little bit.
- [Collins] It's not gonna do it, it's not gonna go.
- Dude, why did I pick such bad wicks?
- That one barely worked, this one didn't work.
You can comment down whose prank turned out better
and we'll be finding out the 10,000 dollar winner
at the end of the video.
We've got the $10,000 and time to find out who won,
so the first round we're judging
is the candle and soap round.
its cleaned my hands thoroughly.
- [Devan] Yes, more candle.
My treat worked-- - But--
- Yeah, the other one, my drink didn't, so.
- Your drink didn't work so therefore I win that round,
so, there we go one point for me.
The next one we're judging is the pizza.
Both weird.
I mean the Sriracha for pizza sauce on yours--
- [Devan] And the strawberry pepperonis were ugh.
- The boba really kinda threw it off,
all in all both were very funky pizzas,
but yours definitely had that edge to it,
you definitely won that round.
- I took the win on that one.
- Devan's got one point, we're now coming
into the final one.
The 10,000 dollar winner will be decided
by a sand castle and a volcano
and your sand castle was magnificent
there were just so many unique elements,
I've never seen before on yours
that really kind of took it to another level.
- But yours had actual volcano stuff flying out of it
and your little dinosaur touches with the water
- [Collins] And it literally destroyed yours.
- Yeah, yeah, you're right.
- I think you won
I think you won.
Dude, I think you won.
What are you gonna do with the money, dude?
- See, I think I'm gonna read all of you guys' comments
and the best comment, that's gonna choose
how I spend this $10,000.
Click over here,
if you wanna see another video you got 5 seconds
here we go.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done
- Love you! - Bye!