- [Man In white T-Shirt] I know this trick.
And it's where you have to follow the queen.
That's the name of the game.
Everyone follow the queen, okay?
(crowd mumbles)
(electronic music)
Watch.
I'm gonna add in
- [Danisnotonfire] I'm following that girl.
- [Man in White T-Shirt] A four, okay.
And I'll add in, watch, another four.
Watch this right here.
Always watch the queen.
Don't get distracted by the fours, okay?
So right now, hey bro, point to it.
Where is the queen?
Point to the queen.
- [Danisnotonfire] It's there.
- [Man in White T-Shirt] Okay good.
Hold out your hand; watch this.
- [PointlessBlog] My eyes are so on this.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Right.
Watch the queen.
(electronic dance music)
You're watching the wrong card.
- [Danisnotonfire] Why?
- [Man In White T-Shirt] 'Cause see,
I've got the queen over here.
- [Woman] What! (laughing)
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Look what you're holding, yeah.
- [Woman] What!
What!
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Here, watch this.
Watch, watch.
Watch this.
Watch, hold out you're hand.
Hold out you're hand, Joey.
Hold out your hand, Joey; watch this.
Watch the queen right here, okay?
This one gets trippy.
Everyone, can everyone see the four?
I'm spinning the four.
I'm distracting you.
You don't wanna watch the four.
Always watch the queen.
Watch the queen right here.
Ready?
Like that.
Quick point to the queen, point to the queen.
No that's a four; that's a four.
(crowd laughs)
- [Woman] What the Hell!
What?
- [AmazingPhil] Yo possessed by Satan!
(crowd screams)
Wait, now watch.
Watch, watch, watch, watch.
Queen.
Make it easier, watch.
Queen in the pocket.
Queen goes away.
This is the easiest game of all time.
It's like, literally watch.
Just two fours.
Watch the fours, okay?
Joey, right now, point to the queen.
Point to the queen.
- [Joey] It's in your pocket.
- [Danisnotonfire] In his frickin' pocket, man.
- [PointlessBlog] That's the queen.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Aye!
- Alright, now watch.
No, no, no watch.
Check it out.
- [Joey] Oh my god, you're doing magic again.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Yo what's up, brother.
Yo, yo, yo check it out.
So you said it's in my pocket?
You're absolutely right.
The queen's in my pocket, okay?
- [Woman] Yeah.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Watch, look at this.
Unless I want the queen right here,
then the queen's in my hand.
(crowd screams) - Wow, what the Hell?
No!
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Hold out your hand.
- I hate when you do this to me.
- [Woman] How are you doing this?
- Yo, everyone watch; watch Connor's hand.
Everyone watch this, watch.
- [Connor] Is it gonna turn into a chicken or something?
- No no no no, even better.
I'm cheating, watch.
Look at the queen.
I'm using extra cards, okay?
I'm using extra fours.
Right, like that.
- [Woman] Whoa!
What?
Connor's out, Connor's out.
Connor's so out right now.
- You guys were right.
I put the queen in my pocket.
Here's what we're gonna do.
Hold out your hand, hold out your hand.
- [Woman] What is happening?
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Hold out your hand, man.
And hold out yours.
- [Woman] This is endless, going on forever.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Watch this.
Watch this, watch.
Hold your hands a little bit lower, guys.
Hold your hands a little bit lower.
Watch this right here.
Watch.
Four right here.
Watch the four.
Which one you holding man? - The four.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] The four, turn it over.
No, it's a queen.
I'm trying to help you.
Hold out your hand.
Watch watch, watch.
Which one you holding?
- [Crowd] The four.
- [Man In White T-Shirt] No, always watch the queen.
Look what you're holding, dude.
Turn it over.
You got a queen.
(crowd laughs)
- [Woman] How, How are you doing this?
- [Man In White T-Shirt] Joe, hold out your hand.
Watch this, watch.
Always watching, watch.
Which one are you holding?
(crowd mutters)
Name it right now; go for it.
There you go man!
- [Woman] No, what the Hell!
What the Hell!
(crowd laughs)
- [Joey] I don't understand.
- [Woman] How are you doing this?
- Magic!
It's ridiculous!
- [Woman] You have to tell us the secret though.
- Probably.
- [AmazingPhil] You're possessed by Satan.
- [Danisnotonfire] Joey, you have the devil inside you.
(electronic music)