- [Both] Cupcake challenge!
- [Devin] Boom!
- Whew, my gosh you challenged us to another cupcake art
challenge and right, now let's go!
- Is it good?
- Oh man this is good.
- For this round, as you can tell,
we've got way more cupcakes, so right now we are making
Wreck-It Ralph. - Whew!
I dropped it.
First thing, we must assemble the shape
of Wreck-It Ralph. - Yes
- So we're gonna go boom.
Ba-da-boom-boom-boom-boom.
Now, it's time to decorate Wreck-It Ralph.
Shouldn't have done that.
I was trying to be like Wreck-It Ralph,
and just like break the internet, ya know, but nope.
Two eyeballs, bam.
Oh man, he looks very upset right now.
(laughs)
I will give him a big ol' mouth.
He'll be wrecking some food with his mouth.
Oh gosh, it looks so scary!
(exaggerated moan)
- Alright, got two of his shoulders done.
- Dude, what the fu-?
My dude's got massive teeth.
Wreck-It Ralph has got buckteeth.
Oh look at that nice shirt.
- Alright, here we go.
We got arm number one. Boop.
I don't want Devan's...
(tube squeaks)
You good?
Oh there it goes again, dude.
(Electronic music)
Yo, yours is looking, not good, Devin.
- Haters gonna hate.
- I'm not hatin', I'm just,
Yeah, I'm hatin'.
Because that was my spoon.
Well, I'm gonna get a spoon right now,
so whoo-papa!
Bam! A spoon.
Man, it got stuck to the spoon.
It's just coming straight off my cupcake.
- See, only a skilled spoon handler can handle this.
So much concentration is taking place at the moment.
- I can tell.
Collin just went quiet.
- Very true, I live with him.
(electronic music)
- Yo, no, no, no! Dude my icings running out.
- Oh no!
- Please, can I finish the hand?
Please, please, please, please, please yes!
Made it, bam!
Now, time to detail his hands and feet,
because we need to get some fingers.
We got to have him do hand signs,
like yo what's up, peace
- Whoa.
- His eyes are like so close together.
He can only see one thing.
I gotta give my guy some toes, some big ol' toes.
Look, he looks like a duck with
some like flippers or something.
Man, I did not get the toes right.
- Oh, no!
This is even worse!
Oh my goodness!
- Yo, that's actually low-key kind of terrifying.
- Alright, so now I have to go in and add the nose.
No! No! - That is not working!
(aggravated puffs)
- Hopefully it falls in the right spot.
No!
- Dude, you got it on his eyebrow.
You can't have a nose on the brow.
Replace it.
- Yep, oh!
Congratulations.
- Wow!
That looks really bad.
Yo!
The big reveal, here we go.
Three, two, one!
Ta-Da!
- These are the Wreck-It Ralph-
I think I may have nailed this round,
but you get to comment down below
and let us know who you think won
so right now, guys, it's on to the next round.
For this one you challenged us to do
Mario from Mario Odyssey.
Alright, go!
- Okay, what do I, Oh!
(zip sound)
Dude really! (laughs)
I think I'm gonna go pink with his face.
- Pink?
(vocalises)
- Next up we got some baby blue, oh my gosh!
This stuff looks really cool.
This is like jelly, almost.
Yo, Mario looks like he's buggin'.
He's got his hat on like, he's like, 'ah'.
What's great about mine is that from this angle
you got Mario with a hat, some eyes,
but from this angle, he's a terrifying monster.
- So scary!
- It looks like one of those little Goombas, bro!
- Oh, you're so right!
- Bam, we got a little nose.
We gotta do his mustache.
Aw man, it just looks like a mouth!
- [Collin] He's got a massive uni-brow.
- Alright, here we go.
Gonna give Mario some pink sideburns.
Boom!
Booooo.
- Are the sounds necessary?
- The sounds are absolutely necessary.
- Do, doop, doop,-doop, do, doop.
- Now time for the buttons!
'Cause as you guys know,
Oh, the top is still on.
What?
Button number one.
- That's a massive button, bro.
Wait, his overalls are like, straight down.
(laughs)
(sneeze)
- We got big ol' beefy arms.
Woo.
Mario's been lifting!
- Meow
We got to give him some, oh no!
I dropped my top.
Yo, dude, what are you doing to that mouth?
He's like (growl).
And now, after every great art challenge,
(electronic music)
And now it's time for the big reveal.
Here we go!
Three, two, one, Ta-da!
I did my best.
That's all I can say.
We'll be eating these at the end of the video
but right now, it's on to the next round.
This is one of the most requested ones
and you wanted us to do Moana.
So right now, let's go!
I've got edible flowers, by the way?
- Alright.
(crunch)
These are edible?
Bro.
(cough)
- She's got this like a green wreath around her head.
Nailed it on so many levels.
We're gonna get some flowers in the top, bloop!
Boom! (clap) oh!
Awesome!
Alright, now we gotta add the whites around the eyes.
- Oh no, I misplaced one of the eyes.
(gasp)
- I know how I'm gonna use detail like no one else
has ever used detail before.
(high-pitched screech)
Sucks in this round!
- Oh no, my Moana looks super angry.
- Yo!
- What have I done?
She's like side-eyeing you right now.
She's like 'huh'.
- Well, because she sees that my Moana's got
a way better eyelashes.
(airhorn)
(electronic music)
- Alright, the crown is done now, and (clap)
time to flower it up.
Alright, two little nostrils.
And then give her a big ol' happy smile, though.
What are you doing with the cheeks?
- A little bit of blush!
She's got a little bit of rosy cheeks.
- She has sideburns, bro!
- She does, don't hate!
Everyone's special and different.
Yo, you know how people say they have pearly white teeth?
- Yeah?
- I'm gonna give her literal pearls for teeth.
- Alright, here we go.
I'm going around the perimeter of my cupcake.
I don't think this is really working out.
Bro, she's looking like a pirate now!
(high-pitched 'what')
Boom, locked it down.
Mine is completed.
- And, boom!
Locked it down.
- Alright, here we go.
The big reveal.
Three, two, one, wait! - Sorry
- Our 5-Second Subscribe Challenge
- Okay.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel.
- Alright.
- Turn on the channel's post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready?
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one! Done!
- Alright
let's see what these look like,
Ready? - Now we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, Ta-da!
- I think I nailed it,
but you get to comment down below
and let us know who won.
- Mine's more like a wonk, wonk, wonk, right?
Than a tah-dah.
- You wanted us to do Jack Jack from the new Incredibles
movie. We're gonna speed run
through this one because you know
Jack Jack is like "pow, whew, whew"
(squeaking)
Hand in, hand in, hands on, hands on
(squeaking}
Alright. - Okay, time for his hair.
Bro, you have ten seconds left.
- Ten seconds!
Ten! - No!
Nine! - No!
Eight! - No, no!
Seven six, five, for, three, two, one! Done!
- The big reveal!
Three, two, one, Tah-dah!
I was trying to make Jack Jack on fire
because you know he goes like (screams)
and he bursts into flames.
Is that his hair? - I tried to do his hair.
That's so, that's actually pretty awesome.
(beeping) So, you get to comment down below
who won this round, and right now
we are on to the next one.
On this one you challenged us to make Pikachu,
and right now begin.
Oh yeah. Oh that's nice.
This is called the cup'm roll.
Man it just took all my icing off.
If mine didn't look raggedy before,
boy, boy! (loud grunting)
squeeze
See, Devon only does one toothpick at a time.
This is called the double toothpick wa-fananza.
It's where you take two toothpicks
and you go whew, double time.
Oh yeah, oh, oh look at that technique.
Now that we've got the base layer crusted
- Yes
Time to fill it in.
Okay, so we're gonna go eyeball number one
- [Collin] Here we go.
- [Devon] He has really wide eyes, oh no!
His entire eye came off!
- Alright, cool. So, here we go.
Now we've gotta get some eyebrows on my man.
Yo, his brows are thick!
Pikachu is an electric little dude,
so I'm gonna add some lightening to him
(electric zapping)
(laughing) I thought it was going to look so much better
than it ended up looking
- It looks like spider man attacked him.
(laughter) (squirt) webbed him - Yeah
Oh, oh, and done! Awe!
Alright, now I've gotta add the,
- Awe! Dude you've ruined it.
You're gonna make it worse! - Awe!
- Alright, here it is the big reveal. Are you Ready?
Three, two, one, Tah-dah!
You get to comment down below who won this round.
This is a toss up, so guys right now
we're on to the next one.
For this one you challenged us to make a character
from the new avengers movie and you're gonna
have to figure out which one we chose.
So, right now begin.
Alright, so I'm gonna go for the color green,
which will give you no hint
at to which one I'm making.
- I think it does Collins. - Nope
He's got bad skin, he's aged very quickly.
Anger, ages you quickly?
So, I've got to give him some angry brows.
Anger - Anger (roaring)
- This dude looks super, duper, duper angry.
- I'm sorry, but the grinch is not in the avengers.
- The grinch? No this dude would not steal christmas.
He would smash christmas.
- Oh yeah, I have no idea who this is.
- No clue.
What else can I do to distinguish
(gasp) (ping) I'm gonna need some more cupcakes.
Hold up. Bam! Alright, there we go.
I got another green! Yeah boy! Woo!
- I've never seen someone so excited about green before.
- This is coming along saucily
The most important part about my character
is the muscle definition. Here we go, Bam!
Look at that line. Now I've gotta give my little dude
some fingers. Oh, there's a finger, another finger.
Boom!, I'm locking it in. - Oh my gosh.
(electronic music)
- Dude, I'm blown away, that is the most
incredible cupcake you have ever made.
Which is saying a lot.
Here it is, the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- Wait a minute first
the three second like challenge.
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds.
Are you ready? Here we go.
Three, two, one, done! Let's take a look.
Three, two, one, Tah-dah! (laughs)
It's the Hulk flexing like this
- What?
- You get to comment down below
who won this round, and right now,
we are on to the next.
You wanted us to make Chewbacca from the new solo movie.
We're doing this as a speed round. So, right now go!
- This is going to be incredible dude.
- Oh no!
- I'm gonna use only sprinkles for this cupcake dude.
- How is that sticking to the cupcake?
You're getting sprinkles everywhere! Look at that.
(Squeaking)
(hornlike sound)
- Did I do it? Oh, oh, oh look at this
it's actually kind of working.
- But if you shake it a tiny bit, (blowing)
(sobbing)
(squeaking)
Locking it in!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa bro!
I haven't even done anything yet.
- What have you been doing? (laughter)
- I just did his fur.
- It looks like mold. - What are you doing?
- All of the time is up so you better go quick.
- Okay, wait. Sike! Swap! 15 second bonus.
- 15 seconds, no way! - You have to fix it up!
- Oh my gosh! Eye ball, eye ball, mouth,
and pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink
- Why didn't you finish this sooner dude?
- Dude, why did you switch them like that?
Okay, and done. Well there's that.
Dude, I have no clue how you switched them,
but you get to comment down below who won this round.
I'm just extremely confused right now,
and I guess we're on to the next one
For the final round we're doing a freestyle
- Yep.
- And you're gonna have to figure
out what it is we're making in real time. (laughter)
So right now, let's go.
Alright, so we've got these, boom!
Mine is going to be fan-fl-la-la-ipping-tastic.
(horn sound) Oh yeah. Boom-ba-do-bop-da-bing-bop-boo.
- Oh no.
- Are you messing up?
What are you making?
- Ah, there we go.
- That looks like a giant 'S'.
- For what, Shrek?
Next up is the red. - Oh yeah boy.
If you can figure out what mine is right now
I will be blown away because you don't have
much to go on at all at the moment.
- I am making the border around my 'S'
(grunting)
- Why does it look like lip gloss
and not actually, it doesn't look anything
like frosting at all.
- I just have to fill in the rest.
- Done! (sigh) Alright, there we go.
So, Devan reveal what is yours.
- What did you make, like several brains?
- What? No! Dude mine is like the visor
from ready player one, when he's going through the oasis.
- I made the superman 'S'. - Great!
We're gonna be eating these coming up right now
and you get to comment down below who won this round.
And right now its time to feast on some cup cakes.
Now for the moment you all have been waiting for.
Time to try all these delicious looking cupcakes.
We're going to end with the most beautiful Mario
of all time. Before we eat them
comment down below what are some other characters
you would love to see us make a cupcake version of.
We're beginning with Moana
because there's a lot of different textures.
We've got little pearls on mine, some eyelashes,
some flowers for the hair.
- Some terrible flowers though.
Those were whew! - Yeah
These are going to taste really interesting.
Three, two, one.
- I'm getting half of a flower,
but I'm getting some great cupcake. (clapping)
- Oh yeah.
Oh man this is so good.
- I don't know how I feel - It's so good.
Next up we're going for Pikichu.
- Oh yeah!
- Mine got electrocuted, so my Pikichu looks
absolutely crazy.
- Dude I never really took a good look
at mine, mine looks terrifying.
- He looks mildly disappointed at everything in life.
He's like (whining).
Three, two, one!
(moaning)
- Awe man, uh, uh, uh, I got his eye.
- So, mine taste like a slice of goodness man.
It's just that the cupcake is so soft and nice,
and like fluffy, and then like good sugar.
- This one's a really fluffy cupcake.
- That one's delicious.
Before we eat the Hulk, let's try Jack Jack
because he's kind of like a superhero of sorts.
- This is not Jack Jack bro. - That is so Jack Jack.
- I don't what this is
- I'm gonna get a big bite of the blue.
Ready? Three - Mine is just all black.
- two, one!
(electronic music) (moaning)
(mumbling)
- Alright on to the next one.
- Alright, now it's time to eat my hulk and your iron man.
- Dude, I kind of don't want to eat this.
- It looks absolutely incredible.
But, I definitely won.
Let's go for this, you ready?
I'm gonna take a big bite of his big mouth.
- Oh no! Half of his face came off.
- That's so, how could you do that?
This is a scary look, it's just about
to like bite into this man.
- His mouth looks like a brain again.
Three, two, one!
(moaning)
His eyebrow ahh
Dude you've got it all over your face.
(muffled voice)
You what? Yeah, that's a good idea
to use one of the arms.
- Before Mario, time to eat Chewbacca.
Why did you put so many sprinkles on here?
- That was the whole idea man.
- Alright you ready?
Three, two, one!
- Oh!
(moaning)
Oh my goodness, it's so good.
It has like whole another crunchy flavor to it.
(moaning)
- Great job man. - You did a great job too
(muffled voices)
Really fluffy.
- Now the final one, Mario - Awe Dude!
- So Devan, I'm just gonna eat yours.
I'm gonna take the bottom half, you take the top.
- Click right over here right after this
to see another video, but let's take a bite out of this.
You ready Devan? - Yep, I'm ready.
Alright, here we go.
Three, two, one!
Oh bro! You take a bite out of the other side
and I take one out of this side.
(moaning) (muffled voices)
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Next time. Bye! (Beep)
Dude, you're in my space, Devan.
- I'm sorry
- Mario's been hitting up the barber shop.
- Barber shop.