- What's up? It's Collins Key,
and welcome to the the Thursday vlog. Now for today's video,
I'm stepping outside of my comfort zone,
and I'm gonna be doing my very first ever DIY video.
For those of you guys who don't know the lingo -
Oh, that was so bad (laughs)
DIY stands for "do it yourself."
This video is inspired by my friend, Lucas,
and he did a video where he made his own phone case
out of french fries, which first of all,
was delicious, and also, it was a super funny video,
so if you guys wanna watch that, definitely check it out.
I'm gonna put the link down in the description.
But today, I want to take things to the next level.
So I'm gonna be using two of the Internet's favorite foods,
pizza and donuts, so if you guys love pizza and donuts,
let me know by liking this video.
Also, I want to let you guys know,
I'm doing a huge giveaway this month.
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So if you guys want to win a MacBook computer,
let me know by liking this video, comment down below
what's your favorite video that I've ever posted
and of course, you must be subscribed.
That was way smoother in my head.
You must be subscribed to this channel. Um,
before I mess up anything else in this kitchen,
let's jump right into the video.
To start off, we will make
the pizza phone case and for this,
you only need four items:
item number one is the pizza crust,
number two is the cheese,
number three, pepperoni, and number four, the sauce.
You'd be lost without the sauce.
You need to make sure that all the ingredients
are prepared before you put it in the oven.
That way, when you pull it out, it's immediately ready,
and you can have a steaming hot pizza phone case.
So to open this up, I don't know how we do this.
I think you twist it?
Don't know, I've never done this before.
This is really testing my manhood right here.
Like, low-key, this is really hard!
Maybe if I squeeze it from the side?
Hold on, there are probably instructions on here.
Oh, okay, I found something, this could be helpful.
There's a little thingy over here.
Well that didn't help at all,
and now I just don't know what the instructions -
Oh my gosh!
Holy cow!
What on earth?
I don't know if you guys could hear the pop,
it just, like, exploded.
Wow, okay, well that was unexpected.
So I think we take it to ...
Great, all right, so let's see.
What do you do with dough?
I feel like someone like Gordon Ramsey,
All right guys, so if you're gonna be making this,
you have to put the Pam down first.
So we're just gonna lather this
whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
The perfect beginning to a pizza.
So next, you need the sauce.
My hand's all slippery from the dough.
Ayy, I got it!
Okay, so yeah, now we can take the sauce.
We do the cheese next.
Ooh, this cheese smells funky, okay.
I'm just going to be very delicate.
We need a little bit more on there, there we go.
And last but not least,
we're gonna freckle it with pepperoni.
This pepperoni looks like sliced carrots
that have gone bad right now.
Oh my gosh, okay.
And it smells bad, too.
So, there we go, there you have it.
That is the pizza phone case right there,
and next step is I just need to put this thing in the oven,
so let's see how this goes.
All right, here we go.
We got the pizza.
It's important to have a very low oven as well.
That way, you can, like, crouch all the way down.
It'll be like a squad pic, ayy.
Pizza goes in, and I think we can kinda, just like,
guess-timate on how long these will cook for.
It's getting really hot, I'm gonna close that.
I will see you guys in a few minutes.
- [Voiceover] A few moments later.
(phone alarm sounds)
Oh, okay, I guess the pizza's ready.
Wow, it's really hard to grab things
with these mitts on, okay.
Oh, My face is filled with, like,
just burnt air right now.
Oh my gosh, it looks crazy.
Yo-ho-ho-ho!
Okay, right off the bat, I must say,
I think this was a massive fail,
because I don't think you guys can tell how large
this pizza became in the oven.
But apparently, we're gonna make a phone case out of it.
We've got the pizza, now all I need
is just the phone case to make it happen.
All right, there we go.
It's like magic; so here's how this works,
you just take the phone case, put it on here,
and then I just kinda push down, I believe.
Ow, it's hot, but this might actually work.
We're gonna start to cut away the dough at the sides here.
One side, this is two sides.
Go for this side here.
Just gonna remove the excess dough like that.
This worked!
It worked!
All right guys, round one is a huge success.
Look at that, it worked so well.
This is a legitimate edible phone case right here.
I've been acting super cool like this thing isn't
burning my fingers super bad right now, but it really is.
I'm gonna put it down, but it worked, so yay us!
For the second one, we are creating a donut phone case,
and this is the one that I'm by far the most excited about,
and this is a C.K. original.
I've never seen this anywhere else
on the entirety of the internet.
All you need for this one is just the dough,
you need some sprinkles, I'm gonna try to balance it,
you also need frosting, I'm gonna try to balance them all.
For this one, I'm happy I did not get the same type
of container as the last one, because that one scared me.
This one just popped out, too.
Okay so this dough, if you guys can tell,
is very, very different.
No, the PAM, the PAM!
I keep forgetting to do the PAM.
Take one for the team.
Okay, pooh, it's like a cloud again.
We're just gonna take it right now and we're gonna
plop it on there and then just kinda like the last one.
I'm not gonna comment on what this is.
This is a very special technique right here.
That was pretty good right there.
You need to put it in the oven first
before you put all the other things on top of it.
So right now, my hands are disgusting,
so I'm gonna try to use my arms to grab it,
and I'm gonna put it in the oven.
Hey, it's Collins, and welcome to the Food Network.
You're gonna take your pan just like this,
squat down to the oven, pop a squat, and then insert.
There's a lot of smoke coming out of there, holy cow.
Lot of smoke, I will put that in there
real quick and um, yeah, so, Kitchen 101 on how to cook.
I don't know, we're just gonna find out
what happens when it comes out, guys.
Okay, this is kind of an emergency right now,
because the timer has not gone out,
but we smell burning coming from this thingy over here,
so we're gonna open it up right now and hopefully,
oh god, no, no!
No, no, no, fire alarm's gonna go off, no!
No!
Okay, I got to get this out super quick.
Okay, here we go.
Gonna open this up, ooh, be careful, be careful,
be careful, be careful, okay, ooh,
yeah, okay, y'all, this is burnt!
It's burnt!
I completely burnt this one.
Um, yeah, so this is definitely
a cooking fail for me right there.
This thing is so burnt, but we're gonna try to prevail.
We're gonna see if we can turn it
into an effective donut phone case.
You take the frosting now.
That was unnecessarily difficult to open, man.
Ooh, if I wasn't excited before, this frosting,
this frosting just made me excited.
This looks like happiness right here.
I don't know if it's gonna work,
because this thing is rock solid right now.
When I say rock solid, I mean, like, rock solid.
Like, Dwayne The Rock Johnson of solidness right here.
I think that's enough spreading of, ooh,
spilled a little bit, had to take another hit for the team,
man, got to make sure it doesn't drip on the table.
And now, for the most important part,
That was so weird.
The most important part of any donut,
you need to add a ridiculous amount of sprinkles, so.
So I officially used I would say the majority
of the sprinkles on this, but you know what,
it's all worth it and now, all I need is just another
phone case, so where's it gonna come from?
Yep, just like I anticipated,
this thing is rock solid.
There we go, that worked, alright, cool.
Okay, here we go, for this one, we're just gonna ...
Hey, that actually worked perfectly!
And now, we need to do the staple of every single donut,
which is the hole in the center.
No! I think I just cracked the whole thing open.
Did I do it?
Yeah! I made a hole in the donut.
The donut didn't quite turn out how I expected.
I think the fact that I literally burnt the whole thing
terribly did not help out the entire process.
And you know, this one didn't turn out to look so pretty,
but hopefully, it tastes pretty good,
so I'm gonna give it a taste test right now.
Ow, it's like rock solid.
If you guys wanna see another crazy DIY video,
let me know by liking this video,
and if this video gets enough likes, then you know what,
I might try another crazy DIY just like this.
I can't even snap, there's stuff on my fingers.
Insert snap sound here.