(driving electronic music)
- Have you ever stuffed your face with so much ice cream
that it gave you a brain freeze?
Well today, we're turning just everyday foods
into the ultimate brain freeze with liquid nitrogen.
And I asked you guys on Instagram,
"What are some crazy foods you would love to see me freeze"
"and then smash with a hammer?"
So, right now, let's do it.
We're kicking it off with some Peeps, y'all!
(crickets chirping)
Let's just forget I ever did that.
And how this works, there are three steps to it.
Step one, we're gonna place a normal Peep down
and then smash it.
Step two, we're gonna take another Peep,
deep freeze it, and then step three,
place it down and then smash the deep freezed Peep.
Let's peep this out.
(laughing) I can't do that.
That's like some random food channels line.
No one's gonna get that reference, but Devin w...
Let's, let's go.
It's time to choose the sacrificial Peep.
I choose, this one right...
Here we go, step one, smash the normal Peep.
(hammer bang)
Turn it like a Peep pancake.
(upbeat music)
Let's see what happens when we deep freeze it.
Alright so I'm using this dipper right here
to get the liquid nitrogen,
and we're gonna dump it on the Peep to deep freeze it.
So this is going to take some accuracy,
see if I can get it.
(upbeat music)
It's like sizzling off the...
It's cracking!
Alright here we go, round two.
This stuff is hitting the table, this stuff is crazy,
this stuff is super dangerous by the way,
so if you ever do this, make sure
you do it with parental supervision.
(chuckles)
This looks crazy,
oh I want to like touch it.
It's s... you can hear it cracking,
it is solid right now!
This is crazy, I'm gonna do one more round.
I feel so bad man, this Peep, rest in peace bro.
No, rest in peep, hah.
But before we smash the frozen one, I've got a challenge.
I want to see if you can subscribe to this channel,
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you can do that, comment down below "Keyper Squad".
Right now, we're smashing it.
Three, two, one, (hammer bang)
That was crazy, that was so cool!
I am lit, that was so sick!
Alright, next one here we go.
(gentle upbeat music)
Shoutout to everyone who suggested
one of my favorite foods, sushi.
So, we're gonna be freezing this stuff,
we're also gonna be smashing regular,
and then of course,
going to be eating the stuff (laughs)
Let's go.
This one hits home, (hammer bang)
(ghasps)
(upbeat music)
Out of all the ones I did not expect
to blow up all over me, it was my friend sushi!
So this piece here looks like the most colorful one,
so we're gonna do this one.
This feels like you're at an expensive restaurant,
and like you know when you see them
doing crazy things with the food,
like using blow torches and stuff.
This feels like something you would see
in an expensive restaurant.
They're like "Oh you want your sushi a little bit colder?"
And then's like (hisses)
(playful music)
Huh, it's making me sneeze.
(sneezes) (air horn)
So here's what's gonna happen,
I'm actually, I'm gonna tilt this back...
Oh my gosh, it's like half frozen.
The bottom is rock solid frozen,
but the top, the top is not cooperating.
Come on sushi, you supposed to be my best friend.
(funk music)
Aw, spicy!
The sushi is proving to be a lot more difficult
than I initially anticipated.
So right now, we're actually going to take
the whole thing, and submerge it in the liquid nitrogen.
No more of this foo-foo little drizzling.
You know things are getting extreme,
when the camo glasses come out.
Whoa, the whole world is very yellow at the moment.
Alright, we're gonna dump this whole thing.
Here we go, (laughs menacingly)
yes, it's not heavy at all, okay.
Alright here we go, this is super dangerous.
(funk music)
Oh my gosh.
Alright here we go.
I would use chopsticks, but you know what,
now is not the time for tradition.
It's not coming off, it's frozen.
We're going with this piece!
(funk music)
It's in there guys.
We're making a delicacy right now,
the sushi is in there, in the liquid nitrogen.
It's a frozen block!
It's literally a frozen block!
Alright guys, time to smash it.
Three, two, one (hammer bang)
(tropical music)
That one...
Ah, that scratched my eye on the way out.
Who ever knew the safety glasses
would be the most dangerous part
of that whole operation right there (laughs)
Let's do the next one.
I've been instructed I'm not allowed to touch the donuts,
because they're afraid I'm gonna eat it.
I doe-nut know why, (buzzer)
nope that's bad.
Alright right now, it's time to smash a donut, let's do it.
This one might be kind of graphic,
you may wanna look away.
(hammer bangs)
Okay, I thought this one was gonna blow up and go crazy,
but it just literally just like flattened.
Let's see what happens with a frozen one.
Alright we've got the tongs right now,
the donut is going into the liquid nitrogen.
(sizzling)
Oh my gosh, it's floating!
This thing is like floating on it man.
I gotta submerge it, submerge, go submarine mode (chuckles)
It's a submarine donut!
Here we go, three, two, one (hammer bangs)
(upbeat dramatic music)
The hammer's like smoking!
Aw I love this stuff man.
That sounded like glass breaking,
like for a second I was like oh my gosh,
I'm about to get hit with like a shard of glass donut.
It makes no sense, I'm hyped, this is crazy!
(upbeat dramatic music)
Let's go to the next one.
Next up we are freezing and smashing Oreos.
(cheerful music)
- [Woman Off Screen] Hey, we need that for the video!
- Here we go, (dramatic music)
I literally just thought a piece of this flew off,
into the liquid nitrogen container.
Luckily it's closed, we're all good.
Otherwise it could have erupted, I don't know.
So let's now freeze it, and see what happens.
We're using the different technique again for this Oreo.
(funk music)
Like this stuff just sizzles,
which is the craziest thing about it.
Let's smash this Oreo!
Three, two, one (hammer bang) (bullet rebounding)
Oh, what!
Look at this, it didn't even break!
What, I am smashing this again fam!
What is going on!
(dramatic music)
Attempt number two, let's do this.
(hammer bangs) (bullet rebounding)
(laughs)
(dramatic music)
Not a pickle in a bag.
But it'll do.
You have to eat a pickle in a bag.
Alright here we go.
Oh no, it's already getting juicy (groans)
I hate the small of pickles (groans)
I smell like pickles y'all.
I don't even want to do this.
It feels like a messy challenge all over again.
It's like pickle, just, just nastiness! (gibberish)
- [Woman Off Screen] Eww, it's like jelly!
- Oh, it's in my eyeball!
Oh that burns, that burns a lot!
Here we go, three, two, one.
Oh no, I can't believe it didn't do anything.
I guess we'll have to freeze it.
No I can't, I can't do that.
We gotta go for it. (hammer bangs)
(groans)
(dramatic music)
I got pickle all over me!
Alright let's freeze it.
It looks like just like bird poo just (squirts with mouth)
(chuckles) Now this, is what you call a juicy pickle.
Here we go, oh I need my... (chuckles)
Almost put that in without my glove.
That woulda been very bad!
Okay, the juciest of all pickles.
Yo, this is so wild!
There's almost like a, I don't know how to describe it,
there's like a layer of mist over the top of it.
But you can't see it, but the moment the pickle
gets close to it, look at this.
It like envelopes the pickle.
You see that, look.
It's like a layer over the top of it.
I'm sure there's like scientific reason for it,
but that's wild.
Alright here we go, we're gonna plop the pickle in.
I can't see the pickle man.
You know what, there's just not enough
liquid nitrogen in there,
we've gotta fill it up a little more.
Yeah.
Pickles been in there for quite a little while,
we've got the hammer right now, and let's pull it out.
It's actually cracked!
Look at this.
Can you see, like it's got a crack
right along it right there.
This is gonna be explosive.
Here we go, three, two, one (smash) (shattering)
(dramatic music)
That one sounded like glass shattering.
This one is the most popular item you guys suggested,
it's a piece...
a piece, of pizza.
Sorry, no more uh, cheesy jokes. (percussive sting)
Get it, 'cause it's a cheese p...
I'm not looking forward to this one.
This is gonna go everywhere.
Three two one (hammer bangs)
that was it? (hammer bangs) (hammer bangs)
(upbeat music)
Hey guys, it looks like a topographical map of Utah,
Haha jokes, dad jokes.
For those of you who are pizza lovers,
this might be hard to watch.
(upbeat music)
So that's just like just a part of it,
and you can already tell the difference.
Like it's rock solid.
Wait, we're gonna go with the whole piece of pizza in there.
Ooh man, it's sizzling.
The moment it touches it,
the whole consistency of it is completely changes.
This no longer feels like a piece of pizza,
it feels like a slab of rock.
(grinding)
Listen to that sound, crazy!
Alright, time to smash it.
Here we go.
(hammer bangs) (hammer bangs)
(tropical music)
Okay before I go for this last one,
it is just shattered.
Come here, look at this.
Like the cheese actually shattered on it.
Like I can kinda pick it up a little bit.
It looks crazy!
Like the whole thing is just kinda broken apart.
I'm gonna give it one final smash right now.
There's a big one, here we go.
Three, two, don't want to break the plate, one.
(hammer smashes) (chuckles)
Yeah, that was cool.
(upbeat strumming music)
Have you ever seen those commercials
where they try to make eating a burger
look like the hottest thing on the entire planet?
Well right now, we're not gonna do that.
This is gonna be the exact opposite of that.
Like after this, no one is gonna wanna eat this burger.
So, (hammer bangs)
(dramatic music)
This here, has got icicles like all the way around it now.
And this side you can kinda like scoop it off,
it looks like snow almost.
So right now, the camo glasses are going back on.
We're about to fill it up again,
and this burger's going down.
Here we go, the moment of truth.
About to pop the burger into the liquid nitrogen.
Oh man, it's going everywhere.
Okay
So the burger's in, I gotta keep it together,
so I gotta push it down quickly.
What's happening, I can't see it,
my glasses are like impeding my vision,
and I'm like everything's so yellow!
I can't tell where the burger's at anymore.
It's having a crazy reaction,
this one by far the craziest.
Hopefully, the burger will freeze.
This one's the most difficult though,
because there's so many layers to what's going on.
Like the burger just has a ton of different layers,
and so I don't know if it's gonna be able to
freeze through every single layer.
So I'm gonna keep this one in here
longer than I normally would.
Well the cheese is definitely no longer melted,
that's for sure.
In case you guys ever wanted to know,
this is the secret recipe for the Krabby Patty.
Y'all didn't even know,
liquid nitrogen was the key all along.
(cracking)
(upbeat music)
It's literally cracking!
Alright, here we go,
three, two, one.
(hammer bangs) (laughs)
(dramatic music)
It's like a magic trick man!
It's just gone!
Well there's a chunk of it over here.
Woo, woo, woo.
It's like so cold, it's so hot right now.
That makes no sense, but if you touch this,
you can feel it even through these gloves,
like it's like a burn on your finger.
(upbeat music)
Really guys, eggs?
You know I don't like messy videos.
(screeching)
Nunununo, no, no, no!
(chuckles)
This is gonna be so bad.
I'm doing this for you, here we go.
Three, oh no, two, one. (hammer smashes)
I'm good, it didn't touch me at all!
Alright cool, next one let's go (lightly chuckles)
(upbeat music)
Here we go.
(laughs)
I gotta say, I'm very grateful that I still
have a face at the moment,
because that slipped, and you saw that stuff
shoot out everywhere.
(slow motion laughing)
And if that were to touch my skin,
that would burn my skin, and my skin would instantly die.
All's well that ends well.
The coolest thing, is that when it fell in there
it actually cracked.
And look at it, it's like the opposite of scrambled eggs.
So guys, we're gonna put a full one in. (groans)
So guys, we're gonna put a full one in there now,
just so we know what like,
the whole egg will actually look like.
Alright, so the full egg actually cracked
while it was inside.
So I don't know what kind of effect that will have.
We're gonna do this one first,
and then next we're gonna do this mutant egg.
The craziest thing about this one,
is that it cracked, but the shell stayed intact,
but only the egg whites actually came out of the egg,
but the shell it's still full intact.
Here we go, three, two, one. (hammer bangs)
(upbeat music)
Oh my gosh, literally powderized it.
We're going for egg number two right now,
here we go guys, the mutant egg.
Three, (chuckles) two, one. (hammer smashes) (crunching)
(upbeat music)
It's literally just powder.
So I don't think I've ever seen eggs
prepared in this particular fashion before.
(upbeat music)
You guys suggested Twinkies,
I suggest I do it like Salt Bae.
So let's see what happens.
You guys, I'm not excited about this one.
This, is gonna be juicy.
Here we go.
(hammer bangs)
(Illuminati music)
(digital music)
(hammer banging)
This experiment has been so full of surprises,
like the ones you'd expect to just explode everywhere,
have done nothing, and then the ones
that just came out of no where, sushi.
Why would the sushi go everywhere,
but the Twinkie filling inside of it would not.
It's actually stuck to the just ta... it's just.
(bangs on table)
I don't know what to say.
Everyone say goodbye to the Twinkie.
Here we go, making the plunge. (sizzling)
Whoa, hold up.
My tongs, got stuck to it.
Alright I'm gonna have to use a different Twinkie,
this thing is just woo, messed up.
I'm just gonna have to like, kinda like plop it in.
Very safely.
Wanna go far away from it, here we go.
Three, two, one, here we go, ooh.
The Twinkie's just like, floating along the surface.
Alright, so it's kinda sinking in a little bit,
I'm gonna try to like rotate it.
Flip it upside down would be like ideal,
oh okay there we go, yep.
The first time we did this, nothing happened.
This time, after it's been frozen, here we go.
About to smash it, and then eat it.
But first, I need your help.
If you want to be featured in my next video,
comment down below what my brother and I
should do in sumo suits.
Yes, we're gonna be rocking sumo suits.
Also, the Keyper of the week, is Devon.
If you wanna be the Keyper of the week,
all you have to do, is just check out
the description down below,
that way you can be featured in my next video.
But right now, here we go.
About to smash it, and then we're gonna be eating it.
Here we go, three, two, one. (hammer banging) (cracking)
(laughing)
That was crazy!
(slow dramatic music)
Alright here we go,
oh there's a chunk right here.
Alright here we go, three two one. (crunching)
Aw brain freeze, brain freeze, brain freeze, aw man.