- What's up guys?
It is Collins Key, and welcome to the Thursday Vlog.
That's by far my favorite intro I've ever done ever
ever to a Thursday Vlog.
(techno music)
Now, for today's video I want to do something
that I haven't done in quite awhile,
and also I'd love for you guys to find out new, cool,
and fun things about me.
Today I'm going to be doing a "Ask Collins Key."
(whoosh sound)
And you guys sent me a ton of questions with the
#askcollinskey, and we actually trended worldwide,
which is absolutely insane.
Power to the keypers. You guys are amazing.
And reading off all the questions for you guys is
gonna be my alter ego Joseph.
"Are you the real Slim Shady?"
I think the question really should be
"Will the real Slim Shady please stand up."
(hip hop music)
"Uh. I'm gonna stand up cause I'm the real Slim Shady y'all.
Oh. Oh."
Just kidding Dad. It's me, Joseph.
Ha. Swag.
"How excited are you for Christmas?"
Yeah. Woo. Woo hoo.
Oh yeah. Woo.
Turn it up. It's a Christmas tree.
I found, a Christmas tree.
So, yeah.
I guess you could say I'm a little bit
excited for Christmas.
"Are you a night person or morning person?"
Well, that one's easy. I'm definitely a night person.
"If you were a burger,
what part of the burger would you be?"
The most important part. The buns.
"Sum up life in one sentence."
Waffles.
That's a pancake, and it's frozen. Perfect. (chuckles)
"Are you going to release a magic video soon."
Yes. There's gonna be a ton of new magic videos comin
out very soon, and I kind of want to take a little bit
of time to refresh my material so I can bring you guys
new magic with new people and new, crazy reactions.
Hit the thumbs up button if you guys are excited for
a lot more magic videos comin up in the new year.
"Have you ever picked your nose in public?"
Probably, when I was a little kid.
But, the one time where I got called out on it,
like I was in a class and the teacher was all like
"Collins. Stop picking your nose."
And I was just like, "Huh?"
"Do you curse?"
No flipping way. I don't use freaking gosh dang cuss words.
I keep it clean.
You know, I'm all like "Mustard on the beat, yo."
"Can I hug attack you if I ever get to meet you?"
Yeah, for sure, like whenever you guys meet me feel
free to like jump, tackle, hug me.
It's really fun and...
Yeah. I just love meeting you guys in general.
"Justin Timberlake concert or Eminem concert?"
I love both of these artists, but if I had to choose,
I would probably pick an Eminem concert because
"I'm the real Slim Shady yo." (hip hop music)
Just kidding guys. It's still Joseph.
Swag. (giggles)
"How many times do you blink a day?"
Well, during the day I don't think I blink that much,
but if I had to guess I would have to say maybe like
5 or 6 times during the day.
"Can you say yes to this question?"
Um, sure. Yeah.
I will not answer this question. That's a no.
"I really wanted to watch your live streaming magic
show, but I am so broke."
The live streaming magic show was so much fun.
It was insane.
And I'm definitely planning on doing a lot more
of those coming up here in the new year.
And I was really bummed to find out that some of you guys
couldn't make it to the show because you guys said
you had no money.
So, afterwards I spent quite awhile researching and
trying to find easy ways for you guys to make some money,
and I came across this website called opinionoutpost.com.
And it's like, it's super cool.
Like, literally all you have to do is you take opinion-based
surveys and they give you cash and gift cards.
Anyone can sign up.
So I'm gonna put the link down in the description,
so be sure and click that link right now.
Just a cool website for you guys to check out.
"What's 9 + 10?"
21. (small child's voice)
Wait, wait. Didn't someone just ask that question?
I can't use the same joke twice.
Next question.
"How old is Devan?"
Devin is 21. (small child's voice)
Okay, I'm really done with that joke. Let's move on.
I'm gonna be dropping my first rap album coming up here
very soon, but I want to make sure it's really good because
"You've only got one shot. Do not miss your chance to blow.
This opportunity comes once in a lifetime yo." (rap singing)
Oh. Hey guys. It's, uh still Joseph.
Swag.
"What is your favorite thing about your keypers?"
I love how you guys are always so supportive.
And not only supportive of me, but like
supportive of each other.
And you guys are always quick to bring in new keypers
and tell your friends about the family.
"What type of styles do you like on girls?"
I don't know.
I think it's something that's really up to you.
Whatever you feel confident and good in.
I think that's what you should wear because it comes across.
Oh, but there is one thing.
When girls, wear like those high socks. Haaah...
"You gotta bae or naw?"
One hundred percent single right now.
No bae for the holidays. Oh. Turn up.
"If you had to change your hair color what
would you change it to?"
When I was on tour with Demi,
like every day she would come to me and be like
"Hey Collins, you want to dye your hair today?"
And I was like "I don't know what to dye it to."
I'd probably go with, like, dark blue.
"Who is your favorite rapper?"
I mean, well you guys, you guys already know what
I'm gonna answer for this.
Chief Keef. Just kidding.
"It's Slim Shady y'all. What'd you even think.
Uh ha, uh ha." (hip hop music)
It's still Joseph. Still Joseph. Swag.
"Can you make this your last question?"
Sorry, I can't.
And that is our last question for this video.
If you guys enjoyed it, be sure to give it huge thumbs up.
And also, if you have anymore questions for me let me
know what they are in the comments down below.
Make sure you guys check out opinionoutpost.com.
Again, the link is in my description.
And, also subscribe to this channel.
I'll see you guys next week. Peace.
Whoa! (chuckles)
Hi guys. It's Joseph again. Just always...
Swag.