- What's up, it's Collins Key
and for today's video I'm doing something
no one should ever do.
I'm gonna be boiling a brand new
iPhone Seven in Coca-Cola.
Now, the reason I'm doing this is
because I want to test once and for all
Number one, is this phone really
water resistant?
Is it Coca-Cola resistant?
And is it boiling Coca-Cola resistant?
I'm really excited because I'm giving away
an iPhone Seven right now on my Instagram
so if you want to win it all you have to do is
follow me on Instagram,
turn on my Instagram post notifications,
and be active.
The rest of the rules are down
in the description below.
I'm also giving away
a drone on YouTube, a GoPro on Twitter,
all the rules for those giveaways
are down in the description below.
And if you want me to boil even more things
in the future, give this video a big thumbs up
and if this video gets enough thumbs up,
then I will do some crazy videos coming up,
and comment down below what should I boil
in a future video.
And also this video is inspired by Guava Juice
who boils a whole bunch of crazy toys all the time.
I'm going to put a link to his video
down in the description below,
so be sure to go check that out.
But right now, it's time to unbox this iPhone Seven.
So, first things first we don't need this bag.
Yeet.
Alright, so let's open this thing up.
So, first things first you pull of this here.
Yup. Oh, it's nice.
Alright, here we go.
The moment of truth.
Oh! No!
That was not good right there.
So, we're going to remove the protective plastic.
Alright, here we go.
So we're turning it on right now.
Wanna make sure you guys can see.
This is a real working iPhone.
Now, it's the very important part
where we get to set up the passcode
on the phone.
So this is a very difficult passcode,
no one will ever break this.
(taps)
Apparently, Apple suggests you do not even
use this passcode.
Good to go.
Nope, we have absent data.
Man, this takes quite a while to set up.
Let me go through this, and then once
I've got the whole phone set up
then we'll go to the next part.
There's one more setting I'm going to enable right now,
and that is send diagnostics to Apple
whenever this phone crashes.
And then Apple will do the whole data report
trying to figure out how it crashed, so.
I'm going to see what Apple has to say
about boiling Coke being the reason this phone crashed.
So the phone, as you guys can see, is fully working.
Oh, I have a free text message!
Oh, another text.
Wow, I'm getting a lot of text messages.
Can't let you guys see these private text messages
I'm receiving on my brand new phone.
I don't even know how that happens,
how is this working?
So, as you guys can see, the camera works,
let's take a couple of pictures.
Ayyy!
Ohhh!
Snap!
Selfie, ayy!
Yo, this camera quality is awesome!
So, as you guys can see this is a fully working.
Oh, how does it work?
Wait, wait, no, back, whoa!
What the heck?
No, no, no, no.
Okay.
So, what's gonna happen right now,
I think next we're going to boil the Coca-Cola,
and then stick this beauty inside.
It's so beautiful and so clean, so pristine right now,
and it's about to get bad.
So, here we go.
We've got all the Coca-Cola.
We're going to be adding it into this
clear pot right here, because I want to make sure
you guys can see exactly what's happening
at all times during this.
Know what I mean?
Gonna put it on.
There we go!
So, I just kinda shook that one up a little bit
so I'm gonna start with one of these here.
Hopefully it doesn't explode everywhere.
(explosion)
(cracks)
Okay, we're off to a good start.
Let's see.
Gonna add this in.
I don't know what's supposed to happen, either.
So this is going to be a learning experience for all of us.
(fizzes)
So far it seems like, pretty normal.
Like, nothing's really crazy happening.
(foreboding music)
Okay, it's kinda starting to smell a little bit funny now.
Actually, it kinda smells good.
I like the smell of it.
So, at the moment, the smell of it's nice.
(foreboding music) (coughs)
Think we should add one more can.
Alright, so that's about halfway filled up.
I don't know what's going to happen.
This stuff could just bubble up and explode.
What is going on!?
- I have no idea what's going to happen.
So, I think that this is good.
Do we just leave it I guess?
Talk to you guys in a little bit.
(cheerful piano music)
(record scratch)
Alright. Sorry, just checking my temperature
here with my ther, ther, ther.
(beeps)
So, I was just informed that it's actually called
a thermometer.
My apologies.
So, I'm going to check right now the temperature
of the Coca-Cola.
So, I'm going to turn this on.
Here we go, gonna place it in here.
I think I broke it, 'cause it's no longer working.
Hello?
Oh, okay.
175 degrees.
I probably shouldn't touch it with my tongue.
Probably a very bad idea.
So, it's starting to heat up now, I'm going to leave this.
Actually, you know what?
There we go.
Leave that in there.
(beeps)
Tada!
So, right now, as you guys can tell,
there's a very light steam coming off of it.
Ow, geez.
Retrieve it, okay.
(laughs)
We're good.
Alright, so I think I'm going to check the temperature
right now with the charging device for the iPhone,
because I think that's a very accurate way
to see if it's really
if it's really ready.
How many things are on this?
So, we'll take the USB end of what's going on.
Oh, yeah, that's testing nicely.
It's a great test we're accomplishing right now.
I think it's ready.
(laughs)
And from the looks of things
it's not quite there yet.
We're gonna have to wait a little bit longer.
You guys, I learned from my mistakes.
Here we go.
Oh, no, no!
Oh, that's hot!
Hot.
Alright, here we go, the moment of truth.
Time to put the brand new iPhone Seven
in the Coca-Cola.
Now, I had to move it over on the burners
because this one was just way too small.
This one's making it go a lot quicker.
But, here we go.
I want to show you guys one last time.
Going to put in the super secret passcode.
(dings)
One more time, I'm gonna show you guys.
Actually, oh!
I'm gonna record this whole thing.
Yo, what's up guys! We are about to put
the iPhone Seven in the Coca-Cola.
So, here we go.
Alright, let's see how this works.
Gonna put this in the tongs over here.
Check this out.
Here we go.
Oh!
So I'm just gonna say it right now,
I do not think the iPhone is going to survive this at all.
Oh my gosh.
I wonder if it's still recording at all?
That would be crazy.
I think I put it in wrong.
I think it's recording towards the bottom.
I wanted to record towards the top of the.
If it is recording, it's gonna be.
Let me see really quick.
How do I?
Where'd the phone go?
Uh-oh.
It turned off.
That's not a good sign.
Alright. We'll turn it up like this.
So, hopefully it's still recording.
(cheerful piano music)
Right now, I'm going to drop everyone's favorite part
of the new iPhone Seven into the Coca-Cola.
And that is the dongle.
Here we go.
Oh, that just splashed on me!
That was hot!
As well as the dongle in there, let's just add in
the charging port, let's put in the charging cord
a little bit.
And then while we're at it, we might as well add in
these new headphones. Just make sure we get those
all in there.
Give it a nice little mix in there.
Make sure we get all those Apple products
well into the Coca-Cola.
Oh, look, the phone's looking nicely.
Let's kinda flip it over.
It's like we're making an Apple pasta right now.
That makes no sense, but yeah.
It's kinda like Apple pasta at the moment.
It's all browning around it, that's because
the sugar's really helping it all come together
and cook very nicely.
Okay, so this stuff has been boiling in here
for upwards of twenty minutes right now.
So, I think it's time to pull it out
and check to see if this phone really works.
We'll have a strainer, I also have a larger pot.
How am I gonna do this?
We're gonna go larger pot right here.
Put on my safety glove.
And let's see what happens.
- [Narrator] Two hours later.
(beeps)
- Yo, Collins, look at this!
Come here!
Dude!
Oh, that's hot, that's hot, that's hot, that's hot!
(fire alarm beeps)
Oh my gosh.
Alright, guys, I was not happy with how that video ended
and so I've actually taken this home.
I boiled this for two hours.
The iPhone is in here right now.
This thing is just burning.
I don't know what's going on.
My mom's gonna be so mad, I just ruined her pot.
This is horrible.
What do we do?
I need some tongs.
Oh my god, no!
What?
What is this?
Can I pick it up?
(screaming)
It's hot!
My eyes are burning.
Oh my gosh, okay, hold up.
Give me the tongs.
Throw me some tongs.
Okay, here we go.
Oh my gosh.
The Coca-Cola like boiled.
What is this?
Come on in close.
Yo, what is this?
This thing got wrecked!
Oh my God!
Yo, is it on fire?
That thing is on, what is going on?
(coughs)
(hisses)
Oh my gosh, okay!
That got real crazy.
Oh my gosh.
Yo, my mom is gonna be so mad.
This was her favorite pot, and now.
This thing is absolutely ruined.
Wait, hold on.
I want to see what happened to the phone.
Yo, what?
Look at this. It literally broke the screen off of it.
(rewind sound)
If the iPhone works after this I will be amazed.
Okay, here we go.
It's a crackling.
Alright, guys, here we go.
The moment of truth.
Time to check out the iPhone.
Let me grab it out of here.
What?
It's not even damaged at all.
This is crazy.
Oh my gosh it's hot!
I can't hold it properly, but I want to show you guys-
Look at this.
It's not even really damaged.
It really is water resistant.
So, now here's the moment of truth.
Does this thing really turn on?
I can't hold it.
It's literally the boiling and it's very hot right now.
How do I even open this without burning my fingers off?
Because it is.
I'm pretty positive this phone did not survive,
but how do I turn this on?
I'm gonna press the power button right over here, let's see.
Beside the fact that this phone is now a little bit sticky,
that's the only possible damage.
And I don't think, nope.
The phone doesn't turn on, guys.
Well, maybe it's just a key lock on it.
Maybe it actually is dead.
But thank you guys so much for watching,
and I will see you guys.
(gasps)
It's actually really sharp, too.
So there you guys have it
Please give this video a thumbs up for the fact
that I went all the way and really did it.
Like, to the max.
And also, if this video gets enough thumbs up
then I will do another one of these boiling videos.
But, for right now.
I gotta figure out how to clean this up.
Alright, bye.
(sad piano music)
(upbeat techno music)