- What's up, it's Collins Key. Now today I am doing the
1000 degree glowing knife experiment.
I've seen this thing all over YouTube
and it looks like an absolutely blast.
I'm not sure who started it,
the first person I saw was Mr. Gear.
But right now, before we get into this,
I've got a challenge for you.
I wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on channel post notifications in five seconds.
Here we go, you ready for this?
Five, four, three, two, one,
done.
If you could do that comment down below, "Keyper Squad."
And if you wanna see me cut 4,000 matches with a glowing
hot knife that video is live on my instagram.
The direct link to it is down in the description below
and if you liked that video and comment on it "Keyper Squad"
I'll be doing through, Dming a ton of you,
and one final thing.
If you can translate this video, that would really mean
a lot to me.
I wanna make sure keypers from around the world can enjoy.
The direct link to translate is down in the description
below.
Also, you'll get credit in the description link.
Your name in the description if you translate this video,
but right now, without further ado, let's get into this,
and this is the 1,000 degree glowing hot knife experiment.
♫ Three, two, one, go!
(dubstep electronic music)
- First things first, we need to heat this knife up to
1,000 degrees.
Get it glowing and then we can start cutting stuff, so here
we go.
I'm just messing with you guys!
Yieeeek!
Let go.
♫ Three, two, one, go!
(dubstep electronica)
♫ Go!
♫ Three, two, one!
- So basically I just went around my entire house,
found a whole bunch of different random objects,
hopefully they weren't too expensive.
We're kickin' it off right now, this is a giant
jawbreaker left over from a sour video Devon and I did,
so right now let's cut it open and see what happens.
(torch hisses)
All right guys, here we go.
Check this out.
Whoa, that can't be good to breathe that in.
It's literally cutting this thing open, it's crazy.
Next up, I grab this flint stuff right here and basically
use this to start a fire, so you go like this.
So let's just see what happens.
(clink)
Awwwwwe!
(grating sound)
Well, we gave it a shot.
Next up, I grabbed a rubber band ball
So let's see what happens.
(beep)
(fire crackling)
(alarm sounds)
What do we do?
Well, this did not go according to plan.
It's just burnt.
It's just toxic.
Like I don't know what to,
I've never been in this situation before.
Oh man, this is terrible.
Ahhhhhh!
All right, guys this is cookin' with Collins.
This is some filet mignon.
See it's so.
HOT!
All right, guys, playtime is over.
Or not.
Just look at how ruined this thing got, bro.
This used to be copper!
(fire extinguisher hisses)
Well, that did not go according to plan.
At all.
And I just ruined another one of my mom's favorite pots.
So, luckily, she's got another one though.
Yiiikes!
Next up, I've got AXE, but instead of cutting this with a
knife, I'm gonna be cutting this with.
You guessed it.
An actual axe!
All right guys, let's look at the cast iron.
Oh my god!
The axe is on fire guys!
Dude, the axe is actually on fire!
(dubstep electronica)
Okay, that was pretty awesome.
Like I said, I've just been grabbing a whole bunch of random
stuff from around the house.
I've found that mom has some like bath bombs, and like,
I don't even know what this is, so I'm gonna cut these
open, see what happens, hopefully it's not a bomb,
it doesn't explode, and it smells.
It smells nice.
(torch hisses)
All right guys, here we go, check this out.
Ohhhhh! I did it!
Yeah!
It wasn't like satisfying.
It wasn't cool, but I made it through.
I found this funky lookin' one, so let's give this
one a shot.
Have I mentioned how much I love these blow torches?
All right guys, one chance.
One take.
Let's get this all the way through.
(electronica)
I did it!
That was super satisfying.
I don't know if it was satisfying for you.
But it was satisfying for me.
I'm gonna try this again.
Here we go.
Next up, I found our entire stash of crayons
(children yell in excitement)
So, I'm really excited to see what this one looks like.
Hopefully, it like goes everywhere and turns into, like, a
really cool artwork piece, but I guess we'll just find out.
(torch hisses)
Ohhhh, this is crazy.
Whoa.
This stuff is all so flammable, man.
All right, guys, imma separate the stacks now, 'cause
like it's too hard to cut through whole stacks at the
same time.
But now we're just gonna see if I can cut through one stack
all the way through.
There's a ton of smoke coming out.
This thing is actually on fire right now.
So let's just go.
Here we go.
Oohhhhh!
(whistling)
Well, I know we made it through one box now, now let's see
if we can make it through all the boxes,
I think we made it through the second box.
It's literally shooting wax everywhere right now.
This is crazy.
All right, here we go.
I'm gonna do this one final.
Oh my gosh! Actually.
(blows repeatedly)
Like I said, I'm gonna do this one last time.
But this time I'm gonna touch it to the front of all these
different crayons right now, and just see
how melted they get.
So let's just do this.
(electronic intstrumental)
You literally can just like slice right through the crayons.
This is crazy.
Oh this thing is just a mess.
I don't think you guys can see this.
But just look at this.
They're actually getting pretty melted in here.
I wanna see this box.
What do I like more than burning things on fire than
even the hot knife challenge, 'cause that's like pretty
much all this is.
Just a lot of stuff, on fire,
the entire time.
And the boxes, man.
This is on fire.
All right, guys, so next up we've got right here.
The pig.
Now this is my dad's favorite item.
And listen to this.
(pig hums pop goes the weasel)
So we're gonna cut it open!
Sorry, dad.
(pig hums pop goes the weasel)
(distorted humming continues, fades)
Let's see if it still works.
Noooooo!
The pig is gone!
Ohhh, that's hot.
And there's smoke in my face!
I think that's all we're gonna get outta it.
And now it's time.
To cut the cheese.
(classical music plays, pauses abruptly)
I'm sorry.
(classical music resumes)
Ohhhhh, this is horrible.
Imagine, like, a grilled cheese, but just gone wrong.
It just sinks into the cheese.
Trust me, it's awful.
(horn honks)
All right guys, I've learned my lesson.
I'm still gonna use my mom's pan, but this time imma put
aluminium foil around it, that way, hopefully it doesn't get
as ruined.
Now we've got this bouncy ball right here.
Which has, like, a fish inside of it.
So, I don't really know what this thing does, or why it's
in our house, but
(laughs)
we're gonna do it so,
That was cool
(torch hisses)
(knife sizzles)
AWWWWWWWWWWW!!
AWWEEE!
I hope this stuff isn't toxic!
Because, uh, it just shot all in my eye.
Ow.
(beep)
Well, I learned from my mistakes.
No longer will I get water in my eye.
So basically, I froze a coca cola bottle, a glass bottle.
I'm gonna be hitting it with a hot knife.
I'm guessing it's going to explode, so I'm takin every
precaution.
I've got like a hazmat suit on.
I've got my awesome welder's mask on too
and we're just gonna see what happens.
(torch hisses)
(bottle clinks)
(beep)
(laughs)
Yeah, I don't know what to do.
Well, there goes my axe, and I guess there goes
whatever was supposed to happen there.
Yay.
This is crazy.
The axe is so hot when the head of it fell off, it
literally just melted through the table.
I didn't know what was going on, I just heard a clunk.
Check this out.
Look! Look down there, look down there!
It literally melted through the table.
Fam, this video is LIT.
With this wood, I went through the bathroom, grabbed a whole
bunch of bars of soap, and I want you guys to guess which
soap bar belongs to which family member, so we've got
the Dial one, we have Olay, and then we have Irish Spring.
I'll give you a little hint on that one.
(laughs)
So let's cut them open.
Can we do it, Irish Spring?
Make a way, laddie.
(laughs) We did it!
A lot of you guys know my brother, Devon, has really awesome
hair and the secret to it, is this stuff right here.
This is his hair gel.
It's got a "D" on it, stands for Devon, so hopefully he
doesn't need this, so we're gonna cut this open, see
what happens, and yeah.
(knife sizzles)
(laughs)
Is it ruined?
Devon, whatever you're using, this stuff
smells delicious, bro.
If I look, it burned my hand through these professional
welding gloves.
So if you guys wanna know how hot this knife is, it's so
hot.
This is a professional welders glove, and it just burned my
hand through this, so I'm gonna give this one more chop.
(knife chops)
(knife sizzles)
Yo, the gel is literally shooting out every.
Oh my gosh!
It's getting all over me, man.
This is crazy.
Can I get it all the way through?
I don't think so, fam.
Look at this, fam, we are so close.
Sometimes you try your best, but you don't succeed.
All right, we're gonna go over this one final time.
Here we go.
(torch hisses)
Here we go, this should do it.
Oooohhhh, it shot in my face.
Awwww, that actually really hurt.
All right, that literally flew up and flew right underneath
my eye and it really hurts.
So this is why you always wanna make sure you have parental
supervision when doing this, make sure you're in a safe
environment, and do not, apparently, do your brother's
hair gel, because, it will come back to bite you.
And also wear safety goggles, because I don't think your
parent will be able to stop a driplet, of, is that a word?
(beep)
And also wear safety goggles, because I don't think your
parent will be able to stop a drop of this stuff flying
into your face, unless they do a protection dive.
That's not gonna happen, so let's go to the next one.
This next one's gonna be an explosion.
It's a hot knife, vs. a light bulb.
But not just one.
A whole bunch of 'em.
But first, the one you all have been waiting for.
Orbeez!
I'm gonna start off with one of the smaller orbeez first
and move to the bigger ones.
Let's see, I've heard it's really hard to chop these.
Let's give it a shot.
(orbeez squeeks)
All right, that was pretty crazy, but right now we're about
to take this to another level and do it with one of these
large - oh, it's really hard to grab in these gloves.
All right, one of these big orbeez right here, so let's,
uh, let's do it.
(anti-climactic dubstep plays)
I never thought I would say that I feel bad for an orbee,
but right - did you hear that sound?
I feel bad for this orbee.
(orbee flatulates)
(laughs)
Yeah, that orbee just ripped it.
(orbeez shrilly shriek)
And last but not least, we've got the light bulb right here,
but this one here is a little bit too small, so, yehy.
(glass shatters)
We're using.
These ones.
(dramatic suspenseful music)
Are you kidding me?
(torch hisses)
All right, here we go.
The moment you've all been waiting for.
The big one.
Check this out.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Hey have you seen my hair gel anywhere?
- Your hair gel?
- Can you just help me look for it?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. For sure.
(instrumental)