- Three, two, one, go!
(screaming, laughing, crying)
(yelling)
- What's up?
It's Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday blog.
And for today's video, I have two chairs next to me.
This is unprecedented for a video,
so first of all I want to please welcome,
all the way from his bedroom right now,
my little brother, Devan Key.
(snaps)
- [Both] Hey!
What's up, bro?
- Teleportation on fleek!
- Thank you bro, good to see you.
- Yeah, so welcome back - So now we actually have
one more guest that I am actually going to teleport.
- Oooh!
- From Michigan, California, please welcome
- Michigan, California?
- My cousin, Cavanaugh.
- [All] Oooooh!
- There we go.
- Devan needs to work on his
teleportation skills, - Yes
- Just a little bit.
So, for today's video, we are going to be tasting
a whole bunch of super, super sour candy.
But we thought, you know what?
If we just do a whole bunch of sour candy,
the entire time, that's no fun
because it's going to be a whole bunch of
What we thought we'd do, we would break it up, do
super sweet candy in between the sour candy
so that way our taste buds
are in complete confusion the entire time.
Now, since this candy is so sour,
it's going to be extremely painful,
so please give this video a big thumbs up
for some encouragement because
I don't want to be in pain!
So yeah, if you guys give
- Wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on.
We're gonna be in pain?
- Yeah.
- I think so. - You're telling me
I came all the way from Michigan.
- I can't make you go back now.
You saw how bad I did on the way here.
- Yeah, you're right, you've just got to do it, bro.
- You can give me a little heads up next time.
- Alright, cool, will do.
If this video gets enough thumbs up, you know what?
We might make him teleport
all the way back from Michigan and do another video.
So yeah, make sure you give this video a big thumbs up.
Also, I'm doing a huge giveaway on my channel right now.
I'm giving away a MacBook this month.
If you want to win that, let us know by liking this video
- [Brothers] Comment down below what your favorite video is
- That I've ever posted on the channel.
Of course, he watches.
Subscribe!
- Subscribe.
- But right now, let's go right into the video.
- Oh gosh. - So these are
super lemon. That's all it says.
- This isn't even in English.
That can't be good.
It's not even yellow.
- This is gonna kill us.
- You guys since this is our first one,
- Oh no.
- What do you say we do two at once?
- What?
- Let's do it.
- I'm two times the amount of nervous I was before.
- Alright, here we go,
three,
two,
one.
(soft electronic dance music)
(muffled groan)
- Oh, no.
(muffled wimpers)
- Oh my god!
- Wooo!
- That's worse than I thought.
(inarticulate cries)
- Wow.
- It's like in my nose.
(laughing)
- I can taste it with my nose.
- Oh my god.
(muffled cries)
Oh my god.
They're all like nice and sweet now, but
- Hey, it's nice and sweet.
- Alright, that was the first one.
Now we need some sweet stuff now.
That was intense. - My eyes are watering.
- I know yeah, mine were literally, like there's
a little bit of tears coming out,
but we're gonna try the next one.
Right now, let's eat a sweet candy.
I need some sweetness.
For the sweet one we have these Minion candies.
So I don't even know what these are.
- Wait,
- It says try me.
It says push on.
(laughing)
Hey!
(gasping)
- This is awesome!
- Oh I know.
- 'Cause you get to spin it in your mouth
- It does the licking for you.
- Oh that's so cool!
(lollipops spinning)
- Mmm!
- It's oddly satisfying.
(laughing)
- Minions for the win.
- This one here is called Toxic Waste Zaps, sour bubble gum.
So, whoever can blow a bubble first, wins
and the two losers have to do one more
of these really crazy lemon ones we just did.
- Ooooh.
We have to wait for Cavanaugh, though.
He's a little challenged.
(laughing)
- Three, two, one.
(high-pitched squeal)
(muffled cry)
- Dude, wow!
Oh that's sour!
- It's not sour yet.
- Just wait for it. - Oh, man.
(loud grunting)
- Aw.
- You're getting super sour now.
Oooh!
He got it!
Devan won. - Yay
- Alright, so we lost so we have to eat one of these
so we'll open it up.
I'm just gonna do mine quick right now.
I'm just gonna pop it in.
- Oh yeah, uh-huh, feel the pain,
feel the pain. - Augh!
- I feel like where's the?
- It hurts.
- Yes! - It was worse
- Tickle challenge!
- [Brothers] Oooh!
- I'm so sorry, bro.
You okay?
- My arm almost just snapped.
(all laughing)
I'll never touch you again with sour things in your mouth.
- Alright, let's do the next sweet one.
I need something sweet.
So these are
- [Brothers] Kinder Joy
- Wait,
for girls? - For boys.
- Wait.
(laughing)
- Newsflash!
Devan is a female.
- Really?
- I don't get it.
(laughing)
- Show it!
That really is for boys.
- I'm gonna take a picture on my Snapchat.
And then I'll post that picture here on the screen,
that way you guys can see what it is.
If you guys haven't already added me on Snapchat,
you might as well do that right now.
- If you thought that one was bad,
you should seriously see mine.
- What's yours?
- Look at this.
(laughing)
What?
I'm going to take a picture on my Snapchat.
- If you guys don't have Devan on Snapchat,
you might as well add him right now.
- Alright, I'm gonna like pop it inside out.
- It's like an oyster, right?
- Oh, you're right; an oyster?
- Okay, the oyster.
Three, two, one.
- Mmm.
Wow!
- Mmm!
- That's pretty good.
- That was really good!
- Wow, that is good.
- That was delicious.
I like this one, very good.
This next one I do not know what these things are.
They are something Warhead.
- Hey, it actually looks like this red thing could be sweet.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah.
So this is - I'm hoping.
- I guess, ow!
- Oooh.
- First of all, you must lick the red thing.
Dip it in.
- Oh, okay.
- Oh my gosh.
Three, two, one.
- Ha!
- Ooh!
- It's lit.
(laughing)
- Alright, I'm gonna go for it again.
- It's on my lips.
- Hoooo-Oooh.
- I'm doing another one.
- Ho!
- Yeah, I just inhaled it.
(laughing)
- We're doing one more guys, you ready?
- Wait, we're all doing it?
(coughing)
- Ha!
- This is a choking hazard.
- I hurt my lips.
My lips are burning - ha!
Ooooh!
(laughing)
It's hot!
I'm sweating!
- Dude, your teeth are all green.
- Yours are too.
- Am I?
(laughing)
Alright, next one, let's go.
After that horrible experience,
we're gonna eat some pina colada cotton candy.
Take a pinch each.
A pinch!
(laughing) - Alright take it.
- Alright, here we go.
- Hm.
- I love cotton candy.
It just like dissolves in your mouth.
- It's not bad.
- I don't like this flavor, though.
- Cotton candy is cotton candy, bro.
(laughing)
- Here, you want some more? - Yeah.
- Here, want some more?
- That's adorable.
- Back to the sour - No!
- with this blue stuff.
Sour Punch Straws.
(laughing)
Alright, here we go, you ready?
Three, two, one.
- Oh, that's sour.
- Ahhhhh my word! - Woah.
(mumbling)
- Oh it's sour.
Alright, so our reward now - Oooh!
- Is Pop Rocks
- Oh sweet. I've done these like
one other time. - So
Three, two, one, go.
(candy pouring)
(candy crackling)
(all laughing)
(choking)
- God.
- Still popping.
It's not even in my mouth.
It's in my throat.
(laughing)
- They're popping in your throat?
(sizzling sound)
(laughing)
We're just gonna be popping for a little bit now.
- I can feel it right there.
- That is so funny.
- Alright, cool, so let's try the next sour one.
- Next up, we have Toxic Waste.
- Toxic Waste.
I actually have prior experience with these.
I did a video with Mel and - Wait, really?
these were also involved, so How were they?
They were great.
Three, two, one, go.
(inarticulate cries of pain)
- No!
Oh!
- Woo-Hoo-Hoo-Hoo!
- Oh my god.
(inarticulate yell)
- It hurts so bad!
(inarticulate yelling)
- Oh!
(screaming and yelling)
- These are way, way worse than I remember.
- This one doesn't get sweet.
- Mom!
- It keeps going.
(inarticulate yelling)
- Okay.
It finally got sweet.
- It really wouldn't.
- Little Devan is in pain.
(choking)
(screaming) (laughing)
- Are you okay?
- I'm all sweating, so much.
- You know what, all my like water ducts are full.
- Your water yucks?
These are horrible.
The worst ones yet.
We gonna need some sweetness to compensate for that one.
And you're literally crying.
- I am.
Oh.
- And these are called macaroons, I believe,
so they are blueberry ones.
- Macaroons!
Take a macaroon.
- Oh wait.
- I got you, Devan, don't worry.
Three, two, - I'm popping the whole thing
Yep.
Mmm.
- Wow!
- It is really good.
- It is so soft!
- It's like eating cloud.
- Yeah!
Alright, so we're gonna try these ones,
which literally look like organs.
I'm not even kidding.
Cheers.
These look really weird.
They remind me of something body-ish, but I don't know.
Eat it.
(soft dance music playing)
Ha!
(laughing)
(gasping)
(inarticulate sounds)
Woo!
Ew!
- It actually got better.
- Just a little bit.
(inarticulate squak)
- I touched my tongue to my lips.
- Hoo.
- These are just little licorices,
which should be delicious, so.
- I hope they're sweet.
- Yeah.
Ah.
- Oh.
- These are good. - Very yummy.
- These are yummy. - Yeah.
- I like these a lot.
- I dig these a lot.
- These are really delicious.
- Let's get more of these.
- So these are called Sour Twists.
- Nooooo They're made by WarHead.
I'm not excited about this.
At all.
(all groaning)
- It smells wrong.
- Oh, singed my nose hairs.
- Dude, such babies.
- Two at once.
- Woah, chillax bra.
- Fine, I'll take
five.
- Handful, bras.
- Well, yeah, you can't
- Come at me.
- You're anteing up for me?
- I give up.
- Yeah, you can have the rest.
- Three, - This is it.
Why are we doing this?
- I don't know, go!
- Two, I wanted to do one!
Okay.
That was nothing.
- There's no (mumbles) at all.
- Hit me again, bro.
- I can do another handful of these.
- Right.
These ones are rather clever because they look like
little raspberries and blackberries but apparently
they're supposed to be sour.
So you're gonna toss it up and then catch it in our mouths.
Three, two, one, go.
- Ow.
(laughing)
- Three, two, one, go.
- Ayup.
- These aren't gummy at all.
These are awesome.
- Wow, these are really good.
- Or really tasty.
- They were supposed to be sour, but they
are the most delicious ones.
- The most delicious.
- Okay, so these are not honey sticks,
these are chocolate
- [Brothers] Sweet
- Honeysticks.
- How do we open them?
- Just bite it.
- It's gonna explode.
- Oh, hey it opened.
- Mm.
- Do they taste good?
Not my favorite but, okay.
- I don't think I like it that much.
Eh.
- Eh
- Uh-uh, I don't like it.
- Well, I got a taste of it.
(laughing)
- Yours isn't even open yet.
- Yeah, I'm struggling.
(laughing)
Oh man.
Alright, you ready?
- Mm-Hm.
- Oh, it's weird.
(laughing)
It's so strange.
Yo, I can't get enough of that.
(laughing)
- So this one here is called Cry Baby Tears.
Extra sour candy.
- If they're more sour than the Toxic Waste ones,
I'm scared for my life.
- They're like made in the shape of tears, as well.
That's how bad these things are.
- Oh gosh. You cry on this one,
you the cry baby. - I'm fumbling.
- Three, two, one.
(soft electronic dance music)
- Oh, man.
- Don't you cry baby.
- Hold it back Devan.
You're on camera.
- Be a man.
- Or a line about the cry baby.
There he is.
- This one right here, is fish of some sort.
Starfish.
- Starfish.
- They're just stars.
I don't know why they assume they're starfish.
- Please be sweet.
Please be sweet.
- Yeah, these are sweet ones.
- Wait,
- Oh no, I dropped it - Oh no.
No, in the trash
Oh, pick it up.
It got a little bit dirty.
Oh god, it got really dirty.
Augh.
I'm gonna eat it anyway.
I can't taste anything.
- It tastes terrible.
I've got a super sour one.
- I literally can't taste anything right now.
- Oh, really are you not?
- It's sour!
(gasping and yelling)
- Oh!
Why? - No!
- Tastes like salt.
- I .. it tastes like tar!
It's stuck to my mouth.
- This is the worst!
- Tastes like I'm eating dirt,
salty dirt.
(inarticulate yelling)
- It was supposed to be good.
Ew.
I'm gonna throw up.
Please give this video a big thumbs up
for the fact that we ate some of the most sour candy.
- Yup.
- And we were in some serious pain,
- Yeah, that was intense.
- Any thumbs up would be much appreciated.
Go check out them both,
I'm gonna put both their social media links
down in the description below, go follow them.
- So go do it!
- Right now I'm gonna eat - Can we eat now?
- Yeah, I would eat the whole thing.
- Bye!
- Hold on, now let's make him teleport home.
- Alright there we go, and you gotta go
bye-bye. - Wait, what?
- Bam.
I'm all alone.