- [Collins] You challenged us to make
Iron Man out of a watermelon, so let's go!
- [Devan] Time to peel the melon.
- And I've got the spatula peeler, so here we go.
It's gonna peel it off like this.
You always wanna peel away from yourself like this!
(energetic yell)
I got it!
- What?
- I got the melon, bro!
It's dripping a little bit, you know, but here we go.
Just gonna try to gut my melon out, 'cause Devon,
I have a completely different process
than what you're doing--
- Oh!
It's going over the edge! It's going over the edge!
- [Devan] I've peeled the entire melon,
now I'm gonna chop off the bottom,
so I have a sturdy base.
Ta-da!
- It's all peeled and now it's time
to shape the head.
This is what I'm gonna use for Iron Man's mask,
so here we go, we're gonna place it down,
as you can see, through my perfect art skills,
it literally has the eye holes already right there.
So next up, I'm just going to accentuate those,
you know, bring out his eyes.
- You want to make sure you
shave it down very gradually,
because you don't want to lose too much of the red.
See, dude, I can look through the mask, bro!
I'm becoming Iron Man!
Right now I'm scoring the side of it
so I know where to stop cutting.
Now it's time to start shaping the head.
And I'm gonna be very careful,
do not try this at home, but I'm gonna be shaving off
a whole bunch of watermelon here, so here we go.
You made it look so easy when you were doin' it, man,
but this is, I gotta say Devan, not quite as easy
as you made it look.
And done, there we go!
- [Devan] Look at that, dude!
- Yo, that actually looks really good, bro!
I got it fully peeled and now it's time
to fasten Iron Man's face to this,
so here we go, we're gonna pop it like this.
First skewer's gonna go in and then all the way down
and then just go straight in, alright here we go,
goin' straight in--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, where are you goin' with that?
Right now I'm defining the neck
and separating the helmet from the body.
- My guy here, I gotta make the tongue,
but I gotta be very precise with how I do this.
What if I take a little bit of this
and then pop it in here like that?
Bam, now we gotta perfect little clump tongue.
- [Devan] Finishing up the head shape
and now it's time to make the mask.
- Now, for the mask, you kinda wanna draw
on the surface before you cut it.
- [Collins] And I gotta give my Iron Man
some nice buck teeth
you know, he's gettin' that real authentic Tony Stark look.
- [Devan] Now I'm gonna use the paring knife
for the small eyes.
- Wait, what step are you on?
- I'm on the same step as you!
- [Collins] I'm on the step of creating
his face and his eyebrows.
- You're definitely not creating eyebrows.
- [Devan] Pullin' off the side here, a big chunk.
- [Collins] Oh! How is that gonna help you shape?
Wait. What? Oh my gosh bro,
right now it looks like an alien though.
- [Devan] Now all I have to do
is just take off this back stuff.
- And do that, I'm gonna give my guy a neck!
Really quickly just core out the center
of it, like that, boom, see!
Dude look, it like literally created
a perfect ball of watermelon, man!
- [Devan] I'm scoopin' out the face now
to make room for the mask.
- [Collins] And I'm scoopin' out the inside of mine,
because it's very fun and I just, I enjoy doing this.
- Got all my pieces and now it's time
to assemble them and add the finishing touches.
- [Devan] I'll be revealing mine at the end of the video,
and we're on to the next round!
- [Collins] You challenged us to make giant pancake art,
so let's go!
Big 'ol head right there, like that, perfect.
- [Devan] Alright, so we're gonna give Godzilla
some arms right here, so we're gonna give him
a little arm over here, like yeah, what's up!
And then another arm over here, like yeah, what's up!
- [Devan] I'm a little concerned,
'cause he's looking like a plump baby right now.
- [Collins] Devan look, my Godzilla's lookin'
at your Godzilla he's like, he's like,
"What are you doing?
"Why are you crushing all the buildings?"
- [Devan] Gotta get this crazy lean,
'cause Godzilla's really leanin' forward.
- [Collins] I'm gonna give him his little eyeballs
right here, and by little eyeballs I mean big eyeballs!
My Godzilla's trippin' out, he's like,
"What is going on?"
- [Devan] Look, he's like a duck!
- [Collins] Your Godzilla's lookin' like he's gonna quack
while he's spittin' flames.
Does Godzilla spit flames?
- I think he does.
(whooshing)
- I think it's broken, yeah, it's broken, yep.
- [Devan] I got his chest in place.
- [Collins] Alright, now I'm gonna give him little scales,
you know, this is very important.
I know that Devan did this a lot on his,
he gave his guy a whole bunch of scales.
- [Devan] Now it's time to add the little spikes.
- [Collins] I'm gonna give my guy some little red shoes,
like he's little red riding hood.
No, who is it that has red shoes?
There's someone who goes, "Dorothy the Explorer."
- No.
- [Collins] There's someone with red shoes
and my dude's got red shoes.
- [Devan] Mine's grabbin' a car!
- [Collins] That's not fair!
We can't add extra elements into it.
- Yes, I can!
- How would my guy grab a car?
Look at his arms, man, he's like,
"Why would you grab the car?"
- [Devan] Alright, my guy's ready to add color.
- [Collins] Just gonna go all around like this.
No, dude, it's leakin' out the top again!
Shoot, this is not what I want.
You know what, this thing is ruined,
it's done, man, this is over.
Canceled.
- [Devan] I'm taking some creative liberties here
and adding some purple into his spikes.
- Wait bro, you got that idea from me!
Mine have purple spikes!
- [Devan] Wait, you do?
- [Collins] It's right there, bro!
- [Devan] Alright, this is the easy part,
just fillin' it in.
- [Collins] Last but not least, I'm gonna give him
a little welt on his forehead,
because unfortunately he got bonked
with the car that your dude threw.
- [Devan] Alright, the finishing touch is done
and now it's time to let it roast.
- Pancakes are cooked and now it's time
for the flip, but is gonna be way too small, so yeet!
We gotta get the giant flipper!
- Oh no, okay, here we go, here we go,
get the arm!
Hey, hey, stop it, it's goin' great Devan.
Here we go, so let's see, let's keep goin'
underneath like this.
Three,
two,
one,
oh!
Oh my God, bro, first try with a massive flip!
Dude, look at my guy bro, he's so good.
- [Devan] Alright here we go, gonna try
to get underneath it.
- [Collins] Oh man, it's so brittle.
Are you sure you're gonna be able
to do this without breaking it?
- [Devan] Ready, set, go!
(ominous music)
Very delicately.
- [Together] Oh, yes!
- Bro, that looks so crazy!
- [Devan] He's actually kinda scaly.
- [Collins] You get to comment down below,
who won this round, you challenged us to try pizza art.
- [Devan] And we're makin' Spiderman from Avengers Endgame.
- [Together] Ohhh.
- And we're off to a messy start,
well, I got my dough, the thing is Devan
I think you made a large, round, mistake.
You have a round pizza, which is a big no no
in creating Spiderman's head.
- But a big yes yes when creating pizza.
- Yes yes?
- [Collins] All right, well you know what, here we go.
Just gonna stretch it out like this.
- [Devan] Right now I'm just addin' the cheese.
- Yo yours is way farther along than mine.
- Yup.
I'm movin' right along to adding the pepperoni pieces.
- [Collins] Next up, time to apply the tomato sauce
so I've got this tomato sauce applying stick right here.
It's in all the top restaurants in NYC right now.
Just take an even distribution of the tomato sauce
on your crust, just like this.
Just roll it out like that.
- [Devan] I really didn't think that would work,
but it kinda does.
- [Collins] It absolutely does.
- [Devan] Now for the webs on Spiderman's face
I've cut up a whole bunch of nori sheets into small strips.
- [Collins] Just like you Devan, time to add
the white layer base.
I'm gonna add a whole bunch of onions right now.
Boom.
- Wait, did you just say onions?
- Exactly, just like you Devan.
- No. No no no, I added cheese, Hans.
- Wait, what?
- Here we go, got some Parmesan right here.
- [Devan] Hans, that is onion powder.
- What!
- That is powdered onion. (hacks)
- [Devan] Putting in the final little touches, and--
- [Collins] Oh, snap!
- Devan wait. - What.
- Oh. Nope. Totally good.
- What are you looking at? - Nothing,
there was nothing there.
- I'm just wearing the merch.
- Yeah, it looks great on you Devan, oh it's nothing.
- What. - Oh boy.
- No. - Yeah.
- How did that...
It was you.
- It wasn't me. - It was this thing.
- [Collins] That's not me, Devan, do I look like this?
- [Devan] But you put it there.
- Face to face Devan, do I look anything like this?
- Actually the resemblance is uncanny.
Just doing the finishing touches
on the outline of the eye.
- [Collins] All right, now it's time for me to create
my base, so I'm gonna use pepperonis, just like Devan.
- [Devan] Got some sliced up bell pepper in here
and I'm actually adding it around the side as
a nice little frame.
- So to kick it off with his eyes, I've got
two little olives over here, so go bloop.
You need some garlic powder to make the rest of his eye,
so here we go.
Now we gotta make the mouth.
I wanna use one of these bell peppers.
I mean, is this a bell pepper?
Really wanna find out if this is a bell pepper,
you do this, here we go.
Three, two, one --
(bell clangs)
Well, the stem was kinda weak on that one, so yeet.
- [Devan] I'm also on the bell pepper step as well.
- [Collins] I'm adding it on his face here for his mask.
Gonna use my bell pepper as two little eyebrows.
You don't even know if that's Spiderman or not, man.
- [Devan] Do you see these eyes?
- [Collins] I dunno man, I think mine are much
more expressive and emotive.
(laughs)
He's good.
- [Devan] Background's done, face is down,
and now it's time to add the onion eyes.
- [Collins] If that was on a Pizza Hut menu bro,
I would buy it in a second.
Oh my gosh, your eyes are looking so good.
Now he's gotta put a few finishing touches,
then time to pop these in the oven.
Pizza's are fully decorated and bro,
that looks just like Spiderman,
so here's the big reveal.
- [Together] Three,
two, - oh wait!
- [Collins] Five second subscribe challenge,
we wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, you ready?
Here we go. - [Together] Five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
done. - When you do that,
comment down below keyper squad, right now--
- [Together] Ready
set,
go, ta-da.
- [Collins] Dude, that looks just like Spiderman.
You get to comment down below, whose pizza
turned out better.
And we'll be eating them at the end of the video.
You challenged us to make Pumbaa from The Lion King,
so let's go!
- Now that I've got the face down, it's time to shape
him into that Pumbaa shape.
- [Collins] And I've got some blue here to turn
these potatoes into the night sky in the background
of my art, so here we go.
- Collins, Collins. - I'm sorry, I'm just trying
to make it mashed, bro, - This is everywhere.
- That's the reason why I wore blue, Devan,
so this would not affect me at all.
- You couldn't have given me the memo?
- And movin' on!
We're gonna continue to
create the sky right now.
- [Devan] Grabbing some black beans for some details.
- [Collins] You're very delicate with this right now.
The sky is the most important part of Pumbaa.
Next up, time to make the body of Pumbaa, so
boom again, we got some sweet potatoes.
- Well, then.
- [Collins] Now just gotta get in here and just kinda
mix 'em up a little bit.
Oh yeah, try to extract the good, sweet juices.
- [Devan] His tongue is done and now it's time
for the cheese.
- Wait, the what?
- The cheese for his tooth.
Got the tooth cut out and now I'm gonna
make a space in the watermelon.
At what point are you gonna start shaping
that into Pumbaa?
- You don't see it?
I thought I was pretty far along already.
You don't see it for real?
- I mean, maybe that's the eye there.
- No.
Gotta finish up all the hair around Pumbaa's
head right now, so here we go.
Next up we gotta create the eyeballs,
so here we go.
It's gonna go down like this. - [Devan] Nice.
- [Collins] Now we gotta carve it around, so here we go.
Just gonna go kinda like this.
- You're learning, young Padawan.
- Boom, there we go, look at that.
- Eyeball is done.
This is pretty perfect, Devan.
- Are you gonna ignore that?
- I mean, just the fact that it even is
remotely round when it started off in this
very clear square shape.
Even little bit of color is stuck to the side.
You know what I call this Devan?
Blue cheese.
- [Devan] Ah, there it is. - [Collins] Yes.
- [Devan] I'm adding in a second layer here,
just adding more 3D elements.
- Oh boy, he's looking kinda scarier and scarier
by the moment, I gotta say.
- [Devan] Next up I'm using some strips of eggplant
for the eyes.
Your guy is terrifying right now.
(crazed laughter)
If that's what Pumbaa looks like in the movie dude,
I gotta get my tickets right now from Fandango.
- [Collins] Dude, look
he's balding, so not a hair on the top.
- [Devan] Filling in the rest of the face,
then I'm moving back to the eyes.
- [Collins] And I'm gonna make some stars
for my night sky 'cause I really wanna add
some depth and texture to my image here.
There we go, star number one.
- [Devan] All right, the face and the nose is done,
now it's time to add the nostrils.
- All right, well now I gotta add in my round moon.
(laughter)
Shoot the moon.
- [Devan] Time to add in the blue sky and
put on the finishing touches.
- Dude, your Pumbaa looks just like a warthog,
and here's the big reveal.
- [Together] Ready,
set,
go, ta da.
- [Collins] Oh my gosh. - [Devan] Dude.
- [Collins] That looks so good.
- [Devan] And yours looks--
(laughter)
Amazing. - [Collins] Thank you.
You get to comment down below who won this round
and we'll be eating them at the end of the video.
You challenged us to do a Bento Box art Pikachu,
so let's go.
- [Devan] I'm startin' off with the yellow rice for Pikachu.
- [Collins] Add some blueberries in just like that.
Perfect, so yeet.
- Pikachu's done now, it's time for Bulbasaur.
- I gotta say, this blue works a lot better than
the blueberries, man.
It's almost like too much, it's almost turning
too dark right now.
It's like those guys with those crystal balls, man,
they just go like --
- Yup.
- Now it's time for the plop and drop,
so time to activate my Bulbasaur --
- [Devan] You're who?
- [Collins] My Bulbasaur.
Three, two, one.
There we go, perfect.
So here we go. - [Devan] Wow.
- [Collins] Bulbasaur is in.
- The thing my Bulbasaur is missing
is his bulb, so I'm using an artichoke.
- And I'm using an eggplant and an artichoke.
- Next up, I gotta make Pikachu, so I gotta get
some rice here, I gotta turn it yellow.
So here we go, add the yellow color in like this.
- [Devan] I'm thinking this is gonna be more 3D
than my art normally is.
So I'm gonna actually have his foot coming
outside of the box.
- And I'm going to use these carrots
as little chopsticks to grab the chunks of rice.
Here we go, this is going to be Pikachu's head
so here we go, the next one.
Doing Pikachu's body like this.
The issue is I got too much yellow rice
for Pikachu, so I got a different idea.
I'm only going to make
half of Pikachu's head over here.
So half of the mystery is
where'd the other half of his head go?
- I think it's time to move onto the background.
I've got the base done, so now I just gotta
add this lettuce in here like this.
- Hey Devin, I want to suck your blood.
- Take those legs out.
- Why not?
- Yeet.
- Excuse me, Devan, that was a fleet.
If you're gonna fleet my teeth,
you gotta fleet them correctly.
- The key to the background is to take this lettuce
and we'll roll it up just like this
and then place it in.
- Next it's time to place Pikachu's eyes
underneath the mushrooms right now.
The first represents his eye.
- Once the background's done,
now just gotta do Pikachu's tail
and Bulbasaur's face.
- And I got a mango here
just giving me the front of Bulbasaurs, man.
Here we go. It's going to -
- Bulbasaur, Collin, bulbasaurus.
- I'm sorry, I'll get it right at some point.
Here we go.
(groan)
I've got the mango stars,
so here we go, I'm gonna get this out right now.
Let's see.
- Goin' in for Pikachu's tail.
I kind of wanted to twist like a lightening bolt.
- For a piece of art, Bulbasaur's belly.
So, there we go.
Bam, look at that.
It's like, "Check out my cute belly button."
- Now I'm using two kiwis.
One is for the top part of his head.
And now I'm using the other half
for the lid of the hat.
- My Bulbasaur I'm gonna add
a whole bunch of vines
so that's a big part of his personality.
I'm gonna have a whole bunch of different types
of shrubbery pointing out of him here.
So, here we go, gimme a prickly fella.
- Time to add his rosy cheeks,
and I'm actually gonna use these cherry tomatoes
cut in half and those will be his little cheeks.
Second cheek is done.
Man, my guy is looking really cute.
- Yo, imagine if they had a Pokeman bento box's lunchable.
That would be insane.
- So next up, gotta a mango here,
and the mango is going to be Charizard.
Wait, no, no, no.
What's his name?
- Bulbasaur.
- So, that's it.
- I'll pop it here like this.
- Isn't mango Pikashu's hat or Bulbasaur's head?
- Yes.
- I guess I'm not gonna get an answer to that.
- Next I'm adding in the black part to his ears
with the nori sheet.
Oh no, I think I added a little goatee on accident.
Gotta take it off.
Now Detective Pikachu would be nothing
without his magnifying glass.
I'm using this pretzel here as a stock.
- The stock?
For the background, I've got
a whole bunch of nori sheets right here.
Detective Pikachu only works at night man, so here we go.
It's gonna crumple it up a lot--
- Only at night.
Just put a little glitter here.
Exactly, Devan.
Yours is not only look like Detective Pikachu,
it looks like Defective Pikachu.
- Mine is looking defective, dude?
- Yeah.
- What's goin' on with your guy's eyes?
- He's just havin' a weird night, man.
He's a little bit of a tough case to crack, you know?
- Now for the magnifying glass,
I'm actually using this agar-agar.
- Whoah.
- Look at that, dude.
- Mine is holding a whole bunch of pretzels,
to make it look like I'm doing something
'cause I have nothing to do right now.
- So for the eyes, I'm cutting a raspberry
in half and putting them on just like that.
Now it's time to make this thing look saucy.
- The bento box art is facing.
Dude, yours looks so good, bro.
So, here's the big reveal.
- [Unison] Three
Two
- Oh wait.
- Three second like challenge,
we want to see if you can like this video
in three seconds.
So you're ready?
Here we go.
- [Unison] Three
Two
One
Done
Ready
Set
Go.
Tada!
- That looks so good with the magnifying glass
and everything, man.
You get to comment down below,
whose ding thing turned out better?
We'll be eatin' them at the end of the video.
You've challenged us
to make a Guardians of the Galaxy bowl,
so let's go.
- Step number one, we're melting down
the organic unsweetened taro.
- And I'm adding in the yogurt chips right now,
some of the food has been kind of questionable
and how delicious it would be
but this, this looks like it's goin'
to be amazing.
- And now it's time to mix in the colors.
So, here we go, just gonna add
a couple of drops right here.
- I got my premade colors right here.
- You are always one step ahead of me.
I gotta get better at this whole preparation thing.
- I got my spoonful here and I'm gonna
start drizzling it onto the little bowls.
Going in just like this.
- Oh my gosh.
- Done with the blue, time for the pink.
- I don't think I'm drizzling quite right, man.
How did you get your drizzle so nice?
- While you're drizzling,
I'm gonna do the next step
which is painting the inside of these little bowls.
- I don't think workin' out
as well as yours does.
- You gotta finesse it, Collins.
- Is this how you finesse it?
- I'm switchin' up to the spoon technique.
No more brushing.
- Next, I've actually got a different technique,
one where I'll be usin' balloons.
You just dip it fully in.
- Lovely.
- Now that it has a little bowl cut,
just like Devan, when Devan and I when we younger.
Yup. That is actually us.
- Yeah.
- Time to pop this in the cup here.
So here he goes.
- Oooh, he looks like a funny little dude.
Now that I've got the dollops in,
I'm doin' the finishing touches with a brush.
We blended up a whole bunch of bananas,
and this is going to act as the creamy base.
Now, it's time to create the galaxy.
- Time to add in all the different colors.
First I've got some spirulina here.
I'm startin' with blue, you're startin' with green.
Power's all there man.
- This is gonna amazing.
- It looks like a whole bunch
of little stars and planets, man.
- Yeah.
- And get all of the grains and textures in it.
That yeah that didn't sound too confident.
- Yeah, I don't know man.
Next up I'm goin' with black.
- Oh, to represent, like, space?
- Yup.
- Yo. That got real dark, real quick, man.
- This looks like some magnetic slime.
Now it's time to construct the bowl,
so I'm putting down the granola base.
- I got granola bars, man.
These are granola bars,
you gotta mash them down
in the granola you want it to be, just like that.
I gotta get some of this granola.
- Are you serious, dude?
- It didn't quite add enough, so here we go.
Gives it granola, so yeet.
- You wanna add each color one at a time,
right next to each other.
- Next, I'm tryin' to add some of the edible glitter
and oh man you gotta be careful with this stuff, I guess,
just kind of give it a little sprinkle.
- There we go.
- This is your chance to add a different color
than you had before.
- Exactly, time to do the swirl.
- [Unison] Three,
Two,
One,
oh man.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, this multi-skewer approach is,
oh boy, wrapping it very badly.
- This looks great, man.
- What about the one skewer?
Maybe his would be a little better.
- A little dainty swirl, just like this.
Man, you're is looking way cooler.
Why's mine not turning out the same way, man?
Cause we both do the same process but--
- Yours is looking crusty.
- Excuse me.
- Now it's time to add the carrob balls
and the awesome finishing touches.
- Yo, dude, that was just like the galaxy,
and here's the big reveal.
- [Unison] Ready,
set,
go.
Ta da!
- [Collin] Bro, that is so crazy.
- [Devan] It turned out so good man.
You need to comment down below.
- [Collin] Who won this round
and we'll be eating them at the end of the video.
- [Devan] We got all the foods
and now it's time to see how they taste?
- And mine's got someone's garlic powder
and onion powder, bro,
it's going to be an intense experience.
Three,
two,
one,
oh.
- I will warn you, it definitely has the ability
to wreck your entire arm.
- Oh yes, I am figuring that out right now.
- Oh, no! My favorite part, the mouth,
I just wrecked his mouth.
Well, my guy just lost half his face.
- That was his face?
- I gotta get the slice right over here
by his head, man.
And there's my slice.
All right, there we go, we got all the ingredients --
- Oh, oh. Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
I wanna see if the art tastes as good as it looks.
Ready?
- [Unison] Set,
go!
Whoa!
- You okay?
- No.
- Oh my goodness, this is one of the best
pizzas I've ever had.
- That is an assault on the taste buds.
Yo, dude, that was so intense.
And right now, we're on to the next one.
We got out our Detective Pikachu bento boxes right here,
and time to see how these taste.
I got Squirtle and what's this guy's name again?
- Bulbasaur
- Bulbasaur, there we go, I got Bulbasaur
and Pikachu, but just the top half is Pikachu.
Oh, dude, it's going to be a mask.
- Yeah.
- I'm Detective Pikachu.
- Whoah.
- I'm going to--
- You're dropping everything.
- I'm sorry, I--
- Great, I got the face of Bulbasaur,
and I'm using the magnifying glass as the plate.
- I got some blue rice as kind of a base right here.
- It's like his nose.
- Oh my gosh, yours looks way more
appetizing than mine, to be honest.
Can I just eat your Pikachu?
- First, you gotta grab and take
the Pikachu's hat like this.
Just like this over the kiwi.
- Ready, set, go!
- [Devan] What was that?
- I bit the whole kiwi.
- What?
- That was not the best.
- Mine tastes just as good as mine looked.
- And mine tastes just as weird
as mine looked, so right now we're
onto the next one.
- We got Pumba, now it's time
to see how Pumba tastes.
Bro, yours has got some weird flavors
going on like with the watermelon
and the black beans and the cheese.
- You know what?
I got to try them all.
- So I guess for me, I'm going to start
off with my, with my shooting moon over here.
So it's going to slice right into it,
bulb out just like that.
There's half of the moon right there.
Whoa, dude, it looks like it's bugging right now.
Its eyes are like, popping out.
- Oh my Goodness.
- This is kinda scary, man.
- If it wasn't scary already.
- Exactly.
- Oh!
- Going right underneath and just like that
I got Pumba's face.
- Oh my gosh, bro, that's like a pizza slice right there.
- Yup.
- All right, well, I got mine, you got yours?
- I got mine.
- And let's see how these things taste.
Ready, here we go.
- Three, two--
- Oh, wait! If you want to win
a fifteen minute video call with Devin and I
text the word pizza to 81800 right now,
so pause the video, text the word pizza
to 81800, you'll automatically be entered
in to win and let's see how it tastes.
- Ready, set, go!
- I wanted the watermelon to make it better.
- That's a terrible idea.
Why the heck would you do that, bro?
- That was actually the key to this whole thing, dude.
- Really? Mine dish wasn't too bad.
Right now, we're onto the next one.
We got the Galaxy bowls in time
to find out how they taste.
- Dude, look at mine.
It looks nothing like it used to.
- Look at mine, bro.
What happened, bro?
- I think they melt super fast.
- You know what?
I got a finishing touch up for mine and here we go.
We got mine balloon and my bowl.
- Oh, yeah, the bowl cut.
- Yeah, so, maybe, excuse me?
We do it together on the count of three.
Here we go, ready?
Three, two, one.
- Yes!
- Now we gotta flip it up, gotta flip it up.
- Oh my God! - Nice!
- Don't break it, don't break it.
- All right, there we go.
The bowl cut is rather good but not yet really good.
Luckily, we got an even bigger one here.
Oh my gosh, look, oh!
- What!
- Oh my gosh, bro!
Time to scoop up some of mine here.
- I'm trying to break one of these in half.
- Why don't you take the whole thing.
- Yeah, I'll take the whole planet.
Get some granola in there, yeah.
- All right, well here we go.
- Ready, set, go!
- Whoa!
- Oh man, bro!
Maybe one of the best things we've ever made, man.
All right, right now we're onto the next one.
Got the pancake art, time to eat it
and I gotta say, man, this is probably
the crispiest pancake art we've ever made, man.
- I know, it's about to break into ten pieces
just as I hold it right now.
- Dude, I don't even know if I can get mine up, bro.
Okay, here we go.
Oh snap, bro!
Look it up!
He's coming for us, he's like!
- That was a little close.
- The leg came off.
- No, it snapped in half.
My guy's not necessarily scary it's more awkward,
he's like, yo wassup.
- He lost an arm.
Oh! And you knocked off my face.
- You know what, how about this,
I'm gonna take off his head right now, boom.
And this is what I'm going to be eating.
So Devan, ready to take a bite?
- Three, two, one!
- Wow, yeah, that's really brittle.
- Oh wow. It's very crunchy.
Yeah but other than that, it tastes really good.
We're onto the next one.
We got the watermelon sculptures
and time to find out how these taste.
- Those teeth are insane.
- It's something special.
So, here we go.
Now I'm just gonna use this.
I gotta get a piece off, so I gotta find
a way to carve in here.
So, it's like this.
Boom, there we go, man, easy.
- There ya go.
- That's my piece.
You know what? Now that I got it
all busted open, how about this?
Whoa.
My watermelon is hallow on the inside.
- Oh!
Oh!
- All right, look at this.
That ain't good.
All right, so let's see how this tastes.
- Three, two, wait, wait!
We just launched our brand new Keyper Club
and if you become a member, you will
get exclusive access to live streams,
merch discount codes, custom emojis,
loyalty badges and exclusive content
you can't see anywhere else,
so click the top link in the description
right now to join.
It's only 4.99 a month.
And let's see how this tastes.
- Ready, set, go!
- Oh, I couldn't even bite the green.
- Ugh!
- Oh yeah!
- Well, your art looks amazing.
Why would you eat the rind?
All right, right now we're onto the next one.