- [Collins] Dude, it's a candy llama!
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Chug jug! (water splashes)
Oh my God!
- Oh, I think I'm gonna take this from you!
- Well you challenged us to do DIY
edible Fortnite item, it's in my eye!
Oh my God, right now, let's go!
For this one we are making a Boogie Ball so right, ah
Oh, I dropped mine!
- I want the top of this, one, two, three.
Boom! There we go, chop the top, woo!
- Can you do that to mine?
- Here we go, three, two, one, bam!
(sound of sharpening knife)
- Nice!
- Oh, snap! Alright, well, let me get that back.
- Hold out your hand like this
- Like this? - Here we go
- Okay
- Boom! Perfect I got it, okay.
- You can have this one over here.
- No! Are you kidding?
- No - What?
- It's another joke, Devan.
- You got mad puns but I got quick hands, bro!
- Check this out, boom!
There we go Devan, from now,
- What? No!
- Alright, so now we have to kind of skewer
these little treats here into the pineapple.
I got a little bit of a different idea
and different strategy here, Devan.
Oh, no, dude's got a tongue!
It's like a little tongue, it's like bloop bloop bloop.
Yo, I gotta say, my Boogie Ball is coming along very nicely.
And there we go, boom, now my initial part of it is done.
So here we go, now we got the top.
- [Devan] Bro - No, no, no.
Prop it up, no no. Prop it up like, there we go.
I think I won this round.
I mean look at it, it needs a little help to stand up,
but like it's mid-boogie ball detonation, it's like bwah!
And it's about to, ooo, dance dance, I can't dance.
- Alright, next up we add the handle and we add it on the
(snapping sound)
I thought that would be way easier.
I thought it was just gonna slide in, and done!
- Instead of waiting til the end of the video
we're going to eat these right now.
This is literally a full avocado with candy,
you got a piece of pineapple on it.
- Yeah, it's gonna be weird. - It's gonna be pretty weird.
Wait wait wait, first, five second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Done, if you can do that comment down below
"keep it squad" right now and let's see
how this funky thing tastes.
I'm gonna pick mine up here, ooo, oh I lost it.
Alright so I guess I'm just going to take a bite of it?
- Have you ever had an avocado with the skin on it?
- [Both] Three, two, one, go!
- Toothpick, ow!
Ow, ow, this tastes nasty!
You gotta eat that dude!
I'm even eating the candy and it tastes gross.
- And now, wooo! (glass breaking)
We are making the most important tool in a fortnight,
and that is a harvesting tool.
I'm making the pink flamingo.
- And I'm making the rainbow smash.
- Get it, ohh, no we got pretzel sticks.
- No, really?
- Yo we got lots of pretzel sticks.
- First the banana. (laughter)
- And now there's just salt everywhere, mmm pretzel sticks.
Gotta peel my bananer, yeah.
- Poor banana.
- So first stop I gotta choose my pretzel.
I've chosen this one, alright are we just gonna
kinda finagle it in, uh oh, my pretzel broke my banana.
And then I got some Twinkies.
I feel like I'm going to be running into an issue of
how to keep the flamingo head atop a pretzel.
So instead of trying to balance them all on top of my stick
I've actually got a better idea.
I'm going to make my flamingo head here and then
- Bro, this smells really good.
- Boom, beak number uno and beak number dos.
Look at that flamingo!
Eye ball number one, number two
Yo my flamingos are looking,
- That's actually looking pretty good.
- Uh huh.
Now we got Snowballs.
Alright, this part, oh no, no no, bro though,
it feels like a sponge.
- Oh, whoa, that was not expected.
- It doesn't cut, it's just a literal sponge.
I'm gonna give my little flamingos hats.
- What?
- My flamingos, super stylish.
If I don't win this round I will be very disappointed.
My guy's got a little mouth.
- They look like little mustaches, bro.
- Well maybe they are little mustaches.
Dude yours looks crazy, you guys, here's the big reveal.
You ready, three, two, one, tada!
Yo, I must say it was very difficult to actually
put these things on a stick for the actual harvesting ax,
but you get to comment down below, who won this round?
Is it my flamingo, with a hat.
- Or is it my unicorn bro with rainbows on it.
- All I'm gonna say is it literally took like
an hour and a half for him to do this.
- It took a long time.
- That was fun, I think I almost just broke this.
We're gonna show you how to make a
chug jug right now, this legendary item.
Two rings, super quick, let's go!
- Almost hit me in the face.
- That could have been very bad.
(random mouth noises echoing in jars)
Alright, so first step, you gotta
flip the chug jug upside down.
This is a competition Devan, who can
make the better chug jug, fastest?
- So first, I guess we're going with one down, nope,
- One, two, three!
- Every time I look over at yours it's like
I don't even know what's going on, bro.
Bro, bro, - Eeeeeeeeeeoh!
Bro, what are you doing?
- Only issue now, top of the chug jug
has got some duct tape, gotta fix that.
You're gonna tear it, like that.
Now the fun part, now we have to add some liquids.
So first, you're gonna pop some Mt. Dew in there.
This is the chug jug, so,
Oh my god this filled up and this got frothy.
That is not a normal color at all, it looks tainted.
Alright here we go, now we're gonna
add some blue, and hopefully that fixes it.
- Whoa, that looks pretty cool.
- It just turned green.
Alright so now I guess we're gonna try
to add two bottles together at the same time.
This is the blue stuff, woohoo!
Oh, that's kind of cool mid air.
(basketball buzzer)
Alright, and then finally to finish it off we got
a giant thing of Sprite here, ahh!
- Dude, that's so splashing bro, oh no!
Yo, it's getting frothy again.
Alright, I've created a new challenge called
- Where's the pug coming from, bro?
- Perfect, there we go, so we're
gonna get this up here like,
- Like what?
- Bottle cap vision!
Okay, now that I, aww.
This is seriously a thing.
- That's like no vision.
- Alright, done with that first bit, now it's all blue.
Yo, wait a sec, I just realized
this was called "cumcumber soda".
- No! What?
- What? Let's see how it tastes.
- Real good?
Mine's lookin' really good dude.
No! No! Noooo!
Ugh, now it doesn't smell as good.
- It's got a funny tang to it.
- Just for that I am the one who
gets to dump these on your head.
- No, no no, you already dumped one on my head.
- It's not true. - Bam! There we go.
I miss him now.
See, I have the power, alright.
Ow!
That wasn't nice.
I gotta get him with the clapback.
(claps)
Ow!
I'm not a fan of this like Devan ghost, okay?
Here we go. (yells)
First of all, this is ridiculous.
(claps) Oh, what?
- Dude. - Dude, okay ow.
- Really? - Like you're sitting, ow.
- Why would you make me disappear.
- Right now guys, this is the chug jug
Okay, that's enough, we're on to the next round.
- [Both] Crispy fight!
- Oh my gosh, are you okay?
- No.
- So guys, we're making a spike trap
and Devan got spike trapped in the face, bloop!
Alright.
- The first step is to open the rice krispie.
- This one's super easy.
Take the rock candy and then ow, ow.
I don't know what just happened
but I got blue all over my hand.
- [Devan] They're just drooping.
- This is supposed to be a trap
not to get me to get the other people.
- My fingers are turning blue, I'm turning into a smurf.
I'm going to sauce it up with some yellows
because you know this is, oh, no, I broke it.
- Bro, why are you going blue and rainbow colors
that's not the color of a trap.
- I'm different, yeah, I'm different.
The issue is when you try to break it too
you break off the rock candy.
Oh, gotta watch out for this trap spike.
In the center of my trap is going to be all rock candy
to lure people to come and step on it
and try to get some little candies.
- [Devan] Bro, it looks as painful as stepping on legos.
- I didn't even think about that.
Yeah, stepping on legos is probably about
like the top five things I don't want to do.
- Now, I could see someone trying to lick it.
I looks really tasty.
- [Collins] Dude, I cannot wait to eat this thing.
(upbeat music)
- Well, for the first time in history,
I am actually done before Collins is.
- I'm almost done
just gotta add a little more rock candy to my trap.
- Really, is that even necessary, bro?
- Oh, yeah, this is super necessary Devan.
This is how I'm gonna trap them,
see yours looks all scary,
no one is going to go there.
Sorry.
Done, so you guys get to comment down below
who won this round, who made a better one
and you guys remember that's the trap in the middle.
We'll be eating at the end of the video
right now we are on to the next one.
- Hey Collins.
- Oh!
Yo, I'm gonna need a med kit to fix my face
so right now here is how you made a candy med kit
you can actually eat and then it rejuvenates you.
Woo-hoo!
First, I gotta frost my cake.
Now we're going to use this froster.
- See, that's the hardest part about frosting the cakes
is that you've got to get that even frosting.
- Jaggedy raggedy frost. - [Devan] It can't be dude.
- This thing is in my way.
- Alright, next up we go for that
red stripe down the middle.
Alright, Collins, you do you, bro, you do you.
- You gotta stay with the precision here.
Well, looking at it, I think that I messed it up
because Devan's looks a lot better than mine.
It looks all spiraly and
- It's gonna taste great though, right?
- I don't understand how yours is looking so good
and mine is looking raggedy and jaggedy bro.
I hope this stays on, that's not working.
Schmear. - Schmear.
Schmear it around.
Schmear it across the front.
It is time to add the plus thing on the top of it
which stands for med kit, I guess.
So, there we go, that is my finished one and now I wait.
- Hey Colls, I have some frosting on my elbow.
- You should try to lick it, bro.
- What?
- Did you know that it's actually
literally impossible to lick something off of your elbow?
Like, try it right now.
- I can't reach it.
- This is now an upgrade to the med kit
which you can only get if you're an experienced player
it's a handle so you can carry your med kit.
If I don't win this round, I will be so upset.
- Alright, so we're done with that
now we just have to add the
line around it and then I'm done.
- Yeah, that's the easiest part.
- Really, it seems like the hardest part.
- You get to comment down below who won this round.
I think my banana handle, woo!
Clocks the competition.
We're eating these at the end of the video
and right now we are on to the next round.
(yells)
- Battle bus! - What're you doing bro?
Yes, it's battle bus.
- Okay, well guys we're making the battle bus,
and we get to make our very own
and you get to decide, who makes the crazier battle bus.
So right now
- It's flyin', you know like a battle bus.
- Let's go
- It's like a pillow dude, I just wanna just take a nap.
- So I've got my wheels right here,
and this is how you attach the wheels to the bus.
Wrong, no, no I need to take the paper off here so.
- There he goes man, there he goes.
Just usin' his mouth, it's so effective.
- Ooh, yeah, look at them wheels though.
- The wheels on my bus go round and round.
- They look kind of like, stuck on.
- Some of you may have noticed that
this wheel here is not touching the ground.
And if you didn't notice that - That's why there's that side
There we go, ooh we got some Twinkies!
This smells like a banana.
You know what my bus needs? - What?
- No.
- That is why my battle bus is the greatest of all times, so
Actually worked, alright cool.
Now we got some bing dings, or bing bings.
- Those are bing bings bro.
- I lowkey wanna actually eat one of these.
It looks like worm, cheers?
- Alright, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Wait wait, first, three second like challenge.
We wanna see if you guys can
like this video in three seconds.
Are you ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one, done.
- So now let's see how these bing bings taste.
Bing bing bing bing bing
- They smell like strawberries.
That's not what I expected.
I'm not gonna take another bite.
- The bing bing is a no no.
These are the headlights. - Nice!
One of my headlights is kinda wonky,
it's like pointing in the same direction as the other one.
Now it's time to add some windows to my battle bus
because I want the people inside to be like,
woo, is that a banana?
You know what I mean?
And then we go, oh!
- Alright, here we go.
- I think that's a waste of time.
So I understand you try to make the whole like
hot air balloon thing, but bro,
Say goodbye to my banana, you never
wanna waste a piece of your banana.
This banana is actually gonna
be the bumper of my battle bus.
That way, if you ever come late to the battle bus,
you try to get on you're like,
you just slip off the banana peel.
Then we're gonna go, oh. - Oh bro look at this.
No, Devan. - I added a plane dude.
Look at this, it's a banana handle
on a battle bus, it's unprecedented.
Bam, there you have it, the battle buses are completed.
I must say, I think the banana
handle takes home the victory.
So you guys gonna comment down below,
let us know who won this round.
We'll be easting these at the end,
and right now we are onto the next one.
Now is the moment you've all been waiting for.
It's time to eat and feast on these DIY
edible Fortnite candies, working it off
right now with the harvesting tool.
Mine is the flamingo, I'm gonna try
to get some of the hat, some of the Twinkie,
and a little banana. - Bro are you ready for this?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(crunching)
- Oh yeah bro. - Whoa.
Oh, the different textures bro
- Next up, we've got the battle bus.
- Or whatever that is.
- This is my battle bus.
This is the front of my battle bus,
I'm gonna try to take a bite of it right now,
see if I can just eat my battle bus's face off.
Three, two, one.
- Oh! - That's awesome.
- I got a piece of (mumbles)
The banana. - Oh yeah.
- It was that good?
It seems like a weird combo.
- Boom, spike trap, it's time to get trap spiked.
- Oh no, alright.
- So we'll be eating this spike trap,
then we'll go for the med kit and then
we'll finish it all off with some delicious chug jug.
So here's the issue with this trap.
You see, you go for the lick on all the candy
and then you get spiked in the face.
(mumbling)
- Actually that was pretty good dude.
- I got it!
- I'm gonna try to combine 'em together.
I'm gonna take a bit of this.
- Oh, whoa, holy cow, whoa this is super good bro.
- That hurt.
- This is amazing!
I gotta admit, I don't think the banana handle
was the best option for my kit
'cause it all fell off and turned soggy.
That's disgusting!
So now that's how you do it Devan,
take your hand like this - Okay.
And then you gotta just scoop in.
- Ew. - And then ta-da!
- Yep, and then you say goodbye to it.
- Alright cheers. - Three, two, one.
Uh, whoa. - Dude.
Whoa.
- There's like layers of the cake
- They're strawberry.
- The best med kit ever, I hope you (mumbling)
it is time for the candy pinata llama.
Now we were gonna show you how to make this
but unfortunately, it just took forever.
- It was so boring.
- Basically like a whole bunch of fondant,
some cut up sour strips, and Hershey's chocolate
and this thing looks amazing, so right now,
it's time to take a bite of this time.
Oh my gosh it looks so cool.
Just gonna go for it, here we go, three, two, one.
- Oh, is it good?
- Yeah it's a little bit sour though.
- Oh, where should I go?
I'm just gonna go. - On the neck? Oh my God
(yelling)
- Now it's time to drink the chug jugs and guys,
comment down below, what are some other
Fortnite items you want us to turn into DIY edible food?
- And remember Collins, we only
have 15 seconds to drink this, you ready?
- 15 seconds, alright let's go!
- Dude, how can anybody drink this in 15 seconds bro?
- There is no way.
Oh my gosh, if you wanna see another video
click right over here, you have five seconds.
Ready? Here we go.
- [Both] Five, four three, two, one.
- Alright, well we love you guys.
- [Both] Bye! - A pretzel.