- What's up it's Collins Key and for today's video
as you guys can tell from the title I'm gonna be testing
a whole bunch of different girl products but to do this I
need someone very special to help me out
and this time actually I brought along a girl
so everyone please welcome Devin.
(snaps fingers) - [Brothers] Hey!
- What's up bro?
- Wait, what was that you just said?
- No, it was nothing, so yeah so for this video today guys
like I said we are gonna be testing
a whole bunch of crazy girl products.
You guys really enjoyed the first video we did of this
so if you guys wanna check that out I'm gonna put the link
right over there, be sure to watch that video after
this video is done and if you guys want Dev and I to do
a makeover video where we literally make ourselves over into
a completely different person let us know by liking
this video and if this video gets enough thumbs up then
we will go ahead and do that video and comment down below
if we do that video who should we make ourselves over into.
That makes no sense, doesn't make sense.
- Yeah, no I got it, I got it.
- But I think you guys know what I mean so comment
down below who should we become if we get made over.
There we go, that works.
Devin and I are super excited because we are actually
partnering with Best Fiends again and this time Devin,
I think you're gonna be even more addicted to this game
than the last one because this is their second game
in the Best Fiends trilogy and this one
is called Best Fiends Forever.
I don't think you've experienced anything like this before,
Devin, so here you go this is the game.
- Yo, this is awesome.
- [Collins] Okay, so how would you describe the game
right now like what are you doing.
- I'm slapping stuff, I'm collecting stuff,
and leveling stuff up.
Yeah, Yeah.
- Wait, you're slapping, hold on, no you're like tapping,
this is slapping you ready for it?
Bam!
Hey!
- [Devin] Yo, it actually worked.
Crazy.
- If you had like a few words to describe the game,
how would you describe it?
- It's a clicker adventure game, I'd say.
- Alright, that sounds fair enough.
The best part is, this app is free so I'm gonna put the
download link in description down below so go check that out
right now, trust me Devin is already getting into it.
- [Devin] Dude, I am clicking so fast.
- I wanna see if you guys can beat Devin,
the answer is probably yes.
To start things off, Devin and I are getting waxed.
- Yes. - So we have two different
types of wax strips here.
- That was good.
- Did you really need to throw it, Devin?
- Yeah so we have two different exfoliating body wax strips
and body wax strips for normal skin.
I dunno what constitutes normal skin but we're gonna go with
the normal one first and the we'll progress
our way to the exfoliating one.
We should wax each other.
- I think we should just wax you.
- No, I think we should wax each other.
So we are going to wax our arms.
Here we go, hold up.
Jeez, this sounds intense.
- Wow, that is very adhesive.
- Oh my gosh. - That is very sticky.
- Dude, put it on your arm.
- I don't want it to get all.
- On your hand?
That's so weak.
- I'm going all the way for this.
Put it on your arm, you gotta rub.
Three, two, one.
Oh jeez that actually hurt.
Ow, dude look at that.
- That's why I didn't do it on my arm.
I'll do my leg.
- Okay.
(laughs)
Okay so we've got strip number one right here.
Bro I feel so bad for you, okay.
He doesn't even know what he's in for man, this terrible.
- I really don't.
- Okay there we go, that's strip number one
and then I need the exfoliating strip
so that way your legs will be fully exfoliated.
Pomegranate and grapefruit scented.
Ooh, that smells toxic.
- Ah, it does.
- It smells so toxic.
Here we go this is strip number two.
These are terrible quality.
These are absolutely horrible.
So, these ones are terrible quality.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, we were only doing that one to
try it out, you don't need to do a second one.
- Well, yeah, yeah we gotta try this one out too.
- Hey, they might have varying results.
Alright we're just gonna do one, I'll be nice, you ready?
Three, two, one.
(Devin yelling)
- [Collins] It worked.
Oh my gosh.
- [Devin] Ow.
- Yo!
All of the hair.
- That hurt way more than I thought it would.
- All the hair is on it.
- Ow.
That hurt way more than I thought it would hurt.
- Yo okay so thumbs up this video for the fact that
Devin just went through so much pain to get his leg waxed.
- That was painful, if even hurts right now.
I'd say it hurts more than the actual waxing.
- Oh my gosh. - It stings.
- If this video gets enough thumbs up then
we might do an entire waxing challenge.
I don't even know what it would be about,
it just involves a lot of wax strips and a lot of waxing.
- What?
- So, yeah, thumbs up if you guys wanna see that
and let's go onto the next one right now.
Boom.
- What?
- I think I've seen these on Instagram.
- Is this like a jellyfish?
It looks like a jellyfish.
- No, it's like a.
- It really looks, wait what?
I'm so confused.
- Oh, wait, oh, it's a shower cap.
- Oh.
Wow, it's got some nice roses on there, you know.
- Devin, 10 out of 10.
- This is the cap we needed to start the video.
- Yes, these are our imaginary caps.
But they're real.
- Wait, put it on, bro.
- But I don't wanna mess up my hair.
- Your hair is already messed up.
Oh!
- Next one here we go.
Alright, so this one is Scalp and Temple Massager.
So I've actually been like a little bit stressed lately
so I could really, ow.
Yep, it got me.
So first impression for this product, it's very dangerous.
I'm literally bleeding.
I'm gonna go for my temple.
- Oh, it's a temple massager.
- And scalp.
- This is my new comb.
- Oh, I get it, this is for the temple, there's like
a little like ball.
- Aah.
Ow.
It's not very smooth, it really is.
- This should be sold for like, free.
This gets a negative five.
- This doesn't get a rating, it shouldn't exist.
- Negative five.
(laughs)
- This is the next product right here and it is a head wrap.
I have been looking for one of these
for a completely different reason.
Whenever I work out, if like I haven't done my hair,
my hair is like, just flops in my face
and it attacks my eyeballs.
- Can you show us a demonstration
of how it flops in your face?
- But that's like with product in my hair.
- He messed up his hair.
- Wait. - It's kind of, wait what?
- This is kinda - What?
- Not what I thought it was gonna be.
I thought it would be like stretchy but it's not at all.
- I'm gonna use It as like a headband, karate kid style.
Perfect.
- I thought we were doing karate kid.
- I thought we were doing perfect.
- Let's try one more time.
Three, two, one.
Perfect.
I think this will actually make me run faster
because it makes me embody a cheetah.
I don't know what to say about you.
Everyone's different.
Every zebra is unique. - I'm unique.
- Okay, we're done.
Next item are these lint rollers.
- Yeah.
- Yo, okay, people don't know this.
Devin and I love lint rollers.
- Well, I like 'em I don't know about
(laughs)
- I am too lit for these lint rollers.
So for those of you guys who don't know the incredible power
of these lint rollers you just.
(laughs)
Hey guys, it's lit.
Alright, these it says Pro Brow Trim and Shape.
I'm very cautious to go near my brows.
- Yeah.
- Not because they're good.
They're not.
Just because I don't want them to be terrible.
- Yeah, I don't want them to be worse.
They look like little fish.
- I want the blue one.
- Like de-boned fish.
- I'm gonna test it on my hand
instead of on my actual eyebrow
cause I do not wanna lose an eyebrow.
(gasps)
Oh, jeez, I like low key cut my hand.
Yeah, that's a sharp blade.
- It's a knife, dude.
- But it's like a brow trimmer, it's pro brow.
- How else would it trim a brow?
- Be careful.
Leave it to the professionals when it comes to the brows,
I wouldn't say go with this.
- Agreed.
- And it's6 dangerous, so negative five.
In conclusion.
Bam.
Next up are these mini blenders.
Now, we've had experience with the actual
Beauty Blender in past videos.
- Maybe too much experience.
- Yeah.
I gotta admit when I first saw it I thought they were candy.
- It kinda looks like it.
- They look exactly like how candy should look.
They look like little Easter eggs.
- Or little teardrops.
Why do you eat those?
- Every time, I'm like maybe they're flavored.
How innovative would that be?
You're doing your makeup just like Mmm, mint.
They just look like candy and they're not candy
which makes me sad so.
- Maybe they're small so you can put it on your dolls?
(crickets chirp)
Why is it so small?
- I think for like more pinpoint areas like
the inside of the eye is probably like a big one.
Around the rim of the nose.
The ear.
Ear plugs!
- That's what they are.
- These are ear plugs yeah.
- They're ear plugs.
Gimme another one.
- They suck at being earplugs.
That one was in my mouth, just saying.
- I need another one.
- It was in my mouth.
- What?
That was in your mouth?
- Yeah. - Ugh.
Next up, hair towels. I always thought you could just
use regular towels, but I guess not.
- Wait they sell like a specific towel for hair?
- Right.
We're gonna need the lint roller after this one.
- Oh my gosh yeah, for real.
This is.
- I don't wanna put this on my hair.
- It looks like a giant slug, look at this.
- Since Devin will not take one for the team,
I'm about to go for it right now.
Alright, so I think you go like this here and then.
And then there's a little thing in the back
and you tuck it into it like that.
- [Devin] Whoa, super high-tech.
- Uh-Huh.
Perfectly Toweled.
Don't like this.
Don't like it at all.
This one's kinda ratchet.
It just came right out.
- It says Spa Sister.
Doesn't look like a sister doesn't look like a human at all.
- It's just a brush.
I was like waiting for there to be some crazy feature.
- Is this the smallest back brush ever?
Is that what it's for?
- Maybe it like specifically focuses on your earlobes.
I'm trying to make something out of nothing here, man.
This is literally just a little brush.
- It's just a Spa Sister.
- Bye Spa Sister.
- Next up, we have this and it is a hand mask.
- A hand mask?
- Yeah, what did I say?
- Just clarifying cause that doesn't sound right.
Yo, this is wild.
- Whoa.
- It's like two little gloves that you put your hands in
and we just gotta go for it.
Oh, I don't like this at all.
- Yikes. - This does not feel right.
Oh, it feels so funky.
I don't like it.
- I don't want to do this cause I don't want it to drip out.
- [Collins] I know.
- Maybe this, maybe this is better.
Smells like a toilet.
These weren't made for your size hands.
- No, they weren't, they were made for little lady hands.
So, I don't know what to do now.
I looks so weird, it looks like milky almost in the middle.
- It's dripping.
- [Collins] I didn't know it could do that.
- I dripped it into the second one, we're good.
- Ah, you smart.
Yeah, I say we get these off ASAP, alright.
- Yeah, let's get them off, let's get 'em off.
- Let's see what the results are.
So we are about to step outside of our comfort zone
and do something we have never done before
and that is mascara and this stuff scares me.
(Devin laughs)
Like, it's getting so close to your eye and Devin
already has, like people have complimented him,
he has like luscious lashes.
Yo, this stuff literally is pretty scary to me because
I feel like you could easily poke yourself in the eye.
Whatever mascara's made out of you have that all in your eye
(Devin laughs) Is that ink?
- Is mascara the stuff that you put on your eyelashes
or is it the stuff that you put above your eyelashes?
Like on your eyelids. - No, eyelashes.
So I dunno what the size requirements are
but this feels excessive.
- This stuff does not look like it's gonna work.
- You ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready, I'm waiting.
- Okay, look right here.
- Wait, where?
- I dunno just stop doing that.
- Wait hold one maybe if I.
- Look up, I think they tell people to look up.
No, but don't like flutter your eyes.
These are max volume.
These are max volume for sure.
- Aah.
Bro, you need to not.
That is in my eye.
- Oh, I'm sorry. - [Devin] Oww.
- Sorry, I kinda missed a little bit.
Just open up your eye, do what you were doing.
- Ow, it's in my eye.
- And then close your eye.
(laughs)
So I think one is enough, we kinda get the example.
- What? - Yeah, just we.
- No way, dude no.
I did it, you have to do it, bro.
- Yeah, already know what it looks like, no no no.
- No way, bro you gotta do it.
- No way.
- Yeah. - No!
- Dude.
- No, we know what it looks like.
- Fine, then I'll do one more on you.
Like, one really bad one on you.
- That's fair, okay.
Alright, let's go for the next one.
- Next up is this thing.
- What is this?
Oh, I'm holding it upside down.
- What is this, Devin?
Dramatically brightening.
What are you brightening?
Not my nose tip.
No, not the tip of my nose, give me highlights.
I've heard about these on Instagram.
- Where do you give highlights?
Is it like right on the center of the brow?
I think it has to be spread out, I think
that's what the highlight is, like this.
- Oh okay.
Dude, what.
(laughs)
- I don't like it, stop it.
I feel like I look weird, I look like an alien.
- No, you look beautiful.
- No, don't highlight me ears.
- How about on the bottom of your lip.
- Do not dramatically brighten my bottom lip,
no, what about my chin. - The chin.
I gotta give it to you. - Wait, where?
- I'm gonna highlight your smile.
- No! - I'll highlight your eyes.
- You won't. (laughs)
No you won't.
It's dangerously close to my eye, I will fence you away.
Let me highlight your smile.
- No, you can't.
Ha, I have all the power. - No!
So next is the tutorial on how to do
a Halloween alien look.
(Devin laughs)
It just doesn't look real.
- It's like a Cirque du Soleil thing.
- It looks almost like clown makeup.
Triggered.
(dramatic suspenseful music)
It says step by step instructions inside to look like this.
(Devin laughs)
Made with 100% natural minerals.
I'll be impressed if they were like.
- Made with some rocks.
- Yeah.
Some rocks.
So, I think I'm just gonna throw this at my face
and that's how you apply it.
- Alright. - Here we go.
Ow, frick!
It hurt.
Let me try that again.
This time it'll work, I bet.
Ow.
- Whoa, it actually worked, dude.
- Yeah, it did?
Cool.
- Yeah.
How did you do it?
- I saw this like tutorial on Instagram and I was just like
oh, cool I'll try that so then just tossed,
like I'll try it on you right now.
You were like tripping out.
So next are these like Hello Kitty looking rings.
- Take a blue, right away, taking the initiative.
- Alright, I'll go for green.
They smell nice, maybe it's like scented rings.
This literally won't even fit on my pinky, bro.
- Whoa, dude. - What?
- There's a little flap. - What?
- You open the flap. - Yo what is it though?
Doesn't taste like anything.
Maybe it's for applying makeup quicker
like you just have a whole.
- I love how those just fit on the.
(laughs)
- They don't even fit on the first joint of my fingers.
- They make it past the first one for me
and it's to the second joint but they don't
go anywhere past that.
- As you're doing your makeup you're just like oh, I need
this color and maybe it's like an extra hand.
- But it's really glossy.
(gasps)
It's lip gloss.
Ohh.
- Why?
How would you even put that on you?
It just hurts.
I gotta admit you walk into the club you're like yo
Ya stuntin', you'll catch eye with these man,
just be like what up.
You walk into Subway and they're like
hey you want a five dollar foot long?
You're like nope I got four dollars.
These are a massive fail.
Kiddie drop.
- I caught three of 'em.
- Right now, Devin is about to go nude.
- What? (laughs)
- No, Devin, it's a nude makeup thing, I think.
Yeah, actually is nude makeup, you're lucky.
Alright here you go.
I'm also gonna fleek on Devin's brows.
And last but not least, we need to make him have
bright eyes cause right now he's got mascara
but he doesn't have bright eyes.
- Nope. - We fleek the brows first.
- You sure you know what you're doing, right?
- Oh, yeah. - Great.
- Shoot.
(laughs)
- That better not be tweezers.
- Let me. - No!
- Let me check you real quick.
- No, bro.
You better not take an important hair out.
- Devin has like zero unibrow-ness, I must admit,
it's like a scarce wasteland in between his eyebrows.
Big fan of the Darth Maul double makeup brush approach.
So there's one end that's like a harpoon spear
and then one's like a brush.
- That's like the most blunt harpoon spear ever.
- I'm trying to make it interesting, Devin.
- [Devin] The shark is swimming, just gets hit by a pillow.
- He's like Ah, shoot.
Alright, look right here I'm about to darken your brows.
- Oh no.
- This is terrible, it's just shedding all over you.
Ah, look right here?
(laughs)
One brow is like magnificent.
It's huge!
- I haven't even seen it and I know it's bad.
- Just a little bit more.
- No, do the other one.
- No, no, no.
Look right here.
- Before you do that one, man.
Oh no.
I can tell with the care that you're using,
you really take pride in this.
- I do.
I don't normally do things like this,
but when I do, I do 'em fiery.
- You messed it up, bro.
- Oh, I did.
Shoot.
That's that the brush side's for, so you can recover.
- It's like an eraser.
- Ah, shoot, it's spreading.
(laughs)
- Move onto the other one.
- No, we're leaving it at one brow, I just need to erase it.
- Just that one brow?
- This stuff's like permanent.
Alright, there we go.
Alright, next I need to make Devin's eyes bright.
- Wait, just one eye, dude.
- Just one eye bright.
- Why would you leave me unsymmetrical?
- I'm gonna go with the glitter one cause you love glitter.
- You better not, dude.
No glitter! - Okay, fine.
- Bro, you can't go glitter.
- Go with red, and kinda spice it up a little bit,
make it a little bit spicy.
- Are you sure this is what you do?
- Positive. - Ow.
- It looks like you have pinkeye.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Do a little under eye pinkeye.
- Why?
- Cause then you look like you have pinkeye.
Looks like he has pinkeye concentrated in like one eye.
Now, it's time to make you nude.
What do we do with this?
Alright, so I'm actually gonna nude out
one of Devin's eyebrows. - Nude out?
(laughs)
- Yeah, is that a term? - No.
- I'm trying sound like a makeup guru.
- It's not. - Alright look right here.
(laughs)
It just looks like you have a ton
of dandruff in one eyebrow.
The most dandruffed eyebrow of all time.
Well, it's getting nude alright.
Alright, well, now Devin's nude,
he's eye brighted and he's browed.
(laughs)
He's browed on fleeked. - Yeah.
- Fleeked on the brows.
Fastest out-tro of all time, thank you guys so much
for watching I love you guys so much
and I'll see you guys again soon, bye.