- You know, they said one piece.
Technically, that was one really, really long piece.
- I can't keep talking.
My jaw cannot move enough to talk.
- Sup, fam?
How you doing?
My name's Gabriel.
- And I'm Jess.
- And I know what you're thinking.
Where's Collins and who are we?
(upbeat music)
So we're gonna make him appear because we're
magicians too, so here goes nothing.
Ready?
(buzzing)
- Woah!
- Oh my god!
(laughing)
What?
- Yo, so what's up guys and welcome to today's video.
Now this is a very special video because
I was initially gonna do the boyfriend versus girlfriend
but things have escalated very quickly and
she is now engaged.
Well, they're both engaged.
That's how it works, right?
- Yeah sure, I just don't have a ring.
I get a ring when I'm married.
- I had no idea about this.
(laughing)
Single life, ay.
I don't know about any of this stuff,
so today we are gonna be putting them
head to head and testing to see who knows
their relationship better.
I've prepared some questions and we're gonna see
just kinda how this goes.
How do you think it's gonna go?
- I think I know more,
so I think I'm gonna win.
- I think so too.
- There is a consequence and if you get the question wrong,
the other person gets to put a piece of tape on your face
and so by the end of this, one of you guys
is gonna be looking really funny.
Now we also filmed a video over on Gabriel's channel
and they also have a vlog channel together,
so make sure you guys go check that out.
We put the links down in the description.
Also, right over there.
I did some crazy magic for them
and their reactions were priceless
so go watch those right after this.
Make sure you guys go subscribe to both of those channels
because these guys, Gabriel's the homie, man.
I remember when he first told me about Jess
because they did-
- Really?
- I won't go into too much,
but they met over Instagram and now it's...
- Put a ring on it, yo.
- Put a ring on it, for real.
Give the video a thumbs up if you wanna
have a relationship like Gabriel and Jess
cause I know I do.
If I do another one of these videos
where it's boyfriend versus girlfriend,
who is another couple you'd love to see me do that with?
Comment their names down below and right now I'd say,
without any further ado,
let's just jump right in and this is the
now fiance versus fiance.
- Woo.
- There we go.
- Let's do it.
Basically there are two parts to this challenge.
Part number one is gonna be a speed rally
so I'm gonna ask you a question.
- What?
- I'll go, "Three, two, one."
Whoever can say it first and fastest,
they win that round.
- What? Okay.
- Actually, I'm just gonna say the question.
Whoever says it first, like I could be mid-question.
If you already know where I'm going with it,
then you can say.
- Oh, god.
- This is all about speed right now, so here we go.
Question number one, where did you first meet?
(incoherent mumbling)
- Oh wait.
- Instagram technically, but her cousin's house.
Her front door when she slammed the door in my face.
- What?
- True story.
I knock on the door, she comes up.
She opens the door and goes, "Hold on one second."
Slams the door back in my face as I was about to say,
"Hey, how you doing, how are you?".
Wow.
I thought to myself.
I was like, "Oh wow, she's really not interested
"if she's gonna pull that crap."
- Yeah, right? (laughing)
You win round one so you get to go...
- Let's do this.
- You get to go for the tape.
- And it's just one piece, right?
- Oh.
- Yeah, one piece per.
- Wow, thank you so much.
- I'm a good fiance.
- Oh my gosh.
- I feel so weird right now.
- Next question.
This might go along with your first question,
but where was your first date?
- Three, two, one. - Malibu and Santa Monica.
Why did I say three, two, one?
- Three, two. One. (laughing)
Where was it?
- Malibu and then we went and had dinner in Santa Monica.
- Here's the tape.
- All right, there we go.
- Feel like I'm gonna be nicer.
- That's fine.
(laughing)
- Well, I am so happy that I am just really the host
for this challenge and I'm not taking part.
Next question, we'll get a little bit more intimate.
When was the first kiss?
- First kiss?
February 21st. - February 21st.
(ding)
2016, 2016.
- No, that was a tie.
You gets get to put a piece of tape on me.
- Yes.
I say we do that, all right?
Why did I do this?
This was a terrible idea.
This is not lit.
(laughing)
Breathing out of my nose, who needs that?
Suffocation?
I've heard it's great.
- We're all lookin' good.
- All right here we go, next one.
First impression of each other.
- Okay.
- She slammed the door in my face, she was rude.
- And I thought you, wait, how does that work?
- I guess he won.
- Oh really?
- Oh she's getting one too, yes.
- [Gabriel] It's the best move.
- I look so squished.
- When did you first meet Jess' family?
- When he went to Australia in July.
(ding)
- Well played, tape him.
- Okay, over my eye?
- Your eyebrows.
- Bring it back around, do another loop.
- Yep, there we go.
- Sexy.
- Oh yeah.
Who was the first one to say I love you?
- Him. - I was.
- Oh, I think she got that first.
- Did she?
(laughing)
- I watched the instant replay.
- Him. - I was.
- After consulting the instant goals replay,
Jess said it first so she gets to tape Gabriel again.
- I can't even laugh.
If I smile, I'm just like.
- Do you remember when it was?
- Right underneath the Hollywood sign the last day
before she left on her first trip.
- That is so romantic.
Can we just take a, that is so romantic.
(laughing)
This is crazy, all right.
- I can't look at you, sweetie.
(laughing)
- Zero to 100 real quick right there.
All right, here we go.
We've now concluded the lightning round
part of this challenge.
Now we are on to the whiteboard part.
That's a terrible title for this part of the challenge.
This is the part of the challenge
where we can't just yell it out anymore.
How this works is I'm gonna be asking
a question like, I don't know, what your favorite food is
and then they're each gonna write down the answer
of what they think it is for the other person
and we'll go like that so.
- I'll write down her favorite food.
- Yeah, so-
- And I write down his.
- Yeah exactly, so how this works is this gets
progressively more difficult because let's say
they both get it wrong.
They each have to put a piece of tape
on the other person's face.
This challenge, it'll be a lot more tape going everywhere.
Let's kick it off and let's just
go with that one, their favorite food.
- Favorite food?
- Go for it.
- Oh no.
- This is gonna happen,
you guys are both gonna say your favorite foods,
turn around the boards at the same time
and hopefully they match up.
- I know I have it wrong.
- There we go, three two one go.
- Pizza. - Hamburgers.
Ugh.
- I just got it.
- I guess that's a piece of tape for Gabriel right there.
- Ugh, let me just erase my winning board real quick.
- You've never told me that
your favorite food is hamburgers.
- Well what do I order at every restaurant?
- Not a hamburger.
Is this not goals right now?
- No, this is goals.
- Oh, doesn't feel like it.
- So goals.
- If you're sitting in front of the TV,
what is that person watching?
Oh she's on this one.
She's got it like immediately.
- I know what she's writing but there's two for her.
- Three, two, one.
So I think it was way too confusing to have
both people turn around their boards
and say the things at the same time
so we're gonna go one by one right now.
We're gonna see Gabriel first.
Say your favorite show and Jess you can
show him what you wrote down,
so what's your favorite show?
- Okay, ready?
Three, two, one.
How to Get Away with Murder.
(gasp)
- No.
- Woah, The Office?
- This is your favorite show.
- That is my favorite show, but I've watched it all
so now I'm on another show.
- Wow, all right.
Now it's your turn, Jess.
What show would you be watching on TV?
Three, two, one.
- Monk.
(buzzer)
- What the frick?
(laughing)
I know it's your favorite TV show,
but if we're sitting in front of the TV-
- I know, we are watching that at the moment both.
- [Gabriel] That's why my answer was for both of us.
We're both like-
- [Jess] But Monk is my favorite show.
- But he didn't say favorite show.
- [Jess] But that's how I took it.
- Since they both got it wrong,
they get another piece of tape on me.
I don't know why that makes sense logically at all,
but that's what we're gonna do
cause I'm feeling left out of this challenge.
Oh no.
- The same thing here, right?
This is how you did it I think.
- I feel like I'm gonna get the worst out of this challenge.
- You know, they said one piece.
Technically, that was one really really long piece.
- I can't keep talking.
My mouth, my jaw cannot move enough to talk
and I'm the host of this and I can't even talk.
All right, here we go.
All right, what kind of dressing do I get on a salad?
- Do you?
- No, no, no, you guys, sorry.
(laughing)
Like if the other person gets dressing on a salad,
what would it be?
You say it first.
What is it?
Three, two, one.
- No dressing.
- Ooh, that's impressive.
- Oh I don't even know yours, I'm sorry.
- Okay, ready?
- All right, here you go, three two one.
- Ranch.
(gasps)
- Oh, way to go babe.
- Congratulate, wait.
- Goals.
- No, I have to get another piece of, no.
(laughing)
- [Gabriel] I'm gonna erase that.
- I literally won't be able to do anything
after this piece of tape.
Really, really just-
- Oh my gosh.
- Really just how am I losing the worst?
All I'm saying is I don't know what happened.
I literally thought for the first time,
I am actually gonna be free from these challenges.
And now I just look constantly inquisitive.
All right, here we go.
What's one food the other person doesn't like?
Ya'll better get this right cause if ya don't, I'm screwed.
- What's one thing you don't like?
Hold on, time out, time out, time out.
She has to flip it around and I have to confirm
like yeah, that is one thing that I don't like.
- Okay, all right, go for it, three two one.
- Vegemite, true.
I don't like Vegemite.
- Congratulations.
Flip yours around, go for it.
What is it?
- Hawaiian pizza, I don't know.
(buzzer)
- That's a random answer, but all right.
- I like Hawaiian pizza.
- Ooh, I am putting some tape on Gabriel.
This is game over.
- Dude, you're closing my ear.
You're just taping my ear shut.
And...
(laughing)
- What size shoe does the other person wear?
- Done.
- Done, all right, here we go.
What size shoe does Gabriel wear?
Turn around, three two one.
- Ten and a half.
(ding)
- Bam, nailed it.
You?
Oh no, please don't be the same.
Oh gosh, what is it?
Go, three two one.
- Eight.
(ding)
- No!
Ya'll better be giving this video a thumbs up
for the fact that I have just, I've lost.
- [Gabriel] Oh my god.
- Right?
(laughing)
- All right guys,
it was all fun and games in the beginning
but now I just literally look like a monster,
so I'm gonna just take this stuff off real quick
and we're gonna go back to just you guys
having tape on your face cause this is,
I look terrifying.
- [Male Voice] Weak.
- All right, on to the next round.
- On to the next round.
- Now that I don't look like a demon.
- If the other person collects an item or something,
what would it be?
- I got it.
- But I don't even know my answer.
- [Gabriel] You do.
- This is so wrong.
- All right, what is it?
- Calendars.
- All right, that sounds really weird.
- But she does.
- I don't collect calendars, I just print a lot.
- Is that right?
- Shoes?
That's what I was gonna say.
I was gonna say clothes and shoes.
- All right, cool.
Well since I'm not out of the challenge,
no tape on me, no one gets tape on their face
and we're on to the next round, yeah.
Since it's the final round, we're doing a speed round,
no more whiteboards, right now.
What is the other person's middle name?
- Marie.
- Ugh.
- Gabriel for the finale, win on that so Gabriel,
you get to put the final piece of tape on Jess,
but first make sure you guys go check out the video
we did on Gabriel's channel and also
the video we did on their vlog channel.
Link is right over there, also down in the description.
Go subscribe to them right now and thumbs up
for the fact that we literally got tape all over our face.
I love you guys so much and now...
- Please be nice.
Oh my gosh.
- I love you guys so much
and I will see you guys again very soon, bye.