- You would never eat a real worm, right,
'cause I wouldn't eat a real.
Would you? - I wouldn't, no.
- Yep, well, we would not under normal circumstances,
but today, one of us at the end of this video
is going to find out what it tastes like
to eat a real worm because we asked you guys,
what are some real foods and what are some gummy foods
you would love to see us eat?
So right now, let's try them out.
Devan and I have no idea what is in store for us
because our dad is the one who went through all
of your comments, picked them out,
bought the gummy foods and the real foods.
So we're gonna be surprised.
So this right here is the first food
that a ton of you guys suggested.
We have no idea what it is. - I hope it's good.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- [Devan] Oh my gosh!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- [Both] Dude!
- Oh my gosh. - Three, two, one.
(screaming loudly)
- [Both] No.
- This is.
- Oh.
- How does one eat just a fish?
See, the thing is I don't even know
how one would go about this.
Oo, look, it's squishy.
- You're going in in the middle?
- Well, where do you eat a fish?
- You're using a butter knife.
Bro, that's not gonna cut anything.
- I don't have anything else.
- These are good.
What are these, Swedish Fish?
Yeah.
- Dude, I can't. - Don't disrespect the fish.
- Damn, I might have to.
Little fin.
- No, no, no, I got a little bit of it.
There we go.
It's got scales everywhere.
For the fam.
I taste the ocean.
(laughs) Next round.
Here we go, I think it's gonna be delicious.
Three, two, one.
- Oh, what is that?
- Dude, that's an eyeball.
- What? - That's an eyeball.
- What, I can't eat this.
Bro, I can't eat that.
- I've got the gummy ones.
- Dude, I'm gonna throw up.
- The smell is nau-zhee-a-ting.
Nauseating?
I am going to enjoy this.
I got some gummy eyeballs here.
- Do I really have to eat this?
I am definitely not picking this up with my fingers.
- It's gummy, but it also kind of tastes like gum.
It has a bubble gum flavor to it.
- Oh, it's squishy, bro.
Oh my gosh.
OK, I literally feel like I'm gonna throw up.
Oh, it's looking at me.
It's looking at me.
It's on the fork, it's looking at me.
Oh no, OK, I just gotta get it over with.
(laughs wickedly)
All right, here we go.
Three, two-- - OK, wait, wait, wait.
First, we've got a challenge for you.
Right now, we want to see if you can subscribe
to this channel, turn on the channel post notifications,
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
Here we go.
Seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one, done.
If you can comment down below, Keyper Squad right now,
I'm gonna be replying to a ton of you guys
who were able to do that in seven seconds.
But right now, Devan, here we go.
Time to eat the eyeball.
Oh, dude.
- OK.
Three,
two,
one.
It's so salty.
- (laughs) Man.
Yo, bro, you are a trooper.
Right now it's on to round number two.
A ton of you guys suggested whatever this is.
Again, I don't know what it is
because our dad picked them out.
But let's find out what you guys suggested.
Hopefully, it's delicious just like the last one.
Three,
two,
one.
- Yeah, I didn't get the real ones.
That's the real egg.
Aye, aye.
- Eggs are actually kind of delicious.
You can scramble them.
- No, bro, you gotta eat those raw.
- What? - Bro, you
can't scramble them.
That's weak, bro. - Raw eggs?
- Dude, I had a raw fish eye, come on.
- Dude, I've never actually drank raw eggs before.
- These are practically raw.
It's got a little citrus vibe.
It's real good.
All right, here is your glass.
- I am not excited about this at all.
So I think we're gonna crack the first egg.
I guess there's just no easy way around it.
Gotta drink it.
- Hold on. - What?
- One more thing.
Before swallowing, you have to
swish them around in your mouth.
- That's not a thing.
If I do both, what do I get as a prize?
- You can have the rest of my gummy here.
- [Collins] OK.
- Oh my gosh.
- I want the gummy. - You can have them all, bro.
- Let's go to the next one before I throw up.
For this round, we're making things a little bit
more dangerous because now we're gonna trade
off having the ability to swap trades.
So Devan, right now you can choose.
Do you want to keep the trays we have or swap them?
- I'll just keep it, I have no idea what I have.
I'm just gonna keep it. - So who knows,
if that was a bad one, you could have
swapped it, gave it to me.
Next time it's gonna be my turn.
Let's go right now.
Let's see what you guys suggested.
Three, two, one.
- [Devan] Aye, it's sushi!
- I love sushi!
- Either one of these would've been amazing.
- Sushi dance, sushi dance, sushi dance, uh.
Give me that, sushi dance, sushi dance,
sushi, sushi, sushi dance.
I like sushi a lot.
Here we go. - Cheers.
Whoa!
It's a marshmallow.
- Hmm? - Bro, you gotta try that.
- Uh uh, I want to try this one.
- This is so good. - What is this?
- It looks like some licorice stuff.
- Bro, what about this sushi with this sushi?
- That's gonna be gross.
- That's horrible.
Here we go with the next round.
And remember, I can either choose this item or switch.
I want to be dangerous.
I don't like what's in front of me right now.
I'm gonna swap them out.
So we're gonna do a little shimmy shimmy here.
- Shimmy shimmy roo.
- Three, two, one.
No! - Yeah!
- Bro!
Dude, these are, like, crazy hot peppers.
- I am so bad with spicy stuff.
I'm so glad I got this.
(ominous music)
- These are hot.
These little ones, I think, are the most intense because
they look little, and the little ones, you know, they bite.
What? - These are slightly spicy.
I don't do well with spicy stuff.
It crossed my mind as I was biting it
that this might be spicy.
It is spicy.
- Why did I chew it so much?
Dude, this is actually really, really, really hot.
- Why would you make a gummy version
of this that's so spicy?
- OK, this was no joke.
This round was intense.
Next round.
What kind of pepper is that?
Next up, my mouth, ow.
It's still in some serious pain from that last pepper, man.
There's just this afterburn on my lips, on my tongue.
Ow.
Next one, let's see what you guys suggested.
- Wait, did we get to switch them or not?
- No.
I forgot.
Well, I guess pizza's good both ways, right?
So one of these is gummy.
- We don't know which one though.
- One of them is real.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Aye, I got the real one.
I have to try a piece of that.
- I'm having a reaction, bro.
Look at this. - That looks so crazy.
That, I have to try a piece of that.
- Oh my gosh, it's a full pizza made out of gummy.
And now it's time for my gummy one, man.
Yeah, help me get it off.
This looks so wild. - What the heck?
I feel like we're gonna break the pizza.
- Don't break the pizza, Devan.
- We got it. - Dude, what if I
could fit this whole thing in my mouth?
It's just so tough.
Now it is my turn to choose whether
or not we switch or keep them.
I have had a horrible experience thus far
with switching, so we're gonna keep 'em.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Aye, yo, this is just a regular Coke.
- I got the gummy one, dude. - Bro.
- Here we go. - Cheers.
- Cheers, bottoms up.
- How does it taste? - Actually,
it tastes just like it, dude.
It was super hard to break it off.
- It's stuck to my teeth.
I wonder, this and this, come on.
- Go.
Well?
Next round, let's go.
This is it, the final round.
You guys suggested real worms versus gummy worms.
We don't know which one is which and Devan, it's your turn.
Do you want to switch or leave it?
- You know what, last time I switched it
and it actually was the best choice.
I'm just gonna do that again.
- Let's hope. - Let's just do that again.
- Let's hope it pays off.
So we're gonna go for the switch.
- Dude, I'm so nervous.
- Why would you guys suggest this?
- I have no idea.
- Three, two, please, one.
Yeah!
Woo hoo!
They're alive.
- [Devan] Oh my gosh.
- It's moving. - Oh!
- This is perfect payback because I got so much
gross stuff throughout this entire video.
Devan, do you want to pick one
up really quick and show them?
Oh, it moved! - It moves so fast.
- Oh, it moved.
- OK, I don't want to go for that guy.
I don't want to.
(distorted screaming)
- Devan is about to eat this worm.
But first, if you want to be featured in our next video,
comment down below what are some super sour gummies
you would love to see us eat.
And also, the Keyper of the Week is Molly.
If you want to be the Keyper of the week
and feature in one of these videos,
all you have to do is just check the description down below.
And right now, the finale.
Here we go, Devan, you ready for this?
Three,
two.
I'ma eat them.
One, go for it.
It's moving.
It moved.
- Dude, stand up, what are you doing?
Well, there you have it.
See you guys later. - I feel like I'm gonna puke.