- You guys, this is gonna be so weird.
This meant gummy food versus real food smoothie.
Let's blend it up, alright.
Three, two, one.
Yay.
Dude, I got a gummy burger.
- Dude, I got a real one.
They're both awesome.
- No, that is not good, Devan 'cause at the end of this,
you have to put this in the blender, and then drink it.
- Oh, wait, why?
- This is the gummy food
versus real food smoothie challenge.
- Oh, this is gonna be so gross.
- It's gonna be so nasty.
Here we go.
Burger cheers, aye.
- That was a long bite.
- Oh my gosh, bro.
- How was it?
- It's so good.
I wanted like half of the burger too, look at this.
Boom, there's no other piece left.
- You just have to eat the burger.
- (mumbling) this burger was absolutely delicious,
but now the time has come to add it.
- How?
Wait, how about you hold it - I'm gonna break this.
- And, I'll take off the top.
Alright. - Okay.
Yay.
- Teamwork makes the dream work.
- Yay.
(clacking)
- Don't we need that?
- I was hoping it wouldn't hit the glass table back there
'cause we do need the glass table.
- Alright, you got it?
- I got it.
Aye, pew (giggles).
For this round, as you guys know, there are,
what are you even doing over there, guys?
- Peace sign, number two.
- Oh, round number two, yeah.
You guys, we're gonna keep it or switch it.
So, Devan, would you like to keep 'em
or switch 'em right now?
- I think I want to keep it.
I'm feeling good, it looks good,
I get some good vibes from this one.
- You gettin' good vibes, alright, here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
- That was fail, hey.
- Dude, I love sushi and gummy sushi.
(lip smacking)
Delicious.
- Oh, look at that.
- Bro, I'm like a preying mantis right now.
I'm like (cackling).
- Is that the sound of a preying mantis?
- Yes.
(cackling)
- A lot of people eat it with their hands,
but you can stick it through that.
- Alright, so here we go.
You ready, three, - Alright, I'm ready.
Two, one.
- Oh my God.
It's like a marshmallow.
- It doesn't look like you're enjoying this.
- It's sour, man.
- Wait, what, what sushi is sour?
- Why.
- Mine is delicious, so.
- Dude, it's in a tiny, little container.
It's so cute.
(gasping) look at this (gasping).
It's like a seaweed.
I'm a walrus.
(walrus squealing)
Hey, what's up, dude.
- Oh, dude, you just suck it up like a noodle.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Like spaghetti.
(slurping)
(gagging)
(mumbling)
Not bad.
- Dude, it tastes like root beer.
- Really?
Really?
- Yeah, you try.
- No.
- If I'm gonna put these in the blender,
I'm just gonna keep eating these, so I'm gonna get a pop.
Plohp, that one in there.
- Sushi and a burger?
That's gonna be so gross.
- No, no.
I cannot wait to start drinking of mine smoothies.
This looks so good.
- Yeah, not so much for me.
This looks nasty.
Anyways, you wanna keep it or switch it?
- My decision is I'm going to keep it.
Sike, switch it.
Yeah.
I think I had a little bit too much sugar right now,
and like my energy level's gotten like bee-oh,
off the roof, off chain.
One, two, three, four, change.
- Hey, I got a gummy one this time.
- Bro, my pickles ain't crisp.
Bro, look at this.
You see how I'm squeezin' it?
You cannot do this to a new, fresh pickle.
Well, Devan, on the bright side,
you finally got a gummy to add to your smoothie.
- What, this is the worst gummy to get.
It doesn't even smell good.
Smell it.
- Oh my gosh.
Dude, it smells like a pickle. - I know.
It smells terrible.
- It smells more like a pickle than this.
If it smells like a pickle and if it looks like a pickle,
your gummy might taste like a pickle.
So, let's find out right now.
You ready?
Here we go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
we'd have to get a challenge for you.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this challenge,
put it on, ow, channel post notifications
to give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
Can you do it?
Here we go.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you can do that, comment down below,
Keyper Squad right now and Devan, let's take our bite.
Let's go. - Alright.
- Mm.
- Ugh.
It's sort of spicy.
- What?
- It's sort of pickle-eeh.
Bro, who eats a pickle like that?
- Me.
I love pickles.
Pop, pop.
Your turn, Devan, do you want to keep 'em or switch 'em?
- Uh, I wanna switch it 'cause last time was terrible.
I'm switching.
- Alright, we're switching it, here we go.
Three, two, one.
No. - Yeah.
You got the real lemon.
(laughing)
- I have had it with eating lemon.
Birds on YouTube, then I'm on Disney Channel,
and then right now, bro, I am not about this.
- This isn't even sour.
This is so sweet. - Are you kidding me?
Alright, here we go.
This is gonna-
- No, you just got to eat it, dude.
Come on. - Dude, that was sour.
- What happened?
- Why is it so sour?
My lips are burning.
I can't, I can't, I can't do it.
- Alright, you did good, you did a good job.
You can dump it in there now.
- Dude, it's so sour.
Alright, onto the next round, ow.
- Alright, it is your turn to call us.
Do you want to keep it or switch it?
- Dude, the thing is right now, Devan,
I'm feeling extraordinary.
- What?
- Extraordinary, so I'm gonna keep it.
- (chuckles) okay.
Three, two, one.
- Yeah.
Oh my God. - It's a pizza.
- Oh my God, it's a pizza.
This is the greatest.
Yo, I wonder if I can spin it on one finger.
Oh yeah, my pizza's so good.
Oh, look at my cheese.
- Wait, wait, wait, toss it to Mike, toss it to Mike.
- Three, two, one, bee-oh.
- Ah, oh no, oh no, we'll cut that out.
It never happened.
- Yup, never happened.
(beep)
Ugh, it's so stretchy.
See, this is what happens, guys.
A little life half when you get a small pizza,
and you really want a large, you just do this
with your pizza, and then, suddenly, you'll have a large.
- It works every time.
What?
How's that effective?
Have you eaten it?
Have you had any of it yet?
- None, but I put all this teeth marks around it.
- Yeah, so now, I can't eat it.
- Yup, exactly.
It's a way to protect your pizza.
- Oh, that's a lot of gummy.
(laughing) - Mm, so delicious, okay.
- Alright.
Alright, onto the next one.
- I have gummy in my teeth.
- Alright, it is your turn again.
Do you wanna keep it or do you wanna switch it?
- I have a feeling
this one's gonna be a very important decision right now,
so I'm gonna go dangerous, switch it.
- Switch it, alright, here we go.
- Three, two, one.
- No.
What are the chances of getting peppers twice?
The smoothie's gonna be spicy.
- Oh my gosh, didn't even think about that.
- Ugh.
- We'll do this again.
We'll start with the green one,
and work our way down to the yellow one.
- I remember this one.
This one wasn't bad.
It was a green pepper. - You ready?
Three, two, one. - Yeah.
(hacking) I can't, oh, it is bad.
Oh, it's way worse.
A lot of times I put one in spicy.
- Red one's next, here we go.
- Ah.
- Oh my gosh.
- It's on fire.
- It starts young, now it's gummy.
Unless they think they're hot.
Spicy (mumbles) man.
- Ah.
- Are you okay?
Oh my gosh, why is it so spicy when it's gummy, man?
And, last but not least, yellow one.
This one's the worst.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Ah.
- Mm, ow, ow, ow.
Now, we're gonna add these in too.
And then, you're gonna pop those in boom boom,
and we can leave that one out.
Ow, my mouth is burning on fire.
- I need milk.
- You need milk, alright.
- Oh, I feel lightheaded.
(slurping)
Mm.
You have no idea.
My teeth are literally tingling.
- Devan, you are suffering right now, so you know what,
it's your turn to choose one, keep 'em or switch 'em?
- I wanna keep 'em.
- Keep 'em?
Alright, here we go.
You ready, three, two, one.
- Okay, I love carrots.
Carrots are awesome.
- What if these actually taste like real carrots?
- To tell you the truth,
I can't really taste anything right now.
- Luckily, I got the gummies.
We can see if they actually taste like carrots.
- That's weird.
- They actually taste like carrots.
- Really?
- That's crazy.
Why would you make a carrot-like tasting gummy?
Alright, gonna pop 'em in.
Oops.
I'm a vampire.
- No.
What, you're gonna like turn me into a carrot or something?
(thunder roaring) - Muahahahaha.
It tastes nasty as a carrot does.
My drink still looks actually kind of delicious.
Yours, on the other hand, does not.
And, this round was suggested
by the Instagram Keyper of the Week,
so if you want to be shout out
as the Instagram Keyper of the Week, check the description
down below, but again, congratulations,
and let's find out what you suggested.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Hey, it's a hot dog.
- I have never seen a gummy hot dog before.
(gasping)
Look at his buns (laughs).
- That looks so awesome.
- Like even the attention to detail.
It's like the yellow mustard on the top of it,
oh my gosh. - I know.
I'm ready. - Here we go, three, two, one.
I think this may be one of, if not,
the most tasty gummy I have ever tried in my entire life.
You wanna try it right now?
- Yeah, I actually really do.
- Dude, this one is so good.
- Mm, wow.
- Mhm.
- Wow.
- Oh, you bit it, now I have to put it in my drink.
Oh well, I guess we're brothers, so.
(claps) yay.
We forgot whose turn it is to switch or keep it,
so I'm making the executive decision right now
that Devan's gonna make the executive decision right now.
Which one is it gonna be?
- I-
- Executive decision on my end, we keep 'em.
- I'm cool with that.
Alright, let's do it.
- Three, two, one.
Yes, - Oh no.
- That was the worst executive decision ever.
- I am so not happy about this.
- Never happened.
Never happened.
First try.
- Yeah, that was the first try, okay.
We're definitely not gonna leave you on the fail dim there.
- Exactly.
- I wonder if you could like pre-scramble an egg
by doing this with it 'cause I have to drink this egg.
- Don't crack it.
- I'm gonna crack it into my mouth.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(cracking)
- Oh, it didn't work.
- Oh, it's danglin'.
- Your strategy didn't work.
- Ah.
It couldn't have gone worse.
- That was so gross.
- I almost like almost threw up, bro.
Okay, put the egg, put the egg in there.
- Alright.
Ugh, it's on my fingers now, ew.
- This one here is looking a little bit suspicious, Devan.
- Hm (chuckles).
- So, do you wanna keep it or switch it?
- I'm gonna take a risk, and actually keep it.
- Alright, here we go.
- I'm probably gonna regret this.
- Three, two, one.
- Hey, it's a watermelon.
- Oh my gosh, the only thing better
than watermelon is a watermelon gummy,
and the only thing better than a watermelon gummy,
is a water mehl-ohn on a stick.
It's got like a little bit
of a different kind of smell to it as well.
Ooh. - Oh, it does.
Wait, take this thing out.
(coughs) I choked on my watermelon.
The stick won't come out.
- You must try harder.
- Hey, it came out, yay.
- No one eats the rind, yeht.
Where did it go?
- (chuckles) it disappeared.
- Oh, gonna pop my watermelon in here.
- I'm hoping this adds a little bit of water
to the base of the smoothie 'cause it's a really dry one.
- So, we forgot again whose turn it is,
so we're gonna do rock, paper, scissors to decide.
Rock, paper, scissor, shoot.
Yeah. - No.
- And on that decision, I wanna keep it.
Here we go, three, two, one.
No. - No.
- This isn't peeled, fam.
My corn is super harry, bro.
My corn has never shaved in ages life.
Look at how harry my corn is.
- Dude, my corn is delicious.
Oh, let's see what happens if you spin it,
like one of those things where you like wind up and spin.
- And, the hairs went everywhere.
Wah-gah-wah-gah-wah-gah-wah-gah-wah-gah-wah-gah.
What if you crack the corn in half?
- Whoa.
Wait, I want to try. - It juiced on me, bro.
- No, not gonna happen.
- Give it a good old chomp.
- Alright.
Dude, it's not, it's literally just corn.
- And, it needs to be cooked.
- Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
- Not a fan of that, okay.
- Yeah, it should've been cooked.
Oh, I got it. - Ow.
- I got a piece off.
It's all stuck to my fingers.
- Good lord.
- It gave up.
Oh.
- It's going in yours.
- Wait, no, no, no, no.
No. - Yes, it is.
Dropped it in, it's going in.
Last few rounds, let's go.
No. - You got to put some hair
in yours. - No.
- Alright, are we switching it or keeping it?
- Switching it right now.
Three, two, one.
- Yes.
Wait, so that's turkey
and so, that must be- - This must be a turkey leg.
- Yeah, I guess.
Cheers?
- Cheers.
Yeah, bro, it's turkey.
- Yup, it's gummy.
- Alright, here we're gonna add it in.
There we go full.
- You have no idea how hard that was.
- Boom, alright, final one, here we go.
For this final one, Devan,
do you wanna keep it or switch it?
- I'm feeling good with keeping it.
- But, to let you know, I'm getting great vibes from my end,
so I'm very happy you're keeping it.
- Really, you are?
- Yup, three, two, one.
- Yeah.
- You're kidding me.
- Hey.
Muah.
- I can't.
- Alright, let's sit down, cool.
- I was gonna put the whole thing in, man,
like just gotta, make sure you gotta eat
your mustaches, kids.
I'm gonna be eating those for like a week, man.
Coming up right now, guys, about to top the top on,
and then, we're about to blend them up, so let's do it.
What happened to my top?
Wait, what do you mean what'd I do?
Took the top, yeht.
Oh, back over there. - Oh yeah.
- Alright, gonna pop my top on.
- Alright.
- Time to blend it.
Wait, what?
- Is yours doing nothing?
- Nothing.
- 'Cause mine's not doing anything.
- I know what we're missing.
- I smell smoke.
- Pickle juice.
- Oh.
- Oh, that looks really gross.
- Oh my gosh, I'm not excited about this-
- Oh, no, no, that's enough, that's enough.
I'm just grabbing water for mine.
There's no way I'm using that pickle juice.
- Did I mention that I am ready 'cause I am ready.
Are you ready now, Devan?
- Ooh, that's dripping everywhere.
- You're dripping everywhere.
Three, two, one.
Yeah, boy.
Mine's going.
- Mine's not.
- Look at it go.
- Alright, I gotta shake mine.
- Mine's a little blender who could.
Oh my gosh, yeah, yours is like broken.
Are you gonna like actually break it?
Oh my gosh, mine's actually smoking out the back.
Do you see the smoke coming out of mine?
- I just did, and I can smell it.
- Dude, coming from the bottom.
- Bro, we got to open up a window.
That smells.
Alright, well, mine didn't do anything,
so I got my spatula here, no wait,
why are you doing it at the same time?
All the sushi stuff.
- Oh my gosh.
- Ew, I can hear it.
And, there's a burger all the way at the bottom.
- Oh, that's why it's not blending.
- Yeah, alright, well, let's try this.
- Hey, it's working.
You gotta go deeper, bro.
Oh, that smoke.
Oh, there we go, there we go,
it's working, it's working, it's working.
Oh, no, this is so gross.
- So nasty.
- But this is the gummy food versus real food smoothie.
- Whose idea was this?
- And, comment down below, what are some other random foods
you would love to see us make into a smoothie.
Cheers?
- Oh, my stomach is already churning.
- Oh my gosh.
Three.
- Two.
- The little hair sticking out of it, bro.
One.
All I taste is the gross things.
None of the gummies.
Where did all the gummies go?
Who put them out?
If you have any another video, click right over here.
And also, I dare you right now, click right over here.
Five seconds, just right over here.
Five, four, three, two, click here, one, go, bye.
- Bye.
- Like when you bite into a pickle, man,
you want that crunch 'cause you want to know
that it's fresh to depth.
- What are you, some like pickle offician-ah-toh?