- [Collins] He's bending it.
Dude, he going to mend it. This is Hayes magic right here.
- What you got?
- [Guy] Hayes Magic 2.0, let's see.
- [All] Oh!
- [Collins] It's still ripped.
How'd he do it?
(beep)
- Stop.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
- Take it. Take a look at that card.
Show it to the camera.
(laughter)
Four of hearts right here.
- Yeah.
- Four goes in the middle. Push it in. Push it in.
Push in that five.
(snap)
And snap, look what jumps on top.
You ready for this?
I'm going to blow your mind.
- It was a five.
- Okay, okay, jk.
Bam.
Did I get it? Two, okay take it. Um.
(laughter)
- Sorry.
So I'm getting a little bit nervous, screw this.
Hold out your hand, man.
Okay I'll use your hand.
Hold it a little bit lower.
What was it, five of hearts? Right?
See we go through. Five of hearts, okay.
I missed it by a lot.
What if I told you I can fix this?
- Fix it.
- Watch, right here.
Take the five. Hold the nine a little bit lower.
And watch, right here.
If I wave this five like this,
I can get the nine to soar to my hand.
Like that.
And yeah, look what you're holding.
Go for it, turn it over.
Turn over those pieces.
- [Male] He literally ripped up a card.
- Yo, that's kinda freak.
- I can fix this, I tore up like a seven of clubs, right?
- Yeah.
- Watch, if I just give it a wave like this.
See right there I can get the seven to this card right here.
And then look what you're holding, go for it.
Turn it over.
(laughter)
- [Ansel] I like that trick.
- [Collins] Let me see it. And then reach out your hand.
- Are these pieces about to change?
- Hold out your hand, hold out your hand.
And squeeze tight, squeeze tight.
Nash, put your hand on his.
- Woo!
- Daniel put your hand on, you gotta pile your hands on.
You're going to start to feel them heat up.
This isn't going to hurt or anything, just tell me
when you start to feel it happen.
Squeeze tight, as tight as you can.
Feel it start to heat up?
- Yeah.
- They actually melt.
I want you to open up those torn pieces.
- This isn't torn!
- Aw man, his hand!
- I saw the five of hearts that was in his hand.
- Watch this, you ready?
It's not going to hurt, but you're going to
slowly start to feel it heat up.
You're going to feel it heat up.
Feel it?
- Little bit.
- Ahh!!
- Yeah they're going to actually melt.
Right there.
- If that's a four...
- Now open it up, open up those torn up pieces.
- Oh my God!
- This is not even...
- That was freaky.
- That's not possible, man!
- It's crazy!
- Do it again, do it again!
- If you love Nash, Hayes and Ansel, make sure you
give this video a big thumbs up right now
to show your support.
And also, share this video with your friends.
If you want me to do even more magic for your favorite
celebrities, you know what, comment down below who are your
favorite celebrities you'd love to see me do magic for.
And right now it's time for me to feature one of you.
The most active fan this week is:
Ashley Keyper.
So congratulations to Ashley.
You are the Keyper of the Week.
And Ashley, I always see you on my Instagram.
You are posting the coolest edits all the time.
You're super active on Twitter with my Youtube videos:
liking, commenting, sharing them.
So thank you so much, I love you.
So everyone, go follow Ashley right now.
Show her some love.
And if you want to be the Keyper of the Week,
all you have to do is just be super active
on all my different sites.
Make sure you have my Twitter notifications on, Instagram
notifications on, Youtube notifications on, Snapchat.
Make sure you guys are liking, commenting, sharing
my videos, basically the more active you are, the better
chance you have of being featured in one of my videos.
Subscribe to this channel.