- What's up, it's Collins Key
and today I'm going to attempt to read your mind.
I have five cards right here.
Now I want you to take a look at these cards.
I want you to pick one card and memorize it.
Keep repeating the name of your card
over and over and over in your mind.
You got it?
Perfect.
I'm just gonna mix them up right now
and as I mix these cards up, again just keep repeating
the name of your card over and over in your mind.
Awesome.
And right now I want you to look into my eyes
and I want you to imagine sending me the name of your card.
(snap)
Got it
You are thinking of
this card right here.
So hopefully I got this right.
Keep repeating the name of your card
over and over in your mind
and hopefully I was able to read your mind
and remove the one card you were thinking of.
Now if this worked, I don't know please let me know
by giving this video a big thumbs up
and also share this video with all of your friends
to see if I can read their minds as well.
And make sure you subscribe to this channel,
there are new videos coming out each
and every single Thursday.
I hope this worked, I'll see you guys again soon, bye.