- What's up everybody, it is Collins Key,
and welcome back to the Thursday vlog.
So today is the day I am officially back to vlogging.
By the way, for a moment, can we just appreciate,
y'all see this desk?
This desk is gorgeous.
It's not cluttered.
And maybe just in case you're new to my vlogs,
I just want to show you what my desk looks like
before I cleaned it up.
(dramatic music)
And now that I'm back from the tour,
you know what that means!
No Collins, what does that mean?
It means these Thursday vlogs are back on schedule,
every single Thursday.
If you guys are excited that Thursday vlogs are back,
let me know by hitting the like button down below.
To celebrate my return to vlogging,
I thought it would be kinda fun to do a #AskCollinsKey.
Because, I mean, who knows, over the last few months,
I might have changed a lot.
Probably not.
But anyways, I asked you guys on Twitter
to send me some cool questions,
and here are a few of my favorites.
If you had a chance to speak to a camel in Egypt,
what would you tell it?
Probably either,
Bro, you're a camel.
Enjoy it.
Or,
♫ My hump, my hump, my hump, my hump
Emmy said, "Collins, try to say your whole name backwards".
Yeek Schnil-lock.
Schnil-lock, that sounds like villain's name,
it sounds like it would be in Harry Potter.
All the students are like,
"Oh no, I hate Schnil-lock, meh!"
'Cause that's how British people act, meh!
If you're British and watching this video,
please, I don't mean to offend you.
And actually, I want you guys to comment down below:
what is your name backward?
Ana said, "Does Houdini play a role in your magic?"
No, but that's only because he's dead.
♫ In the arms of the an-
Would you rather have a pause button
or a rewind button in real life?
Definitely a pause button.
Basically when it comes to my life,
anything I've done in the past,
I kinda live it under the guard of--
- No regrets.
- So the reason I wanna have a pause button
is because I could do freaking awesome magic.
Could you imagine if I was here one second,
I'd just pause, and the next thing you know I'm just gone.
Like, I'm just not even there anymore.
How crazy would that be?
And then I just pause again, and then I was back.
What do you think about lip piercings?
Not for me.
Can you hug me?
Absolutely, I don't know how to do this through a camera
but I'll give it my best shot.
(camera muffling)
That's probably the most awkward thing I did all day.
Is magic really magic if you know
that the magic behind the magic isn't magic?
#Magic
Magic!
What?
How much does your key necklace mean to you?
I forgot to put it on for this video!
Earlier, I said that I would definitely pause time.
Now I think I might rewind time, put on my key necklace
and shoot this whole video over again.
Alright, there we go. See, boom.
Basically, it was on this entire time,
and y'alls didn't even know it! (laughing)
My god!
Hit that like button if you guys actually noticed
that my key was missing.
You got a bae or nah?
(tongue clicks)
Or nah.
♫ Don't play with a boss
♫ Is you really 'bout your money or nah
♫ Is you with this shiz or nah
♫ Or nah, oh nah
- No regrets.
- If you guys enjoyed this question,
be sure to give this video a huge thumbs up.
And if you guys have any more questions for me,
just hit me up on Twitter @CollinsKey,
and use #AskCollinsKey.
I could not be more excited that I am back to vlogging,
and I want you guys to pick
who do you want to see me collab with,
let me know in the comments down below.
If you guys enjoyed this video,
be sure to give it a huge thumbs up.
Also, if you could, of course, subscribe to this channel.
Once again you guys, my name is Collins Key.
Thank you for watching this week's Thursday vlog.
I'll see you next week, peace.
(upbeat techno music)
- No regrets - What?