- What's up it's Collins Key.
And welcome to the Thursday vlog.
And for today's video,
I'm going to be showing and teaching you
a brand new, super easy life hack
that you guys can try at home.
And this is also a super cool prank
you can try on your friends and your family.
So all you're gonna need for this, to follow along,
is just a water bottle.
I took off the tag and label on it,
so you guys can see exactly what's happening inside.
And you're also going to need a friend.
I've got my very best friend, my little brother, Devan.
- Hello.
- So yeah, so take the water bottle.
First of all, if you were to tip a water bottle,
what would happen?
- Water comes out?
- Well, demonstrate.
- Okay.
- Yay, okay, cool.
So, water comes out.
If you can hold the cap for us.
And this is where the prank element comes in,
cause Devan you're gonna take a seat right now.
- Okay.
Why?
- And here's how this life hack works.
You need to make your fingers are absolutely dry, so.
(blowing air)
Hold up.
Okay, if you put your fingers on.
- Oh gosh.
- They're absolutely dry.
- No, okay.
- Stay right there.
- Yeah, I'm ready, okay.
- And if you turn the water bottle over, like this,
you see how the water stays inside?
This is where it gets risky.
Take your fingers, we go one,
- Dude I don't want to do this.
- Two,
- What the heck?
- Three.
The water will stay inside the bottle.
I wouldn't look up right now.
Okay, there we go.
I have to be very careful.
If you hand me the toothpick.
- There ya go.
- Alright, great, here we go.
The toothpick, watch we just take it.
- What?
- Let me see, do we have the pencil?
The number two pencil?
Check this out.
And then if I can have the jumbo pencil,
this might not work, I don't know.
This thing's like massive.
We'll see if we can keep the water tension.
- Scoot back for this.
What?
And then hand me the cap, really quick dude.
Okay cool, here we go.
Hold it that way, that way it doesn't all spill out.
And yeah, so that is the water bottle hack.
And yeah, if you guys enjoyed this video.
And friend, you can take it,
you can just dump it all out, by the way.
- Okay, just on here?
- Yeah, go for it.
(water splashing)
Dude, chill!
Okay, cool, so that is the water bottle hack.
And if you guys enjoyed this video,
make sure you guys give it a big thumbs up right now.
And also share it with all of your friends,
if you want me to make even more crazy life hacks,
just like this.
Dude.
Okay cool, and also the keyper of the week,
no do not!
It is Caitlyn Kaus.
You are such a bae, I love you so much.
If you wanna be a keyper of the week,
all you gotta do is just make sure you're super active,
follow me on all my different social media platforms,
comment, like, subscribe.
No!
Okay, but yeah, I love you guys so much,
and I will see you again next week.
- Deuces.
- Dude chill, okay we're done.
Alright, bye.