- What's up guys, it's Collins Key and today
I'm teaching you a brand new life hack
here in Beverly Hills with some money.
I'm gonna teach you how to make money instantly
and you can get rich real quick,
so all you have to do for this is grab a few bills,
I like to use one, two, three, four, five dollars,
nothing too crazy, but check it out.
If you take this money, and you're gonna need
on more thing as well, you're also going to need a lighter
because what people don't know is that when bills
are printed, they're first printed as hundreds
and then over that they're printed as ones, fives, tens,
and so on, so if you heat up the ink like this, watch.
Be careful, it's like that, look,
it actually changed, you guys see this?
Look it, that's now one, two, three, four,
$500 just by activating the ink,
so if this life hack blew your mind
make sure you guys share with your friends right now
and give the video a thumbs up if you want me to do
even more crazy life hacks like this in the future.
Comment down below, what other random objects
should I use in my life hack videos
and this is $500 to celebrate the fact
that I just hit 500,000 subscribers here on YouTube.
Shout out to each and every one of you
who have subscribed to me, supported me,
watched my videos, and if you haven't already,
make sure you guys subscribe to this channel,
new videos every single Thursday.
Bye.