- What's up everyone, it's Collins Key and you're watching
Magic Monday!
- As most of you guys know, I just recently performed
at Digifest.
One of my favorite parts about the Digifest is I get to see
all my friends from YouTube, I get to hang out with them
and of course do magic for them.
And if you see any of your favorite YouTubers in this video,
be sure to hit the thumbs up button.
And without further ado, let's get to the magic.
If you see a card you like just touch it.
Just touch a card, any card you like.
- [Man Offscreen] I like the number ten.
- [Collins] All right, take it out.
Just feel it, make sure it's like a regular card,
it's not like tricky or anything.
- It's a regular card.
It's not tricky or anything. - [Girl] Are you sure?
- [Boy] Troye Sivan
(laughs)
All right check it out watch.
So we use this this one in the set.
If you see your card just touch it. Touch it.
Six of hearts, all right.
Take the six, show it to the camera.
Here, put your hand on top of hers like this.
No, her hand.
Six of hearts.
Put your hand on top of hers like this.
- Nuh uh.
Nuh uh nuh uh nuh uh! - Open your hand for me.
Check it out, watch.
When you use a king, that's where it gets crazy.
Raise up one finger like this for me.
Go like this.
It's all good.
Take and touch the king.
Hold out your hand.
Watch the king of hearts.
Take one finger, just touch that king of hearts.
- No. No no no no no
- No!
(screams)
- This is where it gets crazy.
I'm gonna have you turn over the king.
(screaming and yelling)
Turn it over, turn it over.
- No way!
- No no no no no no no no no
- What!
- Now watch here, again we'll try it again.
All right so hold your hand down here like this.
- Oh my
- We'll use a six.
- Do you have more tricks?
- Yeah. Put your hand on top.
- [Girl] This isn't the six anymore now.
- Now put your hand on top.
Put your hand on top.
So you're gonna put your hand on top.
Use the six of hearts all right?
So put your hand on top.
- [Girl] Me too?
- And then Bryan you put your hand on top.
I'm just gonna grab the card out.
Watch I'll give the king a wave.
You'll see what actually happens right there.
- What!
(screams)
- Turn it over.
(laughs)
See look what happens.
I'm actually gonna grab the card out of your hand.
- [Woman] No way. No way no way.
- Watch it here.
- No!
(screams)
- Give this video a huge thumbs up
if you enjoyed all of those awesome reactions.
(clattering)
Dropped my phone.
If you guys enjoyed this video, I've got great news.
Because this video is only part one.
There's a whole nother part two video.
I'm gonna put the link right over here
so be sure to go click that right now.
If you haven't already clicked it, it's gone.
It's gone, you guys can't even click it.
It's gone now.
It's gone.
But in case you guys missed it, it's back now.
So you guys can check it out.
If you guys enjoyed this video,
please give it a huge thumbs up.
Also don't forget of course, subscribe to this channel.
(claps)
Score.
Now if there's a YouTuber you want me to do magic for,
put their name in the comments down below.
Once again you guys, my name is Collins Key.
Thank you so much for watching this week's Magic Mondays.
Peace.
(snaps fingers)
(techno music)
All right let's see, ace of diamonds.
Watch the ace, you ready?
Let's give the ace a wave like that.
- Uh uh!
- No!
- What?
- No no no no no no no.