- What's up, guys?
It's Collins Key, and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Today I'm all the way out in St. Louis
because I have a very special guest with me.
Joining in this chair of awesomeness,
everyone please welcome Lauren Doss.
(snaps)
- [Unison] Hey!
- Yay, welcome to one of my videos,
it's officially happening.
For today's video, we are going to do a
Battle of the Magicians.
For those of you guys who are wondering,
what is going on right now?
Lauren is actually the winner
of the one lucky fan collab,
which I did at my last live performance.
And basically, anyone who participated in the show
was entered into a chance to have me fly out to
wherever they live, have dinner with them,
shoot a collab video,
and I found out today that Lauren is actually a magician.
And if you want me to actually fly out to wherever
you live and be able to shoot a collab with you,
let me know by hitting the Like button down below.
Without further ado, let's get to the battle.
And one more thing, I've been getting a ton of requests
to do another Christmas fan mail blog.
And so if you guys want to send me crazy wacky
fun weird gifts, I'm going to put my PO Box
in the description down below.
So be sure to send them in,
let's get started with the video.
Now for today's magic battle,
we've brought along a deck of Bicycle playing cards
as our weapon of choice.
So I'm going to unsheath the cards.
Extra sound effects.
All the cards are different, and Lauren,
I want you to touch any card you want.
Just touch it, let the magic begin.
Right there, take it out.
I want you to show it to the camera.
Make sure everyone at home memorizes that card,
it's very important, let's see,
the queen of clubs.
So I want you to watch really closely right here,
check this out, watch the queen.
In the middle, push it in.
Lauren snap.
(snaps)
And actually the cut rises all the way through the rest,
to the very top of the deck.
What?
That's crazy.
- Okay, okay, that was pretty good.
I have to admit, that was pretty good.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
- But I think I can do way better.
- Oh, okay then, wow.
Let the competition begin then, let's see this.
- [Lauren] We're going to take the queen of clubs,
we're going to place it about, let's say,
halfway in the deck.
- [Collins] All right, halfway in the deck.
- [Lauren] Okay, just to clarify,
we're going to make sure that the queen is not on top.
- [Collins] It's not on top.
- [Lauren] We're also going to make sure that it's
not the second from the top.
- [Collins] Not the second from the top.
- [Lauren] Or the third.
- [Collins] Not third from the top.
- [Lauren] And it's not in the top three, right?
- That is absolutely correct,
it's nowhere near the top at all.
- All right.
(giggles)
So what I want you to do is I want you
to snap your fingers.
(snaps)
- What?!
I don't know what just happened here.
But let me see it, because actually watch,
if I take this card right here, the four?
Watch, come on in close, watch.
Just by snapping again, Lauren, snap.
(snaps)
You see because you actually, when you snap,
you missed it and you actually didn't quite get the queen.
It was there the whole time, it was.
I was rooting for you.
- What?
- Okay, but watch this,
look right here at the cards, all right.
So watch the queen right here.
The queen goes in the middle.
This one's insane, push it in, Lauren.
Push it in.
You'll see the moment it actually rises
all the way to the top,
look at the queen, the four [Unintelligible].
The four's on top.
Watch right here, watch the four.
Look at, we go one, two, three
(click)
four, like that.
Queen actually melt all the way to the top.
- All right.
- Now that is pretty insane, guys.
That's pretty.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay, yeah.
- I have to say, that was even better than the last one.
- Thank you so much, I really appreciate that.
- But I still can do better.
- Okay then, let's see it.
(laughs)
- We're going to take the queen of clubs,
we're going to take it, we're going to place it about
halfway in this pile.
- [Collins] All right.
- [Lauren] Please push that in.
- [Collins] Push it in, okay.
Push it in.
(snaps)
And I win, because that is not the correct card.
So that's offish.
I think, I think that, at some point, that's just unfair.
Watch right here, look at this, queen.
Goes in the middle.
Push it in.
All the way in the middle.
I think it's about 23 cards down.
This is an insane trick shot,
if this wins, I win it all.
Check it out, right here, watch,
one, two, and it's right.
There.
- Sorry.
- Well, we kind of split that one 50 50.
We'll call this actually a draw.
If you guys enjoyed this video,
be sure to give it a huge thumbs up,
and I want you to comment down below,
who should I visit next?
Lauren actually has her very own magic channel.
I'm going to put the link to it in the description
down below so be sure to go subscribe to her,
and also all of her social media links will be down there.
Now make sure you guys, of course,
subscribe to this channel.
Being a magician, I think you should
make me disappear this time.
Let's try this.
(snaps)
Oh, party time.
Turn it up!