(upbeat music)
- Hey, you look great!
Fantastic, really.
- [Collins] I don't think it's the right look.
- Collins, let's just see what it looks like
under the lights, okay?
(upbeat rock music)
- Pose is good, on your mark.
- What's up, it's Collins Key,
and for today-- - That was great.
Let's reset for the trick.
Get the fire marshal in here.
We're shooting this with the pyrotechnics.
- Has anyone seen Martin?
- I mean how did you do that thing
with the handkerchief and the egg?
That was like insane.
I almost forgot my lines.
But like seriously, how did you do it?
(knocking on door)
- One second.
Oh, hey.
- Woah.
- Yeah, I know.
I didn't think you would come.
- I know how important today is to you, so.
Eddie told me you DMed him to apologize.
That was really sweet,
but I came here to actually talk to--
- Hi, I'm Ashley.
I'm playing his best friend.
- Would you mind giving us one minute?
- Sure, but I'm gonna get that secret out of you
one way or another, Collin.
- Actually, it's.
(door slams)
Do you wanna sit down?
I'm really sorry I let you down man.
I've been an absolute jerk. - No, don't.
- I get why you're mad.
- No, you don't.
I,
I've been thinking, you know about
me and Eddie and,
and you.
- No, and I get that because
you want to be with Eddie,
and I'm going to be
way more supportive. - No, no, no, no, no.
That's not what I'm trying
to say. - No, I know
you're trying to say.
What you're trying to say
what you and Eddie have is,
it's a real relationship,
and I think that's why I've been
so crazy these last few days
because it's the first time in my life
that I've actually
had even the opportunity to have
what you and Eddie have.
I think I was really falling in love back there.
(soft music)
Now she's gone.
And look, it's just a picture of a trailer.
There's no clues, no puzzles.
Time's almost up.
- I just didn't realize
how much you actually cared about her.
What would you do if
you loved someone so much but
you knew something that would mean
that they would be happy,
but it would also mean
that they-- - But what?
If you love someone, you want them to be happy.
- Yeah?
I know where she is.
- What?
- She hasn't left L.A.
It's just another clue.
The trailer, you can rent it.
See, now you know.
- God, I love you, you're amazing.
Thank you.
- But before you go, I need to tell you something.
(knocking on door)
- What's up?
- I um.
- [Ashley] Collins?
Collins, they're ready for you.
- You know what, nothing.
Just go.
Go, go, go.
- You're the best.
I love you.
All right guys, I'm coming.
(door slams)
- Love you too.
(dramatic music)