- Ready? - Start
- Whenever you want, say the word, "stop".
- Stop! - You wanna stay here?
- I do. - Alright here take it.
Then we're gonna show it to the camera.
Got it? - You guys see this junk?
- Heyyyy! - It's your birthday!
- Say stop whenever you want, say stop.
- Okay wait, stop! - Right here, alright.
Great, take it, show it to the camera.
- Dog, you just showed it to them!
- Doesn't matter, doesn't matter.
- Oh it doesn't matter if he sees it?
- Watch, watch the King. - I'm watching it.
- King goes in the middle, push it in Andrea.
- Push it in? - Push it in, push it in.
- That's what she said, ah-haha!
- Ohhhh! - My right ladies!
- King right here.
Goes in the middle about halfway,
snap over the cards, go for it, snap.
- K - Your card,
what if I told you it actually jumped all the way to--
(funny mistake sound effect)
- That wasn't there.
- That actually gets your card to jump all the way to the
shoot, that was the wrong card, right?
- Yeah, yeah! - Yo, it's not that way
(laughing) Hold on,
I'm getting a little bit nervous.
I'm digging on, ya know let's just forget about this,
hold on check it out we'll try it
we'll start out, hold out your hand.
- You literally ripped-- - Don't do this to me!
- Yo, yo here watch, hold out your hand.
- No, no, no I can't do this (censored)
- Okay, actually hold on hold out your hand.
- Don't do this because I'm gonna scream
and Casper's gonna get mad at me again.
- King of hearts, watch the King, you ready?
Now hold your hand a little bit lower.
- No, uh-uh I don't believe this (censored).
- I tore it, I tore it out
but I can fix it 'cause if I wave it like that
then I actually get the 10 right here.
- Yo, what the (censored)?!
- And I tore up one-- - Back in pieces
- No, no (censored) way!
(hip hop music)
- (Crying) No, no, no, no, NO!
- I just ripped the Jack, put it in your hand.
Watch this. - Dude, this is stupid!
- Actually right there, the Jack was torn in my hand
- Wait, how was the Jack ripped, what?!
- And then look what your holding, turn it over.
- Oh my god - No!
- You ripped it dude, it doesn't make sense!
- That's not fair!
- Torn up, right? - Makes no sense!
- No. - You're a wizard, Harry.
- These straight here, now hold out your hand.
These are all, you guys saw me tear 'em up.
These are all torn up hold out your hand, hold out your hand
Make a tight fist.
Now watch, squeeze tight, squeeze tight, tight, tight, tight
- You guys, everyone pile your hands on.
Everyone put your hands on, put your hands on.
- This is so not okay!
- I can't get to it! - This junk is the King
and I swear I'm gonna change it--
- Watch this, watch this. - I'm not letting this happen.
- Okay you're gonna feel it start to heat up, is gonna melt
- You guys, I'm feelin' it, I'm feelin' it!
- It's gonna melt it's gonna melt
it's gonna heat up right now, open it up.
- Oh my god it's melting, it's melting!
Open up all those torn pieces.
- Oh my god, no! - No, no, no, no, no.
- (Censored)
- Shhh, how is it?
- He fixed it!
- Get the (censored) out! (censored)
- Now we're gonna start to heat up.
See right, right there it's gonna start to melt.
Open up your hand, open up those ripped pieces.
Open them up. - (laughing) No!
I told you these ripped cards, bro!
What the heck! (laughing)
- What, nooo!
(electronic music breakdown)
- This is not okay.
- What are you?
- I'm not okay with this (censored).
(electronic music)
- Subscribe to Collins Keys, if you don't,
your mind won't be blown.
- Look at my face right now.
- If you love with Max reaction, let me know
by liking this video.
Now if you want to see me freaking out
even more top YouTubers and Viners,
let me know by sharing this video with
as many people as you possibly can.
And don't forget of course
subscribe to this channel.
And I want you guys to comment down below and let me know
who should I freak out next?
What celebrities, YouTubers, Viners.
If you guys enjoyed this video, I've got great news.
There's two other videos with all of your favorite YouTubers
and Viners absolutely tripping out.
I'm gonna put the video links right here,
and right here so you should go click
those videos right now if you wanna see
some more awesome reactions.
Like, like for real go click those videos right now.
My name is Collins Key, thank you guys so much for watching.
See you guys next week, peace.
(heavy electronic music)