- (Laughs) No.
(lively music)
No, really? No.
(fast speed audio sound)
What's up?
This is Collins Key and as you guys can tell,
I'm in a brand new location today.
I've got a pink wall behind me
and you know what?
I also have an empty chair.
So I need somebody to help me out.
So I'm going to please welcome,
my friend, Lucas. (snaps)
- Hey.
- Yes.
I was self what?
Just appeared.
- Yeah, where'd you come from bro?
- I came from Subway.
- Subway. (laughs)
Are you fresh?
- I was eatin' lunch.
- (laughs) Yeah, well, hopefully,
you didn't get any food in your teeth because--
- I made sure.
- Yeah, yeah, good, yeah.
So for today's video, we're going
to be doing, I believe, the dental opener mouth challenge.
Don't quote me if that's the name
of it or not.
We're taking this to the next level.
We are doing three rounds.
Round number one is physical.
We're gonna try some different
physical tasks with this giant
mouth opener thing in our mouths.
We look so ridiculous.
(Lucas laughs)
Round number two is verbal,
where we're going to be prank calling
some YouTuber's with this thing in our mouth.
And then, round number three,
is going to be a battle of guess the lyric.
And whoever wins the most categories
out of each round, at the end,
gets to hack the loser's Snapchat.
Is how it works.
- It's gonna get real.
- Also we did a video over on Lukas's channel.
So make sure, after this video,
you guys go watch it.
Go subscribe to his channel, it's freakin' awesome.
His videos are amazing.
- Thank you.
- If you guys are one of my people,
then go over to this video,
just got to give us a big ole thumbs up.
And if you guys didn't know,
I'm doing twice weekly videos over the summer.
So make sure you guys have subscribed to this channel.
Make sure you guys turn on the notifications,
that way, you can see the videos
the moment they come out.
Also, I'm doing a big giveaway on my channel right now.
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So if you guys want to win that.
- Gosh.
- Right?
Let me know by liking this video,
comment down below, what's your favorite video
I've ever posted on this channel.
And of course, you must be subscribed to this channel.
Are you ready for this?
- I'm so ready.
- Let's do it.
- Do we just put them on then?
- Yeah, I guess.
How does it?
How does it go?
- Wait, oh, I think I know.
You go like this.
- Oh.
- I did it.
- You're good, you're good.
- I got so high.
- Oh yeah.
- Do I have it on upside down?
- I think so.
Let me look it up to make sure
that I put this in right.
Oh God, okay, it goes down, alright.
(bell dings)
- So right over there, I have a list
of everything we are gonna be doing.
So to start off with, we're going to start easy
and we are going to drink a glass of wa.
- Oh no.
- I can't say, of water.
Is David scarce?
- He is.
(lively music)
- (laughs) No.
(laughing)
No.
- My God.
- Look at my nose.
- I'm going to beat you.
(lively music)
(laughing)
- I just spit water.
Alright, I win that one.
(bell rings)
For round two, we need to use bubble gum to blow it
and I cannot say a "B" with this stuff in my mouth so.
- It definitely looks like we peed our pants.
- And here we go.
- Okay, three pieces is all I need.
This is easier.
- Yeah, it's a lot easier.
- Okay, I'm going in for the kill.
- Alright, drum roll.
(drum roll)
(laughing)
(blows)
Round two.
We got to call it. (laughs)
Alright, round two was a draw.
(beep)
You're not the winner.
Round number two includes bubbles
but now, we have to, actually, blow bubbles.
- Blow the bubbles with the mouth.
- It should be easier, alright.
- Without lips.
Well alright, let's do this.
- Let's do this, okay.
Whoever can do it first wins this round so.
Oh I hate this weird, soapy stuff.
- I know.
(laughing)
(breathing)
- It's just that I had to have
an asthma attack to do it.
(laughing)
- Oh, you win that round.
You won that.
- You blew before me though.
- I don't think so, no.
- I was out.
- I was going to be nice, okay.
- Oh no.
- Okay, I'll take it.
- I think you got it first.
Final category of the physical round,
is we need to, oh gosh.
- Oh God.
- We need to blow a balloon.
- I can do it.
I believe in myself.
- Alright, here we go so.
Three, two, one.
(blowing)
(laughing)
- How'd you do that?
- (Laughs) I can't do it.
Okay, another draw.
I'm going to get a light head.
I'm gonna. (laughs)
- No, no, I can feel a pass out coming.
(laughing)
- I feel a little light headed right now.
(slow motion) I feel a little light headed right now.
That was the end of the first round
which was physical and we are both tied with one point.
- One-to-One.
- Going to the next round, verbal.
(bell dings)
For this round, you have to say
a tongue twister of your choice.
Do you know any tongue twisters?
I think I do.
Sally sells seashells on the shore at Sunday.
I think I did it.
- Sounds good, okay.
Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.
(laughing)
A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked,
if Peter Piper picked a pair of pickled peppers,
where is the peck of pickled pepper Peter Piper picked?
You win that one.
- That was hard.
- That was hard but you win that one.
- Oh my God.
I'm in the lead, not trying to brag.
- The next round is going to be
one of my personal favorites and we both
are going to prank call a YouTuber
and see how long we can last without laughing.
- Without laughing?
- Without laughing.
- Okay, I'm gonna call my little brother.
- Okay.
- He's a YouTuber.
- Alright.
- Let's see here.
I'm gonna call Jacob Cook.
I got in a car accident.
On a, I'll try, on a bicycle.
- [Jacob] Hello.
- Hey, what's up?
I'm home because, you know how I got a dike,
I got a icecale?
I got in a wreck and I bumped into a guy
on the sidewalk and now the icecal's ruined.
Now the icicle's ruined. (laughs)
I made it to 50 seconds.
- That was 50 seconds.
- Hey Jacob, I'm doing a video
with Collins Key and I had to prank call you.
- Yo, what's up?
(laughing)
- No but we're wearing a dental thing.
- That's so funny.
(laughing)
(slow motion laughing)
Alright well, peace out little bra.
Bye.
- Later.
- I lasted 50 seconds.
- 50 seconds, okay, so I got 50 seconds.
So let's see.
Okay, let me call one of the Marrow twins.
I'm going to say I got in a fight.
- Oh a fight.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Hey, I got a question for you.
- I was filming a video, (mumbles)
and we were getting on this really funny thing
where we got in a big fight.
But he, actually, ended up punching me in the face.
- I left the room for a second,
cuz I don't really know what to do.
- Yeah, I think he knocked out a tooth or something.
- Yeah, it was pretty gnarly.
- Yeah.
- No it's not, so like.
(Lucas laughs)
- Now I'm drooling, no.
Okay, sorry, I was just doing a video.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna pass out cuz
I'm, literally, drooling right now.
I feel like, okay, I got to take it out.
The dental mouth thing.
I'm did a prank call for.
I'm so sorry, yeah.
(laughs)
Thank you for being cool and awesome.
(laughing)
- [Vanessa] Okay.
- Alright, cool, talk to you later.
- Alright, bye.
I think I lasted a tiny bit.
That was, I think.
- You lasted longer.
- A little bit longer, okay.
- So I couldn't say bicycle.
(laughing)
(mumbles) so hard are the Bs.
So, we are tied again. (bell dings)
- Are we actually?
- We are tied again.
So this is coming down to the final round
and the final round is guess the lyric.
(bell dings)
- We pick a song and then we have to sing it?
- Sing it or you can talk it.
Cuz I'm a horrible singer.
If you can sing, go for it.
Sing your heart out.
- I can't sing but I do it.
- Then do it, go for it.
- Yeah.
You go first.
- Oh, I have an idea.
- Okay.
♫ Close the hair tie (laughs)
You know, like.
(laughing)
- Sweatshirt, with Jacob Sartorius.
- Wait a second, I get to play or you do?
- (laughs) I think you get to play.
(bell dings)
Cuz you sang it correctly (mumbles)
- Yeah.
- You see me at work, work, work, work.
You see me do my dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt.
- (laughs)Rihanna.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
I didn't do anything.
I just had to, literally, just like.
- I know, you can't understand what you're really saying.
- I saw you at work, work, work, work, work.
You see me do my dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt.
- You nailed it.
- Alright, cool.
So I go first.
I'll just keep going, don't you think?
- Keep going, okay.
♫ My mamma don't like you and she likes everyone.
- Love Yourself.
♫ And I never liked you.
- Is it Love Yourself?
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, Love Yourself, Justin.
I got you New York.
♫ Nugget, biscuit, nugget in a biscuit.
♫ Do you like mashed potatoes
- Cake By The Ocean?
- No. (laughs)
(beeps)
No, I just sang a old Tobuscus song.
Called Nugget, Biscuit, Nugget in a.
- I didn't know it.
- Okay.
- You lose.
- I lose, no.
- No wait, oh.
- No, I lose, okay.
- Oh.
- Alright, I guess.
(slow motion) Oh.
I think Luke is the one.
- I won it?
- Yeah, you won, congratulations.
- I'm so proud of myself.
(trumpet plays)
(crowd cheers)
- Yeah, so he gets to hack my Snapchat.
- I get to hack your Snapchat?
- Yes.
- Hey it's Collins.
What's up?
That's so creepy.
(yelling)
- Alright guys.
Well that is if for the open mouth
dental thingy challenge.
If you guys enjoyed this video
and it made you smile really big,
just like us, let's all give us
a big thumbs up, also, comment down below.
Love your video and part of the video.
You got to come check out the video
we did on Lucas's channel.
It's really, really awesome and really fun.
I taught him how to be a musically master.
So go check it out, the link is right over there
or down in the description.
(mumbles) I'll see you guys again next week, bye.
(snap)