- Donut!
(Screams)
- Oh my gosh!
- It's Play-Doh, bro!
You're telling us to turn real food into Play-Doh food
so right now, let's go.
I gotta wash my mouth out, my gosh!
This round we are going to be making a hamburger, no!
Let's start with the lettuce.
- The what?
Oh the lettuce.
- Called a wham bam.
This is how you make some good
quality organic free range lettuce.
- Where'd you get this bowl?
- I got it from my restaurant.
- What?
- I own a restaurant now.
Oh, oh oh!
Got this thingy here,
which you put in the middle and then you're like.
(screams)
- You okay?
Oh, you didn't see this on your own tool?
- Yeah.
- I thought you owned your own restaurant.
- Yeah, but I wasn't fully trained.
Then we got a, ooh straight cutter.
Whoop!
- Are you qualified to be making Play-Doh food, Collins?
- Maybe not!
- All right, my patty is done.
Next up I'm gonna go for some cheese.
- Some cheese?
- Some cheese right on that burger.
- [Collins] Now I'm just gonna cut my lettuce
in a very squiggly manner.
- They look like green bacon strips.
- Slice
(thuds)
- No, whoa, whoa!
Then I want your bacon.
- No!
(babbles)
- I'll give your bacon back if you give me my burger back.
- No.
(buzzer sounds)
Next up we're going to get the tomato going.
Going to use my little stamping machine.
Check this out from the front, and then from the back.
On a legitimate level, what is the point of this?
- Well if a two year old can figure it out, Collins,
I think you should be able to.
(buzzer sounds)
- And for my tomato, I've got to cut out some,
like you know how tomatoes have holes in them?
Yep, definitely not the right tool.
Yo, yours is actually looking pretty good.
- Aw thanks man.
- Squeeze, squeeze.
- Look at that cheese, look at the cheese.
- I want this whole piece, I need this piece.
- No, my burger!
(slow motion yelling)
C'mon.
- Here we go, so now we got my tomato.
Well, it's a lot smaller than I thought it would be.
(whooping noises)
- To me it kinda looks like a fidget spinner a little bit.
I don't think it'll spin.
Now it's time for the lettuce.
Come back.
- Wait, are you making lettuce again?
- I need to have a super duper long piece of lettuce.
- That's completely unbroken, not a single hole.
- Now the burger part of it
is the most expensive part of my--
So for this we really gotta make sure
that we don't give them too much
so you're not losing money as a business.
So it's gonna, there we go, there's the burger.
But we'll disguise it
with a massive tomato outline around it
so they won't even know it.
Brilliant.
What can this orange be used for?
My burger comes with a fully unpeeled orange.
- Wow.
- All right so now we've gotta place a massive orange in it.
There we go.
Yeah, I've run out of bread
so I'm left with no other choice
but to make the top of my burger
the actual hamburger patty part of it.
So here we go, we got the perfectly round
and symmetrical burger.
Place it on top of the orange.
Actually, game changer.
Coat the orange in the burger.
- That way nobody sees it.
It's a burst of flavor.
- Bite into like an orange rind, like
(chomps)
- [Devan] How is your restaurant still open?
- And then of course to end it off.
(dings)
So now I guess it's just gonna be boring
and I gotta sit back and wait for Devan to finish his.
That looks so good, that is not fair.
All right, here's the big reveal, are you ready?
- Three, two, one.
- First--
Five Second Subscribe Challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, are you ready?
- Five, four, three, two, one, done!
Now if you can do that, comment down below.
- Comment down below.
- Keyper squad right now.
- Three, two, one, tada!
- I am not happy with how this turned out.
So I'm gonna change it a little bit.
- What?
- I need to grab this roller over here.
And uh, see if it works.
Yo, it's perfect burger!
- What?
No, how did you do that?
- Magic.
- What?
- The best thing is, it even talks.
Check this out.
Hey, I'm Bruce the burger.
- The burger's pretty awesome but it's pretty obvious
Bruce is not actually talking, bro.
- [Burger] Oh my god, it's Collins and Devan!
- What? No!
- I am not just a burger.
(both shouting)
- All right, well that's round, let's go.
(trills)
- For this--
- No, not again, really?
- Oh man, we are making a pizza.
I was trying to balance it, but it didn't work.
I'm gonna make this into some dough.
First we gotta actually spin it around
because we gotta get the pizza dough looking good.
So just gonna...
No wow, all right.
- For this I actually have a pizza roller
and I'm going to be making some long bread thin crust pizza.
- Some long bread?
Do we have another roller by any chance?
- You can have it on loan.
- Wow, that's a really thin crust.
It's more like paper crust.
- That's how you know it's thin, Devan.
When it's thin enough to write the independence of decla..
- What?
- [Collins] Declaration of Independence on it.
Got the tomato sauce.
- Ooh.
- Guys ready for this?
It's called the slap pat.
You go slap and then pat!
- What? - Pat!
Luckily I got another one!
- Mine is gonna be a deep dish.
I just have no clue on how to do it yet.
- All my ingredients are super fresh.
I got a special tool right here.
And this turns into the freshest ingredients around.
Check it out!
Bam, there we go!
Fresh tomato!
- You can't use that, that's a real tomato.
- But it's my magical tool, of course I can use this.
Now, I'm gonna crush this into tomato sauce.
(record scratching)
- Whoa whoa whoa bro, you can't do that!
It's a real tomato!
- Okay fine, so I guess we'll have to use the magical tool
one more time, here we go, three, two, one, boom!
There we go, now we got a little tomato.
- How do you do that?
I'm pretty sure this is against the rules, bro.
- Now we go!
- No!
- [Collins] Whoohoo!
- [Devan] That was such an awesome tomato, dude.
- Well now I gotta that for my tomato sauce, Devan.
You don't understand the way my restaurant works.
It's all about the element--
- [Both] Of surprise!
- [Collins] You totally didn't expect real and fake ones.
- Should've guessed.
- Two more tomatoes for
the rest of the tomato sauce.
Boom boom boom boom!
You're gonna do a little bit of bowling here,
and...
(rolling)
Oh, strike one.
Oh, strike two.
Last one, here we go.
(smacking)
Oh!
- Now you messin' with my play-doh.
- That was a gutter ball.
- That's a no-no.
Can I use one of your tools, Collins?
- Sharing is caring, Devan, all yours
- Thank you.
All right, gonna cut a big circle.
- Nice, great job, Devan.
Crushin' the game.
He's not.
- What?
- I mean, look at my tomato sauce!
I have this--
Ow!
- Sorry man, I'm making a masterpiece over here.
- Okay, now it's time to add one of my final elements to it,
which is of course, the cheese.
And you guys, this is a fancy restaurant,
and so we do what's called little cheese.
- Yours looks like a continent, bro.
- [Collins] Kinda like Africa, actually.
- I'm just gonna sprinkle a little bit of cheese on there.
- All right, next up I have to roll this out,
and speaking of rollers, where did my roller go, Collin?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
- Last bit of cheese and now for the finishing touch,
you ready, a pineapple!
(buzzer rings)
What?
- Well, looks like you got automatically disqualified
for putting pineapple on your pizza.
That's a massive no-no.
- Oh my gosh, really?
- So we're movin' on to the next round.
- This round we are making some delicious ice cream.
- Ooh!
- So I'm gonna make a massive ice cream cone
with a ton of scoops, so yay!
- Okay, whoa, all right.
- Whoo-hoo, and yeet!
- Ow!
- I call this the two hand palm to palm technique.
Palm to palm to palm to palm.
- Bro, I'm gonna make a swirl with mine.
Ooh!
- Yeah, well done.
- [Devan] That looks awesome!
- Next ball let's go!
Boom, there we go color number two,
we gotta of course get some vanilla, yeet!
- You've been hitting me this whole time.
Yeet!
Hey!
- You got me!
- Yeet!
- In the back in the head.
I'll get you soon.
All right, my first one is done, look at that thing.
That actually looks pretty cool.
I don't know what kind of flavor this is, but--
- [Collin] What kind of flavor do you think that is?
- Lemon?
- Yeah, maybe.
Tumeric?
- Tumeric?
Ginger!
- Ginger ice cream, you know,
- To give you a little bit of spice.
When you're eating your ice cream.
New game, it's called
"Get the Play-Doh balls in a cup of Play-doh."
Here we go!
(both cheer)
- First try!
(excited babbling)
- What?
Don't mess it up!
- So close.
- So not even close!
- Ice cream scoop-a-doop number one,
- Scoop-a-doop!
- Scoop-a-doop number two,
oh that's coming along nicely.
Scoop-a-doop number three, four!
Boom, and--
(both groan)
Locking mine in right now,
I added some extra flavor to it.
- And I am just about
to add the chocolate dribbles to mine.
(exclaims)
There it is, there it is.
- Looks like a squid!
- Or chocolate dribbles.
- Yeah, or chocolate dribbles.
- That's not even looking too bad, yeah!
Maybe take that one off.
- You even have a whipped cream dispenser?
- Oh yeah, I do.
Alright here we go, ooh this looks so good.
- [Collins] That actually looks like whipped cream,
that's crazy!
- Dude this looks so good!
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
(both exclaim)
- Done!
(stammering)
And locked it in!
- Here we go with the big reveal, you ready?
- Three, two, one--
Tada!
- So you get to comment down below.
- Dude you're cheating!
That's not play-doh!
- That's totally play-doh!
- It's really cold.
- It's just cold play-doh.
- And it tastes exactly like ice cream.
- So guys leave a comment down below,
who won this round,
and we are on to the next one.
- I could have sworn that looked different.
(both screaming)
I guess this round we've got pop-tarts!
(screaming)
- That makes sense!
- Let's make some pop-tarts!
Oh my gosh!
- Alright I'm starting with my pop-tart base.
Hey it didn't hit me this time.
- Check this out, yeet!
(both exclaim)
Time to roll it out my dude!
Alright I gotta make sure my pop-tart's really thin,
because I have a super duper special idea
that I'm gonna be doing with it.
- Wow, dude, you even have a fingerprint in there.
- Here we go, we got the pink first,
oh, this is kind of cool,
this is like a little fleet yeet shot, just--
Sorry.
- You almost messed it up.
- My bad!
So I've got my first layer,
it's called the
"roll in a circle with the palm of your hand".
- Alright, I'm kind of close to being done.
- Well, I--
It always happens!
Next ingredient, I call this one the plum!
- What kind of plum is flat?
- Oh this is gonna be great.
Now for my master strategy to work
I just gotta fold it over.
(gasps)
I think it's gonna work.
Alright here we go, I got a precise slice and dicer!
- Hey, that's my dicer!
- Slice!
And then I'm gonna give it a nice little...
Dice!
In my mind I thought this would look
a lot cooler than it's currently looking.
Well now we gotta seal up the edges,
pinch it together like this.
Looks more like a hot pocket than a pop-tart!
- That's like the chunky veggie hot pocket right there.
(laughs)
- Oh, no you didn't.
This is my final save right here, got my frosting.
Frosted!
Finishing touches, gonna add sprinkles to it.
Ooh, that's a nice sprinkle.
Ooh, that's a very nice sprinkle.
Boom, my best sprinkle yet!
This is what they call, in show business,
or I think in just about any business.
- In play-doh business.
- Make it or br--
- Sorry.
- Make it or break it moment!
Here it is, slice down the middle!
Oh, that does not look promising!
This looks real bad!
Before I fully reveal it,
I'm locking it in right now.
You guys are gonna have to see how it turned out.
Wow!
Here we go with the big reveal, you ready for this?
But first, 3 second like challenge.
We want to see if you can like this video
in three seconds, are you ready?
- Three, two, one, done!
Ta-da!
- Why didn't you work?
(screams)
- What are you doing with my best friend?
(all scream)
- This round we are making some pasta.
So right now, let's make some noodles!
Yeet!
And then we go woo, and then we go yeet!
- How do those all hit me?
Why do you get to go first?
- Because I'm the older brother.
Devan, I am the older brother, you can't do this,
it's against my--
- I made it!
(grunts)
Look at that!
Okay, well-- Oop.
Oh yeah, look at those nice noodles man.
- Well, I just have one long noodle.
Just gonna make one super duper long noodle.
And just a little bit of spaghetti sauce,
just to like coat the top of the noodle.
It almost looks like a snake of some sort.
Boom, spaghetti, yeti.
Three, two, one!
Boom! Oop, where'd it go?
Got it!
Here we go, I'm making meat stars.
- Oh, snap!
Cool.
- Time to shred my meatballs!
Why is it yellow, that's not good.
It's still yellow!
This is the finishing touch on my dish, you ready?
If this meatball lands in the dish,
you get it in your order.
- What happens if it doesn't?
- You don't get a meatball.
I'm gonna close my eyes and see if I can do it.
Three, two, one.
(swoosh)
Has it landed yet?
- Yep!
It totally landed.
- Where did it go?
- I think you made it disappear man.
Your magical powers are failing.
- What?
No way, because if I want my meatball back,
I can get it back.
(claps)
Oh my gosh, where did that come from?
Goodness!
Done!
A masterpiece.
- But it didn't technically land in there, so uh--
- What it did, it was like a meteorite,
and it was like magic, and now it's there.
- Uh, okay.
- Locking it in.
Devan's taking forever, but remember guys,
at the end of this we'll be looking inside the mystery box,
and I've heard there's something super cool
and delicious inside of it so,
we can't eat any of the play-doh food,
but hopefully we'll be able to eat
whatever is inside of the mystery box
and hopefully it won't actually be terrible.
- Alright, it is finally time to lock it in.
- Three, two, one, ta-da!
- So, yeah, you get to comment down below,
who do you think won this round
and made the better whatever.
Remember, mine's creative,
you've never seen a one-noodle pasta before.
So, right now we're on to the next round.
- Check this out!
- Dude!
- They smell so good!
- They're like tiny little versions of candy!
- What is this?
Oh, I thought it was a mustache at first.
(old-fashioned music)
- Hey, it's a pineapple!
- It's a pineapple!
- Do not put this on a pizza, I learned my lesson.
- I won't.
Bro, this one even has a bruised bit!
- Man, the attention to detail on these.
- So I guess you just wanna try them?
- Uh, yeah!
- Comment down below what other foods
should we make out of play-doh.
I guess we should try the ice cream cone first?
- I'm gonna go for the watermelon Popsicle, bro.
- Alright, here we go, ready?
- Three, two, one.
(moans)
- The texture!
It's like cookie dough!
But like way sweeter and not chunky at all.
- Oh my god.
- Wow.
- Yo, this one looks like a tomato!
- I'm going for the strawberry, dude.
- And the craziest thing is
the texture kinda reminds me of play-doh.
We weren't able to eat any play-doh this whole time.
- Oh, you're right.
- That's why it's in the mystery box.
Alright, let's take a bite, you ready?
- Three, two, one.
(moaning)
- What?
(mumbles)
- It's plastic?
- Why would you eat the plastic?
- I'm gonna take a bite of this one.
- Flamingo is the best one!
- Alright subscribe right here for another video,
(mumbles)
- Five, four, three, two, one!
Done!
- Thank you for watching,
- Bye!