- [Devan] You challenged us to make slime out of shampoo
so you can get luscious locks, just like mine.
Oh no, where's the shampoo?
- [Collins] Oh no!
(screaming)
- All right, enough with that, now it's time
to open up the box and get our ingredients.
- [Both] Whoa!
- They're like balloons!
We got baking soda, contact solution.
- Glue!
- We got some shampoo.
And also got some glue!
Bam, all right! We got the shower ring things.
We're gonna use these to open up the balloons.
So I'm gonna go with glue first.
- Oh okay, okay, did it work?
Oh! - Oh!
(coughing)
- Baking soda. (air horn blasts)
- Oh!
And using balloons to get like slime ingredients
is currently trending on YouTube.
That's a weird noise.
- Bro! I got Sharpie all over my hands!
- Oh man, I'm nervous about this one.
It's up in the air again.
- Mixing time!
- Is that the mixer?
- Yeah, dude, this is totally working!
- Three, two, one. (splashing)
(screaming) (sad piano music)
- Dude!
- It went in my eye! Oh snap, this is awesome!
You may be questioning my fashion,
but this is what they're really for.
In the loofahs while I loofa-cate it.
- Dude, I found a hair in mine.
- Oh, it's from the wig!
- You get to comment down below
who made cooler shampoo slime,
and the real winner should be the one
who has the most loofahs on their wrists.
That's me.
- Last time, you challenged us
to make a slime out of a toothpaste.
- Yes!
- So we got the toothbrush-- - The what?
- Gotta brush my teeth now.
No time for plaque!
- All right, now it's time to add the toothpaste
to the water.
(screams)
All right, time to empty the water bottle
that we have to drink out of first.
(mumbling)
(coughing)
- This is going great.
(mumbling)
(screaming)
(gurgling)
- It went down my shirt.
(swallows) - Got it.
I'm gonna empty out the rest right now.
Got a light saber.
- Dude, what are you doing? (mumbling)
No, we're making slime, we're not brushing our teeth.
(mumbling)
- Oh!
- Oh, now it's time to shake it up.
- All right, so we're going to pop this out, here we go.
Oh! - Oh!
- The baking powder!
Okay, (blabbers) the top is not on!
So we're going to say about, like, that much.
That's it, that's it, right there.
Bam.
- Did I add too much? - You added way too much, bro.
So now it's time for the shake-a-rake. You ready for this?
(shaking)
Oh snap!
- Now it's time to add some of this stuff which is...
Face wash.
Or face mask.
- It's party time.
- Ooh, the sound.
- And then you add some of this baking soda.
- Better not use this as toothpaste
or it's gonna add the face wash in.
(squelches) - Ugh!
- Next step, you stir it with your toothbrush.
- Peep these out, bro.
They're like little sticky jumps. Boop. - Oh, yeah.
- Oh, these are awesome.
- No, no, no.
- Trickshot time, here we go.
(pop) (buzzer)
Well that didn't work.
All right, let me try it one more time.
- Oh, hey.
- Woo, trick shot!
- Once you have this mixed over here
and you have this all shaken up,
now you combine them together.
(sneeze)
Dude. - Sorry.
- Now you mix it together.
(angelic music)
It smells so good.
I think it needs more.
- I don't know if you know what you're doing, bro.
- I don't.
- Next step, you get a little bit of contact solution
you gotta add in here. - Wait, what?
- Bloop, that's it.
Whoa! Have a little slime dance like
(yells)
All right, here we go, the moment of truth.
Is it going to work with the toothpaste?
Oh. - Oh.
[Devan] So, that's how it's suppose to be.
(yells)
Dude.
- Wow, that is, like, so pungent with the mint.
- Oh, man. Like it really just makes your nose just go
(voicing silly sounds)
- I love mint.
- You know, I think my slime was a little bit better
before I added the toothpaste, to be honest.
Dude, yours is literally the craziest slime
you have ever made, so here's the big reveal.
Three, two... - Three, two...
- Wait, first.
We've got merch! - We've got merch!
- And you can own some too 'cause just imagine
how cool you're gonna look wearing this.
- Or this.
- So, click the top link in the description
or go to ShopCollinsKey.com right now
to get your merch before it's all sold out.
Ready, set, go!
(both yell)
- No, mine totally failed, bro.
Dude, yours is so cool, what? - What?
It's, like, literally toothpaste slime.
So, this stuff looks absolutely crazy.
- It's almost like it has glitter in it.
- What?
You can get to comment down below,
who made cooler slime for this round,
and at the end of this video
we're gonna be making a grand slam slime
with ingredients from this whole video.
We'll be saving the toothpaste to add to our final slime
and right now, we are on to the next round.
Time to get clean. (squirt)
Oh! - Oh!
- Snap! See, we gotta keep things clean,
so we're gonna show you how to make soap slime, bro.
This is how you clean properly, bro.
Just go like this, and get it into the bowl.
- Oh my gosh, the concentration.
It's like the lake at a putt-putt golfing place.
- Oh, snap.
For something so clean, man, it sure made a mess.
But I'm gonna scoop it up here, wash my hands
as it goes in because ya always gotta make sure
to wash your hands thoroughly.
- I made a bubble! I made a bubble! There's a b...
- I got it!
- Bam! Now I'm gonna transferred to this finger.
What?
I am like a bubble factory, bro.
- This is my chance!
Oh my gosh!
- All right, in order to separate the yolk
from the egg white,
I have to use this water bottle.
But first, I have to get the water out.
- [Collins] Hopefully I don't get soap on the bottle.
Devan's almost done, but I can beat him.
(tape whirring)
(coughing)
- And done!
You can not beat me.
Three, two, one.
(squirt)
Oh! What?!
I did not expect that to work.
Oh, oh no.
Oh, I got it.
Oh no!
When it's a broken yolk, it doesn't work.
- [Collins] Here we go.
And I emptied out, two more eggs,
I'm gonna do these at the same time.
Head-to-head competition. (crack)
So who won? - This guy.
I'm just gonna go for a different method.
Just hand-grab.
It's a lot easier, just like this.
This gets the yolk out.
All right, just gonna transfer this--
- And intercepted!
- Oh! He stole my yolk!
- [Devan] Is yours already mixing?
- Yeah, dude, I'm mixing my stuff.
- I haven't even added my soap yet.
This looks like some weird snot, dude.
(sneezes)
- Oh oh! Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, bro.
It increased its slimy-ness by like 5% just now.
Dude, you're mixing like a chef.
Like a professional Michelin Star chef.
- Thank you for the compliment
- Got little boats, man.
Little eggshell yachts.
Uh-oh. We're encountering a storm.
(thunder)
- [Devan] Dude dude dude dude dude!
Yo, my drips so good.
- But, I mean, can yours do this, bro?
- Uh, no, what?
- Woohoo!
There's a bubble, yes, I have a bubble.
I've never seen that before!
Wow!
- Oh, don't leave us!
- Oh, it popped.
Yo, dude, that is so cool. - Oh, dude.
- The only issue, though, is that this is not a real bubble,
because it's also got egg in it.
So you don't want to get this bubble everywhere.
So you get to comment down below, who made cooler slime?
Is it my bubble slime?
- [Devan] Or is it my Ghostbusters slime?
- So, yeah, comment down below right now.
We will be adding dish soap into our final grand slam slime.
And right now, we are on to the next round.
In this round, you challenged us to make
one ingredient slime, and all you need is gum.
Dude, how did you blow such a big bubble?
(deflating)
It's a balloon.
So we're gonna get this out there.
(grunting)
That's what you call "shelling the gum".
Check this out.
Yo, check it out, bro, it's all shelled!
Just like that.
Three, two, one...
(exclaims)
Yo, I had no clue this is what gum looks like
on the inside, bro, it's like...
(voicing silly noises)
All right, guys, we're gonna shell all of these.
Or just unwrap them.
We'll be back in like five seconds.
Here we go. Boop!
We shelled all the gum.
So, I've got Bubble Yum.
- I have Orbit.
Oh! - Oh my gosh!
The only thing left you gotta do is
just to add some hot water into it.
So, I have the Bubble Yum
and we're trying to see which one is,
what?! - Ow, I got it on me!
- Be careful when pouring hot water.
- I poured too fast.
- So, now I'm just gonna kinda, like,
let them soak in here for a little bit.
Let's rub some balloons.
(squeaking)
- I'd rather pop them.
Three, two, one.
(pop)
(yelling)
(buzzer)
(blow)
(yelling)
Dude, it hit me in the side of the face.
- Let's see how our gum is doing.
All right, our gum has been sitting here
for about five minutes.
Time to dump the water out.
(yelling)
- This water looks really tasty, though.
- I don't think you should drink gum water.
Probably not the best thing to do.
So now it's all melted down and,
time to see if we can turn it into slime.
Yo, dude!
It like totally melted the the gum down.
- Look at mine!
- Whoa!
That's why we tried two different gums, 'cause we're
gonna get two different results.
- [Devan] Oh!
- [Collins] Oh, it's like juicing now, man.
This water's just kablooshin' everywhere.
- Dude, it's, like, legit turning into slime!
This is so cool!
One-ingredient slime with gum, bro.
This is the future!
- [Devan] Why is mine so gross?
- What?!
This is by far the coolest slime ever because it's also gum,
so you could technically chew it at any point.
- [Devan] Avert your eyes.
- [Collins] Why? Oh.
So, there is actually one flaw with mine;
It's very sticky.
- But that's not a flaw.
This is a flaw.
- Dude, I think I'm like one of the
professional taffy-makers, you know, they're like...
(voicing silly noises)
It looks like a burger more than it looks like slime.
Maybe you made the first-ever slime burger.
But dude, you gotta eat it, but first you gotta give it a
woohoo!
This is what I call "the stick test".
Three, two, one.
(slap)
- Whoa!
- Yeah, this definitely doesn't pass the stick test.
My slime.
Bubble Yum worked super duper duper well for this.
- And this worked terrible.
- Three, two, one.
(chomp)
(stretch)
- [Devan] That seems so amazing.
Can you blow a bubble?
(blowing)
- All I gotta say...
(mumbling)
This gum!
- Oh, this gum is...
- Really good.
It looks like a pizza.
All right, go for it, man.
- Three, two, one--
- Wait, wait, first!
Five second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel and
turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready? Here we go.
Five, Four, Three, Two, One. - Five, Four, Three, Two, One.
Done. - Done.
You can comment down below, Keyper squad right now.
And Devan, time to eat it.
Let's see how this thing tastes.
(chomp)
wooh! - Oh!
It tastes so good.
All the bubblegum-ness left, and all the mint stayed.
- You can comment down below, whose gum slime turned out
better and now it's on to the next round.
Soda hat!
Eh! - Wait, what?
What is going on?
This morning, you challenged us to make soda slime,
so right now, let's go.
Now it's time to add the soda.
- Why is mine so small?
- 'Cause you're the younger brother and so you get
the smaller soda, you know how it goes.
All right, just gonna add a little bit in.
And I've got Coke, you've got Pepsi,
so you know what that means, right?
(yell)
(grunt)
(lightsabers clashing)
(yelling)
(deep voice) Devan, I am your older brother.
- No!
- Well, that was fun, and now.
(screams)
Time to mix it up and hopefully create some bubbles.
- Uh, Collins, when you said "create bubbles", did you mean
actually create bubbles?
Look around for a second.
- Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
(blowing)
Now it's time for some contact solution.
The reason you use contact solution is because
it'll actually create a clear slime,
which is kind of what we're going for in this one
where the Sta-flo makes it kinda milky.
Around the circumference of the bowl.
- Ah, it just hit my face.
- And I am very excited because I've got a new way.
I'm mixing up this slime.
It's little tongs with these little holes in them.
See, you put it in here and now you, like, scoop it up.
You'll be like, whoa, okay, how's my slime doin'?
I must admit,
this contraption worked a lot better in my head.
So, I think I'm gonna just go in with the hands.
Whoa, this slime did not turn out well at all.
You get to comment down below, who made cooler soda slime.
It just, like, it just breaks apart.
- At least yours is actually slime.
- [Collins] Yeah. - [Devan] Mine is just glue.
Oh! - Oh snap!
Well you challenged us to make kinetic sand slime.
First step, we gotta add the glue.
So I'm just gonna pick this up right over here.
(clicking)
- Whoa, whoa!
Did I break it? - Yeah, you broke it.
Oh, I hope it doesn't break!
(screeching)
(yelling)
All right, there, easy.
- His name is Asbestos.
- Uh, what?
(yelping)
Dude, it's a fork.
There you go, now tip it.
Yeah.
It's stuck, it's stuck.
- So now, next step, we gotta add the Sta-flo,
but first, Devan, you gotta put on your decorative hat.
- I feel like a bird.
You know, like...
- Next step, gotta add the Sta-flo,
so just gonna pump it in there.
There we go. (Devan growling)
- Dude, what are you doing?
Are you scuba diving?
It's not recommended.
(gurgling)
It sounds like a car.
- All right, well, for this next part, guys, I'm goin' in.
And you know what that means.
- No.
- Too small for my head, wow.
(grunting)
Ugh! - Really?
Luckily we got some smaller goggles.
So here's what we can do. - Nice.
- Put these on right like this, and you need
smaller goggles, nemma nemma nem.
Only with my, ow, let go, let go.
- I can't, I can't, you trapped my arm.
- No!
- You know you could just use the goggles, right?
- Ow.
(yelling)
I got two goggles!
(tape whirring)
There's my thingy!
I'm goin' in.
You gotta mix up the slime.
(mumbling)
- [Devan] Time to add our sand.
- Ooh! - In the slime.
This stuff smells weird.
Oh, this is not like sand at all.
- Use your claws to make it slimy.
- Yeah, you didn't do a good job with that slime,
no offense.
- Uh, offense taken, bro.
Uh, what?
All right, gotta pop it in my bucket of joy.
And then just...
(squish)
- Ugh!
(laughing)
- All right, this stuff here is called Connecticut sand.
It comes from Connecticut.
- No, it's kinetic.
- Kansas. - Connecticut.
- Kansas! Comes from Kansas.
So now I'm just mixing up my slime.
- [Devan] Whoa!
- Yo, it's already kinda, like, sandy.
You get to comment down below right now,
who made crazier sand slime.
And this stuff feels so wild,
you can feel all the grains of sand in it.
But it's really satisfying at the same time and right now
we are on to the next round.
(yelling) (leaf blower blowing)
Well, you challenged us to do toilet paper slime
so right now let's go.
- All right, so the first step is to
tear up some toilet paper.
- I got you, bro!
(leaf blower blowing)
(yelling)
- I got it, I got some!
- You might need to share,
I might need a little bit. - No!
- Let's tear up the toilet paper now, so we gotta get these
into as small pieces as we possibly can.
Next up, we gotta add a little bit of Fiji water to what's
going on, so we gotta open this up.
Just a little bit, Devan.
- Wait, why Fiji water?
- Because it's from Fiji, it's a little island.
- You make no sense.
- I know, not.
- What are you a robot now?
(robotic voice) I do not make sense anymore.
- Toilet paper.
All right, so now I guess we just mix it up a little bit
with the water.
- [Devan] There is no mixing up, it just turns into a ball.
- It's snowing!
So next up, you're gonna add some stuff.
(singing)
Yeah!
- Got my hype-man over here.
- [Collins] Gonna add some glue into what's goin' on.
Gonna take this toilet paper off of here and you're
not gonna need it again.
You need a little dispensary over here,
so just use it to just dump the glue in.
- It actually seems harder, Collins.
- Oh!
No! - Dude, no!
- Nothing happened, all is good.
My toilet paper is not, like, at all doing anything in here.
- Same with mine, actually.
- Ugh, can you not?
It looks like a giant, melted marshmallow right now.
It's like, I kinda wanna... I shouldn't eat it...
Dude, my slime's, like, clogged up.
I gotta fix this.
Here we go.
- [Devan] Wait, what, dude...
- Oh no!
- [Devan] It's like it got cemented in there.
(yelling) - What happened?
- (booming voice) What? - (laughs)
- You yelled right in my ear.
- I wonder if I can, like, do it to the table.
Oh, snap!
Oh, woo-hoo!
- Next step for me is to add some clay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. (record screeches)
Excuse me, it's not just clay, it's Soft Clay
(soft piano music)
by these guys.
Whoa, my slime is kind of chunky, funky,
not at all optimal, but it's time to add the clay in now,
because while Devan's doing it,
I don't wanna be left behind.
Gonna place it here,
and now it's time to get it in!
This plunger, man, it definitely does not do the job.
Come on, get out of the bowl.
Woo, this has gotta be one of the messiest videos
we've ever done, bro.
(yelling)
Well, I now added the toilet paper in mine.
Hopefully that makes a better slime.
- [Devan] Okay, okay, okay.
- [Collins] All right, all right, gonna mix it in now.
- Dude, yours looks insane.
- (demonic voice) The workout is real.
In through the nose, out through the mouth.
- Yo, leave us a comment down below,
who made cooler toilet paper slime.
And we'll be using toilet paper in our final
grand slam slime at the end of the video,
so right now it's on to the next round,
dude, you better chill.
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Whoa, no, dude! - All good.
- Banana time!
Hey, yo, it actually worked!
So, we're gonna show you how to make some lotion slime,
so right now, let's go, banana time.
(glass shattering)
Gotta pop a banana out, put it into my thing of glue.
There we go.
Yeah, this is the unprecedented,
you ain't never seen this before.
It's the first time ever.
(laughing)
- Ugh!
Next up, we add food coloring.
Wait, dude, no, not lotion.
- Is that too much lotion to use do you think?
- Definitely.
- All right, dude, you gotta add a couple dots of the blue.
- That's why you don't use hand lotion
before you make the slime.
- [Collins] Whoa, that's, like, the coolest color of blue
I've ever made with a slime before.
Gotta take this banana and then just crack it in half.
And now you got mushed-up banana in your slime,
which is exactly what you want.
- It should be called the Break-Up Wake-Up,
'cause you breaked it. - (buzzer)
You broked it. - (laughing)
- [Collins] All right, well the food coloring's mixed in,
so next up, it's time to add baking soda.
(jolting noises sounding)
- [Devan] That's a lot, right?
- Yeah, well, not really.
- Oh wow, wow, wow, wow. - The air tastes weird.
- Ugh.
All right, we're gonna get the spatula out of here,
it's messing with my jam, so.
- [Devan] Yeah, should've been mixing from the
front part of the spatula.
- [Collins] Have you ever used a spatula before?
- Apparently not.
Next up, we add the lotion.
- But first it's time to demonstrate the
power of the lotion!
Got a piece of a dried up banana.
Yeet!
Lotion!
(laughing) - Jeez.
- Thank you!
Just rub it right on there and...
Tah-dah!
You have a full banana!
(mumbling)
You can eat it.
And now you know (booming voice) the power of lotion!
- All right, movin' on.
I'll just add this for you.
- [Collins] Yeah, can you please add the lotion for me.
- [Devan] All right, there you go.
- The power of lotion! - Whoa, no no no!
(yelling)
(sighs)
- [Collins] Right off the bat, the lotion has actually
kind of turned this into slime.
And also, like, chunks of banana in here, so
hopefully that doesn't mess with the whole concoction.
(squeaking)
Whoa! - Whoa!
I got it on pants.
- So basically the lotion, ow.
So basically, this lotion acts like the Sta-flo,
so it acts as the activator in it.
Man, this is coming out so slow.
(growling)
[Collins] Is yours working?
- [Devan] Yep, it's workin'.
What? Why is yours so gloopy?
- [Collins] Ugh, there we go, oh!
That's a ton of baking soda.
Dude, I think it worked!
- Yeah, but look at mine.
- Wooh!
Quite the workout, I gotta admit.
Like, lotion is usually soft, smooth, and suppulent.
Suppulent?
Succulent.
No, that's not it. - I don't know.
Dude, it actually worked!
You get to comment down below, who won this round and
who made better lotion slime
and right now we are on to the next one.
For this one we are making a--
- Payback!
Wooh! (leaf blower blowing)
(coughs)
That's what I'm talkin' about!
- Well, I'm now wearing a toga.
For the grand slam slime, we get to use any items that
we want for this time to make the coolest one possible.
So I'm kicking off with toothpaste right now.
And then next I'm gonna go for some sand,
so I'm gonna pop.
(pops) Oh!
So we're gonna pop some sand in here, just.
- Bro, I should not have started out with gum, it's so slow.
- Get out of there, toilet paper, it aint your time.
[Collins] Why did we never use this earlier, bro.
Gotta get a little.
(making screeching noises)
Then they're being like, aw, skert!
- [Devan] Now, this soda should dissolve the gum,
just like the water did, so, hoping it has the same effect.
- It was hot water, bro, that's, like, cold soda.
- [Collins] Next up we got some shampoo.
- And I've got lotion.
Dude, this does not come out.
I'm scooping it out.
Nope, that doesn't work either.
(squish)
- So, I'm just gonna take off my toilet paper toga right now
and pop it in here like this.
This was a lot of toilet paper and not a lot of slime.
- [Devan] This looks so gross.
- [Collins] That is not a pleasing color at all, man.
- No it's not.
- [Collins] Here we go, so that should mush it down.
Break down the toilet paper just kinda bit by bit, you know,
and then just adios, amigos.
Oh. - Oh.
- You gotta relax, guys.
More glue!
- I hope you didn't need lotion,
because I'm kind of using it up.
- My slime's got the sand in it,
so it's got a certain amount of grain to it.
- Oh!
- It's, uh, not the best. - I forgot about the sand.
Well, there we go.
- Well, mine's turning into like a slushie soup
that looks kind of like melted ice cream.
(tape whirring)
So here are the final mystery slimes.
Mine's like a toothpaste, toilet paper, lotion,
shampoo, slime, what is yours, Dev?
- Mine's like a red dragon, grainy, crusty slime.
- Comment down below, what are some other household items
you would love to see us use in a future video.
If you want to get your very own Keyper Squad shirt,
click the top link in the description right now!
If you want another video, click right over here,
you have five seconds, here we go.
Five, Four, Three, Two, One! - Five, Four, Three, Two, One!
Done, love you, bye! - Done, bye!