- [Both] High five!
- Oh my gosh.
Would you challenge us to mix together
every single sour candy into the largest
giant sour gummy bear of all time, but there's a twist.
So, right now let's go.
All right, Devan, so with your eyes closed,
you gotta guess what this is.
Oh my gosh.
- Oh, okay.
- Pop it open.
- Sounds like a bag already.
(coughing)
Bro, what?
(clapping)
- Holy crap, my eyes are literally watering right now.
- Is it there?
- [Collins] Three, two, one.
- All right, it crunches like a chip,
but oh, oh, whoo, oh, it's spicy.
- It's spicy.
- Dude, what is this?
(screaming)
- What are you hitting?
- The sticks of glory.
- Ow, my lip.
- Wait a second.
Open your mouth, Devan.
- Okay.
- [Collins] Keep your eyes closed.
Three, two, one, here we go.
- Oh, ah, what was that?
That was not the same at all.
Dude!
- Take a bite of it.
- Ow, my lips burn.
Ow, is it a fish?
- A fish?
- It's a chip.
It's a Dorito.
- Yes, but what kind of flavor?
- A spicy fish?
Spicy tuna.
- No! - What?
- Devan, you can open up your eyes.
- Okay.
- They're Wasabi Doritos.
- Oh.
- And I literally put a chunk of Wasabi in your mouth, bro.
- Oh my gosh.
Now you can choose a sour candy
from the Mystery Bag of Doom.
- Okay, got it.
- I guess we'll have to make this go away, so here we go.
You ready?
Oh, snap.
So, Devan, now let's see what sour candy you got.
- Oh!
- It's like a clump of gummy worms.
Yo, so wait, are you just gonna take a bite of that?
- Yeah, I mean, I think I have to at this point.
- Well, save some though because we need to use this
for the giant gummy bear that we're making, so.
- All right.
- So I guess, put a little bit in here.
- Dude, you're just slamming everything around.
- And, here we go.
And take your bite, Devan.
- All right, here we go.
Oh, oh, dude, whoa.
- Make sure you stick around because we will be making
the largest giant sour gummy bear in the entire world,
but right now, you're onto the next round.
He's gone.
Where did he go?
- All right, Collins, close your eyes.
- Okay.
- This is the next item.
- What is that?
It sounds like it's gonna chip my tooth.
- Oh, it might.
- Let's see if I can get some flavor.
- All right, go for it.
- Oh, what is that?
- Let me see this.
- What is this, bro?
- Wait, can you guess it?
I mean, it should be pretty obvious by now, right?
- I think it's a cucumber soda,
which is the weirdest thing.
- Dude, you got it!
- So, we got the Bag of Doom back, Devan.
Choose your next sour candy.
- No, oh, it's sticky.
It's got ants in it.
- That reminds me of the liquid glass that we made.
- Oh, no.
- But it has ants in it.
(laughing)
- Oh, really?
- Dude, if the ants just wanna crawl
away on the table, that would be so freaky.
- No, don't even say it.
- But you got it now, Devan.
Take a lick of it.
- Dude, is this even sour?
- Yes.
Yeah, look at it, it's got the malic acid
looks like on there.
- Oh, no, you're right, it does.
Three, two, one.
- You're gonna chip a tooth.
- Ow, that hurt so bad.
All right, oh, oh.
- Are you good?
- No, dude, what do you think, it's malic acid.
- Bam!
- Look inside of this.
- Dude, you cracked like on an ant.
All right, guys, so Devan and I,
we're gonna do the largest gummy bear ever.
We'll be doing at the end, but right now,
we are on to the next round.
All right, Devan, close your eyes.
- All right.
- And here is the next crazy, weird, food.
Check this out.
- Oh no.
- Wait a second.
That is not what was supposed to be there.
There's only way to fix it. It's called Yeet-Za.
(laughing)
- Oh, dude!
- Yeet-Za is not for everyone.
- Oh, man.
- Let's just see if it worked.
Boom, there we go.
That's more like it.
Devan, I'm so sorry.
- Dude, can I just win this round automatically for that.
- You literally, hold up, hold, up, hold up,
on your forehead.
- What?
- Nothing, you look great.
Here we go and remember, a sour candy is on the line.
- It's a pizza.
It's like a Pringle and it's a pizza.
- How did you get that right so quickly?
- Dude, you said Yeet-Za.
- I'm gonna go with the claw, you ready?
Move this off to the side that way.
- No, no, no.
- I don't wanna do this.
These are gonna be terrible.
This is, hang on, sour pink lemon.
Feel likes a pink lemon.
- It's a grapefruit, bro.
That does exist.
- Here we go.
Three, two, one.
- No, you can't pull that all the time, dude.
You gotta eat it, bro.
- Okay, fine, okay, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Yeah, oh finally.
How's it taste, Collin?
Really good?
All right, well, maybe try another one.
Maybe it'll help.
All right, onto the next one.
What, I don't, what are you saying?
I already said onto the next one.
- The bowl!
- The what?
- Oh, got it.
- All right, next round, let's go.
- Collins, close your eyes.
And this is the next item.
Whoa!
All right, ready?
- Yeah.
- Three, two, one.
It's not that bad.
- It's all like hairy and fluffy.
- Any guesses?
- This is not good
- I feel like this would actually be pretty good.
Really?
- Oh my god.
- Well, do you have any guesses?
- Oh, it's got a sweet and kinda salty...
Oh, oh, bacon!
It's Bacon Cotton Candy!
- No, how did you get that?
- Yahoo!
- Dude, how did you get that?
- Sorry, what did you say?
- How did you get that?
- Sorry, one more time.
I can't hear you.
- How did you get that?
- Sorry, what did you say?
- What, bro, how did you do that?
(Collin mumbling)
- This one's really cool.
- Dude, what?
How did you do that?
- Magic!
Damn, Devan gotta choose one of the Bag of Doom!
- All right, fine.
This one!
Whoa, it feels really light.
What's inside?
I don't know.
Oh, wait, what?
- What?
- Yo, they sound like they're little maracas.
- No!
- Yes, I've never seen a sour candy like this before ever.
- Three, two, one.
- But first, 5 Second Subscribe Challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds.
Are you ready?
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you can do that, comment down below "Keyper Squad"
right now and Devan, go for it.
- Oh!
- It's like all the little beads
all around your teeth right now.
He's rocking back and forth.
- Wow.
- I don't know how to do this, but this looks like
such a weird candy, I want to try it too.
- Yeah, go for it.
You okay?
- And next round, let's go.
Here we go!
Next item, but this is not exactly
what I wanted it to be.
All right, hold on, I gotta get it ready, so.
How it comes in the wild, you know?
Perfect!
All right, so let's do this.
- Oh, oh, it's a drink. It's a drink of some sort.
- You have to take a little sip of it,
see what you think.
- Oh, man.
- Are you okay?
- No.
- What do you think it is?
- It kinda tastes really sweet, like a butterscotch.
- Is that your final guess, butterscotch?
- Yes.
- Bro, it's corn.
- Really?
- Yes, it's corn soda.
Bam, Devan! You are losing this challenge.
- Oh, no.
- Those look almost like a nicer version of Smog Balls.
- Yeah, all right, well, three, two, one.
- Bro, they're coloring your teeth.
- No, really?
- Yes.
- Aw, bit my tongue.
- Put them in the bowl.
- All right, Collins, you ready?
- Yep.
- Close your eyes.
I am very confident that you're
not going to get this next one.
- Bro, I am a master of taste flavors.
I am a master of flavor taster, tasting.
- All right, here we go. Open wide.
And there.
- Whoa, this is really good.
- Can you guess?
- Got it! Pineapple.
- Pineapple what?
- Flavored stick.
- No, it's Mango Pocky.
- Man, I do not want to have to eat another sour candy.
- You missed!
- This one.
- Wow. Great claw, Collins.
No, no.
- Worms!
- Wow.
- The little bottles of soda.
This looks super duper sour.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Are they delicious?
Do you want some more?
No, are you sure?
- So, for this one, I'm gonna need to
prepare it a little bit, and to do that,
I gotta heat things up, you know what I mean?
Oopsie.
Devan, stay right where you are.
- What is going on?
- Nothing is happening.
All right, step one, done.
- This is one item, right?
- Oh, yes, for sure.
Gonna pop this over here.
- Oh, gotta sneeze.
- And then a finishing touch.
(Devan sneezes)
- Bless you.
- Oh, thanks.
- Now, it's time to roast it!
Wow, so cool.
- It sounds like you're making a fool of yourself.
Just sounds like it.
- What?
Stick out your tongue.
- Okay.
- Guess it. What do you think it is?
- Like a graham cracker or something.
- So we're gonna feed this to you
the way it's intended to be eated, you ready?
- Eated?
- All right, Devan, open up your mouth.
Three, two, one, bite down.
One more thing, open up your mouth.
What is the original item that this is?
- Goldfish?
- How did you guess that?
- Cause of the shape.
- Yes, you got it.
It's Goldfish S'mores.
Ah, man, I can't believe you guessed it.
Oh, yeah, these are...
- These are not good.
- These are rough.
Three, two, one.
- I remember these.
I think I tried these.
We're grabbing the bucket, bro.
Are you good, no?
(Collins mumbles)
All right, onto the next one.
What? All right, cool.
I hope you feel better.
All right, Collins, your eyes are closed.
- My eyes are closed.
- As they can see.
This is the next item.
All I can say is good luck, Collins.
I'm very glad I'm not doing this one.
I'm just gonna toss them in there.
All right, here we go, Collins.
Three, two, one.
- Wait, wait, wait!
First, let's do a 3 Second Like Challenge!
I want to see if you can like this video in three seconds.
Ready, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, done.
- All right.
- Three, two, one.
I missed some.
- It's a little bit spiky, a little bit.
- Any guesses so far?
Dude, you dropped one.
- Chocolate covered, I don't know, scorpions or something?
- What?
Chocolate covered insects, bro.
- No, god.
- We've got crickets.
We've got worms, bro.
- It stuck to my tongue at one point.
I was trying to get it off my tongue.
- You sound like a goose.
- That was horrible.
I can't believe I have to have another disgusting
thing after I just ate bugs.
These actually, if they weren't sour,
I'd probably really enjoy them
cause they're like Life Savers all much.
- All much?
- But I.
Let's see how these taste.
- All right, there we go.
- One, two.
- Oh, yeah, has it hit yet?
Oh, there it is!
- Number three is the charm.
- Bro, are you good?
Wait, did they get better?
- Yep.
- Nice.
- So, this is definitely the weirdest one
we've had so far.
I am so happy I don't have to eat this.
I'm serious.
- Weirder than insects?
- Oh my gosh.
- Three, two, one.
- He counts himself down.
- It just tastes really fizzy and very sweet.
- Well, take a bite of this and try to mix some flavors
together to give you hint of what this is.
What is it?
- Well, they taste exactly the same,
so I'm going to guess that it's either bread soda
or toast soda.
- No, you didn't get it.
- What?
- It's butter soda.
- Butter soda?
- With some bread.
Instead of butter, I was gonna put a little bit of the soda
on top of the bread and then try the bread now.
- I don't think so.
- Dude, try it.
- You try it.
- It's part of the rules.
I can't eat the item that's not my round.
- Oh, so good.
- Unfortunately, Devan, you gotta get another sour one.
- I know. I choose you!
- Let's see what we got.
- Oh, no.
Oh, these don't look good.
I'm gonna pour a little bit back in.
All, right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
- You went fish lips, bro.
Do not spit on me.
- Oh, man.
- I need to grab the bowl.
- Okay.
- Don't spit on me.
- I won't. I won't.
- Oh, gosh, it got on me.
Yo, all I gotta say is this sour gummy bear is going
to be crazy and we'll be making it coming up here shortly,
but right now, we are onto the next round.
- It tastes really good now.
And here is the next item.
- Yay!
- Wow, it actually smells exactly like what it is.
I'm gonna do it, so you can't smell it.
Three, two, one.
Just bite, just bite, you can't smell it.
- I think I know it!
- What? Yes?
We're all waiting.
- It tastes like ketchup.
- Yes, dude, you got it!
- Dude, right, you know what would be even better?
- What?
- Oh, yeah.
- What? Oh, dude, what?
Where did that come from?
Oh, man.
- Too much mustard.
- All right, I'm going for this bag here.
I think you clawed this one.
Oh! Oh, snap.
- Like sour rope.
- And you know, since you lost the challenge,
I think you're gonna have to be the one
who eats the giant sour gummy bear, bro.
- What? No!
Three, two, one.
- Oh, yo, it's like a guitar.
It's like the sourest spaghetti
you've ever had in your life.
We'll put these in here and now the moment you've
all been waiting for.
Time to mix all of the sourest candies in the world together
and make a crazy giant gummy bear,
so right now, let's head to the kitchen.
Welcome to our kitchen!
So guys, we're gonna be showing you how to combine
all of these sour candies into that gummy bear mold
to make a giant gummy bear.
You guys have seen us make Jell-O a whole bunch of times,
so we're gonna do this really quickly this time.
Super fast, check it out.
(bouncy music)
- Devan!
Now is the moment you've all been waiting for.
It's time to take all that candy and pop it
into the sour Jell-O.
Let's get the candy and I think
we're gonna go with some vines first.
Just kind of sprinkle them.
- Just a whole chunk of worms, bro.
- I was going for a handful like this.
Dude, watch out, are you ready?
Hold on, I gotta start mixing it in though.
Dude, you're missing like a ton of them.
- I forgot, bro, the clump!
There we go. That's the amount that we want!
Oh, I'm stepping on it!
- All right, Devan, get the gummy bear mold.
It's time to dump it in.
This is the moment of truth.
Can we get it in without messing this up?
Okay.
- You got this, bro.
- Oops, a bit of overflow.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
One noodle left.
Let's go, we gotta go to the fridge.
Teamwork makes the dream work, bro.
Let's go, let's go. - All right, all right.
- He's got foot power.
All right, great.
- What? What? What?
- Foot action!
It's the sourest gummy bear in the world.
[Collins] Here it is, the big reveal, you ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one!
Dude, it's like they expanded on the inside.
- What happened?
- I don't know!
- And they juiced.
- Don't do that! Don't do that!
- Devan, you lost the challenge,
so you get to eat it.
- I get to? What a privilege!
- I feel bad though, so how bout this?
I'll take a bite of it as well.
And comment down below, what are some other giant gummies
you want us to make the most sour version of?
So, Devan, I guess you should go for it.
- Here we go. Three, two, one.
- I'm gonna try, I'm gonna take a bite of it now.
Here we go. Three, two, one.
(both screaming)
Oh my god, he's gonna read us another video right now.
You have five seconds.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one.
- Bye!