- I made up this game, check it
it's called Follow the Queen.
Alright, so always watch the Queen
actually I've got um-- - Right here?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've got over here, I've got-- - Wait I wanna feel it too
- Okay. - Okay, okay.
- I'll use one more card, I'll use another four.
Alright, always watch the Queen,
don't get distracted by the other fours.
Alright watch the Queen right here
- You know Collins Key is craaazy.
- You guys can see it right, watch this right here.
That's-- - That's literally
- Yeah, yeah, yeah that's, did I give a four to you?
- No, no that is not - That (censored) is not real!
(laughing)
- Yo, yo, yo check this out.
Watch the Queen, you ready? - Okay... shit!
- You're watching the wrong card right there,
you see I've got the Queen over here.
(screaming) - What the--
- Yo watch - I don't like that
I don't like it! - Yo watch
You always gotta watch the Queen,
watch the Queen right here, alright watch the Queen.
Wait yo, where's the Queen? - Right here.
- No, no, no see the fours right here.
- What the hell?! (cheering)
- Ohhhh! (censored)
- Yo, yo, yo it gets better!
- Always watch the Queen don't get distracted okay
watch, watch the Queen, watch this right here.
Yeah point to the Queen, point to it.
No, that's a four, that's a four.
- Ahhh! (Laughing)
- Whaaat?
Lohanthony, right now point to the Queen,
point to the Queen.
No, no that's a four. - No (censored) way!
No way, this isn't real, this is not real.
- Turn it over, turn it over - Noooo!
- Yo watch, Queen goin' in my pocket, okay.
- It's like the easiest game ever
- Two fours - K
- Lohanthony, point to the Queen.
No that's a four - In your pocket!
- Okay you're right, you're right, you're right.
I'm trying to help you, I'm trying to help you.
Unless I want the Queen right here.
- What the (censored)! - No, no, no (censored)
Jay Z, point to the Queen, where is it?
- In your pocket. - Where do you think it is?
- No, no I think it's right there.
- No, no, no, no it's in my pocket
- What?! - It's in my pocket.
- Unless I want it to be right here, then it's right here
(gasping) - Oh my god!
- The wizard, Harry.
- He's a wizard, Harry!
- Point to it, where is the Queen?
- Stop doing that! - In your pocket!
- Yeah absolutely, you're right
- No, shut the (censored) up!
- Okay, okay - It's not here,
unless I want it to be here the Queen is here.
- No! - Holy, stop doing that!!
- Watch, watch, unless I want it to be right here.
- No! - Right?
- No!
- Sam, hold out your hands.
You see what's going on, I'm using extra cards alright?
I'm using extra fours. - Ahhh!
- Hold out your hand, Jay Z. - This is stressing me out.
- This is what I'm doing, watch, I'm cheating alright?
I'm cheating, I'm using extra cards, using extra fours.
Watch, hold out your hands. - I don't know how you do--
- Stop it!
- I'm cheating, I'm using extra cards,
I'm using extra fours alright?
(laughing) - Oh, what?!
- Right here, watch that Queen.
I'm cheating, I'm using extra fours,
I'm using extra fours like that.
(gasping) - Stop doing that,
I hate when Collins does that, Casper I'm sorry.
He's freakin' me out.
I don't need to mace him because security's coming.
Hold out your hands, hold out your hands.
Watch the Queen right here, you ready?
You're holding on to the wrong card
that's a four, that's a four. - Dude, no, no way!
There's no way! - Watch, watch, watch.
- Watch, watch, watch.
Queen's over here, let me help you watch.
Watch the card right here, which one are you holding?
- Four. - No, dude
Always watch the Queen, turn it over dude.
- Watch look at this (screaming)
- Watch, watch, watch right here look at
hold out your hand, hold out your hand.
Which one are you holding? - The four?
- No, always watch, yeah there you go.
- I don't know how...
- Crazy - Are you hyperventilating?
- Oh my god. - That makes no sense.
- Queen right here. - Yo!
- Watch it
- What the (censored)!
- I'm out, I'm out (censored).
- Bring it here, man. - That was dope!
- Watch right here, which one are you holding?
- Four! - No, turn it over.
- You're a liar!
- Four. - No, no
- Always watch the Queen, turn it over, turn it over.
- Noo! - No way!
- Guys watch, come here, come here.
Check this out, check this out.
- I'm gonna cry. - Hold out your hand, watch.
Which one are you holding? - The Queen.
Your absolutely right. - Wait what?!
(screaming)
- Watch, watch, watch one more time, one more time.
Right now, what was that one? - The four.
- No it's a Queen. - Noo!
- No, who did this? - (laughing) Who did this?
- There's no way dude I'm freaking out, like what?
- Right here, right here which one are you holding?
- A four. - Turn it over.
(screaming)
- What the (censored)?!
- CRAZY!
- Collins is a (censored) wizard, bro!
- If you wish that you could meet
everyone who was in this video,
let me know by hitting that Like button.
I want you guys to comment down below and let me know
who would you like me to freak out next?
And also bonus points if you guys can comment
the name of everyone who was in this video.
And don't forget of course to
subscribe to this channel.
This video is only part one,
part two and part three right here
so go click on those videos right now
if you wanna see crazy, awesome reactions
for more top YouTubers and Viners.
Once again, I'm Collins Keys
thank you for watching this week's video, peace.
- Rebecca has been tricked, I've been tricked
we've both been tricked.
- You went to Hogwarts! (censored)