- Three, two, one!
- [Both] Ooh!
- Oh my gosh! You challenged us to do
the Mystery Wheel of Pancake Art
and right now let's spin for the first pancake.
That was a solid spin. - Dude, that was a crazy spin!
What do you think it's gonna land on Devan?
- I'm gonna guess blue, I like blue.
- I'm gonna say purple.
- Purple?
- [Both] Ooh!
- I got it!
- That is not fair!
Alright, let's see what the first one is.
Bowser!
- Oh sweet!
- Let's kick it off right now with Bowser.
Gonna get some awesome spikes on this dude.
Bom! Bom! Bom!
Oh, its the up top drip drop drop drop.
To be good at this Devan, you really
gotta get in touch with your inner Bowser.
You know what I mean?
Just like this!
Bowser!
- Dude what? That's terrifying!
- Bowser!
And then bo, bo, bo, Bowser!
And then for the big one Devan,--
- No!
(dramatic music)
Dude, okay I think I have to let it go!
- Bowser!
- (laughing) Whoa!
- [Both] Alright, I gotta get back to this pancake.
Did we just? (laughs)
- I gotta finish up his shell.
So just gonna fill this folly in with green right now.
(upbeat music)
And now, time to give him so jacked arms!
- Alright.
Here we go.
Give 'em one arm like this, look at that arm bro.
(laughs)
Oh no, what have I done?
- Oh no, mine's extra dripping!
It's double dripping!
Look at this!
- That's horrible!
- What is going on?
(upbeat music)
- It's kind of squished, 'cause
I'm running out of room at the top here.
It looks a giant shoe or a foot! (takes deep breath)
- Lot's of deep breaths there.
- This is not good.
We'll give 'em little teeth.
(upbeat music)
- [Devan] And outline is done!
- Dude, that took you forever!
And I am not having it, and neither is my pet dini-saur!
- The what?
- My pet dini-saur!
- Can I pet him?
- No! Do not pet the dini-saur Devan!
- Why?
- You know what happens when you pet a dini-saur, right?
- No, I don't!
- Alright, Devan you can pet the dini-saur!
- Okay.
- [Both] Whoa!
(loud roaring)
- Dude!
- Whoa!
- Wow!
- Okay!
- I warned you!
(upbeat music)
- Time to flip over my pancake right now!
- [Devan] Nice!
- Here we go, I got a giant shovel scooper.
This one's just gonna be a slight flick of the wrist.
Three, two, one, yeet!
- [Both] Aw!
- Oh, no, no no!
Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oh no!
- You lost the head. Ta-da!
- There we go, ta-da!
A little more respect for Bowser man!
- You just plopped that thang right down.
You didn't even treat it gently.
- Do you see what I'm dealing with here?
- You literally had no care in the way you handled it.
- I'm sorry, what?
Can we just rewind back to your flip?
See dude, look at that!
And now it's time to flip mine!
You ready for this?
- [Collins] Dude, this reveal is gonna be crazy!
- Alright, it is successfully on a spatula, three, two, --
- Oh wait!
Click the top link in the description
or go to shopcollinskey.com right now
to get your merch before it's all sold out!
- [Devan] Oh, what?
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
- [Devan] That actually turned out pretty good.
- Dude, what?
Well, there's Bowser from Super Smash Bros.
and this is a battle and you get to comment down below
and let us know who won this round.
Time to spend for the next pancake.
Here we go, three --
What was that? - What?
- What do you mean?
It was my turn.
- I wanted to spin it.
Alright, well it's on blue.
Ooh, we got Wreck-It Ralph.
The thing about Wreck-It Ralph
is it kind of looks like 8-bits,
so luckily for me, this is right up my alley.
- Wait, when did you do 8-bit Collins?
- Because it's like more chunky and funky
which is the way that I like to make my pancakes.
Gotta make the inside of his mouth first.
See, Devan always starts with these little small lines,
so I'm gonna try that this time
because I need to get better at this,
so he goes like (sound effects).
Oh no, the bottom stopped getting square and nice and cubey.
- [Devan] Is that just his mouth?
- (laughs) Yeah.
You know what, see, it's all about squares.
So I'm gonna do a little square tongue.
There we go.
I think I'm crushing the game right now.
See, oh, look at it.
It's just, no.
I'm gonna make eyeballs.
Wait, you've done only a square?
- It's the most crucial square though, Collins.
It's the center.
- We got his eyeballs.
So here we go, we're gonna get some side brows.
Oh, there we go!
Dude, the eyebrows are side brows.
- [Devan] Where do you put those side brows?
- [Collins] Off to the side.
- Next up, I'm going for the eyes.
- Fill these little babies in.
- Alright, Wreck-It Ralph's gonna have some green eyebrows.
(upbeat music)
Just gotta put this last little touch right here --
- [Both] Wait no!
It's Hoot-Dini!
- Who is that?
- It's basically the owl that will randomly go off
each round, which means we have to spin for a wild card.
- Alright.
- Alright, bro I guess we gotta spin the mystery wheel
to find out what our wild card is.
Bro, I was goin' so well!
- [Both] Three, two, one.
And this might mess-up your whole game right now.
I got blue.
- I got red.
What? Hot sauce?
- That's not bad, do you know what mine is?
- For the rest of my pancake-making,
I'm not allowed to use my hands.
How do you make a pancake without using your hands?
- This is gonna be so weird.
I think I have to take out the cap of this,
and combine the two 'cause there's no way
just sriracha sauce is gonna work.
- (yells)
- Alright, here it goes.
- I can use my shoulder though.
Aw man!
It's so hard without my hands.
- Okay, whoa!
- Oh my gosh!
- Whoa!
(upbeat music)
- [Devan] Oh, it's so gross!
- [Collins] Oh, it looks pretty funky.
Yo give me a spatula, dude!
- What? Why?
- The spatula, 'cause I need it.
- Here you go.
- Other way.
- This way.
- Dude, what are you doing?
It fell over.
- Oh no, it's not really comin' out now.
(grunts in frustration)
You weren't using your --
Alright, my sriracha's added.
That was super easy!
- There's a spatula right there.
- Yeah, see the thing is to get
that spatula, I need another spatula.
- Here you go!
Nice, alright there you go.
- I'm losin' it!
- It's now time to --
Whoa! - Ow!
Do you have another spatula?
- No. (laughs)
- You know what, I'm over!
- You're over?
Over what?
- I'm goin' in for it bro!
- Oh, whoa, wow!
That's really skilled man!
- Dude, I think you can use your hands now.
I just feel so bad for you --
- See, here's the issue Devan.
When you spin for no hands, it literally means no hands!
- What?
- I have no hands!
He took my hands away!
- You had hands a second ago, what happened?
- Oh, I have an idea.
I thought of a loophole.
BOOM! Claws, bro!
Alright, here we go so now I'm
just gonna fill in his face, oh!
Why is it so watery?
This is great man, the no hands
thing is all working out for me.
Let's see, we're just gonna give him a whole mess of hair.
And, done!
So now, just gonna have to, uh-oh!
That's not cooked!
- You're kind of encroaching into my space.
Your head's like resting on my arm!
- Bro, that smells like sriracha sauce on your side.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
He just can't get the height, man!
- There we go!
- Whoa! Don't break it! Don't break it!
Look it, it's done!
- Where's the other spatula?
- You want the ones that were in or out of my mouth?
- (laughs) Not in your mouth.
The sriracha turned it so that the
pancake batter split and doesn't actually cook.
- Dude, and you're gonna have to actually eat that!
At the end of the video, we'll be eating these pancakes bro!
- Oh no! It's kinda breaking.
Three, two, one --
- We're in the first five seconds subscribe challenge!
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel and
turn on the channel post notifications in just five seconds.
Here we go!
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done!
If you can do that, comment down below
Keyper Squad right now!
- [Both] Oh!
It's so bad!
At least my guy didn't lose his forehead.
Right now, you get to comment down below
and let us know who won this round.
Time to spin for our next pancake.
Three, two, one.
What do you think it's gonna land on?
- Green.
- I'm gonna say yellow.
- [Both] Oh!
- Alright, well let's see what it is.
Oh snap! Okay!
- What?
- It's the most famous detective in the entire world.
- Sherlock Holmes?
- No! Pikachu!
- Oh, what?
- Right now, let's make him.
Just gonna start off over here.
Ear number two's gonna be a lot smaller.
I'm playing with perspective a little bit, you know?
Ha-ha, art words.
Pikachu's got his little head. (evil laughter)
What is that?
I've gotta build some static electricity, Pika-chu!
Oh snap!
Oh my gosh!
Wait, let me see if I can do it.
Let me see if I can just, ow!
Bro, this is crazy!
- [Both] (yelling in fear)
- Okay.
- Alright, enough of that.
Let's keep making the tail.
Of course, detective Pikachu's got his hat.
What I'm gonna have to do, I'm gonna have
to build a little stick on his head
Because this little stick, is gonna support his hat.
- It's like one of the propeller hats upside-down though.
- We're getting little propellers.
Nailed it!
Here we go, so now we're gonna give
him a little magnifying glass.
There we go.
A little lightening bolt coming out of his tail.
See now I know why you use these little precision ones bro
'cause it's actually a lot easier.
- [Devan] And I made his ears super wide.
- Now for the most important and skillful part.
Gotta start filling in his tail.
Oh snap!
It's Hoot-Dini!
- Seriously?
Mine was going so good!
- Alright well I guess we gotta spin
the mystery wheels and let's hopefully get something good.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Man I can't believe it.
- I got red.
I don't have a good feeling about this.
- What? I got a switch up, bro!
- Oh yes!
We have to switch pancakes!
- No! Seriously?
- Oh yeah!
- It was going so good!
- No!
- What? Oh you got a blindfold?
- I have to be blind-folded!
- (hysterical laughter) Okay so now what?
- Pika-ah-ah-chu!
- Wait, dude, what?
I teleported like two inches.
- Yeah, but we did it with lightening.
- Yeah, but we could've just switched trays.
- Yeah but we couldn't do that with lightening.
- Man!
- I got my blindfold on.
- I'm gonna have to do a lot of reconstruction of yours.
- I can't see anything.
I have a system figured out for this.
Put it down.
We'll go around until I find, oh, found something here,
and then I'm just gonna dispense.
One ear moved.
I think this is his eye right here.
You know what?
I'm gonna just kinda guess.
So there we go.
We're gonna give him a little eye, perfect.
There we go, give him a little nose.
Devan, is this red?
- [Devan] No! This is red.
- Okay this is red, here we go.
I'm gonna go 'til I hit the side of his head.
Oh, okay something's here.
Gonna give him a little cheek over here,
and a little red cheek over here.
Now this is the most important part,
'cause this is all just kind of a,
I'm guessing right now but I gotta figure out
which one is yellow so I can fill in his face.
I think this is yellow!
- It's not yellow!
This is yellow!
- No!
- Use your twin telepathy right now Devan.
Send me the yellow!
- Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oh! Ow!
- I got it!
It is right, --
- [Both] There!
- [Devan] No, no there!
- Twin telepathy is so great!
Here we go, maybe a little bit on this side,
and maybe a little bit more up here.
- Wow!
- Are you breaking, what are you doing to my pancake?
Okay, I take a nap now.
(upbeat music)
Alright, mine smells like it's perfectly
cooked and ready to be flipped.
- Collins, it's not even on.
- Could you turn it on?
- Yeah, I could totally turn it on.
- Okay, Devan I need a spatula.
- Alright, here you go!
- Okay, perfect and, (gasps) no way!
You got me an extendable spatula?
I'm tryna find it.
- Careful of the top!
- I got it!
- Yeah, you kind of got it.
- Time for the flip.
Three, two, one.
(laughter)
- It actually flipped!
- Yes!
- You missed the pan.
- Oh, it worked!
Oh my gosh!
Pretty interesting!
Let's flip it around like that.
You know what bro?
I'm very disappointed.
- Why?
- It appears you have discarded the majority of my work.
You ready for this?
Three, two, one.
- Pikachu!
Oh my gosh! - Dude, it actually worked!
- Well done!
Alright, well those are the Pikachus!
You get to comment down below who won this round!
- Time to spend for the next pancake!
- Alright I'm gonna put some Pam.
- You're Pamming it already?
- Here we go, yellow!
Alright, I'll take it. - Let's see what it is.
- Bumble bee.
- I'm great at doing bees!
- Oh, no, like the Transformer.
- Oh! I thought for once I had this.
- I can't believe we got yellow.
- Alright, well you know what?
Time to make a Transformer.
They are all about the shapes.
The issue is I make my pancakes huge.
There we go, we gotta get his whole eye, circular pupil.
Here we go, this is working perfectly!
Oh, look at that!
Squiggly eye brows!
Yeah, boi!
And then we'll give him a little square,
a red square tongue.
(high-pitch sound)
That's Bumbleebee right now.
(upbeat music)
Man these lines are gonna be coming
all disconnected and everything, bro this is not good
- Oh no! It's Hoot-Dini! - Wait, seriously?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Alright, well let's see, oh snap, I got purple.
No way!
I got no thumbs bro!
- Dude, I got a chopstick flip.
- Oh my gosh!
- So that could be really bad.
- I guess now we're just gonna tape 'em up?
Well, hand number one is done!
The one hand tape tear is not easy
when you don't have a thumb!
(squeals)
I think it's time to start filling it in.
We're gonna grab some yellow, double peace sign!
Who needs thumbs when you have 8 fingers?
Grab it! Grab it!
- I got it!
- Not your chopsticks!
- I'm sorry that's all I have in my hand.
- [Both] (screaming)
- Just pick it up, dude, get it up!
- I don't have thumbs!
Ah! It's ruining everything! - Support it from the bottom!
- No! It's totally ruined it!
Devan, this is horrible bro.
- [Devan] Move over an eye.
- We're gonna get some over here.
- Are you almost done?
(screaming)
- It's overlapping the lines a bit, Collins.
- Well I'm not perfect.
(upbeat music)
Alright, I got my spatulas and now
I gotta flip this one over a little bit.
- At least you can use spatulas, bro.
Oh be careful, dude, be careful!
- [Both] Three, two, one. Oh!
- Alright, well there you go!
I flipped it!
- Cool, it's looking great.
Now it's time for my flip, you ready for this?
- I believe in you Devan.
- [Both] Three, two, one. --
- We're at our three second Like challenge.
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds.
Are you ready?
Here we go!
- [Both] Three, two, one, done! Oh!
- [Devan] What?
- [Collins] Dude, that thing looks insane!
- Dude, it turned out --
- [Collins] You get to comment down below
who made a better Bumblebee!
Time to spin the wheel for the next pancake.
Three, two, one.
- What did you do?
- Wait, it's gonna fly off Alright, there we go.
- Well, let's just go with it, alright?
- Alright, I got purple.
- Alright.
- Aye, we got Fortnite!
- Oh, sweet!
Wait, what should we make?
- What if we did the llama?
- Oh, sweet, yeah I'm down.
- Alright, llama from Fortnite, here we go.
I'm gonna start off with the head of the llama first.
The most important part.
- We're gonna go here, there's an ear.
- Whoa what is that?
- That's his head.
And then the body of his llama-ness.
- I love his little legs they're like,
- My llama is gonna have some saber tooth fangs.
That way no one can loot this llama!
- Wow Collins, I don't think I've
ever seen you this quiet before.
- This is what concentration looks like, Devan.
You should try to learn something.
- [Devan] It's very difficult for me though.
- [Collins] Are you actually making
all the little individual confetti thingys?
- I mean most of 'em.
- We're gonna start filling mine in,
but I have a different strategy than Devan.
Instead of just doing 'em all the same color,
I'm gonna randomly do them in all different colors
to make mine a rainbow loot llama.
Whoa, that's so much detail!
- I didn't have enough room to add
the legs, so this will have to do.
Now it's time to start roasting my pancake.
Wait, why is it stuck?
- Victor the Laser Pony fixes all!
Alright, here we go!
- Whoa! What mode is he on?
- Let me see.
He's just on disintegrate mode.
- (laughs) That sounds too intense for this.
- Don't worry, boom!
Obliterate mode!
- (laughs) No!
- You don't want that?
- No, no we don't!
- Completely world destruction mode!
- No! How is he that powerful?
- Dude, this is Victor the Laser Pony!
- Can't you tone him down a little bit?
(grunts)
- That one and then that one.
Alright, now he's on lucid mode.
Ready? Three, two, one.
Oh my gosh, Victor the Laser Pony, you're fighting back.
Bro, he's tryna turn it up!
Turn it down, down, down!
Oh snap!
Man, Victor the Laser Pony, you did a great job!
And you loosened some light bulbs as well
but thank you for your service, Devan -
- Thank you.
- Touch Victor the Laser Pony.
No! It was a test!
You can not disrespect Victor the
Laser Pony by touching his snout!
- Okay.
Whoa! What? - I think it worked bro!
I feel like if this goes wrong,
it should go very wrong 'cause it's so much detail.
(upbeat music)
- Alright, it is time for the flip of my pancake.
Three, two, one.
Oh! He lost his head.
This is probably my best pancake I've ever made.
- Alright, it's time to flip mine, here we go!
- If you break it, you will automatically lose
'cause you're probably gonna lose anyway
'cause you don't have four legs!
Dude, this is so much pressure!
- Three, two, one --
- Wait, if you wanna win a 15 minute video call,
with Devan and I, text the word PANCAKE to 81800 right now!
So pause the video, text the word PANCAKE to 81800,
you will automatically be entered in to win
and right now let's see how this thing looks!
- [Both] Oh!
- I did it, I did it!
- That looks so good though!
- [Collins] You get to comment
down below who made a better Fortnite llama.
- Time to spin for our next pancake.
- Aye, I got it!
- What do you think it's gonna be Collins?
- I think it's going to be, I don't know purple?
Oh! - Oh, so close!
Oh, Aquaman!
- We're gonna start off with his trident
because I'm feeling pretty bold right now.
- You may have noticed that I flipped
my hot plate vertically and that is because Aquaman is tall.
What are you doing?
- I'm making his trident and then
we're gonna have to give him a little arm.
- Alright, here we go.
- Man! I always run out of room really quickly.
So this'll be his little head --
- Oh my goodness.
You have no idea how hard it is
to do a straight line with this thing.
- He's got some awesome, beautiful yellow hair.
We'll give a little yellow belt.
He's like meh.
(upbeat music)
- [Devan] Oh no!
I'm losing my eyes!
- That's not good bro!
- Aw man, his face is gonna be all whack now.
- I'm gonna start filling in my shark.
This actually kinda reminds me of Sharkeisha a little bit,
Sharkeisha, where are you?
Sharkeisha, where is Sharkeisha at?
I know how to get her here.
Sharkerisha, I have your favorite rice cakes!
(screaming)
- Sharkeisha no, I need to work on my pancakes!
- Well let me at least give Sharkeisha some rice cakes!
It's time to flip my Sharkeisha.
Oh no, Sharkeisha lost a tooth!
- [Both] Three, two, one. Oh!
- I lost a fin!
Now it's time to flip Aquaman, uh-oh.
His arms are very fragile.
Give me a spatula please.
- Okay, okay.
- Gotta get his trident over here.
- [Devan] Aw, lost some of this hair.
- Three, two, one.
- [Both] Ah!
- I totally broke my Aquaman!
- [Devan] In pieces man!
- Sometimes when Aquaman falls down,
you just gotta figure out what goes where.
Aquaman!
- Alright!
(creepy laughing)
- Alright, time to flip mine.
Are you ready for this?
- Bro, this looks so crazy!
- Here we go!
Three, two, one!
- It flipped! Oh my gosh!
- You get to comment down below who won this round.
We'll be eating these at the end of the video.
Time to spend the wheel!
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- What is it gonna land on?
- Green, that's my safe bet.
- I'm gonna go red.
- [Both] Oh!
Yes! - What? No way!
- Alright, let's see what we got.
Yo, we have to make the Avengers!
- All of the Avengers?
- Okay fine, how about we pick one Avenger each
and then make that as a pancake?
- Alright, that sounds good.
- Starting off with the outlines.
You have to guess what superhero I'm making.
It always ends up looking so much cooler in my head.
(screams)
So much delicate work goes into this.
Ooh, this is tough!
It looks more like a waffle than a pancake.
- Yeah, you're making a waffle cake.
- Check this out, you ready?
Three, two, one.
- Oh we gotta clean that off.
Check this out.
I got it!
- Whoa!
- Yes, I got my rice cakes!
- Are you done?
- You know what?
I gotta save it for later.
I'm gonna stick it to the ceiling, here we go.
Got it!
So now let's keep making this thing.
- Wow.
- And now, it's time to create
some building in the background.
And he just shot a web at it.
Why (laughs) does it look even more like a waffle?
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna make spider webs.
He's built himself a nice web in the background.
Web number two, man it looks like
he's in the middle of a heatwave.
(upbeat music)
I mean this building really did not turn out -
Oh my gosh! - No, seriously?
- It's Hoot-Dini again!
So I guess we gotta re-spin the wheel bro.
This thing just randomly goes off at the worst times.
Alright, here we go, your ready?
Wild card.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- I hope I get a good one.
I hope I don't get a bad wild card.
- Blue.
- I got yellow.
- Oh, it was so close to blue!
- Oh no!
- It's in the middle, I don't know what to do.
- Re-spin it.
- Alright, what did you get?
- I have to use my left hand!
- You what?
- And I am very much not left-handed
and there's a lot of details to be done.
- Oh, I hope it's a good one!
What? Kaleidoscope glasses?
What are those?
Whoa! It's like seeing quadruple, bro.
Like, my pancake's here, here, and here at the same time.
I'm not looking forward to this!
- You're not looking forward actually at all.
- I'm not?
Oh. I'm looking forward to this!
- You're not looking forward at all.
- I'm not?
I need some blue!
I got it!
Wait, is this blue?
Is this blue?
- No, that's purple.
- It's purple?
- Yeah!
- I got it!
It is time to add the blue of the eyes, here we go.
Oh, I actually nailed it!
Okay!
- Alright, let's do this left-handed.
This makes it harder.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
- Oh, I got it!
I got it!
Yep, right there!
I think I got it.
- Okay, even with the kaleidoscope things,
how are you still so good at this?
- Okay, hopefully this don't mess it up.
(upbeat music)
Red! Ha-ha!
This is red!
- That is red, yes.
Great job!
I think it's done.
Do I have to flip it like this?
- Yes! With the glasses on!
- Really?
- It's time for the flip and I can only use my left hand.
Oh, I got his head!
- You need help?
- Yeah!
- See, I can help you.
Just give me a spatula.
Got it right?
- No, Devan if you don't feel it, you don't have it.
- There! - There you go!
Teamwork makes the dream work.
Left-hands, you ready?
Go, go, go!
Yes!
Look, he's caught in his own webs!
- Here we go!
Three, two, one!
- Oh that looks so good!
- Does it look good?
I can't really see it.
- Comment down below who won this round.
We'll be eating these at the end of the video.
- Time to spin for our next pancake.
What do you think it's gonna be?
- I'm gonna say green.
- I'm gonna go for blue.
- [Both] Oh, we were both wrong!
- Alright, well let's see what we got.
Oh, this one's poppin!
- Mary Poppins!
- How'd you know that?
- 'Cause I looked at it.
- Let's get some umbrellas and float away,
- Alright, umbrella done!
That was easy.
- You got lines going through it,
because umbrellas have lines.
This is like what happens when you have no vision for it.
'Cause this was suppose to be here arm.
You know what?
She'll have a giant triangle arm.
- [Devan] Aw man, she has a teeny little arm.
(laughs)
- How am I so bad at this?
Looks more like the Pillsbury Dough Boy
than it does Mary Poppins.
I don't think I'm doing the dress the right color right now.
Oh no, it's Hoot-Dini!
Oh snap, if I was in a bad place,
it's about to become even worse right now.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh, I got red, that can't be good!
- What? Batter hands?
- I got tentacle fingers.
- Oh, so you have to like dip your hands in batter!
- No!
- That's gonna drip all over,
That's gonna ruin it!
This is gonna be impossible, bro!
Oh boy!
- Oh man!
- Alright, time to pick up some pancake batter.
So let's see, just gonna --
- Oh no, you know what?
I'm just going for it.
Add her dress, the longer I stay here, the worse it gets.
- Let's see if I can just start getting the tentacles --
- Gotta add some more cityscape --
- How is it that 10 tentacles can't
even pick up one of these things?
Yes! No!
(upbeat music)
- [Devan] Now for the dark blue!
Alright, and done!
- These tentacle fingers are the
worst things that's ever happened!
She is gonna have a green body.
See, it all goes so great until
Hoot-Dini interferes with our game.
Well here we go!
I have 10 tentacle fingers
- [ Devan] And where exactly is Mary Poppins?
- [Collins] Part of her eye is right there.
She's wearing a green dress, like the wicked witch.
- Now it's time for me to flip mine.
Man, I don't like this at all.
No! Stop! - I'm trying to calm you.
- [Both] Oh! (screaming)
- Loud noises!
You're dripping so much batter everywhere, bro,
- Three, two, one. Oh!
- [Collins] What? It looks so good!
- I need that my hands far away so I don't drip on it.
- [Collins] You get to comment
down below who won this round!
Time to eat the pancakes, but there's
a mystery wheel twist to this!
Basically, we only get to eat one pancake
and they mystery wheel gets to decide which one that is.
So, we'll spin it, pick it off,
and whichever one it says, that's the one we get to eat.
I'm super excited!
- Dude, I'm super excited too!
I mean, all of mine are amazing!
Except for Wreck-It Ralph!
I hope I don't get Wreck-It Ralph!
- Dude, you put hot sauce in it!
Here we go, the final spin and
possibly the most important one.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- Please not Wreck-It Ralph!
- Alright, I got red, what'd you get?
- I got blue, it's a good sign!
- Nice, I got the Fortnight llama, yes!
- What do you think the chances are,
that this is not Wreck-It Ralph?
- I mean here's the thing bro,
You got Ironman, you got Aquaman, you got Bowser.
Let's give him a little drum roll!
- It's more like a little flipper roll, what is that?
- Enough goofin' around, Devan.
Let's see what you got.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- No! I got Wreck-It Ralph!
- Oh my gosh!
- How?
- Bro!
- Out of all the pancakes!
- Well, I'm gonna take a little bite of
my Fortnite llama right now with you prepare yourself
to take a bit of spicy Wreck-It Ralph.
It's kinda like a chip, almost right now.
It's so crisp.
- Oh, it smells so bad!
Dude, what are you doing?
- I'm eating my pancake, and it's great.
Dude, he looks just like you!
You gotta bite it quickly, it's falling apart.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Does it taste good? No?
- Right now to get your merch before it's all sold out.
And comment down below who is your favorite character
you would love to see us make a pancake out of.
Right now, click here.
You have five seconds, ready, here we go!
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one!
- Alright, we love you guys so much!
- [Both] Bye!