- [Both] Three, two, one!
(squirting) (beep)
- You guys challenged us to do the pancake art challenge.
We're kicking off with minions.
That's not a minion.
It's like a very long yellow worm.
First things first, we're just going to forget I did this.
Oh whoa these are kinda like bouncy, bro.
I just shook this thing up.
(screams)
- Dude, what did you do.
(laughs)
- [Devan] Already?
- It blasted my thumb, bro.
Oh no, this is terrible.
We haven't even started yet.
Devan's already creating art over here.
- [Devan] I know, I got my little overalls, I'm ready.
- I'm not good, this is not going to be good.
You guys know Devan is like a professional artist.
I'm not.
My minion, he got very wide in the hips all of a sudden.
(laughing)
My minion, he's like wearing a dress bro.
Like a skirt or he's hula hooping bro.
Dude, my minion is swole.
(crashing) (screaming)
(dramatic music)
I thought you got like batter all over me.
(laughing)
- At least it's not as bad
as the first time you did this to me.
(tape player squealing)
- [Collins] Devan, what just happened bro?
- So I was told to shake up this pancake batter.
Oh nothing will happen.
It'll be fine, Devan.
- Another one, boom.
Winning.
Now the last thing I want to do,
my minion's awesome and trendy
so he's going to have purple hair.
(screams)
Got me again.
- [Devan] You'd think you would learn.
Oh no, what are you doing?
- [Collins] Making little hairs bro.
I want to get him so he's got some little ear hairs.
- What?
- [Collins] Boom, full heat, roast 'em.
This dude's arms look like a second pair of legs.
- No they look like nice stiletto high heels or something.
(laughs)
- [Collins] Bro my minion looks more like a scary monster
than a character from Despicable Me.
- It really does.
- [Collins] Can we just appreciate the attention to detail
that Devan's doing?
Time to flip my minion, here we go.
- Dude it's smoking.
- No it's sizzling bro.
We're going to eat all of the pancakes at the end
of this video, and also after each round you guys
can judge us and let us know who you think won each round.
Alright let me see if I can get my stiletto high heels.
Oh there we goo, boom.
The flip, three two one.
(laughing)
Burnt toast so bad.
His face is like, "I got roasted."
Three, two, one.
Oh that one looks so good.
- [Devan] He has no eyes, but--
- [Collins] Bro, mine looks like he hits the gym
way too much and skips leg day every day.
The big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one, ta da!
So you guys get to comment after each round
and let us know who you think won,
but right now we're on to the next one.
Y'all suggest--
(clears throat) Y'all.
- We'll just start with the y'all.
(beep)
- Y'all suggested that we make...
Did yours not fire?
- I didn't know we were doing it for real.
- Yes. (beep)
Y'all suggested the laughing crying--
- Whoa.
(gasping)
What?
- I got it all over my shirt.
Three, two, one, go.
(bell dinging)
I need the black stuff.
Get it to me.
- [Devan] Okay have fun.
- This is going to be the laughing crying emoji
and it's going to be legendary.
(upbeat music)
Yo this guy's got brows on fleek man.
His eyebrows are the biggest part of his entire face
currently at the moment.
Yeah, yeah his eyebrows are massive.
Ah, his eyes are too small.
Oh well.
(upbeat music)
Bam, nailed it.
Oh my god dude I'm crushing this bro.
- [Devan] Oh my gosh, those teeth though.
- Call me an artist.
I really made this way too big.
Way too big.
(upbeat music)
Ah it splattered all over me, not again.
Oh no, something moved.
That was not good.
The pressure's on.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- [Devan] That's kinda weird but.
- It turned out pretty good.
I'm using red.
And even though it's not exactly what we though it would be
that's what life is all about.
(laughs)
- [Devan] I want to get in on this action.
This looks like fun.
- [Collins] Let's go bro.
(upbeat music)
- [Devan] Going for the long distance shot.
- [Collins] Boom.
Oh man.
- Look at that.
Oh no!
- Are you kidding me?
You got it on my face.
Here we go, three, two, wait wait wait.
First I've got a challenge.
I want to see can you subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
Here we go, you ready?
- [Both] Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you can do that comment down below Keyper Squad
right now and let's flip this pancake.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(screaming)
- No, no, no!
You ruined it, my beautiful pancake.
It's ruined no.
- [Devan] Wait you flip it, I'll flip it backwards.
- No.
- Hold on your elbow's in my face.
- Sorry.
It's a catastrophe.
Flip it.
(laughing)
It looks so scary.
It's like evil bro.
- It's like the laughing, crying, angry face emoji.
- I'm literally crying, like my face is this
because when I laugh my face turns red.
Well we are laughing, we are crying about this emoji.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(fanfare music)
- Yeah, this uh--
- I don't know.
(screaming)
- It touched my finger.
It's so hot.
I'm going to flip it back on.
Next up, a rainbow.
(bell dinging)
The dude's literally spreading his oil.
I am Picasso.
I must make my pancake batter look awesome.
(upbeat music)
My (screams) oh it got me again.
My hands are just a mess currently.
- Your hands are more like a rainbow than your rainbow.
- Yeah.
(upbeat music)
Alright.
(suspenseful music)
When is enough?
(upbeat music)
This is one of those moments where I'm taking a risk.
It's a creative risk.
You'll have to wait and find out what it's truly become.
(screams)
- You left it all over the base of the thing so it dripped.
- It's not my fault.
- Yes it is.
- It is my fault. It's all your fault.
- [Collins] Yeah this did not go according to plan.
I tried to turn it into a rainbow mushroom.
- A what?
- A mushroom that's a rainbow.
- What is that?
- I thought it was going to be very cool conceptually.
It didn't work.
Yes, we disconnected successfully.
And here comes the flip.
(gasping) (laughing)
- I need the green.
- Oh no, I broke you my rainbow.
On a casual flip, no!
My rainbow, help!
I have an idea.
I know how I'm going to win this round.
It's a double rainbow!
It's a double rainbow all the way.
Victory is mine, I've clearly seized the win on this one.
In the meantime I'm going to work on my pancake flippery.
(splatting) (laughing)
- No, yeet.
(glass smashing)
I've fallen.
Somewhere over the rainbow, skies are blue Devan.
You hear that?
- What?
- I don't know.
- You mean the song?
- I cracked my knee.
- Alright.
- I don't know if you heard that but it was powerful.
- Time to flip.
- Yes!
- [Devan] Three, two, one.
Oh my gosh!
It looks great but there's no yellow, so yeah.
It's my no yellow rainbow versus his--
- [Collins] Double rainbow.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Ta da. - Yeah.
- It's tough on this one.
I don't think either of us really won.
- What?
(laughing)
Clearly definitive leader here.
Let's go to the next one.
- You're right, you're right.
Next up.
♫ Spiderman, Spiderman
♫ Does whatever a pancake Spiderman
- What? - Let's go.
- [Devan] Alright.
(upbeat music)
- The sizzling as it knows my Spiderman
is going to be awesome.
(upbeat music)
Now for the moment of truth.
Flipping Mr. Spidey.
- Ooh I can't wait.
- I'm going to go for like a slide and
(imitates thudding) technique.
Three, two, two, here we go, one.
(imitates thudding)
(cheering)
It looks like Spiderman got mixed with like a basketball.
- It does.
- [Collins] He has like a little freckle.
(upbeat music)
- Alright here we go.
- And this was suggested by the Instagram Keyper of the Week
so shout out to you and if you want to be featured
as the Instagram Keyper of the Week,
check the description down below to find out how.
And let's see how this turned out.
- [Devan] Three, two, one, whoa!
That actually kinda turned out okay.
- [Collins] That looks so good!
- [Devan] That turned out better than I expected.
Basketball versus face mask.
- It's fine, you can vote for his.
I won't be offended.
This is by far the most requested one
and it is a fidget spinner.
So right now Devan, back at it again
making another fidget spinner, this time out of pancake.
So let's do it.
- Will it spin?
- Uh probably not.
(upbeat music)
I've really got to get some wins coming here
in this home stretch because--
- Ooh.
- Things have not been good so far coming up to this round
but hopefully this last one will be redemption.
See Devan has just begun his while mine is being flipped.
If that gives you any metaphor
for how Devan and I are different, that's how it goes.
Mine looks like a weird glob with like hands
with eyes on it.
It looks like everything except for a fidget spinner.
It looks like a flying saucer with eyeballs all over it.
Three, two, one go!
(cheering)
Yeah it works.
Alright now time to see if they actually spin.
Here we go three, two, one.
- Ooh, ooh it's hot.
It's not.
(cheering)
Should we eat it now?
- Now it's like a weird ring bro.
(cheering)
For the final freestyle round we have 30 seconds
to create our masterpiece.
Begin. - Oh no wait!
Really?
- [Collins] Oh man I'm going way too big.
- [Devan] Why are you bumping me?
Why are you bumping my arm?
- [Collins] I'm going way too big.
I had a brilliant idea.
- [Devan] That actually kinda worked right there.
Okay alright.
- [Collins] Oh that was such a good idea.
- [Devan] I need purple.
- [Collins] Nope, oh my gosh this is not enough time at all.
My masterpiece is not a masterpiece.
- [Devan] Take the blue.
- [Collins] I need the blue.
(screaming)
Bro, this is not going to work.
- [Devan] No, it's stuck, it's stuck.
- [Collins] It's like running out of time.
- I'm done.
- Five, four, three--
- I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
- Two, one.
- Is this time for you or for me?
- Done!
(laughing)
Time to reveal the masterpieces
and if you want to be featured in the next video
comment down below, what's your favorite food
we should turn into a pancake?
But right now, let's flip them
and then reveal what they are.
Three, two, one, you first go.
- [Devan] Oh wait, what?
It's the Instagram logo.
- [Collins] Oh that's cool.
Alright mine in three, two, one.
It's a beautiful beach.
See the like little clouds and the sand?
(laughing)
And the ocean?
Which is kind of like the sky as well.
- You did not go for something simple.
- Nope.
- That's a complex masterpiece.
- Now that we've done them all, you get to choose
who won each round.
Comment your full answers down below.
Alright bro time for you to taste it.
Let's see how it is.
- Alright, ready.
- If you guys want to see our last pancake art challenge
click right over here.
Things got absolutely crazy.
- And if you want to see our latest gummy food
versus real food challenge click right over here.
- Giant gummy worms and giant gummy snakes,
a whole bunch of crazy stuff.
- Bro is yours as good as mine is?
Mine's really good.
- Bye!
- See ya later!
Bye.