- Hey guys, it's Collins,
right now I'm in the middle of nowhere
and we're gonna try to catch some Pokémon together.
I've heard there's some super rare ones around here,
so let's give this a shot.
(video game music)
We're gonna need a bigger ball.
(record scratching)
- Oh, no!
Oh! (bleep)
- What's up? It's Collins Key.
And for today's video,
we are gonna be creating a giant DIY edible PokéBall.
Now this was all inspired, obviously,
by the Pokémon-Go craze that is literally happening
across the world right now, and I thought, "you know what?
Why not make a giant edible PokéBall
and then try to catch some real life Pokémon with it?"
If you want me to do even more DIY videos,
let me know by liking this video
and if this video gets enough thumbs up,
then in the future I will do more videos just like this
and also, I'm doing a huge give away
on my channel right now.
I'm giving away a MacBook, so if you wanna win that,
let me know by liking this video, comment down below:
What is your favorite video
I've ever posted on this channel?
Of course, you must be subscribed to this channel.
Without any further ado, let's jump in right now.
Let's create a giant DIY edible PokéBall.
Alright, guys, to get it started, here's what you need:
Measuring cups, cake mix, eggs, oil, cream cheese,
fondant, fondant roller, edible black spray paint,
because I could not find black fondant.
So, here's the game plan of how we're gonna make this.
We're first gonna bake a cake,
then we're gonna stack it and layer it,
from there we're gonna shave the whole thing down
into a ball shape, and last, but not least,
we're gonna decorate it to look like a PokéBall.
Step number one is bake the cake.
Alright, so we're gonna open up the cake mix first.
Oh! I almost spilled it everywhere.
That was close, dump it out.
I think we're gonna need a bigger bowl.
Packet number two.
Now I do understand that I'm using a lot of cake mix
for this, but that's because I wanna make a giant PokéBall.
So, the bigger, the better.
Next up, we are going to be adding eggs,
there we go, that's one egg.
We now have two eggs, and three.
Oh, no! I just cracked it.
Oh, yep, it definitely cracked, let me just use my spoon,
get the egg out of there, and we're good.
Egg number two I'm going to try to crack with nothing more
than a flick of the finger.
Ouch! It worked, but that hurt a lot,
and it shot all the way over here.
There we go, that's egg number two.
I'm gonna try to crack egg number three
with egg number four.
(eggs crack)
I'm gonna use the blunt end of the cup to crack the egg.
It worked!
I'm not gonna say I'm like an innovative chef right now,
but I'm finding brand new ways to crack eggs.
I think that's worth a Nobel Prize or something there, man.
For this final egg,
I'm gonna use a cardboard box to crack it.
This is unprecedented
in the egg-cracking community right now.
I don't think this has ever been attempted, so, yeah.
(box bangs against egg)
I got this.
Switch sides
(box bangs against egg)
(video game music)
Well, I gotta say it worked.
Um, man, I cannot just be basic with eggs.
That is one thing you guys have learned.
I wonder how this tastes.
Urgh!
After the recent excitement of adding all those eggs,
I have a feeling that the vegetable oil
is not going to be nearly as exciting,
so I'm literally going to fast-forward
through this part right now.
(speedy music)
Like I predicted, that was absolutely boring,
for both you and I.
Next step, that actually worked, is to mix it all up.
So, I've never really whisked a cake before,
but I think you just kinda do this?
I don't know.
Alright, well, um,
I gotta admit, this is kinda just like,
not looking like cakey at all.
Is this like what baking is really like?
I always thought it was like fun,
it was like throwing flour everywhere, but this is,
this is not fun.
This cake is not mixing very well at all,
it's always like stuck in the middle of my whisk
and that's where the majority of it is
and the rest is all this like weird slimy.
(whisk taps against bowl)
It's actually mixing though, hey!
Okay, yeah, it's starting to look better.
I need to take a break.
Okay, I'm done. Give me one second.
Alright, we're good to go, here we go.
Oh my gosh, okay.
- [Narrator] One eternity later.
- Now that it's all mixed,
it's time to dump it into the pan.
There we so, this is gonna be a lot of cake.
Don't lose the spoon, oh, that was so close.
Yeah, next we're gonna back the cake.
- [Narrator] Later
- As you guys can tell by the fact that
it's gotten rather dark outside, the cake is finally baked
and now it's time to create the layers.
So, to make this easier,
I cut out a piece of paper in a circle shape.
That way, I can put it over here, cut out one circle here,
one circle here, and then a half-circle
and another half-circle.
So, we're gonna do this right now.
I'm pretty nervous about this,
I really wanna get this DIY right,
so I'm so nervous to mess this up.
Getting close to my hand, don't wanna cut it.
That turned out really well!
Okay, I'm excited, I'm getting more and more excited
as this goes on, this is gonna turn out so well.
So, now that I've cut out the outlines,
I'm not exactly sure how to remove them
without really destroying the whole thing,
so there's gonna be
a little be of trial and error right now.
I'm gonna see if I can remove all the stuff around it first.
Alright, here we go, the moment of truth.
So nervous, okay,
this is going to be so legit!
Yo, I'm being like so careful right now,
'cause I don't wanna like mess this up, okay, there we go.
I'm so hyped right now! Oh my gosh!
Last, but not least, the two pieces coming together,
finish it off, we'll go one right there,
Oh my gosh, first of all this is the first cake
I've literally ever baked in my entire life
and look at how it turned out!
And there's like little gingerbread things,
well these aren't gingerbread things,
but there's these things too, yay!
Okay, here we go, hold on.
It's amazing.
Now, we're gonna use that cream cheese frosting
to glue this cake together, so that's the next step.
But, that catch though.
Well, another interesting part of the video.
I literally have nothing interesting to say about this,
like at all, like nothing is coming to mind, hmm...
That wasn't fun.
Alright, now, the moment of truth,
get these layers to glue together,
so there we go, boom right on top of each other.
Yeah, I would say that works out pretty well,
now it's time to glue these two layers to that layer.
And we're back again for the most interesting
part of the video, round two.
Alright, so here we go, half number one and half number two.
There we go, perfect.
Now onto the next step, which is shaping the cake.
Once you've created the shape of the PokéBall,
now it's time to add the cream cheese frosting
to the outside of it.
We are almost there and the next step right now
is with the fondant.
I'm just gonna roll it out and create the PokéBall.
We are literally at the final stages.
Mwah!
I've never really worked with this stuff before
and it's like a, ow, it's like a brick.
(fondant thumps on the counter)
What?
It smells just like Play-Doh too,
which is the most disgusting part.
Luckily, we've got a roller here,
so I guess we can use this to, I don't know,
roll this stuff out?
Just go for it I guess, I don't know.
Alright, here we go, so we're gonna cut it in half first.
Oh! This stuff is solid.
Holy cow, okay, this stuff is really disgusting.
Is this edible? I don't think, this can't be edible.
Oh! This is not easy, no, this is like folding on itself.
This stuff is not easy to work with, that is for sure.
The whole chair is like turning
as I'm trying to spread this stuff out.
This is not easy at all.
Okay, I'm gonna try to channel my frustrations right now
into creating this fondant better.
Alright, so after years and years of work
to roll this thing out,
now it's time to place the red on the PokéBall.
So, we're gonna place it on the back here.
Yo! This is going to look so sick, oh my gosh!
Okay, there we go, part number one is done.
Now it's time to smooth it all out and make it look good.
But, this is looking dope.
Alright, now it's time to take the white fondant
and put it on.
This PokéBall is coming together so well, oh my gosh.
Yo-o-o-o!
Yes, yes.
And now for the finishing touches, which is that black band
that goes around the PokéBall.
So, I had to spray paint some of the white fondant
because I don't have any black fondant, but here we go,
let's give this a shot.
Oh! No, no, no!
That was a lot more difficult
than I initially had anticipated.
Bam! Things are coming together.
The moment you've all been waiting for, the big reveal,
here we go, 3-2-1!
Yo! Like it actually turned out so well.
So, right now, I've got my real-life PokéBall
and all I need to do is just catch a real-life Pokémon.
(ball hits Pokémon) - Oh!
- If you want me to continue making DIY videos like this,
let me know by liking this video, comment down below:
Who is your favorite Pokémon character?
Of course, please subscribe to this channel,
that would really mean a lot.
I will see you guys again very soon, bye!
(snaps fingers)