- I like whipped cream on my waffles.
(laughing)
What's up, it's Collins Key and for today's video,
I am doing something very special.
To start this, I need someone to help me out
so are you ready for this?
- [Mikey Bolts] No, I'm not gonna do it!
- You said you would do this.
What are you talking about?
- [Mikey Bolts] No, no, no, I'm over this, no.
- You are teleporting here right now.
(snaps fingers)
- (sighs) All right.
(Collins laughs)
- So guys, today I am joined
by the master voice impressionist himself, Mikey Bolts,
and today we're going to be prank calling
a whole bunch of super-famous YouTubers
with voice impressions and we're gonna to be telling them
that we just found this brand new feature
on the iPhone 7 that will actually change your voice
into a cartoon character's voice.
And hopefully, they believe it.
I mean I can get creative because I've done a lot
of pranks on these different YouTubers
and so they might be catching on by now.
So today is going to be a challenge to see
if we can pull one more prank on them.
And you have to do a thumbs up if you guys want a part two
with even more of voice impressions and comment down below
who are your favorite cartoon character you would love
to see us do a voice impression of.
Now make sure you guys go check out a video we did
on Mikey's channel.
We called Apple employees and let them know the iPhone 7
was having some major bugs via cartoon voices
and a whole bunch
of different voice impressions on that one.
Link is right over there and if you guys are one
of my people, very important, go subscribe to Mikey.
This guy is the man.
So, so talented.
I've been a fan of his for three years now.
So make sure you guys go show his channel
some serious love.
Give us a video thumbs up
and just like comment and be like,
"Yo, Collin's channel sent me."
Without any further ado, right now let's jump in
and just get to the prank calling.
- Let's do it.
(laughs)
(phone ringing)
- You what, how quick was that?
(giggling)
- Sure!
You guys are like very giggly tonight.
- OK, I just got the iPhone 7
and there's this new feature on it
and it's kind of like a hidden feature.
You can basically manipulate your voice
into any cartoon character's voice.
So just give me a sentence.
- Boopadegumbo?
- OK, I'll try boopadegumbo.
And, I'll try like do you guys know Family Guy at all?
OK, well they have a Stewie voice.
Let me try it.
- Boopadegumbo
- Right?
- Yeah! It's freaky!
No, no give me another sentence.
- Lactise em what?
I'll just give it a shot.
I'll try like in Peter voice.
- Lactase enzymes
are good.
Yeah!
(girls giggling)
- Right?
- Hello, ladies.
Kermit the frog here.
I want you to submit whatever you have promptly
and I will say it.
Thank you.
(girls giggling)
- You guys know I have zero voice impression skills
Hello, I'm Stewie.
That's kind of savage, but yeah.
- The rain in space stays mainly in the place.
- No, I'm just messing with you guys.
I am actually collabing with the creator of Family Guy
right now, Seth McFarlane.
(gasps)
- Hi!
Yeah, so say hi to Seth.
- Hey, how's it going?
How are you?
- Thank you.
- Are there any other questions that you guys have for him
or anything you guys want to say to him?
- Oh, thank you so much, ladies.
That means a lot.
Thank you, seriously.
Oh, okay.
I'll follow you both on Twitter.
All right, you guys are fun.
- (laughing) So guys, I'm sorry.
This is a prank call.
This heartbreak has been Mikey Bolts
It's totally here, I'm sorry.
(laughs)
- Now we can (mumbles), you ruined it.
- I'm real sorry!
- He's so much lamer.
- I'm sorry guys.
Yeah, I know!
You guys better get me back,
that's all I'm saying!
So sorry, guys!
All right, guys, I love you.
I'll talk to you guys later.
All right, cool, bye!
(laughing)
- Oh my!
- Yo, I'm sorry Veronica and Vanessa.
You guys, I love you guys so much.
You guys are the homies.
So, I'm waiting for you guys to get my back.
This is literally my fourth time of hard core pranking them.
All right guys, I'm calling the...
Hello?
Dang it!
It literally came in on the worst freaking sentence.
Oh my God!
The guys are pranking, oh my God, and you answered.
Well, that was great!
Uh hey, so you heard about this new iPhone 7, right?
Well, did you hear
that you can make new voices with it?
- Hello Gabby!
(laughs)
- Yeah!
All right, well, that was worth a shot.
All right.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Bye!
- That was great!
- That could not have gone better, in my opinion.
- Perfect!
- Nailed that, from top to bottom.
I'm calling BruhItsZach or Zach Clayton.
So I hope that this goes well.
Yo, what's up bruh?
I just got the new iPhone 7, dude.
There's this new setting in it where I can like
make my voice in like Family Guy.
Right, give me a line to say.
- You look like a monkey!
- You
look like
a monkey.
- Right, bro, it's crazy!
Dude, it's nuts!
Even like Peter.
Give me another line to say.
You smell, okay.
- You smell like cheetos.
- What's like a popular song right now?
What's the Justin Bieber one?
How does that one go?
If you feel yourself sinking in the cold, cold water.
Right, but check this out.
- If you feel yourself sinking in the cold, cold water.
(laughs)
- No, bro, I'm doing a prank call.
Yeah, that everyone.
Have a great night!
(laughs)
All right, cool, talk to you later, bro.
- Bye, Zach.
- All right guys.
The next person I'm calling is Chloe Couture.
- [Voicemail] You have reached the voice mailbox of
- This is Chloe.
She called me back.
Hey!
So with the new iPhone 7, like I just got one.
You can manipulate your own voice in a cartoon voice.
So just give me a sentence to say like I'll show you.
- Chloe is the best YouTuber of all time
and she is awesome.
- Yeah.
It just manipulates my voice into that.
Let me just try something, hold on.
- I think you're great.
You're so pretty.
You're always pretty.
(laughs)
- Right? It's so..
Yeah or even if it's just on a call like this.
Here's another one too.
- If you sneeze, make sure you use a tissue paper.
- Yeah, I know.
It's really, really, really cool!
And there's even Patrick from Spongebob and stuff.
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- Like I don't have to go to the bathroom.
I was just saying that and stuff.
So my idea is like if we prank call YouTubers,
and use the voice on them.
Cause what would happen would be like we would call
the YouTubers and prank them and they would think
that I am actually calling them to set up a collab.
But in fact, I'm actually calling them
to prank call them with these voices.
Kinda like right now.
(laughs)
No, this is a prank call.
Yeah!
Yeah I'm here with my friend, Mikey,
who does voice impressions.
- Sorry for pranking you.
- No, it's Mikey.
- Nope, all me.
My bad!
- Yeah, no, I'm so sorry!
Have a great night!
All right.
We're going to give Rachel a Facetime.
Is that a thing when you give someone a Facetime?
- I'm gonna give her a Facetime.
- One Facetime for you.
Do you know Family Guy at all?
Okay, well you can do a Family Guy voice.
I'm gonna try this one.
I like cheese a lot.
Right?
And I can try a Peter voice too
and it's like
I like
whipped cream
on my waffles.
Tell me like something to say.
What's the deal with airplane food?
Cool!
Well, yeah, this is actually a prank call.
I don't know how else to say it.
That's just yeah.
Yeah I'm here with my friend, Mikey,
that does voice impressions and stuff.
- Hi, sorry for pranking you!
- Yay!
All right, so we're calling Jake Foushee right now,
and he has a new number so I don't have his new number.
Mikey does.
- There'll be a couple of hooligans doing voice prank calls.
- Yo, brother.
This is (mumbles) Collins.
Why?
I appreciate it!
You're the man, bro!
Do you have the iPhone 7?
Okay dude, I just got one.
There is an e-straight feature on the iPhone 7
that will manipulate your voice
into any cartoon voice or something.
Give me a sentence to say.
All right, I'll try it like Peter.
Let me see if the Peter one works.
- Ah,
I just started a fire.
- Right?
Even if it's like making noise, you can turn it
to Kermit the Frog and make weird sounds
- Hip hop hebop sneerop.
Kermit the Frog here.
Hap ho up keep up.
- I know, man!
Apple took away the headphone jack
but they gave us the voices, man!
It's like crazy!
Yeah and it even works with song lyrics and stuff
and it will sing popular songs like...
Yeah that's so awesome!
Wrong, this is just a prank call.
Do you know Mikey Bolts?
Yeah, well he's right here with me right now.
He's the one doing the voices.
- What up, Jake?
My bad!
We didn't mean to joke on you.
You're a good guy!
- I'm sorry, bro!
(laughs)
No, bro, you're good.
Too funny, bro!
- You're the man, Jake!
- Let's hear it! - Which one?
- Yeah, I gotta give that one a shot.
I can't do it.
I'll be like Autobots, transform and roll out.
That's legit, bro.
Go check out the video we did on Mikey's channel
where we prank called all the Apple store employees.
The link is right over there.
Give it a thumbs up.
Comment that this video sent you
and subscribe to Mikey.
This guy is amazing!
And like I said, thumbs up for a part two
with even more cartoon voices.
I love you guys so much!
New videos coming out two, even three times a week,
so that means you've got to subscribe.
Without any further ado,
would you like to make me disappear right now?
You get the honors.
- I would love to, Collins!
- Psych! Too late!
- That didn't go as planned.