- Okay, that's it, Collins Keys,
I'm roasting you and you are horrible.
And look atcha, you look like Donald Trump.
- (laughing) What?
- What's up it's Collins Key
and yes I know I don't normally upload
on a Sunday, but something happened
that I really need to address.
And I can't, it's been like weighing on me.
I can't just have this out there, I got roasted.
And no I didn't get roasted by Rice Gum.
I don't get roasted by Drameller.
No, it's the worst roast possible,
I got roasted by you guys.
Now granted, I did ask you guys to roast me.
There's three different rounds to this roast.
Round number one takes place on Instagram.
Why I released this photo right here,
don't even ask why I released this photo.
And in the comments, you guys went in.
You guys were savages, you roasted me so hard.
Round number two takes place on Twitter.
I released this photo and fun fact,
I made that face on national TV on Cartoon Network.
My voice just cracked, that's how
embarrassed I was, it was terrible.
And round three is a dis track round on SnapChat
where I asked you guys on SnapChat
to roast me with your very own original dis tracks.
So that's round number three, we're gonna be going in.
I'm gonna need like ice, I'm gonna need aloe,
I'm gonna need water, I'm gonna need lotion,
I'm gonna need sunscreen, I'm gonna need everything.
Because I'm gonna be so burned
and roasted by the end of this video.
If you guys do one thing, just give this
video thumbs up for some encouragement.
Because seriously, I allowed you guys to go ham on me.
And if you're excited about this bonus video,
well get excited because they're gonna
be a lot more bonus videos cause from
now on I'm doing two videos a week on YouTube.
One on Thursday and then one bonus video
every single week, gonna keep you guys guessing.
So make sure if you haven't already,
subscribe to this channel and even if you are
subscribed, make sure you turn on the channel notifications.
So that no matter when this bonus video comes out,
you guys will be notified and the first people to see it.
I'm also doing a huge giveaway on my channel right now
where I'm giving away a MacBook this month.
So if you guys wanna win that,
let me know by liking this video.
Comment down below what is your favorite
video that I've ever posted.
Of course, you must be subscribed to this channel.
And I'm gonna put the winner of
the May giveaway at the end of this video.
Without any further adieu, right now,
let's jump in and yeah, get roasted.
Alright, round one is Instagram
and this is the photo that I posted.
And I dressed up like this for
Harry Potter's book release because if you guys
have read the books, you know that wizards
when they try to dress as muggles, they're
not able to do it and they always
end up looking really crazy so that's what happened to me.
I'm so nervous, let's go to the Instagram comments.
Everything in that outfit is actual okay.
But what he forgot to wear is a bra.
I mean if you wear a pink top, you need to wear a bra.
Hey, you don't know I mighta been wearing,
what are they called training bras, I don't know.
I think if you added some bling around your neck
and a big black shirt, you'll look exactly like Eminem.
(laughing) That's not even, that's not even a roast on me,
that's a roast on Eminem, oh my gosh.
When you realize that you look so fabulous,
the modeling agency fired you (laughing) what.
When half of you wants to go swimming,
but the other half doesn't.
This picture reminds me of your first
musically, a complete disaster (laughing).
Yo, I thought my first musical was cool.
Those shorts are higher than Wiz Khalifa (laughing).
When a girl says she likes nerds, this isn't what she meant.
No one likes you, stop acting like you're perfect.
I hate you so much, look at yourself, you look
like a dork or an idiotic person.
Go die somewhere otherwise you'll end up like Jacob S.
Like that stupid kid for asking something
stupid like your life, die Collins die.
I was expecting a roast, not like a death threat okay.
Your hairline looks like a bald eagle.
Why don't you slip into something a little
bit more comfortable like a coma.
Are you supposed to be Kylie Jenner with that pose?
Come on man, grow some balls.
America's got no fashion skills.
America's got no fashion skills, that was the show
I was on guys for those of you who are wondering.
Shine bright beautiful as you always are Collins,
no matter how you look or what you wear.
What a sense of style and then person
below was like, y'all suck at roasting.
Dude this is a game of where's Waldo with your muscles.
I was like 12 okay, I didn't have like any muscles.
Give one dollar a month to help this poor person
into buying two pairs of shoes that are the same.
Or donate a blue croc, this will help a lot.
I showed my dad this picture and he said that's a cute girl.
You look like where's Waldo so stop
acting like him and get lost.
Round two is Twitter and this is the photo
you guys are roasting me on, so you guys
thought the last round was intense.
This one, this one's gonna be
even worse, so yeah, let's get to it.
When you're trying to be cute because
you're failing badly with them caterpillar eyebrows.
(laughing) Oh my god do they look like caterpillars?
When diarrhea attacks, part one (laughing).
What is part two of diarrhea attacking?
It says your bottom lip looks like
it's trying to eat you top lip.
Alright this one is when Bob the Builder
tried drugs for the first time.
Oh my gosh, you look like a goose
who's ears are about to pop out
of your head (laughing), oh my this photo (laughing).
Shrek called and he wants his face back.
You remind me of a creepy doll I once had
after my little cousin melted its face off, what?
Even Bob the Builder can't fix that face.
Oh my gosh, I see no difference.
That's cold, that's so cold.
Round three is SnapChat dis tracks.
This is obviously the one that
I'm the most nervous for cause I have
no idea what you guys are gonna say, so yeah, let's do it.
- Your hair actually looks like the tsunami
that hit Alaska ten years ago that killed
over 200,000 people, like please stop.
- Oh my gosh, (laughing) wow.
- You are just a lameo, a lameo bleep.
I'm sorry you are a lame bleep.
- Oh, gotta bleep all that out, holy cow.
- I think it's stupid man.
- The hair looks stupid okay.
- (Talking like a baby).
- (Laughing)
- [Contestant] Bigger than your lobes.
Nose so big, big grape jelly is it
Collins Key or the Fruit Loop bird?
- (Laughing) That was super like sneak dis right there.
Like you weren't even in the video.
- You're hair looks like a mushroom.
Your head looks like a mushroom.
- You look like a piece of shrimp
that sat on my table all day.
- (Laughing) what?
- Tell me why Collins Key look like Donald Trump's son?
- (Laughing) What, I'm waiting for a roast.
Out of all of them, that one hurt the most.
- Yo Collin, you gotta hit the weight room bud.
- Those traps are not gonna get
you to a million selfies bro.
- Not gonna happen.
- (Laughing) Those traps are not gonna
get you to a million selfies, what are traps by the way?
Alright, I'm gonna stop right there.
That is definitely enough roasting for the day.
If you guys enjoyed this video, let me know
by giving it a a big thumbs up.
Because trust me, I went through
a lot of roasting for this video.