(upbeat music)
- [Girl] I love watching skaters.
Because they're so free, messy, wild.
We spend our lives being told that we need to be in control.
We are told to write between the lines,
the test only has one answer, and above
all, be a good girl.
Even when we do everything they say,
one day we wake up to our parents divorcing
and the universe laughing in our face.
Control is just an illusion.
The big secret no one ever tells you
is that once you let go of control
that's when the real fun starts.
- Yo Collins, did you find her?
- Not yet.
Hey have you guys seen this girl?
- Yeah, she was definitely here.
- Yeah.
- I think, like earlier today.
- Do you remember when?
- Yeah, it was like, earlier.
She was taking like some sick art photos.
She had mad style man, I remember
because he was like, dude, she's a dime.
(laughs)
- Yeah she was a dime for sure.
- I was like, yeah, if you're into that.
- [Collins] Did you talk to her, do you know where she went?
- Sorry, but hey, you should come watch me skate some time.
- Okay.
Did you guys just see that?
He was like, see me skate, but really
he was like, let's touch mouths.
- What?
- Yes, totally, that was so cute!
- Carla, where you been girl?
I hit you up like six times!
- Hey, babe, I was gonna text you.
- No, it's my bad, she's been helping me out.
- I wasn't talking to you boy band.
- Eddie chill.
- What, don't make me look bad in front of my guys!
- You don't need help with that.
- What was that?
Why don't you go back to your little webcam!
Make another stupid Youtube video.
- Oh, yeah, like ollies with Eddie Z.
How many views did that get?
- Ollies with Eddie Z!
- Eddie, don't you dare!
- What?
He knows I'm just messing with him!
We're bros, right Collins?
- Yeah bros.
- Cool, so why don't you and your
little sidekick get out of here
so I can spend some time with my girl?
- Yeah he's my sidekick, we're going to a street jam!
- What?
Let's get out of her Carla, come on!
- You know if you continue to pretend
to be a jerk, eventually you'll just be a jerk.
- Dunch bag!
- Whatever!
I'll see you later tonight anyway Carla!
Yo ten bucks says I can tre flip over that, first try!
- Ollies with Eddie Z!
The only reason why I showed you those
videos is so you'd know you have something in common!
Now he thinks I'm talking!
- Well what was I supposed to do, knock him out!
Look, I've got a black belt, it wouldn't have been fair.
- Wow you're such a tough guy Collins,
you and him both, why don't you just grow up!
- Why don't you just chill out!
- Do not tell me to chill out!
Jake stop, just, look I know you've
never really taken him seriously,
but the fact is he's my boyfriend.
So the next time you decide to get
into it with him, stop dragging me in the middle!
- No, what is there to take seriously about this guy Carla?
You want to know the facts?
The fact is that you can do so much better than him!
Look, he is doing nothing with his life!
And you are so driven, you work so hard!
You take care of people, you're beautiful, you're smart!
(dramatic music)
(beep)
- Carla, come on!
(dramatic music)
(ringing)
- Who's that?
- I don't know, I don't give out this number.
- Maybe it's your girl?
- Hello?
- Yeah, I knew you were screening my calls!
- [Martin] Yeah, this is Martin, that's right!
Next time you wanna act like you're
disappearin' how 'bout you tell
your homies not to take pictures.
'Cause I can see 'em all on the internet,
and I know your phone's working!
Listen, we talked about rehearsing today!
Where were you?
Listen Collins, do I have to remind you
that this week is the most important
week of your professional life?
You know how hard we've worked to get here!
Please do not ruin this for us, okay?
I got to go.
- What am I doing?
- What do you mean?
- Why am I risking it all for some
random girl that I don't even know?
I've made a lot of sacrifices to get where I'm at.
Don't get to be with the girl of
my dreams, whatever, I'll live.
- Okay, excuse me, can you pull over right here?
Please, thank you!
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna walk.
- Oh come on, Carla!
- [Collins] We're three miles from home!
- I'll have Eddie get me.
- No we're not gonna leave you
on the side of the road, come on, get in.
- No.
- Fine!
- Sit down!
Just go back to your career or
chasing your dream girl, or whatever!
I just can't sit here and listen to you guys!
I'm fine.
- Text me!
(dramatic music)
- [Girl] I used to get so confused and lost trying
to figure out who everyone thought I should be.
Then I realized that being lost
is the only way to find out who you are!
And what you really want.