What's up, guys?
It's Collins Key,
and welcome to the Thursday Vlog.
Now, for today's video,
I've got a brand new challenge for you,
and I need someone to help me out with this.
You haven't seen him in quite a while,
so everyone please welcome back to the Thursday Vlog,
the mini-fridge version of me, Devan Key.
Hey!
Catch the egg!
- Oh!
- That was close.
For today's video,
we are going to be combining two things.
One thing you don't know about us is
the fact that we can both juggle.
We have juggling skills,
off the skillet, yo.
I don't know what I was doing there.
- Off the skillet...
(laughs)
- What?
And the second thing is
you guys love watching us get destroyed by eggs,
and so we're combining two of those things today:
the juggling and also the egg-destroying.
There's three super difficult rounds to this.
Whoever wins the majority of these difficult rounds,
they get to destroy the other person
with a full carton of eggs.
Whoa!
So basically,
if you guys are ready for this video,
make sure you guys give it a thumbs up right now.
Without any further ado, Devan, catch the egg!
- No!
- Dude!
You ready?
- I wasn't ready.
- Catch it, catch it, catch it.
Yay, alright, let's do this.
Round One, the classic juggle-off!
(laughs)
Whoever can juggle for the longest wins.
Here we go.
One, two, three, go.
Dude! (mumbles)
- Nervewracking!
- You can't hit my hands, bro! That's cheating.
- Ah! So nervous!
- Oh, dude! You can't do that!
(laughs)
Well, I lost first.
- I lasted like one second longer than you did, so.
- Alright.
Yeah, you did, by one second.
So, I lose that round.
Round Two, not my arms.
Yay.
They're not really my arms.
Whoever gets the most tosses
without dropping wins this round.
And, begin.
One, two, three, four. Oh! Dude!
- Hey, what's up? Hey, hey!
- Dude!
(laughs)
That was so-- Dude, seriously?
- Oh! What?
- You can't do-- You can't do that to me, bro!
- No! That was not-- No!
I wanna hug you, you know? Just--
- There we go! That's what you get!
(laughs)
I kinda-- Oh!
Round 3. Ah!
Dude, chill! Chill!
(yelling)
- Oh, no!
It's going into my ear hole!
- Round Three is called stealing.
You'll see why in a second.
Without further ado, let's get started.
And begin.
Oh, snap! Oh, he's thinkin' about it!
Uh oh! Uh oh! Oh! Oh! See, this is actually-- bro!
Devan wins this challenge.
He gets to destroy me with a full carton of eggs.
- I'm so psyched.
Oh, no! I can do whatever I want!
(laughs)
- Alright, cool!
Let's do it.
Give me a thumps up right now
for, like, some encouragement,
'cause I'm not looking forward to this.
- I call this move "The Clear."
Are you feeling okay?
(machine noise)
Clear!
(laugh)
- Ow!
You just punched me in the chest!
(laughs)
Oww!
Oh!
Dude, seriously!
You--
- Gosh!
- Yeah, I'm a crazy kamikaze.
Ay!
This is called the pocket egg.
If I really don't want these pants anymore,
it's all ready.
(laughs)
Now, there's like egg yoke running lie all down my leg. Ow!
(spitting)
Eww!
You're spitting, like, all over me.
Da da da da!
Oww!
No!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
(laughs)
Oww!
My nipple!
- Whoa, dude!
No!
- Oww!
(laughs)
- Oh, yeah!
It got my freakin' arms!
Oh!
No!
- Oww!
Ooh!
That hurts! Leg!
One egg left.
I've got one shot to hit him.
Go for it.
- Yeah!
Yes!
- There's another egg!
- Oh, no! Ah!
- Whoo!
If you guys enjoyed this video,
make sure you guys give it a big ole thumbs up
and share it with your friends right now
if it made you laugh or smile.
And also,
comment down below what other videos
Devan and I should do together.
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel.
There's weekly videos every single Thursday.
I'll see you guys again soon.
Bye!