- What's up, guys?
It's Collins Key and for today's video
I'm gonna be completely destroying my taste buds,
and to do this, I need a friend to enjoy me.
So everyone, please welcome Brent Rivera.
- What is up, everyone?
Hope you guys are having an amazing day today.
Thank you so much for having me.
I'm sorry, that just comes with it.
- That was impressive.
Yeah, Brent.
- We are gonna be creating the most sour drink
in the entire world.
We have a whole bunch of sour candy right here.
We have Toxic Waste, lemon juice, we got some sodas,
we have malic acid.
This stuff is death to your mouth.
This is what they put in sour candy,
like this is the main ingredient and its like concentrated
in this container right here.
So basically, we're gonna be trying each one of these
individually first and then dumping it all inside of here
and then we both have to drink the most sour drink
in the entire world.
Hopefully, we don't die.
Give this video a thumbs up for the fact that
we probably won't be able to taste anything for
I would say, a month after this video.
Now we also did a video over on Brent's channel.
We did social media in real life
and it was absolutely hilarious
so make sure you guys go check that out after this video.
The link is right over there, also down in the description.
And make sure you guys go subscribe to Brent right now
because this guy is the man.
Go show his videos some love.
- And if you guys are from my channel,
make sure you go subscribe to Collins.
I'm gonna give you - Oh thank you.
- Five seconds.
- Five, four, three, two, oh oh one.
- One, aye.
If you guys could do that, comment down below RIP Tastebuds.
Just comment down below if you guys could subscribe
to the channel in five seconds.
And right now, without any further ado, yeah let's do it.
First thing we're trying is a soda so here we go.
(electronic music)
- Oh, that's sour.
That's sour.
- That's pretty sour.
Alright, well um, this is the first ingredient
so I'm gonna dump mine in first.
Here we go.
(suspenseful music)
Alright, so you know what, Brent?
I think we give the people what they want
and we'll kick it off right off the bat
with some Toxic Waste because as you guys know
I've done this in one other video.
Literally, this thing killed me.
Toxic Waste, three, two, one, go.
(screams)
- The trick is, if you get three blue raspberries, one lime,
it's not gonna be as sour.
- Really?
- No, I'm kidding.
- Oh, I was like I did not know this.
I messed this up.
Alright, here we go.
Oh, mine has a hair on it.
Let me get that off, yuck.
Alright, here we go, you ready?
Three. - All at once?
What do we do with it? - Two, one, go.
I'm good.
(deeply inhales)
(grunts)
(screams)
- I can already feel my taste buds 50% gone.
My taste buds are legitimately gone at the moment.
(screams)
I had a little bit on my lips, and I just licked my lips.
Brought it all back.
- Okay, to add all the Toxic Waste to it now so
I'm gonna drop a few in.
- How many should I drop in, two?
- Two works, yeah. - One, two.
My tongue is numb.
Think that might be a good thing
'cause then our tongue is numb for the rest.
(suspenseful music)
Next, this looks good.
What is this?
- Yeah, that actually looks delicious.
It's more Toxic Waste, wait.
- No, wait, wait, wait, hold up then.
No more Toxic Waste, uh-uh.
I think the Dots Sours look good.
- Alright, let's give it a shot.
- Hopefully this is better than that Toxic Waste.
I expected it because the name is Toxic Waste
but that was more than I expected.
- Here are the Dots.
So, I say we gotta do a handful as well
'cause like this is an extreme challenge, bro.
- Okay.
- Alright, you probably can't see but there's like
a whole bunch of like powder stuff on here.
That is the malic acid stuff, okay?
And we're about to take that straight at the end of this
so here we go.
You ready, three, two, one, go.
Mm.
My mouth's so full of them, I can't even talk.
- Okay, well, I mean.
- We can have a lot of these, these are nothing.
Next these are Warheads Extreme Sour candy.
(moans)
Oh, this does not look good. - Wait are they like
What are they, gum, is it gum?
- I don't think they're gum.
- Okay.
- Ready, three, two, one, go.
(grunts)
Oh my god.
(screams)
- My tongue.
- Can't even walk right.
- Oh, I have so much saliva in my mouth right now
it's not even funny.
My tongue.
My tongue - My tongue, it's like
I would say 80% gone now.
So we're gonna add just a few of these.
- Oh no.
- Well that's all of them.
(suspenseful music)
- PEZ SourZ.
- I didn't even know this was a thing.
The worst part about this challenge is knowing that
in a little bit, we're gonna have to drink this.
Think about our individual reactions so far
to each one of these individually but all together.
Will we survive it?
- No, no, no, we won't.
- I'm just gonna take quite a few at once.
- Okay, me too.
- I don't, these might not be that bad though, we'll see.
Ready?
- Yeah.
- These are actually really good.
- I expected that, that's why I picked it, mm.
- Mm.
- They're good.
- That's what we just had.
Thank you, PEZ.
Alright, let's dispense these in.
(suspenseful music)
This is straight lemon juice.
- Oh no. - It's called
Italian lemon juice.
- I've experienced very bad situations with this.
I actually dared a friend to chug a whole thing
and ten seconds later he threw it all up.
- I say we'll go with the bubble gum instead.
Alright, here we go.
Three, two, one, go for it.
Oh my god.
(screams)
- Not again.
- Oh my god.
- My god, my god.
- I can feel it hurt, it's still hurting (mumbles)
(screams)
(crying)
- [SpongeBob Narrator] Twenty minutes later.
- Dude.
- What?
- My voice dropped like a whole octave.
- When I was buying these, the lady was like
be very careful not to do more than one
because her boyfriend did one of them, and lost his
like legitimately lost his taste,
and we just did four of 'em.
- Wow we are freaking
- Is my tongue messed up?
- Yes.
Oh my god, it's all red.
(laughs).
What color is my tongue?
(laughs)
- It looks like a bird.
- So it looks like a peacock?
- [Collins] Yeah.
- Yes, that's what I wanted.
- Alright, here we go.
We're going for it because we love you guys.
There's one, that's all that's left right there.
- Sour Farts candy?
Wait, what?
- Did you fart the farts?
- It better not taste like farts.
I swear I'm gonna puke.
You have to go first on this one
'cause I'm not eating a piece of fart.
What is that smell?
Is that fart smell?
- It, oh my, okay.
It literally smells like a fart.
Let's give it a shot.
(screams)
- What, what?
- I can't tell if it's because my taste buds are gone.
(laughs)
- What it is, it's not that sour.
Because like at first, it was like (groans)
and now it's like (groans).
Alright so you get the honors of adding the fart candy
to the mix.
- Alrighty, here we go.
(suspenseful music)
(fart)
- I just wanna get it out of the way.
I wanna go with the smog balls.
- Okay.
- By Toxic Waste.
- Anything by Toxic Waste is not good.
- The difference with this one though is like
the outside looks smooth like a jelly bean
so I don't know how sour this is actually gonna be.
Here we go.
These taste good.
Shout out to you, Toxic Waste, for not killing me.
- Not as sour chewy center.
- We're gonna add these 'cause these are delicious.
(suspenseful music)
- I vote these.
- Yeah, 'cause after what Toxic Waste just didn't to.
I'm excited for these.
The green one looks pretty gnarly so we'll go with that one.
- Okay.
- Alright, here we go, three, two, one, break it in half.
- Oh it's kinda, oh there it is.
- Okay, here we go, you ready?
- Yeah.
- Oh my.
It really is shockingly sour.
(laughs)
- Oh god.
- My mouth is literally on fire right now.
- My tongue needs a massage.
Oh gosh, I am not looking forward to this,
this smoothie. - I am not.
- [Brent] At all.
(suspenseful music)
- There's one more Cry Baby?
- Oh no.
- I literally died.
So guys, I though that Toxic Waste was the most sour candy
I've ever experienced.
These Cry Babies are on another level.
These are actual tear drops.
I might cry.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm good. - Oh.
- I'm fine.
- It's fine, right?
- Oh yeah.
- I think my tongue is bleeding now.
I can taste the blood over the candy now.
(groans)
Should we add 'em?
- Uh-huh.
I am sweating bullets right now, man.
This is just extremely painful, alright.
Here we go. (suspenseful music)
- Extreme sour candy, savor the sweet.
- There's two packets open.
So we'll just go with these.
- Contains soy.
- Contains soy. (laughs)
Cheers.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, ooh wow.
Wow, oh my (screams)
- [SpongeBob Narrator] A few moments later.
- I need a second.
- That was really bad.
- That was horrible.
Worst part now is I can feel little cracks in my tongue,
and like every time a sour candy goes in,
it just like seeps into those little cracks.
Okay, here we go.
Gotta man up, gotta add 'em in.
Here we go.
(suspenseful music)
We're saving the malic acid for the last one,
but right now, I say let's do a squirt of lemon juice.
- Okay.
I have a feeling that - This is gonna murder us.
- Oh, I know, it's gonna really.
- So I'll take a squirt first.
Here we go.
It actually taste delicious, after all the nasty stuff.
I'm not even kidding, that was amazing.
I need a little bit more.
I'm not even joking, this taste incredible right now.
- Same.
- I will add this liberally, bro.
(laughs)
This was, oh my gosh.
(suspenseful music)
- Supercharged chewy candy, Cry Baby Extra Sours,
and then we have the malic acid which is just
the hardcore stuff.
We're saving that for last, but right now.
Three, two, one.
I'm good.
- Uh-uh, uh-uh.
(groans)
- It's just actual pain.
It always is.
The worst part about this is my teeth.
I know I'm gonna have a cavity after this, dude.
Like there's just no avoiding a cavity.
Alright, here we go.
- Uh.
- Here we go.
Oh, there's more.
Now that moment you've all been waiting for.
Time for us to eat the malic acid
and please give this video a thumbs up
for the fact that our mouths are already dead.
And this is gonna be like the finishing shot right here.
Basically, I've heard that people take malic acid
for health reasons and what they will do,
it'll take like a half of tablespoon,
put it in a whole thing of water, and then drink it.
We're about to go full tablespoon, with no water so
- Oh no.
- Rest in peace, us.
- Looks like sugar, like it looks like
mm this will be delicious.
Alright, here we go.
Are you ready for this, bro?
Three, two, one, go.
(screams)
- Oh my god, I can't do it, I can't do it.
My mouth came out firing.
(screams)
This is not
- Hands down, the most sour thing I've
My mouth is numb, my mouth is literally numb.
(screams)
Oh my god, okay hold up.
That was hands down, the worst experience I have ever had
making a YouTube video.
And now we have to add this stuff to this drink.
I'm not hyped.
- Just a little bit.
Oh, okay that's good.
- That's good (suspenseful music)
Okay, so these are two of Brent's friends
and they did not believe us that this stuff
will destroy your life and so they wanted to give it a try
right now so we're like okay.
Three, two, one, go.
- No, no, don't spit it out, don't spit it out.
- Don't spit it out, don't spit it out.
- And now they know.
- Now they believe us.
- Now they know.
- Dude, look it, he's literally
- Oh my god.
- Oh my god, bro.
- Swallowed it, I swallowed it.
- You swallowed it? - Are you serious?
- Why would you swallow it? - What?
- [Collins] Are you okay, bro?
- Mhm.
(laughs)
- Now we have officially constructed the most sour drink
in the entire world, about to blend this thing up,
and then drink it so let's do this.
(groans)
- [Brent] That looks
- Oh my gosh.
Alright, well now the moment you've all been waiting for.
Time to drink these most sour drink in the entire world,
but first make sure you guys give this video a thumps up
and the moment we finish drinking this,
go check out the video we did on Brent's channel.
Go subscribe to him.
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel.
That'd really mean a lot, especially after
everything we've been through.
So right now, it's time to drink the most sour drink
in the entire world.
Three, two, one, cheers, go for it.
I drank it and in my stomach I feel it.
It's killing me.
I can get another drink, I can do this though, man.
(screams)
- I gotta drink more.
- Here we go.
I can't do anymore, I'm in (screams).
Alright guys, thank you so much for watching
and we'll see you guys again I don't know.
Bye.