(gagging)
- Yeah, my tongue looks like I feel right now,
just messed up.
This smells like a fart!
(sniffing)
(grunting)
- I love chocolate.
(laughing)
There are dead ants in it.
(beeping)
- What's up, it's Collins Key.
Now, today, I need some friends to help me out.
We are going to be doing something absolutely crazy.
So, let's give this a shot.
(screaming)
Oh, man!
Oh, that hurt, I'm not used to a wall
being right there when I yee.
My yee is just so powerful.
(screaming)
The wall stopped me, but today, guys,
we are doing the Gelli Baff Challenge with a sour twist.
Yes, this is baff, B-A-F-F, I don't know why.
Right now, we have a challenge
for you! - You!
- We wanna see if you can subscribe
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds.
All you got, five seconds, here we go.
Five,
four,
three,
two, one,
done.
If you can do that, comment down below
Keyper Squad right now, and make sure you guys go follow
all of us on Instagram.
Show my friends some love over here, also my brother,
yeah, show love to everyone.
Yay, no, I'm jokin'.
Alright, let's get into this video.
The point of this challenge, we have eight ping pong balls
that are being submerged in the gelli baff,
and then mixed all around.
Five of them are yellow.
If you pick a yellow ping pong ball,
you have to eat a piece of sour candy.
Two of them are pink.
If you pick one of those, you get to eat
a sweet piece of candy,
and there is one final one, and that is purple.
If you pick a purple one, you get the bag of mystery.
- Dun, dun, dun!
- We don't know what's gonna be inside the bag of mystery.
Each round, it'll change.
It could be really good, really bad, we have no idea.
So, right now, let's jump into this,
and let's submerge all of the ping pong balls
into the jello, or gelli?
What is this void in the oobleck or in the substance.
(screams)
Alright guys, here we go, round number one,
everyone raise your right hands.
One the count of three, we're just gonna stick it
in the stuff and try to find a ball, and then.
(laughing)
Pretty easy game playin'.
Three!
- [Christian] Three, what?
- I got one, I got one.
- I got one.
- I got one, so everyone get one.
- Here we go, three, two, pull it out.
No! - No!
- Yes!
- Alright, so, we all got sour candy,
and so, Christian got the only sweet one.
- Yeah!
- Not cool.
Alright, guys, so Christian gets to eat
a delicious chocolate frog from Harry Potter.
We have to eat Toxic Waste.
So, I think we're all gonna do it all at once.
Alright, here we go.
Three,
two, oh this is not good,
one, go!
(screaming)
- Oh, oh my god.
(grunting)
- I love chocolate.
- My mouth is on fire!
- My eyes are actually watering, guys.
There we go, that is round number one.
Whoa, that's intense.
One more thing I wanna let you guys know about.
My eyes are actually watering.
At the end of this, we are doing a lightning round.
It's gonna be three yellow balls, one red one.
After each round, we're gonna use whatever sour ingredient
was used to the bucket of doom.
So, kicking off, we have Warheads.
(dramatic string music)
Whoever picks the red one has to eat all of the sour candy,
but right now, we're onto round number two.
I want a sweet one.
I want a sweet one so bad.
Alright, guys, raise your hand, and begin!
I wanna, I want, no, no!
- [Devin] I'm goin' for that one!
- Tell me when everyone has one,
and we'll go for there, guys.
You ready, okay, I got one.
- Got one. - Got one.
- Three two one, go!
- Oh, I got it! - Ah!
- No! - No!
- Wait, but that's not necessarily a good thing.
- Well, I guess we're gonna find out.
Now, we get the bag of mystery.
So, first of all, we both got sour, Devin got sweet,
and you got mystery.
So, I guess we're gonna find what it is, here we go.
Devin, what did you get for your sweet item?
- I got some chocolate mixed
with some salt and potato chips.
- So, we have to eat Sour Farts.
- Yay.
(laughing)
- And Christian's been waiting.
He doesn't know what he got yet.
So, he gets the anticipation and the build up.
So, right now, we're gonna open these up,
and then, we're gonna go for it,
and then, we have to see what Christian got
in his bag of mystery.
I'm so sorry.
- This is like a Willy Wonka
chocolate factory
bar. - That looks delicious, bro.
- I'm so jealous.
- It's got the gold on there.
- Oh my gosh.
It smells like a fart!
(sniffing)
Here we go, three, cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers, guys?
- No.
- Two, one, go!
- [Christian] Gotta see this.
- Mm.
(gagging)
(laughing)
- This is so good.
(gagging)
- Look at your tongue, look at your tongue.
(exclaiming)
Yeah, my tongue looks like how I feel right now,
just messed up!
Alright, here we go.
Now, it's time for the bag of mystery.
Christian, you get you find out what you got.
It could be good, could be bad.
- What is it?
- Chocolate Dipped Insects?
- Oh!
- What?
- Oh my gosh
- Why?
How many do I have to eat?
- Dude, we took a handful. - All of them.
- Put all of them--
- I mean, I took at least five
or six bites of mine. - Christian, you should
- pretend it's the potato ships.
It's crunchy! - Yeah!
- No, there's legs sticking out of 'em.
- It just gives it extra texture.
It's like a fun little
surprising little treat.
Never know what's gonna pop out of it.
Alright, here we go, three
two, - No!
- One, go!
- Oh, the noise!
- It tastes like things it shouldn't taste like.
(laughing)
- Yo, ya'll better give this video a thumbs up
for the fact that Christian just ate
a ton of crickets.
- The aftertaste tastes like wet dog.
- Like wet dog?
- You had a leg on your lip.
- Oh!
Bro, I'm gonna be sick.
Alright, guys.
Christian, you're a trooper.
We're moving on right now to round number three.
(dramatic string music)
I have one goal, and that is to not get a sour one.
- Same. - So here we go.
Three, two, one, go!
I need to find another one.
Oh, it shot in my eye!
- You splashed it everywhere!
No!
- No, I need one, a new one. - Yes!
- No!
I can't even find one!
Are there enough in here?
I literally can't, I found Christian's hand.
I can't find it!
- Here's one.
- No, I want that one.
I want it, no, no, no!
Where'd it go, you got it?
- Yeah! - No!
- I got another sour one!
- I got another mystery!
(laughs)
- Ow, oh gosh, tweaked my shoulder.
So, Ava got her very first sweet piece of candy.
What'd you get?
- Marshmallow chocolate something.
- That sounds delicious. - That sounds pretty good.
- Devin and I got Smog Balls,
which I think I know, we love these ones,
and Christian got the mystery bag.
You get to open it up first, Christian.
- A paper. - A paper!
- What does it say?
- God card, you get to switch everyone's candy.
- What?
- Okay, so, Ava and Collins
are doing the Smog Balls.
- Why me?
- Bro, I'm your sister!
- Oh my gosh. - You get the chocolate.
- You're my sister, and I don't like you.
- Family, I am so sorry.
What have you done to us, Christian,
this is not cool, bro.
Alright, here we go.
Three,
two,
one.
(exclaiming)
- This is really good.
(gagging)
- That doesn't taste like candy,
it tastes like...
Oh my god. - Oh my god!
- Bro, Christian?
- Yo.
- If I ever get that wildcard one,
you are going down, bro!
You are going, I have yet to get a sweet one, fam!
(dramatic string music)
Alright guys, here we go.
I want a sweet one, go!
I gotta find a sweet one.
- [Devin] No, you got a head start!
- I can't even find another one.
- No!
- Yes!
- Here we go, hold on, here we go.
I don't know what it is.
No!
Christian, what do you have?
I got a gummy pizza, a gummy hot dog,
and a gummy burger.
- Sounds terrible, let's go.
Three, two, one.
(exclaiming)
(laughing)
No, no, no!
This is a no!
Ingredient number one,
death, death, death!
(dramatic string music)
I don't know what I'm doing wrong,
but I'm doing something wrong.
Go!
No, no, no, come on, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
- No!
- I got another one!
- No! - Yes!
- Woo-hoo!
How did you get another purple one,
Christian? - I don't even know.
- I like purple!
- I can not be more enthused right now.
I got chocolate.
That's a word, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, alright cool.
This has got orange bits in it.
I love orange, and I love chocolate, and I am excited.
What'd you get, Devin.
- I got Warheads Sour Pucker Packs.
- Yay.
- Ava get that too?
- Yeah, and we literally have
to dump the whole, ahh.
- And then, Christian.
Again, I don't know how it happened, got the mystery bag.
So, let's find out what's inside it.
- Ant candy.
- Oh! - Oh!
- There are dead ants in it!
- Wait, wait, wait, let me see this, bro,
there's no way.
- There are dead ants. - Oh my gosh!
- Those are big!
- Look at the ingredients.
Syrup and black ants.
(laughing)
- Natural artificially flavored!
- Fam, I got terrible stuff this whole time,
so I'm really excited.
- Everyone's throwing me bugs.
- Cheers. - Alright, here we go.
Three, two, one.
(coughing)
- It's in the bag of my throat.
- Oh, it burns.
- You know, I'm enjoying this.
(laughing)
(dramatic string music)
- And, begin!
I got one, I got one, I'm ready to go, I'm ready to go.
Three, two, one.
- No! - No!
- Why?
- I got sour!
- How did he get sweet again?
- You got wild card, though.
You better hope it's a good one.
This is a brand new sour candy.
Devin and I have never tried in a video.
It's called Warheads Super Sour Double Drops,
and the ingredients are literally acid,
like malic acid, just, a lot of acid.
- I got chocolate and wait, oh, what?
- What is that?
- There's new coins!
Ah, they're crunchy.
- Keep enjoying that.
Ava, what did you get?
Oh! - Oh!
- Oh my gosh!
So guys, this is the the Bean Boozled challenge.
For those of you that don't know,
half of the beans are delicious,
half of them are horrible.
So, we are gonna take this to the next level,
and we're not playing around with beginner ones.
We are only playing around with the black color,
which is either skunk or black liquorice.
- Oh no! - Oh my goodness.
- Here we go, not excited.
Three, two, one, go for it, and I'll go next.
- [Christian] Oh my gosh, you just put like 20 of them in.
(screaming)
- Ah, it gets worse!
Oh!
- Ah!
- Yo, Christian, you want some?
- No!
- You got no sour candy this whole round, bro.
Give it a shot!
- Oh, come on!
- Dude, it has a lot, a lot! - I'm gonna try some of it.
- Oh! - Oh!
- Oh my god!
(gagging)
Oh my god, oh my god.
- Alright, Christian is back now,
and Ava, it's time for you to find out
whether or not you got a good Bean Boozled,
or a bad one.
So, here we go, drum roll.
- What?
- I proud, no, I'm happy for her.
She's gotten all bad stuff this whole time.
So right now, we're onto the next round.
Let's go!
(dramatic string music)
Everyone hands up!
And go!
Alright, guys, here we go, you got one?
- [Devin] Uh, yes.
- Alright, here we go, three, two, one, go!
- No! - Oh!
- Really?
- I don't know, this could be good,
this could not be good.
- I literally gotten sour ones every time.
- Christian finally got his first sour one, yes!
- Ah!
- Okay, so, apparently, we have to do Cry Babies,
and these things are absolutely the worst!
- And hopefully, in the bag of mystery,
I get something sweet.
Let's see here.
It's a paper, yay!
Oh, sorry.
(laughing)
- He's recovering.
- No!
- What?
Oh!
- I have to eat everyone's sour candy!
- That's like, the whole box of this.
- Yay!
(soft piano music)
Fam,
pray for me.
Alright, all of em?
Alright, here we go. - Chug.
- Yep, I can confirm that's all of them.
(exclaiming)
- Oh,
oh!
- You missed one.
- Oh, mm, oh!
Oh, oh!
- He's tearing up the box.
- Okay, oh, uh uh.
I love this challenge.
(dramatic string music)
This is the final lightning round right now.
How this works, there are three yellow balls,
one pink one.
You get that pink ball,
you have to eat all of the sour candy that we used
throughout this video.
If you get a yellow one, you're safe.
Here we go, guys, three, two, one, go!
This is the round!
I got one.
I'm holding onto it.
I've got a good feeling about it.
Three, two, one, open.
Oh! - Oh!
- Oh, the goal was not to get the pink one.
(laughing)
- This is the perfect payback,
'cause Christian all the best stuff
throughout this entire game,
so you have to now eat every piece of sour candy.
You guys want a giant baff version of this challenge,
let's go by liking this video,
and now the moment you've all been waiting for.
I must say, this is like instant karma right here,
because he got no sour candy, and he's about to get it all.
Here you go, it's full of stuff.
You gotta do it, bro.
Here we go, three, two, one, go!
(screaming)
- Oh, dude, it touched me!
- Oh, it's goin down my leg!