- Have you ever eaten so much sour candy,
it made your face look like this?
(laughter)
Well today, we are taking real food verses gummy food
and making it sour off of your suggestions,
and today I'm here with Cole, Savannah, and Everleigh.
We also did a video on their channel.
So make sure you go check it out,
subscribe to their channel, and give
that video a thumbs up, and stick around
till the end of this video because we all
have to drink the sourest gummy food drink
in the entire world out of this blender.
But right now, let's get into it.
So for round number one, you guys suggested gummy bears.
We don't know which is which.
One of these is super sour, one of them is normal.
We're gonna find out which is which.
You wanna pull it off on the count of three?
- [Savannah] Uh-oh
Alright, here we go. Three, two, one, go!
(screams)
- We got the, no!
- You got the sour one!
- [Devan] No! - [Savannah] No, Everleigh!
- [Devan] She's switching sides?!
- [Collins] She switched sides on us!
- Hey babe, do you wanna... should we, should we family?
- They're just going family style.
I guess we're family as well.
You take that end, I'll take this end.
Alright here we go, three, two, one, go.
You take your bite. - Oh!
(painful hum)
- Come on! Come on! Get it! Come on!
(laughs) (disgusted sounds)
- This hurts my tongue!
- Oh! - Ah!
- You wanna lick one of the bear's paws and try that?
- Yes, a little piece.
- A little piece, just lick the paw right there.
- [Devan] Just lick it!
- Good!
- [Devan] What?! (laughter)
- What?!
- [Everleigh] I like the sour!
(laughter) - What?!
- Well, lucky you, you're gonna really enjoy this challenge!
Alright guys, so now we need to add a piece
of this super sour gummy bear,
I'm gonna go for the head and the ear over here,
into the drink. (laughter)
This is a tough gummy bear.
This might be kinda graphic. We might have to censor this.
(straining grunts) (laughter)
- What are you doing?!
- I can't even get it off.
- [Devan] Dude! - Alright, there we go!
- That's a little barbaric, don't ya think?
- The first piece of the sour drink.
- [Cole] Let's get a little bit of the
sour powder in there too.
(screams and laughs)
- [Savannah] Eewww!
- Alright guys, on to the next round.
- Alright, but I'm gonna take another bite.
- Alright, cool.
Is it that good? - [Savannah] Uh-huh.
- It smells delicious, we got the terrible one.
- The regular one is pretty good.
- Next up, you guys suggested gummy worms
versus sour gummy worms so one of us
is gonna be getting sour ones.
You ready? Three, two, one!
(screams)
- Wait wait wait!
- These are real worms!
- Oh my gosh!
New rule, I will give one switch rule,
which means that each of us will have
one opportunity to switch, so if you guys
wanna choose this round to be your switch round,
you guys can switch and you won't have to --
(Cole screams) (laughter)
- [Savannah] How'd he touch it?
(screams)
- They're not like normal worms!
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
(Everleigh screams)
(laughter)
- She said, hey hey next round, let's go.
Do you wanna switch it now?
- Yeah. - We're swapping.
- Swapping? Oh no!
- [Cole] Hey babe, I'm gonna pick yours and you pick mine.
Okay I'm eating this one. Okay, ready?
(screams and laughs)
- I don't know if that's a good swap!
Babe, try this one.
(laughter)
Yeah. Yeah. (Savannah screams)
- Oh my God that's so sour!
(Everleigh coughs)
- I got extra sour powder on there, you see that?
- Yeah just a little bit. Oh no!
- [Everleigh] Try it!
- It's that bad?
- Yeah! No, it's great! It's gnarly.
- They ate the first sour and they're both like...
(Collins laughs)
- That's the way to go. - Oh!
Oh my gosh.
- Yeah, exactly. It's bad. - [Devan] It is very sour.
- [Collins] Grab your worm. Ah! It moved. It moved.
(laughter) It moved so much.
- They're worms, of course they move.
- Ah! It's so active bro. They got muscles.
- This guy seems super chilled.
- Yeah grab the chilled one. Mine's like, whipping bro.
Alright guys, we're about to eat real worms right now!
But first, we've got to challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications,
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
You guys ready to do this countdown? Alright here we go.
- Seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
done!
If you can do that, comment down below "Keyper Squad"
right now, we're about -- (Everleigh screams)
- Ah! Ah! Ah! It's eating you!
- I know! Alright, here we go!
- Dude! Mine is doing moonwalk, look at this!
(Collins laughs) - Here we go!
- It's totally moving backwards.
- It's on my wrist.
Three, two... - No. No.
(Everleigh screams)
- I gotta pick it up first.
- I'm so sick.
(Collins screams) (group screams)
- Oh, I need a moment. (laughter)
I need a moment. (beep)
Alright you guys get to put the gummy worms...
I'm gonna pretend I'm not traumatized. Next round...
Ya'll are crazy. Who would suggest this? Let's go.
- Alright, but I'm gonna take another bite.
- Next up, you guys suggested watermelon, so here we go.
Three, two, one. (group screams)
- Oh wait, does that mean it has sour stuff on it?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, is that glazed?
- [Devan] Hold on.
- There's, like, already, like, chunks taken out of it.
- [Devan] Wait. I'm sorry. What's --
- I'm, I'm super suspicious.
- What has been done to this watermelon?
- I feel like, this one looks like it's the bad one,
but in reality, that's the bad one.
- Alright, so they're gonna do the sour watermelon.
We've got the real watermelon.
Our's looks very tampered with, like,
if this was in the store I would immediately ask for my
money back. - I'm very suspicious.
- This looks -- Ah! Sorry, it's just watermelon.
Why am I trippin'? Alright, ya'll ready?
- Dude what's that?! (slow motion voices)
(laughter)
- Scared me. So, I was about to like, fling this.
Watermelon's about to be on the ceiling.
(Collins laughs)
So I guess we're all gonna go at the same time.
Oh, she already went! - Oh, she's already in!
- It looks tampered with, but I'm sure
it's just a regular watermelon.
- Sourest watermelon ever.
- There's gotta be nothing different about,
I mean, nothing's popping out of it, there's nothing
- Alright, here we go, three, two, one
(screams)
(high pitched screams)
- Ah!
- [Savannah] So sour.
- Ah! - My lip is burning.
- What did, what did you do to it?
Are we really puttin', I guess we're puttin this
super sour watermelon in, I guess we put
it in along with the sour candy
as well. - Should we put these too?
They are sour.
- Yeah. - Yeah, we'll do both,
- So, yeah. Go for it. - That's a good one.
- She's goin' for all of'em!
- No, no. That's good.
- Alright, yeah, we're gonna call it off with that.
On to the next round. (scared scream)
- Alright, but I'ma take another bite.
- This next one, we kinda have
a hint of what it is. It's lollipop.
So here we go. You get to pull it off.
Three, two, one (screams)
- Yes! Yes! - We got the sour one.
- [Devan] She's already goin' for it.
(happy whistling music)
- The worst thing with, like, a sour lollipop
is like, it's not like you can chew on that gummy
to get rid of the sour, it's like you're licking sour.
- [Collins] Oh, no.
- Okay. - [Collins] Oh, no.
(gasps)
Oh, no!
(Savannah laughs)
- Babe, you gotta, like, get rid of it.
(laughter)
- Ouch!
- It hurts, right? - [Devan] Oh, no.
- I'm gonna go for this big powder spot, right here.
- [Devan] Oh, no. - [Collins] Dude, really?
- [Devan] Oh!
(Savannah laughs)
- Oh, and you got more than I did.
- You are like, so much more powder.
- So, I think, I think unfortunately
for the lollipop, we can't stick it in.
I think we're gonna move on to the
next round right now, but in thought --
- Why don't we just do this?
- Yeah just give it a good dunk.
There you go. (laughter)
Just, some good old saliva DNA sourness. It's all good.
Alright guys, next round. Here we go.
- Alright, but I'm gonna take another bite.
- Three, two, one.
(screams)
- Yeah! We got soda!
- Soda? - Is that like, what is that?
It's like a, sour soda gummy.
- Look, this is like, cola gummies. Okay, so
- Okay, okay. We'll go first. - We'll go first.
- [Collins] You guys go first?
- I'm like, I can do sour stuff now.
♫ We get the good soda
♫ We get the soda
- [Collins] There you go. Go.
- [All] Oooooooooooh!
- How was that?
- Bad.
(laughter)
- What's this one? (candy clinking)
(Cole screams) (laughter)
- Let me see it.
- Babe, do that. Do it! Just like,
suck on the candies inside of it.
- I swear, he's like a third brother, man. Like, I swear it.
- Do you taste that? - Oh!
(laughter)
- So now we get to eat some delicious soda.
Here we go. - You're gonna eat soda?
- I'll go first. Or, drink this soda, yeah.
It's soda, why not? Here we go. Three, two, one.
(gasps)
(laughter)
- Hold up! Hold up! Who said that this is gonna be sour?
Why is everything sour? I th--
- No one said it was sour! That's the issue!
- I thought it was sour verses not sour.
- What kinda soda is that? How did it--
- What is happening?
(sucking teeth) - Ah!
This is not a sour verses real.
This is let's prank people, especially Collins and Devan.
(laughter) - What?
- Ugh. I think we're just gonna dump this in here.
We need a liquid base for this, for this drink anyway.
- Oh! And, let's put some, some--
- I think we might need a little bit more soda later.
- Let's do it later, yeah.
- This drink is gonna cause some serious issues
when we have to drink it, but right now,
I guess, let's go for the next one.
- Alright, but I'm gonna take another bite.
- My teeth are already starting
to hurt from all this sour candy.
I can already feel it happening.
Let's see what this next one is. Three, two, one!
(gasps and screams)
No!
- Oh my gosh!
- [Collins] Wait, what is that?!
- Cat food! It's cat food! It's Friskies!
(screams) - [Collins] Wait!
- This is even a Friskies promo.
- We got, like, sour cat food? Okay.
- Bye bye.
- Aww, it's so gross.
(Savannah fake cries)
- You ready? I'm just gonna count down
and you just go for it. Ready?
- Okay.
- Okay, ready. Three, two, one, go!
- Chew it up! Chew it up! Chew it up! Chew it up!
(Collins and Devan groan)
(Cole laughs)
- Chew it up! I see it!
(laughter)
- That's gross.
- You are a, you are the real,
you are the real MVP on that one.
- [Collins And Devan] Oh my God!
- [Cole] Everleigh, did you just put it in?!
Everleigh put a piece in!
Everleigh put a piece in! - [Collins] Oh my gosh!
- [Savannah] Chew it up Everleigh, chew it!
(Everleigh grunts)
(laughter)
- Here we go. Three, two, one
- Hold up, I gotta, hold up! Bro--
- He's goin' for it! He's goin' for it!
He's goin' for it!
(candy chattering)
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
(Collins grunts)
- Nothing came out of mine.
- Here, take one of mine!
- No! No way! (Collins heaves)
(Collins heaves in slow motion)
- Oh! Oh! Oh, he's down! He's down!
- There's literally nothing coming out.
(Collins groans)
- Alright, I'm done!
(Savannah laughs)
- Let me warn you (mumbles)
- I guess we, I guess we just have to move on. Bummer.
- You gonna go for it? She's doin' the whole thing?!
- The whole thing?!
- Just a little bit! Just a little bit!
- [Collins] Wait, what?! What?!
- Oh! Why are you doing that? No!
- We have to drink this!
(groans of disbelief)
- Oh, Everleigh! Why'd you do that?
- You're a sneaky one! - Everleigh, you are--
- She is sneaky!
- You are drinking this, okay?
- It smells disgusting. We are almost there.
I think we've got one more thing left
and then we're drinking it. I'm not,
I'm not looking forward to it.
- Alright, but I'm gonna take another bite.
- Okay, so, something-- - What is that?
- [Cole] Something's a little uneven.
- Yeah. (laughter)
- I feel like it's not the same.
- I don't think we got the same thing.
- No. You wanna pull it off? You ready?
Three, two, one!
(screams) - Oh, it's her favorite!
- [Collins] Toilet candy?
- This is like, her favorite - We got water.
- This is Everleigh's favorite candy.
- Oh, really?
- We take her to the candy store and this is what she picks.
- Alright, so we just get some water.
- [Collins And Devon] Cheers!
- Hydration. Love it.
- [Savannah] That's toilet water!
- What?!
I'm sorry, what?
- You're kidding me! You're kidding! How ma-- You can't!
This is, it's like human cruelty, bro! I'm gonna die! Yeek!
- Whoa! Bro! Bro! Bro! Bro! Bro!
(laughter)
- Oh my gosh! Why would you? This is not,
this is unprecedented. We've never done a video
where we've been pranked this much.
- [Everleigh] Mom, I didn't even flush last time!
- [Collins] Oh my God! Ugh!
- We got a yummy one though.
- Yeah, you guys get some good candy. Oh my gosh.
- [Savannah And Cole] Mmm Mmm.
- That's a good lollipop, blueberry!
- [Savannah] Mmm-hmm.
- And they're enjoying it. It's not even punishment.
They're just enjoying it.
- Sorry you guys got toilet water.
- Yeah I know. I guess it's all,
cause we all get toilet water.
- Oh!
- Gonna put some, some of that in there.
(ding)
- Here we go. The time is now.
We're about to blend it, so,
Everleigh, you wanna press right here?
Press it. - Oh oh! Press it again!
(screams)
- [Devan] What is in here? (screams)
- [Devan] That's good. That's good.
That's good. That's good.
- Alright, there we go. That is disgusting.
- [Cole] Oh! - [Devan] That is very chunky.
- Can you smell the smell now?
- It's a mix between, like, half of me is like,
mmmmm, delicious. [Devan] Oh!
- Which cup? You want that cup. Alright.
Here we go. So this is your cup right here.
- [Savannah] Okay, I'll have the next one
cause I don't want--
- There you go. Alright. Okay.
We're gonna get one for you. I can hold the--
(screams)
- Mine was chunky!
- Devan is gonna get more of the chunks.
- And then I need, I'm just goin'
straight outta this I guess. Alright.
We are about to drink it, and this is gonna be
so disgusting and right after this,
make sure you go watch the video on their channel.
You can click right over there or down in the description.
Go subsribe to them, and go give their video a thumbs up.
If you wanna be featured in our next video,
comment down below, what are some Brailian foods
you would love to see us eat.
The Instagram Keyper of the week is Rosie!
If you wanna be the Instagram Keyper of the week,
all you gotta do is follow me on Instagram,
Turn on my Instagram post notifications,
and like my recent photos.
Make sure you guys to follow all of us on Instagram,
but right now, three, two, one go!
(screams)
Three, two, one, go!
- Oh! The chunks! The chunks are everywhere!
They're everywhere! They're right nasty!
- [Cole] Oh!
(Savannah screams)
(Collins screams)
- Alright guys, love ya'll so much!
[Group] Bye!
- Alright, but I'm gonna take
another bite.
(Everleigh laughs)
- [Cole] Hey, don't touch anything yet Everleigh.
- Okay.
(Everleigh squeals)
(Everleigh squeals) (laughter)
- [Cole] Every time.
(laughter)
- [Cole] Oh, gotcha.
- [Collins] You good and ready? Three...
(panting)
- Oh my Gosh.
- Two. Oh, no! - Dude, no. No!
- One!
- Go! Go! Go! Both of you guys!
Chew! Chew! Chew! Chew it up! Chew it up! Chew it up!
Chew it up! - Oh, I can't. I can't.
I can't I can't!
- [Cole] You got it, Collins!
(screams)
- Whew! Alright!
Come at me bro! Whew!
Aah! Aah! Aah!