(upbeat music)
(brushing)
(beeping)
(laughing)
- [Carla] Collins?
Collins?
- What, I'm just trying to figure
out why would she create an Instagram
account and then not reply to my DM's.
(sighs)
- Oh, you're obsessing over that girl.
Look, Jacob has date tonight, with
the cute boy, don't you?
- You didn't tell me bro what's up?
- I think it's a date, yes I think it is.
Guys we were in improv reading poetry,
and I told a joke about Chaucer
and he laughed and it wasn't funny.
I know it wasn't.
- Oh, crap, I totally forgot, Eddie's
taking me out for dunch.
- Dunch?
- Yeah, it's the meal, you know,
before dinner and between lunch and dinner?
Dunch!
(laughs)
- What?
- [Carla] Screw you guys all!
- It's not a word.
- [Collins] Enjoy your dunch!
(laughs)
- [Jacob] That's so fake!
- It's real.
- [Jacob] He lied to you.
- [Collins] Yeah enjoy your dunch!
- Thank you, bye!
- [Jacob] It's a fake meal!
- [Martin] Oh they are gonna love
this trick, I cant wait for them to see it man!
It is so good, it's so sexy, you know.
And I don't see cards as a sexy thing,
you know mean, like ever.
Never had anybody, well I play cards
with my grandma so it's never been sexy.
But you, you make it sexy!
See, see.
- What?
- Are you paying attention to me right now?
- The eyes thing, yeah, yeah.
- Say sex yeah!
- Sex, yeah, we're gonna kill it.
- Come on man, this is a big step up, man.
You gotta be pumped about this.
- No, I'm super pumped!
- You do not sound super pumped,
you sound average pumped.
- Super pumped!
- There we go!
- Yeah!
- What's on your mind, what's wrong?
- Like this is such an amazing
opportunity and the last thing I want
is for them to last minute, switch
it up and want to put me in that
stereotypical, like creepy, weird, magician thing.
Like that is not me at all, like I don't
want to be put in that box, I want
to be able to do my own thing, but yeah.
- Right, guess who understands?
- You, yeah.
- That's exactly right!
Who am I Collins, who am I?
- You're Martin.
- Martin the man!
- Martin the man.
- That's exactly right, I got your back, man!
Like bra straps, bacne, that's back pimples!
Okay?
Back sweat, got you like the other side of
a t-shirt, not the front, alright?
I got your back Collins!
Okay?
Now we gon' go in there, we gonna play
the game a little bit, smooth.
Hey, hi, then...
(claps)
Hit 'em our game, okay?
Open the game up, hit 'em with the game.
(claps)
No man harder than that!
- Like that?
(loud clap)
- Yeah there we go!
- Hit 'em with the game, hit 'em with the game!
(banging and cheering)
Whoa buddy, no!
Don't do that to my car!
Look, we gon' open some doors alright?
(clapping)
(upbeat pop music)
(cheering)
(laughing)
- We really appreciate you coming
in today Collins, just so we can get
those final little nuances into the script.
You know, just get to the heart of
who Collins Key really is.
- And we got you a great stylist!
- You're gonna die!
- We're very thrilled for this transition,
ain't that right Collins?
- Yeah.
- Collins!
- Yes!
- See you on set!
- See you on set man, thank you guys so much!
- Alright.
- Killed it in there boy!
- That was awesome, that was great!
- Did you see their faces, they were like.
(gasps)
- They were freaking out, that was for sure bro.
- That's how you do it.
- I think like they finally get it,
like what we want to do with it, so, so.
- Yeah, man, and you hit 'em with that magic
and they caught it, they caught it.
- [Jacob] Like if you're straight,
that's cool, but tell me before I pay for dinner.
- Yeah, at least your date didn't
end in the parking lot watching your
boyfriend and his crew land 360 flips.
- Wake up girl, he does that every time,
and he never lands them.
(sighs)
- He asked me to move in.
- Again, what'd you say?
- You guys!
- Carla's moving in with Eddie!
- No, I'm not!
- No, she posted!
- Wait, what?
You have 120 hours, come find me!
- What does that mean?
- I don't know, but it's a clue!
- A keyhole, I'm detecting a theme here.
- I'm gonna post this, someones gotta know what it means!
(pop music)