- What's up everyone?
It's Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday blog.
You probably saw the title and thought to yourself.
Hold up.
Collins Key is the most manly man in the entire world.
I wish I could say that was true
but just like everyone else.
There are some things that freak me out.
So if you're excited to find out what freaks me out.
Let me know by liking this video and let's get started.
Spiders.
I honestly don't know why I don't like spiders.
Besides the fact that they freaking bite people.
People die, they eat bugs.
They have weird creepy legs.
They shoot webs out of their butt, which is just weird.
Scary movies.
Personally I don't like to be in fear.
I don't understand the joy of being in complete
and utter terror for an entire hour and a half.
Let alone paying like 12 bucks to go to a movie theater
and be terrified.
I've never heard someone say,
"Oh man, I'm so happy after I leave a horror movie.
"They're the best.
"If you're ever having a bad day.
"You should watch The Conjuring."
I will never take a girl on a date to a scary movie
because we're gonna be sitting there in the theater.
And she's gonna be like, "Awww cute, a scary movie.
"That way I can lean up against him.
"I can cuddle with him
"and then he'll protect me from all the scariness."
No.
The exact opposite will happen.
I'll be sitting there in my chair,
ready to punch anything that comes close to me.
And if God forbid, you decide to snuggle at this moment
and I feel something start grabbing my arm.
You know what's gonna happen.
I'll be like Chris Brown, Poow.
I don't know why but I'm still sometimes scared of the dark.
Which is really stupid.
Blood.
Okay, that's kind of a funny one
I never really share with a lot of people
but I don't like blood and it's only my blood.
Someone could be laying on the ground right over there
and they're just bleeding out.
I'll be totally calm.
Be like, you what do you need?
You want a juice box?
So I'll be totally cool about it.
If I see so much like a drop of my own blood.
I'll be like, something is seriously wrong.
Taking out the trash at night.
The moment I stepped outside.
It goes into like horror movie mode.
It gets to a point where I'll check the trash cans
because I think there like people hiding in the trash cans.
I feel like I'm in the middle of The Purge.
When I have to take out those trash cans at night.
I'm like, this is completely anarchy.
Anything could happen.
Don't make me hit you with a trash bag.
Also let's combine two of my least favorite things.
Spiders and trash cans.
Because our trash can have spiders.
How awesome is that?
When guys don't wash their hands
when they leave the rest room.
Yes ladies, it happens.
An estimated 80% of men leave the restroom
without washing their hands.
I always wash my hand.
I'll use paper towels to open the door.
Clowns.
Who likes clowns?
I have yet to hear someone say,
"I love clowns.
"I'm a big proponent of clowns."
I think the only people who like clowns are clowns.
Like for real, how do they still have jobs?
Garbage disposals.
I don't know why but from a young age.
I've had this unrational fear
that I'm gonna lose one of my hands
in a freak garbage disposal accident.
And then I find out that you're actually not suppose to
put anything in the garbage disposal.
Like eggs or orange peels or any of that stuff
because apparently it's bad for garbage disposal.
And then I'm like, well what the heck is the point
of a garbage disposal if you can't dispose of stuff?
I don't know.
Forgetting about homework.
And then you realize you have two options.
Option number one,
you can do your best to complete the homework
or option number two.
Which is what I do.
Go on YouTube, start watching tutorial videos
about the project and then slowly
but surely I end up watching fail videos.
I really don't know how it happens.
And last thing on my list is moldy food.
When I was a kid,
our mom would always have jars of apple sauce,
and if she found mold on the top of the apple sauce.
She would just scoop out the parts of mold
and then have us eat the rest.
And then we found out the worst part about mold
is not actually what's on the top.
It's the fact that the mold spores go down
all the way into the food.
And the lower and deeper you get.
The more mold spores there are.
Now whenever I see mold, I'm like,
I'm not gonna eat that.
Nope, don't scrape it off the top.
Don't even try that.
I ain't gonna eat it.
But even if I see food that looks remotely bad.
I'm like, yow this lettuce looks a little bit soggy.
I can't, I can't eat that, I can't.
Alright now, if any of those things
that I've just named off also freak you out.
Let me know by liking this video.
This Saturday, I've got a super special
surprise collab video that's gonna be coming out.
And also I want you guys to comment down below
and let me know.
What freaks you out?
The most creative will get shout out in next week's vlog.
Don't forget of course subscribe to this channel
and I'll see you guys on Saturday.
Peace.
(dramatic music)
I'm always tweeting or texting
or Instagramming or Snapchatting.
I lie about the last part.
My Snapchat game is really weak.