- What's up guys?
It's Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now for today's video I wanted to do something
that I don't normally do and I wanted to let you guys know
10 reasons that I hate waking up in the morning.
So if you guys are not a fan of waking up in the morning
let me know by liking this video
and without further ado, let's just jump right into it.
Let's do it. (laughing)
Number one, alarm clocks.
(alarm blaring)
(rhythmic electronic music)
Good morning.
Number two, being woken up in the middle
of an awesome dream.
- The winner of the one million dollars
and the star of a headline show in Las Vegas is...
Collins Key!
(audience applauding and yelling)
Thank you guys so much.
- Yes, I won!
Wooo, yeah!
This is awkward.
Number three. (smooching)
The absolute worst, bad hair days.
Here we go.
(rubbing palms together)
Hope this goes well.
Over here.
All right, we're off to a great start.
Messy, all good.
And just one more finishing touch, and done.
What the heck happened?
Number four, trying to pick out what you're gonna wear.
I literally have nothing to wear,
I guess I'll just have to wear this.
(rhythmic electronic music)
(laughing)
Number five, missing your alarm.
(alarm blaring)
- [Man] One eternity later.
- Oh my god, I am so late!
Number six, not having time to eat breakfast.
(throat clearing)
My favorite meal of the day.
- [Man] Collins, what are you doing, you've gotta go!
(Devan roars)
- Oh, dude, dude!
(laughing)
Number seven, waking up with a giant beam
of sunlight hitting you right in the eyes.
Never let that happen because oh man, that hurts.
Oh, that really does hurt.
Number eight, when your family tries to have
a full on conversation with you, doesn't work.
(rhythmic electronic music)
- Yo, Collins, check it out!
This super scrubber has like super poke technology.
It has like super, I could swift your arm and your face.
And dude, why are you giving me this face?
See like. (whooping)
- Go away!
(laughing)
Number nine, finding out that people played a prank on you
while you were sleeping.
- [Devan] Oh my gosh, dude.
Someone said I farted on your face.
- What, did you do this to me?
- I didn't do it, no. - Bro.
- [Devan] Why are you looking at me, man?
- And last but not least, number 10.
When you finally have the chance to sleep in,
but everyone decides to be super loud that day.
(pots banging) (yelling)
(alarm blaring)
Guys, be quiet!
(yelling in foreign language)
- You, stop it!
(laughing) (pots banging)
If you guys agree with any of those things
let me know by liking this video.
And also, I'd love for you guys to comment down below
and let me know what are some other things
that you hate about waking up in the morning.
And also share this video with all of your friends.
If you would love for me to do more videos just like this.
Subscribe to the channel to see my new videos
every single Thursday.
I'll see you guys again next week.
Love you, peace.
(fingers snapping)
- [Man] You don't have time to eat right now.
(Devan roars)
(laughing)