- What's up, it's Collins Key
and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
For today's video, I've taken a whole bunch of DIYs
and hacks from Pinterest and BuzzFeed and today,
we're going to be putting them to the test together
to see if they actually do what they're supposed to do,
or if they even work.
Honestly,
I'm expecting quite a few of these to fail pretty miserably.
If you want me to do even more DIY videos
like this in the future, let me know by liking this video.
If this video gets enough thumbs up,
then I will do even more videos just like this.
Also, I want to let you guys know
I'm doing a giveaway this month.
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So if you wanna win that, let me know by liking this video.
Comment down below what's your favorite video
that I've ever posted on this channel
and of course, you must be subscribed to my channel.
But right now, without any further ado, let's jump in.
Let's try these DIYs and hacks.
For this first one, we are going to be trying
to create a DIY Lava Lamp.
I really don't know how we're gonna do this
because I don't have any actual lava,
and this thing did not include lava, so...
Yeah, we're just gonna use what we have.
So basically we've got a glass jar here
that kinda resembles a lava lamp.
We have oil, we have salt,
and last but not least, if you wanna be extra special,
you can also use some food coloring.
You guys know me on this channel
with these kind of ingredients.
Yeah, we don't need that.
So all you're gonna need for this
is just these basic ingredients.
I actually need that.
For step number one, all you need to do...(chuckles)
Food coloring's back!
Is just take the jar and fill it up
with a whole bunch of water
and I guess I will be using food coloring for this.
Ow!
(gloves snapping and clapping)
Le's do it!
These are, by far, the most attractive looking gloves
you can ever wear.
Put a couple drops in there.
Next, we'll go with red.
Looks like blood, this is actually kinda creepy.
We got some blue next.
I think I might actually be puttin' too much
of the dye in there, but hey we're goin' for it.
Well I think I messed up already
because I think I put way too much dye in there. (chuckling)
Now it's just all black.
Hey, you live and you learn.
I'm going to be leaving the gloves on
for the remainder of this DIY because I cannot actually
remove them from my hands.
(gloves snap) Ow!
Next you wanna take the oil.
Trying to open this with gloves on.
Aw, man.
Nah.
Once you perfectly open the top of it just like this,
you're going to add the oil to the bottle.
(liquid trickling)
Hmm.
Now that you have the oil
and just the black mass of liquid in here,
you're gonna be taking the salt and apparently the salt
is what really makes this DIY come to life.
Cannot get anything off with these gloves on.
This is like nearly impossible.
There we go.
So apparently the salt will actually drag the oil
to the bottom of this, and then shoot it back up to the top.
I don't know how it really works, apparently science.
Huh.
Let's see if I can kick start the whole thing.
(liquid shaking)
No, it's basically just oil and water
with just a layer of salt on the bottom.
For this, I'm going to be making a phone case
out of a balloon.
(balloon farting)
First, you need to inflate the balloon.
Get the balloon.
Ow.
I just whipped my lip.
Next, you're gonna just take the phone like this
and put it on top and then deflate the balloon.
Release it on three, two--
or just now, okay.
(balloon farts)
Whoa!
What just happened?!
(cackling)
Can't really like do too much!
Like this weak little thing flappin' off but I mean hey,
if you're into funky different phone cases, this is for you.
So yeah I guess this life hack, we'll give it a win.
We'll give it a tentative win.
I'm super excited for this one,
because I'm going to be trying to create rainbow bagels.
The only part I'm not excited about
is the fact that I have to wear
these gloves again.
Glove number one.
Glove number two.
Ready to go.
So first is my personal favorite, this stuff.
(label tearing)
There we go.
That one's not goin' this time.
(popping) Oh jeez, it got me again!
Next you're gonna be coloring
each one of these individually.
- [French Voice] One eternity later.
(dinging)
- I just mixed up all the dough and now the next step
is you're gonna take them all out,
place them down flat like a pancake,
and then stack them one on top of the other.
Alright, we'll start with the green one here.
Next is the orange.
After that, we'll do the purple.
Last but not least, a touch of pink.
Cut the dough and then you're just gonna kinda roll it
and kind of twist it like this.
You're gonna form it into a bagel.
This is the most lopsided whack-lookin' bagel.
Kinda failed.
Next you're gonna put these in the oven
and just find out what happens.
- [French Voice] A few moments later.
- You know, these actually turned out way better
than I expected.
Oh, we lost a bit of the bagel!
This actually looks pretty awesome,
like with all the stuff on the inside.
Yeah, I guess that one, it's a win.
This one, using nothing more than vitamins
and a little bit of water, we're gonna try to create
glow-in-the-dark liquid.
I have no idea if this is gonna work
and I don't even know what you would do
with glow-in-the-dark liquid anyways,
but ey we're gonna try to make it.
You're gonna wanna take, I would say, three of the tablets.
It should be perfect.
I saw online, they suggest that you crush it
with a spoon inside a bowl.
Personally, I don't think that's gonna be enough.
So I have another idea.
Alright, here we go.
Gonna use this.
Take the three tablets.
Dump them out here,
and I need one more thing.
A sledgehammer.
Alright guys, here we go.
This is how you crush the tablets.
We go three,
two,
(beeping and crashing)
Don't think I'm crazy?
No, I'm not gonna use a real sledgehammer.
We are gonna be using the baby sledgehammer.
(ding)
There we go.
So Collins, what'd you do today?
This.
Next, we're just gonna take the finely crushed B12 vitamin
and put it inside the bowl and add water.
(spoon scraping)
Gonna mix it up.
Oh God, this is boring.
Now it's time to find out whether or not this stuff
will really glow in the dark.
Now I can't tell if it's actually glowing
or if it's just the black light making it appear
as though it's glowing, but I'm feeling nice.
So I'm gonna give this one the benefit of the doubt.
This one gets a win.
The final one, we are going full spy mode.
I'm gonna be showing you guys how to turn your phone
into a blacklight.
Hopefully.
Literally, all you need to do is just tape...
But that catch though!
And sharp, the catch again!
And the catch again!
I'm just catching things left and right.
I can throw as many times I,
(gasping) I can literally throw as many times
as I want and catch it!
I got way too excited.
All you need is just tape and Sharpie markers.
Let's see if I can get it one more time.
(buzzing)
We can cut that part out, right guys?
This is really easy.
Just take the tape, place it directly over the flash.
Then you're just gonna color it in
with a blue Sharpie marker like this.
Cover the flash again with tape
and then repeat it again the blue Sharpie marker.
This might actually work.
Now for the last one, cover it up again,
and using the purple Sharpie, do one more circle over it.
And now it's time to see if we've really
created a blacklight or not.
The only issue is I don't have anything to actually
test the blacklight on, but from what I can tell,
this thing does not look like a blacklight at all.
Even when I turned on the blacklight,
it was very different looks for each one of these.
So this one is clearly a fail.
If you want me to do another video
where I test life hacks and DIYs,
let me know by liking this video and comment down below.
What's one life hack you've seen
that you really wanna see tested?
I'm posting two videos a week,
so make sure you guys subscribe to this channel
and have the notifications turned on.
That way, you guys know immediately
whenever I upload a new video.
I'll see you guys again very soon.
Bye. (snap)