- What's up, it's Collins Key,
and welcome to the Thursday vlog
and also happy St. Patrick's Day!
Turn up, we're gonna have a great time today,
and to join me, I have a very special guest.
All the way from Ireland,
I have captured a little leprechaun,
his name is Devan, yeah.
(laughing)
- I wasn't sure, you just said his name was Devan,
I was like "That's not a hype intro."
- It's Devan!
- Yeah, what's up!
- Welcome, my little leprechaun buddy.
For today's video, in honor of St. Patrick's Day,
we are going to be doing our very own
St. Patrick's Day challenge, and we really want to test
our knowledge, go head to head right now
and see who knows more, (laughing)
- I know nothing.
- Yeah, I really don't know that much
about St. Patrick's day.
So we're gonna see how this goes,
and basically how it's gonna go
is we have a third party (coughing) my dad
and he went up and he looked up
a whole bunch of different St. Patrick's Day
trivia and questions and he's gonna be reading them off
and whoever answers it first correctly,
that person is awarded one point
and the loser has to do a punishment
and we have our little punishment bucket right here
with these little scrolls inside,
which is kind of cool.
So you have to pick one out at random
and you have to do whatever is on the scroll.
I also want to let you guys know
that I'm doing a huge giveaway on my channel right now.
I'm giving away an iPhone 6S, an Instax camera,
so all you gotta do if you want to enter in
to this giveaway, just let us know by liking this video,
comment down below, what is your favorite video
that I've ever posted, and also you must be subscribed
to this channel and I'm taking into account
my Instagram and my Twitter.
So make sure you guys are following me on Instagram,
have my notifications turned on, be active, liking,
commenting, same thing with Twitter, follow me on there,
have my notifications on.
Also guys go follow Devan,
cause he puts up with a lot for being in these videos
so go show him some love on Instagram and on Twitter,
but without any further ado, what do you guys say,
let's jump right in to the St. Patrick's Day Challenge.
- [Dad] Great, first question:
Do leprechauns get angry,
(incoherent laughing)
- He said leprechauns, we got leprechauns.
Do they get what, do they get what?
I'm crying, do leprechauns get what?
- Do it again.
- No no, what's the questions?
- [Dad] Do leprechauns get angry
when you make fun of their height?
- [Both] Yes.
No.
- I don't know. - They get happy.
- I've never met a leprechaun.
- A little bit?
- I don't know.
(laughing)
- [Dad] It's actually only a little bit.
- That's so stupid.
So I just got a point now, so Devan,
you have to remove from the leprechaun pail of not-gold.
Just get something out of there and let's see what it is.
- Eat as many gold coins as you can in one minute.
- Three, two, one, go!
(country music)
- Ow.
- Ow? What hurt?
Are you okay?
What just happened?
Dude, you're running out, man, what are you doing?
He's so ticklish.
It's so gross.
- [Dad] What is a shillelagh?
Is it like a,
- [Dad] A:
- Oh, okay.
- [Dad] There's four choices.
- I know, what are they?
- [Dad] A: A big stick.
B: A four leaf clover.
C: A pot belly pig.
D: A mode of transportation.
- I think it's a big stick.
- I think it's D.
- Final answer, big stick.
Is it?
- It's a big stick?
- I was totally joking.
Pick out your punishment, dude.
- Alright.
Get pinched in the cheeks, aw.
- By me.
(record scratching) (laughing)
Bro, chill!
Oh my god, you were way too ready for that.
Oh my god, dude.
There was no hesitation.
You saw that, you were like "This can only mean one thing!"
Alright, here we go.
Boop, boop, and then,
alright, and then stand up, you asked for it, bro.
- I did not ask.
- You did, you literally stood up
and put it right in my face dude.
- If you want to do it, I mean go for it.
- Now you're making this really awkward, bro.
I don't necessarily,
- I don't either, man, it's up to you.
- This is so bad.
We're flipping a chocolate coin to find out
whether or not I'm gonna pinch his butt.
- That's the easy way out. - What do you want?
- That's the easy way out.
- Heads or tails, which one's your butt, heads or tails?
- Tails. - Tails is butt, of course.
Flip it.
Heads, so I don't have to pinch your butt, congratulations.
- Oh thank goodness.
- Yep, okay, that was close.
Alright, so let's go, next question.
- [Dad] The official emblem of Ireland is?
There's four choices.
(laughing)
A: The shamrock.
B: The harp.
C: The Barley Stone.
D: The leprechaun.
- The lepre, no, no, stop, I know it's not, sorry.
- The shamrock.
- No it's not, it's the barley, the sharley, the darley.
- I'm going with A, whatever A was.
- C, what C, I'm going with answer number C.
- [Dad] A is the shamrock.
- Yes. - [Dad] Wrong.
- What? - What?
- C is the barley stone.
- [Woman] Blarney. - [Dad] Blarney.
(laughing)
- Blarney. - [Dad] The Blarney stone.
Wrong.
- Oh, what was it, was it the leprechaun?
- [Dad] It's between the leprechaun and the harp.
- It's gotta be the harp, it's the harp,
it's gotta be the harp.
Leprechaun's just kind of weird.
- It's gotta be the harp, it is not the expected answer.
- What is it?
- [Dad] It's the harp.
- Whatever this is, we'll do it together.
We'll both take the punishment
cause we didn't know what it was.
Peel a potato as fast as possible.
So that was the initial punishment.
But since we're gonna be doing this,
we're gonna take the challenge up to another level
so what's gonna happen,
we each have our own peelers right here
- Woah, woah, woah.
- Yours is smaller. - Oh yeah, nevermind.
- I'm trying to give you somewhat of an advantage here.
Here's what's gonna happen, we have to peel our potatoes
as fast as possible, whoever peels the full potato first,
that person wins and the loser has to take a bite
out of their fully peeled potato.
Begin.
- I feel like I could cut my fingers off.
(accelerated audio)
- You're on the table, that's very smart,
you're very intelligent, Devan, the way you did that.
- Oh thank you.
- Oh three, two. - No no no no.
- Peeled, I'm done, yes!
- No, I had like two little bits!
I had like two little bits left!
- Alright, here we go, take a bite of my potato.
(mumbling)
- What?
Take a bite out of it, don't swallow the whole thing.
- It was stuck, it was stuck in my teeth,
I have to dental floss after this.
It doesn't taste good. - No, it's a raw potato, dude.
- Wait, you didn't say I have to chew it.
That didn't work.
- [Dad] When is an Irish potato not an Irish potato?
- When it's in Devan's mouth. - When it's a seed.
- When it's not in Ireland.
- Oh, when it's an American potato.
- When it's a french fry.
(laughing)
Is that right?
That is so stupid.
- Eat an entire bowl of lucky charms in under one minute.
No.
- And you know what Devan, this a matter of fate
that you did get this one
because you're gonna have to eat it
out of the bowl that you spit all your,
- We don't have another bowl? - No.
- We don't have another bowl? - This is the only bowl.
- You're telling me we have only one bowl.
- I am telling you we have only one bowl.
- In our entire house? - This is it,
this the only bowl in the neighborhood,
quite even possibly in the town.
Looks like you're gonna have to make do
with what could be turd or chocolate, you never know.
We've got Lucky Charms right here.
I am feeling lucky.
(laughing)
- You are apparently lucky.
This is how I do my cereal.
- Did you see like, what the heck?
You act like you've never poured a bowl of cereal before.
You have one minute to eat this whole thing.
- Oh I have, the whole thing?
- Did you not read it?
- I kind of glossed over it when I saw I had to eat
my own chocolate that I already spit out.
- Okay, here we go, go.
His mustache has gotten,
the mustache is like right in his mouth.
He's literally eating his mustache, oh my god.
Bro, I don't want to be close to you, take your mustache,
(screaming)
Take it, dude, my god bro, no, stop it!
- I just wanted a hug, what the heck?
Oh my god.
No hug?
- No, no no!
- [Dad] This is a question.
- Okay. (laughing)
As opposed to an answer?
- That is shocking.
- Can't believe it.
- [Dad] Why can't you borrow money from a leprechaun?
- Because they got none.
Because they're too small.
- Because they're a little broke.
Because they're a little short at the moment.
- They're short?
Alright, drink green water till your tongue is green.
- What?
Oh, we have food coloring.
- No.
No, it's gonna turn my teeth green.
- I'll do this with you, I'll do this with you.
Whoever gets their tongue to turn green first
doesn't have to drink the entire thing, go.
- What?
(inquisitive grunting)
(laughing)
(insistent grunting)
- Dude, literally,
you just took like the most highly concentrated
food coloring in the world and put it directly
on your tongue.
It's pretty messed up, bro.
- The whole thing.
Drink some more.
- Woah, hey.
- You gotta drink the whole thing, bro.
- I know. - I ain't playing around.
Obviously.
Oh, what?
That's in my freaking eye.
- No!
Why? I'm freezing!
- No, what, you had to drink it, you can't do that,
you had to drink it.
- Fine, fine.
- What? - I drank it all.
- That wasn't,
- Chill, bro.
Alright, next question, let's do it,
let's wrap this thing up.
- [Dad] What do you call a fake stone in Ireland?
- Shamrock.
(cheering)
Yes, I got one!
Yes!
Choose it!
- It says speak in an Irish accent.
- Okay, that's a punishment, really?
- I guess.
- I won one so he would have to do that?
- [Dad] Wait, here's one.
May the dust of your carriage wheels
blind the eyes of your foes.
- I like that one.
Eat all my lucky charms there boy.
- It's like a pirate.
(laughing)
- May the dust of your,
- It's a pirate.
- An Irish pirate.
May the dust of your carriage
kick them in the enemy of your eyes.
The eyes of the enemy.
- That's not even right.
- Make up your flaming mind.
Make up your flamer.
May I keep flaming till the day I die.
- What's this?
- It's the Irish, the luck of the Irish.
It's my shamrock.
It's my bloody shamrock necklace.
Look at your shamrock hat, you shamrock fool.
- This isn't a punishment, this is awesome.
Sorry, I got a little bit too lit there, boy.
- Well that wasn't a punishment.