- Go!
- I just ate a cricket.
Aah, I ate that!
(bleep)
- What's up! It's Collins Key,
and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now, for today's video,
if you guys can't tell by the empty chair right here
I need someone to help me out,
so everyone please welcome my friend, Mel Joy.
(snaps) Hey! Whoa! - Hey!
- Now for today's video,
we are going to be taste-testing foreign candy.
But we wanted to turn this into more of a challenge.
So basically, we had a third party go out there
and buy a whole bunch of candy.
My dad, he did that.
Shout out to my dad, love you.
So yeah, he went out and he bought a whole bunch
of different candy and we're gonna close our eyes,
he's gonna give us the candy,
we're gonna taste, try to figure out what it is.
Whoever guesses what it is first,
that person wins that round.
And the loser of that round gets one tooth knocked out.
Let me explain this.
You guys know when you were kids and your parents would
always tell you that if you eat too much candy,
your teeth will fall out?
Well that's what's gonna be happening today.
So we got this stuff from the costume store.
And so it makes it look like
you have no teeth in your mouth.
For every candy you get wrong,
you have to black out one tooth.
And so whoever loses the most amount
and gets all their teeth blacked out,
that person loses the challenge.
We also did a video over on Mel's channel
if you guys wanna check it out after this one.
We did truth or dare, got pretty crazy.
So yeah go check it out.
Also subscribe to her channel.
- Thank you. - She's pretty awesome.
Also wanna let you guys know I'm doing a giveaway
on my channel right now.
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So if you guys wanna win that,
let me know by liking this video.
Comment down below what's your favorite video
that I've ever posted.
And of course, you must be subscribed to this channel.
Without any further adieu, let's knock out some teeth
and let's try some candy!
- [Guest] Hands out, like you're gonna grab something.
Yep, there you go.
- Oh boy.
- Wait, what? I'm like really scared.
- Three, two, one.
- Where's my mouth?
(Collins shouts)
- It's Pop Rocks.
Oh my god I love this.
(Collins gags)
- I love the noise.
(candy popping)
- You win the first round.
So I have to black a tooth.
I don't like this challenge.
Okay. Easy, breezy, beautiful Cover Girl.
Oh my gosh, here we go.
- Let's try this out.
- Tooth number one is gone!
'Cause I lost the first round.
- [Guest] This is going to be something
you squeeze into your mouth,
and you have to squeeze it as much as possible.
Set.
- As much as possible? - Oh God.
Alright. Good luck.
[Guest Voiceover] One, two, three, go!
- It's gonna kill me.
- It's not coming out at all!
- It's like toothpaste.
Oh, I don't like this.
- I can't get it out of this thing at all.
- It kinda tastes like skunk.
- I can't even get it out!
- I don't like it!
- Okay.
- Or is it barbecue.. bacon.
Bacon! Bacon paste!
(clapping and laughing)
Yes!
- I couldn't get it out!
- (laughs)
- I guess another tooth is gone.
(hair dryer blowing)
- Alright, you got another tooth gone.
This is not fun.
Alright next candy, let's do it.
[Collins] I have to win this one.
For real. - [Guest] Go!
- Okay.
- It is a...
I know this. I know this.
I know this.
- I don't like it.
- Laffy Taffy. (buzzer)
- I don't like it, I don't like it.
- It's like ginger.
Is it ginger? (buzzer)
Is it anything ginger because it's a little bit spicy.
- It's getting spicier as I chew it.
- Yeah, it really is.
Is it like Hot Toffee or something?
(ding) - Oh yeah!
- Oh no, I have to do it now?
- I'm sorry, but now it's your turn.
(hair dryer blowing)
- I'm gonna do a front one.
- You look great. - Oh thank you!
- I think it's actually,
honestly -- - New look? New look.
- Yeah - Yeah.
- I think it's part of
the everyday make-up routine from now on.
- I think so.
- Yeah.
[Guest] Put it in your hand,
and then it has to go directly into your mouth.
[Mel] Okay.
[Guest] K? - [Mel] Okay.
[Guest] Hold on one second.
- I'm scared.
- [Guest] Hold on.
- What?
- [Guest] Two... - I can't even feel it.
It's like soft. [Guest] Three, go!
- What?
Is this larvae?
Did you give me larvae?
- Is it bugs?
Oh my God it's definitely a bug.
- It's definitely...
- Yeah no, it's totally a bug
What is it?
- Oh my God. - I can feel the little legs.
I can feel the little legs on it.
You swallowed it?
- Yes! (laughing)
- Oh my gosh.
Is it larvae?
- Cricket! I just ate a cricket.
Is it a real cricket?
Aah, I ate that.
No!
That's so gross.
- I just found a leg in my tooth.
- [Guest] Okay, who lost?
- I lost. I did lose.
(hair dryer blowing)
- [Guest] You gotta grip this with your other hand, go.
- Oh I have to dip it?
- Oh is it dentist flavored?
Is it dentist office flavored?
Oh bad idea.
- What'd you do?
Did you just put it all in your mouth?
- Yeah.
(coughs)
- I inhaled the powder.
- I'm gonna try to get a lot in my mouth
so I can figure it out.
- What if we just pour in the mouth?
It's like soda-y. Like bubbly.
- Cherry, it's cherry, it's gotta be cherry.
Did I get it right? - Oh oh! Cherry coke?
- Is it cherry? - Cherry coke?
(buzzer)
- Did we get it right? - [Guest] Nope.
- What? Okay.
- I don't really know like what they would mix
with licorice to taste good.
- Sour Patch Kids!
(buzzer) - [Guest] Nope.
- Sweet tarts! (buzzer)
- [Guest] Nope. - Dangit.
- [Guest] Sherbet Fountain.
- Sherbet Fountain? - Sherbet Fountain?
- I've never even heard of Sherbet Fountain.
- Is that the thing?
- Just so you guys know, this happened.
- [Mel] Yeah.
- And now I think since we both lost,
what do you say we both get a tooth?
(hair dryer blowing)
- [Guest] Collins gets his first.
- [Collins] Noooo!
Noooo!
- I'm scared.
I'm scared.
- [Guest] Three, two-- - I'm scared
- Nooo!
(crunching)
- Oh! I like it!
Actually, I don't know if I like this.
- These are actually pretty good.
I like these the most.
- I kind of feel like these are shaped like a--
- It's so familiar.
- Green tea.
(ding)
- Aw it's so cute, look at that.
You're too good at this, it's not fair.
Alright guys my lips are officially dried out
from the blow drying but now I'm missing the bottom tooth.
- [Guest] Guess the flavor of what it is
You can open your eyes, go.
- It's like a little soda can.
- Soda.
- Sprite? Is it Sprite?
(ding)
Yeah! Did I get it right? Yes!
No!
(hair dryer blowing)
- [Guest] You have to guess flavor. Set, open your eyes
Go!
- It's a speed game! This is --
I can't open it.
- Are there different flavors?
- Toxic Waste?
- Yeah.
- If you kill us...
- Oh my god, it's so sour.
- Are these like Warheads or something?
- I'm scared.
- Oh, it's so sour.
- Oh, I think I got lemon.
Lemon is the most sourest.
Have to give me something.
Oh my God.
- [Guest] Eat another one.
- I have to eat another one?
- Oh, this green one's gonna be... I know it's bad news.
(chokes)
- This is like the Warhead challenge.
We're totally doing a Warhead challenge right now.
- Another green one.
I'm literally crying right now.
I don't know, is it lemon?
Why did you do sour apple first?
- [Guest] Do another one.
- I just wanna end with black cherry.
I think black cherry, I win, right?
- I've got four in my mouth now.
- Yeah, me too.
That's it, I'm done. Abort.
- That was painful.
- Ow! My tongue really hurts.
So that one was kinda cruel,
neither of us are gonna have to put anything black
on our mouth cause that was a form of punishment.
- I like that.
- [Guest] You have to guess the flavor.
- Cheers? No cheers, you're going for it. Cheers?
- There was no tink, though. There's no tink.
- There!
- There we go, hey!
- Oh, it smells terrible.
- Uh. Hmm-mm.
It just gets worse the more you keep drinking it.
- Mm. It's horrible.
- Wait, are your eyes closed?
- Yeah!
- Okay, just... (laughs)
- [Guest] Keep drinking!
- Is it boar puckey?
Cause that's what it tastes like.
- No, it's just getting worse, it's getting worse.
- I don't like it, I don't like it.
- It honestly tastes like
rotten egg when you first drink it.
And then the aftertaste is like marshmallow.
Sweet corn.
- Is it sweet corn?
- [Guest] Yes!
- No! It's so gross!
- I would not drink this!
- This is disgusting!
- It looks like--
You all know what it looks like.
(hair dryer)
- Alright guys, I am now missing, I think, all my top teeth.
- So you're about to lose.
- So yeah, it's kinda like the last round right here.
We'll do the finale.
- Yep, the finale. Let's do it.
- Winner takes all.
- [Guest] Guessing flavor.
Three, two, you can open your eyes if you want to, go!
- Okay.
It's very chemical.
- Licorice?
- No.
- Socks. Mm-mm, no, no, no.
- It's very chemical.
It's so chemical.
- Like Windex? It tastes like cleaner.
- Mm-hmm. It tastes like soap.
- It's detergent.
- [Guest] No.
- Aah, this is terrible.
Horrible.
This isn't even candy.
- Don't eat this for fun, please.
I'm convinced it's Clorox.
- I can't... What is it?
- Clove!
- What's clove?
- Clove! (laughs)
- What is clove?
- [Guest] It says it'll make your mouth numb though.
- Oh, numb, numb.
It's working, I'm gonna be honest.
- It low-key is.
Before you guys go any further,
make sure you guys go watch the video
that is on her channel.
We even put a link right up over there.
I'm also going to put a link down in the description.
So go check out that video.
If you're one of my people, go support it,
give it a like, leave a comment on her video.
- Thank you.
- I love you guys so much.
I will see you all again next week.
You know what Mel,
you get to snap and make me disappear right now.
- Alright, I'm excited. Ready?
(snaps)
Bye guys! (laughs)