(exciting music)
- Yo, what's up, guys?
This Collins Key.
I'm doing a meetup right now.
I've got some friends who wanna say hi!
(cheering)
Do you guys want to see some magic?
- We're at the Santa Monica Promenade.
Why are we here, Collins?
- Well, we are here, Sam, because we're doing this thing,
a little meetup here.
- [Sam] Our boy Collins is gonna have a magic show.
- [Collins] Magic.
- Well, let's go to it!
(exciting music)
- [Crowd] No way!
- You guys wanna try one more right now?
(cheering)
And I need one person to help me out for this.
- Let's hear it for her, everyone.
C'mon, let's hear it for her.
(cheering)
I want you to just touch any card you want.
(driving electronic music)
Show it to everyone, make sure everyone can see it.
If I can have you sign it.
Perfect, just like that.
Alright, let me see it.
Question mark, alright.
So we're gonna take this card,
and I want you to bite down on the card,
Is that alright?
Okay, alright, this will be my card.
You have the king of diamonds.
I'm gonna sign it.
This is where it's gonna get kinda wild.
Ready for this?
(suspenseful percussive music)
Your sign, ace.
- [Crowd] No way!
- So that means if I have now this ace of hearts,
you've got one card.
I want you to, yeah, take a look at it
and show it to everyone.
Is that it?
(cheering)
Thank you so much for helping me out.
Really quick, what was your name by the way?
- Uh, the card.
- What?
Wait a second, wait.
She just left me like, an @ handle.
It says like, UnlockAll.
- Let me see.
Do you know what that means?
It says unlock all doors.
I don't know.
Is that?
(slow percussive music)