hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so if
you guys follow me on snapchat which if
you don't you definitely should you see
that I posted a few days ago about
redoing my entire camera setup I
actually did snap that I wasn't gonna be
posting at all this week because I'm in
the middle of redoing everything from
lighting camera lenses graphics and
everything on this channel I am so
excited now they have so many cool
things and ideas and concepts in the
works and you guys will be seeing them
very very soon but people were like oh
just film James we don't care and I know
you guys are always so supportive which
means the world to me
so you know I set my booty down and
we're gonna film today so if you check
your calendar it is officially August
which is absolutely horrifying because
summer is coming to a screeching halt
and you know it comes at the end of
summer school as many of you guys know I
did graduate early and I don't plan on
attending college so thank the Lord and
heaven above I will not be attending
school this year but I know so many of
you will and I myself did for 17 very
very long years so for today's to do I
sat down and we're gonna film a
back-to-school quick and easy makeup
tutorial
almost all the products I have in front
of me today are drugstore for those of
you who are on a budget I feel you girl
makeup can be super expensive when I was
in school four years ago lord knows I
did not have 42 dollars spent on a new
foundation that was going towards a new
textbook school is also super
time-consuming as well I know I had so
many nights staying up until 4:00 or
5:00 a.m. editing videos they're working
on a test or a paper or a project that I
had to wake up an hour later and get to
school so this video is also gonna be a
little bit of a challenge for anywhere
like I want to do this makeup look as
quickly as I possibly can I was gonna
limit myself to ten minutes but knowing
me let's be real instead of take a
little bit longer so I'm just gonna do
this pretty pretty quickly this is gonna
be a super easy light makeup routine
that you guys can use when you were
waking up Li ten minutes before your bus
gets here because we've all had those
days with all that being said good
morning sisters I hope you guys enjoy
your day in hell I mean school today and
without further ado let's get started on
this super easy everyday school makeup
routine
[Music]
all right sir I already went ahead and
prep my scan it by a showering of course
in the morning don't want to be stinky
for school and then I probably face
using my favorite moisturizer for
foundation today I'm gonna use the brand
new covergirl healthy elixir foundation
and I'm gonna mix a shade 725 and 745
then of course I'm just gonna bounce
this into my skin at using my damp
Beauty Blender all that needs to not
happen so this foundation is definitely
a light to medium coverage foundation it
is definitely not full coverage glam
which is great though we definitely
don't need to be rocking a full coverage
HD foundation stick to high school it's
really not that serious we don't have
anybody to impress so don't worry about
it you can see my face today I'm using
the Maybelline fit me concealer in the
shade light if there's one thing that we
do definitely wanna focus on it is
probably gonna be concealer just make
sure we really hide any blemishes or
under-eye bags because I'm like I said
we are definitely gonna be a very very
late working on papers and projects and
not getting very much sleep in school
I've been there before so let's do
everything we can to fix it and once
again just having my Beauty Blender and
I'm gonna pounce it into place school
could definitely be super super
stressful as well and we have all woken
up with symbols before and stress
breakout so if you do get one never fear
don't worry just grab your favorite
concealer just put it over your pimple
just destroy this bit and then instead
of using a Beauty Blender I'm actually
gonna grab a very really light fluffy
brush and instead of a pouncing aunt I'm
just going to lightly tap over the area
and just blend out those edges by doing
this we're keeping the concealer exactly
where you want it to be right over the
pimple obviously so it's hidden and then
just blending out those edges so it
looks natural because that my face in
place today are gonna be using the Cody
or some powder you guys know I
definitely have a very very interesting
history with this one but it wasn't
oldie but a goodie for the longest time
so I'm gonna try her again today
hopefully she won't do be dirty I'm just
gonna grab a little bit of powder really
lightly on my r-13 brush from morphe and
just set my under eyes in place that
understood my ar0 brush once again for
more free to set the rest my face
I know Murphy's obviously not a
drugstore brand that is sold in like CVS
or Walgreens or anything but their
products are super super cheap compared
to a lot of their competitors and they
are very very good as well and you guys
know you can use coach James for 10% off
all their products to highlight and
bronze today I've got to go to my NYX
highlight and contour palette and my
morphe m 5 on 9 brush and I'm dip into
this shade right up in here and I'm just
going to lightly
to conquer my face because let's be real
we definitely know how time to do both
I'm next ender grab the same exact
Murphy I'm a 509 brush that I used for
the contour and I'm gonna dip into the
elf blush palette and i'm gonna use this
shade right up in this corner right here
for just a little bit of orange pop of
color to the face just add a little bit
of life back in so next we're gonna
really quickly plate the brows today and
for this I'm actually gonna using a not
drugstore product and I'm gonna be using
the benefit persistent eyebrow pencil in
the shade number three but I am using
this for a very very good reason so if
you guys saw me talking about on
Instagram a few days ago I had a very
very exciting announcement that I posted
about and that is that I am teaming up
with Benefit Cosmetics well my favorite
brands in the entire world to work on a
very very new and exciting project that
I am literally so pumped for I haven't
actually talked to this on youtube yet
though so hello hi get ready because I'm
gonna be one of your four influencer
coaches for the benefit brow search
benefit is basically hosting a
competition to find that they're a brand
new bras now so basically once all the
entries get narrowed down 20 people are
gonna win a trip to Lake Tahoe here in
California where you guys are gonna be
basically going to a brow a boot camp
and all 20 contestants will be split
between the four judges so five of you
guys will be on hashtag team sisters and
of course we're going to it because you
guys know sister James never loses a
good at competition I love my escape
rooms I love competing in general so we
definitely have a very very solid chance
I also forgot to mention as well it's
really not that important though but the
grand prize winner will be winning only
$50,000 if you're interested in the
benefit bro search and you want to be on
hashtag team sisters make sure to check
the description box down below because
I'll put a link where you can check out
the full information and details on how
to enter
good luck alright so I just went ahead
and I quickly said my other brow off
camera we're already getting close to
10-minute so I definitely to speed this
up a little bit because we're gonna be
late for first period I'm not gonna do
any eyeshadow for this look today let's
be real if we're getting up 10 minutes
before the bus gets here the last thing
we have time to do is a freaking smoky
eye are some like halo eye or some type
of fancier look so I'm gonna go to the
wet and wild liquid liner though and
just do a quick little line I'm keeping
this liner super super thin and hugging
the lash line very very tightly I'm not
gonna be doing a dramatic wing today and
I'm also not gonna be wearing falsies
this is just gonna help
more volume two lattes when it comes to
adding mascara just a super super simple
then easy line if you want to be brave
and do a wing
be my guest girl play that wing get
ready to cut those [ __ ] from the
other end of the biology room at Bowl
view in fourth period we've all been
there we're definitely not to be messing
with falsies today nobody has time for
glue and lashes in the morning not me
I'll tell you that right now so I'm
gonna be focusing a little bit more on
my lashes to prep them for mascara I'm
just gonna curl them quickly then for
mascara today I'm gonna be using the new
L'Oreal voluminous last paradise you
guys know I am a ride-or-die for the
benefit roller lash
but that $31 is another textbook so
we're gonna have to go chug source today
oh my god I actually really like how
this mascara applies for highlighter
today I'm gonna use the brand new Wet n
Wild mega glow in the shade golden
flower crown out of this entire makeup
routine I feel like highlighters by far
the most important part of it not only
will you look like a beautiful glazed
donut walking through the halls but also
when your teacher comes up to and it's
like um do you have last night's
homework and you know damn well you were
up until four am watching makeup
tutorials you can be like BAM and she'll
be so shocked and blinded that she won't
even remember her question
never underestimate the power of a good
glow sisters and then last but not least
for the lipid doodoo dress today I'm
gonna go to these soft matte lip cream
from NYX in the shade London my best
friend sister Laura swears they're these
she wears them every single day all day
long and I love them as well so
definitely a very very easy lipstick to
carry on the go to school and last but
finally not least to set our face in
place there are eight hours of Hell
sorry again I mean school I'm gonna grab
my morphe prep and set setting spray and
I'm just going to post my entire face
alright guys so this is the super easy
and quick back-to-school glam makeup
tutorial all completed let's go ahead
and actually stop the timer and we are
at 12 minutes and 52 seconds oh not bad
at all actually definitely not the 10
minutes I was anticipating for those two
minutes in 52 seconds can definitely
make a huge difference in the morning
but also not bad at all for those of you
who are going back to school I hope you
are super super excited and definitely
may comment down below tell me what your
favorite school subject is minor is
actually math I love math so much and I
actually miss it all the time so yeah
let me know what yours is if you guys
enjoy this video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you haven't
ready I post three videos a week on
Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays and I'd
love to have you join the sisterhood if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
the scenes links up is James Charles
that extra ass after Charles this week's
out it goes to sister Taylor thank you
so much girl for always falling and
supporting you know I love you so much
if you would like to be at next week's
sister shout out make sure to always
read to my video links and they go live
on Twitter all right sisters thank you
so much for watching have you back to
school season I will see you it next
week
[Music]