hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel oh my
god you guys I have never been more
excited to sit down into a video that I
am for today I have not been in this
actual studio in over three weeks now
and it feels so crazy those you guys who
do not know I just launched my first
ever collaboration with morphe these
sister collection we launched a
beautiful rainbow palette and an iconic
brush set as well perfect for unleashing
your inner artist they sold out
internationally in less than one day
which is so crazy I am so incredibly
grateful for all of you guys and all of
your support my life has been is so
crazier than the past several months and
you sisters have olive definitely
noticed it I've been of course posting
on my regular production schedule but I
have not been as active on snapchat on
Instagram and obviously you guys all
know now what all the work and love was
going into it was creating the palette
and the commercial of all the beautiful
looks surrounding it but as soon as it
launched I was ready to for once in my
entire life take a little breather
moment relax chill hang with my family
and friends and also celebrate and it
has been an amazing three weeks and I am
so incredibly grateful for all of you
guys for understanding letting me
breathe that letting me actually take
some time for myself but I am back and
today we are celebrating so first and
foremost before you even jump into the
makeup of today's video I first want to
say thank you most importantly to every
single one of you guys out there for
everything and for supporting me because
we have a lot of things to be
celebrating in today's video um let's do
a quick little recap so this all started
a few weekends ago with myself and my
team traveled to Minnesota to open the
biggest Murphy store in the entire world
located involve America it was so beyond
crazy oh my god hundreds and hundreds of
sisters showed up literally hours before
you guys are even supposed to we were
able to bring them hot chocolate and
donuts make sure everyone was safe in
the cold winter people ended up taping
inside at the mall and it the next
morning we were greeted by thousands and
thousands of you guys
at the mall for the ribbon-cutting it
was so crazy one of the best days of my
entire life anyway truly never forget
then we had a hop on a plane to LA acts
really quickly because my family and
little brother just got to town to
celebrate the fun events coming up with
him in the next week and the next day
thanks to all of you sisters voting like
crazy every single day we won together
the People's Choice Awards for 2018 best
Beauty influencer of the year which is
so incredibly crazy and I am so grateful
for it I got to give it to amazing fans
and makeover on the red carpet and
accept my trophy right then and there
you may have missed it since my category
was not televised apparently when you
get hundreds and hundreds of thousands
of votes if you're a digital influencer
or you're still not important enough
which is just lovely so fighting against
that every single day but regardless
it's the People's Choice Awards and that
means you guys voted and that means way
more to me than any trophy that we can
win any single day so still thank you
the most
so the PCs were on a Sunday and the next
thing was Monday meaning it was my
pallet launch party tonight and oh my
god you guys I was so beyond excited
this party was planned at very very
last-minute so myself in the morphe team
were literally hustling all day long
picture was actually gonna be ready for
everybody to come and celebrate inspired
by the unleash your inner artist theme
of the palette it was an all-white party
which proved to not last for very long
judging by myself getting paint pour all
over me and my iconic custom outfit but
it was truly a night I will never forget
and I am so grateful to have every
single person in my life that has been
supporting me since day one I was
sobbing crying during my little speech
with Linda Murphy the owner and CEO I
really don't cry or get emotional that
often I will say I definitely have built
up a very very thick skin over the past
several years but there were just so
many people they were supporting me that
I could not help but get so emotional
and be so grateful for everything that
has happened in the past few months so I
sobbed thank all the makeup was okay but
after that I got ruined by gallons and
gallons of paint being poured on me
regardless and my outfit being
completely ruined well not really ruined
oh I guess because everybody got to
unleash their inner artist at the party
which was so much fun I am so incredibly
grateful for everybody in my life that
was able to make it and also everybody
who wasn't able to make it as well
obviously
a lot of charges going on at the time in
California with the fires and so many
other things but the support has meant
so much to me regardless and also major
thank you as well to every single person
on the murphy team that i have worked or
that sense day wanted this collaboration
it has been so incredibly amazing and i
could not believe it is finally here and
without everybody this would not have
happened so you guys know who you are
love you all the most after the launch
party everybody jumped in the party bus
back to my house and we were literally
awake until 5:00 in the morning
celebrating um everybody got very they
had fun and so did I but I'm a sister
sober of course as if you guys know
because I had to wake up in literally
two hours because the next day was a
launch day waking up at 7:00 a.m. with
my parents and some of the more fut
members who had slept over was neither
fun nor rational either right now but it
was all worth it because at 8:00 a.m.
Pacific Standard Time
we broke make up history with the launch
of the James Charles X morphe palette
and oh my god you guys I am so
incredibly grateful we launched with
quite a lot of units I obviously cannot
release those numbers but we sold out of
the entire collection in Europe
Australia and Canada in less than 10
minutes and sold out globally in less
than one day breaking morphe records and
having their highest sales day in
history which is iconic well I'll be are
celebrating the palette sellout I don't
even know how it happened but you guys
pulled together and we had 10 million
sister subscribers on this YouTube
channel oh my god you guys we started
this channel only three years ago now
and never in 10 million years did I ever
think we would get this far
I like I cannot believe the progress
that we've had together as a family
this journey has been a quite the roller
coaster but I started this with a
mission in mind of creating beautiful
and creative makeup looks creating
entertainment content making you guys
happy and I can truly say we haven't
shaken up the beauty industry for the
better and then literally one day later
we also some have energy to hit 10
million on Instagram as well bringing
our total like social media reach to
over 20 million sisters which is so
beyond crazy I feel like we're literally
running a nation up
here and it feels so amazing and I am so
incredibly grateful for every single one
of you guys trust me if it were not for
you I would not be here and that is a
judgment promise I love my job and I am
so grateful that I get to do it and
inspire you guys every single day and
thank you from the bottom of my heart
truly after all those amazing things
that went on I decided for once in my
life to take a little bit of a break
most importantly I wanted to celebrate
with everybody in my life that means the
absolute most me but I also wanted to
chill to relax it take some time for
myself and my mental health because it
was a little sister struggling and
[ __ ] Ally but I also took a few days
as well to plant some really amazing
content coming soon I am so beyond
excited and after all that I am ready to
be back to pump up some amazing videos
for you guys of course using this baby
right here and that leads us to today's
brand new video
so you guys saw the finished and
beautiful 52 second commercial that I
was so incredibly proud of but what you
don't know is that that commercial was
shot not once but twice and both times
took well over a week to produce we
literally hired a videographer to come
on set and film the makeup creation
process of every single one of those
looks so I could later convert it into a
tutorial for this YouTube channel but
that didn't exactly work out when it
started taking five six seven hours to
create each look so unfortunately I do
not have tutorials of the campaign books
except for of course the unleash your
inner artist book which if you have not
seen that video make sure to click right
up here and I'm trying to think what I
want to do for my ten million video I
have to do something big iconic I have
to celebrate and I thought do I want to
brace myself and do every single one of
those looks again and film them as
tutorials and I came to the conclusion
no I'd rather not die on camera so then
I was thinking okay and maybe I'll make
it a lot easier for myself and just do
one of the locks so I created it and
after reading through thousands of
replies I gathered that you guys kind of
liked all of them and nobody could agree
so I do of course have a compromise
hopefully I can actually pull this off
but so my favorite looks that I've been
seeing so far from you sisters that have
been actually able to get the palette
and start to play with it happen looks
or you can bind a few different of the
campaign images into one so for today's
video since you guys could not decide at
which look you liked better I thought I
would have went out the palette
absolutely literally every single color
in here and try to recreate all the
campaign images on my face
one time this is gonna be a little bit
of like a weird mix of a tutorial video
but also mostly just be playing the
actual palette
I'll show you guys every single color
and they're the techniques that I like
to use for maximum color payoff and
blend ability and also a little bit of a
behind-the-scenes look of how I created
every single one of these looks so
without further ado Oh Kyra pink kitty
drink idiot grab a snack and let's get
started and I'll leash our in our
artists
[Music]
after looking at all the images and
stalking a few guys on Twitter as well I
saw this look by yani Mui she's home
credibly talented and she actually
combined all the campaign looks into one
I'm gonna change a few things but I'm
gonna use her photos inspirations today
because I think she did a really good
job picking the places to put everything
so thanks girl let's get started my base
is already on because this video is
gonna be focused on mostly at shadows da
so I'm gonna go ahead and grab my Mac
Paint Pot in the shade up painterly and
my morphe m17 3 brush that this is in
the jamesrowe specs morphe brush
collection and we're gonna use this to
prime my eyelids and get ready for
shadow sorta often that's gonna grab up
my palate oh my god it feels so crazy to
actually say that holy crap um I
promised yours will not come looking
like this this is actually the first one
that was ever made so I've been
traveling with this and using this for
several months now she's been through
quite a lot she's been dropped she's
been you she's been dug in too but she
still gets the job done so I'm gonna
first grab with my morphe m4a3 3 brush
and just dip into the shade at you're
kidding which is literally the best
Bruntlett which is literally the best
bright red and the entire world and I'm
just going to it start laying that on
the eyelid this property's gonna be the
easiest eye look you'll ever do because
we were literally just doing a look at
how pigmented that is I'm just packing
this color right onto the lid over top
of my Mac Paint Pot aka dry base
formulated specifically for the eyes
because those are the techniques that
are gonna give you the best results as I
said a million times I'm gonna use that
brush to kind of stamp out roads a
little bit because I am gonna kind of
wing it this out and pull it towards my
temple and then with whatever access
shadow is left on that brush I'm just
gonna start lightly going over those
edges to buff them out and make sure
they are nice and blended
I'm gonna have a little bit of a
fluffier brush and use this to go over
the edges and start drying out this red
eye shadow down underneath the eyeball
and also kind of everywhere else as well
to make this look less weight and I
don't 501 brush I'm gonna dip into the
shader literally it next to you're
kidding
I'm gonna give that a quick spritz I'll
buy a weapon set setting spray and use
that to meld together the red tones and
the highlighter that I already had on oh
my god I love the shadow so what much
the last step of the love stay click
it's of course the hearts now on the day
of set I actually put on a heart sticker
first and then did all the red and just
peeled it off and we had a nice and
negative space moment I do not have any
more heart stickers and I could not find
them at the craft stores today for some
reason so we're now going to draw them
on and hope that it looks okay I'm gonna
put one right here oh thank god
oh my god okay I'm gonna put another one
right here I'm gonna quickly set that in
place with just a little bit of canvas
on a tiny little pencil brush just to
make sure that concealer doesn't move
around I do a little heart in the inner
corner to kind of cue alright that is
the elastic I've already done and
completes I'm gonna grab the same brush
and painterly and pop some on the other
eyelid and get started on the blue book
I'm first gonna grab the about four five
six which is my brush that I actually
created with morphia this is the tiny
blending brush and dip into the shader
Cola and I'm gonna use this to start
building out the outer V I'm placing on
this color first because in order to get
really really pigmented and bright dark
blues you do have to use a slightly
different techniques than a typical
eyeshadows like I talked about in my
original video which for some reason
caused quite the controversy very
literally no reason at all for me
personally I definitely felt as though
my reveal video was very very upfront
and honest you guys about the palette
and the different aromas and the
techniques that you should be using and
the different products that work best of
it in order for you guys to obviously
get the best possible results and for
some reason a lot of people seem to
think that I was lying or that I was
trying to get more money out of you guys
which first of all I don't even
understand how that even be a thought
process considering the product that I
recommended to work fast with this
morphe eyeshadow palette was a Mac Paint
Pot they are sharing none of the same
monies that's not even helping morphe
it's just generally a really bomb
product that myself and the morphe
product development team have found
works really really well with these type
of shadows but also as well if you guys
have follow me for a very very long time
you would know that I definitely used to
get involved with quite a lot of drama
in the social media space and I used to
have a very very snappy mouth and I've
been working on that
over the past several years and I feel
like I've definitely gotten way better
at biting my tongue and not replying to
people but watching these Palin videos
oh my god you guys third but it
definitely a few at this point that I
wanted to literally reach through my
computer screen and be like why what are
you doing now if any of us actually have
the palate you may have noticed that on
the front packaging it says the James
Charles artistry palette now this is not
because of the unleash your inner artist
bono it is actually because when I got
the opportunity to create this palette
with morphe I said I wanted to create
literally the best rainbow mattes on the
market and that we definitely did but
what I've learned is that when
pigmentation is your number one priority
which for me it 100% was some of the
shades actually do have to be formulated
just slightly differently than a typical
eyeshadow in order to get those really
really bright and vivid pigments to
create beautiful rainbow looks I've
talked about that several times now
that's what I was talking about in my
original reveal video when it came to
press pigments versus typical eyeshadows
and people really really read on that
and I'm really glad that this is kind of
created a bigger discussion about the
actual ingredients and makeup but who
some of the things that I've been seeing
people saying or doing regarding these
actual shades have been interesting to
watch say the least
since this is the unleash your inner
artist palette I figured the best
possible example I could give to you
guys would be an actual artist if an
artist was going to paint a picture they
would never slap paint onto a canvas sit
back and wait for it to magically blend
together to create a beautiful piece of
art no that is the whole point of being
an artist you actually have to put in
the work you have to build up your
talent level you have to use the right
materials tools paint brushes paints and
put it on the right canvas to produce
the final product if you want to create
a beautiful watercolor painting it does
not matter how bright how vivid how
blendable or how expensive your
watercolor kit is because chances are if
you apply those colors to a canvas
they're simply never going to perform as
well as they could if they were applied
to watercolor paper now same thing goes
to acrylic paint or oil paint if you
apply those paints to a watercolor paper
chances are the paints are probably
going to soak through and melt it and
it's going to be a huge mess now of
course you can do those things if you
want to there are no rules to art but
for me I've always looked at makeup
specifically eyeshadow and in the same
exact way both art and makeup are not
easy they take a lot of time a lot of
raucous and a lot of talent but I nature
artists knows that sometimes switching
up your products and techniques to get a
better final result is always worth it I
was literally so far and deep into that
tangent that my camera stopped recording
and I just missed half of this purple
look sorry about that before I move on
I'm very proud of this palette I've
worked way too hard on has to do with a
lot of speculation so I just wanted to
clear all that up moving on that as the
blue look all complete I used the shades
hello playground Cola and a little bit
of brother to pull this all together
love how this look turned out and I'm
going to move on to it the galaxy log
before I do any of the art because the
purple is going to be it's super super
easy so what I've done so far is grab
the morphe M 4-3-3 brush and I've just
dip it into the shade single and I've
used this too it just kind of stipple it
all over my face
really really nicely just to get a light
wash of purple on there I want to get
like that nice kind of almost splotchy
wash of color lay down in this area so I
can add on lots of other things on top
and even though we are doing this mostly
I am definitely trying to keep most of
the pigment like right around kind of
the nose bridge and around like this
inner cheek region and lightly blending
out those edges so even if it's splotchy
it still looks good now with that same
exact brush I'm gonna dip into the shade
escape and I'm gonna use this once again
to kind of splotchy Li just dab on some
more pigment and dimension and then
final I'm just gonna take an AM at 5:06
brush and dip into the black shade it's
spooky and I'm just gonna do a little
bit of this because it definitely goes a
long way it this is so pigmented and I'm
just gonna add on a few more little
sister splotches here and there for some
final bits of a galaxy dimension now to
tie it all together I'm gonna grab the
shade artistry which is this a beautiful
metallic duo call blue purple shade or
right here and I'm gonna go this on my
finger and then it's going to a top over
some of the areas at the Galant oh my
god look at that
I'm gonna tap right over some of the
areas of the galaxy it to pack the shade
on there and to add some blue glow now
like I was talking about earlier with
different formulas being used this is
definitely one of the more unique ones
in the palette I've seen a lot of people
watching this one and being a little bit
disappointed by the color payoff it can
be used on its own if you want and it's
still absolutely stunning but the shade
is actually meant to be layered over top
of other colors hence what I'm doing
right now for the fall beautiful effect
by the way that shade literally is the
same way as well this one is meant to be
a kind of mixing shade for a highlighter
and blush but can still be used on its
own
very very beautifully and then last name
it's gonna grab a simple white liquid
liner to add on these stars so probably
the hardest part this entire campaign
was drawing and shading in every single
one of these hexagons when it came to
the B look now I think I'm gonna get it
done right now to get it over with so I
can do the slime and the flame because
those are gonna be kind of easy let's do
this
to do this I'm just gonna grab an angle
brush and I'm gonna dip into the shade T
in the top right corner let's start the
first one right here for the next one
it's gonna do the same exact thing but
leave a little bit of a gap in between
if first I'm a really odd reason do you
want to recreate this at home which I
don't know why you would but if you just
want to be a queen bee for a day and you
have trouble with patterns because let
me tell you this is hard okay
we had lipstick Nick we're literally on
site trying to figure out what shape we
were doing for a good like two hours
before I actually ended up looking okay
so I would definitely recommend
practicing on like your arm or your leg
before you go right onto your face so
you don't mess up so now I'm gonna grab
the tiny little faulty brush this is the
m15 to two of these come in Maya brush
set and dip it did the shader punish me
which is this cool toilet light brown
and I'm gonna use this shade to blend
out all those lines so I want to do the
top right corner to be the most dark so
I'm gonna focus the color right in there
and then lightly blend out the arc
furnace okay I'm just gonna go in now
and blend out those edges I'm next to
get a little small brush and dip into
the shades in canvas and also a little
bit of it be at the bright yellow and
use these two colors to kind of
highlight the middle of these honey
columns so now that the combs are all on
there at the last and final step of this
look is going to be to grab a little bit
of concealer and a very tiny liner brush
this is the amma two-five-zero it's in
the brush kit and you can take again so
what we're gonna do
[Music]
alright so I'm gonna leave the queen bee
look alone for right now of course they
do want to add honey and later on but
that's gonna get really messy and really
sister sticky so I'm gonna go ahead and
move on to the flames to start sketching
out the fire I'm just gonna grab a matte
orange liquid lipstick this is
flamethrower from jeffree star cosmetics
I would use an orange eyeshadow with
that it's gonna take me eight hours so
sorry about it
everybody's just gonna go in and start
like sketching the flames for the orange
I'm gonna grab four three three brush
and dip into the shade at 5:08
first I'm gonna lay this down over top
um
the local dough stick didn't do you have
to bring it down to my neck okay right
like try to take this off I wonder oh my
god what I was scared and it's not one
video without having a mental breakdown
like just one
that took way too long okay now to add
some more dimension into the flame so
we're gonna do is grab a little pencil
brush and dip into the shaded B which is
literally the best of bright yellow
pigment in the entire world and I'm
going to put this in like the center
areas of the flames so that is the fire
look all complete we only have two
colors left being the green it's live
and then also the pink bubblegum now I
want to put this line right here join
for my jaw line so it like makes sense
grab a brow garment gravitationally grab
gravitationally it's not a word
thank you the gravitational pull
gravitationally it's a word now I'm
gonna put this line here so it makes
sense gravitationally but doing that at
least this big open space right here I
wanted to put a butterfly there but I
can't find them that's an issue so I
think because of the fact that the pink
look was and I look and then that I just
the bubble I need to somehow get like
the pink in here somehow so I think I
want to draw in a bunch of little pink
bubbles as if they're like floating so
to draw the outline of the bubbles I'm
gonna use the Kylie liquid lipstick in
the shade
no more this is literally an exact match
to the shade skip so this will be a
really good fresh to draw it with that's
gonna grab the shade to skip on a flat
packing brush and just put that right on
there using that same brush I'm gonna
dip into the shade of pink idiot trinket
which is to get a matte super light baby
pink I'm gonna put this like here okay
with a little pencil brush I'm gonna
grab a little bit of playground just add
in just a little bit of blue because why
not
and then same thing with a little bit of
a social blade as well a little bit of B
as well then I'm gonna use the white
liquid liner once again and just add in
some reflections now I'm gonna draw the
slime at first using a cream paint just
to get the outline
and then just let it get in place using
a packer brush and the shader social
there's there's definitely a less self
hair in there and then describing a
packer brush and that shade a packer
brush and the shade socialblade scary
with that same Packer brush I'm just
gonna dip into the shades B and also a
little bit of flashback as well and use
those to highlight inside of the slime
this tiny little detailing brush so
going to dip into the shade daddy and
I'm gonna use this to shade more of this
line and add in some little drip tips
and then once again at some more white
highlights I'm gonna put on a black
liquid lipstick up because it's the only
color that will not clash with every
single one of the other colors in my
face this is Oprah in the shade dear
Bronx you can use Kojima's for 30% off
[Music]
all right sisters I'm just gonna pop on
the lashes I'll be right back with the
finished look all right sisters I just
popped on a pair of my favorite lashes
that Lily lashes in the style Miami of
course used coach James for 15% off just
like basically every single product in
this video it also popped on some honey
onto at the honeycombs and that
completes this campaign makeup tutorial
I had so much fun creating every single
one of these original looks for the
campaign commercial and I'm so proud of
how they all turned out and I feel like
they all showcased the different colors
in such a beautiful way and I had so
much fun again at today REE creating all
them together as one I really really
hope you guys enjoyed all these looks
and like today's a brand new video if
you decide to recreate any of them on
yourself or literally create any look
using my palette please don't forget to
tag me on Instagram I cannot wait to see
all the photos and see all of you guys
unleashing your inner artists if you did
enjoy it please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below enjoy your
sisters support it means so so so much
to me I'm sorry that I could not do
tutorials every single one of these does
it the best I got
hope you all still love me if you've not
already make sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below as well and
come join the sisterhood we are over
Millie and sisters strong and I'd love
to have you join the family I could not
even believe I get to say that thank you
guys once again so so so much and I
cannot wait to see it what is coming for
the future if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both does
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes and stuff is James
Charles the dexterous after Charles this
videos sisters shadow goes to every
single one of the ten mill any of you
guys out there and I promise that's the
last time that I'm doing that cheesy
moment for a while now don't forget to
always reach me your video links they go
live on Twitter if you want to beat the
sister shadow for real next time alright
you guys thank you so much for watching
this video and today don't forget to
check out morphe calm and also Ulta calm
sign up for the mailing list to make
sure you get the palette as soon as it
comes back in stock it has literally
sold out worldwide thanks to all of you
guys I can only just see your finished
looks and I will see you next time for a
brand new video
[Music]
I'm pleased you're an artist