hi sisters
welcome to the official 2020 house tour
actually no no no don't show that just
yet
in honor of hitting 20 million
subscribers we're giving away
100 000
okay now that you guys have seen the
upstairs and the bedrooms and also the
main floor
there's still one floor left of the
house that i have not yet
shown you guys ever since i started
doing youtube about four or five years
ago now
i have been dreaming of what it would be
like to have the perfect
sister's headquarters we've been
renovating for months
and i'm so excited to tell you guys that
those dreams have finally
come true when i was looking to buy my
first ever house it was really important
to me that i was able to have a good
work life balance but for me since my
work takes up so much of my life it was
really hard to actually find that so we
found this house that had a basement it
was like literally
a message from heaven above and i knew
that this was going to be the one
because we were able to turn this
basement
into the dream sisters headquarters and
i'm so excited to show
you guys there's a lot that i want to
show you so let's go ahead and get
started with the first room which is
the sister cinema
[Music]
[Applause]
sure you guys obviously all know trevor
andrew
we're here in the movie theater which is
like i can't believe that that sentence
just left my mouth like the fact that i
have a movie theater in my house
is so cool it's not even funny this was
actually not on like my
requirements list when shopping for
homes but i certainly am not complaining
this is like
the best thing to ever happen to us as
you can see we have a bunch of different
reclining chairs that do actually
recline
would you like to demonstrate trevor of
course oh yeah sure
oh this goes right back favorite
projector with a big screen obviously
there
we have some gorgeous candies instead of
gorgeous i love gorgeous skin
some delicious candies really lined up
so you can pick your favorite a popcorn
machine over here as well so literally
any snack that you could possibly
want to indulge in a gorgeous snack if
you will
we have right here in the cinema well
i'll let you two boys watch
this for some reason
coming out of the theater right over
here we have the conference room which i
actually was not really expecting to use
that often
in the last house we honestly had a lot
of our meetings in like the kitchen and
the living room
but this has been really really helpful
to just kind of separate once again
living and working
and my team and i have meetings in here
literally all the time we have this
massive table a bunch of different
dining chairs we also have a tv on the
wall which normally is
not playing my videos it's for airplay
any like presentations or projects or
anything
and also for virtual zoom calls we have
an acrylic board over there for any
calendaring and planning then finally
two different art prints from different
exciting moments in my career
okay so coming out of the conference
room we have don't fit into this just
yet
and over here in this hallway is the
sister salaam now this is once again
a room that i didn't expect to have in
this house but i'm definitely not
complaining
it is so cool in here obviously being a
beauty guru beauty related tasks are a
huge part of my calendar and daily life
so this room is like the perfect place
for all that to happen we have these
massive beautiful vanities for
impressions with barber chairs as well
so i use this area to get ready and also
get my hair cut which is
so nice in the last house i was getting
ready and filming in the same studio
which was you know not the end of the
world but it would literally look like a
tornado had gone through it every single
day which was an absolute
nightmare so now i get to separate
getting glam for fun
and actually filming videos we also have
a table over here where i get my nails
done with
chad you guys saw that in the long nails
for a day video which was absolutely
crazy
we have our 1 million and our 10 million
plaques and then finally we have this
beautiful wall of fully sound wings
ready to go if i ever need to do a
transformation now you guys have seen
the movie theater the conference room
and the salon and there's one more room
that i need to show you guys in the
basement and it is my favorite room of
the entire
house having a master production space
has been a dream of mine for so
long now when i first started doing
youtube videos almost four years ago i
was filming in a little corner my
parents paste it with just two soft
boxes finally in this house i can
finally say that i have my dream
production
space come on in to sister studios
[Music]
okay so obviously this space is
absolutely massive this is definitely
where most of the renovations took place
and you're probably wondering james how
did you end up with a production studio
in
your basement and that is a great
question when we first moved in
fun fact this entire area was actually
an indoor pool which is
yes a subtle flex but was just so
unnecessary to me so we decided to fill
it in
put it in hardwood floors and now this
is the absolute dream
studio space as you guys can see right
over here i have my full-on
camera setup which is such an upgrade
from the last studio i am such a massive
nerd for production at heart so it has
honestly been
so much fun for me to challenge myself
and to try to keep upgrading our studios
and our setup to ultimately make the
best content for you guys
we have our camera and our tripod we
have our monitors the microphone
the diffuser the big lights everything
from the backdrop and it is all hanging
from the ceiling as well which makes it
so
much cleaner if i sit down to film a
video this is what you guys see
i have a monitor in front of me to see
what i'm doing there's a monitor behind
the camera for lewis and there's also
a tv right over there so any guests can
see it as well
which is super awesome i always like to
have a lot of people in the room when
they film my videos and our last studio
was really small and crowded which
became a problem quite a lot so it was
really important for this face that we
were able to have a seating area
we have our couch and chairs and then
also like i was saying this tv here as
well
which is great for anybody that comes
over has a team or assistance along with
them
they can sit and get work done and also
have easy access to see what's going on
behind the camera as well opposite the
sitting area next to the filming setup
we also have another paper backdrop
system
and this is for photos we have the same
exact camera and the same exact lens
some more lights as well and just a fun
little backdrop so you're able to shoot
photos for assistance apparel or any
other photo shoots that we have going on
which is honestly really really helpful
as well so therefore we don't have to
keep doing everything around taking
lights up and down
it's honestly just such a hassle so this
just makes everything so much easier
and i cannot wait to see what magic
we're going to create in this photo
studio
moving right along to this wall we have
two very very special rooms
and these are the sister studios but not
the video studios
the recording studio these used to be a
steam room and a sauna once again for
the indoor pool
but we really wanted to make it much
more personal and you guys know how much
of a big part of my life
music is so we figured it'd be only
appropriate to build out the ultimate
recording studio
to mix the music one day it is not done
quite yet we're still waiting on some
equipment and furniture but
we are so close and it's looking so good
so far
the walls are fully padded and
soundproof we have a custom desk built
we also have these really cool clouds in
the ceiling from the brand room cloud
they gifted them to us and it just
creates such a fun vibe in here and i
cannot wait to see what we're going to
create in here as well
one day very very soon and then right
next door to the mixing room we also
have the recording room
which is
[Music]
obviously very secure door very
soundproof in here so you can record
vocals and nobody's going to hear it
some more of ib clouds and then you have
a window so i can see lewis yelling at
me telling me that my pitch is wrong
from the other room all right you guys
and the last place that i want to show
you in the sister studio
is the sister store so many fun s words
this like i was saying
used to be the indoor pool so this is
actually the indoor gym
but now this is the stuff
this is the storage room so it was
really important to me that we were able
to create an area oh look at trevor just
being such a good employer working at
the store
it was really important for me that we
were able to create an area not only for
storage of sisters apparel
but also for all of our makeup stuff as
well as you guys can see this entire
wall is all different makeup items that
i have in my collection
once again similar to the pantry
organized by the queen herself
have all of our categories foundations
powders brow stuff we have
palettes tools we have all these eye
glitters and eye tools we have
lashes lipsticks literally everything in
my collection is beautifully displayed
so i know exactly where it is and i can
pull it really easily if i need to go
film a video out in the studio and then
on the other side of the room we have an
entire wall dedicated to sister's
apparel we have all of our different
colored hoodies that we've released
and we also always have our current
collections as well it was super
important to us to have a full on stock
because friends and family come over
literally
all the time and are complaining to us
that the last collection sold out way
too fast
that they need their hoodie so whenever
we have friends or guests over we could
always put together cute goodie bags or
we also have the full collection
for giveaways for you guys we love love
love doing giveaways and sending out
packages to all of you sisters whether
it be on the sister's apparel account
which you definitely need to follow or
my own account
if you guys did not know fun fact i've
been giving away 500
to whoever comments the secret emoji on
my instagram photos make sure you follow
charlie to post notifications to all my
social media platforms because we
absolutely love
sending you guys packages thank you
trevor can you pop her in the mail for
me
good to go sounds good speaking of
giveaways you guys make sure you keep
watching to the end of today's video for
a 20 million subscriber special
i think at this point that is the
basement all complete which means
the house is all complete but there's
still one last place to take you guys
and that is upstairs to the backyard
[Music]
okay you guys just like the basement the
backyard literally looked
nothing like this when we first moved in
because it underwent a lot of different
renovations
and this is probably the space that i'm
most excited about i know i keep saying
that but literally like i just love all
the spaces
and i'm so excited to share with you
guys the last house in the last yard was
really not it for a lot of different
reasons the first one being it was just
too small not for us but for fit again
the last yard was so tiny but now we
have this entire space dedicated to this
little one
running around having the time of his
life with all of his toys and he has
never been
happier also as you can see there is a
massive pool which has been
incredible in the last house we were
really never in the pool because of the
way that it was positioned in the yard
anytime after like noon when the sun
starts to go down it was completely in
the shade so the pool was always cold we
were never in it but
this pool is not the case at all it is
huge and it is smack dab in the middle
of the yard
it gets done all day long and we have
been spending so many days
chilling by the pool or just swimming
and it has been literally like a dream
come true now i want to take you guys
over to this side of the yard because
this is where most of the changes took
place
and i am literally in love this is like
the outdoor kitchen and
seating area now when we first moved
into the house there was actually two
different pool houses
one right here and one over there where
the fireplace is now which you'll see in
a second a lot of times builders in la
will add guest houses or pool houses to
their properties
just because they can add square footage
to the listing which literally equates
to hundreds of thousands of dollars
sometimes which is
like mind-blowing to me it's truly a
sister scam and obviously i had
no reason for either one of them so we
converted the first pool house into an
outdoor kitchen which turned out
absolutely
sunny we have these beautiful black
countertops and bar stools so my friends
and i can sit out here and eat if the
boys are over
and grilling some nice delicious meats
um we have
an outdoor fridge and we also have a tv
as well which does rotate so we can
watch music videos or the boys can watch
sport games
during our outdoor barbecues we have
these four trees that surround the
outdoor eating area
along with string lights as well which i
feel like creates just like a magical
vibe
and i really like how it feels a little
bit more separated from the rest of the
yard as well
we went with a massive concrete dining
table in the middle with a ton of
different seats around it so we can all
have family dinners
when the backyard was finally finished
my friends and i decided to cook for
once in our lives
and set up a cute little dining table
out here i think i posted on my
instagram stories actually and we ate
dinner
and then brought out some card games and
stuff and we ended up being out here
losing chocolate time until like three
in the morning
it was so much fun it was such a good
vibe and that's how you know you've
created a magical space
now if you guys follow me right along
this way next to the outdoor kitchen we
have a cute little ping pong table
for nice games we have three little
trees as well which are babies right now
but will eventually be limes lemons and
oranges for our citrus in the morning
and then this is a really fun part of
the backyard as well
this is our outdoor fireplace so right
here used to be the other
pool house as well which we ended up
removing but now it is this beautiful
sit-in full stucco white fireplace and i
am
absolutely obsessed we've already had so
many fun nights roasting marshmallows by
the fire and just sitting in here and
talking and relaxing and a much better
use of the space than what was here
before
also i mentioned in the last video that
i really wanted to give shout outs to
the people that made this home
renovation project rewarding instead of
stressful
and one person that i definitely owe a
ton of thanks to
is jonathan juan with racing green
construction he literally
took this backyard from drab to fab and
i do mean that literally just like
leclaire decor as soon as jonathan and
racing green came onto the project it
was like magic waiting to happen and i
was just so
so grateful every single step of the way
their team was professional
super fast and just honestly cared a lot
as well this is obviously my first home
purchase which was
really exciting but really really scary
as well there are so many things
that you would never like expect to deal
with being a homeowner i know that i
didn't expect to deal with obviously
jonathan and his team were amazing at
construction
but i also just want to say a major
thank you to him because he truly kind
of like took on a fatherly role with me
with this whole process
which just made it so much easier and
way more fun as well so to jonathan i
love you the opposite most
and if anybody watching this happens to
be in l.a and needs any renovations done
hit up jonathan and racing green that
are the absolute best okay let's come on
down to this here
and on to the basketball court if you
know me you know that i'm not really a
sporty person so you're probably
wondering
why the heck i have this in the house
although i will not be using this very
often i do have quite a lot of boys in
my life
louis loves basketball a lot of my
friends husbands do as well
who knows maybe one day with a little
bit of practice i could be lebron james
charles
i'm gonna stick with makeup now i
clearly am not a basketball star and
that's fine
okay i know what i'm good at and i'm
gonna leave that part of the yard to
everybody else
but this part of the yard is mine we
have this massive oak tree right here
which is
so beautiful we have this fun little
hanging chair as well which is
such a vibe honestly i have been just
sitting out here reading and looking at
my phone going over business emails so
often and then finally the best part of
the entire house
the in-ground trampoline now when i
first moved in this entire area used to
be a putting green and no offense to any
golfers or anything it's just the only
thing that i would want
my house but i have wanted an ingrown
trampoline in my home for so long now
and it is finally a reality and oh my
god we have literally been out here
non-stop jumping doing tricks being
flips double bouncing each other
and also just sitting out here talking
and trying to touch the leaves as well
this is literally an olympic
braid trampoline and it is so
much fun
okay you guys i'm absolutely exhausted
i'm out of breath
and this has been a very very long day
of filming this house tour video
but i really hope that you guys have
enjoyed seeing what we've built over the
past
nine months this renovation has been so
much fun and it was literally
only possible because of each and every
single one of you guys i know you've
been waiting i promise at the beginning
of the video
we're gonna head down to the sister
studio because i have one more thing
that i want to talk to you guys about
the 20 million subscriber special let's
go
oh all right you guys that was quite a
lot of walking around
before this house tour is officially
complete i wanted to take you back
downstairs to the studio for
one last thing and that is the 20
million
subscriber special first of all the fact
that we're even talking about a 20
million subscriber special is
so beyond crazy to me like just thank
you thank you thank you from the bottom
of my heart i cannot even believe that
this is a reality i am so grateful that
i get to do this job
every single day we were actually
supposed to film this video last month
we hit 20 million but some of the
renovations in the house took longer
than expected and now we're almost to 21
which is just
like literally insane like i said i am
just so grateful and i am so thankful to
each and every single one of you so
thank you thank you thank you this house
would not be possible if it were not for
you guys so in honor of that for 20
million subscribers i wanted to do
something
really really special to give back and
say thank you you guys know that we've
done a ton of different giveaways here
on this youtube channel
every holiday season we always do our
holiday give a slice and literally
earlier we were just talking about our
assistant's apparel pr packages
and our instagram prize winners we even
gave away fifty thousand dollars to the
winner of instant influencer and are so
excited for season two
but in honor of hitting 20 million
subscribers
we wanted to raise the stakes just a
little bit higher
so we're giving away 100
000 okay so here's how it's gonna work
in honor of 20 million
five of you amazing sisters are each
going to win 20
000 and a cute little sister's apparel
pr package
as well all you have to do to enter is
give this video a thumbs up down below
subscribe click that bell icon so you
get notified whenever i upload a brand
new video
and also make sure you follow me on all
my different social media accounts i
will be
checking this way you can stay up to
date with everything that i'm doing and
also be notified if you happen to win
and finally leave me a comment down
below with your name
your age your location your social media
handles and i want to know
what you do with 20 000
would you start a new business would you
pay off your school loans would you get
a new car would you give it to charity
or maybe even put a down payment down
on a house let me know and the winners
will be selected one week
from today all the legal rules for the
20 million subscriber special will be in
the description box down below so please
make sure you guys go check that out
with all that being said i think that is
this house tour video
all complete like i said in the
beginning this project has been in the
works for such a long time now but i'm
so glad that it is finally over with
this is literally my dream home and it
would not have been possible if or not
for each and every single one of you so
thank you thank you thank you
so so so much and today's sister shout
out is of course every single one of you
guys
that is all i have for today's video i
love you guys all so much good luck in
the 20 million subscriber special
and i will see you in the next one bye