my sisters James Charles Sturt and
welcome back to our YouTube channel as
you guys didn't see we're not in the
normal makeup studio and for today's
video we were doing a super super fine
makeup challenge
I am literally so pumped for this but
also a little bit nervous I'm not gonna
lie if he makes ago I saw my good-ass
sister nikita dragon do video where she
got ready and Sephora using all tests or
makeup and for today's I'm gonna
recreate that video by nikita but we're
gonna try to do it under 30 minutes
I feel like 30 is a pretty good number
for this video being that the average
person probably sends around 20 minutes
on their everyday makeup routine and for
a special event they may take a little
bit more time also for me my average
makeup routine takes me around two hours
so 30 bits is definitely a huge major
challenge we also have to take into
consideration that every Sephora is
different and the layouts are all
different so a lot of that time is
probably gonna be spent finding my
shades and finding the products in
general I'm gonna be getting ready today
using all the makeup in Sephora
including their spooky lighting and
mirrors but I did pick out a few things
that I wanted to bring here from home
starting off with a damp Beauty sponge
to blend in my foundation
I've brushes that I felt like I could
not do a makeup routine without being a
contour brush that I'm also gonna use
for brush lush hello in powder a nose
contouring brush a a flat tub concealer
brush a highlighting brush and then a
pencil brush and finally I also grabbed
a pair of lashes these are the new
bouncing Bella's obviously being a
makeup source Sephora does sell all the
items that I'm gonna be bringing with me
today but first of all that's kind of
really unsanitary I'm definitely not
trying to get any size or disease or
infections spooked and to all the
sampled makeup that we're gonna be using
it's like out and open to the public to
you but all these items are prepackaged
and that folks is what we like to call
stealing and for me personally I'm
trying to get a house and a boyfriend
not a lawsuit and jail time without
further ado it let's call our uber by
the way you can use code sister James
for five dollars off your first three
Birds I don't know if I've ever actually
mentioned that in a YouTube video but
you're welcome
beebeep ahead at let's get started with
the Sephora makeup challenge
[Music]
all right guys we have arrived here's
the poor end of the challenge is ready
to go I'm gonna set the timer for 30
minutes guys I'm a little bit spooked
I'm gonna try my best to clean all the
products of four keys and then because
it can sometimes be a very very
unsanitary but we're definitely gonna
get a full clan maple work done fingers
crossed at least in under 30 minutes I
have my timer right here ready to go
we're gonna set this baby for 30 minutes
exactly on the clock okay we ready go so
we have to start on the way to just
prime our face so I'm gonna go for the
tachi area wherever that is and that's
gonna be in skincare so we're running
running running running so we got her
doctor brush it's dr. Brandt
oh it's touching not in this nipple run
scared way bozhe origin believe it or
not I missed áfourá BAM okay
starting off water cream primer you guys
know this is my all-time babe I always
gonna moisturize the face before
starting on my makeup routine really
good really fresh and then at the new
touches seal canvas primer as well as
they whopping $52 hello Tasha getting
real brave with their prices God what I
love you the most
this primer is so bomb honestly one of
the only good primers that I've ever
tried that actually makes a difference
we're gonna put this right on the face
of challenge I need a mirror I forgot
how spooky to Sephora letting a
foundation let's go
we need the Too Faced brother safe
foundation do you guys know that's my
all-time holy grail faith and they do
carry a two-faced website in Sephora I
think my shade is warm I know my not
spray tan shade is warm nude but I'm
still spray tan from Coachella okay I'm
just gonna go with it you know what go
big go home this may be a classic
married type of day a but better be safe
than sorry I know this one it matches me
so we're gonna make it work what I mean
right now I have my damp Beauty Blender
still you guys know that is I talked
about my tips and tricks to getting a
perfect SCANA when you're doing your
base makeup and the one trick that I
talked about was when you're shopping
for a foundation you should always go
outside and look at your shade range
with a mirror before you actually put it
on and buy in a store because the
lighting in Sephora is all obviously
fluorescent lights and outside lighting
is obviously where you want to make sure
your foundation really really matches
but we did not have time for foundation
check today so I'm just gonna blend this
in all over my face oh Lord any more I
don't have enough coverage all I got
mascara can't forget to get in the neck
if this foundation doesn't match it's
gonna be the one saving grace to hide it
all the way down I am wearing a sister's
apparel hoodie said is so oh wait it's
on the front this is so hard don't
forget to check almost out for your cute
sisters beer coverings up on the ears as
well okay I don't even have time we need
to move on to concealer welcome to
Taiwan easy oh my god shake papers until
the Sephora okay Urban Decay all nighter
here she is okay oh wait or the NARS
radiant creamy concealer to do ah
where's nurse oh no oh no oh no no no
Kat Von D Sephora with a beauty Urban
Decay igloo face buxom where did NARS go
I know we saw NARS hello I don't have
time for this we're going with the Urban
Decay Naked skin because I libera cannot
find the other concealers so that's
great that's too late oh my god okay
this is in the shade light warm that is
too yellow oh my god you've got to be
kidding me light neutral let's try this
again
my phone is ringing don't even know who
it is sorry then they'll make up
challenge gonna put in all the high
points my face center of the forehead or
right down at the bridge of the nose
over the massage area I did shave before
this video if shaving is part of the
challenge we'd be here for an extra hour
thank all my Beauty Blender somehow
managed to stay wet on the uber right
over here because if this was dry we it
would be screwed to the next level
oh my god using this concealer really
reminds me how much I need a tape tape
in my life why does that mean old tape
school say they really play this good
with that one gal minutes on I literally
only have two steps doll I'm scared my
skin looks horrible okay whatever we
need laura mercier chances matter now
I'm holding my eyes open so I don't get
creases or mistake oh here she is
hello this is not good these are empty
we're gonna try this I don't know what
this is Laura Mercier translucent powder
I'm just no no mirror okay let's write
this blend in the creases oh my god this
looks horrible I guess I'm just gonna
get my beauty blender into whatever that
says that this implies Oh God Quantic
Mary is coming out to play I'm scared oh
the two-faced be peach powder wait that
oh boo hoo not here back oh my God my
face looks the worst and scared okay
everybody to put the sock okay next we
need to I'm sorry I don't have time for
that
okay next three touches Lau and bronze
our face so we're going well Miska Von D
shade + light you guys know I must have
sir Stan I have it using that damn
shading light pulse as I started to make
up it looks busted and cry oh
hello this is the only what mine looks
like kind of shows how I'm using a
morphe amplifier brush not slow to
Sephora but these co James for 10% off
the lighting in here is literally the
worst I'm scared that's harsh ha hoo we
said we were contour sisters today and
Kesava jawline we have to be a sister
snatched by the thought forehead a fool
the gals into thinking I have a forehead
and 7/5 had really snatched it up good I
have blush on this brush to perform a
bar light here for contouring but I'm
very scared that I'm looking probably a
little bit pain I'll think I'll be only
have 18 minutes 5 how has it already
been 12 minutes you have got to be
kidding me
got a chisel out the nose my nose
contour is like we'll just fight us out
tomato routine I don't care how long
I'll make up challenges I am getting an
oath contra in there even if it takes me
the entire time y'all thought I was
playing what brand has setting spray is
here and let's see um okay perfect so we
have all nighter I'm not ready to really
set my face yet but you know what we're
just gonna get like a Dewey right we
need to highlight let's find anasazi a
Beverly Hills I know she's here
okay we have the glow kits here you guys
know my all computers on a South ESL
Hollywood but they actually don't sell
those in stores anymore which is so rude
I don't know what miss laura mercier was
doing with that setting powder but she
was not the t if my face is creasing so
bad I'm scared I need to blend this in
okay let's do nose highlight
same is our product over here my face
looks bad I'm really scary I need more
translucent setting powder what brand
has a loose setting powder I hate to
bake my face
oh here's the NARS counter wow gray Oh
cover fax yeah okay it looks like
there's some powder oh great we found
powder we talked how do we thump how do
we turn powder goodness add some of this
up real quick my Beauty Blender stuck at
the bottom of my thing haha they're
kidding me how you to bake my face
because this looks like horrible right
now that's white I'm scared okay for
baking
oh my god I'm topping things okay it's
time for brows
and I'm very scared because I feel like
if anything a brows are gonna be the
very very long process perfect benefit
purse it's my Brown number 4 let's go
over here I can usually do my makeup
routine actually you know what maybe I
should use the goof proof brow pencil
instead okay
Kratz op we're using the benefit
precisely or hollow benefit group we
don't even have my shade we're using the
benefit group ooh prep pencil number 5
to snatch my brows up really quickly I
normally hate these shape of brow
pencils but it's much bigger and we
really don't have a lot of time left so
I need to cover the most
Brow's space in the short amount of time
possible disabilities and like normal
starting at the bottom of the brow using
light strokes and then going right in an
affiliate oh no you're kidding hello
that's the worst eyebrows hours in about
our life what's going on I'm scared of
the eyebrow okay you know what we do
have a concealer brush so we're gonna
clean it up in a second we'll see if we
can do this one a little better my brows
are by far my longest and also in my
least favorite parts I make appreciate
it because it's to do the same thing
every single time like you never get to
spice it up or anything like think if I
can finish my eyebrows and have them
looking decent with a few minutes
remaining I will actually be golden for
this challenge I can pop out of mascara
and lashes and a lip pretty quickly but
these brows may be my death wish oh my
god this iros bad I feel like we can
read this work okay
I don't know that finish this anymore
what time we are left
well NARS is over here no it's not her
is here where is the NARS kind of we
just saw I this is a joke
where Thanks thanks Carl
where's the concealer oh right here okay
great want any more of that and we're
gonna use this to clean up our brows
let's grab the brow kit right here we
have our flat top concealer brush okay
okay okay okay not not a thought we can
do that you can do that you guys that is
a decent sense of round let's be real
could be a little better but it
definitely could be a whole lot worse
let's pull in that concealer down to my
eyelid because what I'm use that as an
eyeshadow primer I definitely do how
time for eyeshadow look today but I
think we should go for a wing
can use my fingers to blow us houses I
didn't bring up one day brush I feel
like at this point we're not even gonna
get a line around so let's just get
right to mascara I know
benefit roller lash okay let's go over
here benefit were a little ashes on my
all-time favorite mascaras for literally
the longest time I stand by this it's a
really really bomb mascara using mascara
from Sephora testers is probably one of
the worst ideas ever in the entire row
because I use are so easy here to
transfer you guys know I've already
legally blind so I can't wait to wake up
tomorrow with a stye but you know what
we've gotta make do with what we have so
just gonna pop this on I'm gonna keep my
mascara right here we have the losses
and it lips to do still so let's see if
you can do this I have my lashes right
here and my last glue right here let's
see oh my god I don't have to be first
oh my god that is not okay you're
kidding me I'll clean that up oh my god
I can't even put lashes on width
squeezers let alone without this is a
Joe be careful without sticking stuff on
the floor oh you're kidding me don't get
up and fix that okay blood stuff hook
those up we're gonna do this one right
here
that's the worst lip application I've
ever done in my entire life setting
spray we need to lock into place oh my
god we my beak looks evaluate actually
let's evaluate as I clean up the floor
hold on let's see what we can do here we
love a humble sister this was so much
harder than I expected
like I was saying going into all the
products that I usually need are all
over the place in every different
Sephora whereas in my neural maker
pretend I have everything right down in
front of me I think majority of this
challenge is actually spent with me
running around Sephora not being able to
make decisions on what products they
wanted to use or where I wanted to use
them and not really took away from a lot
of the time doing my actual makeup I
feel like the primary foundation
application were really fine but we've
definitely lost it at concealer you guys
know that my go-to is always the charge
tape tape which I don't actually carry
out Sephora and I have not used the
different concealer than that and
literally it's been a good like year I
think now I think it was definitely
little bit shook when I had to use a
lesser coverage concealer and I think
from that moment on we were just screwed
miss laura mercier she was a smarter
sister because she didn't stock up a
single Oh
hooray stock Dustin you played me real
good with a cow well now there's powder
here but beforehand
there was no miss Laura Mercier so I did
not get to set my face today Wow I love
when that happened hurts and then we
moved on to of course contouring of
course we had the Kat Von D and light
palette you guys know that is my
all-time favorite and then baking once
again we had no chances of sending
powders and we had to end up going with
rubber FX powder which I've never
actually used it for let's see how she
looks
oh not that bad okay it went on very
very white and was definitely sticking
on my face white as well so I was a
little bit spooked not gonna lie that it
wasn't gonna work out but I think my
face actually looks really really good
the lashes are there but I wouldn't
necessarily call them on I don't believe
in a good pair of tweezers for la chop
location so definitely not the best and
then of course we did we had a few
seconds up to put on our lipstick I went
with just a tart liquid lipstick I hate
that's color but it'll be the first
thing that I grabbed with me looks fine
at this challenge I think was a success
I finished everything in time my face
doesn't look the best but from far away
and a little bit of Phase two I feel
like we could definitely power for a
full on event ready glam
maybe alright you guys we just got home
from Sephora and not complete says get
ready with me in Sephora using all
tested makeup at under 30 minute
challenge we need a better name for that
ASAP I had so much fun filming this
challenge today you guys an overall even
though my face doesn't look as perfect
as I usually like it too I'm definitely
really happy with the results and I
think that that answers the burning
question that we've all been wondering
is it possible to get fully ready in
Sephora yes I think it really is of
course I did bring a few tools but you
know we're just being a sanitarium
sisters just a quick little sister just
claim her as well at the end of all my
challenge videos I always say baby I
showed this one at home make sure to
shoot me a picture and let me know how
Wetmore for this one please do not try
to duplicate this one we did talk to the
manager staff a Sephora beforehand and
made sure not only was it okay to fill
in there but also do this challenge in
general they were kind enough to let us
do this but that's only because they
knew who I was I shop there all the time
and I know that I was a beauty guru
filming this for a YouTube video lets me
straight up and real we have all brought
products before especially from
drugstore where you can't actually try
it out and we've put it on and
literally loved the worst so I think
that the fact they were able to try out
products in Sephora before actually
buying them is such an incredibly
helpful system that makes makeup
shopping so much easier and although
this challenge is very very fun to film
for you guys please do not do this
because at the end of the day it's very
much taking advantage of Sephora and I
don't want to do that to them if there's
an emergency situation definitely go in
for a good impression sister glam
touch-up the staff is all amazing and
will definitely help you look at the
beautiful and fabulous but anything more
you're doing that at your own risk
you do not hear this from me Oh Papa
being said guys I really hope you
enjoyed this little challenge today and
if you did please don't forget to be
able to make a thumbs up down below
enjoy your support it really does mean a
lot and as well if you haven't already
make sure to hit that big red subscribe
button down below and come join us
sister we are pretty lit and click that
Bell icon so you can automate every time
I upload a brand new video
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
turn you can follow me at Instagram and
Twitter they're both is James Charles my
snapchat for more Mojave flips up as
soon as Charles that extra asked after
Charles this video is sister shadow goes
to sister Kenzie thank you so much love
for my styling at supporting you I love
you so so so much and have you'd like to
the next video sister shout out make
some toys or reach a Twitter links and
they go live on Twitter all right
sisters thank you so much in this video
I love you and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]