hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
halloween is coming up literally in a
few days now and I am so beyond excited
Halloween by far is my favorite time of
the entire year but I've been working on
a lot of different projects behind the
scenes this past month and I have not
had any time to do a single Halloween
look or tutorial and I am very sad about
it I do have a few things up my sleeve
for the next few days of Halloween time
but for today's video I thought I would
do something truly iconic perfect for
sister spooky season something that I
have wanted to do literally since I was
a little kid and for some reason it
never got around to doing playing with a
Ouija board oh my gosh wow it's almost
like the spirits are ready for me to
play so as you can see I have a brand
new Ouija board right here and I am so
beyond ready to contact the sister
spirits my mind is open I'm gonna set
some candles and really get in the mood
and for today's video you know on this
channel we always like to set the bar
higher so I figured why not try to have
a Ouija board pick my makeup since I've
never played at the Wii deeper before
and the last thing that I want to do is
anger the sister spirits because that
sounds not fun I'm kind of fun not gonna
lie but probably not good for me I
thought I would read the directions so I
don't die Ouija board the quest begins
dim the lights oh we're already feeling
step 1 this is a makeup tutorial so
hopefully the spirits love some good
Beauty lighting as it glides across the
board the Ouija planchette will reveal
headed messages Ouija are you there
place two fingers lightly on the
planchette oh god here we go okay I just
got my nails done hopefully the spirits
like them speak your séance to contact
the spirits okay let the bravest among
you ask the first question
give Ouija enough time to respond or
ember and spirits can't be rushed
it's so true that makes two of us
concentrate deeply if the planchette
doesn't move ask another question and
focus always speak slowly and clearly oh
it's gonna be a problem
always speak slowly and clearly just as
friendly spirits prefer oh my god if I
speak my normal speed am I gonna contact
a demon and don't forget to say goodbye
when you're done my mind is open I think
I know what to do I'm ready to contact
the spirits hopefully their sister
spirits and they're kind and nice and
they want to talk about makeup so here
we go I'd like to sell in one of the
spirits of my fellow Beauty girls
careers who've died rates
rest in peace
sister spirits are you there
show yourself if you dare
I need to be number one and kept my
views up so please come help me pick my
makeup are there any spirits with me
today hello okay let's let me try it
again
are there any sister spirits of me here
today
oh my god
I'm not moving it okay hey sister
okay spirit I'm feeling a video today I
know you're gone but my channel still
alive been doing well do you think that
you could help me maybe do a makeup for
this video today okay rude Oh will you
do it if I give you a shout-out in the
description box of this video that's
what I thought okay you guys I was able
to contact the spirits I am so excited
for this honestly truly what p degree
would ever be on this level nobody you
know I'm just gonna have this spirit do
my makeup today hello are you there okay
show me us show me a sign oh oh oh my
god i morphe m4a3 9 brush good taste
okay I'm gonna need you to drop the
attitude sphere already let's get
started
okay spirit what stuff do you want to
start off with today be our brows brows
first
this is so crazy
okay oh my gosh okay before you like
really get crazy into the problems I
just want to let you know that I used to
have really bad eyebrows a few years ago
and I killed them because they were
disgusting and needed to die I know
we're reviving you today but if you
could do me a favor and not revive the
brows they'll be great are we done oh no
okay I'm gonna take this back things Oh
kind of good okay even though we did the
brows first they kind of still low-key
look pretty good and fresh thank God you
do not make me look like old James thank
God he's done oh no offense okay what
Steph is next
lashes says I don't know what your
makeup routine is looking like but this
is a little bit backwards
are we like not doing any eyeshadow or
anything no Wow okay love a lazy ghost
this is probably why your channels dad
oh sorry I kind of had that one coming
what see oh D code Oh love my sisters
fear on a budget use cookies for 50% off
your purchase either alive or tab please
[Music]
oh that's like you Fiona
Wow it truly is so hard to find good
help these days but I guess nobody
thought to check the afterlife
oh I'm literally more scares that I only
have brows and lashes on right now than
I am
that it goes to doing my makeup so that
should show you where we're at right now
foundation time Oh what shade is it
gonna be today
vanilla oh do you think it's gonna match
me oh sorry about that oh I love a good
squirt what's that it's there's nothing
spirit here oh it's moist as a matching
lead for the smell really all right
foundation is done Oh
looking ghostly if you will no okay
okay next up concealer sorry
all ready to set my face in place oh my
gosh how rude of me Speer I forgot to
ask for your name what do I call you a
are Mary
flashback Mary no Mary it's been two
years I I wanted to move on okay Mary I
know that you really really like your
powder but I have things to do later
today so please don't do too much I
don't know what you look like in the
before life but I'm not trying to go
over like the dead contour looks though
like maybe like these two for a good
nice natural contour okay
Mary how's it been in the afterlife
needed no fish so Mary what's it like in
the afterlife need a good nose oh yeah I
could imagine there's not much worse
than that take it from me I don't know I
should ask you you're so skinny you
can't even be seen on camera the
definition of skinny legend honestly oh
no girl Kottayam James James relax
Mary
Mary I have a question for you as you
may or may not know just moved into a
beautiful brand-new house love it the
most but there's been some weird things
happening recently and I am scared that
it might be haunted please don't love
that for me well how do I find out if
it's like a good spirit or a bad spirit
I don't wanna be haunted excuse me Mary
sorry literally Mary I'll be filming and
I'll like go downstairs to get it quick
like a snack or drink of water and I'll
come back upstairs and all my makeup
will be on the floor like this ghost is
rude I think like between us I've been
looking for a personal assistant like a
lot recently so like I'm gonna do think
I could like train the ghosts to be my
personal assistant I'm not Jim like I
wake up in the morning and like get in
the shower and by the time I'm like out
of the shower like all my pillows it's
not really flying around my room like
getting back into bed kind of good wait
Mary I have a question what's it like
dating and after life have you found any
like spooky ghosts boyfriends Oh kind of
true how's your dating life big mmm not
the boss not gonna lie mr. shame yeah
still sister single
[Music]
if you were to become a ghost what would
you do a sister that's how we're a
really good question maybe like Oh
probably possess some straight boys into
like dating me pretty good idea huh oh
I'd be dad oh ah it's our look complete
oh my god let me see yet sorry I can't
no no where you going hey pearl Oh
oh my god oh my god actually not bad for
a ghost I kind of look good in fresh
yeah not after you kill me hmm yeah
sorry about that but you how to go well
speaking of having to go marry thank you
thank you so joining in this video today
thank god that's over
all right you guys I think that it's all
I have for this spooky Halloween video
today I hope I got you in the Halloween
spirit
I honestly did not think I was gonna be
able to conjure up any sister spirits
but I guess the Ouija board worked if
you guys did enjoy it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and you show yourself sis know I
already said goodbye if you have not
already do forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood it is a good and
fresh and also spooky time and I'd love
to have you join the family if you like
to follow me on my makeup journey you
can follow me on Instagram and Twitter
there bolts is James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes
types up is James Charles and extra ass
after Charles this video is a spooky
sister shout out goes to sister Haley
thank you so much love for always
following in supporting you I love you
literally so so so much and if you like
to be the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always retweet member
likes Lea go live on a Twitter also
quick little sign up if you like my
really cute sisters trunk suit that I
have going on right now there is a huge
new collection launching on sisses
apparel this Friday I am so beyond
excited I promise you guys that I was
very very serious about this and that I
was taking this holy line to the next
level and I definitely did not lie the
line launching is going to be absolutely
iconic so I hope you guys are super
excited
make sure to follow our accounts
Esther's apparel and Instagram for all
the updates regarding the collection and
don't forget to shop all pieces at
sister's apparel calm I'll write my
spooky sisters I hope you guys know this
videos today I love you so much
happy Halloween
and I will see you in the next one
goodbye
[Music]