hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back my youtube channel first
today's video I am very very excited
because we're doing something a little
bit different for me at least obviously
you guys know I don't really do reviews
that often on this YouTube channel I'm
definitely a person that six are the
same makeup products in every single
video I mean if it ain't broke don't fix
it every once in a while I make our
brand and the industry will come with a
product that is very very exciting that
everyone cannot stop talking about and
that is what happened today because of
my favorite brands of all time Anasazi
at Beverly Hills just launched their
brand new at foundation and they're
setting powder duo that get effect
that's a little scary
3 James is who Kimberly have a bill on
let's be real okay and it's no secret
that for me foundation is a little bit
of a sore subject when it comes to a
makeup routine like we've had some great
moments we've also had some really
really awful embarrassing moments I'm
not afraid to admit that I'm definitely
not a foundation export in any way shape
or form I struggle quite a lot with it
honestly but at this point I have tried
quite a lot of different foundations to
modify like my perfect foundation that
works for me so whenever a new
foundation comes out that I'm excited
about
I definitely always want to try it out
and for today's video that is exactly
what we're going to do Auto sauce they
sent over their entire shade range of
the foundations and their loose powders
and we're gonna test it out I have some
at meetings I have some phone calls and
I also have a photo shoot today so we're
doing a full we're test giving you guys
the healthy I'm brand new bodice Asya
Beverly Hills foundation
[Music]
all right you guys let's just jump right
into this review I'm so excited if
everything that I have to do today
actually this will be really good at
where test as well because it will be
wearing it all day long and also through
a photo shoot so we'll get to see how it
really photographs in front of super
high definition cameras which could be
very very scary or it could look really
really bomb Anasazi sent over these PR
packages super early this morning and if
you open it up here's what's inside if I
pull one of the shades out of the pr box
this is actually what the packaging
component looks like it is just a super
simple glass rectangular bottle which I
really really like I'm says Anasazi
Beverly Hills luminous foundation on
this side and on the other side it says
Foundation and really huge black letters
and when I first saw this I'm not gonna
lie if something did it like it it's
just something that I'm definitely never
seen before and when I thought at first
I was a little bit taken aback but I do
follow more Vita on Twitter who is the
president of Anastacio and as somebody
asked her about it and she said that
it's actually for a makeup artist
because when you pack everything in a
kit it can be really really hard to kind
of distinguish everything so if it's
labeled you know exactly what you're
grabbing for you kind of think that
that's located very very smart and
straight to the point now in each bottle
I believe there is yep one fluid ounce
of product which is definitely the
universal standard when it comes to at
foundations at this point and this will
be retailing for $38 which i think is
also like kind of the standard - I think
the 21 is $35 the two days for this way
that I always use is 38 I think the
Urban Decay one is 40 of all those
prices are right in my head for some
reason so it definitely is like an
average price point in terms of the
other foundations of the top-tier brands
now in terms of shade into this
foundation that there are five different
categories fair light medium tan and
deep and they come in a 50 different
shades which i think is so what's so
beyond incredible there's not a single
skip or gap in between there's a nice
beautiful ombre from super super pale to
super super dark and everybody I'm sure
I can find a shade somewhere in here
hopefully we include it because you guys
know that I struggled quite a lot but I
think this is really really important so
many brands heard about the makeup
industry or coming out with that
foundation lines with like I super pale
white color and then a dark brown and
are like oh my God we're inclusive what
do you do but in reality there's like 12
shades and
undertones are all off all inclusivity
means that literally anybody can go to
the line and anybody can find their
color and I think that it's very very
important I'm not gonna swatch all 50
shades because I don't think that's
showcasing the deeper skin tones on my
skin tone is gonna help literally
anybody purchasing it duh but I do want
to give some quick love to Nima tang and
Alissa Ashley they have some of my
favorite foundation reviews for women of
color and also make up Tiffany J just
because I freaking love her and I've
been obsessed watching her videos
recently if you guys want to check out
their videos on this foundation I'm sure
they'll be up very very soon I wanna
quickly go over the claims before we
actually put the foundation on the
anasazi Beverly Hills luminous
foundation is water-resistant long
wearing with a medium coverage formula
okay it gives the complexion a fresh
already a lot with a lightweight second
skin feeling it is a no flashback
formula we will definitely be testing
that with our photo shoot later on today
it is suitable for all skin types
including sensitive skin which you know
is very very important for a lot of your
sisters out there it is clinically
tested dermatologist tested and the
formula is also cruelty free and vegan
lastly before we actually get into our
makeup application I know this intro is
very very long at associate also
launched their brand new setting powders
as well which I'm a very very powerful
and will be using in this video it comes
in at 5 at different change which i
think is actually really really cool we
have the shade of vanilla for light skin
tones we have banana for medium skin
tones we have deep peach for tan skin
tones we have golden orange or deep skin
tones
that we also have a translucent which is
the universal shade for everybody
wow that's some good balancing right
there look at the on associate setting
powder is a lightweight silky powder
that sets makeup with a flawless matte
finish so hopefully there will be no
shine fingers crossed it delivers a long
wearing of that to the makeup okay we
will test that today and see hopefully
it wants to do many touch-ups
it has clinically tested and also
cruelty-free and vegan and this setting
powder will retail for $36 which is just
like Dee Foundation is very like average
pricing oh my god okay the intro is
finally done
this is why I don't do reviews okay that
was like three hours of me just talking
and stuttering and trying to say the
same thing over no too much information
this is why I just like to put on the
makeup and call it a day but I'm so
excited to actually get into this in
China but now we have another challenge
but if we actually get into our makeup
and that is color
this should be interesting
okay so we have the two hundredths which
definite looks like it could be bad for
me we had the three hundredths which is
too dark I feel like definitely we have
the 100's which I feel like are two
lights we have the five hundreds which
are definitely not right I'm gonna go
ahead and test some of the trades in the
light category we have 160 200 210 220
and 240 and see if any of them are a
good match for me let's try it 160 on my
hand it looks a little bit light on my
face it looks a little bit light on my
chest it looks a little bit too yellow
let's try 200 W now my hand also looks
way too light on my face it looks too
light and on my chest it looks not great
let's try 2 10 neutral under told us a
little bit better but it still looks a
little bit too light on my hand on my
face it looks not anywhere close to
anything on my chest the undertone looks
definitely better but still no let's try
220 neutral let's go a little bit darker
honestly yeah okay let's try 250 oh wow
that like blends in with my neck so well
kind of ish maybe not
I mixed together 250 and 220 let's see
how this looks that looks really good
that undertone looks really good yeah
okay we're going with that one okay out
of all the things that we try it I think
I'm actually going to end up going with
315 and neutral which is a lot darker
than I thought it would be but as you
can see this color matches my hand
almost like exactly and once I blend and
weigh down on my neck it's gonna match
touch my body - like I said this process
is very very irritating and frustrating
for me to deal with but you gotta do it
you gotta do I'm gonna stuff with just
my touch out water cream to moisturize
my face before I go ahead and put on the
foundation and then describing a tiny
little bit of the dragon Beauty color
corrector just to cover over some beard
areas just like I normally do finally
let's go ahead and put this on I'm going
to spot my face in half and do a Beauty
Blender on one side and a brush on the
other
both of these are from morphe which you
guys can use KO james for 10% off and
will see it which one it looks better
well that actually looks like a really
good color the foundation claims to be
lightweight and medium coverage which i
will say it is building up really really
nicely and it is covering over the color
corrector which is obviously important
because we don't want orange
shining through the points just to
cancel out those gray tones you
definitely can still see my freckles and
a beauty marks to the foundation which I
really really do like but it is doing a
great job with evening everything out
which is obviously the point of a medium
coverage okay it's definitely feeling
really really nice on the skin it does
not feel super heavy it just like it
cleaned which is obviously it really
really good and I feel like it did a
good job of evening everything out
covering everything it looks really
really Bob okay let's go ahead and try
out the brush on the other side I've
honestly always just been so confused
and also jealous of people who are able
to use a foundation brush and like do
their foundation no matter how much I
blend it out I always feel like I need a
Beauty Blender to go and just like make
everything look like perfect and get rid
of brush strokes like is that just me
like am i literally crazy I'm definitely
a Beauty Blender type of person no we
just have to blown this down really
really far in here okay you guys so this
is how the audition looks on the scan at
with a Beauty Blender on one side and a
foundation brush on the other oh wow
okay we are close up and ready to go how
it looks really really pretty it
definitely is luminous just like it
claims but it doesn't look like gross
oily I definitely will be setting this
down with a powder and a few minutes but
this is off to a really really good
start I definitely do agree that it is
medium coverage even everything got
really nicely but you can still see my
freckles popping through there is this
pimple popping through which is annoying
me but I wonder if I add just a little
bit more if it like buildup oh yeah it
does okay so it is definitely buildable
- this is good advice let's do a
concealer quickly for concealer that's
always I'm just gonna grab my shape tape
and highlight the middle points of my
face
all right you because that is everything
all blended out the concealer layer over
top of everything are really really
nicely at nothing weird at all and the
foundation is looking at so what's so
beautiful at this point but I do want to
go ahead and set it and please so we're
gonna test out the brand-new Anastasio
setting powders as well I'm gonna
prescribe this shade at vanilla because
these can be used for brighten a I don't
know why that I love how big these jars
are it feels very luxurious I'm just
gonna dip in my beauty sponge into that
powder and pop this right underneath the
eye to do some nice bright at night
wondering how brightening this actually
is that could've been a mistake could
also put this right in the middle of my
forehead
has not to always work its most Whaley
well that modified things really quickly
what Chrissy was kind of like in the
center of my face then it's gonna grab
the translucent shade and with a fluffy
brush that's gonna dip into this and
he's just too sad do you rest of my face
in place okay so they were not kidding
when they said that it would be very mad
wow I'm just gonna get myself a quick
spritz of the anastacio doing setting
spray just because this is the Luminess
of foundation and if i assume you guys n
this is what the foundation is looking
like now that is all set in place it is
setting on the scanner so nicely there's
no creasing at no fine lines no texture
this is good okay you guys so this is
pretty much the base routine all
complete and I will say right now I'm
really really liking how it looks but I
have a full face of makeup now to add on
to this but for my photo shoot which I'm
not running very very late for so I'm
going to go into that off camera quickly
I will check in with the finished look
and about an hour for now and then we
will continue checking in throughout the
day to see if it continues to look
really really good or this could turn
into a major fail later on we're going
to find out together
all right you guys of your gawk and this
is the finished look all complete this
is not a special look it is for the
photo shoot like I said obviously we're
focusing on the foundation and as of
right now I think it looks so what's so
beautiful it is currently 2:30 oh you
can't even see it it is currently 231
p.m. you're gonna have to trust me on
this one I started this video about two
hours ago now but I did have to take
about a 30 minute break for a phone call
meeting and through talking through the
entire thing I did not get any creases
the foundation still looks really really
beautiful I am getting a little bit of
shine right here in this area which I
don't love but it is a luminous
foundation which is a little bit
different for me so I'm going to go into
this open-minded and just hope that it
doesn't get really really bad later on
if it stays like this I'll be super
super happy okay guys and here's how it
looks in it natural lighting - honestly
you guys I think it looks
so it's so good I don't know jinx that
comes me believe it but a little how
about but it looks so Bob and the color
like guys let them out this is rare how
would you say my foundations looking so
far I'm doing a little review today okay
it looks really good it looks like a
good match okay so about four hours and
right now this is pretty good for four
hours yeah great
hello blog is coming 6:42 p.m. we just
finished our photo shoot and I was super
hungry because they realize I forgot to
eat today don't do that kids it's not
good for you I thought I'd be really
keen to just like take some photos with
my McFlurry and my french fries but I
wanted to do a quick little check in
because as I was looking through the
photos of her a little at McDonald's
parking lot photo shoot that we have
going on right now the first thing that
I noticed was my skin was looking really
really good and I'm very excited about
that the foundation has been on for
about seven hours by now it was also
okay about 105 degrees in California
today which was absolutely disgusting
I was literally sweating and deimos
during my photo shoot TMI start you
didn't know that but you do because it's
a foundation review I didn't do any
touch-ups but I did have to like blow
myself a tiny little bit with the napkin
earlier it's really hard being Instagram
model you but point being it still looks
really bomb we are seven hours in at the
foundation wear test it's going pretty
well
if I look in the mirror I'm not really
seeing any creases aside from just this
one in at my mouth region but I get that
all the time
my nose region is getting a little bit
oily if this happens literally every
foundation that I've ever worn it but
it's not bad so I really happy what do
you guys think you can't answer that
joke then you put over in the comments
Peter on let's get out of here this is a
vas
Oh like hell are you kidding all right
sisters we are finally back home after a
very very long a but super super
productive day I cannot wait for you
guys to see what we've been working on
it is currently 1108 p.m. at night that
is how p.m. maids oh my god
I am beyond exhausted and this makeup
has been on for 11 hours now and it's
time to give you guys my final thoughts
I am pretty sure you guys can guess one
thing about this foundation since I
definitely have made it really obvious
to all the check-ins today but I do want
to give you guys just a quick little
sister summary my skin definitely is
getting pretty oily in a few different
places it specifically at my nose region
right here on like my under eye cheek
type of region and then kind of above
the brow bone in the center of the
forehead this is pretty typical for my
skin no matter what foundation they're
wearing especially if I don't do stop
shops throughout the day which I
normally do obviously for this review I
did not so I could give you guys the
unfiltered result but concerned this is
a luminous foundation I really don't
think it looks bad at all I think this
is exactly what the foundation claimed
to do and if I'm being honest I don't
even think the oiliness looks not bad
personally I would definitely take a
little bit of powder and touch up this
face but I know a lot of people do
prefer a more dewy
natural skin like type of finish so for
those of you guys I think this
foundation will be absolutely perfect
and this is definitely thing that I'll
be adding to my kit and using a lot more
often all right you guys that I think
that is pretty much everything that I
have for today is a brand new video I'm
trying to make sure that I didn't forget
anything but I think we're pretty much
all good if you enjoyed it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and show your love and support it
would really mean a lot to me and also
leaving a comment down below and let me
know if you actually like seeing me do
or reviews let me know if this was
helpful let me know if you are intrigued
and you want to try it out I'm
definitely looking forward to hearing
you guys as thoughts
I obviously love trying out new makeup
products and would love to do these
videos more often of course only if you
guys want to see them as well if you
have not already make sure to click that
big red subscribe button down below and
come join these sister here almost 16
million cysts are strong I hope to have
you join the family and also click that
belt like button so you could be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me and I
makeup turned you can follow me and
secure with Twitter their posters James
Charles my snapchat for more behind the
seat sites as she has Charles that extra
us after Charles and my twitch for
gaming content is Jay Charles beauty
this video of sisters how to close the
sister and thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting here in
love we literally so so so much and if
you'd like to the next videos a sister
shadow don't forget to always reach a
vitiligo live on Twitter and also try to
my youtube post notifications thank you
so much for watching this videos today I
love you and I will see you in at the
next one
[Music]