hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
cutting straight to the point
hello everybody we are back and we are
sitting down for episode two of this
mini makeover series
if you have not yet checked out episode
one which is last week's video this mini
makeover series make sure to click up
here or up here I'm not sure what side
it's on where we got my makeup done at
Sephora it was so much fun for today's
video we're going to be going to match
to get the same full glam makeover I
made my appointment and we're gonna be
heading out in a few minutes but before
we do that I definitely wanna make a few
quick disclaimers because some people
majorly missed the point of last week's
video and this entire series while a lot
of you guys definitely loved the first
makeover video if there was a lot of
people that misinterpreted the point of
the video first of all I can't even
reiterate how many times I've said it
throughout the video but apparently
y'all's ears were closed the artists in
the video asked for word did such an
amazing job I'm gonna leave the artists
Instagram right here her name is crystal
marine go like her last post and go
comment saying sister James sent you and
show her the love because she did such
an amazing job and I don't know why so
many people were thinking that the point
of the video was for me to shine on her
because it was not during prom season of
all season event season and wedding
season so many people go to these
various different stores and get their
makeup done in order to feel beautiful
and confident on their special day at
the end of each makeover we're gonna
come right back here I'm going to show
you guys the finished look and then
we're going to talk about it every
different makeup store trains their
artists in different ways and every
artist has different styles and
techniques that they do makeup in which
is why I think that this series is such
a cool and fun idea to be able to
showcase different artists different
styles and different techniques and then
how they may differ from my very own
that you guys get to see all the time
obviously I'm not gonna like everything
that they do on me and if I was to do
the makeup on them I'm sure they would
not like everything that I was gonna do
on them either and that is totally okay
I'm not gonna sit here and drag any
artists because the whole point of
getting your makeup done is to have a
different style than your own which is
the whole fun behind it but I will talk
about things that I would have done
differently or preferred so therefore
you guys are watching me from makeup
tips can get a rough idea of what your
makeup or experience may be like if you
want to get your glam done at one of
these places so you can make it more
educated decision next time you have a
special event to go to and finally
before we get this video started the
last thing I want to address is the
comment about me of being treated like a
normal customer at Sephora I want to be
able to give you guys an accurate
rotation of what a normal makeover at
one of these stores may look like but
that can sometimes do you really really
hard when the employees know who you are
there have definitely been times in the
past where I've walked into various
different makeup stores and have been
greeted with special treatment I've seen
a lot of different products before they
actually hit the shelves I've gotten
products that were supposed to be out of
stock and I've also gotten different
things for free because of my name I do
want to apologize if I came out as
entitled or conceited in the last video
I definitely missed the mark on what I
wanted to say so I'm very very sorry for
that I do not think of myself as any
higher than any other artist I'm just a
normal HTML kid with a few blending
brushes like my Instagram bio says but I
did want to address that because it has
happened in the past it's just the
reality of the situation it's really not
that deep all about being sent though
there is no denying that I have worked
my ass off to become a name in this
industry if you hate me if you hate my
videos if you hate the way I do my
makeup if you hate the way I talk that's
totally fine but word of advice stop
watching my videos stop commenting and
stop talking about me because you're the
ones keeping me relevant on that
trending page I'm alright that is
everything I have to say I hope that
cleared everything up and without
further ado let's head over to Mac and
get our damn makeup done alright guys so
we are back home from our Mac make over
my appointment was at 4 o'clock today
and we just got home and is currently
601 actually and was about 15 minutes of
travel time there and back it was
probably about an hour and a half
appointment total so it definitely not
bad for a full glam make over my artist
today was named Helen and you can find
her an Instagram and I heart Helen
definitely go show her all the love from
his sisters tell her sister James sent
you she was so sweet and so nice and
just like the last video my artist did
not know who I was and one point she
asked me if I was a youtuber and I was
like yes girl but I only have a small
channel which may have been a little bit
of apply because all your sisters out
there know how big we have become we are
so close to 2 million subscribers so
definitely click that subscribe button
if you have not already but she was so
sweet and so nice without further ado
let's pull in this mirror and look at
this makeup a super close-up so before
we actually went in and started on at
the glam makeup today I showed my artist
a picture of two makeup look that I
wanted being the same exact one from the
last video I'm Jacqueline Hale it is
right here just in case you need a
little bit of a reminder but I'm gonna
be asking for the
same look from all the different places
that might go I know a lot of you guys
in the last video we're definitely
commenting that it was kind of stupid
for me to just tell the artist to do
whatever they want because as the client
you are definitely supposed to ask for
what you want in order for the artist to
give it to you which I agree with so
once I showed her the photo I clarified
that I wanted book Herbert Foundation a
lot of glow
not too much bronzer and a more snatched
nose and she said okay to all those
things which I thought was really really
great to give her a little bit in board
direction based on my personal
preferences so therefore the end result
won't be judged on personal preference
things because a lot of people were
really mad about that in the last video
don't worry I got you
so the first thing that she did was
start off with priming my face and she
actually used a Mac of BB cream which is
saying that I've never seen done before
she said it was a light and sticky base
to make the skin a more natural and even
off the route for the foundation process
later on she next one into my brows
using a Mac brow pencil and I honestly
really really like how the brows turned
out I felt like she added a really
really nice perk she definitely did not
make them too thick and I definitely
love love love all the love that she
defined the tail and pulled it out as
well as many of you guys know I've
recently been try to make my tails more
out as opposed to more down which allows
for a lot more eyeshadow shape these
furrows are definitely a huge win in my
book next was the eyes then she first
started off by priming them using the
Mac painterly paint-pot
which is a Paint Pot that like literally
every beauty guru in the entire world
uses except for me for some reason
I have no vendetta against it I just
have never actually gotten around to
buying one but she used it today and I
think it worked beautifully as a
eyeshadow base I really do plan on
trying it out eventually I sort of go
ahead and then for the eye shadows today
she used the Mac single shadows in the
shade soft and gentle brown script I'm
into it Swiss chocolate sweet heat and
nylon and this my look is really really
good looking at the eye shadow close-up
I am so so chef this honestly looks
really really good as you guys can see
there was a really really smooth and
even transition between of course the
problem highly the transition shade the
deeper shade in the crease the darker
shade in the outer corner and then even
there's a smooth transition between the
metallic shade on the lid which is so so
well done she even went ahead and added
a black winged liner to this look I'm
actually not even sure if Jacqueline has
a wing on in the original photo you
really can't tell based on the angle
that her face and
is that but she went ahead and out of it
anyway and this liner is so good too
she used a gel liner which I was really
really spooked about when she pulled it
out because doing a really really even
and tiny precise winged liner with a gel
is not the easiest thing in the world
but she absolutely slated this liner
it's ready to cut a [ __ ] that is for
sure on the lower waterline she lines
that using a block I call it and then
blend it out using the brown script
eyeshadow I believe I don't think once
again in the photo of Jacqueline she has
black in her water line but it
definitely is a very very smoky look and
I really really love how this turned on
as well I actually think I prefer this
over the light water line I haven't done
black in the water line for a smoky look
in the longest time ever but honestly I
really really missed this because it
makes my eyes well my contacts pop so so
much when it came to the lashes once
again I did ask for falsies and I didn't
catch the name of these ones
unfortunately but they were Mac branded
and I was really really spooked because
they were like the original size and I
was like girl my eyes are very very tiny
I usually cut a lot off the lashes and
she measured him and she's like oh
you're fine and I was like woah okay but
she actually glued on the full band and
she glued them on so well I don't know
what she did I don't know what she used
but I need her to glue my lashes
everyday because they looked so good I
literally cannot feel them either and I
have no idea like how this is even going
on the way eyes right now but I'm not
even gonna ask questions I'm just gonna
appreciate the thought that somebody was
able to glue and a full eyelash onto my
eyelid and it feels amazing after the
eyes came the base makeup and like I
told you guys I definitely did ask for a
fall Carmen foundation scioscia end of
the Studio Fix fluid foundation which is
definitely full coverage if you are
familiar with Mac products and she mix
together the shades NW 13 and C 4 and I
think that this is one of the best
foundation not just I have ever had in
my entire life she then went ahead and
used the lightest shade in the Mac Pro
conceal palette to highlight under my
eyes and in the center of the forehead
and she actually blended out this entire
look using one of those triangular throw
out Beauty sponges which I was so so
surprised and impressed by obviously at
places like Sephora or alter you're
gonna have Beauty blenders but obviously
Mac it does not have those so I was so
impressed that she somehow managed to
get such an even and go to blend using
those tiny-ass drugstore sponges so once
the foundation and concealer were all on
and blended out she went ahead and set
my face using the Mac prep
powder which I will say is not my
favorite looking closely at Lumiere it
definitely is starting to wear down a
little bit under my eyes as you can see
there's some creases up in this region
and then also around the mouth and if I
touch my face it is a little bit tacky
this is totally personal preference but
I do wish she would have applied a
little bit more powder to my face to
really lock it in place and make sure it
stayed all night long because if I was
wearing this out I feel like I
definitely would start to sweat the
makeup off a little bit
next it was hard to contour my face and
once she was doing it I couldn't help
but wonder what she was using because I
had never seen it before
it was there blotting powder in the
darkest shade when I asked she told me
was because it was a cool tone shade
which really obviously helps to sculpt
the face but it doesn't really have that
much covered so it allows for a really
really light and blended out contour
that looks almost natural and girl when
she told me that I was so shocked
because I did such a good idea
and as you can see it this contour looks
amazing she then used that same a dark
blotting powder to contour my nose which
I was so excited about obviously in the
last video my nose looked a little bit
big because I did not ask her to be
contoured but when I asked this time she
was very very happy too can we I
snatched nose looking at in the mirror I
do wish she would have pulled the lines
a little bit closer together to make it
more and more snatched appearance but
that's totally personal preference and
when she was highlighting she did use
that tiny pencil brush like I always do
to draw a very very thin lie I know the
highlighter looks a little bit bigger
now but that's a sweat and oil Mountain
highlighter I promised it looked really
good at the time once the contour was
all on and nice and slayed she went into
the blush and for today's look she's the
Mac blush in the shade peaches and I was
literally so so excited to see her pull
it out I said not asked for I did not
request it but as many of you guys know
that is literally my favorite blush and
the only blush that I ever wear in my
looks it is such a beautiful warm tone
peachy orange shade that I absolutely
love and she was so shook and she told
me that it was one of her favorites as
well and I thought it paired perfectly
with this look so next came the glow and
she was the Mac highlighter in the shade
soft and gentle which made my heart so
so warm because that's actually the
first highlighter that I ever ever used
on myself I used to use that same eye
harder every single damn day for every
look that I ever did because I could not
afford to buy another one so it has a
very very special place in my heart and
it is still to this day one of my
all-time favorite highlighter shades
looking at my face in the mirror I will
say that she definitely stuck by the
name of the
later being soft and gentle it
definitely is a subtle like glowing from
within type of look and based on the
picture with Jacqueline you can
definitely see that her highlight is
blinding and you guys know I love a
blinding Harley as well so I will say
that I wished she applied a little bit
more highlighter last certainly not
least she went and did my lip study
using the matte burgundy lip liner and
then filled them and using the
carnivorous liquid lipstick looking at
my entire face I think that the lips are
probably my least favorite part of this
look today I do like the color that she
chose I feel as though it is a pretty
close match to that original picture
that Jacqueline wore but I'm not the
biggest fan of the shape before she went
started my lips I did tell her that I do
like my top lip a little bit over life
it is one of my favorite things to do my
makeup techniques especially because I
feel like my lips are a little bit
uneven so over lining them allows me to
get a really really even and perfect lip
shape but when she applied it I feel
like she actually underlined my lips a
little bit you can almost get a tiny
little border surrounding almost the
entire lips of where there is lips but
no actual makeup product which is
definitely not my favorite thing in the
entire world this is the finished look
and I honestly it was love how it turned
out I am so Chuck in a good way
that's for sure going into box today all
the employees were so so nice and my
artist like I said Helen was so kind so
sweet very very comforting and also
really really talented as you guys can
see she's only that she didn't working
it back for the last ten years which I
was so so impressed by and as you can
see her skill level and experience
definitely reflects back in the makeup
thinking about my full experience today
at Mac and looking at my makeup in the
mirror I would rate today's makeover a 9
out of 10 the only two things that
really docked points today like I
excited to be the setting partner I do
wish she applied a little bit more
essentially like around my smile lines
under my eyes because I am definitely
getting a few creases and there and I do
feel a little bit oily and also the lips
I do wish you would have lined them a
little bit more to over line them or at
least even follow my natural lip line I
feel as though they are a little bit
underlying which isn't the most
flattering for my face but neither one
of these two things are deal-breakers
and this makeover was so successful in
my eyes at least alright guys and that
is all I have for this video today
definitely leave a comment down below
and tell me what you think of this
makeover do you love it do you hate it
and my opinion I think sister Helen
absolutely killed it she did such a good
job and I loved so many elements of this
makeup look definitely go check out her
Instagram and go show her some love if
you guys did enjoy today's video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
below Instagram you have not already
doing the sisterhood and click that
little bell icon so you can be notified
every time I upload a new video if you'd
like to follow me on a makeup journey
you can follow me on answered with
Twitter if they're polls just James
Charles and my snapchat from overhead
and seen things up is James Charles the
next you're asked after Charles this
successor shadow goes to a sister Kimora
thank you so much paper always falling
in supporting I love you so much and if
you would like to be at next week's
sister shout out make sure to always
retweet and share my video links when
they go live alright guys that is all I
have for this video today don't forget
to check out part 1 if you have not yet
seen it where I get and makeup done at
Sephora it was so much fun to do it'll
be linked in the description down below
these videos are so much fun to film and
get to see different perspectives on how
different artists do my own makeup and
don't forget to stay tuned for my next
video where I get my makeup done at Ulta
as well and then we're going to talk
about all the makeup looks I'm gonna do
the makeup look on myself and I'll tell
you guys which out of the three that I
recommend the most love you sisters so
much thank you for watching and I'll see
you in the next one
[Music]