hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
not only welcome back to my channel but
also welcome back to a sister upload
week if you have no idea what's going on
I've been uploading every single day
this week it has been so much work but
it has also been so much fun to put out
so much condit for you guys that I'm
honestly really really loving it well I
do it ever again definitely not but it's
fun well it's lasting if you guys and I
have checked out all the videos that
have gone up for the past few days and
make sure to check them out they'll be
linked down below and in the sidebar
probably somewhere over there I'm not
really sure check out the channel
welcome to the sisterhood sick everybody
I'm not ready for today's video I am so
so pumped because today is the finale of
my little mini makeover series as you
guys know I am a beauty guru and it is
my job to do my own makeup almost every
single day but I rarely ever get my
makeup done by other artists last week I
started a super fun at makeover series
on my channel where I went to Sephora
Mac and Ulta and got my makeup done at
all three locations I asked for this
picture right here of Jaclyn hill I'm
not gonna forget it this time and each
time came up with a very very different
result getting these mini glam makeovers
and showing you guys the results was
honestly so much fun and so cool to see
all the different artists different
styles and techniques that they use on
me I honestly learned so so much but so
many of you guys were saying that for
the finale you guys wanted to see me do
the look on myself and do how I would
normally do the same exact look so for
today's video that is exactly what we're
doing I'm gonna be recreating that same
exact look from Jaclyn hill on myself
are gonna be talking about all three
makeovers and my own makeover we're
gonna be comparing them all talking
about the prices talking about the
products talking about the truth tea
whatsoever I recommend you guys to go to
if you have a very special event so
without further ado let's go ahead and
get glam for one last time for this mini
makeover series grand finale
[Music]
for my first step of my makeup routine
today I'm gonna grab the top out water
cream which is my all-time favorite
moisturizer I absolutely love using
moisturizer before my foundation and I
think a really really good skin care
routine is absolutely vital to a really
successful makeup routine and the places
that did that were Ulta and Sephora
before my makeover so major props to
them for that one side face is already a
nice and moisturized
of course my next step is going to be a
foundation and for today's economies in
the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD stick and
I am in the shade y2 45 right now the
makeup forever stick is definitely my
all-time pure foundations if you guys
been subscribed me for a while you know
that I've been using it for a very very
long time just as a reminder when I went
to Sephora the artists use the bare
minerals foundation on me when I went to
macrame artists used of course the Mac
Studio Fix fluid and when I went to Ulta
they used Born This Way and born swings
actually one of my all-time favorites as
well but the color was not exactly the
best match you guys know that I
definitely live a very very full
coverage type of base even when I do my
more light natural looks I still like a
very very full coverage foundation
because I do have pretty uneven skin
naturally and as well in the picture
that Jacqueline posted she is definitely
full beat glam there's no questions
about it so I feel like we definitely
needed a very very full coverage
foundation to match this look today for
consider today of course I'm going to
using my heart shape tube concealer you
guys don't this is my all-time favorite
and I'm in the shade light sand I'm just
gonna apply this underneath my eyes on
the sides of my nose for the snatch look
when it comes to contouring and all the
high points of my face just to add a lot
of dimension and my Sephora makeover my
artists use the NARS radiant creamy
concealer and iMac makeover my artists
use the new Mac Pro Longwear concealer
and it might also make over my artist
use that arch shape tape just like I'm
using right now so honestly we had a
really really good selection of
concealers in all the different places
that we went to then I'm gonna pond this
in it very very well using a damp Beauty
Blender unfortunately we have no
triangular makeup sponges today Mac's
gonna take my damp Beauty Blender and
dip it into my Laura Mercier translucent
setting powder and just use this to set
my entire face and like my foundation in
place and my Sephora makeover my artists
use this powder which as you guys know
is my all-time favorite have I Mac
makeovers to use the Mac translucent
setting powder which spoiler alert I
absolutely hated that a my Ulta makeover
he used the it cosmetics trust as a
setting powder which I literally did not
even know it
said.but worked fine next to come onto
my face today I'm gonna grab my Kat Von
D shade and light palette a breeze my
morphe m14 one brush and dip into it the
last shade and that's tiny bit into the
middle shade and use this to it chisel
out my cheekbones in the photo that
Jacqueline posted she definitely had a
very very light and soft contour which
honestly is not really my cup of tea you
guys know that I love a good snatched
cheekbone a very very chiseled jawline
and definitely a contoured and lowered
forehead that is for sure
but obviously we're doing our best to
recreate the photos today so I'm gonna
go very very light on the contour powder
and make sure not to go too too crazy
and I support make over my artist use
the hourglass ambient lighting bronzer
to contour my face which I thought was a
little bit weird first of all I didn't
know it existed which obviously means
nothing but I felt as though it was a
little bit of a shimmery product which
is kind of weird for bronzer it
definitely was more of like a bronze or
harlot combo rather than a contour so I
do wish it was a little bit more chilled
out and a more cool toned softer type of
situation and Mac my artist actually
used the Mac of blotting powders in the
darkest shade which I thought was so so
cool because she used blotting powders
instead of an actual bronzer or contour
it gave her a really really light washed
a color which i thought was super super
dope I've never seen that done before
and I think that by adding that light
wash the color instead of like the
intense bronzer in contour and by far
gave that contour the most accurate to
the original picture of Jacqueline and I
loved how it looked and then finally for
the ultimate over my artists use the
anasazi Beverly Hills contour kit this
is definitely one my all-time favorites
their products are so good and blend out
so smoothly it wasn't the best contra
but it also wasn't the worst now when it
comes to the nose I'm using a morphe
m4a3 3 brush in the same exact shades
from the Kat Von D shade and light
palette and I'm drawing my nose contour
very very tight together I'm not gonna
talk about my nose contour in respect to
my Sephora makeover because I did not
ask for it to be contoured which is
definitely my faults that one is out of
the picture but I did ask for a pinched
nose contour at both Mac and Ulta and I
think that the result of both were
honestly not the best it is definitely
not like the nose contour and Mac or
Alta looked bad by any means it
literally took me a year to figure out
how to actually contour my nose and make
it look decent rather than just editing
it in every single photo so I really
don't blame them at all
but I definitely do think it both
makeovers if I say pinched nose it could
have been a little bit smaller and then
once again get er done by Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder and my damp
Beauty Blender and I'm going to lightly
my face to really intensify in my nose
contour and my cheekbone contour I
personally don't think it's that weird
that none of the artists chose to bake
me today honestly a lot of people think
that it's really really stupid and
doesn't really make a difference I
personally do see a difference
especially when it comes like the nose
contour baking the sides my nose has
literally changed my nose contour for
the better but I don't blame them baking
is obviously a technique that started
from dry-cleans and is slowly trickled
its way until I can online social media
makeup but I feel like hasn't fully
integrated into like the regular beauty
world so I don't really think it's that
strange I ever won like I said I do love
baking so I'm just gonna do it on up
myself today
to really intensify those highlights all
right so while my face is baking in the
oven at 350 degrees I'm gonna go into my
brows and for today's also gonna use my
benefit precisely my brow pencil I
always terrify brows are drawing little
hair like strokes in the center just to
add a little bit of dimension and fill
them in slightly but not make them super
super defined and then I'll just go in
and start doing the tail all the tail
more out as opposed to down this design
that I actually recently changed my brow
routine too but I feel good is honestly
made the world of her difference it
makes my brows look more arch with stare
for it just gives me a more like lifted
and pretty look to my face and it also
gives me a lot more room for eyeshadow
so I feel like drawing them out is my
new favorite brow trick and it just
flatters my face really really well for
both my Sephora and Ulta makeovers my
artists use the anasazi at Brown to
finer to define at my brows and for my
Mac makeover she use the Mac brow pencil
which I've actually never used before
brows are definitely a really really
personal thing when it comes to makeup I
feel like things such as like base
makeup contouring highlighting and then
like eyeshadow or very much like one
style fits most type of situation but
brows like frame the entire face they
can change your entire facial shape or
structure or expression so I feel like
brows are like a very very vital thing
and are very very personal which is
probably why I didn't really like any of
the brows for employee restore and I
definitely do how much to what I would
normally do I don't think any of the
eyebrows were particularly bad all of
the Ulta one definitely could have had a
little bit more attention paid to them
but I just think they weren't really my
style and then just gonna go to my
benefit give me a brow gel just to brush
through all those hairs and lock them in
place you guys know that I am definitely
someone who has a lot of eyebrows that
is for sure so I always like to use a
brow so just make sure those hairs are
not gonna go
anywhere and they're gonna say it nice
and defined all day long so once my
eyebrows are almost laid and in place on
my eyelids are all primed and ready to
go for shadow and of course gonna do the
eyes and for today's like I'm gonna use
the brand new morphe 15 D which is the
day Slayer palette I'm first gonna grab
the shade in the crease I'm I am 513
brush and put that shade in the crease
Alexson use the m4 3/3 brush in the
shade editor and use that to deepen up
the crease and the outer corner add my
Sephora makeover my artists use the
Sephora Pro palette in the warm tones
and by Mac makeover she used individual
shadows and I my ultimate go over here
use the Anasazi of Modern Renaissance
palette I felt a so for the actual color
of this eye look none of the makeovers
actually were that accurate to the
original I feel like all three of them
turned out very very red in the end
whereas this look is obviously super
super orange which is a little bit weird
I remember at the Sephora makeover the
honest I don't look was actually done
really really well but the gold shadow
used for the actual lid was just a
really strange color that didn't match
very well my Mac makeover I think was
the best eye shadow look overall it
looked very very beautiful and
well-planned it and then my Alta
makeover I felt like my artist used the
closest technique to the original but it
was just a really really weird at crease
shape I'm exited I might add one to four
which is just a small Packer brush and
dip into the shade mob and use this to
it deepen up that outer V that are
sitting on my m4 33 one more time for my
last step and go over those edges to
make sure that there are no harsh lines
they're gonna grab the brand-new morphia
cream shadow in the shade of bronze this
from the new holiday collection you guys
have to check these out and I'm gonna
use that to carve out the lid and then
just add a little bit more glitter to
make it pop we're gonna grab the Urban
Decay heavy metal liquid glitter liner
and just pop a tiny bit of that on the
lid when I came to the actual lid my
alte artist was the only one who
actually embraced the whole half cut
crease type of situation which was
definitely going on in the Jacqueline
photo but even still all three artists
only use it I shadow for the actual base
I found that a little bit weird because
in the photo of Joplin you can
definitely tell it there is a little bit
of a glitter situation going on I was
disappointed in the lid situation to all
three different locations especially
Sephora and Ulta because the steel and
liquid metals things are sold in both
locations and those are so beyond
beautiful I use those for almost all my
concrete's and they're extremely
glittery as well so I do wish something
a little bit more glittery or true to
the original photo was used so that is
why we're going extra glam
today for the lower lash seven person
we're going to add four three three
brush and the shade editor and just buff
that in and then just using ym5 13 brush
that i have my original transition shade
on I'm gonna go over those edges to make
sure they are really really blended out
I'm then gonna grab an Abbott one five
one brush into the shade mauve and I'm
going to use is to hug at the waterline
and then I'm just gonna line my lower
waterline today using the pretty vulgar
pencil and obviously the nude shade I
definitely like a good and new water
line I feels like it opens up the eye a
lot so now that the eye is all done the
next up is obviously going to be the
eyelashes and for today I picked up
through Billie washes in the style Doha
I feel so these are the closest pair
that I have that looks close to what
Jacqueline was wearing so I'm just gonna
pop on this one today for my Sephora
makeover I was given a Sephora brand
lash fry Mac makeover I was given a Mac
brand lash and for my ultimate over I
had it in our Dell brand lash all the
lashes were actually applied like the
artists all had a really good knowledge
of how to apply that right to the lash
line and how to make it the glue like
knock it I'll walk Ian sucked my eye
clearly I don't have that knowledge
because I'm having a lot of trouble
putting this on right now
lashes are Selma at least a part of my
makeup routine because they're always
are really really wonky free I don't
know what it is but I can just never get
okay example uh there are no gaps that
are comfortable to wear which is amazing
but I felt as though all three
lifestyles were not really that close to
the ones that Jacqueline had on and I
would definitely not choose wear any of
them again alright guys that is when I
all complete I'm gonna go ahead and
quickly do the other one on off-camera
to save some time and I'll be right back
to finish off the rest of this love
alright guys and those are both eyes off
complete and the next step is going to
be of course the glow before we go in
and actually play anyhow later today I'm
gonna play a light spritz of these skins
a navy eye makeup finishing spray I
always like to apply a little bit of
settings right before I apply my
highlighter just so it's really really
vibrant and of course you guys know I'm
gonna use my Anasazi illuminator and so
Hollywood and my morphe M 501 brush so
my artists at both Ulta and Sephora use
the chocolate health elaboration with
Becca cosmetics champagne pop
highlighter and I thought it was so cute
sense obviously this look it's a
chocolate hill inspired look and then my
artist that Mac used the soft and gentle
highlighter I thought my Holly had all
three looks was decent they definitely
also had a little bit more vibrant I do
love a good glow and in the picture of
Jacqueline she is definitely like
blinding the haters left right with your
highlight which I am love what I did
think was weird about the highlight from
all three lunches that all three artists
use a really really big brush for
applying a highlighter don't get me
wrong I definitely love a good duyst
again luck you guys see me trying to
achieve it all the time but I do feel
like the replaces the highlighter should
be in place the highlighter shouldn't be
and because of the size of the brush to
all three artists use I didn't feel like
the cheeks and like the under-eye region
was a little bit shinier than I
typically like it when it comes to
highlight me the nose I'm gonna once
again it got that tiny pencil brush and
just draw a really really thin line onto
the tip and then down the nose bridge
once again going back to the contour
thing you guys know I love a pinched
nose and to achieve that with makeup it
definitely takes a lot of different
steps one of them is definitely using a
really really tiny brush privacy Holly
is gonna bring the eye forward and draw
attention to it so by using a pencil
brush you're just furthering the
illusion and the only artist that did
that was my back artist Helen and it was
so amazing and I felt like her nose
contour was by far the best
and then finally to finish off this look
today I'm gonna go into the Kat Von D
liquid lipstick in the shade Vampira
when I first saw the photo of Jacqueline
this was the first liquid lipstick to
come to my head I feel so it'll be a
perfect match to the photo so I was so
excited to see my Sephora artist playing
this oh that my Mac artist used the
carnivorous look on the website from
the back and my altar artist he was the
anasazi logo that was in the shade
trust but then again we remember I
picked that one up from a band not him
and yes what I'm applying this I'm
making sure to over line while applying
this I did go ahead and add two coats
because as you remember it in the
Sephora video and even looking in it
right now this lipstick is a little bit
streaky so I did want to make sure to
get it super super opaque and then
finally last but not least I'm gonna
finish this off using the skin to Navy
eye makeup finishing spray alright guys
and that is the beauty guru gets a
makeover at his own beauty station look
all complete here is the finished look
now that you guys have seen my version
with all of my favorite techniques and
products let's go ahead and compare all
four looks my first makeover was at
Sephora and my artist was named Crystal
she was so so sweet my makeover ended up
costing me $50 and they rated it a 7 out
of 10
my artists did a really really great job
and this makeover was a little bit
different for the other ones in the
series because it was the first episode
and I wasn't asking for specific things
like nose contour and for less harsh
bronzer and stuff like that so I don't
want to knock her too hard although I
did dislike the foundation I thought it
so it wasn't really that full coverage
and I felt as though some of the
eyeshadow tones were a little bit off
from the original my next makeover was
that Mac my artist was Helen it cost me
$60 and I rated this makeover an 8 out
of 10 my artists had been working at Mac
for over 10 years and her expertise
really really showed her blending was
absolutely impeccable I love the eye
shadow on this look although I do wish
she added a little bit more setting
powder because I started to get very
very oily very quickly and I felt as
though I was getting some creases and
she also underlined my lips which I felt
wasn't really that flattering to my face
shape my next night cover was at Ulta my
artist was Darrell it cost me once again
$60 that I ended up writing this
makeover a 7 out of 10 I really liked
this makeover in the sense that he used
a lot of the same products and
techniques that I usually use in my
normal routine such as Too Faced Born
This Way Foundation and turn shape tape
although there was some weird things
that the pink of the foundation shade
was nowhere near my skin tone once I
left the store but that's like a whole
lighting situation that I don't even
want to get into and then of course my
cut crease was a little bit of a really
really wonky shape that I don't think
flattered my eyes now that we've
compared all the details of off for
makeovers let's compare them
side-by-side
first we went to Sephora
then he went to Mac then was Ulta and
then finally my own work looking at all
four of these books next to each other
it is so cool to see all the different
techniques and products to use but all
the different artists even though we
went into each experience with the same
exact photo I think it is the R is so
cool that each look looks very very
different and unique in their own ways
there are things that I love on each
look and there are also things that I
don't love as much but overall I think
all three makeovers were a huge success
in the end taking into consideration the
final look techniques use products use
prices and just treatment overall I
think my grand prize winner for this
makeover finale is Mac getting a Mac
makeover I felt incredibly comfortable
the entire time my artist was super kind
it was definitely extremely
knowledgeable about the makeup process
which obviously you want if you're
getting a glam makeover well $60 wise on
the higher end of the price tags for the
makeovers I felt as though I was
definitely paying for expertise I feel
as though the things that I didn't like
as much about the look being the lack of
setting powder and the underlined lips
are two things that can really easily be
fixed by simply saying something
obviously you guys watching this know
that I tried to say as little as
possible just to see what the artist
would come up with on their own but
obviously if you're gonna get makeup
done you should speak up because any
artist is being paid to paint your face
and to make you look good so you should
be getting what you want as a client
even though Mac was my personal winner
today I definitely wanna hear from you
guys which out of the four looks was
your favorite did you like the Sephora
look the Mac look the Ulta look or my
look at the best leave me a comment down
below I can't wait to see what you guys
have to say alright guys and that is
like how for this mini makeover series
I've had so much fun filming this if you
did love this video please don't forget
to go to big thumbs up also if you guys
want me to like continue this series
definitely let me know like I said I
absolutely love filming it so if there
are any other stores or any famous
artists you want me to get my face beat
by let us sister now if you have not
already make sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below
we are literally so close to 2 million
it is so crazy I love you guys so much
also don't forget to click that little
belt icon so you can be notified every
time I upload a new video we are in the
middle of sits are uploaded recreate now
where I am uploading every single day it
has been so so crazy don't forget to
check out all the previous videos that
have already come out and stay tuned for
tomorrow and Friday for the last two
videos of sister
old week you guys are not gonna want to
miss them if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both dis
James Charles and my snapchat for behind
the scenes lights up is James Charles
the next your ass after Charles this
week sister shout-out goes to sister
Scarlett thank you so much baby for
always following and supporting and I
love you so so much and if you'd like to
beat next week's to sir shout out make
sure to always reach it over there links
and they go live on Twitter alright guys
thank you so much for watching today I
really hope you enjoyed this little
miniseries I love you so much and I will
see you tomorrow
[Music]