hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel as
you can see I'm in a very very different
setup today and I am in my beauty room
of Herbert who are coming soon but by
the way I've been getting so many
comments about it definitely keep your
eyes peeled
but yes creating my viewing room today
we are not in the normal studio setup
and that is because today is a very very
special video
I guess May 23rd marking this be the
18th year from which I was born
it's so crazy I know a legal adult I had
to change all the weight BIOS to now
just an 18 year old kid with a few
blending brushes and now I'm here it is
a very very special day if you guys are
following me for a while you know that
I'm not really like a party animal I
don't really drink or definitely don't
do any drugs and I just basically mind
their own business Panna stay home and
do my thing so I don't really have
anything crazy plan for today's special
events so because of that I decided to
do a meet and greet with my favorite
convict in the entire world more feet so
today not leaving a get ready with me at
Sal video for my birthday glam then I'm
gonna take you guys with me to the bean
green show a bunch of blog footages have
a wonderful time and then stay tuned for
the end of the video because I have a
very very special announcement regarding
a contest that I will be holding and on
a 1 million on YouTube to lay out on
Instagram and my 18th birthday so if you
guys want to see how I get ready for my
birthday glam just keep on watching I'm
first gonna pop in my desi Oh innocent
white contacts a lot of people ask me
how do you get in a contact when you
have nails my answer for you is
carefully I'm gonna be probably my face
using my benefit Porefessional primer as
always I'm getting beating you guys for
three hours you typically want to make
sure my face is locked all the way in
place I honestly am so excited I barely
I'm ready to do a meet and greet just
because they're always so have taken so
crazy and very very hard to plan as well
so I'm super excited that I get to do it
at morphe of all places because y'all
know sister James loves her morphe I
feel like I've already been at 17
forever this year where it's so slow but
there were like so many amazing
helping and so many not so amazing
things too but I'm so thankful for you
guys that I've like stuck with me
through the entire thing I'm a human
being I'm growing I'm learning I
definitely got into the industry it's
super super quickly and I really really
young it was just amazing I'm so
thankful for everything that I
accomplished and achieved and all of you
guys but at the same time it definitely
pushed me to learn it and educate myself
very very quickly I definitely made a
lot of mistakes and I said a lot of
things that I shouldn't have but I think
that it's important to know that as
human beings we all make mistakes and
that the only thing you can do
appreciate you know take them back it's
just grow and better yourself as a
person I'm so excited for what this year
has to hold I can promise you guys there
are a lot of really really cool things
that are happening right now on behind
the scenes that I can't talk to you
about just yet but definitely keep your
eyes peeled because I'm working here on
the lot
I'm just genuinely so committed to work
I feel as I was already super super
motivated beforehand but moving to LA
everybody here has like a major agenda
everybody here has something to do and
living here just really pushes me to
work so hard and be the best version of
myself and just get a whole lot of
I feel like I'm a boss ass [ __ ] when
I'm here and I absolutely love it oh my
god I just I'm so excited for you guys
to see it work like what's coming I
honestly have no idea what makeup I'm
doing today I'm just starting with my
face I'm gonna figure it out I feel like
when I'm taking a lot of pictures I need
to do really really light makeup but at
the same time we're gonna kind of let me
go but I'm definitely not having a good
skin day today which is annoying
days today would be the one to hop if
it's goodbye hey but of course that's
how my luck work I was up so they last
said with all the sisters they all came
over and surprised me have been they
literally is so cute and like a friend
at kamut I sent me a pizza so we all
shouted down the coolest runs in the
entire Bell that I'm so so happy right
now I remember as a child always wanting
to be the 18 so badly and now that I'm
actually here everything is like exactly
the same I mean it's gonna help every
birthday room obviously but I just
remember being like oh my god I want to
be 18 so that's I could be illegal if
don't do all these fun things but like
now actually being here like I don't do
anything anyway
it's so crazy because I've been living
alone for a few months now and I started
that they were when I was 17 I graduated
early and moved across the country which
is something that a lot of people can't
even say when they're 18 or 19 so I'm so
like I think I've always been very like
ahead of my age and older inside that I
was on my birth certificate I guess
that's not so stupid but I really is the
truth the only thing I don't think a lot
of older people I don't think I'm a lot
more mature than a lot of kids that are
my age and I really get really really
cool to me right now
I guess the only real exciting part
about today is now I cannot legally have
a grinder how about let's be real a lot
better do anything anyway so for my
brows that I'm going to use the ax
benefit persistent brow pencil on the
shaded number 4 I'm going to lightly
fill them in and sculpt them
I'm honestly so excited for the next
upcoming weeks I go home back to New
York with all the sisters for my senior
graduation and I am so beyond excited I
opened up a package for my parents
yesterday before my birthday and they
may be like it's too little bunch
of like old cute baby photos in the end
photos from like my friends and stuff
and I just started bawling I don't cry
like ever but oh opening that pocket
just really put it in perspective how
much I miss them so much
I've been wanting to like move out and
just kind of be independent for as long
as I could remember there's three years
old I was in my own apartment
and like if you asked my mom she will
tell you this - hi boys then super super
independent but now that I actually live
alone I can't even explain how much I
miss my mom and things she would do for
me I really do miss her
last two times I've only make up for
some reason my brows keep coming out
really really uneven and it's really
starting to get on my last nerve
I don't know what it's going on but one
side of the tail looks a lot like better
than the other one I guess and it's
father like I think I was so good to go
back home before graduation the only bad
part about it is that at the same
weekend as VidCon and I won't be able to
go well I've been getting so many to
meet some of you guys to ask you if I'm
going to be there and no I will not be
at this year's VidCon I will however be
a play let's DC but VidCon happens with
the stain exactly again as my graduation
and unfortunately I cannot skip it but I
am working with a really really iconic
designer to do something super super
cool my graduation gown so definitely
it's stay tuned for that because it you
guys are definitely gonna want to see
this you will be shipped to the corner
in honor of today is morphine Beyond
videos the 35o palette of course - it's
my my eyes change for 10% off I think
I'm gonna go something really light airy
and smoking today just because a lot of
times intense makeup looks and do not
photograph that will help for one mean
grades and stuff I just want to look
good every photo
lord knows we did not need another
flashback marry me matte situation
[Music]
that's the upper left all complete I
cannot find my lash says there so I
guess we ran out to you I pocket up with
us today to cut these under beating they
Lily lashes on the side of Miami's for
today
I love these lashes so freakin much
these are definitely in my top three
like I said before a long time of my
iconic sub court at my Bella New Balance
owns or my about so I'm sure like
they're so pretty I'm like really
natural looking it like I have lots of
sanctions but don't have to like go
through the hassle but wanting to rip my
eyes obviously event with lots of
centuries
[Music]
I definitely go for a nude lip today
that's gonna last me all day long so it
was not I'm going to be using the Kat
Von D bow and arrow and if you watched
my how to find your perfect liquid
lipstick shade using your Tatas you know
that this is one of the final three that
one and this is definitely my all-time
favorite David's to finish off this hook
once and Fromme going to use my Urban
Decay all nighter setting spray as I
said before we really need this to last
all day long to almost sweat all the
hugs and all the make our brush a
alright guys and this is the completed
and makeup look I'm gonna go to put on
my outfit now honestly I'm not exactly
sure what I'm gonna wear yet but we're
gonna try to pull this together because
sister named soloqueue fingers possibly
don't were saying that I've already won
56 times but knowing me chemically
policy so I said okay but I only was all
over the place you've been running
around all morning I know so beyond
excited to meet all of you guys my
friends have been in and out all day
preparing and stuff so I just hope that
this video came together if you like
this setup as well please let me know I
could definitely more videos like this
in the future
it was very very fun in a different
setting from the regular studio stuff
but that being said I'm gonna go get
changed and then we're gonna head over
to the meet greet and get ready to
celebrate this very very special day at
all you guys so keep on watching and
don't forget to stay tuned until the end
really not on the very very special
contest you guys are definitely gonna
love it love you guys guys we're
currently on the way over to Burbank I
will see you guys soon I'm so okay ready
is it going oh do I look good yeah
alright guys so we just finished up this
is the Alpha Don brain for today I'll
show you guys a better shot when we get
out of the car obviously but we call
their uber we're on our way over to a
Burbank from downtown so we've got quite
the long ride ahead of us but I am so
excited to me apparently we have to make
a brief pit stop before heading out
sister Laura over here has a subclass
tree but I have no idea where we're
going and I'm annoyed so I will keep you
guys posted
how many fathers gonna get a bit push
James off excuse me I think
oh he's over there waiting he is based
in a good picture okay guys I'm gonna
buy him some Easy's but what kind of
find his size I'm gonna be 20 mil these
are mine
what are you planning sister oh my god
oh wow that's bad
my DIY posture change yeah there's some
humor
[Music]
alright guys I am back home now it is
currently 2:00 in the morning I took off
all my makeup my nose is very very
stuffy I apologize and I sound ugly I
know I get a ton of comments all the
time about my annoying ass boys anyway
so here you go it's even more annoying
now I'm currently on my living room
floor on a hello Reverend Lai is leaning
up against a window and my camera is on
my brand-new shoe box that I just got so
this is a very DIY setup but I'm Way too
lazy to go into the filming room and
turn off my lights I am so exhausted but
I needed to finish this video for you
guys first I need to say a major thank
you to everybody that showed up to the
meeting greet today over 300 people came
which is literally literally blessing my
considering I announced it like four
days ago and I cannot even begin to
explain how amazing meeting every single
one of you was today there's seriously
no other way that I'd rather saw the
18th birthday I know that sounds so
cheesy and like every influencer says
that but seriously you guys made my day
so much today everybody was so nice so
kind your hoot little gifts and cards
and presents and everything just I
cannot even like you guys are the reason
they do this every single day and I this
industry really really does suck a lot
and my job sucks a lot of times and I
know that sounds so stupid to complain
about having such an amazing job but it
really does start to get at you
sometimes though and you guys are the
ones that keep me going meeting all of
you guys just really like reinforces in
my brain why it is every single day and
it's for all of you and it's making you
happy and just to know that I'm
inspiring people and make people happy
is why I wake up in the morning and do
my job and do what I do I thought of a
little context that I wanted to do it
just for you guys I thought of this a
few days ago so this is super duper last
second but I'm gonna be giving one of
you guys a full on a makeover I'm gonna
be choosing one of you amazing sisters
out there and I'm going to give you a
full glam makeup makeover by James
Charles myself you also be winning a a
full set of amazing acrylic nails y'all
know I love rocking my acrylics so my
good friend Susie is gonna be giving you
an amazing set of your choice and to top
it off as well you can't have an amazing
look and amazing nails and an amazing
outfit so you'll be winning a shopping
spree at Laura's boutique all you have
to do is be subscribed on YouTube
channel and follow my Instagram they're
both just James Charles give this video
a big thumbs up down below and then
cover
tell me why you love makeup today is
Friday so I would pick in the winter one
week from today I'll be announcing it on
my snapchat and my Twitter's the
definitely stay tuned alright guys that
is all I have for you make sure to check
the description box down below for more
content details and like all the
official wording and all that type of
jaws but I really really hope you
enjoyed my little birthday get ready
with me a vlog contest type of video
this is a very very strange review from
wheeler due just to the fact that it was
a different set up very different style
of footage and obviously this is very
very different as well I've never done a
contest on this channel before so I'm
super excited to see how it turns out
and if you guys enjoy this as well
definitely give me feedback its up
because I'd love to adjust it for future
stuff if you guys enjoyed this video
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and subscribe if
you have not ready I post two videos a
week on Mondays and Fridays that I'd
love to have you join the sisterhood if
you'd like to follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they were all just James Charles
and my snapchat and you dare for more
behind the scenes type stuff aren't
James Charleston extra ass after Charles
alright guys thank you so much for
watching and thank you once again to
everybody who came to mine we created
for all the amazing birthday messages
and tweets and cards and gifts I cannot
even begin to trust you guys how much I
truly love you you guys mean so much to
me and I will see you in the next video
goodbye
[Music]