hi sisters James Turrell turd welcome
back to our YouTube channel and you guys
today I have such an iconic guest
please welcome sister Molly Burke James
Charles called me iconic you are life is
made sure I'm a sister but a sister for
a while when you look at me you're like
just a basic girl but no there's a lot
more than meets the eye huh see what I
did there or doesn't meet the eye
exactly love that you're already rolling
the blind Oaks we like people who can do
that right getting right into it so I
make videos here on the tubes about
pretty much just like life as a blind
person I'm a fashion and beauty lover
the beauty community is what like got me
into you - that is so cool way back when
I lost my vision in 2008 so yeah I'm
just like so happy way to finally make
this happen
these are constantly tweeting me telling
me that I need to collab with you so we
don't reached out I was like dying a
little inside oh my god I'm so excited
you guys we're doing it so many cool
things today for my channel Bali's gonna
do my makeup Clem lately blinds clearly
and I have so many things that I want I
don't even need a blindfold so easy and
then for my channel Molly's gonna
challenge me and I'm gonna have to do
her makeup completely Vitaphone still
gonna be like trading lifestyle I just
have so many questions well just let me
actually wanted to like feel and play
through all my makeup and I was like
you're all at war so down instead of me
just giving her the products to put my
face we're gonna make her pick through
them as well and it was so crazy because
I was cleaning out my makeup table
before I even started and she was
telling me what all my apartments like
oh this is perfect oh this is Mac Paint
Pot I'm so crazy like the obsession is
so deep I like I always ask me like you
can't even see makeup you can't even see
fashion why do you like it so much and
I'm always like going blind doesn't
change who you are
it should know how you live and so it
just had to change like how I do things
you know like I'm still Molly I still
love tattoos I still love fashion I
still love makeup even though I can't
see it my favorite color is still purple
even though I can't see it you know what
I mean no literally so cool I have so
many things that I want to ask you so I
feel like we should just jump right into
the video because I'm so pumped let's do
this girl let's do it
[Music]
and Bernie do you have several pots of
drawers that are filled good new beauty
blenders yeah mac fix+
yes we do oh you don't do lawsuit
bloggers like fake lashes look oh my
goodness are these foundation yes there
are these all gonna be the right shade
no so I will definitely to struggle yeah
are these the two Facebooks yes I'm
telling you I know my makeup I love
problem this is the Laura Mercier it is
perfect
are these concealers yes these are all
the exact same are these tart yes shape
tape yes
Oh benefit yes which one is it though
I'm just gonna have to like literally
blindly pick what do we have it here is
this Too Faced yes how did you even know
the box was on I'm scared
Mac blush yes but can I tell would you
call this okay yeah you can tell by the
texture
protip this is benefit brow product yes
it is are we getting into the single
shadows
these are glitters any loose glitter
sounds dangerous with blowing this
sounds like more blind man I love about
there's like just one lonely like no
product that's glitter gel this is the
most insane thing it's weird and it
dries down to I used it for Coachella
can you see the light reflection for me
yes
so cool I love anything glittery in
anything metallic because when the light
hits it I can see it oh this is just
dose of color yeah it is what can I say
this is obviously an arse yes
I think I'm gonna go with this okay
that's the one that's like the most
reflective to both ah this middle one is
very it's part of you what colors how
what is it it's like a kind of like
champagne atone okay you want to call
chocolate Oh Lord yeah let's do it
can I feel those yeah broken but it's
still good and does her job
Wow you loved this yeah it was a good
one jeez you really went ham but we
started doing this obviously you're
blind yes right so you're gonna do I
wake up I have no idea what you look
yeah I want you to describe to me what
you think I look like well immediately
when I came in and I gave you a hug yeah
I was like he's exactly around the
height that I pictured you to be and
you're the builds like even like your
shoulder width you're more of like a
slim and on the shorter side like I
pictured you being around between like
five six and like five nine and being
like kind of a slimmer build don't think
that's just how I picture five exactly
where I picture you to have like really
good hair and brows yeah like hey star
point is like what I picture you and I
know you're you're pretty into you're
like full glam yeah so I picture to have
like good strong cheekbones strong brows
I would picture you to have like a very
symmetrical face I've been told that I
do have that yeah at least if I don't my
face doing it to look like a song I
picture you to be like a deeper skin
tone than me but still Caucasian no I
don't picture to have freckles I have a
few actually I wish I had a freckle
freckles I have beauty marks all over my
face
they're not like a nicely cutely place
right on the bridge of the nose which is
where I wish they were I have freckles
there yeah you get bossed
and then I pictured up brown eyes yes
Wow yeah I'm impressed with my own self
yeah
no Molly that's awesome this might be a
workers but you want to feel my face
before you began okay first before we do
that yeah I will say that like typically
blind people don't feel faces so if
somebody like me wants to like meet a
lot if you meet me in person if you meet
a blind person in person don't be like
what you want to feel my face they
didn't like no no but in this situation
it does make more sense yes I will be
doing a lot of your makeup with my hands
that's because that's how I do my makeup
because I can feel what I'm doing yeah
is a brush puts a barrier between what
I'm doing right so of course those
things that I'm gonna use brushes for
like I'm not gonna like try to contour
with my finger you know but like a lot
of them the other stuff I do like to use
my fingers to apply stuff right because
it does give me a good feel but like
yeah I don't know what face shape you
have I don't know you know that kind of
stuff so we're going makeup it changes
things right so if this is a pore
filling primer it's gonna be very slick
yep yep thick and slick Oh sister
definitely needs some more help
oh I can feel your little stubble yeah
basically that goes back in like five
seconds flat which is so annoying would
you get wickley's or here I want it
really badly yeah I'm working on it just
for the like purpose of makeup yeah yeah
move canvas everyday yep you have such
like a man's brow line yeah I definitely
have a pretty masculine face yeah for
sure I feel like I have like a very
strong jaw line which I feel like is
more useful in as well I feel like a
masculine dog on a woman can give like
that model ask type of block which is
really good well thank you so question
for you you do you record every single
day I do but because you lost your
vision when you were 14 14 you don't
remember what you look like I don't but
it's insane to me yes it's one of the
like most frustrating things like most
of my blind friends when you talk to
them like it sounds so narcissistic like
if you could see something you'd want to
see your family your friends and
yourself with you just want to see face
it yes like you missed so much when you
can't see they say more than 90% of
communication is nonverbal of course
it's a tone of voice but it's also
facial expression body language all of
that stuff means a lot it's hard not
being able to see other people when
you're communicating with them it's hard
not to see yourself it can be difficult
especially when you're like working in
the entertainment business you're living
in LA with all the pretty people and
it's very much a place pay someone and
you get so many comments cuz like of
course I work in social media so I get
like tons of comments about my
appearance it can really screw with your
head yeah but I really try to not think
about it and just like be positive
because it's really easy to focus on the
negative parts of being blind yeah but
there's also positives that come with it
no they're not as easy they're not as
obvious but I think if I live with like
thinking of the sad stuff that's no way
to a point right you just sit back and
all the time like I can't look like that
no okay I don't wanna poke you in the
eye no worries perfect
I was watching everybody oh that you did
was change yeah you don't really have a
lot of recollection of watching anything
yeah so like visual memory doesn't
really last my mom her best friend
actual boss is blind he lost his vision
on his 11th birthday on his 11th
birthday yeah what again absolutely
horrible right obviously I'm very
ignorant to the topic I know a little
bit but I write pretty much I know to
the topic of blindness as I'm so excited
to learn more from you today he has I
wanted to do is 11 he is much older now
but he can remember a lot of things I
wonder if he actually remembers or if
it's his brain well I will tell you Fred
he grew up in New York City he still
works there all the time for his job and
what's insane to me is obviously when
you're blind a lot of your other senses
are of course you rely on the more yeah
we will be in the taxi together in New
York and he'll be like oh my God look at
that building over there on 56th and
Madison it's so beautiful and I'll look
over bleak oh yeah that is a pretty
building they don't remember oh my god
he has no idea what he's looking at or
he'll be like oh yeah look at there's a
subway station right there like that's
where we need to go so he can't see I
think I have that too like I have mental
maps of everything around me take me to
a shopping mall I know where every store
is located in the mall and I can like
walk directly there like it's like a
mental mapping system like it's a coping
mechanism you know we have to remember
where everything is and I'll talk about
things like a lot of people come and be
like well how does she know like that's
her favorite foundation if she can't see
how it looks like it's about how it
feels or like talked about something as
if I know how beautiful is but never
like how does she talk about it like she
knows how beautiful it is I'm like well
people describe it to me yeah I'm gonna
find a fluffy brush to set you with you
might love
I like the fluffy soft ones oh yeah yeah
that's a good one is it dual fibre yes
it feels like a dual five yesterday's
laura mercier yes ma'am I did this like
series on my channel where I started
trying beauty products and beauty hacks
that I was too scared to try oh my god
and one of them was loose setting
powders that's thing that you've been
afraid to turn I was always afraid
because like loose powder and blindness
sounds like a dangerous combination
there's two base hasn't loose powder
it's their peach powder and I literally
love it because I thought smell like pee
it tastes like peach - oh my god like
I'll be putting it on in like someone
like land on my tongue I'm like you and
then I'm like I actually taste something
you're gonna need to show me that
product i under % well have I gotten any
no nope not much oh I just talked
product over blind girl problems are you
able to visualize things yeah it's
interesting it's almost like when people
describe things because I have like a
history with sight yeah even though I
can't like pull up an image when you
describe stuff it still means something
okay more so than it would to somebody
who's never seen them right so if I said
like oh you're using a white handled
duo-fiber coffee bar so it's like a
far-off it's almost like a memory like
yeah I can still remember green purple
and blue okay guys I see them all the
time I have what's called like I called
him fireworks and basically I see
flashing lights 24/7 and they're only
blue green and purple
but he said purple is your favorite
color purple is my favorite color was
the last favorite color I after had when
I was going blind so it's just like
remained my favorite color oh my god all
right I'm gonna bronze you one of the
reasons I love Too Faced so much is cuz
their products are scented it's like I
can enjoy it you know like I can't see
it but I can smell it and it's like a
way for me to enjoy makeup so this would
be like the Davos question ever but
since you don't have your site what
would be your favorite scents um that's
a stupid question
it's not um I say my hands are my eyes
yeah I'm always going around touching
everything yeah except people's faces
and so that's like definitely one of the
senses I rely on the most I'm a nun
hearing yeah as I say my mom's boss he
carries on a walking cane and he can
slam his cane on the ground as soon as
he walks into a ring
you like a million facts about the room
yeah passive echolocation so I'm gonna
bless you now I've never used this blush
before so I hope I'm not going to like
heavy-handed with it but that's what
happens when you can't see the colors
whenever I got new makeup on like Wars
now the other son goes and I always like
ask somebody usually before I leave the
house to make it to make sure I like
FaceTime my mom yeah she's like my
honest mirror
we all need an honest people in our life
like that yes so do you live alone I do
yes you live alone mm-hmm my mom has
been living with me since I moved to LA
and she will be heading home back to
Canada on Wednesday so just gonna be you
and sister go up oh my god gallops my
guide ugh
yes of course I the way are you nervous
to live alone I lived alone in Toronto
for two years oh okay I'm gonna guess
lightest to darkest no I can't stand why
do brands just randomly willy-nilly go
throwing colors into a curry and so
annoying it would make more sense not
even just for blind people but for like
beginners of makeup yeah if all makeup
went in the order of shades okay so you
live alone in Toronto for two years I
did yes I live alone right now
yeah very large apartment I am lonely
and it was yeah I was the same age as
you when I moved out yeah I was 18 I
lived on my own from 18 to 20 21
I am very people relying like me I need
to be around people at all times X
obviously yes yeah obviously not to see
but just like to feel like a presence
around you yeah yeah what do you say the
gala would be like that presence for you
or if C was the dog I had at the time
okay we live together she was great like
she would get me out going to the dog
park with her and I you know I had a
full-time assistant at the time as a
motivational speaker
I still have loved all but that was like
my full-time job was notational speaking
so I was like touring law and I had a
full-time assistant he would travel
everywhere with me so my parents lived
close by and like would come visit my
dad's office was like 15 minutes away so
yeah it made like living alone
more more company versus like now I love
six-hour flight away from my family
which is obviously like yeah a lot what
have you
you have to come to my place how do you
like I wanted so far I love it I
honestly do I told my parents when I was
five that I was gonna move to LA really
like this is the same all I became a
youtuber so I moved to LA like know it
really like has always been my dream I
always say I want to fulfill like all of
sighted molly's dreams you know I want
to show myself and other people that
going blind doesn't have to change my
life path and you have to change
everything it changes things for sure
but like it doesn't have to be like that
not to make it negative or anything but
like what would you say has been the
hardest part about not being sighted
you know I dealt with a lot of bullying
when it happened which was really hard I
lost all my friends and like went from
being like pretty popular to having just
not only having nobody but being
tormented and know what's really really
hard oh my god I can't even more because
I love my life please do that's what I
talk about a lot with my speaking as
like mental health and bullying and
accessibility and accepting diversity
and that kind of thing because you know
I think a lot of people are very
ignorant about blindness and disability
in general it's not their fault it's
because society's been taught that it
should be this elephant in the room and
that we're not allowed to talk don't
look don't stare don't ask questions
right ignore them you know that's not
how I think it should be we should be
educated and talking about it from a
young age we should have disabled
characters in children's books and in TV
shows and it shouldn't be like the sole
focus of the character all the time no
which is unfortunately how it is we're
rarely representative medium when we are
were represented very poorly I grew up
wanting to be an actress and a model but
I went blind I was like it's never gonna
happen yeah I realized like you know
maybe traditional media is gonna be
really hard for me to work in but like I
can carve my own path I can represent
myself I can represent my community yeah
and make content myself I'm Papa would
you say YouTube has done the best
platform for you to do that oh my god
absolutely I love YouTube YouTube was
like a huge part of my journey to
recovery and my journey to finding
confidence and self love after blindness
and so the fact that I can now use
YouTube to help other people it's so
remarkable yeah do you have a lot of
blind followers I do I definitely have a
lot of disabled followers a lot of blind
followers I have a lot of parents of
kids who are disabled
yeah our teachers but of course I also
have like a ton of able-bodied people
know nothing about disability and come
and learn
and join the conversation and I love
that I love changing people's opinions
and like breaking stereotypes so many
people will initially come to my channel
and be like oh she's faking it cuz XYZ
like all of these stereotypes that I
don't fit but but then they watch enough
of my videos and they realize why
they're misinformed why they hold these
ideas about disability and why they
might be wrong
yeah and actually like on the process of
like trying to catch me alive they
educate that it's all crazy to me why
would you ever do that there's like
those few rare random people who have
like faked cancer or like that guy young
[ __ ] who like pretended to be in a
wheelchair and then stood up the end of
a concert like there's those weird
bizarre random for a few people but they
get attention when they do it and it
gets media attention when the story
comes out that like now everybody who
has cancer it's like they have to prove
it once they buzz it on the internet and
everybody was disabled we have to like
prove it but that's not our
responsibility you know as it should be
it's the one bad person that ruins that
for everybody
exactly that sucks I think there's a lot
of that in the beauty community - like a
lot of us have had sister scandals and
yes about the beauty community
definitely has a very like bad and like
dramatic rap but well I feel like it
sucks but like I'm part of the problem
of that and decides that I definitely
had a messy past growing up but I've
never totally clean it up and I know a
lot of other people as well but that's
you know young like making mistakes is a
part of the journey
you know you learned so much I mean I'm
such a different person now than I was
at 20 and I thought I was like mature
and knew it all at 20 you know you grow
and that's a part of it yeah and
unfortunately like for somebody like you
who started in social media very young
you had to grow up publicly and you like
people have to see your mistakes we all
make mistakes and a lot of us are lucky
enough that we do it privately so I
don't understand like people who fill in
eyes you know young celebrities and
stars who make mistakes because it's
like yeah you did that too you know and
you can't even imagine the pressure
right that these people are under you'll
have less brow bone than me
really yeah I have more you have higher
yeah eyebrows are not very arched and
they're like more course it's not just a
boy thing or is that like a you think I
guess it's a little bit of a boy thing
also my brows have underwent a major
transformation if you were to meet me
two years ago and he had the square
Brown yeah
if you were to meet me two years ago and
feel my brows they literally would have
been down here interesting and scary is
what it was and I feel like oh all the
photos are so public there yeah
they're all there they are all
documented and likely I don't get the
most hate comments ever and I think oh
my god people are so mean I love my
brows and then looking back at it out
you're like why did I love that I was
like thank you all for leaving me those
tough that's all my eyebrows because it
worked my eyebrows so now I learned I
did another a little bit more arts but I
still don't have that big of a brow bone
yeah it's so interesting again like face
structures cuz I just don't think about
it yeah you know I don't think about
faces looking different yeah what do you
really like about doing different makeup
looks
I mean it's art you know it's art that I
can experience because I'm feeling it
yeah versus so much art in the world
I can't experience I can't see I can't
enjoy so for me that's what I love yeah
you need to explain to them exactly what
you're explaining to me about eyeshadow
right were you forgetting that so when I
get a new palette I memorize where the
shadows are so you can probably tell
which ones I love I love this shadow
right here which is like a matte kind of
warm tone brown I love this color which
is a matte peachy kind of shade
I love this color which is like a really
shimmery coppery almost I think I love
these two shades right here I do not
show you a lot which i think is like a
peach shade not as shimmery as this one
yeah but in a kind of deeper peach color
I love these two for like a really fun
beachy look huh which are kind of more
brights like corals yeah and then of
course like this is a great highlight or
I'll do this on the lid which is like a
light gold yes I usually do that like as
a highlight if I want to brow bone
highlight that is the craziest thing the
most amazing yeah it's all memorized why
do I do your makeup like I think I want
to try to go through and a shadow
palette and see if I have any of the
memorize I think I might be able to do
it probably oh my god that that is so
cool to me when you can't see you just
figure it out all the time I'll comment
on my videos and though I don't know how
she does it like I could never be blind
if I went blind I would kill myself I'm
like okay sure there's like times when I
felt like that when I first went blind
and was being bullied and dealing with
depression guys purple on it
oh oh I clean your brushes I'm sorry
wouldn't life hands you a situation that
didn't expect you just figure it out
yeah you know just to I'm gonna actually
go back to the concealer I just use this
as primer perfect hi we're out of budget
always who needs 50 million products you
can multi use what would you say would
be like your all-time favorite makeup
land
I left Hart mm-hmm I love Too Faced
mm-hmm I love Mac since it's what like
brought me into the makeup world when I
was 12 13 and told my mom that I really
wanted to start wearing makeup she felt
like I would probably end up in a
disaster if she just like bought me a
bunch of drugstore makeup and like
handed it to me and was like no and so
she took me to a Mac counter yeah um and
had them pick out all the shades for me
and she had them teach me like which
product goes where and she bought it all
for me and then I figured it out and I
would practice and I loved it and then
every birthday and every Christmas she
would bring me to get a new look as I
got older and that's how I started
collecting so for about five years of
makeup loving Mac was like the only
brand that existed to me and I was like
Sephora what yeah well Mac was the only
brand that kind of existed for most
beginner makeup offers a long time yeah
I took me a long time you know once I
was like deep into the beauty YouTube
world and I was like okay I need to
start trying some of these I think like
probably the first product I bought
outside of Mac was like Make Up For Ever
HD which then ended up becoming like my
holy grail foundation that was my holy
grail foundation when I first started it
like still is I love that oh my god I
love that I just love the texture like
it really sinks seamlessly into your
skin you know I agree so the beauty guru
world kind of really got you into makeup
that absolutely like I loved makeup
before yeah but that's what just got
like the obsession went so deep which
I'm sure so many people watching this
could relate to
yeah that's literally how I started
screws the budget yeah I started
watching like Jacqueline Hale
nikkietutorials were like the two people
that really got me into it what are you
like like watching back in oh nine I
loved
juicy star oh seven Blair Fowler yes I
loved Megan Hart's makeup uh-huh Megan
Parkin I loved bethany mota of core core
Queen um those were like my three girls
they were like my sisters
literally like they were like of course
some of your face in the beauty's face I
really like Jeffery and really
I really like Carli bybel it is crazy
because it is a very very clever
community right now and I always love
people but not many people stick out
what I think all right whose content
really inspires me yeah that's why I
feel like I go outside of the beauty
community for like people inspire me you
know like just like neutral neutral
lipid yeah you're pretty full lips lucky
thanks Juvederm okay rub your lips
together now you have to try to do your
own mascara don't let me go mad so you
can do it easily
okay Loxley oh I always try to go like
into the little baby lashes in my inner
corner and that's when I hit my nose I
think I still do have a slight advantage
because I can see the wand right not
like very well but it's like it's blurry
I'm legally blind clearly I can still
see but like I think by optometrist
standard so you can't drive a car then
cuz you know what I've got okay so when
you don't have your glasses or contacts
in here oh no I would crash in three
seconds yeah yeah my vision has always
been bad but it just keeps getting worse
and worse
just like blindness like blindness is a
spectrum we all have like different
different amount of vision left maybe
one day we'll be able to do a full blind
collapse again you'll be my fellow blind
person on YouTube I don't watch shows I
always found easier the inner corner
lashes I feel like you're definitely not
gonna be as full glam as you're used to
do you do many videos without makeup on
I don't wear makeup as like a confidence
boost yes yeah I wear makeup like to
express myself into yeah I can't see
I let her I cannot see the difference
makeup makes alright I don't look in the
mirror me like oh I look good to not
feel good I would say I'm equally as
confident I love myself just as much
yeah nervous the judgment the judgment
oh my god no it's gonna be a little good
regardless okay Molly looks really good
yeah yeah definitely
way less than what you usually wear I
feel like it looks like this is your
everyday look no yeah I love that people
throw makeup pretty quickly like most
girls like like have an average beauty
routine of like ten to thirty most girls
don't do a beauty guru beauty routine no
you know mostly most girls don't do
full blam daily and you know I've always
wanted to kind of see what I look like
with like a normal person's what sounds
like yeah I usually spend one to two
hours on it and even what I try to do
light makeup I still end up with any
make so much Nicholas and the despite
the fact that you cannot see it what's
going on right now this looks really
good and I love this why did classic
Molly makeup on you and now blindfolded
you have to do classic James Charles
that's good to do that I'm pretty
confident my abilities that I also click
that help the upper hand because I can
see what you look like
yeah boy yeah yes and you've done makeup
so many times on yourself and other
people yeah I believe in you okay well
that's gonna be over on sister of Ali's
channel but regardless I had a solo time
poking this today thank you
I believe this club was obviously
amazing I learned so much like I said I
had so many questions but it's so
amazing that you were so open and honest
about all these things and it's the only
way we can help really change you know
make people feel less weird about it
I love you just have such a positive
outlook on everything that you've dealt
with and thank you for your study my
questions thank you for dealing with my
ignorance about this thank you for
educating me this was so much fun and
you're truly an inspiration so thank you
thank you and now I'm gonna go dig
through your makeup if you guys enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below
subscribe if you have not already come
join the sis note and it's a pretty it
lit time cuz that belt I can't see you
notified every time I upload a brand new
video and also please you need to go
subscribe to Molly Burke right now she
is so impersonal so beautiful so
talented and just the cutest person ever
I'm obsessed with her
so my youtube channel is youtube.com
slash Molly Burke official or just Molly
Burke pretty simple and my Instagram is
at Muhlenberg official it'll also be
listed all down below go up all her go
say yes sister James sent you then we
lots of Q's always and us together and
if you'd like to follow me on a makeup
journey you can of course follow me on
instagram twitter they're both the same
charles and myself check for behind
scenes i stopped me show yourselves the
best after charles are you talking about
wait that's like that I wanted to ask
hold on
eyebrows are in the video that was rude
be completely 100% honest with me please
are my videos hard for you to watch
because of how fast I talk sometimes
your words blend into one uh-huh like it
all like mumbling yeah fast number yeah
so you know articulation James I try
you'll get there
I believe in you you're only 18 I love
that I love the honesty I just think too
fast I'm like my brain shoot that words
faster than I can even think in process
that's why you're so successful you're
like so many ideas going on I'm not a
part of your thing though if you're like
a funny kind of like a James Charles I
mess up a lot so I guess it adds to the
whole like just vibe and it's so funny
relatable well I'll try to slow down a
little bit thank you for the assist or a
feedback that's good to know
this video is sister Xiao de cosas
sister Anna thank you so much pain for
solving and supporting you know I love
you so so so much and if you like to the
next videos a sister shout-out don't
forget to reach weight with your legs
every time they go live on Twitter all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching don't forget to check out the
video did over on Molly's channel I love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]