[Music]
hi guys students on the bus my channel
as you can tell I have a very special
guest with me welcome Ann happy people
they never been here hi I'm Willam
younger easier here this is James and
you J charm beauty and he's gonna make
me into this in the coming second this
is the look we did today we did natural
white lips until it was taking become
dry for a few days
Jag's taking a break for me if you wanna
see how we created this level make sure
you keep on watching
let's go so many brushes so for rotation
today I'm using my makeup art all try HD
foundation set its way dark because this
clouds not planned and it not to me and
not willing but alright so you need your
foundation first yeah okay I don't want
to say about how the what we do like
this reason personally go around that I
do do you really yeah way too much work
cuz I actually like minesweeper or I
like your eyes they don't ya
overlap and then for glitter yes that
doesn't work for the other thing you can
do is you do your foundation first and
then you put your eyes on is not give a
[ __ ] yeah that works as well so for
concealer I are gonna be using our two
phase for my concealer in the shade it
very parents hopefully like enough to
punish it a little bit and make it match
no you just touched that area with
something so what are we doing now no
how'd you use a lot of product which is
too so far don't be this big like I'm
right there with my head's way larger
than yours how many well I have a coding
exon power of this up it's so much oh
this one I know because it reminds me
cocaine pretty said are you gonna use a
wet sponge and powder its be honest with
you I just think it because I feel
trendy doing so that's important yeah
it's very wearable false lash that is
the one when you when you find a lash
and your [ __ ] views when you lean
against the counter has ever happen to
you know yes a husband so now we're
baking there's not
music gluten-free yeah
envy him all those pressures you have
one brow brush yeah go [ __ ] yourself oh
no which I'm about to dump these on
before you so what are you gonna do
after high school
why are you going to you laughter -
don't you have 300,000 good scram
followers you don't in high school I
knew someone who's really serious about
clean brushes and chair and make up
what's up I know I'm a client makeup bag
with me I didn't think we'd be glopping
you didn't think I'm gonna come through
all my stuffing can use it on you but
when I make sure it doesn't bother you
about the clean brushes and sharing
makeup I said I eat a specific very
nondescript well see the things in mind
the foundation always wears off on this
side right here it'll a bright contour
it'll look good for like here down right
here at the Congress we're going to see
a foundation that's everywhere else
since when we have zero eyelid space
we're gonna make do what we have this
has been happening to me a lot lately
with the people I
what all boys Huck no evolution crunch
like hi buggies put the crunch time look
cuz it harder to make up with nails not
really actually
I was puzzled ly surprised it's only
heard of these things come right with
your ass yes a lot harder right on one
row not so for the waterline I'm going
to go to my next my eye pencil in milk -
Oh mouth the eyes may come up
really
[Music]
no good drag name but what this marine
you think that's me
oh cool I post my answer and picture of
my driver I said what should my name be
can you come to the shed funny saying I
like that name yeah UK you're gonna give
our names not believe it pushes leaves
here at part while wearing makeup I can
John
[Music]
relax Internet we're using sceeto
Lushington style wash Napolitan these
are my favorite ever every lifestyle and
you can use code details their money off
so first can I put them on because they
do drag
yeah we're almost on all state
legislator and lift so today I'm gonna
be using on esophagus Emily would
illuminate her to get well on some hello
get below up I've easily Murphy I'm 501
brush to apply the highlighter right
thank you
using the make up for ever miss it first
Santa things actually blended out
wouldn't that be something
when we go it's me here's the thing I
have a certain age and when you're a
person of a certain age doesn't pump the
brakes both chemicals texture you see
that and that's what you're making not
oh so I shouldn't move man I shouldn't
talk no different if you do not today
daddy dude pity
next buddy dude I think he is then I
believe it isn't a Disney marching band
Rock Creek down I'll be watching that
you know more pants to what Disney
so for loves them to be mixing Anasazi
up here Hollywood and dose of colors
sand these are two my fav nude so why
not my opinion a better new out of to
partying good news
hello cookies looks like stroking about
about miss opportunity you're 17
thank you clean put me on this videos
and so hit so far it's good for me it's
been pretty well okay now they have to
take part of alone because I love
freckles and why not
I'm he's honest on the guy's dipbrow at
dark route in this random brush there
what are your trouble
[Music]
thank you all right I'm do it come on
okay no you're also facing up I'm gonna
go ahead and I mean now we're also with
the pace like I'm gonna go ahead okay
now was I really change something
how's that we're done it's like a
hostage situation editing a video I
really hope you guys enjoy this video as
well I don't give up did you know I did
follow him on all of the social media
it's just well not everything you can
also follow me all of my things are
below it if you do this video don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and subscribe if you haven't
already I make videos every once in a
while he's gonna start hearing a more
responsible thing to do maybe do any
last things to say dinosaur loves it
bike