hi sisters tears childhood and welcome
back to our YouTube channel today I'm
done with my sister's hello I'm Ricky it
is October that means it is Halloween
season dysentery month is a little
Halloween okay anybody says hallow Tober
I hated that so few weeks ago it's a
Fiat Nygaard filmed a video where she
had her boyfriend Tyler go to the store
and buy her a bunch of different outfits
that she thought would look good on that
so for today's video
me and Ricky are copying her because
we're unoriginal and we both would be
make me stores in a twist we gave it a
twist we take so you won't go to the
Halloween time picked out three
different costumes so we don't have
boyfriends so we're being so that your
boyfriend's today yeah for each other
yeah so tinder is not going too well in
Vicky's asexuals exactly basically we
picked out three costumes for the other
person and at the end we're gonna choose
which costume we liked the best and then
put a makeup look on the person to
master the costume so we had to like go
above and beyond here so Ricky's ibaka
showed me his Constance that he picked
up for me he has been so serious all day
long about me not seeing them literally
oh I'm all about like a natural reaction
surprised I don't wanna peek so he
didn't he didn't see him okay without
further ado let's go ahead and get
started let's pick it up it's spooky
okay all right okay my favorite word
right now all right don't look Ricky
were filming okay I'm not looking so
this is called sinister sister I just
walked in my eyes went to that I'm like
no way so I did it for my favorite
sister yes but I have some Anakin to us
I'm going onto that okay a nice weapon
who are you gonna walk around and be
like a scary sister okay you know and
then I also don't look Ricky I'm still
not looking
okay but should I go try it on okay or
else
[Music]
oh my god
okay the next one no this one's good
it's the original it I didn't want to
just be basic and be like oh wow I'm ten
UI so I got some more fun things for it
I got you clown shoes I'm the great I
got a clown horn I'll try it on okay
show me your inner clowns this is your
punishment for dragging it alright the
last look is probably my favorite one
took me a while to find something that I
wanted to do but I thought I was like
okay it's like a sexy Pikachu costume oh
yeah not fun if you're gonna have your
pokeball purse oh man I can just carry a
random pokeball cuz you're a Pokemon oh
I did as I was checking out I saw this
and I was like I have to do it oh my god
matching fidget spinner Oh
[Music]
I'll be so honestly like let's do all
kind of like looks like you kind of did
a [ __ ] alright right yeah thanks
hopefully my costumes are you coming is
good they better be after trying all
three those on I think that my favorite
one that I want you to do of the makeup
on me for his sister Pikachu oh good
I'll be the flip you say that okay yeah
I have a cool thing in mind so okay
let's do it okay so let's go head over
to the beauty studio and get glam so
let's get started how long sisters we
are now in the glamour and I have my
cute little Pikachu costume on honestly
kind of living for this look I have your
latest keep this ever so I'm gonna pull
off my lashes this makeup has been on oh
my god for like eight hours now and this
feels amazing after like a full day
makeup I look like this so Ricky is now
going to do my makeup over top of my
makeup which is gonna be the most
disgusting thing ever but if you
couldn't tell my makeup it's been done
gotcha Jamie I'm sure they couldn't tell
okay so what I'm gonna do is when I give
a nice classic Pikachu look here Pikachu
is yellow I'm gonna give James yellow
foundation and then give him a nice red
cheek can't wait so today I'm gonna be
using this makeup forever pro flash
palette yep mmm-hmm look at me
this feels absolutely disgusting boop
boop boop Blanc Blanc now I'm going to
blend we love a beauty guru you're a
great client oh thank you so much you're
welcome
that's enough nice and blended yeah I'm
going to give him red little circles cuz
Pikachu has his red circles we use it
like his attacks they like light up oh
my god that's fine fine fine fine fun
other side was better but whatever okay
so here is the finished product as you
can see I turn this regular boy into an
actual Pikachu thank you oh come well
this is what we came up with yeah not
bad honestly honestly not but if you
guys enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up downs
a lot with scar
already click on notifications on I post
videos sometimes during the week I would
love to have you join this sisterhood
like me suddenly via this video it is
officially October meaning it is
Halloween month I have so many fun
Halloween videos planned so definitely
comment down below tell me what you guys
want to see me do for Halloween costumes
and tutorials
don't come a Pikachu because you already
got it we're not realizing that you
planned this very very poorly because
now you can see where these final look
but in our defense there is a full-on
fashion show two other very good
Halloween costumes that I picked out for
Ricky over on his channel and that I did
dancing I you can want to be in that
process so go over to Rick your channel
subscribe if you have not ready to check
that video out because that one is also
going to be equally as interesting if
not more interesting then and that's why
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey can follow me an image but
everything both just change Charles and
my snapchat from overhead and seems
lights up is Jo Charles that I should
ask after Charles and Oliver I think
social medias will be down below you do
that pretty fast I know but you can like
understand I understood we said this
accessory shout out goes to Julia thank
you so much girl always falling in
support and you know I love you so much
if you would like to be the next video
sister shout out make sure to always
retrieve our video links and they go
live on Twitter alright guys thank you
so much for watching we love you so much
happy Halloween one and I will see you
in the next one goodbye
[Music]