hi I'm James Zambian won't go back to
brothers and sisters hi I'm James and
I'm Ian and welcome back to brother and
sister sister brother brother and sister
sister and brother brother and sister
sister brother brother and sister first
today's episode we're going to be
talking about childhood memories
we actually had probably the worst hell
had ever together yeah we hate each
other yeah like pretty bad now we're
closer kind of if you guys did not know
I have 18 and Ian is 16 so that is a two
year age difference and now it means
nothing but when we were younger
Oh two years goes a long way and
obviously I am loud and obnoxious in
that race get my way and Ian was always
quiet defi was like the good younger
brother like would always just beat down
for anything would always be like nice
kind could not relate I was honestly
nothing like a really huge bully
well we fought a lot and it was up
always my fault but it was usually my
apology would painfully hurt me well yes
but I remember there was one time we
were fighting about something at dinner
he was still staying in a high chair
everybody got so huge where I got up out
of my regular dining chair and I kicked
the leg of his high chair over and his
high chair fell back and we had a
radiator right behind our dinner table
and he caught his entire lip open and
sort of bleeding and had him to the
hospital
remember this Pope really but I hate you
no that was not a fun one deadly was
grounded from Lincoln my Tamagotchi and
like the we for a hot minute well you
have like anger management help so you
were younger like this is making me out
to sound like I was some psychotic
monster but you you we're like psychotic
when you were younger like boys were
fighting keep chasing inside one time in
our old house and I remember I slammed
the front door so he couldn't get to me
and I stand his entire hand in the door
and he broke his fingers me heading to
the hospital yeah that was I remember
that that was yeah but you had a coming
probably I'd have to slam a
thousand-pound steel door on me steel
door where are we living a jail I think
I knew James gay before a lot of people
did I remember when he was probably 10
or 11 he would always take dolls and
braid their hair that was not 11 and 10
that was like 4 5 6 years old 9 4 5 6
I also remember when he was little he
would dress me up with my mom's like
clothes and like boots and you played
along with it are you gay no but I was
like 4 years old what do you want me to
do well apparently you had a lot of
fighting going on until you go to follow
me on a guy to really enjoy it at the
time no I've always been a glam sister
what can I say that's easily how our
entire childhood would be Ian outside of
this friends like playing football and
me inside on the computer on like
webkinz and poptropica those guys were
land memories to go to Florida every
April breaking go to Mimi's house and
stay with our cousins yawn zapper hell's
middle of Bop hey hey it was a fun time
number one we were in the canoe and
decided to tip us an alligator-infested
water that is not really that's like not
exactly what happened though it was a
wondrous in what happened no okay it was
me yo and our cousin Riley were canoeing
in the middle of like the jungle and our
cousin said like oh turn the or to the
right and clearly ever you know me I am
NOT a rower in any way shape or form I
should not be doing any physical
activity upper and I ended up moving us
to the left and we end up tipping the
canoe in the middle of the lake which
had alligators
I have never swam faster in my entire
life like Michael Phelps was quaking at
that given moment whatever he was like
literally
I think he could feel his olymic record
like about to be BM by sister James
swimming remembered me and Robbie had to
go back in there and get it after it's
sunk as you stood on the shore oh you
know I remember the biggest my most
worst nightmare was a kid I thought Big
Bird was like walking down the road
about a cupcake oh my god remember when
you had that dream all the time when
you're younger yeah this is like Big
Bird like walking down the road like
coming into our house and like
kidnapping me and I don't know why I had
it but I remember that dream so clearly
that is so strange first of all why do I
don't know oh my god oh my god I can't
believe you just this is like all coming
back to me right now
I had one reoccurring dream where I was
on a Barbie cruise ship maybe it's all
the [ __ ] Barbie heads that I play
with and do their hair of every single
day hello gay from day one and then they
would drive into like the city of
Manhattan and it would like plow through
the city and then I would get thrown
overboard from like a hundred two
hundred feet up in the air and die every
time that I had the dream it was so
weird and happened to be so many times
think I was about five or six I don't
know what happened but my mom heard a
thud and she came into the room and she
saw that I was lying on the floor so she
looked at me didn't see anything goes
wrong put me back into bed then I walked
down the next morning and apparently I
had dried blood all over my face and a
huge gash underneath my cheek which I
still have a scar from said she couldn't
see you guys in her glasses on speaking
of falling oh my god you just triggered
them I remember I could get sick pretty
often for some reason my dad does too
were like dying at least once a month
when I was sick one time when I was
younger I remember I was like bedridden
like could not get up could not move
like it was spooky boo goo boo I
literally thought I was gonna die God
about to go get an Advil in the bathroom
which is across the hall on the upstairs
level and we have a staircase in the
middle of the hallway and I remember I
really don't remember actually but I
woke up at the bottom of the stairs with
my dad screaming like falling down the
stairs as well because I had walked by
the stairs and passed out right at the
top of the staircase
I just fallen I'll hold the way down the
stairs completely unconscious did not
even feel a single thing and my dad was
like screaming freaking out we went to
the hospital once again thank God I did
not break anything but I literally
general that happening we got I got to
be like we're really going to the
hospital lot we were younger huh yeah
well you were the problems most the time
that's so not true
you provoked that let's see you push me
off a high chair yeah you slammed my
fingers in a door yeah I thought in my
bed that was kind of mom's fault
how's that muscle that you fell out of
your own bad side see that my face was
gushing blood in the middle of the night
she's blind
just like me relax you uh and had to
give me some reason tennis slam your
head fingers in the door and put you out
of your high chair you are you dude I
was like oh ho if I was like a bang I
was in a high chair what would I have
done to you that made you mad like what
am i what am I gonna say to you I have
no we were three I always got my way
every time there was no way that has
never jealous of him do you think our
mom was the worst chef ever still as
delicious still is the worst I've ever
every day oh my god it would be the
grossest looking like poorly plated and
won't know why she's on Facebook every
time she I'm trying out this new pesto
cream vegan gluten-free dairy-free
non-gmo meatloaf every night and don't
get me wrong I'm so thankful that we had
a mom until I cook for us and provide
for us when were younger but girl my
first concert that I ever won she was
Hannah Montana
I went to a Hannah Montana concert yeah
I did what every I just don't never gone
to a
really yeah we you never went to a
concert no what no never didn't we meet
someone was a Demi you met nobody
remember we met someone Alyson Stoner
from Disney Channel yep
yeah chef it was at a concert no it was
a basketball game where she sang the
national anthem of the national Oh the
biggest crush holy [ __ ] on Danny Phantom
from a Dior tune yeah I don't know I
like was convinced that I was going to
marry Danny Phantom he was so hot I'm
pretty sure the ghosts one I marry
talking about yeah I'm pretty sure was
really little had a crush on Dora not
only was I gonna marry Danny Phantom but
I was also convinced that I was going to
be Kim Possible one day like I don't
know why I don't know what it was I just
loved her and wanted to be her like I
just like
call me beat me if you want to reach me
girl like that's the roommate hello like
I just like she was like a strong
independent woman who don't need no man
although she ended up with Ron in the
ends but that's okay she was single for
majority of it that's me one day when I
get married fingers crossed hopefully
one of my favorite shows watches at
Drake and Josh
remember the room they had yeah that was
like my room goals for the longest time
really I was just wanted like an
elevated bed just oh my god we were
younger we tried to convince our dad for
weeks on end
oh my god to knock down the wall in our
house
we could live together we're just now
thinking about it thank God he said no
holy [ __ ] that would've been so scary
can you imagine
[Music]
oh I don't wanted to be when you're
younger
a garbage worker dude yeah it was oh my
god
every morning he would run out of bed
like 6:00 in the morning and run
downstairs and just look out the screen
door for the garbage truck to drive by I
couldn't tell you why I have no idea but
he was just so fascinated by it the
garbage people I mean honest and what
the Agard which work doesn't work I've
had like a million things that I was
just so convinced that I was gonna be a
superstar right when I was doing her I
first wanted to be an electrician I have
like these weird boxes with the plugs
and outlets and cables on them that did
nothing stop what vacuums used to be
obsessed was that I wanted to be a
cleaner for a hot minute oh my god we
could be doing the sanitary business
together I love that do you have garbage
do you have carpet we are sisters
including opening sister and brothers
cleaning company whatever all back to
your floors and I'll take out your
garbage and that's it
call us now at 1-866-931-6190 to next
row s after Charles love you guys so
much thank you for watching don't forget
to check out our other episodes and
we'll see you in
the next one high style