hi I'm James now man welcome back to
brother and sister sister brother
Prabhu sister I am NOT doing this again
for another entire season sister and
brother neither am i it's brother and
sister and that's the name it's been the
name the whole time that's the name
period not doing this again for another
entire season sister and we're back a
few cleaner Tito hope you miss us if we
best you guys we've been gone for a
pretty long time oh and I promise it's
for a good reason I've been working on a
lot of really huge projects on the DL
what'd you find out about eventually and
ian has been in school it's not good nor
for us but guess what it's summer ian is
leaving school hopefully fingers crossed
and now I am more free so that's good
and fresh that was so annoying no one
else is annoying you is going to be on
scoop DD whoop I get annoyed so easily
by the littlest things I want to talk
about them and hopefully you guys will
all share the same annoyances probably
not honestly yeah probably not but my
pet peeves you being gonna oh one of my
biggest pet peeve is immaturity I hate
when people don't act age if they should
like James that is literally it so far
every single kid set as my age literally
is in college failing all other classes
and partying every night getting crunk
and I'm here running an empire
you hang out a little bit the most
immature people ever Hey
stop throwing shade and they're all
immature you're yo that is such a lie
your friend group is literally the
definition of immature you literally
went to a sauna a few weeks ago and were
stopped enemy at 2:00 in the morning
farting in the sauna with your friends
it was funny it's not funny that is
pretty funny some older lady wanted to
just enjoy her time in the sauna and you
guys weren't sitting there farting and
snapchat she probably wanted to dog she
probably did die assumes that's also one
of my pet peeves you like to talk a lot
you don't talk enough so I would rather
not talk and then have you talked the
whole time tell him to shut up
all the comment for that first few
episodes Royce oh my god this is only
the James show of you making your time
man no smells good
well maybe you should open person oh
she's changed her transformation in
school people that don't feel like
paying attention as I could talk and
like mess with the teacher not annoy me
I think that is you in school though I
don't talk in school man every single
class has had my headphones in and like
slept the whole time
oh we're one of those kids I cannot send
people are like disrespectful and
obnoxious and loud in public immature is
a weird topic to like talk about but I
think like everyone is annoyed that
can't really bring ideas to it you know
what I mean
maturity is an epidemic this is not a
PSA thank you for coming to our TED talk
I also remind off with a bang let me
tell you I like when things go my whack
and not in like the business we're all
not like video uploads not in like karma
I like when things happen how they're
supposed to happen sometimes when those
things don't happen how they're supposed
to happen a rush of anger goes through
my body like no other
listen like when you're coming home
after very long time
right and you take off your shoes using
one but to kick it off and then you have
one shoe left on one foot and you try to
take it off and the shoe doesn't come
off by the way literally makes me want
to scream I don't know why oh when
you're putting on shoes like you step on
the back and they get stuck and you
can't pull it off when it hurts your
finger annoying oh this it goes along
with this - I have a hair dryer in my
bathroom it was a $400 hair dryer which
blows my mind literally why it does do a
good job I will say a prayer to God this
hair dryers cord is literally like the
strongest being I've ever encountered in
my entire life how can a poor be strong
across literally let me tell you this
cord is plugged into my wall okay and I
have a pretty small bathroom sink and
for some reason whenever I move the
hairdryer to start using it first yes
that is exactly the issue and I don't
know why it is one of those things were
for some reason this cord was made so
strong that whenever I pick it up to use
it the second it even moves everything
comes off the counter with it why it
wasn't made that way who made a cord not
these sound like the dumbest issues ever
but they really just get me so angry all
I want to do is do my hair I don't wanna
sit there and have to pick up every
single thing off my bathroom floor
we'll use and what about you well yeah I
just leave it there because it gets me
so angry
every time I do I heard my heavy I
usually always scream in some way
just move your hairdryer to a different
place I don't think there's any other
plugs in that bathroom put it in the
living room with a big mirror and you
got a bunch room for activities what I
don't have to walk out of my bathroom to
go to the living room to do my hair
that's like inconvenient practical
instead of knocking everything over I
guess that is true he's known as
personal problems that you can fix very
easily this is just like a subcategory
of pet peeves it's just a bunch of
umbrella things that all just make you
so mad how do you not even understand
this cuz they're personal problems yes
what fixes don't you have these little
things that like that they don't exactly
work right away it just makes you so oh
oh my phone doesn't charge like when the
chargers in there yes yes I'm a computer
desk I have these like charging ports
that I use and you kind of stick your
phone on there my iPhone is so old and
crosses the charger never works like I
literally have to sit there and shove it
on there like eight times until it
actually registers that it's charging
that is another one of those things that
I get so when you kick butt you can't
find a TV remote in your bed covers yeah
and then you shuffle your bed sheets
then you're claustrophobic get right
back to the get a lovino it with James's
arrived difinitely notice how many you
scissors actually recognized us in
public and I think I got really good at
talking you guys you meet you guys but
there's a few things that tend to get on
my nerves
Oh fan pet peeves Oh risky topic people
in public probably my favorite aspect of
this entire job is to get to thank the
people face-to-face citizens including
me at sensei Juan truly such a cool
experience that is like just rolling her
every time there are however some
situations where it is so not cool one
of them being when I'm eating dinner oh
my god
just wait like ten minutes
so rude and everytime happens I'm like
nice to meet you too and it's usually
not the kids either it's the parents who
will come up to the table with their
kids and drilling behind them and say
hello James
oh my god would you mind if I daughter's
get a picture of you I'd always say of
course as soon as I'm done eating dinner
with steak and french fries stuffed in
my mouth about to scarf down a coat I
owe my god I just thought you looks half
I literally I'm getting angry just
thinking about this do you know what my
biggest pet peeve is and this is dealing
with parents of my god let me I'm
getting this gets me so mad
okay let me tell you a parent will come
up and the sentence will be somewhere
along the lines of this
hi are you are you like James and I'll
say
no I'll say yes I am how are you and
they'll say I have no idea who you are
and I don't know what you do and I don't
know why my kids want a photo with you
but they seem to know who you are so
would you mind taking a picture with my
daughters
excuse me jay-j hi Jane
James hi hi James nice to meet you my
kids won't take a picture with you Jamie
I don't know I don't really know who you
are or what you do or what I want to
take a picture with you I'm a youtuber
actually I do makeup
Oh Johnny that that's cool
yeah can my kids take a picture with you
yeah I'd love to
I really don't know why they want to or
who you are yeah I got it
Shelley Shelley come on thanks again
gents I still don't know why they took a
picture with you but um what's your
facebook so I can check it out later I
would absolutely love but to take a
photo with you but if you are too
nervous and if you send your parrot over
please give them a brief synopsis of who
you'll be taking a photo with so one I
don't feel really uncomfortable having
to explain to them what I'm doing
because that's weird that makes me feel
very very egotistical and that it's not
font so let's stop doing that please and
thank you
Oh usually meanie fans in person is a
great expense but there is one thing
online that really okay what is that so
you know those like voting things where
they get like six of us so it'd be like
me you the Dolan yeah like vote who you
would want out first what they're so I
don't like them either what is the point
of that first of all second of all get
really angry when I get voted out it
I've never won one me I mean I will
admit at dusk it's annoying
it does feel pretty guy when you're
looking at one and you like see yourself
make it to the next round kind of I'm
not gonna lie yeah but it's at the same
point but then when you get voted out it
really one of my biggest pet peeves
probably the top pet peeve to me is when
people think money buys fashion like
when people spend thousands of dollars
on clothes by having no idea how to wear
it you know what I mean like don't get
like don't get like $2,000 Gucci pants I
like red and blue and they get like a
supreme shirt that's yellow and black
but this coat a hundred dollars I think
it works well and it doesn't ever no
you're right just because they sent a
thousand dollars at a luxury store does
not mean it's gonna look good in fact
it's usually gonna look bad there's
things that really had a mass cuz
there's just one certain youtuber not
gonna name any names
um just because you wear a lot of
expensive items they're not gonna go
well together for not the same color or
not the same like style at all so fix
that if you were watching
I just don't like that was the worst
call-out ever that's going from you
someone who literally cannot match an
alpha to save their life this is only
the most first real problem issue I will
ever talk about on social media but
seriously that really gets me good gal
my job is very immobilize iMac but I
also have a laptop an iPad and an iPhone
they're all connected okay they're all
connected through my iCloud and the
whole point of iCloud is to sync all of
your devices together why is it but it's
not how it works no you you would think
but of course you nothing ever goes how
you wanted to go if you walked in this
ear welcome for this you can descend me
a check later how much that work is that
if I am working on my iMac for several
hours then I click Save which you do
every single time and you put your iMac
to sleep if I open my laptop and they're
all connected it should be the same
exact act like why is it not that way
how about you desired that mr.
smartypants probably well obviously
probably won't know probably well
somebody else needs to do that okay
that's just how it should work
thanks for listening oh okay
this pet peeve is about you ah yeah okay
so you'll be on your phone or on your
computer correct
thank you I'll ask you a simple question
like what do you want for dinner
yes you won't answer for like five
minutes and you're like wait what no
that's not true
I always here and then I still answer
you but I answer it five minutes late
when 10 minutes later you look at your
exit or you ordered food but don't be
ungrateful you saw your answer at least
keep but it's like James what time is
our meeting tomorrow 9:30
what that you still get your answer well
I don't understand what the issue is
because I need to know these answers
quickly as sometimes like do you want to
go out to dinner do you want to go get
ice cream right now ten minutes later
close
I think together surprising I think is
going better than I expected
[Music]
no kind of guy I'm a good kind of a
mutually beneficial relationship what is
it called in science Oh a symbiotic
relationship
biology this episode is brought to you
by it's symbiosis even though there was
a lot of things out of noise I would say
that we are living our best life right
now really really good yeah definitely
pretty good in price if you see us in
public please come say hi were nice we
don't buy it
please lot of dinner please tell your
parents who youtubers are before
approaching us Apple please connect your
computer ours people please match your
clothing it's not that hard to do
actually at all mmm-hmm James's shoes
please come off easier his bed stop
being so close to phobic hair dryer stop
having a big walkie wire I love a big
walkie wire and if you decide to break
us you better vote univer I usually am
voted up versus why I get so angry
be thankful even on those lists I made
you famous okay anyways thank you guys
so much for watching I hope you did
enjoy the brothers just a show we are
back we'll be uploading these once every
two weeks now just to give us a little
bit more time to work on those make sure
each episode is perfect and really funny
and really good and really fresh stop
mocking me I hate when you do that Pepe
I wasn't over if you guys didn't do this
episode today it please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
show your sister support and love
definitely leave us a comment or tell us
what you want to see us talking about on
the next episode and click the bell icon
so you can get a notification every time
I upload a brand new video or we upload
a brand new episode if you guys like to
follow me on my
those kind of energy crops my Instagram
Twitter and snapchat are all E&J d12 and
my YouTube which I actually just created
is Ian Jeffrey spelled correctly
cuz it spelled wrong a lot of my things
if you like to follow me and I makeup
tourney you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter lyrical just to trust my
snapchat for behind the scenes and stuff
is same Charles and an extra ask after
Charles if you like the hoodie that I am
wearing and want one of your own which
you definitely should they're pretty bit
and crush don't forget to check out and
shop a sister sauce from Harold calm
hope you guys enjoyed learning a little
bit more about our pet peeves and the
things that really get us good gal we
love you and we will see you into the
next one
[Music]