hi sisters my name is James and welcome
to the first ever episode of the James
and Ian show I'll use sisters out there
now that we've even posted several
videos together on my youtube channel
and it's all just he acts like he's
hated them we have been having a lot of
fun doing them together I'm bored of
school I decided I want to be social
media famous too so we decided that
we're gonna make a video every Sunday
discussing various topics today we'll be
talking about relationships if you were
able to know the perfect boy what would
it look like it yah-hey for personality
there's one BuzzFeed producer that I'm
like right now named Eric so his
personalities yeah shout out Eric I
would take like one of the Dolans bodies
slap on like Cameron dalas face and then
like the talent of Shawn Mendes no
you're perfect it body okay finally
Jenner's face uh-huh Oh that'd be a good
and fresh sister I feel like
relationships for me are very like a
weird a topic to discuss being that like
you have to find some that you like want
to hang out with them be your best
friend but also like because you want to
get on top two straight boys well you
got me there
when it comes to relationship like
opposites are supposed to attract right
and I'm very gay so like if I'm in a
relationship with somebody I need
someone to like balance me out right so
that's why I always go for like very
masculine muscular type men and normally
those are like the straight it's also a
fun challenge like if you know me you
know that I definitely love a good
competition and for me getting with a
straight guy is like winning and a
sister loves winning so examine your
relationships and Jamie's convinced he's
better relationships excuse me I am we
decided to ask you guys can you love
problems and we're gonna give you some
really good relationship advice yeah
sister Jack said my ex-boyfriend cheated
on me two times and wants to get back
together okay well fool me once shame on
you fool me twice shame on me
I want to go for the third time
definitely not Amanda Dolan responded
with broken with my ex because he was
being very control
my supposedly friend is now with him lol
okay all relationship problems aside
that is not a true friend right there
you need to cut her out of her life
before you get him out of your life kind
of both off all we ride a cow Jenna
asked my crush will not notice that I
like him and I'm so obvious about it
what do I do
holy Jenna I will just be honest with
him and tell him that you like them
because honesty is key in a relationship
demo we asked no man likes me I would do
you help of that I'll let you know when
I find out golf sister Alfonso last I'm
gay and I like a guy I don't know a
sexuality what should I do
literally welcome to my world that
sounds like I asked the question as
someone who is Ella best many many times
in the past crushing on straight boys
are boys that like you do not know what
the tea is it's sometimes important to
ask but not on an offensive way because
sexuality obviously something that is
very very private and it's nobody's
business but their own unless they
decide to share it so usually I think it
eventually comes out in a conversation
but I definitely do have one crazy story
that I think I want to share with you
guys today okay I'm really paint the
picture for you so you can like really
relive the story with me so like there
is one social media boy that I will not
name for security purposes from the
south no like I message this person on
snapchat because he had posted like a
gym a flexing picture and I was like oh
wow yeah and he actually ended up
replying and he said oh my god James
Charles I can't believe you just thought
how to meet my girlfriend loves your
videos he watched them together all the
time
I don't think oh thanks so much sister I
had hot makeup on because I had just
finished filming and a few minutes into
the conversation he sent back a snap
that was like wow you're the most
beautiful boy in the entire world and I
was like why and I've like thought he
was kidding like I talked to a lot of
straight guys still that like I'm not
flirty with that I'm like genuinely
friends with but they're always like
playing that game just like really get
me know one gal and it's annoying but
like I'm used to it at this point so I
thought he was kidding around we kept
talking and this boy is close to my age
and he was like you're just so
successful like at our age of how do you
do that and I was like well I work hard
he was telling me how he really wants to
move to LA and be an underwear model so
I was like okay like interesting so does
every other little white boy from the
south so
I was like well if you want to be model
let's see what she got at this point I
was thinking he was still messing with
me but he started sending a bunch of
photos in his underwear and me being the
absolute supermodel that I am I didn't
ask for input
I started critiquing his photos that's
the OH your but luckily about in this
one like your faceless really about it
this one like get it together gal if you
want to be an underwear model
they kind of step your game up somehow
the conversation shifted to like his
body and Holly wanted to look better and
then like to relationships and asking if
I've ever been a relationship and then I
told him no what are you doing ignore
that and then whom I'll see got my
hookups which I've also all ended very
very poorly to them him saying oh I feel
like you'd give her very good if you
know where I'm going with that so I was
like yes I do but why are you asking and
he's like oh I would totally let you at
that point the realization that he was
in fact not kidding and was being dead
serious hit me like a bus going a
million miles per hour well he does that
has heard of this or he gets interesting
yeah so he started getting intense
artistry and started sending more photos
that weren't exactly appropriate if you
get what I'm putting on the table here
he was saying all this stuff and
flirting with me and he told me how he
like wants to fight a California I'm
like take me on a date and then like do
stuff at the end of the night and it to
this I was like as hot as you are and as
much as I am enjoying this conversation
I am NOT doing anything with you if you
have a girlfriend and you know what he
said to me I don't he literally said and
I quote she's a huge fan of you and if I
told her she would not even care
oh so she's a sister yeah apparently a
real true hardcore sister I need to take
a step with my pink drink this is
getting intense after viewing this
obviously I was like very very shocked
but I assumed because he said that his
girlfriend wouldn't care and like knows
that he's apparently not straight that
they were in some type of like open a
relationship type of situation so after
hearing that I was in it to win it
that's all happened at like 2:00 in the
morning as well so I'm sure you can
imagine like what was going on in
the brain at this week and things
started getting really really flirty or
really fast and also very very out of
hand and apparently yeah if a photo was
not a - was obviously a lot of details
to the story that I do not need to get
into but I will say that this very long
and late night ended with him facetiming
me and doing his business after that
night fast-forward and he completely
ghosted me for two months straight
his girlfriend probably found out we're
getting in there so I sent him a really
really long message that basically said
if you do not want to talk anymore I
understand why I do not blame you I
don't want to come in between your
relationship and I do respect that but I
respect you as a person as well and I
generally had a really good time talking
to him he was super sweet the night we
talked sexual aid sin that is obviously
really really hard to do but then
clearly a sister was confused so I
basically said if you ever need to talk
to you about it but you know you can
trust and like that will give you good
advice as someone who's been there
before I got you and to that message he
literally sent back the Rudess reply of
Mansoul oh yeah very very salty what
really got me good though and is the
kicker of this entire story is that it
was his birthday a few days ago happy
birthday man no not happy birthday and
he came up on my explorer page on
Instagram because I never actually
followed him in the first place but I
saw a picture of him and his girlfriend
still happily together and I noticed
that he had unfollowed me on Instagram
and I was like oh this is rude but I had
sent him a happy birthday text which is
my second message to him over the entire
process of the thing he ignored it did
not reply and at that point I was like
oh who at his game over you played with
the wrong girl but I'll putting this
aside the situation is obviously been
like on my mind for the past several
months because they caught feelings for
him fast it's very clear yeah and I also
felt really really bad for the
girlfriend after all this went down
because clearly something was going on
and I thought she knew at this point so
I sent a sister a message on Instagram
asking her to FaceTime me ASAP because
it was digging at me and I really just
wanted to tell her the truth tea
basically I told her girlfriend the full
story for I let's start to finish in
full detail which was so incredibly hard
for me not only was I like super
incredibly embarrassed of what I had
obviously done being
I had no idea that she did not know what
was going on clearly he lied you didn't
do anything but it definitely was
assault yeah hundred percent but also
just seeing her being so happy and what
she thought was a genuine relationship
it'll be coming crashing down like over
a FaceTime call was just way too much to
handle obviously she was very very
alarmed and overwhelmed and who wouldn't
be and I told her that if she had any
questions are needed to talk to me
throughout that day that she could
totally come to me I would be there for
her and she told me that she was going
to see him later on so she would
confront him about it not even 30
minutes later I started getting the most
gross disgusting text messages from the
boy who I have not talked to but I've
tried to reach out to several times in
the last two months I've ever seen in my
entire life
they contained racist slurs homophobic
slurs just literally everything you
could possibly imagine
he literally started calling me psycho
and mentally unstable claiming that I
made everything up yeah I'm sure you
imagine him something using a show as
nine-inch just wondering what was your
thought process thinking you'd make all
this up do you have a lawyer I literally
do not know that was my thing too like
why would I literally call somebody at
10 in the morning while I was doing my
makeup in the middle of like going to a
photo shoot just to say like hi I'm a
complete awful person and I got photos
from your boyfriend who you're in a
happy relationship with and I'm now
calling you to admit that because I care
about you and don't think you'd like
deserve that but apparently I'm lying
like Hello I did not tell the story
today to try to like expose the two
people I'm definitely not about that but
I think that this does have a really
good message behind it that a lot of
people tend to forget when they're in
relationships sexuality is obviously a
very very hard and uncomfortable topic
for a lot of people to deal with I'm
very lucky to have an amazing support
system in my family but for people like
this way that I'm talking about it
sometimes becomes a situation where
you're in the closet or you're in denial
and even though we had a really great
time on FaceTime that one night doing
all that stuff he turned his confusion
into literal targeted homophobia towards
me and exchange for helping him which
not only put me in a really horrible
situation his beautiful girlfriend who I
spoke to and that I can tell it's a
really really genuine and kind person is
there an absolutely tax relationship
that she has absolutely no idea about
and it's clearly delusional over and the
boy is gonna have to live with this in
the back of his mind for the rest of his
that not only did he cheat on his
girlfriend but he also like really
messed with me
yeah after hearing that I would also
like to add that although relationships
might seem perfect you have to put your
own well-being first because really she
didn't and ya didn't turn out too well
it's definitely very important to listen
to the people around you who care about
you and love you because they usually
have your best intentions in mind
absolutely I feel like that's really
just took me at 76 years to towel but
yeah do you have any crazy cross stories
maybe my DMS are quite interesting but
that's for a later video
oh ho alright guys that is all we have
for our first ever episode of the James
that Ian show but there are so many more
episodes to come and we had so much fun
filming today and we really hope you
guys enjoyed it too you guys did enjoy
this video give it a huge thumbs up if
you haven't already make sure you click
that big red subscribe button I normally
post makeup videos on Tuesdays and
Fridays so if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me at
Instagram or Twitter they both just
changed Charles and my snapchat for war
or how the seats I stuff is same Charles
the next row ask after Charles if you
like to follow a sister Ian just tell
them your social media my social medias
are in JD twelve alright guys thank you
so much for watching we love you and
we'll see you next week bye
[Music]