hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back at 22 channel and as you
guys can see I've done it's two very
very iconic and legendary
special guests it's the Sarah Kim K and
a father Mario over here literally one
big happy family you guys I am so
excited for today's brand new video
because we're doing a beauty battle
which is a very popular series that I do
here on this YouTube channel where two
different people take half of my face
but for today's video I'm not in the
middle is this the first time you're not
in the middle yeah oh wow that's cool
yeah I'm really excited to see how this
turns out because I'm so used to Mario
on my face I I don't think I've ever
done the half-and-half thing
well I'm not only notice it does your
makeup every single day so that's a
little bit alarming but I can maybe do
this a little bit I'm I'm excited
because I'm just gonna tell you I mean
I've been doing it for ten years of
doing makeup for 19 a little lazy at
this point so I'm like any help I can
get it I'm like I love the idea of like
someone else doing half of being your
assistant said I know I'm gonna actually
try to how'd you do the whole bigger
butt game okay yeah we've been talking
for a while now bunching of videos I was
super super excited at the knw Mario
launch party actually were talking about
North watching my video yes she's
obsessed she actually when this when you
sent me your palette she tried to take
it I saw it with her room and I was like
oh no no no because she's so hard with
it well she just like destroys a palette
yeah so no I took it back and we fought
over your palette
yeah that's good yeah it's kind of fun
fresh like every another one to bring
back so she can see right it'll be all
over the floor so maybe I'll wait to
give it for Christmas that's a good
Christmas Carol I'm super excited
Myanmar volcanic land half of Kim says
we have 45 minutes to do so first of all
things at the beauty industry how we all
met and stuff what it's like working
together and more
[Music]
all right guys so I'm just gonna zone
out and let you do your thing we know
what book you want to do because she's
filming after this day swim for a show
I'm just gonna be realistic and be
practical and I'm just gonna do
something simple and like a Kim K smoky
look that she likes to do for filming
well you do whatever you want you know
I'm just doing that because you know I
just have to be practical
well I wanted to do something like
colorful and funky and fast cuz I feel
like it was a separate time then like I
really do want to do like a full
colorful thing yeah but should we do if
I tell you guys I look like I want like
a bronzy smoke eye with a black liner
and then see what both of your
interpretation of that is oh that's a
fun idea to come see if you guys can
make me look the same
oh I thought that I was walking into I
didn't know it was gonna be like a Mario
in cages like I thought it was gonna be
like let's see who can do a classic camp
like will it look the same I like that
idea though I think that is fun
tricolour another day for a good
Instagram oh man yeah you tell us what
lucky we're in let's pretend she's our
client so what do you want today kid I'm
kind of in love with like those three
okay actually those four those are like
Oh Jerry Henderson off the no beans
I like a cut crease okay I am great at
this no shimmer I like super bad okay
yeah you smoke you agree to it 90s oh my
god grease bronze 90s look darker liner
and lighter lip all right are we
starting yeah I guess we are
I'm constructed foundation I know Mario
started this brows
okay I'm gonna pray that this foundation
matches you the sisters are well aware
that I am NOT the best data at this
point so it's okay it's the thought that
counts and I warrant turn on that good
mom sleep on her bed yeah no we love
that that's me cover everything else you
can't tell that's how we do whatever
work mmm sounds like a personal problem
not at work okay well I have a lot of
questions for both you guys together
I'm super super excited to be sitting
all together as one big happy family cuz
it's been a while since we're all off
together first of all you guys like a
single-handedly have really changed the
makeup industry when it comes to trends
and does everything that goes along with
it you guys have created so many iconic
and beautiful looks together so like how
long have you guys been working together
and like tell us a little bit about you
know the classic story
it's been almost 11 years now I got
booked to do a cover shoot with her it
was a little local magazine in the
Hamptons and a photographer of mine
called me one night and said hey I need
you to do makeup for this girl named Kim
Kardashian for this cover shoot tomorrow
and I was like I kind of heard her name
she was not famous it was like season
one of her show we think she was just
starting to gonna name here in the
States
and I had a job at this other job that I
had booked already so I was kind of like
touring I'm like you know I can't really
do it going in I was like I love it I
wound up doing it did her makeup she was
very sweet and she took selfies the
entire day man you know this is before
like and then she asked me to take her
makeup shopping that same day we were
done oh love I loved it was the first
time I really feel like I looked really
right like yeah and I just felt like
super like this Armenian authentic look
that I just feel like when I would get
my eyebrows done like it would just kind
of like take that away from me and he
just like brought that back but in this
glam way that I had never seen before
I had never had my makeup done like that
before he was like new right away I just
yeah I went back to the hotel and I just
took so many eggs I still have them I
took so many all the truth
yeah on what is it called on your
computer on today's photo booth yeah I
took like hundreds of photo booth photos
and I have them all you know what is now
that she loved was the you know I did
the baking the contouring the
highlighter did all those things in her
that she liked really loved and
never-ending experience before that is
so cool yeah and then she just got
really only getting really super busy
after that she started requesting me for
everything you know I live in New York
and she was in LA so she would start
flying me out to LA and you know I
started working with her doing like all
her stuff there what's gonna happen if I
like James's makeup better well then
when I'm in New York living my life
James can come over here Ella said five
and the more you do makeup sounds kind
of fun maybe one person I'm just setting
it your face lightly in place with some
Prince's a setting powder to really lock
it all in there oh oh I'm so excited
right now
contour James we only have 45 minutes
and I'm gonna do entire ilog to the
crease Wow brave you have to give the
client what they want
thank you cam what has been your
favorite looked at Marion has ever done
on you oh that's so hard
honestly I really did love our met look
that we did last year it was very 90s
too and I think I've just been really
stuck on that with the darker lip and
like kind of reshaping how
do the upper lip a little bit
differently than usual nose humbler know
sometimes my favorites that might make a
person I love just play making it look
like literally I can't thank you I'll
have my assistant Kim Kardashian I'm the
same face right on Kim's cheekbone turn
it side honey
James done her so Phil's an HDTV with
them hmm
you mind your business you learned from
Mario actually favorite track Kim
obviously now you have kkw which is it
so amazing and the products are so long
how I was like starting your own makeup
line changed your career and your love
for makeup it definitely made me see
makeup in a really practical way I think
that a lot of people were really like
the consumer was really scared of
contour but I know all my friends were
really scared of contour you're like
concealer in you know three steps and to
figure it all out so I tried to make it
as simple as possible and to try to
really explain that and bring like the
tricks that I learned
yeah with Mario about the years with
Mario to the consumer in a really easy
way I love about super dope the whole
thing with our line is how to take like
the industry techniques and things like
that but simplify for the girls at home
so they can do it super easily right
because like Kim there's a lot of girls
at home that you know are not like super
artistic when it comes to doing their
makeup and you know they just need
something easier so I figured I could do
it you can do it even though I've sat in
the makeup chair for you know 12 years
straight
I really didn't know a lot about I know
what I like to look at I know what I
like to feel I can tell what really good
formulas are and I think you know
with my k'kaw beauty brand we just have
really like perfected the formulas and I
just wanted something that was really
simple kanga Debbie's obvious like a
very social media-based brand to with
you and Barbie on switch media so much
how would you think social media has
affected the business I'm like what you
do on their day to day life if they feel
like obviously plays a huge role it's
really insane I mean it's fun to
obviously be in a store and to have
people come out and feel and touch and
use the product really you just honestly
you can it's so amazing to me that you
can start a whole business and a brand
fund just social media just creating
your own world and that's been so much
fun is having full control over ID
campaign images and who you work with
and what you do and what products you
pick and rotor packaging looks like and
it can be anything you want it to be and
if something doesn't work you can change
it is because you want like I don't know
if I'm mixing up like owning my own
business and social media but like the
both of them together has been so much
fun to have the creative control a
hundred percent but I honestly couldn't
have done it without Mario you know I
love his advice and his opinion has it
been interesting watching like different
makeup people like beauty gurus like try
the products in seven review it has just
like seeing that like my formulas we
take a lot of time and put into them so
seeing the response online or someone
that I really love and respect and
they're trying the shadows and they see
how pigmented they are they try the
lipstick and they say like my new
lipsticks or the liners or stuff they
use all the time like that makes me so
happy
right okay I'm gonna grab tuned wait can
I also get the first thing that we've
got because it's because of Arielle yeah
Ariana's ariana grande considers with
Nora I took her to the concert and Mario
text me and was like oh my god Jean
there you have to go say hi I was salted
attack another James wrote me and it's
like oh my god sister Kim is here and I
want to be her well I wasn't now hold on
I posted it on my story being there then
you must watch out chef yes and your
plan was a : under Ariana Kim's there
too and I was like no way
and then you were like oh I'm gonna text
her right now and I was like you're
literally ten engage texted her and she
said yeah of course I'm coming and then
five minutes later this huge security
guard shows up in front of I see it's
like I'm looking for James I was like
think about me oh yeah I was like tell
me a seat number then you came over and
you were so nice I was so nervous to
look who's nobody were like a year and a
half ago almost two years ago now
probably yeah
so I wasn't super super nervous because
I was like kind of at the beginning of
like my makeup career like I think I was
only at like two million at the time of
three million maybe so I was like I had
never linked that like a celebrity
before
I always like looked up to you and like
watched Keeping Up and sucked so I was
so excited they put together I think
yeah okay so are like your favorite
things to do with the kids my kids like
very different things so it's really
hard to do things all together oh my god
no this is the key to making up her song
I need we need to talk about ear and sat
down sorry from a few weeks ago that was
the funniest thing I've ever seen in my
entire life
k'kaw Beauty black eyeliner oh I moved
I'm sorry I moved I didn't know it would
cause this much of a big deal my makeup
artists usually don't act this way yeah
he was very confusing because she said
she wanted to film a YouTube video
then okay I'll film it on my phone so I
started coming in and then she would see
the camera and then she fall out crying
oh so I was just like I you're very
confusing so her to work with yeah very
so that she like did a look and then she
didn't like what she saw says she
started crying and I was like it's fine
we'll just you know wipe it off and
start over so we did that maybe for a
different time whole when finally I just
was like I have to give it up this is
your final look this is you gotta figure
it out
did I come together on the end it did Oh
God yeah she really liked it so none of
those like super into makeup ha yeah she
really is yeah she's really into makeup
into squishies and my son is just like
the opposite so she loves to have like
friends over do makeup on dolls on her
on over makeovers it's her thing yeah
she just likes to play makeover doesn't
Iike that with with your palette
oh don't I'll have my people can I try
to people submerge she does a really
good job like on herself but she's
really into making her brows really dark
oh because I mean I have lots of
experience I feel a bronze to director
but she just takes a pen you know I'm
just yeah that's pretty much what is you
bought your stuff over there I've heard
a lot that I like not so cool so like
you can give her tips how I would love
to wait all this right now she is she's
afraid okay so as she hadn't a jet where
like she actually like wants her makeup
her she just playing with that I mean a
little bit of both like she's not fully
there yet where she's like I can't leave
the house without you know rush on or
whatever but she loves like a bright
colors lipstick and then if I go in on
her like it's if it's like a special
occasion like her favorite color is
purple and Kylie had this color junebug
and she
he would wear it all the time then Kylie
like made her our custom own purple
packaging so she'll wear like a lipstick
color out and then like she'll ask me
like 10 times is my lipstick still there
it's all there
can you see my lipstick is really cute
is there a evening cute like letter I
start experimenting at maybe like 12 mm
maybe 14 I give this question a lot too
because I get a lot of parents that like
support my YouTube channel and say that
they watch the videos with their
daughter or sons which I always think is
so cool like it means a lot to me and a
lot of parents ask me like being like oh
well like what parent but what age did
you start wearing it I started at 16
doing my own makeup but I always say
like one of my biggest things that I
preach on my channel it's like I do not
wear makeup like to feel pretty I do not
wear makeup because I feel like I need
to wear a tie breaker because it's fun
yeah feeling beautiful and I love like
expressing my art and like playing with
it and seeing like what I can create
yeah and I think like because I get that
question so for me I owe a sailing if I
were to have kids which I never well I
would let them play with it whatever as
long as I knew like yeah and I think you
know the kids see me with with him
without makeup on all the time so they
know it's not like you know if anything
there was a point when I would get my
hair and makeup done and North which is
like start to cry and be like don't get
your makeup done
and cuz she knew that that's when mom
had to work right and mom was gonna
leave soon after that yeah so she hated
that but I really do agree with that
it's like just about being fun it's not
really I mean for me when I makeup on it
does transform my mood it transforms my
whole you know personality what does it
do exactly when you have a really
amazing makeup on as opposed to when you
don't have makeup on like what does it
do to you as a woman celebrity I think
that it from
it makes me feel more confident when I
have makeup on but I think it's the both
I think it's like hair and makeup but if
you were to say you can only do one I
would pick getting my hair done yeah
because I do like natural beauty as well
well me years ago I would have been
makeup hair I think just like when my
hair is done I feel like I can have a
not more natural face I don't know I
just think that when my makeup is done
like really good you just like feel
yourself you know I mean you really do
really get in to it you just aren't such
a good mood it just enhances what you
have what was the point I'll make out
yeah hey she said that only she doesn't
want shimmer that's good yeah that's
okay to do your own thing sometimes
isn't they wind up living in anyway well
if you pick the shiny end and the good
news is that he gets to redo this I can
when you are just getting ready and
Mario isn't here and it's just you
how long does your LBD routine take you
you're really gonna die at this one
about seven minutes I can do a full face
in like five minutes
so she's um she's one of the most
incredibly patient people in Hindi good
in the universe such an incredibly
common patient but she's just like when
it comes to doing her own makeup she's
like not patient in that sense yeah I
just it just went you doing or something
it just says I'm just like who has time
to blend all day yeah I just don't I
wish I did she's very patient like with
other people working on her lately she
doesn't really rushed people too much
so uh right now it's a challenge north
about the mama challenge
it'll of jealous she always does like
beauty challenges in her room like okay
we're both gonna get this doll and make
up her
let's see who has the better luck but
she always wants to win okay me I think
we ignored leave that I know kind of
fresh so because we're on a time limit
I'm not gonna do any cream contour I'm
gonna go ahead straight into the powder
contour thanks father
because if this is contour viable
contour I'm usually thinking that me
Beauty reckoning powder this is the new
one the best
I still use this all the time ever seen
I love this powder it's so bomb you guys
been working together for a very very
long time now that's been incredible to
watch your guys's journey and like
almost you've created together how would
you say like your makeup style has
changed over the past few years and like
where do you see the industry Dali my
makeup style definitely goes in waves so
sometimes like we were super glam really
into a really light under eye that was
like our thing you know really smokey
eyes are lashes that we would wear would
be like only strips then we got to a
really natural place where it was like
hardly any shadow now we've started to
like glam it up a little bit more it's
always fun like what our papa blue or a
pop of color you know smokey eyes lots
of liner we definitely have like stepped
it up again are you just like messing
the glam yeah I mean I think it's just
like everyone you know you go through
things I think after having kids you
just don't have time for that I've have
your makeup and then once they're a
little bit older you're like okay wait I
know that's fun it's so much fun so
right now I feel like we're in a glam
area you know very painted very beat you
know very much very very neutral these
extensions are these are real lashes
these are my lashes no no no no no no
the 45 on that nothing but the Y no no
no I concern natural estrogen swear
you're kidding you use this looks flesh
from
absolutely
[Music]
it's like Oh James that looks incredible
[Laughter]
every slightly concerned I think you
should I think he's just gonna look up
and then I could just be like okay we'll
only felt from me on this side
okay guys times that I've done I've been
dying by that domestic air
oh wow very unprofessional REO listen
he's probably fire have time to kill us
how it's time to kill you guys what
should I do like the meal could like
post an Instagram picture maybe someone
at our YouTube video right now maybe get
some mascara on the root of this day Wow
just teasing guys are we done we are
done
[Music]
join your clothes off yeah I did okay
ready for this for the grand reveal you
guys I love it this is really good I
feel like this is such a fun video to do
and there's nobody else that I would be
more honored to battle than father Mario
himself oh my god you guys think this
was a so love it and like I can't choose
which look I feel like it's nice man I
feel like it'd be disrespectful to ask
you to choose like yeah yeah I love them
both too soon but that's pretty good
no they're both they're both so you're
both snatch I mean more time this is
what's not well yeah getting lazy earth
my goal was to have someone else in LA
so I could go home and take a little
break she can call you son sister Kim
can't decide at me ed murrow need all of
you guys to climb at da wall let us know
what side you like better already guys
that I think that is all we have first
today's new video with sister Kim and
father Mario thank you guys so much for
coming on them
thank you guys so much for coming on the
channel I haven't so much fun doing this
I'm so nervous and we have to do Oracle
glam something very very soon yeah and
soon we'll be shaking if you guys enjoy
today's video is sister Kim and Mario
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and to your sisters
support I love um you know so so so much
to me let me know if you guys want to
see a video of me doing a camera's at a
rainbow glam but let me know if you want
to see a video with the father Mario
we're here
well sweetest tell them anyways let's
see if anywhere Mario does my glam
spoiler alert we actually just filmed
heirloom that's warning and the look
that I have on right now it looks really
beautiful as you guys can tell but we
just filmed it for fun but if you guys
actually want to see that video we
talked about a lot of things with the
beauty industry
Kevin Mario working together and just
the life of the celebrity makeup artist
I had so much fun doing so so if you
guys want that video leave us a comment
down below if you have not already don't
forget to click that bigger subscribe
button down below come to this
sisterhood we were over 11 million
sister Xiong oh my god I think the
family is growing so fast so thank you
guys so much for all your love and
content
support and also don't forget to click
that belt like until you could get
notifications every time I upload a
brand new video don't forget that this
video is being uploaded in two separate
meeting it's one of the days of the
December holiday give us leis oh my god
you guys we were giving away PR boxes
MacBook Airs
and a logo hoodie from the sisters of
hair loss soda collection don't forget
read all the rules and follow all the
information in the description box down
below to enter if you like to follow me
and I make them turn you can follow me
on Instagram or Twitter they're both the
same Charles a myself more behind the
scenes lights up is James house that I
should ask after Charles these two need
no further interruption but where can
they find you guys makeup I marry also
they're hosting a masterclass on
February 9th in LA the master quest.com
my man James will be there as well but
I've been telling my organs to do an
alley masters hotspur like something
might happen two years ago and you're
said now it's finally happening you guys
better come and get your tickets out the
master family you see hasn't started
it's pretty good and fun fresh this
video is sister psittacosis sister kaya
thank you so much love for always a
falling in support you know I love you
so so so much and if you like should be
the next videos a sister shadow don't
worry it's always a treat removing
leaves when they go live on Twitter all
right you guys thank you so much
watching this videos today I really
really hope you loved it happy holidays
[Music]