hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel this
is definitely a video set up you guys
have never seen before and that's
because today we are playing a crunch
tag game with James obviously if I saw
if I recreated my old soccer bers I used
to be a religious Mario Kart Wii Hummer
recently there has done like a kind of
resurgent rebirth if you will of
Minecraft in the YouTube community and I
am so here for it literally like it used
to be my favorite thing in the entire
world I would go home from school every
single day and be some kitty girls up in
the Minecraft Hunger Games and that is
exactly what we're gonna be doing in
today's brand new video there's a
tournament called minecraft Mondays
where basically you compete to the death
a bunch of other youtubers last week I
was teamed with the legend PewDiePie and
it was probably some of the most fun
three hours of my entire life we didn't
exactly when we didn't even get close
let's be really kind of lucky sot james
team playing yeah that's happening okay
where are you did you die i'll be
revitalised
be my eyes on the sky mama huh that's
right you don't call me mama please
James which is reading all the comments
and the memes and people posting little
clips of our playback was so much fun
and watching it has made me really angry
because I used to be good at this game
but now I saw so for today's video I
thought it'd be kind of fun to introduce
house china games with James to all my
YouTube subscribers and play a little
bit of the Minecraft Hunger Games while
I go ahead and practice and get ready
for next week's minecraft Monday
my twitch stream all up and live which
by the way if you guys want to follow me
on Twitch it is twitch.tv it's lots of
jade Charles Beauty for more hashtag
games of James in the future it's gonna
be so fun and so fresh without further
ado oh good lord this is gonna be a long
video after the chat to pay respect
so in said I'm not disguised oops stop
hitting me oh my god absolutely not are
you literally kidding me oh my god I
love playing this game and getting
targeted oh my god you've got to be
[ __ ] kidding this is homophobia alive
and thriving on Twitch look at me just
climbing the trees
and looking for some chests give me
something good
oh wow I take another pants amazing
thank you so much yes I like to think
that only God but also cheap-ass okay
basically Oh
are you kidding me
that was rude and homophobic I really
want to win at least one game during
this video I just feel like I need you
to like just one like just one literally
just Treasure Island is by far my
favorite map like it's so fun I was
playing that last night too and I won
this one three different times so I
don't know why I feel like Treasure
Island is my good luck charm
ah click off them so bad in this game no
[Music]
this is gonna end up being a company
some video be just die but that's okay
yes my favorite god bow it's a sign let
me out of here
I'm gonna let you fall what will be
under Perrault you're kidding girl what
though
why are we the worst of this game at the
wall I love that we definitely are gonna
fight and then we're gonna
oh my god this is embarrassing this is
this is why I'm not gonna win we're just
gonna keep going until you get a victory
just one just one that's literally all
we need is just one okay the thing is
playing with my acrylic nails isn't so
hard you guys like it's so so so so
challenging because I have a flat
keyboard but like what I write like hit
anything it's like my nails sometimes
hit but the key above it which is okay
oh this is not the way I wanted to go
let's kill some people shall we
oh my god what is wrong
what a little wrong way so awful with
this we're playing on the Minecraft
Monday literally like she had a diamond
sword Oh cheesy like a godly good gal
let me out of here
it's literally first one to find a chest
and a weapon is like the winner oh okay
I bow it's like absolute to see anyone
who's wondering I am before our game
we're so good you guys
[Music]
that was the most embarrassing thing
I've ever done on this game by far oh
thank god you've got to be kidding me oh
oh oh my god are you kidding
that was a team
[Music]
oh my god let me go Oh
Donald's Sugata yeah come in son
yeah absolutely son you guys know I do
love it oh yes and I saw a chest
suddenly we're with it this caucus
Everdeen is shocked oh my god that the
server lag that was so long
[Music]
oh Jesus all right you guys we got our
first actual kill of the server oops why
am i holding my it stick
oh we go with this no [ __ ] each other
[Music]
really it was my mom's favorite this
month punch
what fun sweetie I got pests oh my god I
would lose that hell
thank you don't touch me ever muscle
learn hopefully you know let's go this
way let's light this one look at that
get this ready they're gonna oh my God
look at that look at this look at this
oh they're teeny ma no oh absolutely not
okay we're gonna lose get him go get on
[Music]
look at the airplane oh go away let me
go home
absolutely not to be 60 and 38 don't you
have respect let me out of here oh I
can't or oh shoot
oh it's a bit of all there's some lever
that you can pull here oh wait oh really
[Music]
I'm so bad at this oh this whole spread
thing is so annoying I need to get
better at it this person already has a
weapon nice fun thank you
why are you following me there's so many
other people that you could kill only
wait why why not just guys it's my skin
what doctor you follow me [ __ ] you oh my
god
that's what the [ __ ] hasn't been my skin
the entire time is that why people keep
killing me well not I mean no let's be
real I'm sucking that's not excuse you
to kill people there's nobody even over
here no you are kidding me
do I sound like one of the not really
the tearing this system on the server is
so weird like if you
what I just killed him oh wow
yes okay Treasure Island here we go this
is my favorite I have a very specific
route that I me and Isaac we're taking
last night that I am liking it so I hope
that we get to go that way I think it's
this one it is this one oh there's the
chest right there yes oh my god
I don't know this not at all I think I'm
officially the worst person to at this
game ever oh let's go help this guy out
for the father we're not gonna win
anyway
oh oh oh that was not good idea James
suit oh no really you're gonna kill me
you idiot
good luck oh my god like that's just
dumb
good job like really really good one
dude this is good somebody where's
somebody out who wants to feel my
vengeance
oh absolutely not get out of here gets
out oh my god this is homophobia
let me out of here oh my god oh my god
the choices that I ended up making or so
questionable team okay to still like the
one fire
yeah-ha-ha suit
Oh like a harder this is a sick job
right now
ladies thank you guys so much for
watching at this twit stream tonight
I hope you had fun I don't know if I did
you know I was having a lot of fun last
thing I had a lot of fun on minecraft
Monday because you know I was doing ok I
don't know how can I think I got worse
so that's great and I hope you guys are
excited for Minecraft Monday to watch me
lose clearly because we're not getting
any closer to winning right now I'm
gonna continue practicing every single
day until I win one of these things
because I am putting it on the record
right now James Charles will win a
minecraft Monday ventually but I hope
you guys enjoyed my youtube little
compilation clip of me basically just
dying over and over again if you sisters
into this video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
shared love and support please let me
know if you guys actually enjoying this
like gaming content this is obviously
new for me this is very very different I
would love to continue doing this but
only if you guys want to see it so let
me know with a thumbs up don't give it a
thumbs down or your hair if you've not
read it as well make sure you click that
big red subscribe button down below and
come join this sisterhood I would love
to have you and then family and if you
have not ready make sure you follow me
on my makeup journey on Twitter they're
both just James Charles and myself have
more behind the scenes I said the same
Charlotte extras after Charl and now we
have to add to this by twitch in stage
Carl's Beauty also leave a comment down
below and let me know if you guys want
to see me play any other games as well I
would love to play Mario Kart I have to
figure it out maybe some black ops
perhaps I'll become a professional for
Lia player ninja you better watch out
sister but yeah I really look forward to
hearing what you guys have to say about
this video this video is sister shadow
sister Emily thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting you know I
love you so so so much
and I feel like through the next videos
a sister shout-out don't forget to
always reach me by video listen I go
live on Twitter alright sisters thank
you so much for watching it games with
James today I love you and I will see
you in the next one bye
[Music]