hi brothers
i'm james and i'm ian and welcome back
to brother and sister
sister brother brother and sister sister
brother i can't talk like this for long
as brother and sister that's your
brother
okay whatever
for today's episode we thought it would
be really good
and fun so in case you have not been on
youtube for the past
year you may have missed probably the
biggest trend
of all time first of all you're doing it
wrong
when you talk you have to go like that
that happens later no
it goes on for today's episode
we're gonna be doing asmr if you can
already tell
because we're whispering so it's
probably obvious
ninety percent of the heat comments i
get on my videos on a daily basis
are that people hate my voice and to
those comments i say
i agree so this should be really fun
um and hopefully you really like my
voice if i'm not
really talking so that's good that's
kind of all the way around
shhh it's kind of the other way around
for me what do you mean
like people like my voice like oh my god
your voice is so deep it's not true
right sorry guys you're not gonna be
hearing much
so i've really only watched a few asmr
videos and i'm going to be honest going
into this
i have not really gotten the tingles
from them
i know that they do actually help a lot
of people with anxiety and with stress
for me they help me in a different way
which is
laughing at comedy yes for today's video
we thought it'd be really fun
to go into this with an open mind and
really try to
make it tingle for a real one
we are going to just be talking and
interacting
and we're a sister starting so probably
gonna order some food
and do a mukbang together wait wait
so hopefully we catch a good and you
just
tingle for a real one so
that's girl wait what even is asmr
good question i google that asmr
stands for autonomous sensory meridian
response i don't know what two of those
words mean
it's an experience characterized like a
static
like or tingling sensation on the skin
that typically begins on the scalp and
posed at the back of the neck and upper
spine
i'm scared
[Music]
don't touch me i'll still hate you in
asmr form
so delicious and refreshing
i oh one
oh oh my god oh sorry
today i'm just gonna put on some makeup
mama
not sponsored but it sounds really good
right now
please hello can i place an order for
delivery please
uh yeah sure are you okay yes
can i get a shake chicken shark with no
herb now
i'm sorry you need to speak
[Applause]
[Music]
i didn't shake chicken chocolate no herb
made please i
mayonnaise is disgusting
can i get a vanilla shake is this a
prank call
no please give us our food okay i think
i got it
perfect thanks i want my shake shack
right now
three days later okay
first we're gonna try the red drives
kind of cold
these are kind of the worst ever
not really disappointing
i need to chew my mouth closed ew i've
never eaten on camera before
okay i'm over this next food
hello
okay i'm
jesse
this sandwich needs some more flavor so
i'm gonna squirt
some ketchup on there for a real sister
squirt
lava got squirt
[Music]
oh
okay
how's your chicken chicken
let us know in the comments do you enjoy
watching asmr videos because
while i'm filming this i feel like i
feel very creepy
and weird i'm uncomfortable and yeah but
it's kind of fun and fresh it kind of is
i'm gonna take a bite of this crunchy
chicken slab of
meat it's kind of not that crunchy
though because it's kind of this one
this one's crunchy
this is so weird
this is the weirdest thing i've ever
recorded in my life
and i have to be quiet but i feel like
now the whole world is at like this
talking level
so adding a loud noise sounds weird
it's kind of scary like i feel like when
we leave here i'll still be whispering
oh my god it's like that movie um a
quiet place
[Music]
hopefully the microphone picks that up
and you guys got to tinkle to my
grumbles
we thought it'd be really fun and to do
another phone call
so we're gonna call our mother should we
have a plan
no just call her backwards to say hi we
miss you a lot
turn it up
hey bud hi mom how are you
you okay yeah i'm fine how are you doing
why are you whispering
what are you doing we're filming an asmr
don't tell her
we just wanted to say hi we miss you
i miss you too i love you guys
i can't i can't wait to see you okay we
need to go bye
okay that was so horrible so since ian
is an idiot
and told my mom within three seconds
while we were doing i
was worried she was fine i'm gonna call
my best friend drew
hi sugar daddy
hey kitty girl what are you doing
i just wanted to go and say that i miss
you the most
oh are you crying no i'm fine
oh i thought you were literally crying
it sound like you were like oh my god
you're like
what's up drew who is that ian
yes what do you guys like is whispering
what are you talking about
i'm scared i want to see you
okay wait why are you whispering what
are you talking about you're whispering
we are doing no such thing i'm so scared
you're really spooking me for a real one
i've been really enjoying
very calm things recently such as
whispering
oh is this asmr
yes okay okay hi
guys welcome back to my channel
i'm for you okay i love you i love you
the most
kind of fun who else should we call dad
[Music]
hi james hello
james why are you whispering
we just wanted to call you to say hi and
that we love you and we miss you so much
okay stop wish why are you whispering
what are you talking about
james is dad is your hearing going
i'm gonna hang up on you in a second
this morning
i can't stop whispering i can't hear you
you hear me
james
what are you doing what are you doing
what are you doing
i miss you so much you miss me so much
you're the post can you come back to la
i really miss you
hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
i can't find any outfits for this fall
season
tina not what the attitude
i just found these really cute fresh
eddies at sisters
dashamarill.com perfect for this fall
season
perfect for all the leaves crunching on
the sidewalks
all right sisters i think that's enough
asmr for today
i know i got the tingles did you
i didn't me if you guys did enjoy this
video today
please give it a big satisfying thumbs
up down below with a
and hit that big red subscribe button if
you haven't already
come join the sisterhood it's a pretty
lit time and also click that bell icon
so you can be notified every time i
upload a brand new video
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on instagram
and twitter
they're both just james charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes
stuff it's james charles with an extra
guest
charles if you'd like to follow me on my
asmr journey
you can find me on instagram twitter and
snapchat at enjd12
and my newly made youtube ian jeffrey
thank you guys so much for watching
today's episode we love you and we'll
see you in the next one
[Music]