my sister's James Charles here and
welcome back it's my youtube channel
first today's the day we're doing that I
actually have not done in a very very
very long time and that is a review and
it fills you guys who have been watching
me for a while you know that I don't
really like doing reviews but mostly
because of one they're boring - I don't
release which up my beauty routine that
often and three the general public is
convinced that beauty gurus are
literally spawns of Satan and were sent
down to earth to literally fool
everybody and lied to them into buying
copy products a few days ago I was doing
some sisters shopping the play stylist
online to pick up some really cute
summer clothes and I was on ASOS which
if you don't know what that is
it is a really really cute online
clothing retailer how I can not
sponsored by shag should be and I
actually came across the beauty section
on their website and found out something
that had me shook to the core and that
was that
Crayola the crayon company that we all
used to draw with when we were kids came
out with a full-on makeup line at first
sitting there I was very much sister
stumped on why the heck and our supplies
company would release a makeup line but
then I remembered it's kind of within
the same realm and you guys just saw me
do my full face using only art supplies
a few weeks ago and clearly the actual
products worked out pretty well so it
might not be that strange of a business
move for them but regardless I bought
the entire collection today I'm very
very very excited to see how these
products actually test out will they be
good or will they literally be like
crayons on my face we're gonna find out
so without further ado let's jump right
into the video
[Music]
so lonely isotopes that need to search
up Crayola and it listed that they
launched 57 different items at the
collection which is actually like very
very large I definitely picked up a lot
of different things today that I'm
excited to try out and there are things
on this website ranging from brushes to
eyeshadow palettes to mascaras to
highlighters to face crayons which I'm
have no idea what that a is but I guess
we're going to find out so starting off
I picked up two different eyeshadow
palettes that they launched right off
the bat I'm gonna say packaging
absolutely beautiful this rainbow moment
is so so so cute and I got the nude
eyeshadow palette and the mermaid
eyeshadow palette France if you're
watching this please stop releasing
mermaid and unicorn themed items we are
all over it this has been a PSA the
palette sweet offer $29
and they come with ten shadows and each
kit meaning each shadow is $2.90 Wow I
love being at the queen of math and
they're actually both cruelty free and
vegan which is really really great I
also picked up the Crayola face palette
which once again retails for $29 and
contains a ten different OH
this is the face palette I really
thought this is gonna contain a
contouring color I've grabbed their
customizable lip palette which is $35
and once again contains ten at different
shades perfect for mixing I am very very
excited to try this out later on I don't
know if I knew you guys know this or if
ever tried it but anasazi beverly hills
actually has a really really great
formula for they're customizable lip
palette so I'm gonna be very interested
to see how this performs in comparison
to that one I grabbed the highlighter
cran and the shade shimmering blush and
this one was $17.50 which looks like
this interesting I'm a little bit scared
to put this over top of my foundation
but we're gonna make it work hopefully I
grab two different mascaras and black
and navy blue and these retail for $16
but the years of the collection for me
went a little bit sister so good lord I
picked up some of the Crayola face
crayons and I grabbed a yellow a block a
white a mango color a blue of red and a
nude color just a try out different eye
looks today now these look great on the
website they retail for $14.50 now to me
if this price hike seems a little bit
high beginner you're only getting point
zero seven ounces of product for $14.50
and I know for a fact that milk sells
their jumbo eye pencils for like six
dollars which is literally like the same
exact product hello I literally spent
101 dollars and fifty cents on all seven
of these eye pencils and what I find
even more ridiculous is that you can
literally go to the craft store and buy
a 96 packet of crayons which are
probably let's be honest the exact same
thing is this for nine dollars I got 96
crayons for nine dollars and I got seven
eye crayons for a hundred and $1.50
something does not add up here if you
ask me and finally my last purchase of
this collection is probably the worst of
all them being this Crayola Beauty make
up a brush set in case now when I saw
this breast I online originally I was
like wow it's so cute look at this brush
keys are you kidding me at holographic
Crayola Gorge and then I bought it for
$40 and I opened it up to fines
this for eyeshadow brushes for Quattro I
don't think so before we go ahead and
actually start my look today I thought
we should do some sister swatches of the
different eye crayons because these are
really what I'm most excited to see and
how the heck of these perform so it's
awkwar-- that the shade white okay so
it's definitely a very very creamy
formula thank God it doesn't feel like
an actual crayon on my arm we have the
shade dandelion so cute that these are
actually matching to the real names of
the Crayola pencils putting these on
they actually feel kind of like oily to
apply I really thought that are gonna be
a lot more like hard I definitely am
interested to see if these are going to
try it down because they definitely do
it transfer as you can see it kind of
feels like you're playing a lip stick to
your arm whereas I felt like they were
gonna be a lot more dry next we have the
shade at Mango Tango okay I guess this
one is a little bit sparkly that's kind
of pretty i doesn't wanna try to use
that one as a blush next we have the
shade of red oh wow that you're kidding
that was with literally zero pressure
yeah these are a really sister soft this
is like a lipstick wow that did not last
long this is a mess alright next I
picked up the shade and navy blue this
one also has a little bit of sparkle to
it as well that's a really pretty color
not gonna lie I wanna use on the lower
lash line I also picked up the shade
desert sand which is like a little nudie
color I would caught this for out the
waterline and this is really really
pretty and then finally of course I got
black but it's like the worst block that
I've ever swatch in my entire life what
is that you think of all the colors the
block could be like the best one a tiny
thing okay I'm a little bit sister
spooked
after these swatches but you know what I
want to see how this is gonna turn out
let's just jump right in I'm gonna first
grab the face palette because I'm
looking a little bit flat right now and
I'm literally scared and I'm going to
attempt to contour somehow I'm first
gonna grab the blush brush from this
collection and grab I think this shade
or right over here and try to contour
this let's see luckily there's a mirror
in here which is actually really helpful
it's not like bad it's just like not
there I was definitely right in the
beginning when I said that this palette
ee does not have any contouring option
which is hello it's a face palette I'm
gonna grab my Kat Von D shade and light
palette and just contour that I'm gonna
go back to that in 30 seconds per blush
and highlight and the full shebang okay
we're back with our regularly scheduled
programming did you miss me you know you
did I'm gonna grab the blush brush once
again I'm gonna dip into this kind of
metallic e coral copper shade down here
it actually
very very stunning I want to try to use
this for at blush today so once again
it's not showing up can you see that
what's going on why is it not showing up
with my face oh there it is okay it's
there she's there she came to the party
oh I love that okay
I feel like this blush shade is like
absolutely perfect for a really
beautiful bronze look for the summer
time to kind of transition your bronzer
to your highlight I really actually like
to shade a lot oh my god Wow okay cool
great love that you guys I like to do a
highlighter early on as well so I'm
gonna go back into the shade in a short
second I want to lay down this
highlighter stick at the base first this
is in the shade shimmering blush and
once again I think this was $17.50 these
kind of remind me of like the milk
sticks and that it's barely there come
on Crayola this is like the texture of
what I thought the face crayons were
gonna be like like this has that waxy
kind of more dry texture that I was
expecting and that does not look good
it's actually picking up the foundation
underneath which is definitely not good
do it does not look good that is
canceled a million percent and said what
I'm gonna do is give my face a light
spray of six plus just like I always do
before I apply my highlighter and I'm
gonna go my morphe AB
501 brush and I'm gonna dip into this
shade right here in the face palette
which actually looks like a really
really pretty high later and let's try
out this instead okay not at that see
that looks good great love that the true
test here is Kenneth snatch a sister
schnoz let's see that is the baseball
complete we are chiseled out we added a
little bit of color and now we are
glowing from with Ana I'm actually
really really loving how this is looking
so far but I'm gonna bake my faces set
it in place and I'll be right back a
little bit closer up to start off the
eyes okay
literally about a sword in the eyeshadow
I am literally luck the pocket it's
literally flying apart oh you're kidding
okay this is just getting worse and
worse and worse for the second we're
gonna pretend like that shadow didn't
just fall out of the entire package good
lord I'm scared
okay let's freakin do this thing at this
point I'm gonna start off with the nude
eyeshadow palette which is literally
falling apart at its seams I think I
really want to keep with the theme that
I have going on it's officially summer
time I know someone you guys are
graduating at congratulations by the way
so before I even jump into the eyeshadow
palette I actually
the yellow face cran and I think I want
to pop this in the inner corners like a
little fun a pop of color and see how it
actually it turns out it's actually
showing up on the skin surprisingly I
guess I'm just gonna grab like a
blending brush and see if I can buff
that out okay they do blend thank god oh
wait no they don't
okay so the cranes actually do blend out
but it definitely loses like almost all
of its pigmentation when you blend it
and it doesn't dry like it's still tacky
feeling this is not going well I'm gonna
put a little bit more on to bring some
of that color back similar to the
highlighter - it's actually taking off
the foundation from underneath the
crayon it still looks fine oh my god you
guys can't even oh wow hashtag for Cyril
problems when you buy two sets of a
camera and it still looks good so
looking at the newsprint looks like
there are four matte shades and then six
different shimmer shades which is a very
very bad ratio there should never be
more shimmer shades than matte sheets in
a palette I want to grab that red crayon
that literally melts it off when it was
touching my hand and see if one eye can
create an orange in the middle of this
eye look and also kind of wing this out
on oh my god why is this right doing
this let's grab the one eyeshadow brush
in the entire brush kit and try to blend
this out the sad thing is I'm like
actually really trying here like I don't
want to lawsuit from Crayola but I know
you can feel it coming okay that's not
that horrible what if I grab like a
regular morphe brush okay that's not
horrible it's like bad but like not the
worst me look at everything I'm like I
wonder if I grab a blending brush and
like a little bit of this oh okay that
actually works
okay what's actually really annoying is
that blending the red and the yellow
together like didn't make orange I
wonder if I put this mango shade in here
what that will do nothing it's gonna do
absolutely nothing apparently why can I
make orange like red plus yellow oh look
at me being an artiste oh we we welcome
to petit
maybe these are supposed to be like use
when you're like not wearing makeup
that's like that like it just over like
a eye thing or like you'd like just put
it on the cheek like as like a light on
the go type of thing this is just not
good I think is the conclusion that I'm
coming to here okay I want to figure how
to somehow finish this eye look and I
want to do a half cut crease so I can
turn out some of the shimmer shades in
here because they are so you look really
really stunning and I love the
highlighter in the face palette that we
used beforehand so I'm gonna grab my
shave tape concealer I'm gonna cut out
the crease but I'm actually really
nervous to do this being that these
shadows are
and are not drying down in the slightest
bit so this might all get mixed together
and we're gonna find out in a few short
seconds I'm gonna grab my morphe I'm 2
to 4 brush and start off with this kind
of light gold shade or right here at the
bottom and I'm gonna pack that on the
lid
hello what the heck what like this
swatch so nicely where is this on the
arm hello I do not see that do you I
feel like I need to treat you all the
way children right now because we're
doing a Crayola makeup tutorial what is
going on now that the crease is all kind
of cut I'm gonna grab this like a
metallic kind of ready orange shade
right here on a fluffy brush and I want
to use this to blend out the outer edge
into that red shadow that we have going
on I'm just gonna pop this right here oh
that's a good shadow okay not mad about
it I don't want to deep it up that outer
V a little bit too and add some more
dimension so I'm just gonna grab a Smith
235 brush and dip it this kind of like
muted grey tone up in this corner I'm
not sure how this is gonna turn out
let's just try this it's only one of the
worst a looks I've ever done and I'm
literally not even being ironic yes I am
but I definitely use as much of the
colors as possible so we did get a black
crayon and I want to try to do a winged
liner with this which I know I'm going
to regret but you know what you don't
know unless you try why is this black so
sheer why would you ever want a block
that looks like this oh my god this is
also a cream so it's literally not gonna
dry down either that looks the worst
alright so that is the upper lash line
all complete and it looks not good but
let's move on to the lower lash line I
think I want to add a pop of color
because I really am dying to try out
this mermaid palette I first wanted one
of the crayon in the shade navy blue
first of all this is like a Sur lien
that kinda that we all loved not dark
blue I want to pop this right up here
for a fun pop of color and see how this
works
see that's actually really pretty like
that I can get behind
we love great and then I'm gonna go a
mix of these two shades right up and
here with my morphe m14 9 brush and use
that to epochal right over top to
actually set in the shade because cream
eyeshadow is whether or not Crayola
knows they are
supposed to be set with something with
that same brush I want to dip into this
darker purple shade it right up in here
and give Dada spreads a fix+ as well and
pack that on the outer corner because
purples are so pretty and I feel like
it's very very rare that you see like a
metallic purple and an eyeshadow palette
so I really want to test this out okay
you know what as much as I was making
fun of it there I mean I showed up how a
hundred percent outperform the nude
palette this actually is really pretty
I just can't get over the fact that this
black eyeliner is literally like not
block who does that
how would you ever do that okay so I got
this nude shade desert sand to pop in
the lash line so we're gonna pop it in
the lash line I feel like that did like
very I guess it kind of worked okay
should I tree white instead oh okay
that's actually a bomb white liner kind
of all right that is enough of the
eyeshadows I thought mascaras these were
16 dollars each I'm gonna start off with
the black one on the upper lashes and
see how this mascara actually it
performs
I like this wand a lot actually Wow as
they filming this video literally could
not get any worse I am out of lash glue
a gray bar 20 minutes later alright
finally huh
that is one I look all complete looking
in the mirror I actually don't hate how
this turned out I feel like we had a
mission to go on and although we may
have failed I like the direction that
this is going in and I really want to
recreate this look sometime soon with
like really good at working a product
that being said this eyelid literally
took me 45 minutes to do and I still
don't feel like it's up to par the
blending is not great these cream
shadows still are not dry down which is
very very strange and it's just not as
vibrant and pigmented as I was like them
to be that being said I'm gonna go and
do the other eye off-camera really
quickly and hopefully try to do it a
little bit faster and I'll be right back
to finish off the rest of this Crayola
all right hello i am back and those are
both eyes Oh complete thank God I'm
gonna finish up my look today with a lip
so let's go ahead and grab the custom
lip palette I think I want to do
probably just like a nude lip I did a
rainbow I look so I think I need to like
balance out a little bit something you
thought I want to mix in this shade
together right here with a pink to make
a slightly lighter nude let's see how
this actually works under go this mom
shape eye down here mix it on my arm I
guess and then a little bit of this
white shade
well okay they don't leer really creamy
that's for sure which is great I want to
add a slight bit of yellow as well and
make it a little bit more peachy tone
let's try this what the heck that is not
what I wanted okay it kind of tastes
like like not good
ugly lip color ever for this look I'll
take a bright Barbie baby pink like no
that is not what I wanted I wanted like
a dark nude how do I make that maybe
like shad Brown I would love to tell you
how I got to this color but I don't even
know myself all right guys I'm calling
it quits for this video today this
review has been something else
Crayola sweetie love you the most you
made a childhood pretty iconic but I
think we need to stick to our 96 crayons
for ten dollars because all this is not
working out
overall this collection is not
absolutely the worst but I definitely
not recommend you guys to go and run and
find your money on it these face cramps
I would have to say by far the worst
thing in this entire collection they are
way too waxy it they're not that
pigmented and they do not blend out very
well they don't dry down and they're way
way a way to overprice the next demo eye
pencils are a much better alternative
the eye shadow palettes however we're
actually not that bad specifically the
face one I actually really really like
this one this highlighter shade right
here looked absolutely stunning on the
cheeks and this metallic coral blush I
am literally in love with I want to
reach for this all the time this summer
and the mermaid palette as such as I was
actually making fun of it in the
beginning was actually a pretty bomb as
well and I love how it looks on the
lower lash line
the lip palette although I was having a
really hard time finding a decent shade
at first I think I was actually able to
mix together a really beautiful nude and
the formula feels really really really
nice but I would definitely recommend
buying a lipstick instead because I know
most you guys don't want to sit there I
was thinking wording and mixed together
a lipstick I know I certainly don't the
mascaras were okay they definitely like
did their job of coating and lash and
giving them a little bit of a lift but
they're definitely not something that I
would recommend or say that you needed
in your life and the brush collection is
an absolute now please never spend $40
on four brushes ever I actually really
really do love the look that I came up
with today but it just took me way too
much time way too much ever and way too
much packing and Blandings we ought to
really get
good eyelet going on I'm actually really
disappointed because you guys so I say
all the time
I wrote a big Oprah R and you guys might
grew up drawing painting and coloring
and Crayola actually did have a huge
huge part in my life and it got me
through a lot of really really tough
times as a kid but it really sucks to
say that I will not be recommending this
collection to you guys and it will
definitely not be a part of my future
makeup routine that being said I really
hope you guys enjoyed this video today
and if you did please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not already I'd
love to have you join the scizor this is
a pretty lit time because I've got a bow
like on so you can notified every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me and I makeup turned you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both the same Charles at my
snapchat for more but hasn't seen sites
I've been seeing as Charles the next row
asked after Charles this video is sister
shout out goes to sister Ethan thank you
so much for you boys falling in
supporting - I love you so so so much
and if you'd like to be the next video
as a sister shadow don't forget to
always every twiddling so they go live
on Twitter all right sisters that is all
I have for this video is tonight thank
you for watching this crazy crazy review
I love you and I will see you in the
next one bye