hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
as you guys can see I'm with a very very
stuff so good makeup by Mario barn into
the Dominic K we're here in this video
set up you guys a few weeks ago we did
an iconic beauty bottle with our good
friend sister Kim and so many comments
were saying that you guys wanted to see
Mario clan me and we just like needed to
have you back I think this video has
been in the works for so long we wanted
to do this forever
so like I'm very honored to have you
here today you know thank you I'm very
honored to be here you know you're the
first this is like like my first youtube
my first time being on a youtube channel
do you make that yeah it's good first
fun to be out are you excited are you
nervous how you feeling alright so I'm a
little nervous I have to be honest and
I'm and I never get nervous from anyone
but I don't do guys makeup okay this is
literally like the first time I'm doing
a glam baby on a man on a boy yeah
sister yes and when I worked in
television news like 12 or 13 years ago
I had a really bad experience where one
of the male anchors like basically like
pushed me because he didn't want a hot
guy doing his makeup and so ever since
then I about this game ends make good so
I'm basically what anyways okay so this
is very interesting
I'm excited so for those of you guys who
do not know sister Mario or daddy Mario
is a legendary makeup artist and he is
Kim's makeup artist but also a lot of
other celebrities as well would you like
to do a humble little brag and well I
worked with Jennifer Lopez Katy Perry
obviously Kim grande reunion just lucky
people so many people and they all look
obsolete stunning he also has a
masterclass that he runs and make
applause as I've been to one of them
going to another one coming up very very
soon and they're very nice yeah yes I
will be there setting up front row so
much fun you guys should definitely
check those out for more information but
Mario is just a living legend I'm so
excited to have him here
[Music]
when I first saw you I discovered you
online not discover you but I first saw
you don't mind before with covergirl
yeah and a very very long time I'll
never forget that I that day that I
discovered I said he's gonna be such a
big star yeah so I have I have like a
good night for like discovering or like
knowing who's gonna be really sweet
you're the past what we want to do to
that um I don't know
I fix out I'm so used to talking to a
crowd of people at the classes yeah
weird cuz I want to ask them but I can't
do you guys want glamour you guys what
natural I feel like we should do a glam
look especially using the palette just
because I don't have so many colorful
lugs iPhones like we go you can do
rainbow they want to see something
pretty alright like you're cool so when
I start doing makeup and especially it's
a new client which you basically are
right now because I've never done your
makeup I just started to start feeling
the features of the face and kind of
just envisioning the techniques I'm
gonna be doing that when hair has to go
high or lower so as I'm gonna start by
filling your eyebrows and while I'm
doing that I'm gonna start kind of
planning a look cause right now I have
no idea what I'm doing that's honestly
how I go into most of my makeup looks as
well it's the hardest part for people
whatever they do you have such a good
transformation they were disgusting are
you thinking I don't know and the thing
is - so everyone told me that they were
bad there was not a single person like
within the makeup community be like oh
yeah your eyebrows are good like
everyone's like AHA correct like even
though I saw see Leslie crazy no one
says when I first grew a moustache that
two years ago it was literally like so
long hitting my lips and when I look at
pictures I cringe oh how did no night my
family I told me like oh you need to
trim your mustache
cuz nobody wants to be mean but I wish
more people had bullied me about my
if I was close to you at that time I
would okay god I kind of go back to the
browser throughout the qualification
really the reason I do this because I'm
depends on how Elektra might be I make
up is like if I make up a super dramatic
and I don't want to go too heavy on the
girls so I could have just do like a
midway point with the browser okay so do
you want to tell the sisters a little
bit about like how long do you think
make up for like your education and
training and stuff just so they don't
like a little bit more about so I
started make up in 2000 so it's gonna be
19 years now
oh my god 1990 yeah Wow 14 1999 5 yeah
19 so he was like four months old when I
started doing makeup oh my god that is
insane that's so cool though like just
the level of success that you've reached
and the fact that you've been doing it
for home no only three years oh sorry
okay I hate talking about myself I
started doing makeup 19 years ago yeah
in New York and I got a job at Sephora
when I was 17 as a fragrance consultant
and I started doing makeup there it's
where I discovered makeup in the first
day of work and I got obsessed with it
fell in love with it started researching
it and at this time in the industry is
it's very different than it was than it
is now yep we want to talk about it was
like really really hard back then you
could not there was there was no social
media there was no way to get noticed
and so I started working retail and then
you know I really struggled I want to
say for the first like seven or eight
years and when I say struggle I mean
like barely being able to pay rent you
know like eating pizza and eating tuna
fish and like it was hard because you
you had to assist and a lot of those
systems all you had to do for free right
so you'd be on set for like 16 or 18
hours a day working with these masks and
makeup artists but you know you'd be
doing it for free for the experience hot
well that's how it was and then you know
I'd work for each on the side and then
when I eventually stopped retail I
started working like in television news
on the weekends just I can make you know
some steady income Brahe started doing
my own clients started working with
photographers and eventually like I want
to say after the six years so I started
doing like celebrities in New York some
pop singers and some actresses how did
that happen cuz I sleep that's a very
like intense to over like starting us
before I just testing and playing it out
to like news anchors that I'm also
produces like a something yeah pretty
intense job it just whoa no it wasn't it
wasn't like an attention shop it was
very like gradual gradual it was like
little by little just like step by step
yeah working with a certain hair size
who recommend me to the celebrity you
know that practing but I also had an
agent at that time so I hadn't featured
since I was 21 but even within agent Lee
you know you still struggle at that time
yeah because to get noticed by a
celebrity there was just no way like
nowadays you could just write them on
them social media right Twitter or
Instagram which is helpful and they can
definitely discover you're nowadays -
back then there was just no way at all
you know the industry has definitely
changed you mention how the industry has
like changed a lot when it comes to like
artists and now like the emergence of
social media and there's no denying that
you were like one of the first to really
pioneer like makeup on social media you
have a huge following on Instagram
and like your work is major inspiration
to me and many other artists as well
would you say that social media has
changed to make impunity for the better
and in what ways do you think it's like
a factor that it's interesting for me to
answer this question because I am
considered the old school like anyone
who's like 15 years in the business and
more is considered sort of all its glory
yeah and most of the people that are old
school they tend to not like social
media and they think it's ruined and
they think it's ruined the industry and
they think that YouTube is ruined and
influencers everyone did there's a huge
that's a huge thing yeah it's a it's a
really big thing I feel like I'm gonna
also get it you know when this video
comes out because like people gonna turn
their nose up right you know why would
he do that with the influencer you know
but for me I mean I feel like Instagram
is amazing number one I feel like it's
changed in the street for the better for
me definitely and for many others as
well it provides it's provided so many
more opportunities that we never would
have had as makeup artists so many more
like types of jobs that we can do and
you know just the fact that you could
build a following you could you could
share your work and have control over it
you know Instagram is like a personal
magazine right and so you could share
your work and build a following build a
business a legitimate business million
precise yeah and for me I've always been
sort of supportive of influencers in
youtubers for one because I know the
amount of work that goes into what you
guys do I think
people don't realize you know in the
older generation in particular and even
some of the newer generation they don't
realize the amount of work that goes
into doing a YouTube ad you're creating
content and you know it's like it's
really a full-time job and I think
someone like you in particular who I
really like admire when it comes to work
ethic you know I can see the amount of
work that you put into it you know the
fact that you're able to build a
following by the way I think you
probably get the award for the most
insane engagement like you've literally
grows like a billion dollars every three
days the same you know but that's like
to me like I don't look at that as like
uh you know I look at that as like holy
crap that's amazing like yeah it's
inspiring you know what I mean the work
is there you know to back it up because
you're working on stuff even on your
days off I feel like you're plotting and
planning and thinking of your next video
and yeah you know you're entertaining to
watch on social media and I think that's
really hard not everyone can do that
thank you
and so I have respect for you and for
all the other content creators out there
you know because it really is a hard job
and people don't realize like how much
goes into it and my other thing about it
is that because the industry has changed
right so there's all these kind of new
opportunities for these young artists
that are coming up
I've also look at that as just because I
had to struggle for like almost 10 years
in the beginning of my career and now
people don't like I feel like I I'm
happy for them because yeah they have
these cool opportunities now like if it
was my brother or my cousin or my son
you know and these opportunities came
their way and they're 18 and 19 I'm not
gonna tell them to sit in the room and
say no to everything I'm gonna say go
take the opportunities go get on
successful go with it you know and I
feel like that's how people should think
about it as well I've only been in the
community for 3 years now but obviously
cover garlic was a major pivotal moment
and boys and beauty I feel like cause it
really bought it to like the mainstream
media and even over the past three years
I've seen such a positive change and so
many young boys trying out makeup and
imagine me being like oh no like you
can't like being mad that they were
getting a following or imagined that you
said no to covergirl right I hate
wouldn't makeup artists like oh
influencers are taking our jobs like
when have you ever seen me on set like
doing makeup for a campaign
unless it's my own ever yeah but we it's
two totally different things than I
don't understand why there's so much
hatred between people living within the
same industry that are just performing
different tasks I mind my own business
I'm in my own studio making contests for
a younger demographic and working makeup
artists are on set every single day
working just as hard doing celebrity
makeup and doing like shoot and client
talent campaign and sometimes like
sometimes our worlds collide you know
like a celebrity makeup artist like when
they do Oscars for Grammys you know they
work with the same brands that you guys
do because they're they're getting
sponsored by brands for their red carpet
looks so if sometimes the worlds collide
and I just feel like there needs to not
be a divide between the open generation
and the younger I feel like I just feel
like people needs to support support it
more not bash everyone can learn from
each other yeah look I feel like I've
learned so much from you and from other
industry professionals that I've looked
up to have been falling for a very very
long time like it's people like you
people like Anasazi there are people
that have like really been a great
mentor to me to give me advice and be
like hey listen I have been here for 19
plus years don't do that or like you
should do that so you should talk to
this person like I really value that
because as much as I love makeup and
marketing and stuff there's always
things that I can learn and improve on
and the same thing goes with the older
generation like just like you said
social media has been a huge emergence
in the community and I think it's really
changed it for the better but obviously
a lot of the older generation is that a
touch of that and I think that there's a
lot to be learned from them even for the
working making purpose how they can
build their brand further and still book
those jobs and not how to be taken by
influencers you have two options you
either you get with it and you you kind
of go with the change and you pay
attention to your social media and you
work on it you become part of it because
it's not going anywhere it's not going
anywhere no one has control over that
and so you either do that or you just
kind of get left behind some of the
older makeup artists have resorted to
like sort of publicly bashing and and
shaming or you know bullying certain
even within the middle every to make
parts community like some celebrity
members do it to other celebrity make
parts to think about if they have a lot
of followers or if they have you know if
they work with certain clients and I
just feel like you know for someone who
has 20 plus years of experience let's
say a makeup artist
to have your legacy be that you were
known for bashing people and for
bullying people you know on social media
like that's just horrible for me and I
built a thing it's embarrassing yet and
so I just feel like we need to respect
each other's feels and each other's jobs
or they call it the beauty community but
I feel like it needs to be more of a
community grade kind of said any better
myself so I'm doing a I call it a snatch
I can't leave you've never done this no
okay
so obviously taping his eyes back and
I'm going to be tying it in the back
with a string and what that does is it
enables it pushes the eyes back this is
a very very old Hollywood trick it's
been done for so long in Hollywood and
movies and filming and red carpets and
stuff I might do this I do this pretty
let me not often but I do it quite a bit
especially on photo shoots and you could
do it on a red carpet - if the hair is
down because it clevers it yeah a lot of
celebrities do it you know we just don't
know why planes do it a little Jack
needs of course yeah me for sure though
that dries and then I basically pull
that oh my god you can really even see
it yeah you got to do it really clean
you know sometimes you could see it a
lot and you can actually cover it with
makeup
I mean you will we're gonna see this
though in the video but you know we're
doing a fantasy it's like more for the
photo I mean so let me see something
like that let me pull it and it just
kind of snatches the face in the brows
we put one of my double chin a lifetime
supply and I was on a video lately when
you do some clients thing I just said
transform to another four day to really
feel it you know you mean like yeah it's
like anything I mean it's literally
getting a facelift without any of the
surgery at all like just a facelift and
they just feel like so snatched and
beautiful hell of my face left at age 19
yeah oh all right so now because the
reason why I did this on him cuz I
wanted that was kind of envisioning like
a black line like sort of like I'm never
gonna
they learned okay I just felt like the
brows need to be lifted on the corners
so I'm using a palette for the first
time what this so I have one of these he
sent it to me but I didn't use it in
touch it yet because I think i swatched
one color but I'm saving it so there are
certain products that I save for the
future because I think in like 20-30
years you'll be super iconic and I wanna
make sure I have them like on touch so
yeah yours is one of them so you get the
send me another one guys okay well
alright so we'll probably work in these
ranges here it's more natural like I
said people don't see me do rainbow
rainbow rainbow but nobody has really
seen me do like glam with it yet so this
perfect well speaking of learning new
tips and tracks your masterclass so fun
so fresh I went to one she did so I flew
all the way to New York for you got a
mom I yes I did I was so excited to see
Mario because we had met several times
when I had always been good friends but
I never think I actually gotten to
seeing you work before so super super
excited but I walked with my little
notepad like ready of my little time to
take notes of everything but it was such
a cool experience getting to watch you
work and seeing you play I'm Kim and all
like the different tips and techniques
that you've been using forever like it
was so fun I feel like I learned so much
I think people don't realize it's a lot
more than just technique it's up to
because I feel like the majority of
people that are there are aspiring many
mores right or there are make smart is a
different level some of them are
youtubers it some of them are you know
the lot of them do brides and they you
know they're out there and hustling and
doing clients everyday and stuff like
that so they learn like more so than
just techniques they really learn how to
approach like different face shapes and
how to think about approaching a face
and how to do certain different looks
and how to build and how to you know
it's a very very intense people when
people don't realize that I think they
think in the beginning that it's just
kind of like a technique
thing you know but it's literally five
hours on one face so you can imagine the
amount of like info that's that's
happening it's a lot it's a little
spoiler alert for me it's the most
important part and the most you know the
part of my job that I'm like hands-down
the most passionate yeah because I
wanted to be a teacher my entire life
yeah so I've sort of found the way to
become a teacher and a make worse at the
same time how long have you been doing
the classes for I started the master
class almost tenured almost ten years
earlier in LA so there was a YouTube
video 10 years ago that Kim and I put on
YouTube
and you know obviously Kim she around
that time she was really like starting
to become heavily like a beauty icon
people were girls are on the world and
really not enough to her they loved
their her glam looks and so after that
video came out I started getting
messages from people around the world
basically just asking me questions and
asking me like how can I do this or how
can I advance in this or what I'm like
what are the steps I need to do right
you know to become successful and so I
was sitting at home one day and I just I
was like wow like all of these people
but unless they started assisting
someone because this is before YouTube
was really a thing unless they start
assisting someone and unless they live
in London Paris New York or LA they'll
never have a chance
yeah and so that's when I decided to do
this class I was like let me teach them
the tricks of the trade in this class
and what I believe to be able to have
bands right and so my first class had
like 16 students in it yeah I started
like really small and now there are
thousands yeah and that's how the master
first started but it's like literally
did you know I'm just so one thing I'm
like extremely proud of in my career
alright so I'm gonna just now set using
the laura mercier translucent powder I'm
just gonna set the concealer I'm just
very lightly I'm not gonna do it too
much alright so I'm taking the shady to
ring light which is a beautiful that's
good
taking this heat ring light and I'm just
gonna put that on the inner corner here
you mark your palate with the James
trials and morphe palette I really like
this color anybody's yeah it's really
bright so I really love it for a good
like problem in our corner highlight
nobility it builds nicely too and then
I'm gonna take a flatter brush I'm gonna
use ring light again but I'm actually
gonna mix it with where's this one I
want to so God I'm gonna mix green light
and so good together and I'm just gonna
put it on the highest
where are your favorite table looks to
do on people or what's your look you've
ever done
no I mean there's been thousands yeah
are to say but you know like also a
miniature with the you to it's like your
work changes over the years and
sometimes you can look at your old
working like you know yeah it always
changes my chemically my favorite look
so he's changed what's your favorite
right now like that you felt like
recently okay if that's easier
I mean there's one that I did on Kim for
like her her glam Bible campaign I'd
really lie up with the lake the
lightning-rod going to yeah that was so
pretty I like that one I'm anybody now
usually deeper shade to go over that
consumer what is this call is ten
percent off you know I'm really
impressed that you can remember it like
that means you really like you were
really intensely involved because yeah I
I mean I have bad memory wouldn't
memorize all these names the palate
literally like when I approach my morphe
so you do the palate I already had it
fully designed on Photoshop like with
all the same names included as well we
sent me that photo something I remember
before it launched it was like a picture
of I did yes I remember tax to be like
what would you add to this I was trying
to get a lot of people that I respected
the opinions of like input on the
palette before it launched because I
really Col that obviously was to make it
for working artists and for like all
makeup lovers I remember being at your
house of a bunch of wind up in the
downtown and I remember trigger and I
remember you were working on it back
then
yeah you know you were kind of was
testing out some of the shadows with you
but they were actually really amazing
back then too so I'm just gonna probably
do kind of do direction it's going right
now there's like very blown out smokey I
love cut creases everything to I really
appreciate them and stuff but I just
don't for me I personally my aesthetic
my response I think is more of a blown
out like a really blown out and blend it
up a look because it's it for me it's
more sexy and I love sexy makeup yes and
so probably just gonna wind up doing
that I want to ask you the question
because after leasing this palette I
haven't asked literally eighteen million
times
speaking of creating a palette or would
you ever be interested in doing
a marginal effect makeup line yeah I
mean that's been my goal for like 17 18
years I think it didn't happen the
future of you know I don't have any
solid dates or anything like that but
it's something I've been slowly very
slowly working on the past three or four
years myself yeah it's a lot of work a
lot of work a lot of money obviously I
get offers like a lot of offers from
investment firms and huge companies and
investors and corporations and retailers
to do lines with them right but I really
want to do it myself
without any investment yeah so I could
be fully in full control a bit and which
I think of Stowe cuz I would do the same
thing yeah so I'm not sure when it's
gonna happen I'm really not gonna rush
it's gonna start out small you know
slowly kind of grow it from there but I
don't care about you know rushing it or
you know just coming up to market
because Instagram is hot right now you
know I love that yeah I'm just gonna do
it when it's right and when when it's
ready yeah I I really really love that
in that I mean obviously not hard I
respect you but that just makes me
respect you so much Warren's doing some
cream product here just to tune so it's
to face this is my I think this is my
favorite color image better color really
I love I just love a matte color that
has that like yellowish undertone uh-huh
no a lot of medium and darker skin tone
people have been using it for banana
powder yeah which i think is so cool
this would be a great color for a deeper
skin tone to kind of put on their eyes
yeah like yep alright so this looks all
pretty oh my god so this is one layer of
liner people always get shocked at the
classes like because I typically would
score it by layers upon their for one
look
[Music]
so I'm gonna just go ahead now and start
your skin I'm so excited for this but
I'm gonna put more I'll do more liner
and lashes in everything a little later
are you excited let's good because I
used to have really bad skin growing up
and for me like I love doing eyes but
like I know that I can slay it ah you
know what I mean so like skin for me
it's always like a fun challenge because
I always like my skin to look like as
perfect as possible and it's been like
such a learning process for me
throughout me they kept routine because
I used to cake on all my palettes but I
feel like I've gotten a lot better at
like still using a lot but like making
it look a lot prettier in a lot like
right better both in real life and on
camera too so it's I always love seeing
how different artists do skin feels like
I feel like that's the one area that I
can always really really learn more
about yeah
so that being said should we do the
Cutie like the juniors like dark orange
accommodation or sugar do they coming
from like an hour I'm literally NARS
from my spray tan so the good Lankans
well I've always had a lot of trouble of
matching my foundation because my like
body is pretty yellow tone but my like
neck and chest are like literally like
yeah my god why are you so perhaps use I
actually go dark with conditional I
almost get like who cares I've given up
I'm give like who cares all right
sisters so that is officially every
single foundation that I now own when
it's watched on both my face and my neck
and chest sure didn't concealer before
foundation yes yes ma'am how long would
you say like your normal paint on
somebody else it's always different
because it depends on like the situation
you're in we write in some lip some
clients want it done fast like 30
minutes and some clients give you two or
three hours oh so it really depends on
the client also dependent under the
circumstance I people don't realize like
when you're doing a when your celebrity
make words like the type of conditions
you're working under
usually every day there are pretty good
times intense yet like it's never I
never will have someone ever ever ever
like this that's just like quiet no
phone like you know calm yeah always
they're on their phone their head is
down their publicist is early during an
interview they have their kids there
they're getting their toes and their
hands down they're getting their hair
blown yeah I mean a wig puts you know
put in or extensions right so it's
really like intense moving and let them
moving if you never get to have someone
sitting still and so you know that's
just the reality of it and so like
that's just how how the work is
typically every day so just keep that in
mind everyone when you're judging you
know and then they go on the red carpet
of course everyone judges and right you
know but it's fine I mean it's pretty
bad you like working under pressure
sometimes I get three hours and
sometimes I get 15 minutes it just
depends what is really an ideal
situation would it be like calm where
you just get to like say and play yeah I
mean I would like I'm a very calm person
so I like I like it when I could just
kind of focus and you know not not be
too rushed let me get that being said
like when I'm rushed I usually do really
good work you know when time came 9 to
10 minutes Oh lightly that it laid in
New York this was many years ago we were
at MTV as she was wearing a black
television and we had 10 minutes to do
four full hair and makeup and I made it
work lashes everything you know another
time I remember I've had some crazy
experiences another time I remember I
did this was back in here also the
celebrity arrived late to the hotel room
and we had to go to an event in
Manhattan and we were in Jersey or
hotels in Jersey and so we had that's
mistake number one
whoever booked her hotel there I'm not
sure why she was in Jersey I think she
had another job in Jersey or something
ok ok so we had to run into the car you
know this is like a years ago before I
had an assistant so like I had to pack
everything myself
we had run-ins in the car and she put
her head on my lap in the car in the
back seat in the dark it was dark
outside we put that little light up on
the car yeah and I did her entire face
with her laying in the backseat on top
of my oh and actually the futures game
it was like the most fulfilling moments
when that stuff happened
you've been weakened for 19 years now
you see the trends come and go what
would you say are like your staple
makeup trends that you're just like live
for and actually don't love makeup
trends I'm not a huge follower of trends
but yes for me it's only because the
type of makeup that I have to do every
day like I'm not allowed to just do
trends like I have to just do what they
want sort of what looks best on them but
that being said like recently for
example there's been a huge trend of
glitter right haha glitter and like bold
colors and so I've been doing all that
because sort of when people see
something on social media everyday
celebrities you know like they it's
almost like they become accustomed to it
and so it becomes okay a little bit yeah
which is super dull you know like I'm
even finding that the clients are like
let's do glitter let's do a pink eye you
know this you know things like that so
that being said even though I don't love
trends and because I took oligo can't
follow them I really appreciate them
it's like one of those questions that
editors always ask like oh what trans -
hey it's like I don't hate any of them
there's all they're all fun and bright
you know it's like makeup it's all fun
well that leads me into a good question
that I was actually getting ready to add
there's no perfect sisters right I'm
gonna say obviously like you've been the
pioneer of so in different makeup trends
like how I think I'll try it but have
there been any like techniques or like
tricks that you've learned from other
influences are artists that you have
influenced it and now you use all the
time well let me first clear this up
because this is controversial I didn't
create or invent highlighting contouring
specifically contouring because they
call me the contour King go applause
yeah contouring has been around I mean
Mona Lisa its contoured in her vanity
you know it's been around for ages
drag queens always did contouring myself
with Kim really popularized it in the
digital mainstream or on the mainstream
yeah you know when I was an assistant
for several years I learned so many
tricks of the trade from like literally
the best networks in the world I knew
like so many of those things at a young
age because I was seeing them every day
on set things like contour highlight
obviously like just all tech like cut
creases like all that stuff I learned or
like how to do the tapes and yeah how
did remove eyebrows all these kind of
things I learned I learned more so I
think from regular women like I'm really
interested in seeing how regular women
do their makeup and I think there's
something extremely charming and cute I
love seeing regular women's makeup
because I kind of like in my mind let's
say you know if I see someone in the
restaurant or something I never judge
but like I'll see something look at it
and I'll kind of like create something
in my mind from what they did at home
yeah
and then as far as like influencers and
stuff like that I just get I gets part
of it you know they do really cool
different things you have packing you
what is your favorite step off the
makeup retained okay I know what Miley's
fingers are why some of these favorites
are lashes same hundred verse I hate
doing lashes obviously despise that
especially you know false lashes and the
hands are big so it's like just annoying
for me to get in there I don't love
doing lips either same hey absolutely
hating let's do some other people too
it's so hard
yes especially the dark colors yeah my
favorite would be probably it depends on
the face like if someone has amazing
eyes enemy eyes you know if someone has
like like incredible skin and I would
love doing this I always like a peachy
blush gonna dip into face what is it
face face a sea
so for you so go down the lap so I can
shut up yeah I want to know because they
feel like the people who watch me it was
very like split I definitely valid or
makeup but I also have a lot of really
amazing and talented aspiring makeup
artists so as someone who's been in the
space for so long it's been a role model
to so many of us what would be your
biggest piece of advice to aspiring
artists well if you want to be you know
something if you want to grow in your
career and you want to be successful I
think one of the most important things
is just sacrifice you're gonna have to
sacrifice you're not gonna be able to go
on vacations constantly go out to the
clubs and the bars everyday air and
every weekend you know you have to put
in the work in order to see the results
and so that's number one my sacrifices a
tremendous amount yeah and then my mom
always taught me you know Brooklyn
another country she wasn't allowed to go
to school you know so she's a very
simple had a woman
what she did teach me always that I
followed always is just to be a good
person and I always tell my students
that no matter what you do and the
decisions that you make and the way you
lead your life Delhi
just remember to really be able person
you're making decisions do it from a
good place in your heart and you know
she always said if you if you'd be a
good person marry well
everything good will come to you
sometimes they may take years sometimes
days but it will go all right so I think
we're done oh my god really and this is
literally the first time I've ever done
glam makeup on a man in 20 years my
sister a sister
mara oh my god I look so beautiful on
you literally kidding me like a doll you
do it at all the sisters ah this is the
bass can we I think I'm gonna need to
take him from you sorry is literally so
beautiful how do you feel like are you
hungry good luck
oh yeah I I had Sam you know I'd said
before I was nervous because I don't do
boys makeup but I really think it came
on nice it looks I feel so beautiful
thank you so much for having me today
like I just look it's like I feel like
I'm red carpet-ready
which is not very often for me and I
feel like I like I feel very very
powerful let's look and I feel like it's
confident and I feel snatched as well
like these face tapes it's gonna take my
tapes back though no come on I think I
need them now don't be rude alright well
thank you so much for coming on so
you're literally one of my biggest role
models and have been such a good friend
to me over the past three years and it
means the world to me that I was your
first boy and YouTube cloud like it's
literally so cool you guys if you do not
already follow Mario please go check
them out at makeup by Mario Mario Tabata
Mike made-up legend also I'll be at the
master class on a February 9th Here I am
soul sister can it's gonna be amazing
and like I said last night I feel like I
learned so much he's such an amazing
role model and teacher for us staring
artists everywhere and I really hope you
guys enjoy this fun little video today
if you guys enjoy this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and show your
sisters support and go say hi to Mario
and show him all the love as well and
also make sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below
come join this sisterhood we're I don't
even know how many sisters very strong
cuz this videos going out in the future
so hopefully well over 13 million it
that's Kenny crashing oh my god
huh and also put that back on so you get
a notification every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
and I make I'm pretty good Colombian and
so you and Twitter are they're both the
same Charles when stop check for I had
the deed sites I miss James Charles that
extra ask after Charles
you could just find me at makeup I'm
Mario on Instagram on Twitter and on
snapchat this video sisters how that
goes to sister Thomas thank you so much
love for always and falling and
supporting Olivia literally it's so so
so much and of you at home late to the
next videos sister shadow don't forget
to always reach a two video links and
they go live on Twitter all right
sisters I think that's all here first
today's brand new video and sister
Mariana thank you so much for watching I
love you
[Music]