hi Cesar Jade Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel so as you can
see today I am blessed with the presence
of a very very special guest me Maureen
yes a living legend of YouTube today
brand has a very exciting event to go on
so I'm gonna be her face actually I'm
gonna leave I look great
so I'm gonna go I just wanted to tell
you guys that you can watch me in my
channel cuz I'm better than James and I
know it's a lot of hate so I had
everyone go I'm hating on him and then
he apologized so later so that's on my
channel go check out
[Music]
take care holy balls are going to be
there beating her face tonight for a
very special event that she is going to
she's currently late already
real fast and try to get this done but
i'm in lounge we've been trying to do
this for a bar these are all coins with
the first one with my benefit
Porefessional primer i'm sorry you're
the favorite my favorite please touch my
face i want you to touch my face have
you sell honoree girl dreams come true
dreams come true i so good we probably
got to do that i me what you need to do
another one yeah because we want to sing
together we have a very fun I do plans
but sisters are not a time today we're
going to be using the NARS light five -
sure go up here glow do you ever like
how can you do other people's makeup I
feel like I mean you do for collabs and
stuff but like you know I look mad no I
don't know ever I used to do clans like
when I was still living at home you just
said I used to do plans clients oh
clients clients meaning like your 14
year old friends yeah 14 yeah I'm old
enough to be your mother just say yeah I
love the lighting in my house is
destroying your video okay so we have to
talk about something I don't think we do
we do need to talk I don't like reviews
new James
so you tweeted a picture of you eat
together as Miranda but now my Twitter
is exploding November 19 2013
no I said would you like a vlog or
Coleen's corner and you said caline's
Carter I love you
so much oh my god I better meet you on
January 11th at your show oMG I want to
give you a bit hug good and then someone
said a blow up and shirts yeah that's
like represent oh my god and you're so
cute
cute is not the word I would use to
describe so B and Ricky were driving
over to Colleen's today and he was like
oh my god seems like have you ever
actually met Colleen before I was like
the last time I hopefully was literally
when I bought tickets to her being
greedy and it's great it's not crazy and
I need to find marks I know there's more
there are more you're my idol I love you
so much oMG I'm can't wait to meet you
in New York City I want to give you a
big hug
if you search from : James Charles
although all one word space your
username they were just so sweet from
James to you Oh God you are a super fan
way to celebrate this September 6 2013 I
wanted to make a starships video on the
beach so bad but my parents wouldn't
film it for me
oMFG I'm still mad at them October 10
2013 I'm seeing you New York City and
it's honestly going to be the best day
of my life and if I don't meet slash
take a pic with you I'll cry oh my god
we need to find the picture this is the
worst October 12 I love you so much site
for the semi nudity and there's a
picture of James with no shirt on these
look like the spookiest ever Coleen's
parents just stop oh my god
I wrote the lyric stuff it's just so
weird too because like before like I was
easy where I was like a huge fan of all
like everything anyways friends wow so
cool so I'm not specially just anything
fine whatever made you a drawing oh oh
my gosh guaranteed to give me this yeah
I did lots of them all I just wanna had
a new Kuwait's I was really quickly off
camera and now we're gonna make her face
are you like okay are you fangirling
right now you're sitting those Swedes
are even really funny thinking about
that like that me know is scared I
didn't see the picture of you and me
like you and Miranda anywhere it's like
it has to be there somewhere
hashtag Murph and of her life I love you
Miranda you're so beautiful and perfect
you're my idol
so haters back off Sharon Hill killing
the game the best cover about this
palette talk about it way too much but
it's Miranda sings is selling tickets
and my mom won't take me oh my god who
wants to go text me ASAP yeah I can't
from the picture of the two of us here
they know where it has to be there
somewhere now I think about I remember
me and my best friend at the time
complaining that Rachel took the photo
mm anything gonna be blurry and maybe
not posted for the way I'm gonna grab
the Stila liquid metal thingies these
things are sort of everybody what
they're actually called but this is the
shade of Kenton karma your have used
these before
okay so you need to look down okay and
not look up and then Josh goes mad yeah
okay I'll be great what these go on like
a liquid but then they dry down and
click on that better so they don't move
either in the prettiest pepper and
they're gonna hurt it is there so I says
[Music]
I will say this like I get my makeup
done
everyone's to offer like events and
stuff makeup artists always complain
about like beauty gurus online and how
they're all fake and they don't know
what they're doing and like they're
taking their jobs and blah blah blah bit
they're so they're so bad about it but
let me just tell you I have never liked
how any of them have done me know like I
always prefer like when I do collabs
with YouTube friends and like they do my
makeup and like it always looks so much
better because you know I think I think
that like when you learn how like be a
makeup artist basically how to care for
a client as a makeup artist has a lot
different than like actually doing
makeup but I think the thought knowledge
is something that a lot of the YouTube
people including myself don't have like
I will never sit there like Jen I'm a
professional makeup artist because I'm
not you can't sit there to explain and
properly sanitize all my brushes really
prevent diseases and something I've seen
all the same all my friends and
good but what I don't like is I feel
like a lot of those people feel like
because they've been working at a lot
longer because they work it like I
support are back that they're for some
reason better or more talented which is
so far from the case because the amount
of times I've seen an awful awful awful
work come out of those different stores
is ridiculous and great look to you
never go to guess where sir absolutely
absolutely but I think amount of time or
experience you've been doing something
does not equate to tell it whatsoever
yeah but it's never easy that so many
people will sit online it would do to
your race kappa no tell me Carla I can
be the face of wave
you can be what this because you've been
working it back for ten yeah it's not
that that's the tape so this is what I
have cut creases if you look down oh my
god it's so hard to look up without like
creasing my face how do you guys do it a
lot of practice like I have my mirror
here at all set and then I drove a car
completely with my beer here like
looking down the entire time because
they see how right here holy animals I
feel like your mother I feel like this
is the do my mom's neck shove her lashes
I have some modular stairs published any
ones though which ones do you have I
have my card l like just generic like
ones his face more to you can
see what they look like move on to
highlight or only wait for sister away
from our collages I'm going to use of
course when it really be a joke Charles
video if I was not using the auto sounds
yet so Hollywood illuminator and
combination with my work I know I'm
gonna put it I feel like whenever I
tried like bronze my face or like blush
or how that or anything at all just
nerves together to see where it's like
to be a time do you want to get those
online these look like a winged these
have like a wing no so why'd you make it
wet basically when you like about your
brush with like fix+ early I'll say
that's been a water before you apply it
for like metallic and satin shades it
makes it
we must care I don't have a lot
Gemological were in there yeah how dirty
let us spooky I'll so get ready for old
age because my lashes needs to be so
long and now they're like stubby little
stubs it's a bank loan fake ones for a
reason so today I'm gonna use the my
hair is so queasy but my makeup looks
beep oh my gosh it looks so good I'm so
impressed
thanks sir how did you do this can you
come over every day finally got to meet
me
it was really it really was so low for
anything guys not that if you walk up
there like yeah what just work just
tweet the crap like you know perfected
your talent and all these you works for
nobody
I
irrelevant to the world aside from my
little town and family to me really
commend by the look of those streets you
didn't see I'm stopped there we go guys
if you enjoyed this video say please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and screen to my youtube
channel click that little bow
notification so you can subscribe every
time I upload a new video
the Brits check our video is it over on
kollene channel won't know Brandon -
Shama
check out the video over on the Miranda
channel that DePalo me other makeup
dirty Colombian Instagram or Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for behead that sees itself is
James Charles that extra ass after
Charles follow me if you like to follow
sister Colleen you can check her out all
for social media platforms I don't know
just look at my wait you want a granted
days today sister shuttle goes to its
sister Lauren I thank you so much for
always falling in supporting me and this
all about make sure you always retweet
my video leave something alive on
Twitter
alright guys we will see you in there
time I love you so much and goodbye
[Music]