hi sisters jean-charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel today i'm
joined with a super super special gust
miss love so for today's video
lauralee just did a my makeup over on
her channel and i'm gonna now do her
makeup that's a beauty guru as we always
get to be in our own faces every single
day videos all the time for different
events but it's really really rare that
we actually get to get our face beat
other people let alone other beauty
gurus exactly yeah intimidating a way
more intimidating because I don't know I
think they'll like you do the full beat
glam like you know the full we clams
yeah oh my gosh okay
oh wow I do too we did however at the
end of the look give a brutal on it yeah
beat down out the last words out things
that James wasn't obsessed with but
you'll have to wait I have to check out
yeah so she's gonna do the same thing we
should go tell me
well the tears if she hates it actually
loves it how she feels so without
further ado I'm gonna be auras face now
make sure you stay tuned at the end of
the video for her brutal breakdown of
the makeup and then I also check out our
video on Laura's tail or she beats my
face in this beautiful glam without
further ado let's get started
[Music]
so those are my preparing Laura's face
using the benefit Porefessional primer
you guys know that I love this primer
and also it is one of Florence favorites
too so we're using the hourglass
foundation stick in the shade beige face
that she already knew she do you prefer
liquid foundations or stick funders
usually um this is I'm a go to but
lately I've been using the alarmist
Mercier a flawless fusion for a liquid
or I love like the Milani
the joke comes we weren't perfect yes
honey I don't try that one it's so good
really yeah it feels like a high-end
foundation so I call it concealer
say it concealer concealer yeah people
say is they wrong I don't hear it come
see what her concealer yeah I don't
think you're saying it wrong I don't
think they're wrong either I think what
does anyone either love our voices or
hate our voices
yeah there's no in-between oh we have in
common I hope you do we have
boys thing Oh people hate my voice oh my
god that makes me love you so much more
people say that I sound like I have
something stuck in my throat when I'm
talking people say I sound like I'm
constantly sick which is I mean I guess
kind of true but minor minor truth to
people sound like it sounds like I'm
whining or that like I have like an old
lady's voice it's like a lot of people
hate my voice because I talk too fast
which we use a lot of people comment
saying that I give them anxiety because
I talk so fast which is really scary
because I really do try to not but I
can't help that so if you're one of
those people I apologize there's
actually a little speed button where if
you click the gear on your video you can
change the speed to 75 per size it was
200 and then I'll be a lot more slowed
down so if you were someone who wants to
hear me talk a little bit slower or
anybody for that matter chocolate mousse
a little or faster that's a really good
hack for you guys okay I'm gonna contro
Laura's face using my benefit hoola
bronzer before favourites anything I'm
worth II am five seventy brush do you
feel like have a small head you do have
a small can you see it now you do it's
like super small I tell people so once
the bronze is all on one check that I
absolutely love doing when it comes to a
contract and bronzing is taking a like
smaller fluffy brush like this one but I
let's go into the more cool toned
bronzer so this one is the Marc Jacobs
bronzer and tantastic which is definite
little bit more cool tone then benefit
hoola and I so grabbed this on a more of
tapered brush and just go in it right on
that contour line it to get a more like
defined contour right in the hollow of
the cheek bone I've never done this
before this is like one my favorite
tricks that I just started doing I feel
like it just adds a lot more dimension
and really like gives you the snatched
I think everything how about someone
does my makeup or I watch someone do
makeup or like I just went to make it by
Mario's seminar hmm I think I learned a
lot of things that like everything you
just never stop learning yeah I feel
like I pick up different tricks from
each artists everybody does the make it
different always cool to see how other
people do their makeup cuz you guys be
inspired and pick up different
techniques and learn to the things I
think it better and better and better
I'm next to God by JD weighty 180 brush
this is my all-time favorite nose
contouring brush from a lot see beauty
on the benefit hoola bronzer and also
dipping a tiny bit into the Marc Jacobs
fantastic and we're gonna check out
Laura's nose I love when I go out we can
see a snatch news so I'm like oh yeah
yeah oh so she's doing natch that nose
then this one I have a powder puff and
uses to bake the sides of sister Laura's
nose
what do you feel like you'd be doing if
you weren't on social media you didn't
take the social media path I'd only have
no idea and I think about that honestly
like you would be in college somewhere I
think I would too which scares me
because I think College definitely was
not for me and I think I don't think
college is for everybody I think
education is really important but I
don't think the college particularly for
everybody I think I would be really
struggling to figure out what I wanted
to do with my life it's like that's a
lot of people and hear me out when I how
I how much I agree with you on that
because I almost didn't graduate high
school but because Society said you know
you gotta go to polish to make money or
be smarter to do anything gray so I was
able to get into a college and it took
me three years into college and I had
filled out I was 24 years old I had felt
out and I was left with a ass load of
debt for forcing something that society
put on me make me feel like I was smart
so as a medical assistant at the time as
well working at dermatologists which I
made decent money I just really didn't
like the job so I got pushed into
YouTube and I felt so madly in love with
it and then me and YouTube kind of grew
together and I created this amazing
career and it's all because I fell out
of college you know yeah I don't think
it's everybody I think that everybody
has a different path and education
definitely is not part of everybody I
don't know where I would be if it wasn't
for you too you know I started this
channel just simply as a makeup lover
and all of a sudden supposed to be a
professional businesswoman and you know
the role model for millions people and a
professional makeup artists and do
everything perfect and and it's just
like so much pressure gets thrown on you
you know you're and then you start
you're like whoa this is a lot yeah so
while Laura's baking in the oven at 350
degrees I'm gonna get my benefit precise
here brought pencil in the shade at
number four I'm gonna slay her brows and
that's right I'm never gonna make
Laura's brows go more out then down
towards the tail we were just talking
about this how I've really been doing my
brows more out then down because I feel
like it gives a lot more eyelid space
and I'm literally the mom off Mean Girls
I'm like what school what's the four one
one
mmm and she told me that this year all
her friends are assessed with this guy
named James Charles and I'm serious I
know I was like interesting I was like
James II she was like yeah oh no way you
know I know yeah
she's like nah it was actually happen
yeah I swear let's go in then we're
gonna grab some more shaped Haven I want
to use that to prime Laura's island
dance I'm just gonna use a Y 16 brush to
blend out that concealer and make sure
the eyes are all primed and set in place
and ready for the shadow all right so
now that the brows are both slated in
place we're gonna start with the eye
shadow and we're first gonna be Laura
Lee Los Angeles Casper dreams you blew
me away is the and one ear on your lips
I was a little little chocolate mole I
was like down to watch this video to the
end I want to see what yes and then you
put on like a liquid live oh but that's
not it what did you do and then you put
that on I was gagged you guys haven't
checked out that video make sure to
click somewhere up here and you know
it'll pop up but yeah the probably is so
violent people were so mad tonight oh my
god he's eating her ass no girl it's a
good about it so her personal stories in
Miami 519 brush I'm gonna dip into a
bomb diggity and start putting this into
Laura's crease as a transition shade
this is honestly like all my favourite
transition shades of all time
thank you I love it too it's just such a
good like mustard a yellowy Browns are
my favorite I'm currently using the
shade of Craig crayon an M 210 brush and
I'm using this to pull out that outer
corner shadow and then also define a
decrease a little bit more another grab
the Jacqueline hip hop from a morphe one
of both of our all-time clearly clearly
she's all dirty
she's been used and loved unless we have
another M to ten brushes just a clean
one and dip into this red tone and brown
shade down here then definitely tap off
the fallout as well it's gonna pop this
right in Laura's over V for some
definition I'm not making sure that when
I take these shadows I'm pulling them
out and winging them as well that's like
one of my all-time three things to do
with my makeup you guys know that I love
a go-to pulled out shadow moment it's
like my favorite thing in the world and
I definitely widened my face when I were
literally just talking about earlier how
she like wishes she could do that and I
was like
you can you can do it I'm just gonna do
it I'm gonna grab fluorescein a
scatterbrain only em or two one brush
and I'm going to spread it a little bit
using some fix+ that's what folks plus
all my shimmers no matter what shimmer
it is yeah I can't oh my god I literally
hate when people are using a palette and
they're like well dry you have to use
sex awesome dah
yeah I mean I don't want to I do not and
even if it performs like a gym dry I'm
still fixing it Sam it helps with
fallout 2 like it helps snatch it all
together and if you don't like when a
purchase fix+
even a little bit of water spray bottle
it don't ya it doesn't have to be fixed
less once I have that legit oh I'm gonna
go anyway r39 brush and dip into the
shade of cray cray and just use this to
blend over the edge of that glitter
pigment and then also the darker shades
in the outer corner make sure that that
is a smooth even transition for the half
cut crease so if you only got to use one
makeup product for the rest of your life
no I'll give you three three products so
generous yes and I'm trying to be
generous here three products desert
island you know yeah that too mm-hmm
what's it gonna be I feel like a
concealer Pam a brow pencil and a
highlighter love it what would you do I
would do I would do a concealer because
I'll put a concealer on with no other
makeup so if you like like what could be
worn alone you know concealer mascara
and probably huggin blotting powder no
why
yeah for the lower lash line in the
Jacqueline palette I'm going to cry
the Sigma eat 20 bucks which is a flat
shader brush and I'm gonna grab the
bright ass teal shade oh we get some
color pop is on a Lois lower lash line
I'm excited about this so good are you
kidding
oh come on fire I'm gonna have an amat
to ten brush and dip it to a little bit
of bomb diggity which is that amazing
transition shade and just buff out the
bottom line about to make sure the blue
isn't too like harsh then I'm gonna dip
back into that blue and then I'm gonna
just add a lot of fix+ to really get a
pigmented huh well she does a good tunt
pop have a weak one but I do it
literally all the time still it's a
popper tones baby she's a weak one
the actual better go the darker blue
shade and the purple shade from the
chocolate palette once again it got me a
little bit of fix+ and I'm gonna put
that in the outer corner mixing it
together the bright blue and then also
kind of mending it into those darker
purple red shades that are on the upper
lash line to kind of connect those
together and then one more time of
grabbing my 210 rush I'm just gonna dip
into a warm tone orange shade and just
blend out the bottom at one last time or
what is your favorite makeup look that
you've ever done on yourself I think I
recently did one with Maya I shoulda
palette because as you know like I have
been doing tutorials as much um I've
been reviewing new makeup that's been
launching but one of my favorites for
sure is look I actually do have a
palette and I actually spent a long long
time doing it I did like a Mac cut
crease but like shimmer in the middle of
the cut crease it was really intricate
what about you um I know you got some
looks I have sort of definitely some
good luck yes I think that my favorite
whatever was probably my Eclipse look
from oh yeah like the food mm-hmm I just
added the came in I have my liquid liner
and didn't really use that as a liner I
just kind of more fill to end and then
use it to define that crease it was good
girl that's you watching sometimes you
just get blessed I should be watching a
movie cuz I'm gonna have Lara Lally
apply her own at mascara that's just our
rules and
Jules in the artistry if you're working
with someone who can do their own
mascara they're doing their own mascara
well Laura is applying the mascara she's
using benefit roller lash of course I am
grabbing the Lily lashes my Emily's
these are my all-time favorite lashes oh
my god so Lourdes is introduced me to
this new lash glue from the Loire called
the lash adhesive and it's the best ever
and I'm so hated to not try this for
myself
good it dries out so quickly and like
sticks which never happens because you
guys know every time I put on an eyelash
I was sitting there fumbling with the
freaking inner corner for like 20 that's
everybody there she is
yep that's good ever been out and about
and then your inner corner just pops up
yeah oh yeah that's why I carry law
school at all times I mean that me -
well I like when I go to events and
stuff if I'm wearing makeup I always
have oslo and a pair of tweezers and a
Beautyblender and blotting powder and
straws that's genius
alright I'm adding straws to my list
that's that's a good one okay so another
one is all complete we're gonna go head
and do them on an off camera right now
and then I'll be right back to finish
all the rest of the law okay guys so
both eyes aren't well what did you see
that
what I'm scared was this shadow oh my
god weird to focus yeah we're gonna use
the why 14 today look do you have most
of the morphe brushes memorized yeah we
do every time they're always like how do
you know that I'm like I don't know I
just use them all the time and of course
wouldn't be a James Charles City without
anasazi it's so Hollywood illuminator
hashtag not sponsored oh are you kidding
I'm also there go a little bit of
scatterbrain on that same brush and I'm
going to use that to kind of like really
lightly blend together the bronzer and
the highlighter I like doing this a lot
actually using like a more metallic
shade rather than highlighter to blend
together just for like a more subtle
glow also using this shade to highlight
Laura's do we do hello your forehead
over oh yeah oh yeah you literally just
it on me yeah it's like everything in
the world some people don't like it so
I'm always gonna tell them you know I do
but yeah
it's my favorite so now that the makeup
is all on our last time it's gonna be at
the lipid a doodahs and for today's look
I'm gonna be using the Anasazi liquid
lipstick in the shade and naked another
good naked lamp and then last but
certainly not least I'm gonna give her a
little spritz of the tatcha luminous
dewy skin mess maybe a little bit more
than a little spread and guys this is
the completed look
yes it looks so good I'm actually really
really happy on it yeah thank you I love
it so much love love love the eyes I
can't quit looking at the viewfinder
sorry guys that's okay oh my god I'm
cute in the same thing I'm looking at
you okay
let's go and do the brutal reveal okay
what would you do differently what do
you think what do you love you got me
hard on this one I love the look I think
the base looks so amazing and like
smooth and buttery and I love the
highlight I love everything James you
have to hate something you don't like
there's nothing I don't like a lot of
immunity so larlie approved makeup right
here Oh your nose contour me is
completely different from what I do but
my nose looks so snatch she's not doing
yeah I'm glad that's what I'm wasting
water always think I want to make
people's noses so tiny but I'm always
like oh my god are they gonna know like
the fact that I'm literally giving them
a nose job right now I'm all here for it
that's let's make it wash yourself a
nice I like it if you guys enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not ready click
the little Bell notification icon so you
can be notified every time I upload
videos if you'd like to follow me on a
makeup turn you can follow me and secure
my Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat from over behind
the scenes I saw a shave Charles that
extra ass after Charles if you like to
follow lauralee for stuff will all be I
talk a little bit slower than James if
you like to check out our video we did
on Laura's channel where she did this
makeup on Mia Oh click down below as
well or it'll be somewhere on the screen
this accessory shadow kosu sister Krista
thank you so much for your always
falling in supporting you know I love
you so much and if you would like to be
next week sister shout out make sure
always review anybody letting something
go live on it Twitter I had a lot of fun
filming today and I hope you guys
enjoyed this video thank you guys so
much for being here watching wait we
should do this was crime to chance okay
and before you leave don't forget to
subscribe to my channel before you leave
subscribe there's a goodbye bye guys
[Music]