first his voiceover took the internet by
storm then he did my blame you've seen
him on top story you haven't seen him in
my bed yet no today daddy's back
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
[Music]
notice very very very long time since
I've had tiny Victor on my youtube
channel as you heard him the very very
cheesy intro that we decided to get to
he did my voiceover and he did my glam
but I've been learning to claim a victor
for so long he's been declining forever
but we finally came to a good deal which
cannot be discussed on camera before we
really get into this video I want to say
a major thank you to one of my best
friends in the entire world Victor for
those of you guys who don't know if
Victor is not actually my father he is
my best friend in the entire world
husband but I call him daddy because
he's extremely hot and I fell in love
with him but we were just best friends
to clarify because we still get
questions all the time even though we've
disclosed in every single video so
Victor is not my father
they just my daddy take at the end of
the day I definitely takes a lot of
balls for a straight guy to say here put
on a full face of glam so major respect
to Victor at the end of the day it's
just makeup so I'm actually here just to
support you that's all that matters wow
I just wipe it off a true man
well thought about being sad this is
definitely gonna be a very for any long
videos I don't want to keep you guys for
too much longer if you want to see me
create this bronzy kilo smokey eye and
Victor Henry makeup for the first time
we talked about everything under the Sun
make sure you ready for this
keep on watching I'm person I start by
priming and daddy's face using our
benefit Porefessional primer which are
how does it feel to have makeup on
mostly who don't know I've been trying
to get Victor to do this video with me
for a very very long time now sister's
been saying no how do you feel to be
finally putting makeup on answer the
question for daddy's foundation today
I'm gonna used to make up forever not
all try you see foundation check the
liquid formula in the shade of wire for
25 kit over here stop there we go come
on Victor no hey stop it's gonna take us
three hours oh you're sweaty wait your
nose is broken but if I push on it
doesn't hurt though right
no I just can't breathe great
this citation is looking a little bit
talk right now I'm gonna blend it down
Victor's neck and that's really well
before head in the studio lights but
apparently this lighting is a little bit
of a different story but I don't really
have a lot of foundation shades a much
darker skin tones because y'all know
that I am extremely pale like Casper the
Friendly Ghost up in here so I'm trying
my best I will even about concealer I
promise for consider said were to be
using the tarp shaped tape concealer in
the shade of light medium honey
cuz Victor is my honey the most of my
talk I've ever been good why you
squinting that one feels cold how would
I do anything I want to close my look
Minna no chin down open your eyes
how the do you look up with your
chin down actually like this I just my
eyes yeah no sorry it's taken by work by
me [ __ ] I'll be honest right now
I really don't hate him I just
mess with him that's what it's our
friendship friendship
oh I'm contouring Victor Stacy's in my
Murphy M 5 to 3 brush and my Kat Von D
shade light palette hasn't always I'm
just gonna chisel his cheekbones Victor
has really really good cheekbones and
I'm already mad because I know his
contour highlight and blush region is
gonna look really really good so I'm
gonna contour Victor's at Vegas forehead
using the same brush that's the only big
thing in contour
oh I'm gonna contractors no seize my JD
baby why need you to brush and my shade
and light palette once again
Victor's nose it's currently broken I
mean it's been broken for several years
now and it's still not fixed so we're
gonna try to fix that today yeah it kind
of broke it a while ago
playing basketball and never really
fully broke so they couldn't push it
back so it's just basically like what is
it a fracture yeah it's a crack do I
look like a doctor to you for me
currently I watched the Bates Motel I
started watching that and I think it
stopped really hang up or well I know
that like the history behind yeah well I
took him like a history whooping pitcher
class in high school and we had to watch
a bunch of black and white movies and
one of the movies was called psycho it
was basically that same setting mmm in
that in that show like the same hotel
the same house in the back my current
favorite show the watch is probably
present break have you guys have like do
they really that was in the question oh
come on
okay that if it's not present remake our
favor sort of watching will be RuPaul's
Drag Race I'm so excited to see this
season unveiling it's so good and I
definitely have so many favorites that I
want to win team shy and team Sasha here
we go
I'm miss really lately of baking
Victor's face to bring out some of those
highlights like I said before and this
foundation is definitely a little bit
dark so I'm gonna try to even everything
out and make him not look dark I'm also
gonna bake underneath of Victor's beard
to get a more a defined line like I said
I've never done makeup on a beer before
so I'm pregnant this works I see man I
do it shout-out sister Minnie
if this doesn't work it's on you oh my
god your nose so it's broke what you
can't see is that I'm actually chained
to this chair oh my hands are tied
behind my back so I'm gonna slay
Victor's browser season my benefit
precisely eyebrow pencil in the shade at
number six just to fill them in Victor
actually has pretty good brows
I just tweets that before we started
this video she said benefit yeah use 10%
off for change
Stephanie oh my god your brow looks so
good
San Francisco's yeah that's like one of
like the first trips we get together
that was pretty cool
second temptress is no trip I didn't get
to do there's someone behind the camera
who did not use his plus-one wisely my
hurt memory of me and Victor together is
probably honestly like right now I know
that sounds so stupid but I've been
trying to get Victor to this video with
me for so long
I just think it's really cool that
Victor is like a straight married man
and is like letting me put makeup on his
face because he's like my best friend in
the entire world so that's cool and it
means a lot to me and I know this video
is gonna do well so you guys better
smash that like button and all of our
daddy
Wladimir do his makeup adidas Chipotle
Friends of me on Twitter today that's so
disrespectful somebody tweeted about
them sponsoring me and I quote read and
they're like we love that you're such a
good fan James suddenly I'm never having
my burrito go with white rice no beans
chicken mild sauce and lettuce cheese
o'clock ever again Victor I have a
question for you yes what's your
favorite makeup of the University me
we're easy flashback Marion oh my god
iconic I'm gonna set Victor's Brown
place using the UH Nastasia tinted brow
gel the shirt is for us so that right
there is a brow oh good I'm mad would
you be if I just want fries that are
amazing the morphe 35o eyeshadow palette
I'm gonna do a halo eye on Victor
because know like we should do something
fun why do you think of halo eye is
gonna consist of I don't know what is it
you know well a halo eye mr. Victor
basically we're gonna have the darker
shade on the outside yeah and then
there's gonna be like a pop of
brightness in the metal is it okay I'm
just gonna start off using my Sigma e35
a tape or blending brush and put this
dark e orange shade into the crease line
under season this shade is my transition
color I'm really not going to try to do
like too dark or too intense my halo ID
I want this to be like really light and
soft especially because if we stay here
for seven hours doing a lock on Victor
I'll probably end up stabbing me so X
under grab my morphe r39 brush and dip
into a medium of brown orange e shade
twos as like the trend
to start off deepening the halo effect
use Coe James wow that's rude daddy
right there I'm really focusing that
color on the outer and inner corners of
the eye and then budding up into the
creases the slightest bat but making
sure to leave the middle of the lid
nice and light in kind of empty next is
that same exact brush I'm going to dip
into a little bit darker of a brown
shade and then place that on the very
inner and outer corners all right
did you really and I'm gonna get Murphy
advant 1 4 9 I grab my darkest Brown and
really deep it up the internal corner as
that like last final darkening shade
they say right here yeah once you use
them a lot of times I have liver eyes
just how you memorize like locations in
the warehouse where the clothes go and
you're speaking my language when you get
like a fine dinner or annoyed you hear
really really mad and then you're really
annoying about it like you can
take a tack look and I'm like you don't
listen to anything anybody else says you
being annoying that it that makes me
feel like that well great answer but it
is when you think you're always right
that's living you though no you both
that way no yes no thank you yeah the
difference the difference is you always
think you're right so do you well know
yes I keep quiet when I think I'm right
but there's some things that you miss
[ __ ] I don't think so squirrel I keep
quite a lot of times the things you say
that I couldn't have a pinion no but I
don't say it because it's not worth it
but when I feel like you're truly wrong
is when I I step in and I say something
sweet way
how does it feel know that I'm 18 and
I'm no longer your legal responsibility
as a father it's great freemen I get rid
of you for 18 years I'm gonna grab my
mac 242 brush in a little bit of the
Urban Decay all later as you just saw
and I'm gonna put this right on the
center of effectors lit as like the
brightness for the halo I
then going back into my r39 person
that's gonna make sure that those edges
are really really it diffused out for
the lower last thing would use the same
brush from before I'm just going to look
up for me oh my god what your eyes just
did something really ugly yeah get over
her lashes today on sister Victor we're
gonna be using the Lily lashes in the
style of Miami alright guys and that is
what I aqua plea over on sister Victor
how do you feel so far very
uncomfortable I told you it wasn't the
easiest thing in the world this is why
people complain not wanting to take
their makeup off at the end of the day
everything's fine until you put these
lashes on
I'm so sorry you're so great thank you
for sharing your story
alright guys we're gonna go ahead and
finish the other eye off-camera so we're
not sitting here for a long time we'll
be right back and we will finish off the
rest of the face okay guys now that the
lashes are both on it Victor is about to
cry right now because he's actually
uncomfortable but you look beautiful and
that's what matters right I like
beautiful before now we're gonna move on
to it the highlighter and for this we're
gonna be using the Oprah Roadeo dry when
we all take the herbs and I thought this
is gonna look really really good on
Victor's skin tone so we're gonna get
the glow on use coat James to apply the
how that I'm gonna use my morphe r-36
brush yeah oh that is a glow mani mu8 is
shaking macdaddy just fell over and died
and Jeffrey's are never heard of her
James Charles never gonna hurt Victor's
broken nose one last time using some
highlighter still looks broke for a lip
stain we're gonna be using the anasazi
liquid lipstick in the shade as Jen I
picked this home because I think it'll
look really really good on Victor's skin
tone is it going to we're gonna find out
damn Kylie Jenner is shaking right now
can you open your eyes they're ready
with the foot and our last and final
step for this glam on sister vector is
going to be to set it so it stays locked
in place all night long for five minutes
alright guys and this is the completed
look over on daddy how do you feel all
horrible I could always speak for myself
here when I'm saying I really thoroughly
enjoyed this process and I say that
because I know Victor did not but I have
intended this for so long so major thank
you to my best friend in the entire
world oh my daddy for doing this video
we're gonna it was a wonderful time
you're gonna have to redo it all and
then even longer
if you guys under this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below it's and if you feel bad for
me please get it to 30,000 lines how
about this and because those gonna do
250 thousand likes I will blame on
Victor again maybe and like a drag look
or something
35 35 30 if you haven't already make
sure to hit that big red subscribe
button down below as well I post two
videos a week on Mondays and Fridays
that I'd love to have you join at the
sisterhood if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup turning and follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat and you
know who we're behind the scenes I'm
stuff where you can see all of us
sisters together I'm constantly with my
daddy our James Charles and that extra
ass after Charles
yes it's so important if you'd like to
follow me you can follow me yet big to
tall on Instagram and snapchat hang up
being six foot six yeah
too tall all right sisters thank you so
much for watching and we will see you in
the next video bye
[Music]