hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's that I have a super super fun
makeup challenge plan for a lovely video
I got ready in the complete pitch-black
darkness which was so intense
the results were spooky Diddley's if you
guys have not checked out last week's
video be sure to click right up here and
go check it out but I had so much fun
doing and I really don't do makeup
challenges that often so I wanted to do
another one today mostly because I'm
running out of video ideas but I thought
it'd be very very fun and this is one
challenge you guys have been requesting
for so long it is always one of the top
comments on my videos this challenge
breaks all laws of makeup and that is
doing my makeup backwards all makeup
lovers both professional artists and
average makeup wears how about we like
to call a makeup routine I personally
like to start off with my face then
eyebrows and eyes then lashes that lips
then finishing touches that I don't like
to do a different routine some people
start with their eyebrows some people
start with their eyes don't even ask me
how they do that but obviously the end
goal no matter where you start is to
look beautiful and confident for today's
video I'm gonna only make up knowledge
upside down and do a makeup routine
backwards starting with settings for it
and then finishing off with foundation
which is normally my first thing I think
you guys get the point at this point
this should be intense I don't know who
the originator heir so I don't know who
to give credit to but I know both Dante
and Michael think I've done an please go
check out the videos they're absolutely
amazing content creators I love them
both but everyone who has done this has
been using it through normal makeup
products in the opposite order for me
I'm gonna do everything in the opposite
order but I did switch out a few
products that I knew would really really
mess everything up because I do want to
try to make this the best-looking result
possible even while still doing it
backwards you guys know what I mean
long story short I am so excited for
this so without further ado if you'd
like to see my makeup routine completely
backwards
let's get started
[Music]
alright sister so I'm starting all this
up today by going in with my morphia
prep and set settings right and I'm just
going to mist my entire face as a base
to this makeup obviously this would
normally be my last step but since is
the prep and sat hopefully this will
still work if you know what I'm saying
second to last didn't wake up or two you
guys know I usually finished off my
looks with a liquid lipstick for today's
video I'm gonna use the Anastacio liquid
lipstick in the shade Archon I really
really love the shade and I think it'll
match really really well with the look
that I have planned fingers crossed that
the eyes go out certainly we have no
idea what it's gonna look like I am a
little bit worried about this though
because while I love the anasazi look of
lipsticks and all of their colors they
are a little bit drying so hopefully
throughout this entire video and throw
out the talking they don't get like
crusted Sahara desert status at the end
we'll see this looks so strange hello
before lifts I'm usually finishing off
my eyes with lashes and mascara normally
likes to do a lashes and then blend them
together with the mascara because I
personally have a really really hard
time at putting on lashes but for
today's video we have to do mascara
first about Masha so lord help me in
this situation we might have a very very
gia Gunn wonky law situation but for
today's video i'm gonna be using the
benefit BADgal bang mascara this is
their brand new a 36 hour of the
luminizing mascara I just got back for
an amazing trip at Oman gearing with
Benefit Cosmetics if you don't follow me
on stop you definitely should I posted
everything over there was so much fun
but we were celebrating the launch of
this mascara and it is literally so so
is so so good if you guys have not yet
checked out this baby you definitely
have to do you see how pretty my Alice
just look right now hello Benefit girl
you snapped
so next obviously comes lashes and for
today's video of course I'm going to use
my Lily lashes and Miami's these are my
all-time favorite lashes and I also just
recently found out you can use KO James
for 10% off of these I know some of you
guys have used it before but I didn't
even know that existed so hey if you
ever want to check out my all-time
favorite lashes coat James gets the
money off you're welcome okay second
time's the charm
she's on there I think the one thing
that's really good about this challenge
is that my eyeliner is got to come after
my lashes so I get to hide all the
mistakes that I just made woo before
doing my lashes I normally line my
waterline
I'm gonna do that using the pretty
vulgar new two liner and then comes
lowered lashline shadow and for today's
look I'm gonna be using the chocolate
hell are some Apollo I guess we have to
go from darkest to lightest which is not
what I normally like to do but we're
gonna have to make it work I'm first
gonna grab an Emma 5:08 this is just a
tiny little blending brush and grab this
dark brown shade right in here and buff
this right up against the lash line I am
of course planning a wing too so I'm
just gonna pull this out slightly in the
outer corner to make sure that that's
blended together and there's no like
really awkward divide I'm next in to
grab my makeup shock t61 brush and dip
into this ready shade right here and use
that to buff out the brown I'm placing
that right below I'm making sure that
there's no harsh edges really using that
to diffuse out the brown because we did
not want it to look like we just got
punched in the eye
but of course leaving room because we
don't wanna pull it too far down finally
I'm gonna go over Smith 247 brush and
dip into this bright orange and this
kind of mac and cheese shade right here
mixed together and then just buff that
out so far actually not that bad moving
on to my upper lid at my last of my eye
looks is always eyeliner if I'm wearing
it and for today's look yes it does
include eyeliner so I'm gonna turn up
the Tom Ford Island our pen and attempt
to sketch out a way over top of my
lashes oh God
Hey did I just do it Oh when it comes to
this challenges you guys might like to
go big or go home
and normally next to be eyeshadow but
for this look I want to do I'm probably
gonna regret this
hey glitter cut crease so I got the BH
Cosmetics glitters in the shades
sapphire and mermaid blue and also the
violet boss glitter adhesive normally
yes I would do this first then this but
let's be real these are never gonna
stick so get over it it's not that deep
I'm just gonna ply these with the darker
blue in the outer corner I'm bringing
into the teal and hopefully we'll be
able to make this look really cute do
you see this hello look at how good that
crease sighs I feel like we might be
able to make this work to start off the
actual cut crease I'm gonna go back to
the light chocolate eyeshadow palette
and my e39 brush and start off with this
dark brown shade once again so much of
the lower lashline and go right above
that crease
okay interesting I'm not gonna get that
same I'm 508 brush from before and dip
into that same a bright red shade and
blend out that line if any of you guys
watching they're like oh gee sisters you
know that this is the technique I used
to use all the time for doing up cut
creases I have more recently actually
switching to the normal technique of
doing it when starting off with the
lightest shadow and then working way in
and then just cutting it but I used to
do all my cut creases by sketching out
the line first and then I'm blending
upwards so I think I may have the upper
hand in this but clearly it's not
looking too great so far so I don't know
I'm gonna really carefully blend that
out clearly she needs a little bit of
work using the bright orange paint from
before
I think I'm gonna grab that mac and
cheese hit from before and just go right
over those edges what's actually working
my favorite here is that since they
don't have an eyeshadow base on if
anything gets too intense I can just go
over with my blending brush and just
scrub really really hard and it'll
actually take off some of that product
since it doesn't have anything to really
stick to okay so that is what I all
complete obviously may still have some
work to do but I'm gonna go ahead and do
the other one off-camera in the same
exact order I promise and I'll be right
back all right now back about 30 minutes
later and that is the second eye all
complete and this should be proof that I
never cheat during challenges even off
camera because this eye is not looking
the best
so before eyes my makeup routine always
comes my eyebrows but I always fill them
in and then use my brow gel and then
clean them up since this is reverse I'm
gonna go out at some concealer and go
right under this and be super super
careful and not to overlap the eyeshadow
and then fill the man wish me luck
I have to try to imagine where I'm going
to actually fill in the eyebrow
[Music]
that looks about right maybe I'm gonna
grab a synthetic bullet brush this is
the e36 and buff that out being really
really careful to not mess up the
eyeshadow that I worked so hard on okay
honestly that doesn't even look that bad
but now I have no idea how we're gonna
fill these in without messing up I
really rely on that concealer afterwards
to fill my brows today I'm going to use
the iconic brow cushion in the shade
medium sister nikkietutorials introduced
me to this in our collab and I feel like
I'll be able to be really precise with
this at an angle brush since it is a
liquid of formula hopefully
[Music]
okay you know what a little bit dark but
I feel like we can work with bass okay
that is the other bra I'll complete once
again not lying about this good brow a
brow let's move on so now that the lips
eyes and brows are all complete it is
time for the base makeup now it is so
weird too because a lot of people
actually start their base makeup with
eyes and brows already done but for me
that is something that is very very new
to me I don't do that like ever so this
is definitely gonna be a major major
challenge normally when it comes to my
base makeup you guys know that likes to
use my powder products but for today's
video like I said I do want to switch
out my products just a little bit to
really try my best to make this a
successful look so out of my basic of my
last step is always a highlighter so for
today I'm gonna use the brand new
married do manizer from the balm which
is a liquid highlight I'm gonna put this
right in the same places as my normal oh
wow that's really pretty
okay I'm gonna put this into normal
pieces as all my highlights usually go
in the inner corners then I'm just gonna
take my damp Beauty Blender and I'm
going to blend it right out oh you're
kidding wow that's blinding though huh
love best whoa I definitely need to try
to sell again in a video where I'm not
like completely messing up my makeup so
before a highly obviously comes a
contour and normally I use my Kat Von D
shade Alam palette but like I said I'm
not gonna use powders because we
obviously have to do a foundation and
concealer later on and that just gets
really really messy so I'm Lee needs my
benefit hoola cream contouring stick
instead just gonna go right in all the
hollows of my face a little bit on the
forehead tell you know reduce that
hairline because lord knows sister needs
it on the jaw line to really snatch her
up and then also right down the bridge
of the nose you guys for this video I
definitely do not think we're gonna have
a snatched nose and I am
very sad about it then once again just
gonna take my damp Beauty Blender and
buff that right in oh that is a little
orange well you're literally kidding me
I look like I was doing my makeup
outside on a really sunny day and only
did my eyes and my brows and then fell
asleep and woke up like seven hours
later with a sunburn what is going on no
this was so good okay say this what I
hadn't grabbed my iconic London a cream
contour kit and I'm gonna go in it with
this shade right down here to both
darken up the contours but also cool
them down just a little bit because
clearly this is not what we want okay
yeah much better
a little intense but we can fix this we
got this in the bag
pretend that little meltdown ever happen
this is scary
so before contouring highlighting and
blush obviously comes concealer and at
the foundation but in between those is
the powder and if you guys are a makeup
lover you know that the number one rule
and makeup is that it's really really
just illegal like the police will come
after you if you put a cream product
over powder it's just the formulas and
the texture and the chemistry behind it
just makes them not really work together
but that's today's challenge we have to
do it now I'm just gonna use a light
amount of my Laura Mercier translucent
setting powder mix together my Too Faced
sweet peach powder on this one oh god my
damp Beauty Blender and dip right in and
just apply a really really really light
layer to the entire face to set it in
place and hopefully not to disrupt the
foundation
told you there are the police Mitchell
now so another face is all set in place
before that step comes concealer and of
course I'm using my guitar shape deep in
the shade light neutral and I'm actually
kind of happy that this step is coming
before foundation because I think I can
kind of use this to my advantage to
really carve out my mistakes being the
eyebrows of course the nose contour the
lips and the contour so everything is
like ready and more clean for the
foundation we could pull this together
let's see I'm of course gonna put this
right in the center of my forehead for
highlighting okay just cut that bra off
a little bit but you know what maybe
it's for the better
[Music]
well this is an interesting look to say
the least
yes thank God for beauty blenders
because they really do fix anything
my contour literally looks like Trixie
Mattel from RuPaul's Drag Race I'm
coming for you girl my god this kids is
why you did not put creams or liquid
over powder because once that is set in
place whenever you put over top will not
blend oh no oh this needs to blend out
oh my lord I cannot have this contour of
my own right now
so my base has gone from nothing and
very very pimply inbred - way to orange
- way too dark
- now way too light and still very
uneven so obviously the next step and
last step is going to be foundation
normally you guys know I use the Too
Faced for other things just like my
all-time favorite hold it girl
foundation it is so so so good but I
will say for my skin type it is a
hydrating foundation that does not dry
down and since this is the last step and
I do not have powder to modify and save
the day I'm gonna go with the LA girl
Pro matte new foundation in the shade
stand these just launched and I watch a
review on them and apparently these do
dried down never try these before so
this could be an absolute disaster but
fingers crossed that this hopefully
finishes us up very very nicely because
I feel like where we're at right now
this look is not that bad
I'm just gonna go into my same Beauty
Blender and really lightly it go right
over the entire face
you guys wait a second this actually
kinda looks good before foundation
usually comes a primer but you guys know
I stopped using it a long long time ago
because I've always messed up my nose
contour so I guess this works my
advantage because I think I'm done okay
you guys looking in the mirror right now
I am shucks out of my mind not even
gonna lie I picked this look today
because I wanted to challenge myself but
mostly because I thought this is gonna
be a major fail and would make for some
really comedic content listen you gotta
do what you gotta do YouTube just is not
the same anymore but I feel like this
challenge we're such a success all right
sisters netis all I have for this video
today definitely give it a big thumbs up
down below if you enjoyed it and if you
think that I Slade and this makeup
definitely make comment down below as
well and tell me how you think I did and
if you guys decide to try out this
challenge please tweet me a picture this
was so much fun to do and I thought the
results are gonna be hilarious
I'm pleasantly surprised of them but I
would love to see how you guys are able
to perform with their makeup routine
completely reversed if you have not
already make sure to click that big red
button down below and subscribe to my
youtube channel I would love to have you
join at the sisterhood it is a very very
good time I promise and also click that
little bell icon so you can notified
every time I upload a brand new video if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat form or how the
themes lights up it's James Charles and
extra asks after Charles this video is
sister Sara Costa sister Alexis thank
you so much for your always following in
supporting I love you so so so much and
if you'd like to be the next videos to
show shout out my super always retweet
video links when they go live on Twitter
all right sisters thank you so much for
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next one
[Music]