hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
you may be wondering why my hair is not
styled and pooped up like normal and why
I'm wearing this very fancy wake up up
on my head today and for today's video
we're gonna doing a drag tutorial I've
only done drag a few times on my
Instagram page but they've all been
looks at I've been super super proud of
and every time I do post one as well
literally all the comments are what are
you doing a video when are you filming a
video we want to know how to do this so
for today's video I sat down and I'm
gonna teach you guys how to go from this
to this I have a ton of products here in
front of me and ironically enough most
of them are actually part of my everyday
makeup routine dry makeup doesn't have
to be some crazy expensive art you can
totally use the products you have at
home just in a different style that you
might not think of obviously I am NOT a
dry queen you guys know I am a makeup
artist and I definitely cannot perform
or dance on stage that is for [ __ ] sure
but 50% of drag is the whole aesthetic
behind edit is a very very cool and
beautiful art form so without further
ado if you would like to see it Mia
transform into a drag queen and just
test out some driving makeup today make
sure you keep on watching alright so
some drag queens have their eyebrows
shaven up but of course I have a very
very bushy brows so our first step today
is going to be to cover them up all
you're gonna use the classic Elmer's
glue stick a spoolie and then a wet
towel I'm basically just taking my glue
stick and running this all throughout my
eyebrows and I'm going super hard as
well I want a ton of glue to get on
there especially for the first layer I'm
gonna grab my spoolie brush and I'm
gonna pull my skin up and I'm just going
to really really roughly go through that
brow and brush all the hairs upwards
it's really importantly you do a good
job spooling through these and brushing
them all the way upwards flat to your
face because once you add a lot of
layers of glue you will be able to a
powder and foundation right over them
and hopefully the goal this will
obviously be that there is no texture
and you can't see them at all so you
really have to make sure that the brow
covering process is done it's super
super efficiently and then once it's all
comb through I just wet the corner of
this towel and then I always like to go
around the hairs and just kind of wipe
away the extra of glue
having the least amount of glue possible
the better but obviously you need to
cover them depending on how thick your
bronzer and mine are super super thick
so I always like to wipe away the glue
around the edges so therefore the glue
it's only on the brow and not on the
skin it because that creates unwanted
texture it later on so by the time that
this eyebrow
flew down and cleaned up this bra is now
completely dry so we can go on to the
next layer so for this layer once again
I'm gonna grab my glue stick and I'm
just gonna press really really hard on
to the actual hairs and I'm gonna make
sure to really kind of dig this into my
forehead as well because once we put the
glue on this layer we are gonna spoolie
through it because that's just going to
interrupt the layer beforehand so from
now on we're just going to layer over
top and then clean it up and we're gonna
repeat this exact process probably three
or four times until we have four layers
of glue total and then we'll go on to
the next step
all right so this is four layers of glue
completely packed on there and dry and
the next step is gonna be to go in with
Cody err some powder and a powder puff
and pack those brows down I'm gonna take
their powder puffs and I'm gonna dip
into quite a lot of powder just dust the
excess off
coughing it because we all know what
this smells like and then I'm going to
pack it into my brows I'm definitely not
going to be worrying about fallout
because we can always brush it away but
basically this powder is going to really
set the brows in place make sure that
that glue is 100% set and then also fill
in any areas that texture is still left
which makes them super super smooth and
ready to cover with foundation for
foundation today I'm going to be using
my new favorite crumble that I've been
telling you guys about and that is the
Make Up For Ever Ultra HD and the Too
Faced Born This Day Foundation
I am in the shade @y at 325 in this one
and then natural beige and the two-faced
one I'm just gonna go in and I'm going
to go over the brows first and I'm just
going to press that foundation in there
pretty hard to really fill in all the
places and you see how that brow is now
completely covered and that's spooky I'm
actually gonna let this Foundation start
to set in place and dry down just a
little bit before I go into my full face
and while I do that I'm gonna go to the
makeup forever Pro sculpting palette and
I'm going to color cracks just gonna
grab any normal packing brush and go
into this orange shade and then rub it
all over my beard area I definitely get
a pretty bad 5 o'clock shadow now that
I'm thinking about it I probably should
have color corrected my eyebrows to
being that they are a blue toned hair
just like all hair and body is so I was
pretty done with me but I guess we're
just going to color correct the beard
and pray that the eyebrows get decent
coverage basically I want to put this
consider anywhere where I normally have
darkness or a body hair growing I
definitely get a lot of hair on my chin
massage area and then in my
sideburns and then I definitely get a
lot of darkness underneath my eyes from
barely sleeping from editing all night
long but basically the orange tones that
the concealer are going to cancel out
the blue tones of the darkness which
just furthers the illusion let's I can
see those all in there and blend it out
I'm just gonna go end up my makeup
forever stick once again and just cover
it over my entire face I'm definitely
putting a lot of this on and going full
coverage tonight this is definitely not
a natural everyday look by any means
this is literally the most horrifying
look ever max I'm gonna go to light our
shave tape in the shade light and just
highlight my face like I said we are not
going for a natural look in any means
for today so I'm definitely packing a
lot of product on I know a lot of drag
queens like doing a cream contouring 1/4
or makeup for me cream contouring is
just something that I'm not really a fan
of so I am gonna be doing all powder
contouring today but that is totally up
to personal preference you can do
whatever you want if you wanted to do
cream contouring and now would be the
time to do it before we get into powder
and the next step and then once again
I'm gonna grab my coat here some powder
and a powder puff and we're going to
pack the powder on today
flashback Mary here we come I'm gonna
start by setting underneath my eyes
because that's we're gonna get the most
amount of creases and then I'm gonna
really pack the powder into my nose
because you're gonna be contouring it a
lot today
and I really want to make sure that the
foundation and concealer stay on there
and don't wear off same thing when it
comes to the eyebrows I'm just gonna be
really really gentle as well because we
don't want to take off any of that
product that we already layer down are
also gonna start peeking back through to
contour my face today I'm gonna use
shocking my Kat Von D shade and light
palette I'm gonna use my Brophy M 405
brush and dip into the left and middle
shade and I'm just gonna go in and test
out my face I usually cover from about
here down to the corner of my mouth but
for actual drag makeup I'm gonna contour
starting at the top of my sideburn and
then I'm gonna go and draw a like more
curved line kind of ending more up here
instead that just gonna really raise my
cheekbones and give them more of a
feminine appearance obviously there's no
exact way we're gonna do drag you can
put your face however you want you can
contour however you want and I know
there's no exact male or female face
shape that we need to follow I'm just
doing it based on these standards that
people usually do follow when it comes
to contouring the jaw line similar to
the cheek bone I am gonna do something a
little bit different to make everything
look more saw
I'm actually going to chisel up my
jawline starting at the corner here and
kind of rounding this out a little bit
just to get my face some more stock and
once again feminine appearance when it
comes to my notes to contour it you
sisters already know that I love a good
chiseled out pinched ass
nose so for today's like I'm just gonna
do the same exact thing just a little
bit more intense
finally to finish off the base I'm just
gonna go in with my benefit hoola
bronzer in my Murphy M five to seven
brush and I'm just gonna use this
bronzer to kind of blend together the
contour and highlight and make
everything at nice and bronzy and
connected same exact thing outcode
here's a powder eye powder puff one last
time you guys know that I stopped baking
my face and my normal makeup routine a
very very long time ago when I moved to
California I just thought that it wasn't
really necessary anymore and I much
preferred the more glowy dewy foundation
look but when it comes to drag makeup
baking is absolutely necessary
it definitely locks the face in place
because these Queens that are doing this
makeup on a nightly basis are gonna be
performing on stage under a whole lot of
lights and dancing and sweating so it
really makes sure all the foundation
stays on and also using the translucent
powder intensifies all the highlights
that we use with our concealer earlier
which just makes the makeup have a lot
more dimension and just look better in
in general
alright so brace yourself because Drive
brows are by far the most complicated
part of drag makeup and even after doing
look several several times and being a
professional makeup artist it is still
so hard for me to keep my brows perfect
and symmetrical but we're going to try
of course so today I'm gonna be using
the benefit curb brow and I'm using the
shade and number three to match my wig
and then I'm just gonna use any old
anchor brush and this is the makeup
shock t-55 okay so I just grabbed a
little bit of product on my angle brush
and I'm just gonna start sketching them
and so I'm basically gonna start my brow
at the bottom of my normal brow I want
my new Brown to be in the exact same
starting position as my old one so
therefore they look natural and I'm just
gonna draw them a whole lot more arched
than my normal everyday brows and a
little bit thinner too
once they have the bottom line of the
brow all lined up I like to Donna start
at the outside and make the tail then I
always like to draw that upper brow and
right about here and then just connect
him well if they have those brows all
lined in and pretty much filled up I
like to take just the side of the brush
and go in and start to pack that product
forward to create a natural ombre once
their ombre now I'm gonna go back to the
very original angle brush being the t-55
from makeup shock and dip it to this
dark brown shading it right up in here
and just create some brown strokes as
always with my normal brows I'm gonna
grab a little bit more shaped tube
concealer once again in the shade light
and then at my morphe 43 brush and just
clean them up with any excess consider
I'm just going to prime and set my
eyelids and get ready for eye shadow
okay so now that the brows are all
complete you can take a major deep
breath because the rest is all smooth
sailing from here so fresh titled like I
said I'll be using the Jacqueline Hale
pill and I'm gonna start off using my
makeup shock t4 brush and dipping into
this neutral tone a brown shade right up
in here and just lightly dusting that in
my crease I'm gonna be cutting out my
crease today so I'm gonna be putting
this just slightly above if you guys
have followed me for a while you've
probably seen all the job looks that
I've done there really hasn't been that
many of them in the first place
but I used to do a really really really
intense style outdrive makeup that
really was never flattering to my face
everyone would always tweet them when I
[ __ ] posted them saying I look like
the dragon from Shrek which yes I'll
give you that they're definitely dead I
recently just discovered a Brazilian
drag queen ever named Pablo avatar that
I am literally obsessed with he's so
pretty he's also a musician so like a
true freaking sister because makeup is
very very natural and not very intense
even for being a drag queen so as soon
as I saw him I was so inspired to test
this out and if you guys follow me on
SAP which if you don't you definitely
need to I tried out this look a few
nights ago and everybody was kind of
shook over I was took over I was so
happy about turned on so I definitely
wanted to film a tutorial for you guys
I'm using a burnt orange shade on my
makeup shock t-33 brush to blend out and
deepen it
our part of the crease then with that
same exact brush I'm going to grab this
medium tone Brown up in here and then
deep in and out even more I'm gonna take
a quick break for my eye shadow for a
second and grab these steel at liquid
metals and this is in the shade of
kitten karma I'm just gonna use this to
carve up my entire eyelid by going
slightly right above the crease I'm just
gonna close my eyes then fan my eyes to
let this dry I am gonna be going back in
with more shadow and liquid liner in
just like it and I don't want this
glitter to transfer anywhere to do
anyway later today I'm gonna use my Wet
n Wild mega liner obviously in the shade
of black so basically for the winged
liner we're keeping the same technique
as normal just making it a whole lot
bigger and thicker now the liner is all
on Andrea I'm gonna go back in with my
233 brush one last time and actually dip
into it the black shade in the Jaclyn
hill palette and just darken out the
outer corners I'm blending this black
bolt into the crease add into the
glitter as well for the lower lash line
I'm going to start off by lining my
waterline using my NYX epic wonder
pencil
then i got my morphe r43 brush and dip
into this warm tone brown up in here and
start to defiant the lash line when I
get to this inner corner I'm actually
not gonna follow my natural eye shape
and I'm going to make this kind of more
a straight line to create the effect of
a new inner corner then are just gonna
take my morphe m4 33 brush and dip into
this a warm tone of orange here and just
blend that out last thing I'm gonna
actually use a custom pair of stock
lashes that I made earlier on and that
is the combination of the makeup Shack
matte eye lashes and my 301's
now normally I would use just a few
pairs of 3:01 stock which are literally
humongous as you can see they're like a
freakin butterfly wing so this is a more
toned down version of drag these are the
perfect combination of lashes if you
look closely as well my lash in the
inner corner is glued down to the inner
corner as it goes out to the outer lash
line and my lashes actually glued
nowhere near my lash line it's probably
actually a good half an inch away from
my outer corner and the end of the lash
is actually sitting in the middle of the
liner this looks pretty weird close-up
and you definitely don't have to do it
by any means but from far away gluing
the lashes up more just helps lift the
entire face and really gives you like a
snatched look that just looks so so good
like I said I'm just gonna take my
roller lash mascara and just dip in a
little bit and I'm going to connect my
regular lashes with these huge ass fake
ones
I'm sorry gonna show the ones in the
outer course are very very coated and
nice and black so they blend into the
liner and the lashes because if there's
any powder on them like you can see it
right now it's really gonna mess up the
illusion of having those lashes glue it
why higher up if you do decide to do
that for highlighter today of course
what else do we used in the anasazi
estelle Hollywood illuminator in my
morphe M 501 brush
ooh pheromone is shaking are you kidding
me we've been baking for like an hour
now so I'm gonna go ahead and wipe this
away oh and see how that just made that
cut so nice oh yes
using my morphe m4 3-1 i'm also going to
highlight Lino's you definitely be very
very careful in highlighting as well
because a nose contour highlight can
definitely make or break a drag look and
you definitely ought to be super snatch
is possible so I'm also gonna grab a
flat top brush and I'm going to
highlight my brow bone today now this is
your first time doing drag I definitely
would not recommend doing this because
highlighting obviously adds and this is
a texture to any area and if this is
your first time covering a brows unless
you are some miracle worker because Lord
knows that took me a whole lot of
practice they might look a little bit
texture for the first time it just takes
a whole lot of practice but once you get
really good at covering your brows and
they're nice and flat like this one is
even this one's a little bit wonky but
this one's nice and flat see how that
bra how they just look so good yes for
my lips today I'm gonna start off with
the Mac lip pencil in the shade of whirl
and just over line them a lot
so we definitely went way overboard with
the overlining but that is definitely
the point dragon makeup is super super
over accentuated and just big and
beautiful in general so I'm next in with
the Oprah South Paolo liquid lipstick
and just fill everything in for some
nice juicy for luxurious lips and last
but certainly not least I'm gonna set my
face in place using my Urban Decay all
nighter setting spray
alright guys so that has to look all
complete but we all know the drag is a
whole lot more than just makeup so I'm
gonna go ahead and change it up and
quickly put on the wig and I'll be right
back with the finished look alright guys
so this is the no makeup natural
everyday woman total complete just
kidding obviously this is a very very
full intense struggle and I absolutely
love how this turned out as you guys saw
I pretty much did use all of my everyday
makeup products that are using most of
my looks there's been a very different
and more intense way and this is the dry
look we came up with today if you guys
get into this video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
let's see if we can get this to 85,000
and definitely leave me a comment as
well and tell me what you think my drive
name should be because I don't have fun
yet if you haven't already make sure to
click that big red subscribe button down
below as well and the little bell icon
next to it so you're notified every time
that I upload I upload three times a
week on Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays
well usually say I'm gonna upload three
times a week is honestly turning more
into a maybe I'll upload three times a
week as long as they have three good
videos to post I'm someone who really
cares about quality over quantity which
is why I didn't post last Wednesday I
didn't have a good video I actually
filmed I stopped midway through because
I hated it but yeah I try to do three
times a week if I can great if I can't
just wait into the next one because I
promise it'll be a good video this
week's shout-out goes to its sister
Cheyenne thank you so much girl for
always falling and supporting you know I
love you so much and if you would like
to be at next week's sister shout out
make sure to always reach everybody Oh
links when they go live on Twitter all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next one now sashay away
[Music]