hi welcome back that's a woman is right
here it makes sense because I haven't
uploaded in 8 months but ok this is Liza
coach I'm so excited to be here you know
I'm really obsessed with you yes see in
my night I'm so excited look at me you
this literally looks like a fan in it
it'll look like well I am so excited
because kill you have no makeup on right
now I do know it doesn't you're so
beautiful thank you gonna literally so
long I think we're finally able to like
make a hot blast you've been gone for
quite a minute I know we've been texting
it for like months right now I know that
girl you're coming over yeah baby yeah
participation editing claps oh did you
question I'm on the other ones three
suman's all like 10% right there we do
it together
yeah first today's video I want to Glen
you up please do I've actually never
been like glammed up with like different
colors and I know you just really just
like a palette come on I wanna let me
show please don't look look at that
this was booty semester as a dash of
Harold talk talk it's just shorts on me
though I have no booty so I can't call
the boys okay so I did I just my brand
new palette it's beautiful
thank you for sending it to me yeah you
got it yet you have your girl
yeah somebody's fired well you'll get
[Music]
this just arrived at my house are you
kidding I'm selling the other one look
at it it's so pretty
I went else long I've never seen this in
person one no I've never actually seen
in person
you're correct I've never seen you in
person until your party which by the job
I have the same essence is brought ulema
Hey oh I love it ah
what about you you're like just as like
pretty and like have an essence in
person as he does
I won't thaw it's super extra beautiful
okay so couple mins and second gaps is
your sec so for today's it I thought
it'd be so much fun to just sit down
chat top lines I think we have us so
much that I want to talk about and just
clam up for a real one I have I think a
look in line that I want to do maybe
what are you feeling I want anything
like fun and colorful and just like have
fun with it okay but at least you're
here artists only show my face right now
yes transition
[Music]
I'm actually just like such a stand with
okay so I love to talk about the fact
that like we've never done anything no
yeah and we just met what just crazy cuz
we've been texting for the past like
literally two years yeah I want a little
bit first let me go boy because
literally like lines I have my number so
long ago and when I was like first
started on YouTube you would literally
text me like all the time you just watch
your video was so good yeah probably
putting about so I thought was always so
sweet Kazan yeah but you said exam blat
ever put me on blast night you just
complimented me well then you change
your no just texting and I was like I
changed my numbers when I want to stop
texted no but I was obsessed with
watching your videos and I think you're
such a sweet sweet soul sister what do I
not know you're you're such a talented
human being like well so much sweet
because of you were a contact crater
well I mean sorry but like you we're now
posting it's been nine months thank you
give me a break you just I tell ya I boy
fine I think your videos are like just
so good like I really always just watch
them like a lot of the jokes didn't how
much effort would we put into them and
like okay so really like comedy Oh like
I was literally nothing like dime and
second like watch a comedy movie I don't
know why just not saying that was ever
into yeah so I really honestly stray
away from a lot of companies they just
don't find a lot of things finally yeah
well just like weird to say but I would
like always been watching videos and
just like somebody said they're like cry
laughing you'd really want to get it on
thank you so like when Irene started
supporting me it just like met a lot so
I've always and like super excited and
to say hopefully your friendship you're
also like 12
so you
below standard for humor so my videos
did I are taking yeah
so you haven't gone for quite a while oh
nine months mr. Lubin nine Mikami baby
yeah she's good she's well huh
she's cute I don't know who the daddy is
that's okay probably um don't be a
beautiful baby hmm I see sweet sister
come here come back video so obviously
you were uploading very very
consistently and then had your YouTube
French ah which I absolutely love watch
every episode my god playing everything
sister Mary and then you kind of get
stopped for a damn while I did we've
talked about a little bit but I'm still
like wondering that the sisters coaching
huh yeah I do all right
are you good are you okay like what's
been going on like I'm good I'm good
okay so basically I stopped like making
videos because I was making my zaandam
and yeah and it was literally so to me
like I got to be a producer and I got to
be like partially a director and it got
to be a writer and I guess we got all
these amazing things and put on these
different hats and stuff and it was so
fun I just wanted to work with other
people I've been working in my living
room and just like screaming at myself
for past like two two-and-a-half three
years right and I just wanted to work
with others like I do everything by
myself I don't I don't know that cuz
don't really like open up about it but I
I do everything on my own so I write
everything and then I shoot everything
and I charge my own camera don't let
people behind the camera for me at all
hey you think you're so brave
yeah I'm so quite thank you I just
wanted to work with other people and you
know I got so excited by that when I
started working with them like I just I
fell in love with the whole process and
I realized that it could be not lonely
and yeah I got excited by that so then I
felt bad I she didn't have enough time
to create on my youtube channel and
beyond like
yeah baby one thing I sister sold my
soul what she has I am good buy my merch
no bikes I didn't have time for at all
and then I also just I felt really alone
doing it all to your own so like wanted
to have fun again hmm and find like why
passion again I take care of mental
health and I feel like you could start
to tell like in my videos that I just I
lost like my passion for it hmm I just
seemed less excited and so I didn't want
to force anything anymore but I think
it's really important to yeah you got a
you've got a prioritizing method I think
that's been a big thing on YouTube
especially this year which chains videos
everybody's like prioritizing you know
taking care of your anxiety or
depression or whatever
buddy has their demons right I
definitely gotta take a few breaks over
the course the why you two I know when
I'm glad you did is you are not like
yeah it's insane he was answering so
many emails right before this like we
started filming and I had to literally
pretend I was text to people saying I'm
right up to the James and even
pretending to do something I think I did
was approve my gynecology deployment I
love oh thank you I don't know I just
really like work a and I've always it's
a good thing we started over 16 you're
you're the age that I was when I started
really yeah I started at 19 when I
uploaded my first video how you doing oh
that's kind of fun frog chic you put in
fresh I'm feeling like really under
tained and a little expired so help me
out here
speaking of and I'm sure everybody's
wanting to know do you have plans on
coming back I do have plans on coming
back and like it was actually really
sweet because James texted me like Assam
do you need any help like let me know if
you're gonna have her bounce around
ideas and no one's ever asked me that it
was weirdly like sweet not like not like
I mean my friend group was like
obviously big Karen yeah I'm gonna like
help me too but I I don't know it was
just really sweet of you like you and
say like I want a bouncer own ideas cuz
I do everything by myself I was saying I
loved you well yeah I know what it feels
like to get in a creative ride I
definitely try really hard to post like
consistently good content my channel I
didn't do I need you really favor of
quality over quantity
yeah so like I know what it feels like
to get in a rut and not know what to
film literally like one of the most like
detrimental feelings ever yeah look it's
whole my thing
that I'm not gonna creative read that's
a scary part is that I'm not a creative
right I have all these scripts and have
all these videos actually filmed I'm
just like low in the confidence to post
it now
what's up yeah I know look at me I'm
beautiful but like it's so hard being
this cute okay but I like Emily tail but
genuinely I do like I really want to
post again it's just it's been a weird
year it's been a weird year but I'm
excited to like are you spending my
passion again okay good are you
scribbling because it's been so long
that like yeah and like I feel bad and I
feel guilty and I feel like I have I've
left somebody kind of like I've never
been an open really about like like I've
never had like even a video like this
where I'm just like sitting down and
talking well I know I missed you on
YouTube like the YouTube community is
just like can be a really dark place
sometimes and like no matter what your
videos were always a very very
consistently super positive I'm just
like funny keep going what else your
apartment is very key I wall sides we
experiment with the rainbow have you
seen this ballet no but what about you
what drives you what do you want out of
all of this what's the driving force
behind everything to look for it
hello it's good that for gonna contour
okay we're gonna blend that out really
good so from me I'm really driven by it
like challenging myself I just like
making people happy to like I grew up
getting bullied a lot by different kids
that I've always had a very very thick
skin so I've always been able to kind of
deal with it but I know so many kids
can't anything I just really like how to
my shame I'll be like a place where
people can go just to laugh and have a
good time and there may be a little bit
about me coming some of the videos and
just the kind of like I'm just like a
chill you know like
I feel like the world is like so dark
you've turned your insecurities into
your career literally I mean insecure
decent to make sure my scandals into my
career everything at this point but I
think that's why am i falling has been
able to grow because they got ya know
you're so honest yeah and I appreciate
that like so much you've no idea really
is I've always script in my videos like
they don't really like talk I genuinely
don't think like my answers to any like
questions about myself are actually
interesting so I script things like
really good sound like fun yeah fun
advice you know yeah I look good look at
me I really want to accentuate your
cheekbones because you have a super bomb
one's really bad cheekbones have to use
the right colors to look at you look you
look at that pimple you turn into a mold
it was actually dick doesn't disgust
thing I wish I would have landed in my
mouth James spitting on Liza for 10
minutes straight
I honestly I'm doing this collapse in
one of those there's one of them
something Oh Grayson perfect see her if
I could erect I've never had my makeup
done by anybody in the beauty community
which by the way you guys are amazing
your party was so fun oh do I get I'm
glad I wasn't excited that you showed up
this foundations matching pretty good so
far okay so since I do my own makeup
literally all the time and I don't
really do that many collabs either I
have never gotten the chance to do a
woman of color on my youtube channel
before like my first was a brown girl
yeah so I was really excited for today
but also really nervous too because the
undertones Furley people of color versus
white yeah it's very different
no it's very tough and like I've always
had like a purpley hue whenever someone
does my makeup like I'm sad sometimes no
shake no shake but I've always had like
a purple kind of like undertone but I
have a naturally red or yellow under
yeah yeah great guys today yes but yeah
no it's hard it's hard to like nail it
yeah I feel really good feel really
buttery right
that's good I'm really doing it like
people color skin is so much fun because
literally yeah so much contrast oh yeah
like it's so good oh I'm like one of
those transformation photos they're
gonna Twitter when you say like the
power of makeup oh don't trust girls and
makeup I am that so I'm going to now how
are you even set you in place James look
so good
really yeah why also I like love sucking
young people you ready no yeah but can I
show you the makeup look that I tried to
do for your party yeah okay so I went to
your Instagram I also watched like a
tutorial to like see how to do my base
yeah by the way look - nothing like this
but I dried I went to this photo and I
was like okay I want her exactly like
that no I did not I love you want a face
to it on this for me wait no there's no
face to none that I'm sure captain
natural just like you're instagramming
right please don't
yeah could we okay we can do that yeah
you can do that on me alternate host
idols good luck charlie James Charlie
what are you using is that better than
midnight well okay so a banana powder is
gonna be really good for like deeper
skin tone so I'm not really going to use
a more like yellow shade when it comes
to like a setting your under eyes are
going over top of it but I don't really
have any of my collection just because I
come over I get PR packages I usually
give away all of my deeper skin tone
complexion products to my assistant or
other makeup artists that work around me
in my industry because I'm not going to
get any you some of them and I'd rather
have them go to people that need them I
guess so much makeup on an everyday
basis and I'll never know yes I would so
much rather like a donate it the woman
shelters are give us to like morning
artists who I know need it or can't
afford it yes I'm not ever going to do
that there's no point in sitting in my
closet you're incredibly generous by the
way why nice to give back to just like
your audience all the time which is so
like makes me so happy enough
I'm so happy but you're also so
uplifting of other Creators and like
that's what I loved about your campaign
like those really fun oh thank you yeah
I like made me want to become a makeup
artist so that I can get attacking
mm-hmm
do you want kids absolutely not no no
really no I feel like just your like
makeup looks on your children would be
great channel baby makeup okay so one
thing that I talk about my channel a lot
of my subscribers like hear me talk
about at least I think so oh yeah the
one thing that I've discussed quite a
lot is like the difference between
traditional media celebrities and
YouTube additional media announcers and
huge disconnect in the space yeah
and I feel like you're one of the very
few craters who's done a really great
job at kind of bringing their brand to
more traditional media so when I was
like how do you feel about that like it
- you have like what are you planning
for your own future and not like whoa
see I don't plan that's my you know I
haven't uploaded but like I think you
don't like actually like know exactly
what I'm doing I'm kind of just like
always just kind of like gone with the
flow you're honest with like traditional
and digital I feel like there's been
like a nice like blurred line now like
Ray Smith is doing YouTube yeah that's
crazy yes that's so cool the fact that
like a traditional celebrity is like
starting to you like dabble in like
creating and on social media and they're
willing to allow their life to be put
out there more and
and be more vulnerable by sharing their
experience it's like even just like Jada
Smith I know this is doing like
read.table talks like that's so whole
it's so cool it's so open and so raw and
and it's so exciting to like see them to
do that like that's stepping into a
whole new world yeah you know I really
respect to those faces Josh Peck because
he yeah I was like reinvented himself
multiple time yes so would you say
they're like you're you definitely feel
like there's like a good shift happening
in the right direction
oh yeah percent and I think people are
taking like digital media I mean social
media like a lot more seriously in terms
of it being considered like a stepping
stone to like a career or be consider an
actress or being considered a host er
it's just exciting yeah those you
spinning my face no thank you ones that
if like really fellow really good job at
like starting that conversation I tried
I really wanted to blow that line
because like it's just another way for
people to come up in whatever community
they want to come up any beauty or that
be entertainment like it's just a way to
showcase your talent or whatever you
have to offer the world and I think it's
really cool that we have this
opportunity and we live in this
literally digital age that you carry you
can do that I want to add some blush for
block somebody's a little bit of code
James mixed with the table literally
yeah I'm gonna give you a quick little
spreads of settings my husband's a my
eyelids big there so I'm so excited for
this look tonight because you have lots
of room thank you I'm gonna use just a
little bit of these powders mixed
together so I'm just gonna place a
little bit of this on to the center
points on your face just to bake oh
that's a good brow I'm gonna clean about
Scott really he's in the Anasazi brow
definer and the shader dark brown if I
say brandy
people send stuff to me because I love
tart and I love benefit and honest
anaesthesia eyebrows do you like them
yes they're sisters no actually they're
twins I'm gonna start off by priming up
your lids using a Mac Paint Pot in the
shade of laying low me so I'm gonna
start my packing D a dark purple shade
in the palette which is called escape oh
wow yes brush it's gonna tuck this right
into here kind of roughly blend it out
what would you say it's been like earth
they were the one in your career okay oh
my god I literally I don't know I it's
been like a whirlwind and like a
blessing and like also like a blackout
I've I got everytime like really cool
things happen so I tell them it's like
it's like my brain every day was I'm I
think I don't know Mangala
I was like not the entire time I was so
cool it was amazing like it was so
exciting and so nerve-wracking at the
same time you can definitely tell I was
nervous I was shaking every summer my
sister shook it seemed a cure and I was
losing my mind with all the incredible
people like I was meeting and like those
are all my idols little people that I
just love and it wasn't even shown on
camera but I got to meet Mindy Kaling
and like oh my just like love and
respect you know in the entertainment
industry and like politically as women
of color to you like it's so exciting to
like meet your idols but uh thank you
for what they've done for you yes and
there were so many like comics and stuff
that I like I did say but obviously it's
an interview and they wanted like a
little side commentary you don't make
they cut out of video so you don't even
get to see the whole thing but like it
was such an honor
that was my like one of my teeth
Pacific now moments yeah yeah because I
was chewed out online for what I was
wearing and how I looked and like that
was a big like breaking point for me
because I have never like handled like a
scanner yeah before and so I was like it
was it was not it was tough I mean yeah
definitely it can be challenging to deal
with for me but I wish like I like
watched your video the other day of your
flashback Mary like for the first time
I'm really a fan I watched it and I was
like wow I wish I would have done
something like this like comedic Lee
address it and like make light of it
because it is it's like it's everything
has its time and always passing and you
know things come and go and just kind of
move on but it was like a step in
traditional media yeah so that was like
that was scary yeah I'm really glad I
did it I try to do things that scare me
I'm taking the yellow seed bead I'm
gonna grab that same pain and I'm
gonna use this to cut out your crease so
I can layer on the yellow I'm basically
gonna pack the same colors that I put on
why this crease into the lid now as well
just in the same ordering staying that
way the same brush is turning off with
love that to blend into the purple I'm
going in a little bit of you're kidding
that's okay your lower last night now
and it's gonna pop some purple so I'm
just packing socialblade right over top
everybody in the inner corner that
doesn't ever check central blade that is
a total lie no you know I've checked it
once before
uh-huh checked it once a day
no but I used to look at it when I
started like growing I guess but then I
just felt that it like wasn't good for
me to like look at that kind of stuff so
I just like stopped I could definitely
get toxic
yeah well I'm gonna brush off the excess
so we can like actually see what's going
on here I think that's the I shot a
portion all completely it should move on
to like lashes and things now yeah I'm
so excited
you want to glue off a real one I thank
you everyone I think that is one I all
complete oh my god it's beautiful it
looks really fun look at it look at it
with the merchandise how do you feel so
far I feel pretty wow this is really
really beautiful do you like this yeah I
love it okay
do you love it I do I love it okay well
that's what kind of a while so I feel
like we should take a little break and
go off camera do the other eye and come
back to finish us at the face very bad
clear about those are transition right
yes okay good I think this is so
dramatic for a you know one two three
open this is beautiful okay this is
gorgeous it's okay it's like not an Isis
isn't for me to just look at the screen
okay because sorry morphine Wow let's do
your highlight so I want to give you a
quick sister sprites are some more
settings right the only love doing this
just to get the skin nice and like
moisten hydrated before adding on a
highlight so I'm gonna got the shade a
little bit of a mix of it's so good and
maybe a little bit of wig from the
palette to that is good and freshen also
I'm gonna put a little bit on item of
your eyebrows well I love highlighting
up here I don't know why I just like it
makes the face look really nice and
hydrated do you see that yeah something
special oh oh oh that's a special suit
something special oh wow that's so
pretty
I'm gonna have a little bit more of the
Shadle literally at the blush eight that
we proud of before and use this to blend
together that highly and the kind of
blush and contour not going to
highlights in too timid
by leaving a little doll up right on
there okay so next we have our Liberty
doodahs let's do like I'm nude just
think I'd probably love you oh yeah we
tale oh that's a pretty color
mm-hmm there's my friend it's like the
color of my nipples oh it's gonna be a
good car yes have you seen that video
look at you've been run for so long but
is are two years old these Dan okay so
I'm gonna line your lips using the
colour-pop eyeless how to eat in the
planner this isn't the color of curvy
that's like we all found nude and it
works for literally all skin tones to it
just like the best part about it I think
that's good we're just going to color
them in with you was she this is Oprah
look at the stick in the shape and then
I'm gonna pop on some fancy gloss balm
in the shade I don't know she just made
one shade I think yeah but now there's
more are there since the original oh
yeah everybody lost sister stop I'm
going to give you a quick spreads my
money prepping set let's go James first
time to market order because this and
lots finally not least I'm gonna give
you a lesson of these anoxic spots in
the shade coal late
this is a
[Music]
beautiful I'm look at this do you like
it I love it look at that you're insane
thanks sister I am so excited that you
would join me say like literally I even
want to learn with you first solo now
like I said you've been such a huge role
model of mine literally since day one
and like you've been supporting me
behind the scenes for such a long time
now and it has always meant so much and
I'm so happy we finally got to be
together
maybe your first ever like close that
may go live hopefully you like and I
didn't scare you away from doing makeup
I forgot no you literally I conspired me
not to make mega blinds because I could
definitely cannot do this clearly well
that without to you know know what that
you seriously like inspire me like I
feel like driven to like post on my
channel expects nothing always keep the
expectation so I gonna clean them but
well like I like feel so inspired like
go home and like film you were such a
hard worker and this how it's amazing
amazing sisters we just restocked go get
yours now alright I think that is all I
have for this video that sister Liza I
really really hope you guys enjoyed it
if you did please don't forget to give a
big thumbs up down below and come show
your sister support and love it means so
so so much to me if you have not already
it don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below as well and
come join this test your head we're
almost 11 million sister strong oh my
god and also like that belacan so you
can get a notification every time I
upload a brand new video
yes and blow smoke up my ass you know
maybe in the comments thank you I think
I'll follow me all my makeup turn again
thought me up Instagram and Twitter
they're both so James Charles and my
snapchat for behind see if I stop and
show your Charles that lecture ask after
Charles you were really shown if you are
not ready go subscribe to at lines of
code she she is literally one of the
funniest age was all time she's but a
huge role model you know the huge
supporter behind the scenes and this
cloud meant so much to me I didn't want
to do that first so long and I'm so
grateful I'm finally able to sit down
today like I said I both said earlier
the palette is officially by the time
yes I don't really know if it's gonna
stay on so hopefully if you want to I
can get it now at more Fiat calm and use
coach James if they're ten percent off
your order
also available at all also retail at
locations also if you like what I set a
nice letter and her really if super cute
booty parts you can job all sisters
impale pieces have sisters - apparel
comm this video sisters how that goes to
it Shan and Nikki thank you guys so much
for watching and following and
supporting you guys mean if so so so
much me and if people hopefully through
the next videos sister shout out don't
forget to always reach me via videolink
so they go live on a Twitter already you
guys thank you so much watching today's
video don't forget that today is one of
the days of my December give us lays so
the same rules apply they'll be listed
in the description box down below if you
want to win a PR box he such as apparel
hoodie the flies the drink right and a
brand new to us and maintain a MacBook
Air
so fun so fresh can I answer no how do
you I said all the rules we don't do so
good luck thank you so much for watching
we love you and I will see you in at the
next one
[Applause]
[Music]