hi sisters team shelter and welcome back
to my youtube channel it is bright and
early rise and shine
I encourage the effort right now with
all my best friends we're about to head
to Las Vegas Nevada for a meet and greet
today at an Ulta beauty location along
with Murphy in honor of the mini palette
collection at lunch I thought it'd be so
much fun to bring you guys along with me
and all my best friends as well we only
have a little bit of time between the
plane taking off and the actual meeting
great so I got to get glam super super
fast so I thought I would take you guys
along with me for a fun little private
jet flight come on in
[Music]
all right you guys the office or plan
ahead of us I'm just gonna go ahead and
get right ready for some reason Cassie
and hey-zeus managed to convince me to
do my eyebrows before everything else
whatever let's scoot well because you
guys really never ever do dot but I
thought it'd be easier to do when the
plane was like on the ground and like
not moving so this waited like tatcha
water cream to give myself some moisture
it is so tiny called what do we know
because getting it very very cold but I
freakin I love this time of year so much
because it's winter vibes slowly grows
chilly girls for foundation I've been
mixing together to what different
foundations and that is first the dior
air plush open opinion are you want to
use a narrow Saul's on planes is it
going to explode oh we're good okay okay
I've been using this one and then
obviously the to pay for this one you
guys knows my all-time favorite just
kind of mixing it the two together for a
nice contraction on the hog like this
I'm just gonna blend this
oops I forgot to color cracks color
correcting over top of this I mean okay
covered a little bit of dragon candy
color corrector mama mama I thought I
would try to like use a few different
things than I receive because every time
I makeup I use the same [ __ ] which I'm
sure you guys are really bored of all
right you guys I'm not exactly sure when
this that it will be uploaded but I do
know that we are filming this one day
after I announced my show that I am
filming I'm leading from channel and I
just wanted to first of all say thank
you guys so much for all the love and
support about the show I was definitely
not prepared for the response that I got
I've only been working on this for a
really long time so in the world
no I guess just like seeing the whole
community like actually come together
like be excited or something was really
really exciting for me obviously a few
people even started uploading their
audition videos to YouTube which was a
crazy thing of all I thought it would
definitely changing a few days we will
to get ready but nope there's already
some lip videos they uploaded which just
is like literally the coolest thing ever
while this color does not match my neck
at all for once it looks to pay our moon
loves to say James your foundation is
way too yellow you
I always say no I actually really don't
think that looks like a [ __ ] beer
every single day and this is what
happens when I use a pink foundation
Tomic concealer and conceal this
lighting in this plane is done in oh my
god I don't know why I'm not getting
ready on it this was a good Wow okay I'm
just gonna contour the living hell out
my forehead because this whole dinner
situation oh no this is not good
what oh my god this is the fastest night
of my entire life
I wanted to do like a full eye shadow
luck what this way is going away faster
than anticipated which I have spooked
about okay so we're gonna try to do two
eye shadow look with the mini palette
super super fast in my reveal video for
the series I had on a neutral Brown like
just matte look which I have never done
before but I literally was obsessed at
how I looked and I felt so beautiful and
I actually got a lot of comments on it
to it which made me really happy so I
wanted to do like a very similar look
today so I'm gonna grab a little bit of
a team on an m4 33 brush I'm gonna put
this in my outer corner just like pocket
into here and there's gonna pull that
into the crease just like this then I'm
gonna go back into that same brush from
before and a little bit more of punch me
honestly I'm gonna get a little bit of
hoola bronzer as well so it like kind of
warms it up a little bit I was going to
buff out that
well I think this is the worst eye
makeup has ever lock I'm so scared
what's going on right now I'm gonna try
to cut my crease now a little bit of
concealer which I'm scared for because
we're on a moving vehicle a vehicle I'm
grabbing the shade of canvas on another
fluffy brush I'm just gonna use this to
holding up her landing I feel nauseous
I'm just gonna pack this Amy I think
we've ever found Oh God I'm just packing
a little bit of canvas and a little bit
of Flash stock onto my legs oh no what
we even do now that was so bad look at
my leg right now what do we even do yes
oh my god I don't even know what to do
[Music]
Oh where's the makeup way all right you
guys so we just landed here in Vegas my
makeup is clearly not yet complete this
is probably the worst idea that I've
ever filmed I did not plan accordingly
but I am gonna finish it and claim when
you guys here come along for the journey
we already started this might as well
finish with a bang so let's get off the
private jet and head into the next mode
of transportation to get some eating
green all right you guys we are back
after that lovely conundrum we just had
in the jet the private jet is fine we
cleaned it all up my pants however are
not and neither is my face at this and
I'm a little bit stiff but think I'll be
have like an hour before the meeting
actually starts we're on the way to get
a pink kitty drink kitty I'm gonna
finish this clamp gonna have a little
bit more punch me and I'm going to use
this to buff out the tear on the bottom
lash line gonna use a little bit more of
a punch me maybe a little bit of tea to
line this down here where are we
Starbucks oh thank god rise and shine
for mascara today I'm gonna use the Lily
lashes xxx mascara I literally love this
one it is crazy
long
long what it's like makes your losses
crazy long we're also currently setting
up this artwork the parking lot which is
what the vehicle is not moving which is
what I'm actually able to look
presentable right now for lashes I'm
just gonna wear the Miami Flair lashes
remember when I drop my entire thing a
setting powder all over my body
cute now I'm gonna take a quick spread
where's the city spray oh it fell that's
so funny let's go see if it's there
we're gonna go on a fun little adventure
cuz we lost our setting spray it was
right here
it'll be right here okay so now it's
time to add a little bit of highlighter
and for the highlighter today I'm for
once not going from using face from the
palette but instead I'm gonna be using a
a brand new thing that just launched
that is the Dhokla cosmetics highlight
our palette and this one is the flash
she just launched her holiday collection
and I'm honestly very excited for it if
we're being honest I feel like
highlighters are cliche at this point
like every single brand has a 50,000 of
them but watching Jacqueline's video I
was honestly very excited to try it a
lot of it especially the illuminating
powder which I put in my setting powder
today it that spilled a little plain so
didn't even get to really try it out but
I do have this palette it did not go
over the plain and that's it and see how
it is I'm just gonna grab actually I'll
use like her just a little brush gonna
grab a little bit of a gleam on this
brush wait let me feel oh I feel so
buttery Wow okay that's a beautiful
formula let's have a little bit of gleam
on this brush and hold it on the chin
that'll get on the brow bone area as
always oh wow there we go oh my gosh
that is the lighting that I needed oh
that looks gorgeous oh my god alright
you guys so pretty much all I have left
of this makeup look it's going through
the lips but since we woke up with the
ass crack of dawn I have not got a
chance to eat yet and we happen to be
right next door to my favorite
restaurant of literally all time not
sponsored but really wish it was the
pains literally Daenerys Keens to where
I live in California is over an hour
away and my friends and I drive all the
time because it is literally that good
so while we were here we're going to
indulge cuz some chicken tenders fries
and Texas toast or Vegas toast this is
now a law instead of just a cheque or
anything so let's come along for the day
all right
here's the goodies homework shaking
because I haven't eaten yet so whoop
aunt I'm just kidding but I did want to
tell you guys what I get it canes every
time I was to the three-finger combo
because you get three chicken tenders
and fries and a piece of Texas oats now
this cans host is literally it's like
sweet and salty at the same time that's
alone this alone makes it just also the
Box combo where you get four titers
instead of three and then you get
coleslaw but that's [ __ ] disgusting I
feel like close all your people and then
you do two pieces of toast instead of
[Music]
okay you guys so the look is all
complete I this is my lips off camera
after eating canes because it was quite
the situation and now that the look is
all gone gonna lock my face in place a
long time these know if it happens that
setting spray and then it's gonna use a
little bit of a mac fix+ and go bite to
really nice shining shimmering so we're
currently on the way to the actual mall
or the meet-and-greet so I have to get
changed because I'm doing a
meet-and-greet looking like this would
be a little bit crusted illegal I agree
definitely leaked also gonna do that
smooth talker under pressure sweaty
palms
[Music]
smoking outside trying to get your
attention
you make me know
[Applause]
all right you guys been officially back
on the private jet about to take off and
head back to LA we only have about an
hour flight ahead of it I'm gonna take
off my makeup and put on my sweatpants
and have a chill relaxing play back home
where I'm not rushing she went makeup
done I really hope that you guys enjoyed
this video today I know it was
definitely quite the mess I wanted this
to be a plane to check her any of me but
we've clearly got a lot of time and I
really hope you guys enjoyed just like
following me and my friends along on our
day off this meet and greet I had so
much fun meeting all the Vegas sisters
today everyone was literally it's so
nice and so kind I cried like three
different times leading a buncha
different people there was one little
boy in particular who was 11 years old
and he just heard a wearing makeup and
his mom was there too and they tweeted
me and it literally made me so emotional
and I just love you guys so so so much
and meeting music my favorite thing in
the entire world so thank you for
supporting me thank you to come join me
in Creed's if you guys like this vlog or
you want more of longstead videos in the
future
definitely give it a thumbs up and let
me know I would love to do more of these
I mean my life is definitely very very
crazy but kind of fun so if you guys
want more vlogs but it couldn't go now
anyway if you have not already make sure
to click that big red subscribe button
down below and come join this sisterhood
I'd love to have you in the family and
also click on that Ballack home so yeogi
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if they do follow me on Instagram
Twitter or tik-tok where your name is
just James Charles and my snapchat for
behind the teeth of Devastator Charles
the next rest after Charles this videos
sisters hanakos the sister Jenna thank
you so much love for always calling
supporting or I love you literally so so
so much and if you like through the next
videos that sister shadow don't forget
to always reach or the links and turn to
my YouTube notifications also I just
want to say a very very massive thank
you to everyone who submitted their
audition tapes for the Jane which house
casting call for my brand new reality
competition show launching in spring of
watching all the audition tapes this
past week has been so much fun there
were so many incredible entries but my
team and I are working super hard to
narrow down to the top six
you guys we contacted it very very soon
and for all of you other sisters out
there I hope that you guys are stated to
watch the competition show because that
is going to be absolutely incredible
alright you guys I think that is all I
have for today's video thank you so much
watching I love you and I'll see you
by
[Music]