it's real Platini compar me
let's fight I dare you I dare you to say
me hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I'm
guessing that you guys probably got the
notification for this video and thinking
what it's doing and trust me I'm sitting
here and I'm thinking the same exact
thing if you can suspend me for a while
on my social media platforms you've
heard me talk openly about the fact that
I do not drink alcohol is just not
really my thing on everyone to parties
in high school and I've just never
really felt the need to but that being
said today the day that I'm filming this
is May 23rd and if you know me it is my
birthday not only is my birthday okay
it's my 21st birthday which obviously is
the legal drinking age here and America
although I do not enjoy drinking I have
always said to myself that I want to try
it at least once a mile I just - you
don't feel the vibes see how it is
experience it see how I would act and
just see how it would feel overall and I
feel like if there's any time to try
drinking for the first time it's on my
21st birthday and I figured if I'm gonna
you know try out drinking I might as
well get some good content out of it
because this is probably not gonna
happen again
at a time soon and I want to spend it
with you guys doing a drunk makeup
tutorial I have my brand new bottle of
Don Julio 1942 and
[Music]
now I do want to make a very quick
disclaimer before we jump into this
video because I know my audience ranges
from very young kids all the way up to
parents in no way shape or form is this
video meant to promote alcoholism or
drinking if you guys know I have never
been an advocate for it I am the biggest
advocate and making smart choices if you
are one of my younger followers please
do not drink until you are of age and if
you're gonna drink please drink
responsibly and most importantly do not
get behind the wheel if you were
intoxicated and don't put anybody's
lives or your own in danger I can't do
this okay so I'm just gonna go through
my makeup routine that like normal but
I'm gonna be taking a shot by 1942 in
between each stat so I guess let's just
go ahead and get started and really hope
for the best with this I'm gonna start
off with my Tasha water cream what
private to give the face and nice oh wow
I'm doing this late at night and my
beard is already growing back early this
morning someone dare me that's been
right and I'm gonna grab some color
corrector and really put it on the beard
areas to call it a crook so lucky things
are getting this video I definitely do
not drink I have no interest in it but
I'm not one of those people that's like
I've never had alcohol because that's
literally just not true I step steps to
my dad's beer when I was younger kind of
taste of God not gonna lie in terms of
like feeling drunk I've literally never
felt anything okay so that is the
skincare and base all complete and to
our foundation okay the only things that
I'm like feeling so far is hot it's not
normal
all right foundations all dime and other
side here we go
it is okay it was myself buzz enough to
sleep like have sex in this room
oh definitely Trevor Linden it'll be too
much just release I'm definitely
starting to feel like I feel like a
little bit I feel fine I definitely feel
like I don't fill up like just put this
on in their house a lot ready it's
eyebrow time I'm gonna grab my morphe
one five eight brushes code age for 10%
off period trying to get that back mama
whoa I'm yeah oops
oh well I'm definitely feeling it now um
I feel like I feel heavy if I
turbodiesel psych
[Music]
like heavy oh but the best eyebrow it's
like heaven inches taller than one of my
eyes are starting to help trouble
focusing
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm gonna go ahead and give me my okay
browser tone that meets another shot
harsh shadows time okay so I'm gonna
grab my James rose I score a few pilot
usko change for 10% off and I'm gonna do
a cotton candy inspired love because of
my hoodie try yeah I'm gonna try first a
little grab brother on an M 4 5 6 bar so
I'm gonna put this in my outer-v not
gonna take them more than four three
three same thing now I'm gonna take it
down for 33 and dip into a little bit of
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
lower lashline to do I don't want to do
this anywhere I'm over at this looks
disgusting yeah now I'm gonna take a
fluffy brush this is the m4 for one four
more feet a little bit of funding okay
that's actually pretty
[Music]
okay I'm gonna take a little bit more of
this brother I blend it with my cut the
crazy solo family is a great life
then it gets three meals a day breakfast
lunch and dinner Finn has lots of
friends British Prince of the Honda and
koa and Kali and can you cope our army I
have a fat purse I'm gonna grab my am I
gonna dip in a little bit of literally
which is the metallic pink shade no I'm
not telling that eyeshadow yeah he's a
little bit of sister let's fight I dare
you I dare you to say me suck awesome
and what would you do then suck normally
I don't think it looks bad yeah looks
good right
I'm such a good makeup artists that's a
pretty cotton candy inside look you're
my best feel and okay that's okay just
go pee this glitter is try the house
down boots leather is mama I'm gonna do
my mascara oh I have to take a shot now
[Laughter]
[Music]
strawberry chopstick like strawberry
chapstick sharper chopstick hey just say
I know let me finish let me finish
oh where I got mascara on my face
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
how do you birthday edition from tik-tok
okay I'm gonna lips I should have never
gotten filler this this is so hard with
lip filler so big
[Music]
no we're good we go Jamie today
oh gosh
3 2 1 this is okay guys this is my
finished drunk makeup tutorial inspired
by the sister land cotton candy hoodie
that I'm wearing right now available at
sister's - apparel calm makes you guys
makes you guys chop now
just kidding I'm pretty sure it's sold
out so you can't even shop it if you
enjoyed it please don't forget to you
with a bigger thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not ready coming
this sisterhood
we're 19 billion sisters show I loved
and also click that doll icon sir
so you give notification every time I
upload a brand new video on Instagram
Twitter Facebook all just James Charles
my soundtrack for behind the scenes I
stopped in state of Charleston extra s
after Charles if you'd like to fix me
I'm a personal phone number I know Emily
hold up my telephone but Louis took my
phone so I don't send any boys and he's
stupid text messages my phone number is
three one oh nine oh five eight seven
four six this video sister said it goes
to James Charles because my birthday's
today thank you so much for always
falling in support I love you so so so
much but if you wanna be the next video
sister channel don't forget to always
reach emoting raging avenue only go live
on twitter and make sure you try my
youtube post notifications thank you so
much for watching this drug maker
tutorial I promise this is never gonna
happen again but I love you and I will
see you in the next one bye
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah can you take it off okay we
have some unfortunate news well they're
ugly take one off you think you're gonna
sweat oh yeah I mean you should take to
add those other unit huh you just popped
mommy
[Music]