mr. James Turrell let's hear it come
back to my house you got for today's
brand-new video we're going to do it a
sister sanctuary to us but you think
about two years ago now I officially
moved to Los Angeles to pursue my really
close friends were all in Orange County
and Whittier so it was kind of right
smack dab in the middle no job town was
a really really good and fun impressed
for about five days and after that if
then we want to dot every single day how
do you guys to see that the constant
mental breakdowns over the sirens over
the lemon ways it over the sky people
are going out late at night and also the
imminent issues have really affected
them on YouTube have a growth this past
year it's been a initiate simply so
regardless the Asian is now over cuz
I've been saving quality have a big
sister sponsorships and we were
obviously the movie bless us right now I
just kissed my downtown America goodbye
sister sayonara never ever but it was
empty through so many of them every sip
each other but not we are here we're
very much I mean right now in the movers
secondly remember that Ana put it all
before we do that in circles and getting
it set up I was just doing a little bit
of an empty house work for you guys
I thought they did plan on doing a
finished house crawler and kind of a
little bit of a decorating series as
well because you guys know I really
really love interior design so I thought
it would be actually really cool to do
an empty house write a finished house
tomorrow so you guys can really see the
before the planning process and the dog
have a little HGTV they are shaking so
hard and I was gonna make the black and
white and answer em selfies personal
problems
the reconnaissance do you do before and
there's a beautiful quiet please I think
this would be a little chill and I
really would put a couch in this general
vicinity somewhere and there's gonna be
a grand you know right there in this
corner but my god you know obviously
music plays a huge role in my life and I
do play the keyboard of my ear but I've
been wanting a grand piano since I was a
little boy we could never afford ads
have been there growing up and Aaron
Burr saving up for a little keyboard it
was on for months as a child so my wife
a grand piano has been a huge role but I
don't know
it's gonna be right here it's in the
linear pathway and then I can play over
the speakers in the ceiling there are
all hardwired so I can listen to my box
anywhere in the house all day long
really what I wanted to do individual
house to begin with I think just really
cool to kind of bring a little nostalgic
element from the Delta apartment back
here to this house and beautiful I think
a huge table for amenities you're
probably just gonna protect it right
here I honestly don't worry anticipate
you think this room very often is
probably gonna be one of those rooms
that are very much first show all the
way eating will probably be happening
and my bed or on the couch in the living
room which you guys will see in a second
or at the kitchen counter because it's a
huge movie like tonight over here and
this is a big open foyer area and family
and everything right now I'm gonna be
helping contribute to do job great but
there's going to be a car park there
eventually
you guys know obviously I'm your uber
everywhere and I think it's time for me
to get a card now that I have a house I
guess it's a lot but I actually do have
my license I can drive I'm just really
not good at it so if you find out about
i-19 you know makeup artist crushin
there's three try again sometime soon in
the news this this absolutely my office
for myself my team at worst or did you
tell me just myself I do now have an
amazing group of people that work with
me every single day to make this full of
video consoles possible and make sure
they have a really comfortable and
beautiful and bright thanks to work
that's why they can be happening right
in here so the way the office we have
this beautiful
[Music]
and here it's too cute little room for
many guests that are over I love the
same things too like this is so cool
it's like a fire hose love that some
water it's so vintage and then in here
this is supposed to be the office space
it's just literally a white box but if I
have a missus way too small if I were to
be working here I would probably get
really stressed and like cram and
washable recognize it a little bit so
that we can hear my house positive
potential of like a recording studio and
my start shaking use it more seriously
but really fun but now for a house is
really Deku sticks so coming out of the
it sisters to do times potential
exercise rooms large white box that I
can lock it in and he's being annoying
whenever that cooking made me back to
the foyer this is going to be a wall of
the entire house and this is obviously a
wine cellar
while James why does your wine cellar at
your favorite wall at the entire house
let me tell you why I'm here all the
internals because guess what's not going
to be there why because it's very just
then was insane well that's very much
material we know these two kinda way
exploding we're talk which are actually
the only two lights I'm going to be
keeping in this house I really love this
I think they are so beautiful and kind
of odd to have like the rustic farmhouse
back which is definitely what I want to
go for I'm gonna have a coffee machine
probably in there
when I'm getting too lazy to cook those
days and that huge beautiful
refrigerator which I will probably keep
very little if there is that night but
one of the main issues with is the
projectors times day based light meaning
I can never watch anything during the
day which is usually pretty good for it
I was able to really keep some
self-control and to get my work done but
there are definitely days where that's
built watching out like something a huge
TV right smack dab in the middle right
here we talked about some of the core
pieces and huge l-shaped sectional right
friendly to my moving up process and
I'll show you guys the little backyard
moment how these dogs are also here -
they will not be staying unfortunately
but me and definitely do plan on
adopting a puppy as soon as we get in
and get some I am so beyond excited
so students about that side there is a a
huge TV and fireplace which i think is
actually so so so cool I want to put a
cute little seating area here so I mean
all my friends kids show up during it
the cool summer nights and then we have
these beautiful backyard so the grass
area is definitely not as big as I would
want to be I grew up in upstate New York
and I'm used to having a ton of property
I think the house that I grew up in was
literally five acres which is any
nature-lovers tree which may come as a
little bit of a surprise to you guys
because I'm very much an inside home
Internet kid but I definitely do love
nature and the rocks and so my next
house that I move into will have a huge
backyard I'm promising myself that right
now but I think I'm just gonna put a
hammock over here maybe some lawn chairs
next to of the pool and probably gonna
fix this dead of grass patch because
it's not looking the best
caroli is the careers of everybody in
the makeup industry yes what we have you
have this little concrete and girl area
similar to the kitchen I'm probably not
gonna get a whole lot of use out of this
but I do have a lot of best friends and
a lot of their husbands love to cook and
Grill my best friend Laura her husband
Victor loves girliest will definitely be
cooking lots of good and fresh big beefy
needs right here we do have a huge
beautiful swimming pools I know beyond
excited about a little house we'll take
a video I am so excited to have a
swimming pool to be able to jump in I'm
really hot Dave it gets so hot outside
I'm literally sweating for me
literally like 30 seconds that has taken
us to film this clip now so that's good
and we do have a cute little photo as
well so we can tell accident on the
colder in the winter so this must
actually 5 bedrooms which is so much my
last the purple was technically three
but one of those bedrooms was I'm
walk-in closet and the other one with my
filming space and the lock was button so
even though I had a three bedroom it was
only really what was being used and
didn't always that asleep on the county
news over it so it all my friends when
they have sleepovers which was really
only not fun I'm really excited have a
lot of space everyone to sleep and hang
out I always have friends over no matter
one day and they're very very close to a
lot of the people in my leg I like to
just make them feel at home and make
them feel confident self this house is
gonna be crazy to you but it is a
laundry room and do you know why I'm
excited about this because I have a
washer and dryer and I'm going to be
able to do my own laundry why are you
excited about that James your house can
but let me tell you if you get to see in
a few episodes of brother and sister
meeting to talk about how the lottery my
own
it was scary it was in the basement it
was dark all the machines were broken
almost every single time I literally
left loads of laundry in there and came
down like five minutes before my local
machine was going to be done I don't
have people taking my clothes out of the
machine because they wanted to cut
there's any staff like that it's scary
so I've been working as long as I was
really generous to make sure my clothes
were clean and not drugs but I'm so
excited to be able to actually get my
laundry done myself make sure it's done
right to do it safely
it sounds so stupid but I'm just really
excited about so one over this table you
have this big storage unit that you're
covering every single day second is not
the actual Vegas - I hope that you'll
even focus on production rather than
make up storage because you guys know I
don't only switch up my products that
often so I can actually use this entire
storage unit to store access paper and
then walking up from here we have a
bedroom number two
in truth and the poor cousin it's really
beautiful and bright and you know really
like this space there's also a pretty
thing I can all fit in here of course is
revealed as well which I'm excited for
obviously you know really really loves
fashion luck and he wants to be a
regular blogger or 2,000 videos on
YouTube one day if he ever actually
decides to post couldn't tell you I'm
gonna be a song and when he comes here I
was hip-hop but they'll be able to use
this woful supposed to distill all his
pieces in here to beautiful for his
videos obviously like make sure you guys
have entered the house or maybe is done
move on to the next row so I'm walking
up right out over here we have a bedroom
number three
this one is Ted or that guest room just
just a super simple room so as of right
now it's probably only going to be the
median sister Keehan living and this
comes together but we are they gonna dog
and you guys heard me say that my team
was here almost every single day working
was really fun I do have actually gonna
have a third roommate kinda trying to
convince and that's been true to move in
with us no but sometimes the English
inaudible you comment on us because any
one day in this room or the other would
be
Giroux perfectly fine guestroom throw my
family or my best friends coming over so
we write a lot with this program you
have such a numbers door and this is my
favorite bedroom that is not the master
of the entire house
there's so great and it is so big the
ceilings are actually involved in as
opposed to flat which really just makes
the space feel like a million times
larger and it just feels very very old
Beth and it just is really good advise
for production videos and it can be
really easy to get into a bit of a
creative rut so for me can you get a
space that makes me feel happy and the
life of a week is super super important
that's our space outside because the
closet isn't actually the big s but
maybe issue later on but like I say I do
want to make sure to go to my connection
and just don't really like what I'm
saying let's make a huge donation of
open and bread and makeup products that
a bumpy our have just never actually
used to a local organ something wasn't
that so so so much to me they were all
so grateful and so thankful and it's
really laughing because I just do guys
like that they pretend to be all the
time and although I am so thankful for
it there is just a nobody that I'd ever
be able to try all that much makeup so
we just want to have art to be able to
give that stuff away to people who are
definitely going to get an amazing do
some of that and we so so so appreciate
about that so that's actually the intera
of you need space I'm suppose to all
diplomatic and production stuff in here
at very soon which I'm so excited for
I'm actually working through to the
1700s - definitely
[Music]
we do have the best I'm so excited about
the space oh my heart is literally so
like so so is there anything walking
there are two huge
but since it's just me it's going to be
the sister and sisters closet which I
obviously love just like I make up my
cash they went through had donated
probably like 50 percent of the items
that I never wear any beautiful
[Music]
[Applause]
well this is a city also saw right
your final render stuff you'll becomes a
[Music]
beautiful hello first of all no bloom on
us as soon as you walk in there's a
countertop and things I'm just any fun
top there's a large countertop and if
you watch me while I was that are
brother and sister with me and you would
know that I have a major issue was my
sister's know I've never seen in my
entire life - now I give really good and
beautiful concert in this amazing of
white marble shovel like hello how
gorgeous is that
and we have a huge beautiful white
soaker tub here as well actually I'm not
taking it off in public
four or five years oh I shall create an
experiment I'm linking words that you
hear a popping in and out bump or two it
was relaxing watching the sunset and
just listening it's music in the speaker
system and just do my best
and they actually completes this empty
house tour oh my god you guys are saying
do not take too long Oh a lot of people
here to help me to start this moving
process so I'm gonna end up this video
pretty quickly publicly said thank you
guys so much for watching this video
today I would make to your kid that now
owns a house in Los Angeles California
for YouTube I never in a million years
of imagine that this is my life but it
is now and it's all because of you guys
and I will never know something so
grateful that you guys actually take you
late for the better names folks in for
this new journey that this house is
going to play all right you guys there's
a huge like I said there's a whole lot
of furniture a whole lot of makeup and a
whole lot of my favorite people that we
have so it works me so I gotta do
process but they keep watching I love
you
[Music]