hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I'm
not realizing that I'm starting this
intro off with my eyebrows a hidden
third down I probably look crazy but
that should be an indication that the
today's video is going to be a drive a
transformation last night I was watching
my all time favorite show RuPaul's Drag
Race
and the Queen's actually had such a cool
challenge and that was to make over five
different youtube stars first of all
very rude that I was not invited
sister rue hit me up girl I would have
been an amazing sister transformation
but regardless it just really got me in
the mood and it's been a few months
since I've done drugs and it's been a
lot of months or many months since I've
actually filled the Drock tutorial I've
tried so many new techniques I've been
watching so many different videos and
hopefully I picked up on some brand new
things so I just feeling my woman
fantasies today and I want to do a drive
a transformation started off my eyebrows
are clearly already glued down which is
a very very annoying and long but vital
process to any good drag makeup tutorial
I don't think I would look very womanly
with the block bushy eyebrows that I
have right now so we got to cover up and
draw a new one on it which will be
coming in a short minute but I'm gonna
start off by priming and moisturize my
face that I using the touch-ups self-cam
bests just gonna put a light layer of
this over my t-zone especially in my
moustache and beard region just to kind
of correct any texture before I go into
any foundation and really kind of clean
up the canvas for all the makeup they're
about to put on we have one last step
which is going to be a color cocktail
I'm gonna take the LA girl Pro concealer
and this is in the shade of orange and
I'm gonna put this over oh God
cut I put this over all my oh hello all
my beard and moustache areas I literally
am a man and I shave it every morning
but I still get 5 o'clock shadow like
three hours later I'm very tempted in
convinced that I want to get laser
surgery so please let us know your
experience with that if it's fun if it's
painful because I literally do not know
but I'm really tempted to get all this
gone and I'm also gonna put a little bit
of this over my eyebrows as well because
they're a little dark and by a little
bit I mean cover them up completely I'm
next good to take any dent a buffing
brush and lightly tap out this concealer
just so it's kind of evenly distributed
and blend it all around because our next
up is going to be it to set it with
powder but if we put powder right on top
of it it's gonna be a little bit clumpy
and grow so this is just a quick little
step in between alright guys this is the
completed look I really hope you guys
enjoyed and I will see you in the next
line I'm gonna take a powder puff in a
little bit of translucent powder and
just packet or right over top of that
formed just to set it in place until we
put the foundation on next it doesn't
all get mixed together because although
we definitely want a bronzed look we
don't want a Donald Trump glam today
that's for sure
I'm also gonna pack this powder into the
brows as well I have gotten pretty good
at brow cover at this point and I've
also shown it in a few other videos
beforehand so make sure to click right
up here if you needed to trial on that I
know I started off this video with it
but it's a very long process and I did
not want to waste 20 minutes of your
time teaching you how to glue down your
eyebrows today pressing in this powder
really hard after all the layers of glue
will really help eliminate some of that
texture and the powder will kind of fill
everything in to create a very blank and
a flat base for everything to go over
top of this is scary for the foundation
today I'm going to go into the Kryolan
TV paint stick and this is in the shade
and B if you guys have never heard of
these foundation sticks before they are
intense arla straightest police they're
literally full coverage enough to cover
my scandalous so we definitely love this
and we have a whole lot that we need to
cover today so I'm going to just go into
this all over my face starting off with
the brows and once again are really
pushing it in their gouge make sure
everything is all covered and then it's
going in with that everywhere else and
there's gonna take a damp Beauty Blender
this one is a very very old one it you
definitely do not want to use a new one
that is for sure because this is full
coverage and I can guarantee you you're
gonna have to throw this out after this
video trust me then I'm gonna grab the
Krylon T paint stick in the shade at
zerozero this one is already just pure
white and I'm gonna use this to
highlight my face starting off right in
the center in between the brows just
like that that I'm going to do one line
oops the nose huh we'll get her there
I'm just gonna put this in the same
place that I always put my concealer
except this is just white as opposed to
normal shades and then once again just
gonna bond that in with a Beauty Blender
if you're watching this video I feel
like it's probably safe to assume that
at least most of you guys have seen the
show or at least heard of the show
RuPaul's Drag Race
literally when my favorite shows in the
entire world and if you don't know what
it is and is a drag queen TV competition
show hosted by the legendary RuPaul and
this season has been so beyond
entertaining and crazy whereas his
favorite slava discussion down the
comments below aquaria literally love
her the most I've been following her
since she had like 30,000 followers on
Instagram and now she's on season 10
which is so crazy she actually do my
makeup two years ago when I was in New
York for I think generation beauty which
is a baby Beauty convention and it was
so cool meeting her and just seeing her
progression I literally love her makeup
so today's look is deathly gonna be
heavily influenced by aquaria I also
love Eureka I'd not heard personally a
few times and she is literally one of
the sweetest people ever in the entire
oath and I think she deserves every
single ounce of her success she is so
funny and we definitely need a bigger a
winner I think it's time so my fingers
are crossed for her definitely the
season I also live for when I exchange
this entire season all from the sponges
to British accent oh just loved it the
most we stay on for this tutorial I
wanted to sing a little bit different I
have actually never done ever but also
never in a job tutorial and I want to do
my eyebrows all my face is still wet and
not powdered I see a lot of different
Queens doing this a lot of we start off
with their eyebrows first can't do that
still a little bit too spooked and
clearly I have to cover mine but I wanna
try to go into the cream product I'm
going to use the anasazi a dip brow and
I'm just gonna sketch the man and then
set powder over top hopefully we're
gonna have to say my hand is shaking
hello
I hate drawing and eyebrows
I'm not like that eyebrow dry eyebrows
as a directory is so hard like oh this
is the research Alan Turing oh no it's
taking out my foundation underneath my
eyebrow what the heck
yes okay this is kind of a wash roughly
I literally don't understand how drag
queens cover their eyebrows and then can
draw on new eyebrows and have it look
like smooth and not crusted I am pretty
good at broad cover at this point but no
matter what like something always still
looks so wrong when I clean that up that
could be usable oh that's an ugly
eyebrow how do people do this
that is way too large like why is that
all the way up there it's like all the
way on my forehead I hate this what's
going on
okay these literally look the worst but
you know what that's we have concealer
for and thank God that I do not set
these in place because now I'm gonna
grab some shape tape and a mac 242 brush
a lot of shaved tape but I'm gonna go
and clean up these brows
[Music]
Oh see the hustle whoa man that's a
woman mm-hmm okay we love her concealer
whoo no this one on the other hand oh
she's the struggle sister it's always
the eyebrows that get me good every time
I'll be good again
all right so literally 45 minutes later
and no I'm not kidding
wish I was but hope brows are now on and
even so what I'm gonna do is just go in
quickly and blend out any creases that I
gathered underneath my eyes while crying
over my brows looking horrible then it's
gonna take a dent powder puffs in some
Kody or some powder whoo and I'm gonna
set my entire face including my brows
with this let's see if this works okay
so far so good
this took 60,000 euros I think I
actually like this technique of doing my
brows while the creams are still wet a
lot more than drawing them on later on
thanks sister Asha I'll definitely be
doing this okay so now that the face is
all set and locked right in place we
have to a contour and contour is a very
very vital step to drag makeup I mean
that you have to go from a brother to
his sister so we definitely do add a lot
more dimension and back to the face so
I'm gonna grab my morphe m55 4 brush and
the anasazi a contour kit and dip into
at the lightest shade right up in here
and just add this right over the same
places that I put the white highlight
earlier gonna pop this right oh okay I'm
actually gonna take the jeffree star
cosmetics blood shook her eye shut up
hello and dip into the shade glucose
which is literally just a white
eyeshadow with the same exact brush but
I know that this white is very very
pigmented so I'm gonna use a little bit
of it to highlight the center of my face
I was gonna place the shade right
underneath my eyes right up against my
nose contour to brighten up the center
oh why should he use the k'kaw powder
I'm gonna grab the k'kaw Beauty
brightening powder and the shade number
1 and the same exact brush to use that
to highlight my face instead and then
we're gonna go back into the Augusta's
their contour kit and I'm going to use
my morphe M 405 and use this to chisel
on my face I'm sorting right at the top
of my ear right in my sideburn region
and doing a circular motions going right
down and I'm kind of keeping this
contour a little bit higher than I would
normally go for more of a feminine
lifted at cheekbone type look
yeah just like that pretty we love
same thing on the other side definitely
need to really chisel out my five head
as well
and when contouring I'm kind of blending
in it like a circular motion if that
makes sense we're like the lightest
point being right here and then kind of
fading out circular ombre sunset
situation into a very very dark hairline
of course you have to also snap to the
no so I'm just going to grab my benefit
hoola bronzer and dejay tear eighty one
eighty from luck see beauty dual ended
nose contouring brush good lord you guys
know I live for a good snatched nose and
drag queens honestly we're definitely a
huge inspiration for me when it came to
learning how to in nose contour and
highlight my nose to really look so
we're gonna make it look even more
pinched than usual and once that
contours on then I'm gonna grab that
k'kaw brightening powder and the Beauty
Blender once again and I'm actually
gonna press this right into at this side
of the nose contour to really snatch it
right up and to give that perfect
illusion mm-hmm look at her she's sister
snatched to really finish off and
brighten that nose I'm gonna take the
NYX jumbo eye pencil in the shade milk
this is the pure white one I am scared
to do this but once again I've seen a
lot of different Queens do this so
hopefully this will work first mr.
genius and I'm gonna put a little dollop
right on the tip
[Music]
you're kidding
hello either worked and lasted finally
not least for the bass I'm just gonna go
to my Mac peaches blast you guys all
this is my all-time favorite on my
morphe e for brush and give myself an
actual for once really decent coverage a
blush you guys know I don't usually like
a lot of blush in my looks but when it
comes to drive we do have to make the
highlights and the contours a lot more
intense so blushes are really nice job
of marrying everything together for a
more soft but still intense look so
finally the base is done we get to move
on to the eyes thank the Lord but I do
want to do one last thing before we do
and that is a bake our face to really
intensify the highlights even more so
I'm gonna grab a little bit more of the
Cody Harrison powder in my damp Beauty
sponge Center it's going to bake okay so
let's move right ahead with the eyes at
the first palette I want to go in with
the city is the Jeffrey's top Balai de
sugar eyeshadow palette and I'm gonna
grab the shade glucose first which is
this white shade right up here and use
this to highlight the brow bone this is
by far one of the most pigmented
eyeshadows I have ever used and I
definitely want to give the brown one a
good highlight to kind of lift
everything up next I'm gonna grab a big
fluffy brush this is the morphe m4 for
one use Cody's for ten percent off and
dip into the shade out and just use this
as a light transition shade I'm gonna
pop this color right above the crease
and just blend this up right into the
white just to give a nice wash of color
and to get the eye makeup started I'm
next gonna switch over to the morphe 39
a palette this is the palette that I
actually modeled for for the morphe
Holiday Collection unfortunately it is
now sold out and gone for good but
basically I'm just gonna be using cool
toned brown shadows today so use any
palette that has similar shades using a
fluffy crease brush I'm gonna dip into
this shade right over here and I can use
just to deepen up the crease a little
bit I'm just using little circular
motions to really build up a color once
again staying right above that natural
crease line because we're gonna make our
eyes look way bigger then going a
smaller pointed fluffy brush this is the
morphe M 506 I'll get a dip into this
dark brown shade right up in here and
use that to really deepen elephant it's
going back into my big fluffy brush I'm
going to blend that out a little bit and
make sure that doesn't look too harsh
now that we have our crease shadow all
laid out and nice and blends and I'm
gonna take a white concealer this is the
LA girl Pro concealer in the shade white
obviously hello and a mac 242 brush and
just cut out
crease perfect Wow cool once again good
a dip back into that Murphy M 2 2 4 and
the Caloocan shade from the blood sugar
pellet and then set that white in place
I do add a little bit of sparkle and
glow to the lid so I'm gonna grab this
Stila liquid metals in the shade of
Perlina and put this over the white area
that I just set in place then before
that sets in place I'm gonna pack on the
mixed glitter in the shade mg/l io5 and
then to be really active before we go
ahead and add the winged liner I want to
do one last step and that is gonna be to
glue on some individual sourav ski
crystals
I learned this trick from and Naomi
smalls and always look so stunning from
far away the crystals just sparkles so
beautifully on the lid so I'm gonna pop
a few on it just using lash glue and
tweezers so next up in the eyes is going
to be the way NAT / like outer shadow
moment and I try to do this technique in
my Coachella festival makeup store but
it did not work at all so we're gonna
try again today fingers crossed
I know aquaria does this all the time in
her looks and it always looks the best
so I need to have faith myself but I'm
gonna take just a light piece of
cardboard i hey I'm miss Laura Lee this
is from her PR package and just a fluffy
brush and dip into a block I shadow
wish me luck tap off the excess and I'm
gonna place this card right here on my
face right up against my on I'm gonna
press it very firmly into my skin and
then I'm just gonna go right in and
start blending the block right up
against our blending on at the edge
blending in the crease just making sure
it looks like nice and not super super
harsh then before I remove that I'm
gonna take a blending brush from before
they had the brown on it and go over
this edge right here and then when I
remove that yeah work this time we have
a nice and defined black line oh thank
god okay great thanks Laura Lee and I'm
gonna continue this block right down
into the corner of my eye to prepare to
bring it into the lower lash line in a
second
once a black shadows on that I'm just
gonna go to the black liquid liner and
just line right up against that
waterline just when we put on lashes
there's no like weird shadow moments so
that is the top lid all complete huh a
lot goes into drag makeup as you can see
but let's go to move on to the bottom
lower lash line which will be a whole
lot easier
think on I'm first gonna shout wrecking
that NYX jumbo eye pencil in milk once
again and lining my lower lash line then
when they get to the inner corner
instead of following my natural eye
shape I'm kind of extending that white
down a little bit to kind of follow
straight forward and out once again I'm
gonna set that white in place using the
glucose single shadow from the blood
sugar palette next to begin the shadow
portion I'm just gonna dip into the same
a block that I used for the upper lash
line top off the access and be super
careful I'm going to blend this right
along the lower lash line connecting the
wing right up in the outer corner and
then using a small fluffy crease brush
is the morphine I'm a 4-3-3 I'm gonna
dip into that same cool tone a brown
transition shade from before and just
blend right underneath the crease and
into the inner corner and last but
finally not least to complete the eyes
today I thank the Lord in heaven above
is going to be the lashes and for
today's look we have BAM the three oh
ones if you are a true drag fan you know
that these are like the best of the best
they are intense but they look so
stunning and when you have this much eye
makeup on you have to match it with a
good and fresh lash so all I did was
stock any regular pair of Lillie lashes
in the style I believe Miami you guys
all those my all-time faves and I use
those because they held a little bit of
a lift to them and just glued a 301
right over top and I'm gonna pop that on
my lash line for a very very 3d and
lifted and beautiful stunning look I
usually like to apply my lashes kind of
in the middle but for these I'm actually
gonna push on the inner corner of the
lash first being that that is by far the
most important part to this look and I'm
gonna take the outer corner of the Lodge
and lift it out to make sure that it's
on the regular lashes and they're gonna
place it down but what I actually put
this lash there I'm not gonna put the
lash on my lash line I'm actually gonna
put it a little bit above my natural
lash line which is going to lift my
entire eye upwards obviously this is
totally optional not gonna lie it does
feel a little bit weird to have your
lash glue
of your eyelid but it really does help
and give the face a little bit of a
lifted look and then also since the area
is fully covered in eyeliner you can't
even tell and it's a full-on illusion
and finally just gonna pop on a little
bit of my favorite mascara to blend
together my fake lashes with their
really large big quads helpful hand too
if you're like me and you have a pretty
long bottom lashes and you decide to do
this like white in a corner moment like
I have right here when you're applying
your mascara especially to the lashes in
the bottom corner be really careful and
pay attention to where you're actually
holding the wand because you should try
to avoid putting mascara right at the
root on the inner corner and only get
the mascara on the kind of second half
of the lash if that makes sense and keep
that first half of the lash white from
the eye liner because then it keeps that
illusion going of the white inner corner
with the black mascara underneath
because if you get black mascara all the
way up to the root in this inner corner
right here it's gonna try to get away
from that illusion I just like I have on
this lash but you get what I mean
hopefully all three sisters and finally
that is what I all complete I am
literally loving how this is hurting Cal
so far I'm gonna go ahead and do the
other one off camera quickly and I'll be
right back to finish off with Rosenblum
okay so those are both eyes all complete
and I was a little bit worried about
this look at first not gonna lie I've
never really confident in my full job
looks until they come together but now
oh my god I am really loving this I
really I just wrapped Aquarius face
right over and just popped it right on
wide and I am loving I feel beautiful
so let's go ahead and move on our next
was going to be the glow I'm bursting my
skin a good spread to the max like plus
being that I've literally put on 64
million pounds of makeup and powder and
my skin's feelings love it dry but
highlighter today I'm going to dip into
my fave dattara top yot pressed pigment
and I'm gonna pop that right on it the
high points of my face ready for this oh
oh yeah there she is girl that of course
is having a pencil brushes in the m-43
one I'm just gonna pop that right over
the sister Asha notched schnoz
[Music]
for the lips today I definitely feel
like I go with the nude when it comes to
draw it looks a lot so I don't want to
do that and for today's look I want to
do a really really bright red so I'm
going to use the kylie boss lip liner to
outline them first and we have to over
line of course then I'm just gonna fill
this then using the matching Carly
liquid lipstick eraser so we are all
done and the last of the day is going to
be it to lock this face in place so your
performance and season 11 ready I'm
gonna use a skin to navy up makeup
finishing spray just myself a pretty
heavy spread all right babe so that is
the makeup all complete but we still
have a little bit more of a
transformation to do so I'm gonna go
throw some jewelry a wig and a different
outfit and I'll be right back and show
you guys the finished look hi sisters
all right you guys this is the completed
drag look for today I threw on a bra and
a t-shirt and some pants I wouldn't so
depiction of the full look right up in
here and I just feel so beautiful and so
confident and I think this is by far my
favorite drama thought I have ever done
I had so much fun filming this videos
today I'm like I was saying before hand
RuPaul's Drag Race is by far my number
one favorite TV show of all time it is
just so amazing and the artichoke has
inspired me so much throughout being a
person and also my makeup routine so
that's super super cool congratulations
the top pro Queens you all absolutely
slayed it definitely make comment down
below and tell me who you want to win I
am definitely team aquaria and team
Eureka if you guys didn't do this videos
today please don't forget to give a big
thumbs up down below and if you have not
already come to in the sister is the
pretty pretty lit time and click that
Bell icon sneak when you notified every
time I upload a brand new video if you'd
like to follow me on my makeup sure and
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter their posters James Charles and
my snapchat for more I had the same type
stuff if so your child's no extra ass
after Charles this video sister saw that
goes to sister Donna thank you so much
for you boys falling and supporting you
I love you so so so much and if you
would like to be the next video sister
shadow we could always a recreate a
video link and they go live on it
Twitter all right sisters thank you for
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next one now sashay away
[Music]