is it recording yeah okay so you know
the
girl one two three hi sisters that i'll
say welcome back to the channel it's
almost like i
it's almost like i've done it before hi
sisters
james charles here and welcome back to
my youtube channel sorry i'm emotional
i know this is the club y'all never
thought you'd see coming i didn't think
i'd ever be in this room again
i feel really good i missed you welcome
back it's been a really long time emma
and i recently reconnected after i think
like two years absolutely insane we've
been texting back and forth hanging out
a few times behind the scenes as well
a lot can happen over the course of two
years and you know it's been really
amazing just catching back up and really
like being in each other's lives again
and i'm definitely happy
to have you back oh thank you for having
me back no it's been really fun i'm glad
that i can now like add another friend
to my like list of
two out of boxes right now totally we
get to catch up like we
lived a whole different life yeah and
then we come back and then we get to
like
talk about it all i know it's actually
so crazy to think about i mean i've
obviously written all friendship in
private and now that we've had a lot of
time to just hang out and catch up we
figured okay we started online
might as well bring it back to online
and give y'all a collaboration that
you've been asking for for a very long
time we're trying to think what would
really
make sense right and you guys know i've
been trying really hard to step up my
fashion game looks like my instagram has
definitely improved since you knew me
last for sure sure no more adidas track
pants and sisters merch every single day
although you are hey and i figured if
there's anybody that i think really has
their fashion game together
it is miss emma chamberlain do you know
how much of a compliment that is to me
because
i always felt like you were 10 steps
ahead in that area and the fact that
you're in fashion
you just have your together and so the
fact that you're coming to me for
anything like i feel
really powerful i feel like me and james
have such different styles like you're
kind of like the ig baddie of it all
yeah and i'm kind of like the um i
listen to tyler creator like in the
shower
crying vibe and like i want to see james
in that
i'm gonna let emma style me for the week
now she already went through and picked
out a ton of different outfits
i did okay so basically i connected with
his stylist we spent a lot of time we
made movie boards
she went shopping i haven't seen
anything yet either
no nothing and i picked out a few things
that i think he's gonna
hate hey two of them i think you're
gonna like but two of them i'm
really iffy like i think you're you're
gonna want to punch me in the face i'm
not
scared me either nervous sure okay
like i feel like when people go whatever
i'm not gonna explain let's just go see
bye
[Music]
like the ones that i feel like maybe are
weaker anyway
close your eyeballs okay that's a nice
layout
i know it's kind of hot right okay this
is
something that i would wear like if this
was in my closet like i'd be wearing it
right now
and i think you're really gonna love the
jacket and there's some really cute like
little black accents and i think that
it's really cute and open your eyes
oh this oh this is good
this is so cute it's really cute i'm
obsessed with it
this is a really good look thank you yes
okay great it's only gonna get worse
from here this is the best one
so let's just ah okay
oh my god that was awesome i missed it
so much
okay he's gonna hate this i'm sorry why
do you think we're gonna hate this one
it's just very like
how would you guys experience it might
smoke oh yeah yeah definitely like
stoner vibes from this
possibly it like sits in parks and like
buys hummus and just like
but not for you no well it is for you
this week james are you gonna trust me
i'm gonna have no choice this one johnny
okay i'm gonna revive you a little bit
james because i feel like
that last one really got you emotional
scared and worried
yeah james this next outfit i think
you're gonna love because this one was
very bella
need inspired three which she's just
like the hottest so i agree
it's like stylish but also kind of hot
because of the shortest look
okay oh yeah i like it yes
yeah this is good oh my god the matching
glasses too i really like that
i love it too yes yes i just want to
come here and steal james's things
he hates the sweater i mean if he liked
every outfit it would be too fun of a
video
okay you have to picture it on this is
the thing about mine it's all about the
way you wear it
i can guarantee that you like this one
without going to a really important
business dinner and being like
look at my collared shirt i hate pink
thank you
listen you're gonna have two really good
days and two kind of
bad days but i think that you might be
impressed once you put the outfit on and
you kind of put it on your body and you
like look in the mirror and you do a
little bit of this there's also one more
day of the week you guys can say we only
so good news for friday i decided to
surprise you so we have an outfit for
you but you're not allowed to see it
until friday
so what everyone's looking at me with
suspicious faces
no emma i'm pleasantly surprised
with the selections this one better than
i anticipated and i think i can make all
of these work
great except maybe the green one just
get in it's monday
you have to start today get the green
one
[Music]
and then i won't be around when he wears
the rest of them because me and james
although we're friends again i don't
think we could spend a week with each
other
yeah we're working back up to there
right we're getting there for sure just
give us like a month
[Music]
um
i do kind of love it but it's also so
weird
james i've never seen you in an outfit
like this in my life and it's so
confusing
i think we did everything enough like
this again without an old man's shoe
right or an ammo shoe i just think the
green
and that shoe just gives me very like
clouds
listen this is my fault i do love the
set on you and i just think that the
dogs would be better
give it a try okay wait oh this is so
much better
oh that is better that is so much cooler
that is definitely better
it was just the shoes okay it was just
the shoes
no no it was just okay but like for
the rest of the week things are only
going to go from here and i'm excited to
see what happens this is true
i can't wait to see it on social media
while i'm laying in bed you're just like
i'll make sure to send you lots of
photos and see you on friday for the
final look
and for our grand reveal yes love you
kitty girl okay you guys just letting
everybody know i'm officially a vlogger
now i got a canon g7x camera which is
one that everybody uses i'm currently in
my emma
chamberlain styled outfit for day number
one it is this green
checkered look as i've had it on for
longer it is growing on me a little bit
it's definitely like not something that
i would normally put myself in but i
feel like the whole point of this video
in the first place was to get me out of
my comfort zone and put me in a fun and
fresh outfit and i feel like she
definitely succeeded sorry i'm moving
the camera a little everywhere this is
why i'm not good at vlogging anyway
trevor loves alfred coffee it is his
favorite place in the entire world
i am going to be wearing these all day
long so i figured might as well join at
trevor anthony on their alfred's trip
what are you guys doing
oh my god
[Music]
this is so gay it's actually like bad
hopefully emily doesn't mind that i
added a black mask
to this look although it does definitely
match with the boots
so it is time to go get some coffee
how do you like what what i will never
understand like people like vlogging
like what am i even supposed to be
saying right now or do it
okay so i just got it okay you guys
we're crossing the street
walking right across right now just
walking taking a step left but right
foot left foot right
left foot right side we're approaching
like what are you saying and hey guys
okay so we're just walking up to alfred
right now it's right here let's do a
taste test with our coffee
this is so stupid i am hi love how are
you
yeah of course let's do it for trevor
what do you think about my outfit by the
way do you want to be my vlog
yeah okay what do you think about my
outfit really cute okay are these doc
martens
yes sir cute do you like it i love it oh
my god thank you for the review
okay he's so sweet okay you guys that
was like really fun so now we're gonna
cross the street again
step step step walk across the street
you guys
so this will be an interesting kind of
background very industrial very la vibe
i think this is the very emma location
oh
sure miss emma oh
oh period a legs
so fun james you should start doing this
more
always giving back oh that's so good
it's an in-motion photo
that's famous if you but it's okay i
will absolutely facetune it for you
okay guys the coffee runs over
it's like okay i don't know if i'm
feeling the oatmeal fantasy honestly
really is this your first time um it's
leaving a weird film in my throat
okay i don't know what to say bye
[Applause]
i feel exposed good morning everybody
it's tuesday day number two
don't ever show that on camera yesterday
we had the green checkered outfit on
i figured today i would do my second
least favorite of the outfits which is
the pink and red stripes just to get it
over with we don't have too much weight
on today i was actually supposed to be
on set for a very exciting project today
which would have been fun
but it got cancelled which is sad but
now less people have to see me in the
look
that's kind of mean that is me emma did
a beautiful job it's just not exactly my
style we're gonna try it on anyway so
let's
get started
whoa oh she didn't take it out that
juicy dump truck oh no
oh yeah oh my god these are the tightest
ones i've ever put on
pushed it out look at my body it's all
about the angle ladies
but this um we can definitely return if
we keep the tag on it was
kind of expensive i felt bad buying it
how much was
how much was that with tax well a little
under 400.
we can keep the tag on that's why i'm
great oh my god this
is so emma emma would look so good in
this
the pants are just not fitting very well
and that's not emma's fault
my own fault for just having a juicy
okay let's go take a photo shoot sure
so we decided to all take a family trip
down to melrose and since
you know obviously i'm in this pink and
white outfit today and i am feeling like
a very basic la white girl so i figured
why not just take it a step further and
match my pink outfit
to the famous l.a pink wall this wall
radiates heat gorge
[Music]
i'm trying to be a good vlogger it's
literally 104 degrees outside
disgusting disgusting we wanted to go
shopping and then we decided actually we
don't want to go shopping it's not even
keep focusing
disgusting disgusting i'm gonna put me
in a wool sweater it's okay though it's
honestly growing on me a little bit but
you know what's not growing on me
this heat so we're going hey
i hate vlogging this is too hard
[Applause]
good morning sisters it is wednesday aka
day number three of this emma styling
series today's gonna actually be a
really really big day i have a very
special video that i have to film
and then also a business dinner tonight
and i think for today's look i want to
go with
the white racing one that literally
everyone loved including
me because i'm filming it's important to
me that the outfit i'm in is like true
to my
normal brand i guess and then for dinner
tonight there's a chance that we could
get paparazzi
so this is the look okay you guys so
this is the full look all completely
honestly obsessed i think this looks so
so
cute this look is it however the fit
is it's oh there you go i'm
not sure what size
pants miss emma thought that i was
they're good around the waist but like
it's producing a little bit of the
muffin top which is you know it's fine
everybody has one
like really have to accentuate some
angles here the jacket however i'm
literally obsessed with this outfit i
think looks
so good and i can see myself reusing
this in future looks as well so
i'm ready for the day and hopefully i
get caught because i'm ready for
oh wow oh my god
hello hi you guys i know you have not
seen me since this morning
um if i'm going to be honest with you i
have not filmed anything
for the video today in my outfit
although it was super super cute
because i'm going to be real um today
sucked i don't know how else to put it
or like what else to say or i don't want
to show
you anything of course that happens to
everybody but i'm just like
so sad and confused had our filming this
morning and it was
terrible um the video was definitely
going to be scrapped which is
very disappointing and weird because
that doesn't happen very often so i've
been in my head about that
all day long and then i had a business
dinner tonight which did go well
but as soon as we got to the restaurant
and walked in with my cute outfit which
i was excited to show you guys
they literally took our phones and were
like hey we're gonna need to put a
sticker
on your phone cameras because we have a
no photo policy which is fine obviously
i can definitely enjoy dinner without
having my phone
but therefore this video with miss emma
which i've been very excited about
i did not get any really great footage
today it's okay
obviously you know not every day can be
an amazing one i'm gonna
get my outfit off unfortunately as cute
as it is and get into bed and
hopefully wake up tomorrow to a way
better day love you guys
[Applause]
all right you guys hello good morning
today is already off to a much better
start than yesterday it is a beautiful
brand new day and i am grateful to be
alive and here and we are sending
positive vibes
into the universe today's outfit is the
harley davidson shirt with the cute
little shorts and the
tan blazer it is currently 11 43
right now in the morning and we have a
sister's apparel restock which is
actually a fun little surprise coming in
a few minutes and then i think we have a
team lunch today right you guys so that
should be fine as well i get to go out
with my outfit look cute
look at the sock to dock ratio not the
sock to dock ratio
it looks great oh the camel top might be
a problem in these
you can't have a camel oh
yes she can yes she can this is the
official
data before outfit all complete it's not
time to go
launching sister's hoodies out of ten
what do you think this is don't care
goodbye
okay you guys hello it has been a few
hours now the sisters apparel restock
went amazing
thank you all so much for the love and
support as always you can shop on
sisters
fastapparel.com but we now have the full
gang alongside with us
we are currently heading to one of my
favorite lunch spots in la called
zinc okay you guys i'm trying so hard to
be a good vlogger we just ordered our
food and we got it i ordered a
bowl with brown rice chicken avocado
lots of things
fries what do i even say i don't get
vlogging
i'm just gonna really dive into this
delicious meal and talk about some
business things
um with my team and then i'll see you
guys later
okay hey what's up james how's it going
it's my favorite
person what's going on with all these
people trying to come out with makeup
lines i don't know i mean
makeup is such an amazing industry
obviously and there's a lot of people
that are involved with it and a lot of
times too there's quite a lot of money
as well so
i think that there's a lot of people
involved that you know really want to
come out with a cool line
and sometimes people get involved for
the wrong reasons as well but it's
really not my position to ever say
it almost seems like they should contact
you though and collab with you though oh
definitely not yeah
who's next you said you got four videos
lined up i know you have a new son
i didn't have a new sun for the day
elliott i have some really exciting
videos
really cool club coming we have the
house tour video that people have been
super excited for
thank you guys everybody see you and you
got the whole crew with you too
good to see you guys take care we just
finished lunch paparazzi my favorite
person in the entire world fletcher from
hollywood picks
i can always count on him to find me
although i only really go to like three
different restaurants so it's probably
not very challenging we're back in the
car and we're going to get some ice
cream this is a cute little fun team day
outfit today oh thank you so much you
guys tell us about your outfit today
well it was filed by a very special
person for a special collab coming soon
she's a cute little pair of jeans from
bb denim we got a harley davidson shirt
and they're just a nice brown blazer but
we're going to store some prada bag to
really finish it off
what about the shoes
today we just had a lovely team lunch
over at zinc it's been a while since
we've all been able to like sit down
together so we're going to salt and
straw i can't join me today james ice
cream's on me
i got i got that okay no no no no no no
no no
i want to have donald today kevin what
do you want anything james
yes sir that's fine thank you james well
vanilla all right i want you to tell me
about your elephant tonight okay okay
today okay james so my outfit today is
the mtv pumas fire
for the puma fan we got the super sports
shorts yes
we got the rare edition delilah oh
fire absolute legend thank you dave
thank you
thank you guys
[Applause]
hi james hi james
hey louise can i hit you yeah um i want
to show you the final outfit of the week
it's friday emma comes over later today
i wanna have you try on the outfit
i any particular reason why i need to do
it right now
yeah why don't i just go in there and
try it on go go in there ready
it's ready okay go ahead and shut the
door okay
oh my god yeah
oh my god what is wrong with her
[Music]
oh my god i think this is the best
outfit you have
[Music]
baby shark dude you look good james
blue's definitely your color
i do like this color so we tried all
this it's kind of
[Music]
no no that's some wet that's some wet
my favorite one is the exposed egg oh
don't do that sorry i'm sorry she's shy
i know she's a shy little shark
i hate all of you for finding this it's
a double door sole
this is the living everyday with long
nails all over again you know my amazing
shark assistant i would love if you
would open up this box
sharks don't have assistance
so i just arrived um it is the end of
the week uh we're gonna go check out
his friday friday outfit which i already
know what it is because i
can pick it up but i just spent my
attention that emma is about to be here
and there she is oh
oh do you like my friday outfit yes like
i did the best job
do you like it oh i love it i completely
agree because i feel like i'm
doing something different for you that
you wouldn't normally do and i feel like
you need that you need to go out of your
comfort zone well i think we should go
down to the studio anyway because i have
to show you all the other outfits and we
can
finish off this chamberlain-styling week
welcome back emma thank you
it has been a lovely week right and i
have missed you dearly i know you have
been here in spirit every single day
because i have been wearing my
chamberlain style
fits and i think it is time to show you
oh gosh
i am so excited well okay i kind of got
a little sneak peek it was weird because
this week whenever i'd watch your
stories
it was so fun to see you in the outfits
yeah like it was kind of amazing i
didn't show any of them in full let me
just go through okay so day number one
i decided to go with the green checkers
because i wanted to get it over with and
this is the photo that i got
wait that's actually really cute it's a
cute photo we went for an alfred's
coffee run and i was feeling very
emma wait that's kind of really good the
coffee gave me explosive diarrhea for
the rest of the day
so yeah didn't really enjoy that right
like that's a really
like cute photo yeah and like super also
that is i
swear to god i have that photo on my
instagram probably i'm gonna give this
one
a seven out of ten i really like it
maybe a six out of ten what are you
getting this one like a solid like
four okay no i get it so for day number
two okay i wore
the pink and red stripes because it was
my second least
favorite i think that it actually looks
really cute
wait this looks so good james i lost a
lot of compliments too the only thing
about it the pants fit me
terribly okay right like so bad totally
my poor like
legs and butt were being so suffocated i
guess that's a good thing because my
butt is just so
i wish i had that problem and i also
like weirdly
how short the jeans are because you can
see the full sock like i'm really so
into this
yeah this is definitely a fun james i'm
really into it i rate this one
a seven out of ten i'm gonna give that
one an eight point two
ten so day number three okay um was
not a good day for me oh it was for the
video that i supposed to film which i
told you about which will not be
mentioned in this video but it
went so and i just ended up having a
really really bad day
which sucked because i planned to put
myself in my favorite outfit of the day
which was the white outfit with the
raisins
and this is the only photo that i have
which is a screenshot of my instagram
story where i'm having a breakdown
but the outfit looks cute wait you look
so cute though yeah the outfit's really
cute
honestly if you're gonna have a
breakdown you have to be wearing a
firefight for it like that's where i'm
at this was like a solid like nine out
of ten for me
it just sucks that i don't have a great
photo to share that's like a nine and a
half for me
i think yeah okay again thursday
day number four we actually went to
lunch and
wait stop james this is hot yeah it was
really cute like that is literally not
gonna give this a 9.3
because i really love it i would rate
this one on eight out of ten okay yeah
and then my friday look is
so this one's a solid 10 out of 10 you
guys i think that your last day was a 10
out of 10 for me because it was super
cute to see
like walking in it was just so endearing
that was really fun james i i'm
god i missed lost you too emma thank you
so much for styling me for this entire
week i actually felt really cute in a
lot of the outfits and it definitely
pushed me out of my comfort zone
which is exactly what the goal was so i
think you killed it well
you guys i hope that you loved emma
styling me for the entire week if you
did enjoy today's video please don't
forget to give it a big
thin up down below also click that
bigger subscribe button and come join
the sisterhood and finally click that
bell icon so you get notified every time
i
upload a brand new video make sure you
guys also go check out the video over on
emma's channel she did my makeup put me
on emma chamberlain style glam what are
you doing i'm sorry
and we really did a nice like catch up
two-year
conversation and it was honestly really
cute so i love it head over there if you
want to follow me on a makeup journey
all my social media accounts will be
linked right here on the screen and also
if you want to text me
on my personal on my personal phone
number for new videos photos merch and
so much more
it is 310-905-8746
um if you think that i'm like not that
annoying and you want to check me out my
youtube's emma chamberlain
and uh all of it everything's up in
chamberlain this video sister shout out
goes to sister bella thank you so much
love for always following and supporting
i love you so so so much
and if you would like to be the next
video sister shout out don't forget to
always retweet twitter links so they go
live on twitter and i'll search to my
youtube post notifications thank you so
much for watching this video today emma
stop
that i'm so sorry guys thank you for
having me bye sisters
love you guys bye
[Music]
you