hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
[Music]
cutting right to the point because
today's video is definitely gonna be a
pretty long one as you can see by the
title below this is going to be a
full-on unbiased review of the brand new
venti by ariana makeup collection so
Vinci PD actually had their launch party
last night in New York City and launched
this before at midnight and Rihanna had
a big event in Manhattan with a
beautiful yellow gown which is why I'm
wearing this yellow hoodie today which
you'll be finding out a lot more about
in Monday's video so stay tuned but
guess who is not invited to that launch
party this sister right here so this
morning I hauled my ass out of bed at 6
a.m. to go to Sephora because they
invited a bunch of influencers in for
early access and I picked up the entire
line I paid for everything one of these
products myself this video is not
sponsored and I'm not being paid to talk
about it either I just want to do this
video because so many of you guys are
wondering whether or not these products
are gonna be good
I myself I'm generally wondering if
these products are gonna be good the
fancy beauty campaigns have looked so so
beautiful so many beautiful models so
much diversity as well and the products
generally do look really really good but
I don't want to be biased I'm going in
with absolutely no knowledge of anything
so without further ado grab your pink
kitty drink at ease and let's go ahead
and get started with testing fenty
beauty products alright guys so you know
that I haven't been really using primer
so much lately I've just been loving
using a moisturize skin or right under
my foundation I feel like it just makes
my skin look so so beautiful and
flawless but 20 Beauty did drop a soft
matte primer so I already went ahead and
I moisturize and we're gonna be putting
this on top before the foundation today
so all the different products come in at
this design of a unicorn it is this like
off-white black spot an ombre pattern
honestly the packaging looks absolutely
stunning and let's go ahead and take it
oh oh wow this looks really good so I'm
fancy viacom this primer retails for $32
and it comes with one point zero eight
fluid ounces which is actually more than
the typical foundation most foundations
are usually one fluid ounce so there's
definitely a lot of product in here I'm
just gonna go ahead and I'm going to
store some on my hands as usual and then
just apply them to my face okay so I
definitely just applied way too much
that to my face that are it's gonna blow
in really really well there isn't too
much of like a strong smell but it does
smell slightly like lotion but like a
really really good lotion so it's
definitely a nice clean scent that isn't
overpowering oh and it does make my skin
feel very very smooth and also a little
bit tacky so this should make my makeup
stick hopefully pretty well I am so
annoyed right now like I said I went to
Sephora this morning to get the
foundation it to show you guys the full
range so I got shade number 100 being
the lightest shade
and number 490 being the darkest shade
of my dumb ass instead of getting my
shade which I determined was number 260
I bought to number hundreds are we
surprised no but are we annoyed yes
because I have to go all the way back
there so so you guys are not gonna see
any time passed because there's gonna be
a jump cut but my eyes will be back in
about two hours - as they do alright so
- very very long overrides later we are
back home and I have the right
foundation shade this time number 260
that's like classic James sorry but
flashback Mary was clearly really trying
to make it appearance I've been here but
not today
the nextstep is obviously going to be a
foundation and for today I bought you
guys three shades and I got number 260
for myself I did do some swatches in
Sephora but lord knows the lighting in
there is not the best so fingers crossed
this one works but I also picked up
number 100 which is the lightest shade
and number 490 which is the darkest
shade so I could show you guys the full
range I also went ahead and I picked up
the precision makeup sponge which I
guess is supposed to be like a Beauty
Blender type situation it comes in the
philip ox and then is in this package so
it is basically like a Beauty Blender
but it has flat edges so I'm just going
to go ahead and it actually sounds like
a bouquet of flowers weird enough but
like it smells good I'm gonna go ahead
and wet this before I apply my
foundation so if we're actually applying
the foundation I do definitely talk
about the shade range because it has
been a very very controversial topic so
I do want to swatch for you guys the
three different colors that I got today
so this is shade number 100 which is the
lightest shade on the top this one is
number 260 which fingers crossed should
be my shade hopefully
and this last sheet on the bottom is
number 490 which is the darkest shade
in the range I want to make it very very
clear that I'm obviously not a person of
color and I'm nowhere near as well I
simply wanted to swatch the darker shade
just to give you guys a good comparison
from the darkest to the lightest and
show the variation between them but I am
well aware that this watch on my
skintone is not going to be helpful at
all to my dark beauties out there so
while I was in Sephora today I did
happen to run in one of my amazing
sisters shout out to you a sister
julienne she definitely saw me
struggling with what to do with this
foundation so she actually went ahead
and let me swatch it on her hand
so hopefully this next step will give
you guys a better idea if you do have
darker skin on what this foundation will
actually look like alright guys I'm here
at plenty beauty and support to pick up
all the items early this morning and I'm
here with sister Jolene I want to show
you guys the darker shade in the range
because there are so many but obviously
I'm Pacey so I'm glad about the swatches
are you [ __ ] on me because but doesn't
help anybody so sister Tati is gonna
hold my camera for me a little swatch to
Devon today alright guys so this is
shades are bent 490 which is the darkest
in the range and to be clear we're on
essentially did run out of more shape as
well those definitely controversy on
Twitter when it comes to makeup but
literally 1s or not so we're gonna be
watching this sister Lena right here
before looks definitely pretty liquidy
and as you can tell this is a little bit
darker than her skin tone and this is
definitely a warm tone shade too alright
so now that that's taken care of let's
go ahead and actually apply the
foundation like I said I am number 260
and this foundation comes with one point
zero eight fluid ounces so same exact
thing as the primer but this one is $34
rather than the primer is 32 I'm just
gonna dip in with my venti Beauty sponge
and go right in on at the skin alright
so first impressions is that this color
is a pretty good match to my skin so
thank God the sephora lighting to not do
me too dirty today but fingers crossed
that it does not oxidize I'm already not
really loving this sponge
it's definitely leaving like imprint as
you can see like right there where I'm
tapping it in and I think that's because
this does have a flat edge to it which
would be really really helpful for doing
like under-eye concealer I feel like but
I feel like the flash is definitely
leaving some weird imprints in the
foundation so I'm not sure if I really
like this alright so that was about
three pumps this is what I normally do
for my foundation but we are nowhere
even close to being a full coverage yet
I literally only covered one cheek and
like this area on this side of the face
so I am gonna do a little bit more so
that is one coat of foundation fully
applied all over the face and it's
giving me like very medium coverage I am
definitely gonna add a little bit more
in areas that are still a little bit
see-through but honestly first
impressions I really like how this
foundation looks alright so that's the
foundation all applied and obviously we
have to wear this and see how it works
throughout the day but initial reactions
is that I really really like it it looks
really really good on my skintone my
skin feels nice and smooth and it feels
very very weightless too like I don't
feel like I'm wearing a lot of
foundation despite the fact that I
definitely just had to do like 10 or 15
pumps of this to get full coverage which
definitely is a con so if you're okay
with using a lot of foundation to cover
yourself with still feeling light that's
good but just know that you're only
getting one point zero eight fluid
ounces for the price pretty good but
still you're gonna use a lot of
foundation so you could go through this
very very quickly so the next up is
gonna be to conceal and contour my face
but I'm actually gonna skip out on
concealing for just one second actually
move to contour because today we're
gonna be using a cream contour from
Fenty Beauty and this is the match stick
and the shade suede each one of these
little cream sticks comes for
twenty-five dollars each and you get
0.25 ounces of product so definitely not
a whole lot but let's go ahead and cream
contour our face today
it's gonna blend this out using the
sponge alright so as you can see I just
tried to blend that in but instead of
really like blending in it kind of
disappeared and I think that's because
the foundation is getting layered over
top of it this sponge is obviously
soaking up a lot of product which is
definitely why it took 10 to 15 squirts
of foundation to get full coverage but I
think we got a switch over to my regular
beauty blender to finish blending this
out let's try this again okay I'm not
loving this
it's definitely blending out a lot
easier using my regular Beauty Blender
as opposed to the venti Beauty sponge
but honestly I'm still really not loving
this I'm having to pound really really
hard to even get the product to move I
really kind of already dried down
completely which for the foundation I
like because I have not set my face yet
with powder but it looks really really
good alright I'm back my camera decided
of course literally what else would go
wrong today at this point but I did just
go ahead and apply my concealer which
was a tar shape tape I was gonna pick up
one of the matchsticks similar to the
cream contour and a concealer but I'll
just be straight up I tried it in
support today and I absolutely hated the
formula I just felt as though it wasn't
soft enough to be able to really use for
under-eye concealer I just thought I was
gonna take off the foundation and
honestly at this point I'm really really
glad I went with that decision because
obviously I did not really like this
formula and using its shape tape with
this fancy foundation looks so good like
my skin looks absolutely phenomenal
right now I have not even set with any
powder I'm not creasing it it dried down
to like a semi matte finish it's not
completely matte but it's also a
slightest bit dewy this looks really
good alright so next I'm gonna go in and
I'm going to set my face so to do that
I'm gonna be using the fenty Beauty
invisi matte universal blotting powder
and there's only one shade in this and
it is very very light so I am praying
that flash like Mary does not come I
mean she clearly was trying it with a
shade 100 of the foundation so fingers
crossed that this does not give us the
worst luck ever under cinder grab my
morphe i'm a 335 brush and tap into this
and i'm going to use this to set
underneath my eyes just make sure that I
don't get any creases I'm next just
gonna grab my morphe m14 one and dip
into the pan to set the rest my face and
whoa as you can see when you dip the
brush in it definitely comes off as a
white powder this is getting very very
scary but when you blend it and I'm
assuming it turns
pretty transparent yeah so hopefully we
will get any flower shock but like I
said I will definitely take a photo and
show you guys in a few or short seconds
alright so as you can see for the photos
I just inserted this powder is
definitely flashback proof thank God
where I lightly dusted the powder just
to set my face and modify it my skin
tone looked exactly the same so if that
is an A+ and where I did really really
pack it on being the center of the
forehead chin and under the eyes like I
normally do it did flash back the
slightest bit and light not my skin tone
but that's exactly what I wanted it to
do so this powder is a major win and
definitely going in my bag when I go
places as well for light touch-ups okay
so now that my face is all set in place
oh we love a good poet I'm gonna quickly
go ahead and do my brows off-camera
fenty did not launch any brow products
with this original lion so I'm just
gonna use my normal benefit brow poets
and I'll be right back to start off the
eyes alright so I just went ahead and I
did my brows off-camera quickly to save
time and then I just stir on this
orangie Brown halo eye with the fenty
launched she actually did not launch any
eye shadow palettes or single shadows
just highlighters so I wanted to throw
this on as a base and then I'm gonna
grab the matchstick not the concealer in
the shade star-struck which is like this
pinky glittery shade it honestly
swatches really really beautifully and
I'm pretty sure this is less be used as
a cream highlighter for the cheeks but
it is definitely a little bit darker for
my skin tone as you can see when I
rotate my hand it definitely gives that
grey cast that nobody wants for a
highlighter so this is definitely look a
lot better on darker skins but I'm gonna
use it to highlight the center of my
eyelids today now it looks really good
oh my gosh I'm just gonna grab my morphe
m22 4 brush and dip into the top of that
cream highlighter and just use this to
blend out the edges lightly oh this is
really pretty I'm also gonna grab my
pinky finger and try applying it this
way too to see how that works this is a
match stick as well so it's also $25
like I said for the first one the cream
contour and a fun side note these are
magnetic and stick together which i
think is so cool and a really good
storage option as well so major points
to them for that so those are the eyes
all complete I'm absolutely loving how
this is turning out so far and now we're
onto the stuff that we've all been
waiting for and that is the highlighter
and I am so so so excited for this so
frenchie beauty actually launched a few
different highlighters retailing at $34
each and you get 0.12 ounces of product
and I actually picked up two of
this duo comes with two shades being a
lightning dust and fire crystal
definitely plus for the names please
excuse my crusty ass bandit but here's a
shade lightning dust swatch we're gonna
do it right here
that's not even showing up on camera and
it's actually really not that pigmented
in real life
- okay and then here's the shade of fire
crystal also swatched
alright so fire crystals definitely a
lot more pigmented and a little bit more
glittery than lightning dust days I'm
actually pretty disappointed in
lightning dust it really does not show
up that well on camera or in real life
so if you want a more subtle highlighter
this may be for you but when you're like
me and you like a blinding glow I think
we might be going for a fire crystal but
even this is really not that landing
either the second highlighter however is
when we've been waiting for and this is
what I am so so excited to use today and
that is the single highlighter in the
shade trophy wife it is this like
metallic ass gold shade that is I guess
more even glittery than hi lady oh
you're kidding Wow
so readö is actually writing this exact
highlighter at last night at the event
which looked so beyond stunning and
after being a little bit of research
what I'm gathering is that this
highlighter is actually more of like a
glittery base rather than an actual like
shimmer base so when you put it on it's
supposed to actually disperse more like
real glitter and look like your face is
like literally glittery rather than like
glowing so definitely not for the
everyday person but y'all know me I love
to be extra AF and I am so excited to
try this and let's give her a little bit
of a swatch with a clean finger oh
you're kidding let's go ahead and move
the Cartier bracelet down and do a
little oh wow I don't know if it's
picking up on camera but in real life
you can see the individual glitter
particles like shining and that is so
stunning oh my god I am so pumped for
this I'm gonna go in with my morphe M
501 brush and dip into trophy wife and
see how this looks
alright so the highlighter is definitely
there was only one swipe and I'm already
glowing but as you can see I definitely
had a lot my brush I was able to blend
it out too which is great because some
people obviously are not gonna want this
full-on glittery
glam highlight but y'all know me I need
to be x-ray app so I'm gonna dip back in
it once again and layer more on top for
that gold glitter effect oh my god Wow
I'm gonna go ahead and apply it to my
normal areas as
well being the brow bones okay so I was
super super excited for this highlighter
but after putting it on let's be real
this is definitely not for my skin tone
it is way too dark and way too golden as
well which is great because that means
that this will fit all my dark sisters
out there so so beautifully so if you
guys get this and try on it definitely
send me all the tweets and pics so I can
be jealous of your envious golden glow
but this highlighter definitely not for
me I'm actually gonna go back into this
duo and into a fire crystal and try that
instead I'm just going with my morphe m
405 ushe and i'm gonna quickly go over
just the highlight area to try to blend
it out a little bit and make it look and
not as intense because this golden glow
is a little bit too golden okay so
instead I'm gonna grab a clean m5a1
brush and dip into a fire crystal from
that duo that I just showed you guys and
try this one instead oh yeah that's a
lot better side note to if you have
nails these are really really hard to
open oh my god I'm like scared that I'm
gonna snap one I'm gonna save my final
thoughts at the end but the last step is
obviously going to be at the lip fitted
doodahs and for today I'm gonna be using
the venti glow lip gloss which I've
heard is literally so so good so I'm
very very excited to put this on so with
this gloss you get point three ounces of
product in its $18 so definitely not a
bad deal so the shade of this lip gloss
is definite like a muted mauve shade
which I absolutely love and there are
little flecks of gold that are in here
too for that high shine look so I'm
super excited to put this on oh wow
okay so I don't know if this is reading
on camera but in person this lip is
literally so shiny that it almost looks
like a metallic lipstick but I really
don't hate it because I'm kind of living
for the gloss so I actually didn't layer
this gloss over anything because that's
how it was marketed in the fenty
campaign I'm pretty sure all the models
how there's over there natural lip
colors and for me the formula is really
really nice but I'm really not loving
the color that it's giving my lips it
doesn't look bad but I just feel like it
doesn't really match with this I look so
maybe if I layered it over top of
something it would look better but as
for the actual lip lost formula and feel
I like it I'm gonna finish off by spritz
my face using my Urban Decay all nighter
setting spray just to lock everything in
place and that is the full face of
fenty products okay so let's go back and
recap for those you sisters who are
interested in buying the primer and
foundation one hundred and fifty percent
I love this my skin looks so good I
barely had a powder on my face and it
dried down so so nicely the shade match
is really really good I look golden and
bronzy and like my texture is not
showing my pores look good I love this
and this honestly and maybe replacing my
makeup forever and two-phase duo but
you'll have to stay tuned in find out
I'm gonna keep braiding this look
throughout the day so I will definitely
tweet and stop and keep you guys posted
as to how it wears but as of right now I
love this next product we uses the
universal invisible adding powder which
I actually use for setting powder I am
once again love this as well it was
super super lightweight and even though
it is a light color which definitely had
me a little spooked at first it does not
give any flash back which is so great
and definitely did a really good job of
mattifying my skin and keeping
everything in please that was rude like
I said at the foundation did write down
a pretty matte so I really do not need a
lot of this but this will definitely be
going in might touch-up bag for when I
go to events because I love this the
next product we used the next product we
tested out was one of the matchsticks
and this is one of the contour shades I
picked out suede and this for me it was
more of a fail so the next product we
used was the matchstick and I picked up
the shade its way to do my cream
contouring and definitely I was a little
bit biased considering I don't really
like cream products to begin with but
this was not for me at all I really did
not like the formula of these it's not
bad by any means but I just focus on how
to work really really hard to really
blend this out and even after blending
it I still felt like it was a little bit
patchy so I definitely would not be
recommending this match stick or the
sponge as well I forgot to mention this
but this is just overall a big no it
really did not do that good of a job of
blending out I feel like I had to work
really really hard at it and also this
soaks up way too much product too as you
guys saw had to use like 15 pumps of
foundation to get a full face which is
never ever the move and it's gonna run
you out of that foundation so fast $34
is definitely a lot of money to be
sending on a foundation so I would avoid
getting this because you're gonna waste
it to spend the extra four dollars and
get the regular Beauty Blender and save
yourself a whole lot of time and product
so even though this matchstick was a
major fail for me this match tip in the
shade
Stardust was a major major win it is
once again a cream stick and it is
supposed to be a highlighter but instead
of using it on my face I did use it as
my eye shadow to be my center highly of
my halo eye and oh my god like I said
before I love how this looks and it's
super super pigmented as you can see and
similar
the contour it was kind of hard to blend
out but for an eyeshadow look that's
really really great because as you can
see it's really not transferring it's
saying exactly where I put it and just
the edges were able to people ended up
with that perfect
glowy halo eye I definitely would
recommend this one so the next part if
we try it out were at the Frenchy Beauty
highlighters and these were a major fail
once again I'm so sad because I was
really really looking forward to these
especially the shade at trophy wife
all the models wearing it last night
looked so stunning with their gold
glittery highlights but it was
definitely way too dark for me honestly
it really not mad at it at all it's
about damn time a brand comes out with a
lot of products meant for a darker skin
tone so definitely if you are later skin
tone would not recommend but if you're a
dark Beauty these highlighters would be
it's so good for you
that's what the other highlighter duo
this one was a major fail for me as well
as you saw the shade lightning dust
really doesn't have any pigment at all
and then the shade of fire crystal was
super super beautiful but as you can see
it's on my face and it is looking a
little bit grayish white um I was
expecting this to be a little bit more
champagne E but it's definitely looking
a little bit too pale so for me I would
have loved to have a highlighter in the
middle of these two because this is too
dark and this is way too light slash
gray so hopefully Rihanna will come up
with a lot more things but for me the
highlighters where I fail and last but
certainly not least we try to feed vent
a beauty gloss and I love this like I
was saying I wish I layered this over
top of a liquid lipstick or regular
lipstick because I'm not loving the
color that it gave me to match with this
look muttering a side though because
that's my fault the formula itself I
absolutely love it feels very very
comfortable and lightweight on my lips
and not sticky which is literally the
best thing in the entire world and yeah
I really really like this and this will
definitely going in my bag as well
alright sister so that has the full
Fanta beauty products I'll try to and
reviewed definitely become a down below
and tell me which product you like best
and what you're dying to try it as well
overall after trying all these products
I think there are only two things in
total that I really didn't love and they
were still not bad at all just
definitely not for my makeup preference
so love that I also love the fact that
there are 40 foundation shades oh my god
I can't stress enough once again thank
all the beauty brands are finally
starting to target towards with darker
skin tones and people of color it is
about damn time and this makeup line at
launch my Rihanna is such a major step
forward for diversity so major hats off
to that and claps for a sister RiRi if
you haven't already make sure to click
that big red subscribe button down below
and join the sisterhood also click that
little Bell button so you can be
notified every time I upload
new video if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
shame Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes aid stuff is James
Charleston extra ass after Charles this
week's shout-out goes to sister Leo
thank you so much girl for always
falling in supporting if you would like
to be at next video sister shout out
make sure to always reach a video link
so they go live on Twitter sino as well
I have two very very exciting things
happening next week make sure to look
out for Monday's upload something
happening on Tuesday and Wednesdays
upload it's gonna be a good ass time and
I cannot wait for you guys to see what
I've been working on already sisters
thank you so much for watching I love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]