[Music]
hi guys James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel as you can
see I'm looking a very very different
right now I don't have a baseball cap on
I have got my freaking haircut oh I
obviously love coeternal my rat's nest
of a man bun is now chopped off
thank the Lord and heaven above god
bless major living legend Jen Atkin if
you guys don't know she actually sells
the Kardashians and a ton of other
amazing celebrities but she doesn't do
boycott that often and her eye we're
talking really girl I need to get this
off my head I'm so tired of looking ugly
every day where's my baseball hat and my
messy-ass hair like what can we do and
she was like sister James I got you
so I went into the salon and this is
what came out of it honestly I'm so
happy with it I hope you guys love that
too
there will not be a baseball hat for a
little bit of time now so hopefully we
can get used to the new look and yeah
moving right along for today's video
we're gonna be doing a first impressions
chitchat get ready to me I'm actually
super pumped for this because do you
guys know that I really don't change out
my makeup routine that often to toys the
Make Up For Ever Ultra HD foundation
stick shape cube concealer Laura Mercier
and benefit brow stop shave tape on the
brows and some type of morphe I shadow
palette some type of highlighter and
then a nude lip like you guys feel me at
this point although I do love Tori
getting some creative looks it's been a
hot minute since I've tried some brand
new products all that being said I've
been saving up some PR packages from the
last few weeks some of my favorite
companies and I have a ton of products
that I cannot wait to show you guys so
let's get started
as always I'm just probably my face
using my benefit Porefessional primer
you guys know this is like my
ride-or-die primer and I probably will
honestly never switched up unless I find
something better skin is always been
something that it's been like a major
problem area for me in my life I used to
have really bad acne but Lily my skin
has been treating me so what's so well
and I am so frickin happy about it so
yeah purple it is I actually just got a
facial a few days ago for the first time
when they did like the extractions where
they said they're like pop everything
out of your nose I was laughing so hard
because the only thought right through
her head was
you could probably pop all the
blackheads on my nose and literally
repackage all the gunk into a benefit
Porefessional primer because that's all
I ever felt my frickin nose purple and a
sheet on these might make up for ever
ultra HD sick and the shade of Y at 325
once again this is one of those products
that is my Holy Grail and will not
change and there was no what foundations
than any of the packages that I receive
so can't switch anything up I'm so
freaking excited because you know all
the sisters are going with makeup
forever tight to a kailani concert here
in Los Angeles and I absolutely love her
and her music I think she's so talented
and just so like cool in general we
actually just got a tux earlier thinking
we're gonna get to hang out with her
before the show something which is
literally is so dope so I am getting
ready for that right now I'm praying
that all these products that I'm trying
on today we're gonna favor because this
is gonna be the look that I'm wearing
tonight y'all know that that self he's
gonna be iconic so hopefully we can pull
this off all right so I just went ahead
and applied my shape tape concealer in
the shade light and then blended it out
as usual is my damn Beauty Blender and
now the next step is ways to set my face
so for today I am using a new setting
powder and this is the RCM a no color
powder you may have seen this before
because I know a lot of people talk
about and abused it if you've used it I
apologize this is not your first
impressions as my first impressions and
I have never tried this before so I'm
gonna use it today you guys know that
setting powder is a little bit of a
touchy subject for me so I'm actually
super nervous to try a new one but I've
heard a lot of good reviews so let's go
ahead and give it a try so first light
is going on really really nicely it
definitely is like pretty finely milled
so that's good because we don't get
those like ugly like splotches that
sometimes it catches on to the
foundation but I'm gonna keep putting it
on and see when I think up deep and it's
definitely a really good job of like
mattifying and setting everything in
place as you can see my nose definitely
looks locked right and then which is
great because lord knows that my nose
loves to slip and slide around I'm also
gonna place a little bit of this right
in the center of my forehead just to set
that area in place and make sure I don't
get any creases because I do tend to
crease up there a lot and then lightly
just a but some excess powder on that
way face lately I actually have not been
setting my entire face I've been going
for more of the like a dewy skin a
foundation
I've honestly been loving it here loss
and doesn't this literally it's so
freakin hot I've had my AC blasting all
morning and all night last night and
it's still it's like a million degrees
in here which is very very rude and
homophobic because I'm about to melt but
we're gonna make it work I'm gonna suck
it up but yeah so I haven't been setting
my entire face and I've been living for
the dewy look but that depends on your
skin type and how it you like wearing
your makeup if you want to set your
makeup and if you're someone who
definitely gets oily definitely a pack
on the powder girl you do you so now
that my face is all set and locked right
and please the next person precious I
wanna pull is actually a brush set James
Charles not using morphe brushes relax
[ __ ] do you know that the Jacqueline
Hill morbid Club is coming in about five
seconds hold up today I want to show you
guys the club that I have a super duper
excited about and it was actually when
my best friends and true sisters in the
entire world
hey Zeus and his club with the makeup
shock I am so beyond excited to this
that I have been with him since the
entire beginning of this even being
planned in the first place so I'm so
excited to have it right here in front
of me and I definitely won't be using
these brushes on my face today on the
back of the palaces I have created this
brush out of my personal favorite
brushes from the makeup shock to create
a full face for the everyday glam a
combination of natural and synthetic
brushes I hope you enjoyed this as much
as I do
xoxo hey Zeus Gomez I am so freaking
proud of them
this set comes nine brushes and there
are angled brushes I brushes compact
brushes and then face brushes as well so
definitely a full on set I know retails
for $75 that the makeup shock which is
definitely a little pricey for a brush
that but y'all know me of course every
staudte that I did get a coupon code so
you guys can now use code chance or
twenty percent or purchase at the makeup
shock that brings the price of this down
to Rome $60 and divided by nine that's
just over six dollars per brush so
definitely not too bad of a deal
so shut off leather we grab the T 27
brush from the brush set and then dip
into my Kat Von D shade and light
palette into this middle shade and I'm
going to contour and chisel out my face
oh my god the bristles on these are so
soft
Wow legend went off we got a contour out
that jaw light as well and snatch her
right up and we definitely are not gonna
miss out on this for yet contour Lord
and nose and now that I don't have a
baseball hat to cover half of this
region we're gonna need to use that
contour to turn this five head back into
around a
three head I'm then gonna grab the t-84
brush in that same shade from the shade
and light palette and I'm going to
contour out my nose oh my god that
actually lay down the color so nicely my
luck see 182 brush is shaking I'm gonna
actually really like this brush yes T 94
you better work before we move onto
baking I'm gonna quickly grab my tea 17
also from the brush set and dip into a
Mac peaches blush and just put a light
wash of color on at the cheekbones okay
maybe that wasn't exactly the best brush
for a light to wash the color but it'll
do alright so I'm gonna grab my Beauty
Blender and dip right back into that RCA
and no color powder and I'm going to be
my face so I'm gonna my nose contour as
always even though the powder is trims
looser I'm really hoping that because
it's white it's still a bright enough
everything a little bit and if it does
were about to look so snatch in a few
minutes and I was super excited to see
how this rubs off alright so while I was
in the oven baking ideas quickly went
ahead into my brows off-camera save some
time same exact process as always no new
products or first impressions so now
that it's been a long really time we're
gonna go ahead and we're going to wipe
this bake off and see how this powder
did okay so I was definitely right the
thought that it is white definitely did
leave a little bit of a highlighted look
but I really really like that that's
exactly what I look for in a setting
powder I really like when I bake my face
and it like really brings back those
highlights so I need help there very
ready to find contour highlight like
very very full focus 360 full glam
snatch that was stupid I apologize so
you know what I mean looking up close my
skin definitely does a little bit more
porous than usual especially in like the
t-zone area right up in here that's
where ports are usually the worst but it
definitely doesn't look as good as it
normally does today I'm not sure if
that's the powder or my skin in general
not having a good skin day but I
definitely want to keep using this
powder because they like how it looks so
far and I will keep you guys posted at
for sure alright so I already went ahead
and prime my eyelids using my shape tape
concealer and then some more RC made no
color powder as usual and now we're
going to move on to the eyes and this is
what I was so so so excited for and that
is the Jacqueline Bo collaboration with
morphe nothing this was actually
released I can actually smell a little
bit of a secret for you bodies but a
long long long time ago Jacqueline
actually showed me the mock-up for this
palette on FaceTime
she showed me like one of the first
trial region
honestly it has changed so much since
then but it is just so beyond beautiful
Joplin if you are watching us I freaking
love you so much
I don't know if any of you guys know
this because the only tour of the story
like once or twice but Jonathan Hills
actually like the reason I started doing
makeup in the first place she's holding
my inspiration I would stay up all night
watching her YouTube videos I just think
she's just like the most boss ass [ __ ]
ever I love her and I respect her so
much and obviously you guys know I love
morphe as well so this club was just
made in heaven and if you know
Jacqueline you know that this is
literally her in a frickin a palette
version so this palette comes 235 custom
formulated shades they are not the
everyday morphe formula and I have not
washed them yet but I've seen other
people I know that these are gonna be
good but I'm gonna save my opinions
until I actually put them on my face
that being said this palette retails for
$35 so it is a little bit steeper than
morphine as usual $22 a palette but it's
living 35 amazing shades for $35 you
really really it cannot be that this
palette won't just in a few days so you
definitely are gonna want to get your
hands on it while you can and as always
you can use coach a store 10% off your
purchase but this is Jacqueline's
palette so if you wanna double support
her
please use code a Jack Attack as well
that has Jacqueline's code I'll put it
right down here on the screen go show
her some love this palette is literally
everything and I'm so pumped to put it
on my face right now I'm first gonna
start by grabbing the shade creamsicle
on my makeup shot t70 brush and I'm just
going to buff this right into the crease
oh my god that's been dead okay Jonathan
I see use the sir
I'm next thing to grab the shade hunt on
my makeup shock at44 brush and I'm going
to buff this right into the crease
because I'm going to be transitioning
from like yellow to orange to a red oh
my god these colors are literally
blending it so beautifully I'm kind of
stuck to the coil right now I'm Mexican
MIT 63 brush and dip into the shade at
Jack's and I'm going to put this right
in that crease for a little pop of red
oh yeah then we can knock it over how
pigmented these shadows are that was
living with one dip into the pan
we got ya like hi okay I'm gonna dip
back into Hunt's with that t-44a brush
and just buff over those edges I was not
anticipating that much pigmentation so
now we need to blend her out or else
this is gonna get real messy real fast
once all those three colors are on there
as well I'm gonna dip back into
creamsicle and just go over those edges
make sure they are super blended out and
their transitions are all smooth I
really want to do a pop of blue on the
eye so with that same exact e63 brush
I'm actually gonna dip into the shade of
royalty which is a metallic purple shade
in this palette but I'm gonna use this
as kind of a transition shade between
the metallic blue that's gonna go on the
lid and the cranberry color that I just
might in the crease and once it's all on
there I'm gonna go back into the same
brush in the shade Jack's which is the
red shade and just bring back the
cranberry color I'm gonna grab my t79
brush and didn't do the shade at work
which is this metallic blue shade I am
so excited for this and I'm gonna pop
her right onto the lid oh my god my
brush Libya is not even wet either miss
Hill suddenly my wig just got ripped off
and flew all the way from Los Angels to
wherever you are in Florida these are so
good I know everybody's gonna say I'm
sucking up tomorrow because I always do
but honestly these shadows are like so
good I genuinely would not expect
anything less than perfect for
Jacqueline and so far that is exactly
what I'm seeing I'm gonna go back in
with Torque you know what I'm gonna
surprise my brushes in the all-nighter
and I'm just gonna lay this on top again
and see how like actual metallic we can
get it oh my god these are literally
beautiful okay I think I want to show
this into a little bit of a halo eye
situation so I'm gonna grab the same
exact brush and dip into the slightest
bit of a pool party
once again gonna spritz that brush that
I'm just gonna layer that right on the
center of the lid and see how that looks
- I'm a little bit love of how this
looks so far so I guess we're going to
move on to the lower lash line now so
I'm gonna start off using the exact same
shade of torque on the same t79 brush
and I'm going to above this in two and
then going to grab a double pool party
and Papa in the center
once again I never got that t44 brush
one last time and dip into Jax and I'm
just going to blend all those editors
and connect it back up to the upper lash
line to highlight the inner corners I'm
gonna go to my Sigma e30 brush and dip
into the shade beam which is this
beautiful bright house highlighting
shade and I'm going to pop that right in
there oh wow before I move on to the
lashes I describe my Mac reflex teal
because I want the center of the lid to
really really really pop so I'm just
gonna grab my tee at 79 brush one last
time
dip into just the slightest little bit
of it and I'm going to stretch my brush
then I'm just going to hop her on there
everything that is there gosh that'll
all complete for laughs today I'm gonna
pop on the makeup shock lashes in the
style Dubai I'm having a really good
makeup day today and I'm honestly it
really and then of course I'm gonna use
my roller lash mascara just to blend
together the fake lashes with the real
ones all right sisters that is when I
all complete I'm honestly hoping this
look so much so far it is definitely a
good makeup day so it's sister James is
happy I'm gonna go ahead and do the
other one off-camera quickly and I'll be
right back to finish off the rest of the
face
alright guys I am back with both eyes
all complete I wiped off the crusty
foundation on my lips brush my teeth to
get ready to go for tonight's event and
now let's move on with the glow for
highlighter said I were using the Wet n
Wild mega glow highlighting powder I am
so freaking excited because I've heard
so many great things about these but
they're literally still don't everywhere
I've looked for them so many times that
my different drugstores you guys know
cried drugstore makeup girl a few weeks
ago I was talking about wanting to use
these but they were nowhere to be found
so I finally got this one today I
actually has a matter of fact wet and
wild just let me a huge PR package with
a ton of their products so definitely
give this video a big thumbs up down
below if you want me to do a full face
using only well products because I would
definitely be down definitely not as
blinding as I was expecting but not bad
to formula that's like rubbing my brush
and it feels extremely soft which is
good because that means that the texture
of your natural face won't show as much
because I know highly a lot of times
accentuate texture especially for me
because they have a lot of pimples in my
highlight region for some annoying ass
reason but the form of this feels really
really good this highlighter is
definitely a really really pretty and I
know this is drugstore price I think
this is like $6 so honestly for $6 it's
really really not bad I'm just being
dramatic here but definitely not as a
blonde
as I was expecting it to be I'm probably
gonna end up lying this with like my
makeup forever 13 pigment or my Anasazi
so Hollywood just to be like blinding
people left and right but definitely so
beautiful for the price I said this how
that is beautiful and I did not lie and
it's definitely beautiful on the
cheekbones but for the nose contour haha
for some reason even though this valley
is literally super super light it is
apparently too dark for my skin tone
because when I'm not hitting the light
like right there you can see it's not
reflecting light so it looks a little
bit darker than my nose contour which
completely ruins the effect which is so
frustrating so I'm just gonna layer over
top the makeup upper 13 right on that
area because lord knows that that is
that blinding and will hopefully fix
this oh great that literally just made
it 20 times worse I think that's
probably a message from somebody up
above saying James stop trying to make
your nose look 20 time sorrow that
actually is because sister you're not
fooling anybody are this is the last
step of this makeup show us obviously
going to beat the liquid you doodahs and
for this I do have a first impressions a
new product and that is the brain news
away high pigment lip gloss is I love
joy Aylor highlighters are so bomb and I
love their lip toppers as well so I was
so excited to see their brand-new
glosses these are all that will right up
in here I'm going to lean back because
there are a whole lot of them for sure
for this look I'm gonna pop on the shade
at PCH alright so as the base I
discipline the colour-pop ultra satin
lip in the shade Aquarius just to give
the gloss something to like stick to and
layer over top up and now I'm gonna
reapply to show you dat PCH I love how
this looks oh my god
freshen the giggles I think Overtown
familiar the G way a skinny dip lip
topper just for some extra glow some
glam some shine why not lastly to finish
off the stick I'm just going to drench
my face using the Urban Decay all
nighter setting spray
alright guys and this is the completed a
full face using all first impressions
glam I am honestly so alive for this
look I love it so freakin much let's go
back interview all the products that we
tried today the first time being the are
CMA no color powder this definitely did
a really good job of baking the face and
lightening it up I loved the effect that
it gave but it definitely did make my
pores and texture look not the best and
it's never looked
usually the alarm RCA powder doesn't
really get up absolutely everything out
so I definitely going to give this
another shot and see if it's just the
powder or if it is just my skin don't
know it looks pretty but I've seen it
look better so I'm quite sure to at
least all in the fence with this one
but did a decent job for today that's
what the makeup stock brushes they're
definitely a big hit for me you guys
know that I'm very very loyal to morphe
and the brushes don't absolutely love
them but I have to support my best
friend in the entire world
Hayes's I am so freaking proud of you
and you guys need to go check out this
brush set as soon as it launches and
remember Co James gets you 20% off
actually the next item on the list you
already know how I feel about miss [ __ ]
over here this pillow is literally
everything I am just so beyond check out
the quality and how they blended and
just the pigmentation in general this
palette is a hundred percent a win as I
said before I am so beyond proud of
sister Jacqueline she is the person who
single-handedly got me into the beauty
industry I've always looked up to her
and now it is literally so freakin crazy
and cool to me that I'm able to call her
one of my best friends so proud of you
as I said before coach James gave you
10% off when it launches or if you want
a double support sister chocolate use
coat a jacket a cat your check out as
well next up on the list was the Wet n
Wild highlighting powder and I wanted to
love this so so so so bad but I think
this is gonna be my one fail of this
video it looks so beautiful on the
cheeks I'm like the brow bone and the
upper forehead region but on the nose
contour it is really not doing it
justice it definitely is a little bit
too dark for a skin which is so strange
because this is already a super super
light highlighter but it's giving us
that great pass when the light isn't
hitting it so this is gonna be a fail
for me but like I said before definitely
give this video a big thumbs up if you
want to see a full face using all wet
and wild products because I do have a
full collection now that I would love to
try out for you guys and last but
certainly not least was the jus a new
ultra penguin lip glosses and these are
so Bob I used to shade PCH on my look
today at once again layer over that
color pop gloss but I absolutely love
how it looks the formula is really
really nice I know a lot of glosses
oftentimes feel really really tacky or
sticky when I go like this my lip lick
sticks together but this wears
beautifully it's lightweight it's simple
it's nice and I love the color so this
is definitely a win up for me alright
guys that is all I have I had so much
fun trying out all these new products
today definitely leave a comment down
below and tell me which one of these
that you'll be dying to try I know there
are so many launches and crazy items
coming out soon I am so frickin pumped
to see what all of you guys come up with
and all your amazing looks if you guys
enjoyed this video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
and subscribe if you have not already I
post two videos a week on Mondays and
Fridays and I'd love to have you join
the sisterhood if you'd like to follow
me on my makeup journey you can follow
me on Instagram and Twitter they are
both just James Charles and my snapchat
for more behind the scenes legs up is
James Charles an extra ask after Charles
our sisters thank you so much for
watching and I will see you in the next
one
[Music]