hi sister James Charles here welcome
back to my youtube channel as you guys
all know I just moved to downtown Los
Angeles and I officially it moved in
rudra definitely a coming soon but if
you're from the LA area you know there's
an iconic place a few blocks down called
Santee alley it's basically like the
hidden gem marketplace of Los Angeles
and as fabrics clothes makeup in all
types of glam and projects DIY crafty
types up but first super super low up
prices we're going to go tell us again I
went over to Santee alley with a few
friends to look for like clothing items
and jewelry but when I was there I
noticed that they had a ton of knockoff
makeup products I was doing products
from all my favorite brands like morphe
benefit Tariq Kat Von D Kylie but once I
got a closer look I realize that they
were all fake products so for today's
video I headed back over to Santee alley
to pick up a nostril all my finger
product and I'm going to be doing a full
phase of all fake makeup I have a ton of
stuff in front of me so without further
ado let's get started so first things
start off as always by priming my face
you might benefit Porefessional primer I
picked this up for a whopping three
dollars this is it in comparison to a
real professional it's one assessing a
little bit bigger and it looks a little
bit bluer as well but I because it's
extremely dirty I guess I'm gonna use
this at the primer whoa that dissolves
like my professional oh my god this
looks like foundation Oh
oh my for furnishing today I'm using the
mac studio fix fluid foundation in the
shade and c40 now if you already makeup
lover you will know that I am nowhere
near and NC 40 but this is the what came
out of the NZ 40 when I open the box
earlier today then it's not NZ for me
but this is the closest shade that I
could find to my skin tone serum try
this out to apply the makeup say I'm
using the out of Salvia for relief of
brushes very funny for one because these
do not actually exact so they're
literally a do both at non existent
products and to the brushes are upside
down inside the packaging great quality
content right here this literally will
not come out my parents to me when I was
oh actually it's not that bad of a shape
match and see for you my ass it's not
like really not doing its job books
forever okay this is just really not
doing the job to get on right so I'm
gonna switch over to my knockoff a
Beauty Blender this is what I got today
for a whopping three dollars and this is
in comparison to my regular Beauty
buzzer so obviously was a lot more pink
because it has foundations and stuff on
but they are pretty much like the same
size a whole lot fatter there's also a
lot more debt so I'm going to use this
try to focus on holton special attender
I know my mask on Dacians pretty well
and this one says is the studio fix
fluid is it definitely not very similar
to the students exclude the regular ones
a Mac is very very very high covered in
a super super beautiful web skin then I
cannot say the same for so we definitely
still see like my redness popping
through especially over an early autumn
my nose where my glasses sit
there's a weird at pimple situation are
going on up in here my five o'clock
shadow
so then shave yet today definitely it
not be a regular max to be full coverage
but honestly it's not like awful pretty
bad could be worse we're going to learn
today we're using the Maybelline a
master conceal concealer in the shade
fair this is the only shade of the
concealer I can find something going to
be
a little bit light but the foundation is
definitely my machine either so
hopefully we can even things out
[Music]
also the firm you should definitely like
matched a few minutes ago and now it
already is oxidizing turning orange so
this is going to get even last my shade
by the end of today great for Mother's
tonight leaving the event i at luxury
and banana toner this was $15 which is
definitely a little pricey for a fake
setting color but oh well what something
really careful to not get this in at my
eyes because I have no idea what is in
this and I'm trying not to go even more
blind than I already am today first
thing I never thought about is this
powder is really really chunky and
splotchy it definitely does an awful on
a very smooth and I have tried to be a
regular Ben Nye banana powder people and
I've done a drive look it's really
really good definitely not it to further
highlight under my eyes I me a Mac
Studio Fix foundation plus powder in
this I have in the shade MC 30s once
again definitely not my shade and this
is what new powder it looks like oh I
forgot I bought this letter for $10 and
in comparison here is my regular Mac
Studio Fix information and this is in
the shade ad 3 so if you mind this is
really not that much later in this is n3
and this is MC 30 something really
doesn't add up there and I'll tell you
it's 27 oh it smells like baby powder
like look like bad baby powder so it
sounds absolutely no coverage at all I
use my real one - usually a highlight
insanities my eyes and in my forehead to
really brighten up my face and it has a
ton of coverage it always like to file
eyes except and covering on my under
eyes
this until you have done nothing because
it still looks like a sister needs to
get another 15 hours of sleep before
we're going to look like very de brazza
controi face today I'm using the Kat Von
D shade and light palette you guys know
this is my Holy Grail contour now I have
my real one right up in here so I'm
using the fake knock on phone today my
favorite part about this is that on the
back of the packaging they show you the
shades I don't know if the lighting is
picking it up but literally this is like
shrug holiday and contouring colors
these are all green so I'm four by to
see what's gonna happen when we open at
the box what we got going on whoa oh
okay a little bit broken and I'm
currently a lot of it dirty so that's
great here's the comparison between it
be fake and it's a real one honestly
they look pretty similar the only
difference is that these colors are a
lot more warm tone and these on the
bottom or a lot more cool toned so the
quality this is going to be a whole lot
better and I was going to say it don't
judge what considering I just open up
that open already shattered I don't
think this sister has a lot going for
her wig I'm gonna grab this pointed
blending brush and use the middle shade
of the pallet insert to contour my face
I guess your honestly this is not that
the Oh light pink please stay back
notice it definitely does not blend out
it's easily as the normal shade of light
does extend it a lot more patching and
it takes a little bit more to blend but
equipping a lot waters so it's not going
to one so far one of my club drawers are
all in place again I'm going to use a
little more of that by my luxury powder
I wear to a baked might be this is
extremely pigmented whoa
while baking up medical notice our on my
Brown and today we beat auto salvia this
brow pomade it has been a long time
since I've used the real mafia Jeff
Brown in general you guys know that I
have made the official switch over to a
brow pencil but this should be
interesting
here comes a tiny liner brush from the
islands of the airbrush collection and
we're going to dip into ash brown which
is definitely not my shade but it was
literally the only shade there that most
like you live remotely mastery's any way
shape or form I'm going to try to you
with maybe the brows okay I already take
this brush via texture up this is really
really like flat and annoyed I hate that
word so much but like this is slipping
around very very easily and I remember
when I used to use dip route it was like
really hard to kind of like mold and get
into place but I like that because it
was a lot harder to make you see simply
with this whole lot easier I'm going to
have a little bit more of that
Maybelline master conceal in a flat top
brush and I'm going to tie to clean up
the brow a little bit we honestly
cleaned up like this does not look that
bad it's like there's going to be a
trend throughout this video of me saying
oh it's not that bad which will reads me
a little bit for the eye of today I'm
reading one of my all-time favorite
policy of morphia 35o palette of course
this is not the real one
we got the sequin it's Angie for sixteen
dollars and this is a real one that we
chose for 22 and honestly they look
almost exactly identical but we're going
to put it onto the tendency probably
actually swatch and apply there off with
this medium warm brown shade right here
and use it as a transition in my eyelid
oh no whoa okay - kitchen that's not
what I want I'm not finna grab an M
4-3-3 and I'm going to dip into this
dark brown shade down here and I'm going
to darken up the outer crease okay for
some reason this I is like blending out
okay and this is just like watching a
patched central up in here
awful but this my like not bad I'm going
to have a clean blending brush and I'm
going to go over the under sisters kind
of one so a little bit more than that
first shot it was a whole lot more
pigmented than I would anticipate but a
little better grab this shade right up
in here with AF flops up concealer brush
I'm going to apply that light on the
inner corner just run off with honestly
the maps were very very much impressing
me shimmer shade definitely is no
comparison to the real one - Morphy
these are like ridiculously ridiculously
dry and I did what my brush a little bit
- I don't know how that actually worked
but they really not look good this is an
awful issue taking it way too long to be
able to layer up a how to create that I
really should and that is the shadow all
done this my honestly looks pretty good
Vince I on the other hand definitely
needs a whole lot more work it just is
really not blending out so it was
sixteen dollars is not awful to master
see fit the shimmer assembly are not
more equality honestly the way better
off to spending the extra eight dollars
in getting the North through California
two dollars and of course you can do so
the chains as we all know for 10% off
your purchase well it's okay but I would
definitely say it find the extra money
get the real version for latter day I
picked up the Jade lashes in the style
902 black they are the most similar
luscious I could find to approach my
favorites because logic electronics so
I'm just going to a copy on tonight and
he's worth two dollars the last bed is
like super super or worked and it's like
going in all sorts of different
directions live with yourself whether or
not I'm going to be able to glue this on
it should be just saying I mean honestly
these are kind of pretty
I go to for you stuff like three of them
together they live me like a pair like
on it whatever I want a lot and we li la
girl floss liner I did buy this
essentially if it's not really a
knockoff I was way too scared and it's
way too dangerous to use like a fake
product in your eye not going to mess
around without today everybody Arabic
means my Holy Grail the benefit roller
lash once again not going to mess around
with that area that is both eyes often
see we're going to go ahead and move on
to the highlighter now for today so I'm
using the on apostate location gleam I
did used to have the areal version of
this but it was broken on airline
I'm not as far as folks you've never
ever checked your makeup this is what
the house looks like at first glance
there's our a and nail marks in the
starburst which is really strange
considering edges opening it's now how
leaders look like okay they don't look
bad in any way shape or form but I
definitely remember the original palette
the hard candy and the crushed pearl
shades are a lot more pink so I guess
we're just going to put these on we're
going to see how they look it's not
awful definitely is not like Nastasia
normal pigmentation up in here because
you guys know that those little kids are
like Oh
blinding it to the gods but I want to
hate it when I can it smells like oh my
go to some like a sneaker store that's
what it smells like I feel like I'm like
walking to the idols of adidas right now
oh my god I'm like scared to know is
what kindness now now that the Holi is
done similar to the eyes this probably
is not that bad but it's definitely not
the same pay attention is quality as
original brand I would definitely
recommend this verging on the Logans but
I guess it's doing the job for today
laughs it's certainly not leads to this
video of course we had to do it lips and
what other brain has more feet than a
highly cosmetic
ever since telling us begin their event
so many scales the people getting
pigmented of 6 and older Lisa from the
cows describes an almost I love website
so of course I had to pick up a fake
Kylie lip kit maybe picked up the shade
exposed this put the lipstick was three
dollars so it's definitely beat the
price of Title 18 but let's do a little
bit of tap and see how it compares
oh my god that's very very pungent
we literally felt like paint this is
where we'll put this on my lips putting
it on I can like taste with smell of
paint the color is actually kind of
ready to go
so basel syphilitic I do really really
like the color I don't have the kindly
actual lipstick in the shade exposed to
compare it to but in general the code is
actually really pretty over the white it
has been about two or three minutes that
actually applies to simplistic and it is
still not fully dry down which is
definitely not a great thing I like
Kylie's lips tutorial because it does
write down a pretty fast and it is
comfortable to wear this is getting dry
but as of like whole bit sicky never fun
because no one kid like these crusty
bits up in here and that is never going
for a liquid lipstick where every
dollars done I don't pay that alright
guys and the crysta completed look that
I created using all knockoff makeup
product looking in the mirror I honestly
do not look it's awful as expected
myself to it is definitely not the
classic James Charles Graham but it
could be a whole lot worse but Lee's
products were pretty comparable to the
originals but overall I definitely would
not be adding any of these to my
everyday and makeup routine this said
almost $150 and all these products
combined which is definitely not that
cheap considering all the stuff is fake
and not the real thing
I definitely recommend spending a few
bucks extra to get the real product and
just get the full quality and making
sure that you're getting at the right
thing it's honestly super-agents video
and I did get pretty lucky my skin is
not reacting poorly I'm not going any
breakouts yet but I would definitely
keep you guys posted on my Twitter and
snapchat over the next few days
hopefully that something's destroyed my
skin often times fake makeup can contain
a lot of chemicals and gradients that
can really mess up your skin and your
immune system so I'm hoping that this
doesn't go with real self real stuff is
gonna fight like this on that being said
I hope you guys enjoyed watching all
this awful stuff on my face today if you
did it please make sure to give it a big
thumbs up down below and determine I'm
not ready if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter
they are both just James Turrell and my
snapchat and you down for more behind
the CSI stuff our day of Charles Podesta
ask dr. char
alright stitchers thank you so much for
watching and I will see you in the next
one bye
[Music]