hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
happy holidays sisters I hope everyone
is having an absolutely amazing week
this year apparently Santa has decided
to bring me a sty I have not been able
to put on makeup for six days now which
has been so incredibly inconvenient if
you've been following me on snapchat you
know that literally a few days ago it
was so swollen that I could barely even
open it so now we have definitely made
improvements please do not leave any
comments I am well aware of the fact
that I look like I am looking in two
different directions
we're just gonna roll with it I have to
get this video done for today's video
have something actually super super fun
plan that I am very excited to do in
honor of the holiday season
obviously the holiday times it's time to
see your family at time for friends love
laughter lots of good food and also the
season of giving I personally love
giving gifts to all my friends and
family it is so much fun for me to be
able to think of really really cute
things just to give back to the people
that mean the most to me and this is
gonna be the first year that I'm
actually not setting up my family on
Christmas I'm gonna be here in LA all
alone so in order to compensate for that
I force all my close friends to give me
gifts no but in all seriousness today's
video is going to be doing a full face a
youtuber Christmas presence I hit up all
my favorite content creators that I
really really love and look up to and I
assigned each one of them 1/7 my makeup
routine and they all picked out a
surprise product and hopefully we can
come up with a good luck by the end of
it without further ado I have my Santa
hat on or to get into the Christmas
spirit of opening all these cute gifts I
have a ton of pockets here in front of
me for all of my favorite youtubers and
some of your favorite youtubers so if
you see someone you love it don't forget
to give this video a big thumbs up
especially if you are enjoying it and
let's get started so let's get right
into this routine and you guys know our
first step was always going to be to
prime our face so our first Christmas
gift today it's what my favorite sister
Sofia 9-yard
so along with every gift each creator
sent me a short cute little video
explaining why they picked what they
picked let's see what Sofia got hello
James Merry Christmas I sent you this
Urban Decay quick-fix
Hydra charge complexion prep priming
spray I also bought myself another
sample size I don't usually use like
primers that you put on with your hands
I like to spray stuff on my face so
that's why I send you this and I hope
you like it
I feel like I don't have as much
experience with primers as you probably
do but I do like this one and it smells
nice when it goes on your face anyway I
hope you like it
Merry Christmas again and a Happy New
Year
thank you sister Sofia so now that our
piece is all primed ready to go our next
up is going to be a foundation and for
this I assigned it the queen of skin
talk to us Brock hey sister James so by
now I'm sure you have looked in the bag
this is the lemare soft fluid liquid
foundation that is expensive but it is a
miracle product and I'm curious what
your thoughts are on it you already have
pretty awesome skin but I think that it
is time for you to branch out and try
new things that are not your makeup
forever stick foundation oh okay I hope
you love it
I'm curious to see how your luck turns
out and I love you lots
Oh so mama Westbrook wanted to come for
me today I see how it's gonna be shot
see let's go ahead a plan is talk to you
got me shade number ivory Oh - so
hopefully it is a good match for my skin
it's a good match you guys know I'm
definitely a very very full coverage
type of Queen even when I'm doing a more
natural look I'll still use a light
foundation and just sheer out I would
normally never reach for a foundation
dish share but I actually feel like it
layered beautifully on the skin so I'm
very excited to keep using this and
trying it out thanks sister Tati
so our next step is gonna be to hide our
under-eye bags and make our face nice
and bright like the star top of the
Christmas tree and for this we're gonna
be using concealer which is sent to me
by it Nicole Concilio hey James its
sister Nicole so my gift to you is tart
shape tape because I really feel like
that was such a staple product of 2017
it was everybody's favorite and I know
that you really like it too so I wanted
to give you a nice gift for the holidays
merry kisses thank you sister Nicole
sent me the shade light which is
actually the strange that I use all the
time so she's that like a true sister
let's go down apply this on all the
right places son sister toffee sent us a
very very light coverage foundation
today obviously you guys know shape tape
it's a very very full coverage so I feel
like these two will balance each other
out really nicely to create a beautiful
base okay so now that the foundation
that conceals are all in place obviously
we have to
to Arkansas it lasts all day long and
for this I signed no other than sister
Patrick stir we all know he's the
full-coverage Queen he always wears tons
and tons and tons of powder but he still
looks flawless somehow so I figured it'd
be the perfect person to give me the
best powder ever hey superstar happy
holidays and ears when I say grab have
to start powder and Patrick Fulop what's
the best gift ever who doesn't let a
juicy lip glass shiny look on the lips
with a classic red it's definitely so so
beautiful and I'm the powders that you
make flawlessly it's so so gorgeous then
I hope you guys love it for this holiday
season
I'm Pascal and Merry Christmas Oh hot
chicks new lip gloss is also in here -
I've actually been rocking this a lot
lately
so this'll be the perfect lip later on
thanks Patrick for chronic turks that I
have a package from one my all-time
favorite youtubers Rob Beauty by
Christie she sent me this pocket right
over here let's see what she got us hey
sisters today James asked me to pick a
contour product and I was like what
product should I pick and I thought
initially
Kat Von D shade + light I know I love
that one and I know James does too but
then I thought what would James do and I
think he would use code James for 10%
off so today I decided to go with the
morphe 9 C palette so have fun
contouring and don't forget to use code
James like you ever could oh she is the
cutest ever and also this pocketing is
the cute as ever she even added a little
bow
thank you sister Christine I reckon
faces all snatch and set and place
thanks to sister Christie I literally
love her and her videos so much and
don't forget to use coach change to 10%
off this holiday season even though our
faces all chiseled out we are missing
one thing and that is blush when I think
of beautiful skin and just happiness and
beautiful rosy cheeks
I think of Alyssa Ashley
[Music]
oh this is a beautiful color thank you
sister Alyssa happy holidays from me to
you
now I'm going to dip into a little bit
more of Patrick's powder and I'm going
to bake my face so while our base is
baking in place at 350 degrees and we
are making some beautiful Christmas
cookies we're gonna move on to the
eyebrows normally I would say eyebrows
are supposed to be sisters and not twins
but obviously you want them to be as
close as we possibly can get so to start
my brows in place today I asked my
favorite set of twins to send me brow
products what's up sister I'm stuck in
bed right now unfortunately but for the
holidays I was able to send you an expo
marker for your eyebrows because I feel
like this is a very underrated product
in the makeup world and it's gonna get
your eyebrows looking nice and thick
because we love a thick sister happy
holidays oh my god what's up sis I sent
you uh what I send you I don't really
know what it is I asked my mom and she
said it was good so I sent it but it's
free I wrote wait these are actually so
good okay Grayson sent me the Kelly
Baker a brow pencil and brow definer
Kelly Baker is a legendary a brow person
hopefully I can make some combination of
this work
[Music]
I hate you Oh
joke's on you sister because this
doesn't even look that bad huh all right
nothing the bras are all snatched in
place it is a Christmas miracle if I do
say so myself
thanks a big wrecking to Vaughn to the
eyeshadow you guys don't I started
updating makeup I was in it for the
really really colorful beautiful
creative looks and when I think of
eyeshadow and really really beautiful
vibrant colors I first think of a sister
Jackie ina
hi James it's a girl Jackie O what it's
so do I really have to explain why I
chose a Pat McGrath eyeshadow palette
come on come on is fab grad like come on
seriously you Billy you Billy Pat
McGrath is not only one of my favorite
makeup artists but I really kind of feel
like you know how to push the envelope
and the boundaries when it comes to
color and playing with the eyes and
shadows so I chose one of my favorite
palettes from her collection I know that
you can put whatever your heart desires
to using that palette so good luck and
have fun
sister jockeys that we the Pat McGrath
mothership palette I've actually never
I've actually never tried it Pat McGrath
shadow before but I've heard they're
absolutely legendary Pat McGrath is an
iconic makeup artist on it very very
excited to play with this today I'm
first gonna grab the shade dark which is
this one right here on Miami for for one
and put this on my crease I'm gonna go
in pretty lightly with this because this
power actually does not have a lot of
matte shade so I really want to make
sure that this is blended out really
nicely and doesn't look too crazy next
add some holiday cheer I'm gonna grab
the shade right here called a blitz
emerald this is beautiful bright green
shade I don't want you to Sprint's it
with a little bit of settings bright and
pop this on the lid to create a halo eye
effect
well that's pigmented that's beautiful
oh my god
[Music]
and then for a bright holiday pop of
color I'm gonna grab this bronze shade
right up in here and a little bit more
settings plate and pop this right in the
center of the lid all right guys that is
the shadow I'll complete thank you
sister Jackie for such an amazing and
beautiful palette I had so much fun
check out the Pat McGrath shades they're
absolutely beautiful absolutely the
pigment is literally unreal I'm
definitely looking forward to playing
this in the future and thank you for a
challenge as well it has been awhile
instead of been able to play with color
but obviously the eyes are not done yet
we need to apply the lashes so we all
know that a good pair of flirty
beautiful lashes complete any good eye
shadow look and when I think of a flirty
beautiful sister I think of our country
gal Laura Lee let's go ahead and see
what she picked out for us today hey
James E Wayne Z so the last year I
picked for you are their little that's
just Miami our little lashes mikonos and
I picked them for you to be a good
friend because I know you love a big v
volume lash I was thinking about giving
you a little art out wispy wispy lash
which i know with sabotager look but I
didn't I just had to be a good friend
and give you a good old thick lash from
Lily lashes I hope you enjoyed them I
love you so much and I love you the best
holidays oh thank you sister Laura Lee
oh my god a good Lily laughing style you
know I just went ahead and I popped on
the lashes from sister Laura Lee I also
applied some mascara to blend together
that the real ones and the fake ones
once again please bear with me here on
the eyes I didn't really want to apply
too much mascara or any eyeliner so if
they look a little bit wonky your just
got to bear with me I'm trying not to go
blind here so now that the eyes are both
complete we are gonna move on to the
rest of the face and of course our next
step is going to be the glow when I
think of a beautiful dewy skin and the
highlight are ready to blind everybody
walking by I think of sister Jocelyn
Hill hello sister James and Happy
Holidays for this Christmas I wanted to
give you the gift of glow and because I
am extra just as we all are
I could not narrow it down to just one
highlight so I sent you three three of
like my top dog I love these three so
much so guys how you get them all to you
I love you glow get them so Q are you
kidding okay so of course Ocalan sent us
her collaboration with Becca champagne
pop we all know this beautiful and
iconic highlighter
she also sent me the Stila heavens q hi
leader I've actually never tried this
one up before as well as the makeup
rubber pigment in number and guarantee
it number 13 I love this one as well
this is definitely a recipe for a
blinding glow okay literally I'm just
gonna apply all three highlighters say
because we gotta be extra for the
Christmas season and of course gotta be
extra like sister Jacqueline so first we
make our way I'm 501 Russians have been
to the store in the shade
this calendar is really really sunny
it's like a beautiful pinky shade but
it's definitely like a glow from with an
type of highlighter not like a blinding
glow so I'm gonna go over top of it with
a champagne pop and last but finally not
least just for an extra pop of this
holiday season I'm gonna layer over top
with the littlest bit because let's be
real this is intense
love to make up forever pigment number
13 oh my god Santa and the reindeer
literally just right into the chimney
that's how bright this how it is are you
kidding Oh Jacqueline snapped
I'm gonna go ahead and live my lips
using the mock Patrick Starr lip liner
in the shade brick and then fill it in
with the Patrick gloss in the shade
Patrick
public on this red is literally so
stunning if you guys are gonna buy
anything for the Matt projects art
collection
you need this frickin lip gloss it is so
sunny I've never really been a red lip
type of person until the last few weeks
for some reason I've just been putting
it on and oh my god like I'm obsessed
you need this
thank you sister project for the amazing
collection and for the amazing gifts so
last but certainly not least our faces
obviously all complete but we have one
last step and that is to set our face in
place so it lasts all day long to all
the Christmas festivities and all the
holiday cheer and for this product I
signed it to a youtuber that I have
loved for ever have looked up to for so
long but knows absolutely nothing about
beauty and that is this sir Shane Dawson
Wow
I love Christmas promo code Christ hi
James
so you wanted me to send you a setting
spray and I don't know what that means
now it's not technically a setting spray
but it is a catnip fray called yawa
Juwanna and you're not supposed to
ingest it or have it anywhere near your
face so good luck sister oh my god well
I may not be able to attract any boys
under the mistletoe this holiday season
but at least I know I'll be able to
attract some Merry Christmas sister
Shane all right guys met is this holiday
look I'll complete using all products or
my favorite youtubers and friends I
throat Akkad I had zero idea what any of
these products were and I'm honestly so
proud of myself for holding back and not
opening it any of these presents that oh
filming this video but looking in the
mirror I feel like even though all these
products were a complete surprise we did
a really really good job and I honestly
love how this look turned out it is
clearly perfect for the holiday season I
want to say a huge huge huge thank you
to everything one of the youtubers who
sent me products for today's video this
time of year is obviously so incredibly
busy and youtubers have very very
intensely so it really meant a lot to me
that everybody was willing to take time
out of their day to not only go to the
store and find product but also go to
ups and show me all this stuff thank you
so much to everybody you all mean the
world to me if you guys are watching for
you sisters who you're watching it
definitely check the description box
down below where everybody channels will
be linked I do love everything one of
these content creators and you
definitely should subscribe to there
check them out if you have not already
if you guys did enjoyed today's video
Andrew that would have giving this
holiday season please click that big
thumbs up button down below and if you'd
like to turn the sisterhood click that
big red subscribe button and don't
forget to click the bell notification so
you can be notified every time I upload
a brand new video if you'd like to
follow me on my make up journey you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind scenes itself
is jana charles that extra pass after
charles you get to see stops my wonky
eye that i've really been able to open
or you also get to see my sister gave us
lace as i've been doing for the past few
days you guys obviously mean so so much
to me so for the past twelve days
leading up to Christmas I've been doing
giveaways every single day on my
snapchat story and giving away prizes to
all my favorite sisters now there you
are definitely gonna want to I'll be
over there and be checking my story
every day because the last you have been
really really lit not gonna lie this
week Sarah shadow goes to sister Cheryl
in thank you so much for always smiling
and supporting I love yous
so so so much and if you would like to
be the next video sister shut up make
sure always reach me via Twitter links
and they go live on Twitter all right
sisters that is all I hope for this
video today thank you so so much for
watching I hope you all have the best
holiday season ever have so much fun
with your family and friends I will not
be posting until the new year I'm gonna
be taking a few days off to celebrate
with my friends and family this year has
been so so so crazy I am so thankful for
all of you guys and I am so excited for
what 2018 has to hold you guys are not
ready you're about to be so shook we're
gonna have to wait and see love you guys
so much and I will see you in the next
one
[Music]