hi guys James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel so for
today's video if you read the title it
is going to be a review and this is the
number two of you on my channel I am
very very excited because I had a lot of
fun doing it the first one I definitely
want to do more reviews in the future
for new product comes out or you see
something that you want me to talk about
and see what my opinion is please make
sure to tweet me Earth's Napoli so I can
definitely make a video on it the new
hottest things for you guys that being
said I just got a package from a wet and
wild in the mail a few days ago editors
their brand-new mega push in a
collection it came in this cute little
cushion looking the box and right up in
here and if you open it up the
collection comes with six cushion the
collection comes with six cushion
compacts and three cushion lip creams I
have no idea how a cushion lip cream is
gonna work but I guess we are going to
find out there's a highlight a contour
as well as four color correctors which I
was super excited to try out I have
never actually used a cushion of product
on my face before I know cushion
foundations were wildly wildly popular
for a very very long time a few like
month so in the beauty scene but I never
actually put one on my face so I'm
SuperDuper excited to try them out today
looking at this collection right now it
says they are fragrance free gluten free
cruelty free and vegan as well so that
means no animals were harmed in the
making of this product which is so
amazing because I know a lot of you guys
to care a lot about that yeah so the
cushion compacts retail for $5.99 each
and the lip cushions retailed for $4.99
each so definitely super cheap and
affordable but let's go ahead and put
these products at the real test and see
how they actually apply on a face before
we go in with any actual base Parts I
want to color cracked my face since that
is what majority of the set consists of
so I'm first gonna go to the shade peach
which is the orange color corrector and
that is for dark circles so each thing
comes with this little cushion on the
inside says wet and wild on it
definitely it's super duper cute and
then it is protected as well so it can't
get dirty thank God and then when you
open it up this is what it looks like Oh
God
okay looking at this on my hand it's
super super light which is definitely
very very worrying to me I did just get
a spray tan so I am darker than normal
and this is gonna be like a concealer
looking color and as well when you do
want to correct dark circles you
definitely want a pretty light
deep or even red shade depending on how
dark your skin tone is to really combat
deep blues and the purple tones of the
dark circles so I'm not really sure how
this is gonna work but I guess let's
just go ahead and get some on the
cushion and apply it under the eyes and
see how it looks I mean the formula
feels right that this is definitely not
the right color that an orange color
corrector should be but then again Who
am I to say what a color should be so I
guess we're just gonna continue putting
this on and see what it looks like later
on since its for darkest I'm also going
to take a little more of this and I'm
gonna put this on my facial hair area
just to combat once again that the blues
and purple tones that hair gives off I
literally just shaved my entire face
like two hours ago and it's already
coming back n never heard a five o'clock
shadow before apparently when you're me
you get 12 p.m. shadow the next one over
to use is the shade green which is for
redness and once again the green is
super super light it literally looks
white on camera the other green is
swatch next to the orange on my hand
literally you can barely even tell that
there's color there normal color
correctors that I've seen before are
usually a lot deeper but once again not
gonna knock it until we put everything
else over our top and see how it really
looks like I said green color corrector
so typically for fixing redness and
honestly I'm having a decent skin day
say so I'm just gonna place this over a
few little blemishes over here
I guess I'm just gonna top the access
pot onto my nose because my nose tends
to get pretty red the other two color
factors in the collection are yellow
which brightens and then purple which
combats yellow and neither one of those
are really problems that I have on my
face so I guess I'm just gonna skip out
on those today and move right into
foundation now what I find it pretty
great about this entire collection is
that it is the magnet cushion collection
but the one product that isn't in this
collection is a cushion foundation the
kind of thing before cushion foundations
were hugely popular at one point and
even still are today I see a ton of
people using cushion foundations and
rocking them so so well so I was pretty
surprised that there wasn't a cushion
foundation in this actual collection but
I went ahead and I picked up the white
and wild photo focus foundation to go
with this look I was debating whether or
not to use the Loreal cushion foundation
or the maple you'd won because I heard
those are superbomb and I did find them
at the drugstore but I figured using the
wet and wild one are probably a lot
better just because these are wet
allowed products so I'm sure the
formulas will kind of like work a little
bit better together than the Maybelline
formula or the L'Oreal formula mixed
together might make things look a little
bit wonky I just want to get these
products a very very fair chance because
a cushion product definitely is like a
weird concept to a lot of people so
gotta be fair you feel for my foundation
today I picked up the shade a cream
beige which is actually the only color
they had left at my seat yeah so I'm
pregnant the shade matches me we're
gonna go right ahead let me try this on
okay this is not the applicator I was
it's right there it's gonna layer this
right over top of all the color cocktail
okay and it's definitely a little bit
dark too we can definitely lighten this
up a little bit of concealer later on it
do not worry
the foundation is also only $5.99 and
wet and loud is definitely not playing
around when it comes to these amazing
prices
they say girlies on a budget we got you
an major respect for that makeup
companies so crazy expensive sometimes
so it's so relieving when we see amazing
and cheap products but I don't want to
call it amazing yet I will let you guys
know in a few quick seconds alright so
that is the foundation all applied over
top of the color corrector honestly
looking at this in the mirror my face
looks so good right now and I know this
foundation is not the point of the video
but for $5.99 I'm a little bit shook to
be honest then I definitely will be
trying this again for sure and
everyday makeup routine because I really
like the base a lot moving on to the
color correctors they were definitely a
lot lighter than normal color correctors
but my darkness and my redness is pretty
even out for the multiple you can't
really see anything especially under the
eyes equally the eyes look really really
bright and nice which definitely does
not work with a lot of foundations
sometimes I'm not sure how like full
coverage this actual foundation is oh my
god the thing on the back first says
goodbye photo flash back maybe that's
why I love this foundation so much it
doesn't say the level of coverage on the
actual foundation bottle but I'm
assuming this is pretty pretty full
coverage my skin looks very very even
and I definitely like the way the color
corrector applied so once again for only
five dollars definitely it not bad I'm
liking this a lot so far what we got to
concealer once again similar to the
foundation there was no pressed cushion
concealer so I went and I picked up the
photo focus concealer I picked up the
shade of light every because once again
this was the only shade they had and
stock at my seed yes see yes you need to
step your up I'm just gonna apply
this like a normal concealer in the high
points of my face and blend it out the
one thing I have noticed about these
products is that they all dry down
SuperDuper fast including the color
correctors I know the foundation and
concealer are not like the point of this
video but like I said I wanted to use
them just to kind of formula match
they're definitely super super drying
but that means I might not have to set
my face today so I'm at the excited to
see how this turns out now that the base
of how they are all on we're gonna do
some cream contouring and for this we're
gonna use the cushion contour in the
shade cafe ah slay that name is
literally so cute I cannot get over it
but similar to the color correctors
we're gonna open up we're gonna have a
little bit of a cushion
hey cover and then the contour shade and
this one actually looks like it's a dark
color I thank God here's another thing
on the back of my hand
definitely a pretty it warm tone so this
contour is gonna be very very bronze II
who probably will not be using any
browser today but let's go ahead and put
out the actual face and see how it
applies all right so this shade is
definitely a very very very light and
like I was saying before I do have a
spray tan right now so it is barely even
showing up my face which is a little bit
disappointing to me just because the
other two shades are definitely very
very light as well so it seems like
anybody that's like dar
her than the shade mayonnaise will
probably not really be able to use this
set come on beauty brands we really need
to stop playing 50 shades of white here
there are darker people in the world
that want to wear your makeup all right
I'm just gonna dip right into my Beauty
Blender with this because of blending
this out with my little sponge is
definitely taking way too long
and I do not have a lot of time today so
I'm just going to blend this right and
using my Beauty Blender I'm gonna try to
cream contour my nose a little bit too
alright and that is the contouring and
chiseling all complete I don't hate it
it definitely looks pretty good but it's
definitely just very very very subtle
barely there type of situation this is
definitely a shade that it's going to
work for very very few people because it
is so light and bright pigmented which
is pretty disappointing like I said
before there are so many other shades of
color other than the 50 shades of white
it's particularly one it's going to be a
pass rate but I like the color corrector
so far and let's go ahead and move on
with the highlighter the last question
that I'm gonna be using is the
highlighter and this is in the shade
who's that pearl you guys know that
normally I would do my highlighter way
later on my makeup routine but I'm just
gonna do the base work today I'm gonna
do my eyes and make my eyebrows myself
off camera because this is a review not
a makeup tutorial I'm trying to get
better at like separating everything and
really learn how this type of content
works please bear with me but since this
is all eye cream and liquid base I want
to make sure that everything is like in
the right order and if I do decide to
use any powders I don't want to like
disrupt the product so this is what the
highlighter it looks like in the pan it
is a very brainy pinky tone time later
for sure so let's go ahead and grab our
little cushion now that is definitely
pretty pretty on the camera you can see
it next to do you color correctors it is
very very light it's almost like white
with just the tiniest little bit of pink
reflecting it so I'm very very worried
to see how this is gonna look on the
face hopefully doesn't give like that
great cast that a lot of highlighters
give but let's go ahead and
on NC okay so I don't know who thought
of applying highlighter with a cushion
but this is definitely not the shape of
thing that you'd want to be applying
glow with I'm gonna go to my yet Beauty
Blender and tied up buns out a little
bit
honestly it does look pretty chalky and
blending in a highlighter with a cushion
definitely will not do that again
alright let me stop while I'm ahead
before I get too crazy and then end up
taking my entire makeup off from hating
it so much this does not look awful I
really really like the color corrector
it worked very very well for me even
though it was SuperDuper light I really
like the foundation and I like the
concealer as well I guess it doesn't
really matter though because the
foundation and concealer were not really
part of this review but that's what it's
come to
now that the base is all complete I'm
gonna go into the other stuff off-camera
so I'm gonna do my brows and my eyes and
then I'll come back for the lips and
we're going to test out the lip cushions
that are in this collection so I will be
right back alright so I just threw
together this pink glowy look I
absolutely love how this turns out this
looks really really pretty on camera as
well for everything I use the I love
SATA II X color pop collection and brand
new when I use this shade over here
which is called heavy glam it is so
beautiful and very very primitive as you
can see I use it for the inner corners
and my glow as well because Laura knows
that cushion highlighter was definitely
lacking but the last thing we have on
our list today is the lips so we have
these three lip cushion shades right up
in here you have this perfectly shape
which is called a bubble gum and
paradise this bright pink which is
called a doll so hard and then this
ready orange which is called melon like
it is I'm definitely not filling the
bright pink or the bright purple so
today I'm gonna go with this ready
orange hope shade to hopefully a match
between my hoodie and the pink and the
inner corners I honestly have no idea to
be completely honest as soon as this
video is over I'm gonna replace it with
a glossy lip for the insert and photo
anyway but obviously I want to finish
the review for you guys let's go ahead
and apply this one the melon like it is
oh so yes this is what it means by a
cushion laughs okay interesting
this is strange
these are supposed to dry down Matt
watch it is definitely doing the firmly
honest thing is not awful if I'm looking
in the mirror it definitely is a little
bit patchy and Crocky I think that's
just because the applicator is
absolutely awful it's really hard to
give it like a precise line as you can
see like over here I'm Way outside of
the lip line I've hired up over a lion
as well and it is definitely not looking
even I don't know why a ball applicator
would ever be useful to anybody trying
to get a precise lip line maybe it was
just like four really really really
quick like just a like padding type
action but definitely not for like the
serious makeup liquid lipstick wearer
all right guys so does it look all
complete let's go back and recap
everything that we've tried out so far
so as a reminder we were reviewing the
Wet n Wild mega cushion collection today
we had four four color correctors a
highlight cushion and a contour cushion
and then three lip cushions in this full
set color correctors they weren't
definitely pretty good they retail for a
$5.99 each I really liked the green one
and the orange one they did a very good
job of covering up my acne and my dark
circles my skin to look super even right
now and I am absolutely loving it
especially with the foundation as well
which was not cushion but definitely
will be used by me again
that's aside from the point though the
purple and yellow color correctors I
definitely would skip how odd I'm not
saying they're bad by any means I
honestly did not even try them but I am
someone who has never ever used a purple
or yellow color corrector I personally
don't really see much of a point for
them as for the highlighting contour
shades these are definitely a bit more
of a Miss for me
the cons well honestly looked really
really pretty on my skin tone it blends
out pretty well once I use my Beauty
Blender but it was not that intense the
worst parts about is that was very very
light I have a spray tan right now and
it barely showed up on me meaning for
anybody that's darker than me which is
like majority of the entire world
population it would not look very good
it would probably would honestly look
like a highlighter shade and death was
obviously not the goal of a contour
cushion but that being said it worked
for me what I recommend it may be it
definitely depends on your skin tone as
for the highlighter this almost
definitely the worst fail of the
collection it just like a lighter
pigment
I really didn't have much of like a high
lady glow once I finished off the look I
obviously packed on a ton of that pink
Cinco shadow that I use in the
intercourse as well for the highlighter
because the highlighter was looking very
very chalky and definitely not doing it
for me as was the three lip colors
economists you really really like the
formula they went on very very nicely
they applied nicely they look nice they
feel nice the only part I wouldn't
recommend is the actual applicator of
the lip cushions themselves the ball
applicator just really doesn't make a
whole lot of sense it's messy it's hard
to get a good lip line I definitely
would not recommend but for $4.99
honestly just get it squeeze it on your
hand and then use a lip brush because I
really like these lip products after
looking at everything I honestly cannot
decide if this collection is a hit or
miss it's not very often that a group of
products is so evenly split like I feel
like there are a lot of really really
good products and there are also a lot
of things that I would literally never
use again so I'm like hardcore on the
fence right now definitely leave me a
comment down below and tell me what you
thought of each product have you used
cushion probably before let me know
what's your favorite type of stuff let's
have a mice little sisters discussion in
the comments down below because I'm
definitely open to the concept like
cushion foundation I would love to try
it more in the future and definitely I
will keep you guys posted on what they
think but for the most part there are
some good things and some bad things so
I definitely wanna hear what you guys
have to say that being said if you guys
enjoy this video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe to me I'm not ready I post two
videos a week on Mondays and Fridays and
I would love to have you join to the
sisterhood if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat and you
never work behind the scenes I said
James Charles that extra ass after
Charles alright guys thank you so much
for watching and I will see you in the
next one bye
[Music]