hi sisters James Charles here and I know
you guys are here for the video with my
mother it'll be coming in a few short
seconds today's video was supposed to be
the face shot recreation video and if
you didn't see my snapchat basically
what happened was I ended up picking a
winner for the face chart and getting
halfway through the makeup book and then
finding out that the winning entry was
not from the United States or Canada so
my lawyer called me and was yelling at
me and legally how to pick a new winner
so I just needed a little bit more time
to work on it filming at the part two of
the video the winner has been selected
so all the rules have been followed
please don't sue me the actual
recreation video will be going up on
Tuesday today's video that my mother so
I hope you guys are excited for that
it's gonna be really really sweet also
as well just wanted to remind you that
sister's apparel is relaunching today if
you guys are watching this now it'll be
up in one hour and if you're watching
this later go to sisters
entrepreneur.com to shop all of your
sisters gear I am so excited to finally
be relaunching with a partner that I'm
really really passionate about and that
I truly believe has my best interests at
heart and finally you guys will have
affordable and amazing quality merch
that'll actually get to you fast and on
time literally so beyond pumped today's
launch was a soft launch so it's kind of
a lot of the classic items you guys have
already seen with a few new pieces that
are super super cute but there are huge
huge huge things coming very very soon
for sister's apparel so I hope you guys
are excited I love you so so so much I'm
currently in Vegas when I was all my
best friends taking a much-needed mental
break but I love you I will see you on
Tuesday and I hope you guys enjoy this
video with my mother love you guys hi
sisters James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel as you guys
can see I'm currently doing a very very
special guest Chris Chris TV my mom with
Jesus right so my family is currently in
town right now my family's currently in
town for a very very special project
which makes me so sad that I cannot tell
you guys about but you'll know in a few
months I promise you and it's pretty
good and fresh my mother it was very
good in French but I was yelling on set
all day yesterday so my voice is a
little bit sister sore a little of our
sister scratchy
a little bit sister strained oh good
what I was gonna say gone but you got me
there I just wanted to do a chill that
all set down videos today and a few
weeks ago I did a video here on my
channel for iPhone the first ever makeup
tutorial
uploaded to YouTube and if you have not
yet checked it out make sure to flag
right up here it was so much fun to kind
of take a little trip down memory lane a
test out all the old and ancient makeup
techniques to try out some or all the
ancient makeup techniques the new buddy
with my mother here I'll go so my mom
brought me her entire makeup bag here
I'm seeing lots of fun things in here we
have like three brushes we have this I'm
so scared for that's my even uses I trap
yeah I can't get it I think what I think
one side is bent or something cuz my
eyebrows still want is always higher
than the other but this is my newest
addition to my collection and I do I use
it every day we can tell she's gonna be
walking me through her makeup routine
that she does every single day to look
this beautiful thank you girl
this video by the way is inspired by
sister Nicci tutorials love what the
absolute most but without further ado
let's get started yeah actually dump it
out yes carefully though be careful I
don't want you to break out honey do
Walter pears oh I didn't know we were
gonna be filming today I would I would
have tidied up oh you're right we I'm
seeing a lot of things you probably we
have somewhat covergirl powders some
Smashbox eyeshadow sacks you have a
benefit brow pencil okay kind of trendy
somewhat dandelion blush that game that
came free with my pencil from benefit
lovely tardy Beauty Linda that you
probably never cleaned an eyelash curler
it's wonderful invention right here that
I'm so excited to use and some really
good quality brushes
here's another one I think these are
brand-new to the collection remember
last time I just use this and you picked
on me
so that's why on the carbon no no okay
I got those two look look oh these are
wearing the garments - okay what he's aa
flat so I use the found a great and then
do use a beauty blender to blend it in
yes how many squares would you usually
do I don't I don't know I don't count I
just put a little bit on and look how
much you polka then you put on like my
hand
well it's gonna be too light for me
[Music]
we're gonna turn me into flashback Mary
it's okay so how long have you been
wearing makeup for um I started wearing
makeup probably at the age of 14 so 51
minus 14 is quite a while 37 years Wow
Wow
from doing makeup when you were just a
young little sister to now how would you
say your makeup routine has changed well
it really hasn't changed that much until
just recently until you became a makeup
artist right then we started getting PR
packages in the mail on a daily basis
and I would snatch y'all know we bought
I borrowed some new products right I
just again started using brushes after
you left a bunch at home when you move
to besides that I always use my
applicators that you just threw in the
garbage which I'm a little sister sad
about thank you okay oh and eyebrows
I've never put on eyebrows before until
just recently that that's new for me too
and I'm that's my biggest struggle my
eyebrows because I cannot even with my
stencil I still can't get him even okay
so after the foundation I would use this
and this is brand new sue I never used
this is called what concealer concealer
I usually just put it right under my
eyes that's a yes that's more than I
usually put on but yes
[Music]
perfect and I would take the
Beautyblender and I would lend it out
yeah in middle school when I started
wearing makeup I remember I used a lot
of black liquid eyeliner and I put it on
and I used so recently again until you
told me otherwise I would put it on the
black eyeliner under oh yeah under my
eye what's next next I would this eye
shadow every day I use it every day I
use the powder us no not yet I like I
let the liquids so can I use this
eyeshadow uh-huh this is a NYX I think
and this brush this is for the next this
is for the darker okay and what do you
do with that I just put it on my eyelid
so lover yeah yes just one color yep
this is in the shade Shira just a kiss
you want to kick with my mom every day
okay that's all that's enough
okay and now did the other one I'm
working on it thank you excuse me
[Music]
beautiful yeah that's it right there
okay the next step I take my second
brush and I use just this color here
okay what preciousness oh I can't see it
morph em2 13 m2 13 ohms code James for
10% off that's right and I just put it
in that the latest color and then just
put a little bit on under my brow
actually from from the lid all the way
up to the brow I put some color on
that's all up here yeah mm-hmm next step
I take this black liquid liner and
instead of putting it under knees like I
used two years ago I just put it on on
top okay how long does their makeup
version take you in the morning five
minutes
well I do my first step and then I'll
tell you when I take and then I go
downstairs and I have my coffee and my
granola bar and then I go back up and
then I do the second steps what your
first that's you like the Hat like
everything you've done so far yeah and
then I go downstairs and have my coffee
and my granola bar and then I come back
up and then I put my pressed powder in
my blood shot cause you like to let the
foundation sink yeah yes why somebody
somebody told me that oh that's not me
[Music]
it's taking away too long I would have
been done minutes ago well maybe if you
hadn't heard that wasn't from highway
2003 this would be working okay so next
you would curl your lashes okay and then
you would apply a mascara this is the
Smashbox super fan fan Thomas hero one
coat on top and then a little bit
on the bottom and you already have
beautiful long eyelashes James but a
little bit you up a little bit on the
bottom see but you're you're taking way
too long I would have been
I'm much quicker come on I want to get
to the next exciting step okay why is
the mattress having sub next oh my god I
just I used it just to just to get it
started what do you want talk a little
bit about your eyebrows in general James
I don't have a lot of hair to begin with
we're gonna get my eyebrows fixed maybe
oh yeah do you guys wanna see a video
where we get my mom's eyebrows
microplane I didn't talk about like her
brow journey let me know the comments
down below because I'd love to fix that
[Music]
see isn't that a godsend I was losing
faith in my eyebrow ability and thank
God the Lord came and saved me with us
today is that what I look like when I
leave the house you yeah well my
eyebrows look absolutely amazing so
thank you so much you're welcome are you
being serious no they they do look
horrible I agree oh all right the next
step is powder finally yes
great so either this one or this one
host would get some packages yep let's
use Miss Ready Set gorgeous you seem to
love her a lot
do you actually use this yes honey why
is it like crusted in here no you can
use your Beauty Blender to apply powder
no I didn't know that let's do that
instead
so now you're done with the pressed
powder step you'll see yeah see now
everything looks nice and fresh I think
it all looks kind of one color beautiful
yeah yeah and then the next step would
be blush okay my third brush that I own
and then here's the blush I use Oh a
blush okay once you about there that's
enough and then just oh my god this is
so rough is it beautiful
and then I'm special occasions I'll use
this little highlighter the benefit
dandelion yeah and I use this that came
with it
mm-hmm this is why I don't use a benefit
products the LAT very last step would be
now during the week I don't wear
lipstick during the wait but on weekends
I would I put on lipstick okay and these
are your choices
let's try this one okay what is this Oh
Anasazi Beverly Hills gloss in the shade
of Kristin see that's very pretty
you look beautiful James look at that
except for those eyebrows they need
someone yeah and what time well
sometimes I use a setting spray so
sometimes if I remember I'll use the
settings right just to lock it all in
very good one for know for a real one
it's a cold and that's it how do you
feel
[Music]
what's the best product that you use the
anasazi glosses are Bob I use them all
the time too
okay this foundation it's not good all
right see now that I buy Foundation and
I will buy my covergirl powder powder
oh and the benefit bro I need to buy
this is awesome
these are good tail okay so your
favorite part was your lipstick and the
worst was my stencil but you like the
benefit product yeah all right so what
product did you like the least
all of them okay well looking in the
mirror this look is like tighter pretty
by us the eyebrows you look beautiful -
the eyebrows I can see how there are
some pencil marks in places that they
shouldn't be 60 cent plastic it was a
lot more than 60 cents but yes James
I've been getting a lot of compliments
on my eyebrows when I've been posting
like they better way better they're way
out of me and this is the reason why I'm
telling you James yes there it's not
perfect but I yes I I would not read
home without this and this alright
scissors and that no that is it for
today's youtube video this was quite the
wild ride but thank you mom for walking
me through your beauty routine and
regardless of how copy these products
are used to look beautiful on a daily
basis so that's all that matters I guess
thank you I think every time I do these
videos people love to comment and say oh
my god James you're so ignorant so rude
not everybody used to put on as much
makeup as you do and I'm like no I do
know that but I do makeup now for a
living
and I didn't grow up wearing makeup so
that's why having to do that style of
makeup using your fingers and using old
products is always a shock factor to me
because it's not something that I'm used
to our styles are very different and the
amount of makeup that we use is very
different but I am excited to learn the
new techniques that you have taught me
over the last couple years when you
became an Emmy way yeah speaking of next
time you need products please text me
because I will gladly send you a large
good and fresh care package and I'm sure
all the beauty brands watching this
video would also love to send you a good
care package so you don't have to use
three-year-old experiment on all right
sisters that is all you have for today's
video thank you so much to my beautiful
mother sister Christy for joining me I
love you the observos and thank you for
coming to California it's not only film
this video but to be a part of something
very very special which we cannot tell
you guys about but that's exactly what
it was if you guys enjoy this video
today please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below on our my
beautiful and amazing mother balm how
many do you think the sisters can get
last video I
wanted 200,000 and we got there pretty
quickly
the sisters come through they do always
so this video I am going to ask for
400,000 thumbs up
alright sisters you heard the woman a
four hundred thousand thumbs up really a
sister shooting for the stars there but
I think you guys can do it also it
definitely leave us a comment down below
and tell me if you want to see a video
or we get my mom's eyebrows my hair
plaited because I'm definitely down
write you down I'm down love that also
if you've not already don't forget to
click the big red subscribe button down
below and come join The Sisterhood along
with me and my mom and seven million
other wonderful sisters out there I love
you guys all so much I'd love to have
you join the family also click the bow
icons Suki notified every time I upload
a brand new video if you like to follow
me on my makeup journey you can follow
me on Instagram and Twitter they're both
just James house and my snapchat for
more behind the scenes and stuff is
James Charles in that extra eyes dr.
Charles if you like to follow my mom on
social media you can find our Instagram
Christy b19 she comets back to people
literally all day long so we're gonna
talk to her she's there
this video is sister Xiao de Costa
sister Bailey thank you so much love for
always falling and supporting you don't
let me literally get so so so much that
if you like to be the next videos sister
shout out don't forget to always retweet
my links when I go live on Twitter all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching I love you and I'll see you in
the next one bye