[Music]
hi guys it's James Charles welcome back
to my youtube channel I really wanted to
film a really fun look this week so I
asked you guys on Twitter what you
wanted to see and almost all of you guys
said do a challenge I do and I was so
down I've been doing a lot of tutorials
so I thought it was finally time for me
to challenge myself and do a challenge
video a lot of challenges in one
sentence since I just got myself a new
pair of very very very pointy stilettos
I might be a perfect day to put my
morphe brushes into retirement for a
little while and do the no brushes
makeup challenge I decided to be this
pinky rose cut crease with the glitter
liner and honestly I'm very very proud
of how it turned out it was not easy but
I love the finished look so if you want
to see her created this using not a
single makeup brush make sure to keep on
watching I'm gonna start out as always
priming my face using my benefit
Porefessional primer this is totally the
easiest step of this tutorial
considering I always prime it using my
hands anyway we're just what I like to
do it
this is about to go downhill real fast
so brace yourselves for condition today
I'm going to use my makeup forever
Ultra HD foundation stick but I guess
since putting it on this way we kind of
be like cheating I'm going to rub it
into my fingers and then put it on that
way oh wow and now I guess we're going
to start to by the side of my fingers
okay okay this could be a lot worse this
is not as bad as I was thinking yet
knock on wood because we all know that's
gonna change in about 15 seconds
for concealer today I'm going to use my
two-faced we're on the suede concealer
in the shade very fair and I'm just
going to tap this in under my eyes and
all around the face using my own finger
once again well is this the first
challenge opening up my channel this is
not the first challenge I've actually
done I haven't tried a lot of the other
challenge that I've been floating around
YouTube but just in my own time they
have been very very fun but this one is
alarmingly dangerous with the set of
nails that I just acquired today I'm
going to quickly say under my eyes using
my code here some powder am at the shade
of translucent and once that's packed
under the eye just revising over to take
more about my entire hand and
really beat my face to contour my face
today I'm going to be using my Too Faced
milk chocolate Soleil bronzer oh holy
crap I'm feeling extremely patchy right
now and it's getting on my last nerves
but there's something I could really do
to fix that I guess so I'm going to go
ahead and bake my face using my fingers
once again in my co2 your thumb powder
[Music]
how many go ahead and let this week for
a few minutes fingers crossed this
contour gets a little bit cleaner
because it right now this looks awful so
I will be right back in a second we can
go on the rest of the face all right I'm
gonna go ahead and do you guys in so we
get started on the eyes to do this
problem I'm going to start off by
dipping my nail into a Nastasia dip brow
in the shade evany this is where having
a lot of nails really is coming in handy
and then to tidy up the bar a little bit
I'm gonna take some room this way once
again on the tip of my finger nail and
just go under the brow I need you to
stay right there don't move once I have
the relative loopy and I'm just going to
take the remainder of the concealer on
my finger and blend that in as well as
cover my eyelid for my outlets today I
decided to do a cut crease I know I just
did one recently on my channel but I
wanted to do a little bit of a simpler
one for you guys at home and I know
Hokies will be super super hard to do
with just my fingers so I wanted to
challenge myself I'm gonna start off by
drawing that bottom line of the crease
using my fingernail and a cherry cola
from makeup geek
and then I'm taking a tiny bit of morphe
brick shadow and on my pinky I'm gonna
start to blend in that line okay I guess
that's this ghost we're going to get so
I'm gonna go back in now with cherry
cola once again on the tip of my finger
nail and to find that crease line a
little bit more this is definitely a
challenge to say the least and not as
easy as I was expecting getting to like
product in the flicks that I wanted to
is extremely easy having nails this
pointy but actually blending out the
product is extremely hard because I
really have access to my fingertips
because um the nails in the way and then
to finish off the cut crease I'm just
going to define it a little bit more
using anasazi a beauty mark behind of my
brow bone I'm going to mix together the
pink and the white shade from The Oprah
Beverly Hills highlighter
now normally I would go in with some
concealer underneath this crease just to
really really cut it and make it super
sharp but today I'm gonna be doing some
glitter liner underneath the crease
knives gonna be kind of my cut so I
don't even need to worry about it for
the glitter liner I'm gonna dip my nail
into my mehron mixing medium and just
draw a thin line right under the
concrete and then dipping right into eye
candy glitter in a double bubble I'm
gonna press that glitter right into the
adhesive well I guess now we're going to
try to do a wing I am immediately
regretting this and I haven't even
started yet but I'm going to dip my
fingertip into more via gel liner in the
shade in Slate and pray
holy crap I can't believe I actually
just said that okay
not the best wing liner but definitely
not the worst for my lower lashline Oh
goodies makeup geek bit and and just
quitted by pinkie and smudged out into
life oh okay so apparently that didn't
work too well so instead I'm going to go
to the bidding on at the tip of my nail
and bout that into my lash line I heard
like the lower lash line was missing
something so I just did my finger back
into the mayor of mixing game and into a
double bubble and just pop it a little
bit on the inner corner her mascara
today I'm gonna be using my usual
benefit roller lash but since I can't
really use the spoolie tie brush I'm
going to put some on my finger and then
try to apply it that way and pray that I
don't get it all over my eye hey this is
actually kind of working yes to finish
off the eye look I'm gonna pop on at the
bottom eyelashes in the style I go home
I'm gonna go ahead and do the other eye
off-camera now I promise I'm so gonna do
the challenge though this is much more
fun than I anticipated it's currently
2:00 a.m. but I have to wake up for
school in like 4 hours
lovely so I really need to focus and get
this done I'll be right back and we can
go ahead and finish the face and the
rest of the look okay there we go I
finished the second I literally 45
minutes later but you know what they
look good I'm happy with it
let's move on the Holly my face today
I'm gonna be mixing together the pink
and white shades again from The Oprah
Beverly Hills High later it's one of my
face and you can use code James Charles
for 30% off okay that actually looks not
bad at all and lastly to finish off this
look I'm going to very very very
carefully apply anasazi liquid lipstick
in the shade it's a girl and there we go
guys that completes this no brushes
makeup challenge thank you
all in all I'm really not too happy with
my skin I don't think I'll be putting on
my foundation with my fingers anytime
again soon but honestly the eyebrows
eyes lips and highlighter all really do
not look that bad I'm pretty proud of
myself for what I was able to achieve
there definitely some experts out there
who did much better than me okay
tutorials but I've burned out of myself
for succeeding and definitely of trying
to challenge myself if you guys did
enjoy this video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you haven't already on
those videos every single week I'd be so
happy for you to join the family if you
like to follow me on my makeup journey
my Instagram and Twitter are both Jake
Charles booty it's a wonderful time and
if you'd like the more a private life my
snapchat is James Charles the next your
ass after Charles alright guys I think
that is over this video thank you so
much for watching I will see you next
time bye