hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I am
very excited for today's video but I am
even more excited for Friday's new video
because it is the official world
premiere of my show
instant influencer I cannot believe that
the day is finally here it is in less
than one week this is that so crazy I
literally have never been more proud of
a project in my entire life and I cannot
wait for you guys to see it in case you
don't know insta influencer is my
reality competition show executive
produced and host long with you two
originals and a search to find that the
next Beauty superstar it'll be streaming
right here on my youtube channel for
free starting this Friday April 24th at
12 p.m. Pacific Standard Time and I
literally can not wait make sure you
guys set your alarms I hope you're as
excited as I am but we still got a few
more days to go in our countdown
so until then let's jump into it today's
YouTube video as you all know right now
we're going through a global pandemic
because of Koba at 19 we are all doing
our best to stay at home and stay safe
and stay healthy in order to beat this
together and because of this quarantine
there's been a major surge in the app
called zoom if you don't know what zoom
is basically it is like an online of
video chatting software similar to
FaceTime or Skype where you can keep in
contact or host meetings with large
groups of people a lot of teachers have
been hosting zoom classes with their
students to conduct their online classes
I've had to use that a bunch different
times for business meetings that I
couldn't actually get to in-person but
overall a lot of people are just using
it to stay in touch with their friends
first today's video I thought it'd be
really fun to try to you zoom in a
slightly different way by the way this
video is not sponsored and now that I'm
thinking about it I really should have
reached out beforehand because this is
literally an infomercial anyways I
tweeted earlier telling you guys to grab
your friends and grab your makeup
collections and tweet me at your Zoo ID
and passcode and now I'm here in my
studio with Mya makeup collection I have
nothing on my face right now so I
thought it would be super fun to pop in
and surprise you guys under different
zoom calls and get ready with you let's
get started
[Music]
okay you guys we have our zoom open and
ready to go and I think it is time for
our first meeting and we'll type in a
zoo well yeah go ahead so it's gonna
glam for a few minutes and I'm going to
talk to you guys about whatever you want
I have been at birth I was really
enjoying it because I was getting so
much work done filming so many videos
like getting prepared for show but now
that it is like you know a few weeks in
I'm not gonna life and getting really
really overwhelmed stuff with just so
much I just like think and get in my
thoughts and like deal with stuff so
it's been like a little bit spooky but
I've been trying to just like get work
done replied a lot of business and I'm
also watching congratulate you on how
positive you are your fans when they
write all these funny comments and I
were watching you putting on different
funny think up to respond to the word I
don't know stepsisters say say alright
guys well I have my base done so I'm
gonna hop off and go say hi to some
other sisters but thank you for guys
stay safe wash your hands and stay home
oh you guys so for this zoom chat it's
apparently one of the girls 21st
birthdays so I want to pop in and say
hello and sing happy birthday as well so
let's jump into number two okay I really
want to end is literally like well I
figure collections we've ever made my
thing is I'm just like the right time
because right now I might be waiting a
little bit longer into another well I
wish you guys
[Music]
oh this is so so so happy thank you well
how would you say like positivity so I
kinda nice eco you have so much hate
when the date night sense um I really
tried to like not let it get to me to be
honest I know that sounds so stupid to
say it but like really like surrounding
myself with good positive people and
friends that I can like talk to and
bounce things off of and might just be
way of like is honestly like what helps
me get through the day focusing on the
positivity and something I continue this
like a way better solution already looks
like it says there's less than a minute
left and I finished my contour say hello
to some more sisters but thank you so
much I think science want to say James
thank you for like amazing I hire to
like sneak and buy my makeup like this
is all fully from behind my parents back
and OH - oh you know it's like it's
really too cold but I keep getting to do
this and like I feel so like inspired by
darling first off I'm talking to you and
like all these people here like the
sisters is so special and like it's just
incredible so thank you all I have at I
shadow on a simple brush nice but like
I'm making it work I feel so thank you
so so so happy and I'm immediate are
well to me like my videos give you the
confidence to do that and I really
really really hope that one day in the
future like your parents will see you
and will like love this would be just as
proud of you for expressing yourself and
wearing makeup as you feel on the inside
when you're actually doing it back makes
my day so thank you guys
[Music]
I see that you're already I'm gonna do
my brows oh can I chill with you guys
for a little bit and do my brows with
you what's your favorite song okay it's
a song called 2002 by Emily it's okay
it's such a bomb okay so I can't ever
well your eyeshadow looks a beautiful so
far thank you okay you guys well
eyebrows are all done so I have to head
into another route to supply some more
sisters but thank you both so much for
me the sweetest and freedom I love you
Jai well alright let's do another zoom
call and this one I know for thought is
filled with a bunch of Maya loyalists
and accounts that I've known it since
like day one I was headed to pop in and
surprise him and do my eyeshadow
together oh my god Zoe you have the day
one Martin oh yeah picked what I talk
that I do as well see I love that you
guys are the way my marketing team you
want me to do a nice little fix my
brother into influencer logo like make
it look like splatter beauty he'll like
it is in the right clothing - oh okay
team know your singing has been
improving so much I was wondering like
are they make a poundage that I could
like do myself so that's our and some of
them aren't
what's cool about into influencer is
that it's not just a makeup competition
show and I'm really excited for people
to see that because the reality is that
big influencer is so much more than just
being good at makeup like what about
marketing and we want to sell products
with other people yeah so the challenges
that are on the show really focus a lot
I'm like what it takes to be successful
influencer not what it takes to be
successful makeup artist all the time is
going to do with Lika but they're not
all just makeup focus okay thank you
guys so much I appreciate you ever see
one of you so so much love you guys see
you soon okay you guys so that soon call
was literally all of my biggest stand
accounts that I am so incredibly
grateful for I love them and they picked
a super cute eye shadow look eyelid
obsess that how this is turning out
right now I would've an undo the other
one off camera quickly just we can save
some time and I'll be right back to join
in on a few more sisters alright you
guys we are back with both eyes all
complete I finished the other I added
some lashes and mascara and I am
literally so obsessed with this insane
influencer logo inspired look the colors
are so cute and I love doing the
splatter paint effect I've done a few
different times I didn't turn before but
never would this color combination and I
literally love it so much you're almost
out of this look it's been a few hours
now so I'm hoping that there are still
some of you guys on zoom' let's head
into our next meeting and like I said
meeting Oh picture of me as their
green-screen bang I can see all of you
guys 1113 people blah and like sometimes
yes it does like you have done the exact
attention that they want but I would
rather like just not see that type of
comment or energy like it's just like
really
so like another does know how to do it
all right you guys well I thought it's
my highlighter so I need to
thank you all so much for three times
but you sign my nut canes oh my god
I'm with you guys because we're on our
final set which is going to be at the
lips so you guys get to pick what do you
guys think that I should I have
literally anything what do you think I
should do feel like I think you should
go for can we throw in a sparkly blossom
is it definitely do a neutral look with
a sparkly gloss thanks to you guys I'm
not officially done with my makeup look
I love every single one of you guys so
so so much thank you for letting pop
when you're cold and everybody stay safe
and healthy I love you guys all right
you guys I suppose several hours several
sister surprises later that is as a
makeup look chosen completely by you
guys on zoom' meeting is all complete
this video was literally so much fun to
do and I am obsessed with how the
finished look turned out oh my god I
cannot wait to go take selfies in a few
minutes obviously right now the world is
going through a very very tough time and
you guys are truly what helps me get
through every single day it was so
lovely getting to see all of your
beautiful beautiful faces don't forget
that my brand new show instant
influencer starts streaming for free
right here on my youtube channel this
Friday April 24th at 12 p.m. PST we are
on the search to find the next Beauty
superstar in the end only one person can
take home $50,000 and become the
first-ever instant influencer if you
guys enjoy today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and share your love and support it
really does help me out so much if you
have not ready makes you click that big
red subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we were 18 million a
sister strong and I would love to have
you join the family and also sleep
so you don't use every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on my makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram Twitter tick tocking Facebook
for all these James my snapchat for more
behind the scenes ice up its James
Charles electric ass after Charles and
also if you want to get text from me yes
on my personal phone number right here
for any exclusive videos merge updates
and everything else my number is three
one oh nine oh five eight seven four six
this videos sisters how that goes to
Sister Dee thank you so much love for
always following good supporting I love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be the next videos sister channel
don't forget to always reach people
putting links in they go live on Twitter
all right you guys thank you so much
watching this video today I will see you
I'm fighting for the mayor pins the
influencer stay sieve wash your hands
and most importantly stay home I love
you guys see you in the next one
[Music]