me antennae are rocking back and forth
and Huggy not because we love each other
because we were both horrified yeah
we're about to do something that no
beauty guru has ever done before a
beauty guru now no job no straight in
your community right the community is
just fine today we were building a get
ready with us in our private helicopter
I don't like Heights
Tanner doesn't either I don't know how
we did this literally Tanika not even
convinced you to papered over SUV so I
don't know how I just bookies before
chopping come on we're not gonna be the
next brand I'll use code sister James
for a helicopter I'm honestly horrified
but there's no other person in the
entire world that I want to be doing
this with wanna see yo if we go down we
go down together sister Rick finish mom
and dad sisters I love you guys all so
much
if I die you probably are legend it's
too late my sister Lisa if I die mom and
dad and sisters I love you guys so much
and I think we've had enough of the
ground with the fence boring yeah the
girls so boring I totally want to be in
there ain't no do they make up let's go
[Music]
and I love the ground
I needed a friend to talk to and almost
four hours late to the conversation
me to be a little more tape and no
that's not a traditional friendship but
that's definitely what a lot of you may
not know Buffy is I'm kind of always had
the business mindset that I do now I
made money off when I was 11
I was like oh marketing is just to get
people really talking I think you're
very much the same way and this people
we're gonna keep coming back and
watching there's a lot of marketing that
goes
I think one of the people's and berating
things for me is that what other brands
work with me or somebody's posting about
me oh my god yes I absolutely have if
you took three seconds to do research
that's James Charles and I'm so sorry -
every single sister who likes makeup I
don't deserve to be here
you need like a Geoffrey start actually
service up here can't do my brows on the
ground let alone
[Music]
okay like relative Oh everything one of
your compilation of all the routine I
make sure when taking the photo
- likely back to where like my shoulders
are significantly at an angle behind
like my legs and ass and then flex my
stomach muscles so that the first thing
I can do in space soon is details so it
looks like it's yellow like today where
I got details it's very crazy though I
feel like in LA especially no one does
it okay that's why I think it's so funny
when I get called out for all the time
whenever it's like oh thank god hello
like I look amazing do you think I look
like that person but everybody I've seen
all your faves before and afters because
I edit a lot of people's pictures I just
know and since your days on the base
tune a lot of different people you guys
like when I see the reporters in this
what do you what do you guys think my
energetic oh you're
it's wrong with everything someone you
almost get into my zone which is toxic
it's not okay but it's like it becomes
easier to just take the latter option
because you don't want to deal with the
criticism it's like people criticize you
until they push you to a point where
they for you to expect perfection of
yourself except when you're acting like
that they're mad at you and they call
you babe that's that brings us back to
our very first
are you putting on boxes already first
of all I could see us like getting good
at this it's like doing your makeup in a
car I had to do it for red carpet oh my
god I look into the winged eyeliner look
hello look at her she's good
[Music]
for the fact that we did this in a
helicopter I like my makeup generally
does not look that bad and I'm honestly
kind of happy with it but for being the
queen of noses I just realized I forgot
to highlight mine today so I'm scared
hi sister sister Tana here not really
not satisfied with my makeup sister I
was really hoping I can snatch my nose
better next time to Shara's love you if
you guys didn't do this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and support and
really does mean so much to us
definitely psycho this won't tell us
where do you want to see us get ready
now oh my god mister get ready series
eyewear - you know what I had so much
fun today if you guys have not ready
make sure that big red subscribe button
down below comfort the sisterhood is a
pretty lit time put that Bell icon to be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me on a
maker attorney can follow me on
Instagram
they're both the same Charles and my
snapchat before I had the tea sighs have
the same choice that extra pass after
Charles we can find it off if you want
to find her my name is yeah I don't know
this video sister shadow goes to sister
wait why are we still hugging this
ministry this video sister chowder go
sister Edgar thank you so much love boys
all I kept deferring it I love you so so
so much and if you'd like to the next
videos sister shadow reach the base
region video links we go live on Twitter
also secondary sister show there goes to
sister Robin who flew us here he got us
back here alive thank God in one piece
thank you go check him out alright guys
that's all for this video I love you so
much I will see you in the next one
[Music]
you