[Music]
hi guys its James Charles welcome back
to my youtube channel first off I just
want to say it thank you guys so much
for 200,000 subscribers that is so
ridiculous and I am so thankful for all
of you guys I know I have not been the
best youtuber in the past and I know I
keep saying I'm gonna try and now I
really truly am because now there's so
many of you guys watching and I really
want to make sure that I am putting out
the best content possible so thank you
guys and I am so excited to put out more
amazing videos and show you guys so many
tutorials and show you all what I have
in store however that being said a lot
of my past videos have been some crazy
outside of the box looks which I know
you guys and myself obviously love so
for today's video I really want to tone
it down just a little bit and doing more
classic but still gorgeous glam look
which is perfect for the upcoming
holiday season I created this dark
cranberry smokey eye with double glitter
liner glow of course in this dark purple
lip I absolutely love how it turned out
as always all products and discount
codes will be listed in the description
below and if you want to see how I
created this look make sure you keep on
watching to start off this tutorial
today I'm gonna begin with my morphe 35o
palette and just wanted the light orange
shades on my morphe m4 4-1 brush this
brush is great for blending out creases
and that is exactly what I'm doing so
I'm just putting the shade right into
the crease using windshield wiper
motions and circular motions to really
blow this color out if you want
everything to be it nice and blended I'm
then going with the darker orange shade
on my m4 3 3 brush and it defining the
creates just a little bit more same type
of motions there's gonna be a lot of
different colors going on to this I want
to make sure everything is seamlessly
blended together and then with that
excess color I'm just going back in and
I'm going to shade in the eyelid same
brush same exact color once we have
those colors placed on there I'm going
back in to the m4 for 1 and the light
orange transition shade I'm gonna buff
all of those edges to really make sure
everything is nice and blended out to
begin my lower lash in I'm going into my
m4 33 and the dark orange shade from the
35o palette and I'm gonna begin to buff
it into the lash line I'm not gonna go
all the way into the inner corner
however because we are gonna be putting
a pop of highlighter there and I really
want to make sure my eyes look nice and
open
same thing from before I'm using my m4
for one in the light orange shade just
to buff over the edges to make sure
everything is super blended out we
really don't want any harsh edges with
this and it's really gonna come in handy
when we add the Purple's which is going
to be right now I'm going into the dark
purple shade from the 35b palette
friendly reminder you can use code James
for 10% off all Murphy products
I'm just using my m4 33 and brushing the
shade all over the lid just to create a
nice cranberry color repeating that same
step again I'm going back into that dark
purple shade on the M of 433 and just
dusting that shade lightly onto the
lower lash line I'm once again not
focusing that on the inner corner but
rather the outer and kind of creating
that v-shape that we know and love
unlike all of my J Charles eye tutorials
to finish off the eye shadow portion of
this look I'm going in with my m56 to
brush and the red shade from the 35 P
palette and dusting this in the crease
this is really gonna help the purple and
the orange blend together and kind of
create this like blended sunset smokey
eye type of situation you get what I'm
saying you know we're just kind of move
right out of the liner I'm using the
morphe gel liner in Slate and Maya m25
0-0 brought to create this sharp and on
fleek weight I am drawing the swing
pretty thin because I am gonna be doing
a double liner and I'm gonna be using
glitter so I'm just kind of try to keep
this pretty like subtle so it's not like
over attacking my eye this voiceover is
seriously a mess I apologize it is very
very late at night I just returned for
my trip so give me a chance and I also
ordered a microphone as well so these
voiceovers are soon gonna be a lot
better quality yeah I heard you guys
talking about it and I promise I'm
working on it anyways I'm now taking my
M
213 brush and taking that dark purple
shade that I was using before and
buffing out that black liner that I put
in the waterline just to create a nice
even transition and make that bottom
waterline SuperDuper smoky and dark then
to make sure that it's nice and blended
out and that I don't have a block I I'm
just going in once again with the m56 2
and the red shade from the 35b and just
buffing over that line SuperDuper
lightly for the double glitter liner
portion of this look I'm going with my
Mac mixing medium on my morphe gel liner
brush obviously not the same one that
had the black liner on it from before
and I'm just dipping it to my copper
alla glitter from violet Voss I figured
this glitter would match absolutely
perfectly with the cranberry and the red
and it did I really really love how this
looked I'm just super carefully laying
glitter right over top of the black
liner being pretty careful to avoid
fallout but to fix it up I'm going with
my NYC liquid liner obviously in black
this liner is super duper opaque so it
really helps to cover over any follow on
that black liner from the glitter after
putting on mascara I'm just quickly
popping on a pair of false lashes I
honestly do not remember where these are
from but if I can find the name I will
leave it in the description below I've
been wearing these for a few weeks now
and I do not remember I lost the box but
they are pretty similar to how slashes
ikonics
so definitely check those out if you
have not already and that is one eye all
completed I'm gonna go and do the other
one off-camera that we can go ahead and
get started on the rest of the face BAM
thank God for movie magic for my
highlighter today I'm going to my M a
501 brush for more feet and my Anasazi
illuminator in so Hollywood you guys
know this is like my all-time favorite
combo for glowing golden skin to finish
off this look I'm using my over liquid
lipstick in the shade of Queens it is
this beautiful dark purple shade I
absolutely love how this paired with
this look yeah that made sense right
okay anyways this ramallah is so Bob and
you can use code Jay Charles for 30% off
all their products definitely would
recommend you at checking them out and
that is the look alright guys and that
is the completed dark fall inspired
makeup look perfect for the upcoming
holiday season if you guys enjoyed this
video please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and subscribe
if you haven't already I post videos
every single week if you'd like to keep
up with me on my crazy makeup journey
don't forget to follow all my social
media accounts my Twitter and Instagram
are both just James Charles and my
snapchat is James Charles but with an
extra s at the end of Charles yeah
alright guys thank you so much for
watching and I'll see you next time bye
huh oh wait a second that is animal
that's purple lipstick Oh tell me I just
did that entire intro with purple
lipstick on my cheek oh I'm gonna