okay ready nope hi sisters james charles
here and welcome back to my youtube
channel as you guys can see today i'm
done with a very special and iconic
guy hey everyone it's jojo welcome back
to my youtube channel you guys
i
and my nightmare at the same time i have
been asking jojo to film a video with me
for literally
almost two years now two years okay and
we're gonna dive into that
too that's a lie i've been wanting to i
just haven't been wanting to do
this okay that's fair i literally said i
want to
but i just don't want to do that but now
i'm like i'm comfortable we're gonna do
it yeah
for today's video i'm giving jojo a full
on makeover no glitter no rhinestones
getting my makeup done number one is
just like a nose like
i like to do it i don't let anybody else
do it it's just to know my hair
even more so i'm nervous too because i
want to make sure that the look is
appropriate
this is gonna scar you for the next five
years there's literally so many things
that i want to talk to you about today
your rise to fame you being an internet
superstar
thank you jojo and her bobo business
mobile okay i feel like people need to
understand how much of a genius
that you actually are going on in there
jojo and i did make a business deal i
would get to give her a full
transformation
in exchange she gave me a full
transformation into jojo on
her channel so make sure you guys go
check that out it's absolutely insane
thank you for
good business and if you guys want to
see jojo in a full-on transformation a
full makeover keep on watching but this
is going to be so much fun you have to
trust me
i trust you but before we jump into
today's transformation
you obviously have quite a lot on right
now i do i went full jojo because i need
to feel
the most jojo's that way when i'm so not
like i'm no joke then like i'm good you
know
perfect well i think we should get you
changed get everything off so we can get
started on this makeover completely
fresh
okay okay here we go we'll be right back
you guys
all right you guys jojo and i are back
she has no makeup on so jojo the first
thing that i want to ask you about
before this video is today before we
even get into all the exciting things
that i want to ask you about
okay i texted you asking to collaborate
on february 7th
2019 and i said 2018
yes okay i want to do a video together
so bad where i give you a full
transformation
yes and talk about how your business
will go all these things you literally
responded and i quote
hey sorry i can't do that i did well
okay
at the time you have to think i was 15.
yes that was
a lot scarier to me because i was so
young
you know well so like this is obviously
something very very different for you
and we're doing this like full
transformation where i want to turn you
into
not an instagram body but a and just
like a glam
we met in the middle i didn't want to be
an instagram baddie but i understand
but i also was like yeah let's do
something different like i get why you
wouldn't want to do
a pink unicorn look because what's the
difference you know i feel like when i
first
wanted to do the collaboration with you
it was with good intentions like i
wanted to give you a full makeover but i
think
at that time you know a big thing in the
internet is like a lot of people think
you're like acting or this is like some
crazy character for you i
was even one of those people that made
me believe like okay maybe this is some
sort of like act like
let's go like the real jojo but like now
i'm understanding like this is the
glitters the bows
everything it's all like so many people
do you think it's a character
and like the reason why it works for me
and like where my life is how it is is
because it's not a character you know
and like i'm in charge you know at the
end of the day like it really is me in
charge obviously i have nickelodeon and
i'm a manager and i'm my mom but like
they're all working
under me if that makes sense right like
it's we everyone i work with like i
don't want to be like you're the boss or
i'm the boss like i want to just like
figure it out together yeah no yeah
that's very
we are very much the same way here at my
team lovely there's little glitter
everywhere
i know is there always glitter ever on
you yes my house like if you walk
through my house your feet will just
turn glitter oh that's great
it's insane but no i obviously like i
wanted to do a video with you always
like your james charles but i was like i
just i can't but i don't know what to do
but i can't do it but i want to do it
but i wanted it i don't know
well i think what opened back up the
conversation was honestly like when you
started posting your tech talks totally
because i feel like
we've seen you in glitters and bows and
rhinestones for so long and that is
classic jojo
i started to kind of explore yes and for
me like as a fan
i was like oh my god this is so exciting
and as a friend who would ask you to
collab i was like
oh she's giving the reveal that i wanted
makeup all the time my makeup is such a
huge part of my brand but like i
am in sweatpants at the end of each time
totally so i think it's so cool that
you're like not afraid to show that
although for the
longest time i actually did sleep with a
bow and a side ponytail
i don't anymore but like dance moms days
yeah every single night literally every
single night joe doe
i would wake up and i would just
re-slick my hair oh yeah take my
hairline make them really receding
so far back we're gonna put some good
contour to really bring it forward i
love it i want to ask you because i feel
like
dancehalls was my absolute favorite show
growing up i've seen every single
episode every single season i would
challenge you to a dance moms who knows
more well considering were on the show i
think you'd probably wear
free when i was on the show oh that show
was literally my everything and i feel
like a lot of the girls that were on the
show
no shade to anything because i love all
them don't like talking they don't like
talking about it yeah but i like that
you still do
everybody can do whatever they want
totally of course i feel like the show
was literally your guys's childhood so
of course everyone like has a right to
do
whatever they want about it like is
there a reason that you still do talk
about it and like so openly
you know at the end of the day dance
moms was our lives and it was a reality
tv show and it wasn't scripted
but like at the same time like it was a
tv show you know and like
off camera like it was always so much
fun and for me i think i can just see
like past
all the bad and like i don't want to
remember the bad memories you know you
always have a choice in life to look at
the bright side of the dark side yes
i think very much the same way totally
and for me with dance i was like i just
try to remember like the fun memories
and like hanging out with abby and
hanging out with the girls and hanging
out with the crew and doing school like
going to the competitions and being
stressed but then like the winning you
know it's like i
know that i would be nothing without
dance moms like it's where i started
it's what got me my platform
and so without it i'd be nowhere and so
i was like you gotta remember where you
came from you know
always always come on cover girl no yeah
literally i don't remember i was gonna
say it's really cool to look at it that
way like i
obviously i like how the opportunity
working with covergirl i don't actively
do anything with them
anymore anymore but like i'm i'm so
great i would never talk bad about them
like they literally gave me the platform
that i have today and like i'm so
grateful for that like i didn't know her
without covergirl so oops excuse me
i've never actually put concealer on
what i don't do it
you're kidding no i'm giving it to you
gal so you were just speaking about how
you always like to look at the positives
and things and i
love that and i very much think the same
way how do you always stay
so positive and so bubbly and like does
that ever turn off especially when the
cameras are off no
it never turns off the only thing that
happens is i'm not gonna
i wouldn't say the word shy but like in
public i'm either
super extrovert or super introvert like
i just like my group of people like i
don't like if i'm at like a party
i'm so like in my little bubble but yeah
i don't know i just like to stay really
positive
i don't really have like a switch that
goes off it's just like kind of
whatever's in the moment
yeah i feel that it depends on where i'm
around but how i stay positive
is really my people around me i always
say like you have to have a good team
obviously because that's who you work
with every day
but you also have to good have good
friends you know and i i have i have
great friends
and the best friends in the whole world
i feel like we honestly have quite a lot
of like similarities just in terms of
our internet existences we both have
really loyal fan bases but i feel like a
lot of people outside of our fan bases
find us annoying
yeah oh yeah it's like it's a very huge
thing both been able to
make a joke out of our music totally
like stay positive and like
quarantine my fan base has completely
changed like for the better it's insane
so it used to be like super young kids
which is amazing and incredible and i
love my little babies so much
and now it's like still the young kids
but it's also
like teenagers because of tick-tock they
realize like oh she's not fake and she's
not
crazy like she's a normal person it's
like a whole new group of people it's
awesome yeah yeah okay look forward
[Music]
oh my god i love setting powder there's
so much on my face really
okay oh i feel like you're used to it
from performing huh so much i remember
at one point when um
tic toc had like first started before
you really like joined the app and
started making your videos i feel like
there's a lot of videos going around
of the tour people being like oh my god
i can't believe like kids go into this
and stuff which makes me feel
so mad like totally it's very obvious to
me that you are just literally trying to
have fun
and are making so many young kids really
really happy
yeah and i truly don't understand like
where people would find a problem with
that
right it's crazy but for me i'm like hey
they're posting about my tour but it's
insane i mean like the kids
scream everything like it's insane and
the parents too the parents are singing
it's unreal
my skin looks good do you like yeah
great
let's do catch me
wait you hold the brush you hold the
brush
did you drink a little bit too much
jojo's juice before coming over why
haven't you come out with jojo's juice
before
oh period it's in walmart of course
oh my god speaking of things in walmart
i want to know
okay miss queen of licensing okay can
you name for me all of your products
and like just in walmart or everywhere
everywhere
so we'll start with accessories that's
like the bose that's like earrings
that's like necklaces that's like
bracelets that's like scrunchies
purses sure sure then we have bedding
bedding at home
so betting at home is like actually i
have the number one girls betting in
target
i'm the number one girls bedding and the
number two overall kids bedding i think
star wars is what's ahead of me oh yeah
so rude there's jojo furniture too so
there's like jojo like chairs
bean bags um toys are my number one
category
and like that's like my number one
seller for everything your toys are out
selling your bows
yes my toys and my bedding and my
apparel what so regardless hundreds of
millions of dollars in revenue for
jojo's bubbles
my brand is a billion dollar brand
oh my god that is now i'm not ability i
do not have a billion dollars
like like i need to make that very clear
i am not like so many people are
totally but like the jojo siwa brand is
a billion dollar brand which is insane
that is
insane literally insane i do not
understand how people online can make
fun of somebody that's 70 years old
because i'm a giant toddler and i have a
receding hairline and i would make fun
of me too
we have like a boomerang i was just
gonna say do you have a boomerang
i'm sure there's a boomerang yeah i love
not knowing
i'm sure because obviously you're i'm
sure you're creative directing all this
stuff but like who's like running this
nickelodeon oh she got the big contract
yeah so they're they're handling like
all licensing all marketing like
literally
totally okay i'm gonna get ready to do
your eyebrows yeah i wanna pluck out
only a few straight hairs
how many like pick your number five
eleven
no twelve seconds later
okay you get two more on this eyebrow
what two more i think i'm good is there
one right there nope it's about that
this one yep yep i'm gonna kill you
all right you guys so jojo's face oh no
not you too
jojo's face is all on and she's
currently baking in the oven at 300
degrees
no we're not very bad
the brows are both on how do you feel
about them because you've never had your
brows done that you like
you know i i'm sticking to my plan i
look like a dude but i'm here i don't i
did completely disagree i'm here for it
but i want to give my opinions on the
final look
okay so type eye shadow okay see all
these nice and rainbow colors
we should use those we're actually not
going to today why not we could use like
the pink
the whole point is that we're taking it
completely out of your comfort zone so i
kind of want to do something like
neutral
and like just like we'll go in like
fully opposite of me
yeah okay i'm gonna have a little bit of
concealer and i'm going to just lightly
cut
jojo's crease i'm going to use some
glitter on you
i just realized i'm sorry to just take
you home one more time one more time
glitter on you it's a little bad we
should like teal glitter nope
all right now i'm just going to use one
of the stila liquid metals that's so
pretty
that is really pretty i know
the father fan no okay i guess i really
still don't yeah so we're going to do
the eyeliner
one second we love a winged eyeliner we
do
we love a bubble of wild wing i'm just
gonna do a little bit of a shadow
below your lash line now just gonna grab
a little bit of face and a little bit of
ring light as well just for that inner
corner glow
okay you guys i think that is what i
done on sister seawater i knew you were
gonna say it thank you
we're gonna cut for a little bit and do
the other one off camera apply some
lashes and be right back to finish
the rest of this look okay you guys we
are back in both what are you doing
get up here
how are you feeling so far i feel heavy
happy
yeah my eyes feel heavy but they look
pretty
[Music]
okay so i have one last question for
this makeup process while i do it your
lips and then of course we have the full
transformation
jojo you are only 17 years old you've
become a global superstar
i want to know where do you see yourself
when you're like double your rate it's
like
when you're 30 what are you going to be
doing it's so weird to think about
i mean in the future what i my next like
big goal is i want to perform at the
super bowl
oh my god that would be everything major
thing i want to do i want to perform at
the super bowl i love
performing performing is like my number
one thing like it makes me the happiest
i love
doing it i want to keep being on tour i
want to keep releasing new music new
music videos and hopefully eventually
i'll be in the super bowl that's right
that's everything
i'll be right there in front of her
actually i'll be back up dancing lovely
i'll give you my backup yesterday
perfect we're going to go off camera get
jojo changed
do a little judging to her hair and i'll
be right back to show you all
the finished look
thank you i don't know how you got me to
do this i have no idea
do you like it i do i will say it's very
pretty and you did a wonderful job on
the hair
and on the makeup you really are
bringing back the hair by james's roots
for them no you did do
really good the makeup is stunning it's
very pretty it's obviously it's not me i
mean you know how i showed up here
in sparkles and bright pink and neon
and rainbow and but it is really pretty
and you did an incredible job and
like i said if it was on any other human
i'd be like that human is the most
stunning person in the whole well you
literally look the most exciting in the
entire role absolutely like a different
version
i feel like i'm joelle right now oh
oh oh well jojo thank you so much for
coming on the channel today
thank you for trusting me through this
glam process two years in the making and
i am just so glad that we got to sit
down together and i got to pick your
brain about how much of a genius you
actually are thank you for entering me
thank you for inspiring kids all around
the world with everything that you do
and thank you for also teaching them
that literally you can put into anything
anything any dream can come true
period if you guys enjoyed this crazy
transformation on the queen
jojo siwa please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below and share
your love and support also click that
subscribe button to come join the
sisterhood and finally click that bell
icon so you get notified every time i
upload a brand
new video oh this is some jojo's uh fast
talking oh let's hear it
if you want to follow me my makeup
journey all my social media links are
going to be if you guys if you want to
follow me on makeup
doesn't mess up
if you want to follow me on a makeup
journey all my social media comments are
going to be linked right here on the
screen and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number for new updates on
videos photos merchants so much more it
is 310-905-8746
this video sisters had a ghost's sister
clarisse thank you so much love for
always following supporting i love you
so so much
no you would like your sex videos sister
shout out don't forget to always read
two people links will go live on twitter
and also turn on my youtube post
notifications
make sure you guys check out the video
we did over on jojo's channel where she
transformed me
into her go check her out on tour as
well she's a living legend and make sure
you buy all of your jojo branded
products available at target walmart
claire's
probably literally everywhere everywhere
amazon's department store in the entire
world
thank you again to jojo for joining us
of course thank you for having me
i love you guys and i will see you in
the next one bye
[Music]
you