hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel just
in case you guys missed last week's
video which if you did you need to click
right up here and go check it out you
will not work on I promise there's a
huge trend going on on YouTube right now
where different youtubers try to follow
and recreate beauty gurus makeup
tutorials
jenna Marbles did mine biggest honor of
my entire life Thomas Hobart dinner
Rachael Ballinger did and also Rylan
Adams that a so cool so my favorite
people in the entire world but they're
wanting some my favorite youtubers that
I know and love and respect I quickly
realized that I sometimes tend to skip
over a lot of the information and tips
that would be helpful to a beginner
makeup artist and a lot of my tutorials
are missing the content that actually
makes them tutorials I definitely always
love to kick my videos up a few notches
and really just take them there for you
guys you know I love being full coverage
intense glam colorful makeup look and I
see so many of you talented sisters
always rocking the same styles on
Instagram I feel like in my head you
guys are like way up here in the makeup
world but I do have to remember that
there are so many sisters out there as
well that don't have a million makeup
products and don't have a million
different brushes and don't spend hours
every single day beating their faces so
for today's video we're taking it back
to the basics back to the beginning and
I'm gonna be doing my makeup routine
while answering all of the most popular
Beauty questions everything from how to
avoid having cakey foundation how to
have a blinding highly and how to put on
lashes without stabbing my eyes out so
without further ado if you want to learn
a little bit more about your everyday of
make our routine and just how to look
flawless and beautiful let's get started
[Music]
so the whole even though not any makeup
products today you guys are the first
step to a makeup routine is usually
priming and the number one question that
I get when it comes to makeup is how do
I put on my makeup without looking at
cakey and texture and gross I'm gonna
talk about primers in a few short
seconds but the one step that is
absolutely vital to any good makeup
routine is skin care and the way I
always like to prep my skin before
putting on makeup or before videos is
with a moisturizer I'm probably gonna
blow your mind right now
well maybe not hopefully you guys are a
whole lot smarter than I was when I
first started doing makeup but you never
know I certainly do not know
oily skin is not the same thing as
hydrated skin no matter what your skin
type is even if you were dripping bodily
oils by the
of the day you know but I can really on
a spiritual level you should be
moisturizing your skin it very very well
before starting your makeup routine
popping water and your face is really
really important while you're doing
makeup because after putting on a
million pounds of foundation powder at
settings bright highlighter like the
whole shebang it really does kind of
suck the life out of your skin so having
a good moisturizer kind of underneath
everything to really keep everything
hydrated and locked in place is very
very vital I personally love the touch
of water cream this is my all-time
favorite but I will say it is very very
very expensive and definitely not like
an affordable product for everybody out
there I would just say find a good
dermatologist recommended a moisturizer
that's gonna work best for you and your
skin type but no matter what your skin
type is I would definitely recommend a
good water gel moisturizer and I really
just make everything going up much much
smoother and preserve the life of your
face and your makeup I'm just going to
go into my knuckle and grab a little bit
on there and just play some dollops all
over my face I did wash my hands before
starting to film this video and I'm just
going to rub this all over the next step
is going to be a primer and for today's
video I'm gonna talk about the benefit
Porefessional primer I don't really use
primers that often but when I do I
always reach for this one it is one my
all-time favorites and this is a
silicone based primer obviously it's
called it professional so because of the
silicone this is going to act as kind of
a barrier between the moisturizer that
you just put on your skin and all the
makeup which both protects your skin and
the silicone will kind of fill in your
pores I'm just gonna grab a little pea
sized dollop I'm gonna place this primer
in the areas that I have most skin
texture and pores and that is going to
be kind of right here on the cheek
region right in the middle of the
forehead and on the chin what I'm not
gonna do is put it on the nose and I'll
get to why in a few short seconds you
guys know I live live live live for a
good sister nose snot I love a contra my
nose is probably what my favorite stabs
on my entire makeup routine we're gonna
get into contouring later on in the
video but one question that I get asked
all the time is how do I get my
foundation to stay on my nose and I'm
suing this is probably or lease can
people who are asking this question and
this is actually something that I used
to struggle with all the time but I do
have one little hack for you guys and
has really saved the life of my nose
contour
when my skin is more oily and giving me
a lot of issues basically what we're
gonna do here is what I like to call a
priming at the nose that is why I did
not put any actual primer on my nose
because I feel like a lot of times
primer on the nose makes everything kind
of slip and slide around which is
obviously the opposite of the goal so
I'm gonna grab a really really
full-coverage heavy-duty concealer I
would normally use like a Mac Paint Pot
or a benefit kind of boying concealer
just something very very creamy and
heavy I accidently cannot find either
one of those today so I'm gonna grab my
iconic London a contouring palette these
are just cream contour shades and I'm
gonna grab it like probably this shade
right here with a more packing brush and
what I'm gonna do is literally just go
all over my nose and really pack this in
I know this might look absolutely
ridiculous and crazy please do not do
this if you're going for a light
coverage everyday makeup look this is
for intense makeup people you will look
absolutely ridiculous with this odd but
I know this looks crazy right now but
adding this first layer of concealer all
around the nose region is really gonna
add like a layer of reinforcement when
it comes to the foundation later on so
if the foundation that kind of wears off
throughout the day and aware off to at
the concealer underneath another
question I get all the time too when it
comes to nose is if you are a glasses
where is how to avoid getting those two
little circles on the sides of your nose
and messing up your makeup you don't
that is why I wear contacts so the next
type is going to be a foundation and for
today's video I'm gonna be using the Too
Faced Born This Way Foundation
I am personally in the shade nude I
really really love the formula this I
think it was very very beautifully on my
skin at least obviously everybody's
foundation routine is gonna be a little
bit different but the one thing I would
like to point out about this is before
actually putting it on is that this is a
silicone based foundation just like our
silicone based primer all the
ingredients for all makeup products are
always listed on like Sephora and Ulta
and if you are someone who is kind of
having trouble with your makeup routine
you definitely want to look at the
ingredients you don't want to mix a
water-based primer with a silicone based
foundation or vice versa because that's
gonna cause kind of like a chemical
problem that is gonna make your makeup
separate and streaky and obviously if we
don't want that so make sure your
ingredients match up
nicely and complement each other I'm
gonna be applying the foundation to my
face that are using a damp Beauty
Blender all I did was want this under
the sink in hot water and then wring it
out really really well I personally
really really love how sponges apply a
foundation to the face and I much prefer
a sponge over a brush I know one thing
that you guys ask me all the time is
that you love my full coverage looks but
you just simply cannot rock that much
makeup on your face and I definitely do
not blame you wearing this full coverage
and intense makeup is definitely a
choice to say the least so I definitely
really really love bun jizz over brushes
for applying foundation because it does
soak up a little bit of the product and
kind of really pushes it into the skin
which gives a much more natural skin
like appearance rather than a brush that
just kind of like pushes it all around
and oftentimes gives you a blending
issues as well sponges all the way 100%
another question that I get asked all
the time about foundation application is
how do I find the right foundation for
my skin tone and although I might not be
the best person to ask for that we all
know why there is one little like hack
or trick that I learned that literally
changed my makeup game forever and I'll
forever be thankful for it and that is
never ever look at foundation swatches
in a makeup store literally ever let's
be real we have all had situations where
we've tried on a new foundation or
concealer in a makeup store and it
looked so good like perfect match right
in the store when you buy it and then
you go home after spending your
hard-earned coins on that product you
put it on and the color is nowhere even
near close to your skin tone the
lighting of those sources purposely dim
and soft which gives your skin a very
blurred like effect and it's also very
warm lighting which tends to make a lot
of different makeup products look like
they're in the same exact color my best
recommendation for you if you're in the
market for a new complexion product will
be go to the makeup stores prepared
bring a little compact mirror with you
and use that to see the colors of your
foundation do not use your phone camera
because it will not give you the same
effect but find a few different
foundations that are all kind of close
to what you think your skin tone may be
and then swatch them all on your face
right next to each other and make sure
you remember what order they are in
and then once they're all swatched walk
out of Sephora
get out get out of that lighting walk
outside obviously do not steal at
foundations and then pull out your
compact mirror and kind of look and once
you're in the natural daylight then you
make your decision on what shade do you
think will match you best and I promise
you will have so much better results
this way because there is no wonky
lighting to get in your way
our next up is going to be a concealer
so I'm just going to apply this like
normal right in my under eyes and on the
center of my face to kind of brighten
everything up and the most popular
question that I got with concealer is
how do I set it in place and make sure
it doesn't look cakey and Creasy the
shape here concealers are my all-time
favorites because it's full coverage
blends out easily but feels a very very
light on the skin I will say though it
is drying I have oily skin so this works
perfectly fine for me but if you have
dry skin a concealer like this is gonna
be your absolute worst nightmare and
that's why it's so important to do
research on the different formulations
or products before hand a really great
alternative that I love for what I'm
having a drier skin days is the Becca
aqua luminous concealer it is a kind of
medium coverage but it blends out
beautifully has a very very hydrating
type of formula to it I absolutely love
that for doing dewy looks or also if I'm
wearing no makeup at all and just want
to conceal a few pimples it is really
really great before we go in and blend
out my under eyes to get rid of the
creases I'm gonna have my setting powder
at there ready my personal favorite is
actually a mixture of the Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder and the Too
Faced sweet peach setting powder ooh
that's a mouthful I discovered this in
my mixing my setting powders video and
I've been using it ever since but you
can obviously use whatever you have I'm
just gonna go to the pointy end of my
damp Beauty Blender and just kind of
push those creases up being sure not to
be too harsh and then with that same
exact Beauty Blender still damp I'm
gonna dip it right into that powder and
I'm just gonna push this right
underneath the eye using a damp Beauty
sponge to press powder into the face as
opposed to a brush or a powder puff was
honestly probably one of my favorite
makeup tricks that I have ever learned
today and truly change my makeup game
forever
swear to God on that it obviously
presses the powder into the skin which
modifies and says everything in place
but because the Beauty Blender is still
slightly damp it kind of melts the
powder into the skin as well which
really
helps when it comes to skin texture the
ones like Kanta this technique I will
say as if you were like me and you had
very very oily skin and you tend to talk
with a lot of expression throughout the
day since you're not like packing it on
you're kind of more melting it into the
face your smile lines and your forehead
lines might start to peak through a
little bit but I would much rather have
a beautiful smooth skin with a few lines
that mean I talk a lot and I'm very very
happy then to have it very very crusty a
powdery skin texture it's obviously a
pro/con situation that you can weigh out
in your own mind but I love this
technique and would definitely recommend
now that I face it's all powdered and
set in place next obviously comes
sculpting a contouring blush bronzer
highlighter the whole shebang but
there's one thing that I want to do
before that and that is it give my face
a good spread of mac fix+
with my good and trusted sister fan at
the ready
throughout my makeup routine especially
after using a lot of powder I really
like to go in it with a light spritz of
mac's fix+
I feel like this really does a good job
of kind of melting all the powders into
the skin and once again eliminating that
cakiness and then I just run my fan and
make sure to dry it right off before
moving to the next step because as much
as I do love a wet and dewy base
obviously having a wet face is gonna
mess up any powder products later on
now that our base is done and we are
looking even we have to contour because
as good as our skin looks right now
we're looking a little bit Flat Stanley
like so to do that we're going to use
contour and a bronzer which are not the
same thing to contour today I'm gonna
use my Kat Von D shade know like contour
palette I really really love the
formulas and the colors and I'm gonna
use my morphe M 405 brush this is like a
medium sized fluffy taper and a
contouring brush and really allows you
to get right in on that cheekbone but
before I contour I'm actually gonna go
in and I'm going to bronze my face using
my benefit hoola bronzer and my morphe M
5 to 7 brush this is a very very big
fluffy brush which allows us to get all
over color but I'm just going to dip it
right in tap it off because you don't
want too much on there but then I'm
gonna go in right on the cheekbone and
kind of place that powder on there I'm
also gonna follow that bronze are up and
bring it onto the sides of my face and
on my forehead as well kind of all over
the place the point of bronzer is not to
sculpture face it is to give a very very
beautiful bronze glow I really want this
to give a nice sunkissed type of look
that we were laying out and got a nice
tan if you're like me and you lay out in
tan you just get burned so bronzer is a
really really great alternative to that
and this also provides kind of like a
transition color in between our natural
skin tone and the contours that are
about to put on next we just bronze
which brought a lot more color and
dimension to our face but now we want to
contour and the whole point of contour
is to kind of sculpt your face out going
right in on your different bone
structure to really enhance her natural
features our bronzer was obviously a
warm tone shade so now I'm gonna grab
that angle brush that I was talking
about before and dip into mostly this
shade but just a slight tiny bit of this
one top it off and I'm gonna be much
more precise with the placement of my
brush and that is contouring I'm gonna
imagine that there's a line right here
from the top of my ear down to the
corner of my mouth and I'm gonna place
my brush right here and focus the most
amount of color right here we really
want to make sure we're blending upwards
as opposed to downwards because of
blending downwards is gonna give us like
a very very sunken Angelina Jolie type
look which also is definitely good for
like more Halloween types up or if
you're going for a more masculine type
of contour which is totally okay too but
I like to blend upwards with give your
cheeks are very very lifted and a
beautiful look once again holding the
brush level to my face placing it right
in my natural cheek bone and just
blending out lightly downwards towards
the corner my mouth and as you can see
this gives a really nice job of having
an even kind of ombre situation from the
contour to the bronzer to the concealer
we put on so it's like a nice fade and
this gives us a very very rounded and
lifted look like I said the whole point
of how the day of contouring is to
sculpt the face so highlighting is
obviously going to bring whatever you're
kind of featuring a forward and
contouring is going to kind of pull it
back and hide it a little bit so if
you're like me and you have a lot on
your mind at all times
team 5head present I'm also going to use
a little bit of that contour to kind of
chisel out my hairline a little bit and
fake it as if it was a little bit lower
I'm also gonna take this powder and run
it right underneath my jaw line this
shadow plus of course a little bit of
facetune it's really gonna trick the eye
into thinking that my jaw line is a lot
more defined
it really is the most common question I
get when it comes to nose contour is how
do I make my nose look really really
snatched and tiny just like sister James
is well first of all face tune really
gonna save your life here because
sometimes in certain lighting nose
contour doesn't look too fast but if you
don't you gonna be taking a selfie with
good lighting or if you're in natural
daily a good nose contour can really
change your entire face of makeup for
the better if you're like me I'm gonna
take the contour powder on the fluffy
under this brush and start by blending
in two lines I'm kind of the top of my
nose on top of the bridge if you're
someone like me you're trying to kind of
fool the eye into thinking that your
nose looks a lot smaller you definitely
do not want to follow your natural no
shape in the situation and you kind of
want to place the contours where you
wish your nose looks like in the first
place
so for me I'm placing this on the top of
the bridge and the closer you put the
two lines together the more tiny and
pinched your nose is gonna look versus
if you put them super far apart like
this picture of me from Halloween from
two years ago your nose which is gonna
look really really huge make you should
have blend in the contour very very
lightly because you guys know my nose is
definitely a problems not when it comes
to foundation rubbing off but if you
follow all the tips that I was talking
about you should be fine and your nose
contour would look snatched all day long
I'm just gonna plant a light layer of
blush right on up the tops of my
cheekbones making sure to not put too
much on a light wash of color can look
I'm very very beautiful but obviously if
you put too much you can look like a
circus clown and that is never the goal
a lot of people in their makeup routine
tend up a highlighter very very close at
the end of the routine or even last but
for me personally I've recently been
doing it right now
highlighter goes on best when there's
little product underneath and the more
power you pack onto your face throughout
your makeup routine the last the holiday
is going to stick and the less it's
gonna shot so once again I'm gonna grab
my mac fix+
and I'm gonna give my face a light
spritz pause up
water rubbing a wet base is gonna make
the highlighter stick on it very very
nicely and we're gonna grab my Anasazi
oh so Hollywood you guys know that this
is my all-time favorite but my morphe M
501 brush I'm gonna dip it right into
the highlighter making sure to get a lot
on the brush and I'm also gonna spritz
that brush lightly as well to really
make sure it is super super metallic and
then they're just in the place this
shade right on the top of my cheekbone
and you can see already how binding that
is oh litter
so pretty oh my god you just see how
like flawless this looks like I said you
obviously do not need to do this but we
are going to be applying a more powder
and more products to the face so I just
really like adding this layer of glow to
kind of reinforce it later on while the
face is still really really fresh and
kind of dewy because it just makes
everything look so much brighter and so
much more beautiful just trust me on
this one side note as well before I
forget and move on when it comes to
highlighting your nose instead of using
the same brush like the m500 will that
use on your cheeks grab a pencil brush
or a really tiny brush like this one
this is the morphe m-43 one and has a
pointed tip use obviously the same exact
highlighter but using a more defined
brush for your nose highlight is going
to really keep that illusion going and
reinforce just the contour because if
you put the highlight all over its gonna
completely ruin the effect of the
pinched nose but if you put it just on
the tiniest tip of the nose Ridge right
in between those two contour lines it's
really gonna further the illusion and
make it look like your nose bridge is
literally like barely even breathe the
ball finally to finish off our base
we're going to lightly bake our face but
because we're using more powder you guys
know the drill if you have dry skin i
would recommend skipping out on baking
although it is a helpful step it is
definitely not necessary and the
addition of more powder can sometimes
like I said beforehand add unwanted
texture but if you're like me and you
have normal or oily skin baking can be a
really really great technique that not
only helps your makeup last longer but
also kind of brightens and enhance
everything just a little bit more once
again using my damp Beauty Blender and
dipping into that powder I always like
to start off by placing this baked right
on the sides of my nose to enforce the
highlights which once again further the
illusion of a pinched and snatched nose
if you're someone who's just starting
off with contouring or struggling with
placing the contour in the right place
I'm gonna grab a little bit more powder
and just pack this right underneath the
line of my contour and when I wipe this
off in a little while it's gonna kind of
brighten up that entire area and just
clean up the contour which just makes it
look a little bit more defined and a
little bit more cut and snatched while
this powder bakes in place that
completes the base makeup for today next
obviously comes brows and eyes but for
today's video
I'm
go ahead and do the eyebrows off-camera
and skipper on the eyeshadow today just
because I feel like there are literally
so many different questions techniques
and products that I like to use for
those specific steps that I make up
routine if you want a full in-depth
video on different eyebrow techniques
different eyeshadow styles and my
eyeliner tutorial definitely give this
video a big thumbs up and leave me a
comment down below because I could
totally do that
I just don't want to keep you guys
sitting here for 17 hours because I feel
like that's already where we're getting
out here so I'm gonna do that and I'll
be right back to finish off the rest of
the look and yeah BRB ok sister so we
are so close to the end now that our
brows and lashes are all complete I'm
gonna go ahead and a wipe off my bake
because that is rather my face for quite
a long time though as you can see my
brushing away this powder kind of just
did a really nice job of reinforcing all
those highlights underneath our contour
so it just makes everything look nice
and chisel we just wiped away a ton of
powder that was sitting on our face for
a very very long time so I'm sure you
can imagine what we're gonna do Mac's
fix plus and then a fan to kind of
separating in place and really make the
excess powder melt into the skin to make
sure we say dewy and beautiful and
smooth all day long
now that we were completely done with
powder and we have nothing else to add
it to the skin thank God I'm gonna go in
with a little bit more highlighter and
kind of reinforce the glow just in case
any of it was lost to that baking powder
so once I got it over Miami 501 just the
slightest bit of fix+ and just going
right over those areas that we
highlighted before to really make sure
our glow is blinding - everybody passing
by oh yeah that's what I'm talking about
right right there so next I reckon
protein we have our lipid ado to us and
I'm sure you can already guess what the
question is for this but it is how do I
make my lips look bigger if you've been
following me for a while you know that
my lips have definitely undergone a very
very large transformation definitely for
the better one of the best ways to get
bigger more plump looking lips is lip
filler you may think I'm kidding but it
will be completely ridiculous for me to
act like I went from this to this with
just a little bit of over lining because
let's be real no lip pencil can do that
I don't know if I've ever talked about
this on camera before but I do have my
lips done I have one full pile of
Juvederm on my top lip and half
on my bottom lip and they were done by
Johanna then nurse I'm gonna put her
Instagram right here this is not sponsor
I just really really love her and her
work I was genuinely very very hesitant
on whether or not to get them done I
didn't want people to think I looked
really ridiculous or unnatural but I
will say she did such an amazing job and
I am honestly so happy and far more
confident with my lips once I got them
done things like plastic surgery and
filler are obviously a very very
personal decision and I am definitely
not telling you guys to all run out and
go ask your parents for lip filler
please do not but if you've done your
research found your doctor planned out
financials because it can be very very
expensive and you feel deep down that it
will genuinely make you feel more
confident as a person then I would say
definitely go for it but if you don't
feel comfortable with that that is
totally okay I still have a few tips and
tricks to show you guys to make your
lips look more plump just with makeup
the personal impact I have for you guys
today is slightly over lining your lips
using a darker lip liner than the
lipstick shade you plan on using this
will make everything looking much more
plump and voluminous when over lighting
your lips I tortas like to start at the
Cupid's bow to just kind of build up the
natural shape and just go right outside
of the natural lip line now the one
mistake that people always make when
they're over lining is that they keep
over lining the entire top lip in
reality you want to take the line that
you just over line above the Cupid's bow
and follow that down but connected to
your actual natural inner corner of your
lip line this will create that illusion
of a more plump lip without giving you a
wider dry Qui type of effect which is
definitely not what we're going for
today just like that
there we go when it comes to the bottom
lip I really would not recommend
underlining it at all because I just
feel like the effect looks very very
weird in person and is definitely not a
true to the eye type of illusion like
the top lip so if anything just line
your lips like normal that of course is
the pie that lipstick right in the
center of your lips making sure to blend
together the lipstick with the lip liner
for that natural ombre look now what we
don't want is this very very harsh line
that you can see I definitely have quite
your honor right now so if it looks
crazy like this don't worry I'll have to
do is take your lip liner once again and
just go back in and blend right over
those edges you can totally leave them
like this the lip liner will stay all
day long and you can of course bring
your little lipstick with you if you
need any touch-ups
but if you want to take it one step
further and really go for like that
supermodel howdy
look what I like to do is take an even
lighter lip gloss this is the Too Faced
melted latex liquid lip gloss hello and
just place that gloss right in the
center of the lip
I personally am really not a fan of
placing gloss all over the lips because
by the end of the day the outer corners
are always so crusty and so gross you
have to keep cleaning them up nobody
wants to do that but by kind of cheating
and only placing the gloss in the center
you're avoiding all the trouble so
getting that beautiful glossy look that
we all know and love and it brings the
eye right to the center of the lip once
again furthering the illusion of a
bigger lips finally last but not least
the last question for today is how do I
keep my makeup on all day long
of course the question we are all
wondering and I'll want to know every
day of course so many the different
techniques that I was talking about
today are really gonna help your makeup
last all day long so just pre priming
your nose of course setting your face
with powder and a damp Beauty Blender to
kind of melt it into the skin and even
baking to kind of reinforce those
highlights but the one thing that is of
course really going to help your makeup
last all day long is a really good
quality setting spray my personal
favorite is the skin to Navy eye makeup
finishing spray this one claims the last
for 16
and let me just tell you nobody should
ever have a face to makeup on it for 16
hours straight that is so gross and so
bad for your skin but sometimes we do
get in those emergencies where we need
to have a full face and makeup on for a
very very long time
so I definitely like to have a
long-lasting setting spray once in Rick
it was all complete and make sure all of
your powders are wiped off and then just
go ahead and give your face and nice and
good it is very very generous squirt and
then just for the last time today
grab your fan and give it a good warm
and really let that setting spray it and
dry into your face and lock everything
in place
I'll bring scissors and that is the
finished look and the finished tutorial
for today I really really hope you
enjoyed and I hope you learned a whole
lot of new information like I was saying
beforehand I do tend to skip over a lot
of the stuff in my videos I don't mean
to it just happens by force but I
definitely want to include a whole lot
more tips and tricks in the future
because I love talking to you guys about
makeup is my favorite thing in the
entire world so I really really hope you
guys enjoyed it as well if you guys did
enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below it really does help me out and
also definitely let me know by leaving a
comment if you want me to do that full
video on different tips and techniques
and tricks for eyebrows eyeshadow and
liner and like the whole shebang you
guys know this region on my face is my
all-time favorite step in my makeup
routine and I feel like I have a lot of
stuff that I would love to share with
you guys so let us this or know if you
want that I can definitely do that if
you like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
or Twitter they're both just shame
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
the scenes type stuff is Jo Charles the
next row asked after Charles the studio
sister shot it goes to sister Kyle thank
you so much made for always following
and supporting you know I love you so
much and if you would like to be the
next video sisters shout out make sure
they're always retweet your video link
so they go live on a Twitter love you
guys so much thank you for watching this
video it is 3 a.m. I'm gonna go to bed
now and get my sister beauty rest I love
it the most ever and I will see you in
the next one
[Music]