hi sisters James Charles here welcome
back to my youtube channel so today I
thought I would sit down and talk to you
about saying that has been a very very
controversial and why did they talk
about topic right now the makeup
community and just in like the community
I guess in general and that is editing
and retouching photos for some reason
lightly photoshopping and sitting has
been a very very controversial topic on
social media but having a little bit of
a news flash for you guys almost every
single influence or celebrity that you
see posting a photo has probably faced
to again I don't know I recently people
have been getting so surprised and
called out for because this is much time
in this moment since literally the
beginning of time everybody edits the
photos the I guarantee probably how
about you watching a lot of bases itself
on your photos well it's definitely one
of my all-time favorite used apps today
I wanted to sit down with you guys and
show you the process trauma taking the
photo to actually posting other
Instagram everything in between for some
reason a lot of people everything type
all day and certain plugins out of my
assets and it all to make the pod which
is so proud of the truth often times if
you guys we have the satellite post
completely block and none of the photos
on there because unfortunately you can't
have that balance now I wish you could
but yeah
really can't - this stuff I have never
once owned a hype enemy in the first
place I only talk about face sitting in
Photoshop all the time and Here I am
right now making their tutorial free
various than give away all my hints so
that being said if you want to see how I
took my selfies from drab to fab just
make sure you keep on watching
alright everybody welcome to a home
screen this is my kind of one to seven
plus this is where I take all my photos
Andy : editing I used to use Photoshop a
long time ago but now I keep it just on
my phone it makes it a lot easier and a
lot quicker
I go from start to finish now the first
time that I hope it is going to be
obviously snapchat hello - this is real
this is me and the starkly public my
front camera now I never take actual
photos with my camera I always use
snapped up to take my selfies the camera
on here is so good it doesn't appear
your images and it kind of like blurs up
the skin and just puts a really soft
feel sort of everything making the
photos super super high quality but also
almost like self retouched if that makes
any sense once I take my photos I was
just save them and then I'll go through
of my favourites which are right up in
here and I think the ones I like the
best so for today's video I decided to
pieces to this photo right here that I
took this morning the same one that I
have on right now it is currently like
this is 4 o'clock so it is now 5 hours
later
obviously warp down just a little bit
but this is right after was fresh so
this was taking writing from my window
out there in my apartment
and ready to be editing this photo today
for the grab and for the purposes of
this video I do have talked about one
quick thing before I actually start
editing and that is how watching out of
my photos as an artist I like to look at
my Instagram is kind of my portfolio so
they don't want to put out the best work
possible for all of you guys to see when
I do have my photos that always change
things that are already there you will
never ever see me actually editing on a
makeup that includes like editing on any
imperfections
smoothing out skin brightening up the
eyes and the highlights if it was lost
lighting and just stuff of that basic
nature
basic things that can't be fixed with
makeup that have to be fix with either
lighting or plastic surgery to things
that are kind of out of my control
that being said just in case anybody
wants to call me up for Ally I did take
a video this morning of this look and
this is what I looked like this is once
again brought from snapchat on filter
unedited this is my makeup I looked
pretty decent I liked it a lot today and
yeah you can't edit this it's right over
Santa so yeah I'm going to be editing
this picture today just to enhance it a
little bit but keeping in mind what it
actually looks like this morning what
you just saw in that minute know what
I'm doing the first half that I always
happen to is facetune
now this happens the $4.99 in the App
Store which is a lot more expensive than
other apps no this video
although and truly really immersive what
face - please we're gonna hit me up I'm
gonna try to make this icon up here go
on to open photo then put a favorites
and just pick this photo right here now
overall like I said before this is a
pretty good photo so I'm just gonna go
in and really really lightly do some
retouching and the first two avenues is
Rishi if you know a lot about angles you
can topple this photo was taken from
being low angle rather than a straight
hot angle or a very very high I usually
take photo shil this angle because it
allows for most of my eyelid space to be
shown because I have very very heavy
eyes boy in turn this makes my eyebrows
look too small are my lips look a little
bit smaller and my jawline to not be as
puppet and my forehead to look huge so
these are just basic things that I like
to retouch with this make sure they look
as good and natural as possible first
we're gonna do this photo a is I'm going
to zoom in and I'm just going to make my
jawline super duper poppin unfortunately
I cannot afford plastic surgery and I
also legally cannot get positive
surgeons longer age so this is the next
best thing that we got up in here I
really really like the way this looks
just because who doesn't love the really
good strong jawline I think it is one of
the hottest features on a guy going out
to the other side I'm not really going
to do anything here just because my
jawline lines up with the corner out
this wall and if I move it around it's
gonna look very very disordered and
we're so not trying to get called out
for editing today you want this to look
as natural as possible believe it or not
the next thing I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
go to the details tool this tool
basically adds contrast and sharpness to
photo wherever you draw on but I think
this really does make such a difference
I don't think the topic on my eyes it's
just an eyelash the straight to a
balloon when you stand out on the face
of it flirty and big same thing with the
inner brow hairs usually I'll do
anything else but because they're a
little bit prone out I'm not gonna bring
any more attention to them a little bit
on the fake freckles just tell me and
and then also on my Cartier ring because
they were tearing
and people to know that it's there and
that's pretty much all the decently I'm
gonna do I really don't wanna bring a
lot of other attended to the rest of the
faith so much I want to save it my
progress like I said getting before
after that leaders that I'm not much but
I think it really is just a little
things that make this little great in
the end the next one I'm going to use is
going to lead the smooth tool and this
is one that really needs to be careful
because it truly kind of make a bring
your throws a lot of you can turn turn
out smoother and just scrub their photos
which i think looks absolutely awful is
so big lurking and is obviously not
actual and people are going to know you
edited it it's definitely not a look I
actually tend to liberate never infuse
smoother like ways when you smooth and
just build up the opacity I really need
to so when I go with this tool the first
thing I do is I'll go in and I'll just
floor with any pores for the most part
setting as actually having a pretty good
it's game day so I'm just going to
lightly tap over areas that you touch
her which is kind of like in between the
brows on the nose region and then this
smile line that I always get right here
I always just smooth it out I'm gonna
let me talk about my beard area as well
because I didn't shake City because I
was lazy and yeah to the shop in this
room to have when I really lightly go
over the lips I hate the way my lips
have a lot of texture and light they are
very very crusty I don't know why I'm
going to use every lip treatment on the
planet and for somebody's may still have
crusty and dusty especially when I'm
wearing cloth so I just moved about to
get a little more natural look as well
I'd like to over line my lips with them
a little bigger so I want them to look
as real as possible now that I remember
smoothing I'm going to move my all-time
favorites tool and that is with tones
this tool is like my hidden secret not a
lot of you will know how to use it but I
am a freaking queen of tones I love it
truly can make your photos so frickin
good if you use it correctly and
so the first thing that I do on this
whole situation the highlights are very
very empowered now I was standing in
front of a very very large window
hitting after sunlight so you can see
most of the highlights is mr. company I
know is / very very bright but there's
no way any of the sides my face or from
downwards because I hold the thumb
downwards so I'm just going to do a
little bit of tones to fix I'm I think
up and make sure all the highlights are
even and lighting so it's like the
caliph Uthman actually gonna use a color
that's already pre-selected and I'm just
gonna bring it up to the top I'm gonna
go almost to white but not quite I want
to make sure it's not start player also
just literally fake and to like it just
doesn't look right
basically so just gonna pick this clip
I'm gonna tell us that I'd like to do
right on in and I'm still starting by
tapping a little bit hotter than tip it
knows I'm also going to put a little bit
more right up in here basically when I
do this I'm gonna go my phone like this
so you can see but I like to really just
lightly tap on my phone
I never was up there that's from bears
just gonna look really really stupid
like this which is obviously not the
look we're going for it looks extremely
wrong so I'm just gonna grab the eraser
to erase over that but yeah they took
really just lightly tap it and just make
sure I'm getting it really really light
and even effect and then if anything
looks too intense I don't really how
that looks
I'm just gonna down erased and just
lightly talked about already and there
we go looks pretty good this has really
been some surveys out that so I never
had a little bit of highlight under the
cheekbone region now if you look right
here you can see what the texture is am
actual highlighter
now the link is not going to be from the
sides that need from a straight line and
because they were very very able to face
the highlight is not reflecting
I'm gonna lightly tell them a little bit
of highway right here just make sure to
shine with obviously that looks awful it
was going to type over elbows together
just kind of fun to animate the book as
much as possible
and there we go that looks a little bit
better just a little bit with Ivan just
let me know that it's there but it's
certainly not blindingly no
but that is a okay now the next I'm
going to do in tone is the eyes and this
is saying that a lot of you will talk
about they either love it or hate it
I clearly love it because I continue to
do it and it's a trick that I absolutely
love and then it's brightening out with
the eyes I'm gonna go back into tones
and this time I'm just gonna go all the
way up to stark white all the way at the
inner corner I know if you are deities
that I later can't now you can use your
light so I'm just gonna kinda I'm going
to lightly golden tones I'm going to
zoom all the way in and I'm just gonna
start lightly tapping off of the way to
be high just to make them a little
bright and then when it comes to the
actual pupil this is my all-time
favorite trick I'm gonna let the top in
the white on the peoples of the eye
and this really brighten up and makes
them look so freakin pretty oh my god
see how good that looks it just looks so
like dollar lightly almost a cartoon
character but it looks like it can
actually be natural which is why I
freaking love unfortunately my eyes are
a round so I always wear my
contacts anyway they are Desio in the
color creamy beige they're like all 10
viewers they are so freaking beautiful
that they do look good with the
collection and flash why when it comes
to like a photography it's really really
hard adjusting when you're wearing
really fluttery lashes because they
create shadows so I might just add a
little bit more brightness of the eyes
that I do that by the choppers
so I just tried a little bit of a V and
I wasn't sure the the top part because I
don't wanna get rid of any little
shadows because I'm a little really big
so it's gonna out of that white then go
back into the race and just make sure it
looks pretty good right as well the last
and final step for this photo is going
to be to work on it the nose contour now
this is something that has sparked many
the controversy in the past with my
followers people either love my nose
contour or hate my nose contour I
personally love a good snot nose like I
said before I am NOT someone who hides
kind of a very very open about her knee
and might notice one of the most evident
Davis I talked on my channel many times
about my nose contouring how it's
something that I struggle with the
balance and I'm not very good at but I'm
learning and as you can see in this
photo it's honestly not that bad it does
look pretty stuff so we can if I can say
for myself I do really count looks like
I said I would post this but I want to
edit it to make it look even better
because why the hell not
to do this I'm going to take the tone so
I'm going to grab the paper tool and I'm
actually going to zoom in to it and she
cannot go around with the lightest shade
right up in here so I'm going to lightly
top it in that color all the time in the
nose I must get rid of the shadows I
also love this tool because when you do
this it keeps the freckles on the
texture they are they've just changed
the under color I'm not really sure how
it works but it really truly does wonder
so just why I absolutely love this trick
is like my secret to getting the
all-time best to smash nose and there we
go that is the before and after of the
signature James Charles dose match and
it's by far the most interesting about
me but I'm not gonna hide it I have a
very very big secret I do really like
the way this looks though on my photos
my nose the thing that I was insecure
about so if I didn't depend on it if you
know why I had a nose like this don't
do it it's really not that
serious
this is just the techniques that I like
to do and just to show you guys in this
box of how do you fake so now that the
nose is done this is my face basically
complete I don't know as you can see
it's really not that different
the pictures look pretty similar I just
made a little bit sharper a little
greater awareness lot cleaner but
there's one more thing I like to do I'm
a student when we go on the personal
photo if you wanted to be between this
out here everything we're gonna do from
now on for so the video is basically
just filter it and color stuff so this
photo could be coming done you could
post this item post is on my Twitter or
something but for Instagram because I
haven't
decent feet I'm going to whiten the
photo and display the colors a little
bit so the last thing I'm going to do my
facing that's going to it the white
until over here and this is the one step
where I will actually not remind us to
use your finger and go ham with it
scrubbing I really when I'm using this
tool I like to go absolutely ham just
right off the entire image because like
I said we have a erase so this goal will
work in a second and zoom in and make
sure everything is very clean and for
the most part I think we are done with
face daily total spending on the check
back save it save it to camera and there
we are all set to move on with the next
step so for based in the next stop that
I rather to use this vsco cam now music
filters to self assembly for you
I personally don't like filters how they
should fit the raw image and then just
play with the colors a little bit so I'm
just gonna use notes okay for that I'm
not gonna have a filter which didn't
start the little thing in the bottom
corner like this body then I'm gonna go
over to this tool right here which is
called skin tone I personally hate but I
look either to yellow or too big in
photos it is one of my biggest pet
peeves I don't know why I like to look
as neutral as possible and in this
little faint looking way too yellow
so take this fight I'm gonna drag it
down probably to around around like 3.5
looks nice in neutral
I'm not really sure how this is gonna
read on the actual video recording above
my phone this is looking for a very
neutral very very late right in the
middle of pink and yellow so I'm just
gonna go ahead and sing that up right
there
for some reason this really bothered me
I always
this but I hate when my skin tone does
not look the same across all my pictures
so this is one set there's absolutely
vital to our process now the only other
thing is that makes your hand vscocam
basically the boat is done so now I'm
gonna open up the hips you're not gonna
get ready to post so it's gonna
obviously open up I can't go to this
photo that I'm just going to adjust it
to however to be I like doing the
brightness way up so I'm hoping that to
around 7 the contrast I'll boost as well
as probably around some of the guys walk
the way straight way down reservists I
really like the look of cool Toma photos
so I usually bring my work down to
around 15 or 18 I guess whatever not
that serious and all over the saturation
top as well because sometimes the ones
can really build out the photos that I
wanna make sure the vibrancy is still
there it just looks more cool toned the
next thing I do is go into this column
tab and like I said how they're going to
look really cool tone so I'm just going
to pick shadows go over to the blue and
then bring this down to probably around
15% I'm going to highlight that for this
photo I'm going to boost him up a little
bit happy turn around 10 and I was like
to play my shadows down just got a
little bit more contrast and my last and
final step is just to shorten the photo
this is like the one thing that I love
to do and sometimes when you take snap
selfies like I said it makes the quality
super super good and super smooth but we
sometimes do looks a little bit of that
detail and sharpness so I really just
run with the crap any pictures for this
one I'm only gonna set of the round help
me around with 30 just to be safe and
that is the completed photo with that I
would go next write whatever caption a
lot and then click Share all right guys
and now stick pleated face tube tutorial
just for overall reference we went from
this to this like I said before I do
consider myself an artist and for me and
my Instagram was like my portfolio so
I'd like to put out the best quality
photos as possible and that definitely
includes editing almost every single
photo posted by inputs or an online
celebrity has been edited and that's
just the cold hard truth it's something
to be embarrassed huh and tussling to
call people help for in a something to
yell either for the most of us it's just
to fix them imperfections but obviously
people
go crazy but it's not fair to judge all
of us on the people who go and do the
most do you feel me
that being said I do hope you guys
enjoyed this video today and I hope you
were drivin little tips and tricks try
them out like your photos let me know
what you think I'd love to hear your
opinions and your feedback down below
you don't have to do this for chatting
these are just my personal tricks he's a
wildling to do just to make certain
securities and make my photos the best
way possible to match my Instagram feed
if you did enjoy this video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below skirt we have not ready I post
videos twice a week on Tuesdays and
Fridays that I would love to have you
join this around if you'd like to follow
me on my makeup journey you pull magnets
your Twitter if they were both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scene type stuff and for a
completely unedited Rob makeup videos
again selfies and we have James Charles
the next ask after Charles all right
sisters thank you so much for watching
and I will see you in the next video
[Music]