oMG I cringed so hard when he said he
was that makeup artist seriously no
you're not lol did you train did you
study
or go to beauty school now so then
you're not classified as a makeup artist
if you haven't got the certificate and
paper to show it then it doesn't count
you as a makeup artist I would know
because I
rashon ever qualified makeup artists
he's right
really rashon because my 5.3 million
followers and this piece of paper beg to
differ hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
I'm sure you guys are very much aware
comments are a huge part of the YouTube
community I receive thousands and
thousands and thousands to come up to
every single video mostly from you guys
who are always spreading so much love
and positivity and really make me do
what I want to do so thank you for
always being the absolute best but
alongside the love also comes a whole
lot of hate comments when I was younger
probably the most valuable thing to my
mother ever taught me was if you don't
have anything nice to say don't say
anything at all for me personally I
don't think I have ever once left a hate
comment on anybody else's content they
work really really hard on but
apparently that lesson was not talked to
the thousands and thousands and
thousands of people who feel that they
are just superior beings and that
they're unnecessary and rude comments
just need to be heard now don't get me
wrong there's definitely a huge
difference between constructive
criticism and hate comments for me
personally I love a constructive
criticism I did this job every single
day for you guys and to inspire you guys
all around the world and if there's any
way that I can make my videos better my
makeup better my personality better my
lighting better I absolutely want to do
it and there's a very very nice way to
leave positive suggestions but for the
most part people don't know how to do
that because everyone's ego is just too
large including mine this idea came
about how beauty it's know when I was
reading comments I mean do this video
and somebody proceeded there hey comment
by literally saying sister James I love
you so much but I just feel like this
needed to be fat I then wrote something
very very nice to you to creating myself
my hard work and my career needed Oh
Julia
sweetie sno-cones darling pumpkin you
needed to write that comment actually um
no nobody asked for your opinion you
didn't need to do anything according to
this very official piece of paper right
here I am clearly a certified MUA but
according to the YouTube comments
apparently so it's every other person
that watches my video so for today I
thought it'd be very very fun to do a
video inspired by Yuki where I take a
bunch of comments from people that just
thought their opinions had to be heard
and I'm hi those two my makeup routine
because apparently I can't do makeup I
am just so excited to listen to all
these extremely talented and trained
makeup artists tell me exactly what I
should be doing for a makeup routine
hopefully I'll look so much better than
normal and let's just jump right in
[Music]
our first step as always is gonna be our
foundation and our base routine and I
definitely get a lot of comments about
my foundation in every single video I
can definitely admit I'm not the best at
foundation matching so I figured I would
take some advice from the comments today
this comin comes from Haley and she says
James I love you but your foundation is
ten shades too dark you look burnt hmm
I'm just gonna grab a little bit of a
lighter shades today and apply this all
over my face oh yeah this is a way of
better match for me I think mm-hmm I
mean after all the sister scandals that
I've had the last thing that I want to
add to that list is culture
appropriation so thank god we're getting
this advice now another one we have
heard today is from Maria and she says
is it just me or does anybody else think
that this donation sheet is just way too
orange and blue boots are shaking oh
yeah looking back I think Maria is
definitely right when it comes to this I
mean it's not like I've seen every
single video that I always like to be a
little bit more tan so thank god she's
putting this out today let me see what I
can look for if I'm not going for more
of an orange foundation I think I need
to find something with more of a pink
undertone so let me see what I can find
you guys oh my god after three years of
doing beauty videos I think we've
finally officially found the foundation
shade that matches me perfectly it's a
miracle this next time it comes from
Shelby and she says James you're a doll
but sweetie and I'm not saying this to
be cruel or critical just the experience
of a viewer of course it would be much
more enjoyable watching if you slow down
way down you're talking moving so fast
your energy is so frantic that for
low-key people like me it makes watching
you very very stressful your kinetic
energy is clearly very high and I'm sure
that you have to exert a lot of effort
energy to slow it down entertain it but
I assure you and make your videos so
much more enjoyable between Hyper's be
talking in your thoughts hand movements
featured in camera it's just a bit much
hon again I'm not saying this to be mean
a cool or critical simply to share my
experience in watching your videos and
give you a little bit of input much love
to you sister Shelby Oh see this is a
really great example of constructive
criticism and I definitely get comments
about the speed am I talking a lot so
let me see what I can do to really help
you guys out because I've never want to
make my videos hard to watch
all right guys so my next stop in my
beauty routine is going to be the
concealer and for today I want to use my
tart shave tape and the shade fair I'm
just going to take the wand and apply it
to all of the high points of my face I
am just trying a triangle or right
underneath my eyes and kind of filling
in a little bit just to bring some more
attention to that area I'm just putting
some in the center of my forehead and I
am gonna put a line right down my nose
and then maybe just a little bit on my
chin to cover the five o'clock shadow
and then of course just gonna take my
damp Beauty Blender
and blend it out this next one comes
from Rebecca and she says holy Sh why
are you using so much powder I cannot
even imagine how cakey and horrible and
growth you look in person
Oh Rebecca I see myself in the mirror
all the time and I think I look pretty
good but I guess it means a lot more
coming from you guys who really see me
all the time so maybe I'll just write
ooh use a little bit less today mmm you
know what I think that's a lot better
Rebecca I think you'll like this one
girl
these next comments are some of my
favorites and they are talking about
bronzing and contouring this first one
comes from Courtney and she says your
contour looks way too harsh
holy crop why does your forehead look
like it got burnt this one comes from
Jonathan and he says sweetie your nose
contour isn't fooling anybody yes I love
it when you guys leave me nasty comments
about the two things that I talk openly
about began to care about and try to fix
his contouring really means a lot and
does a lot for my self-esteem this last
one comes from Brianna and she said
you're literally red okay whoo I mean I
thought my contour looked pretty good
but clearly we have a lot to fix today
according to these professional anyway
so it looks like we need to make my
contour a little bit more cool toned I'm
a little bit less harsh and I need to
stop contouring my nose so tiny so let's
see what we can do oh my god
yes slay I'm contouring with the ashes I
both left my self-esteem up to this
video and I think it looks so good for
the forehead I definitely I want to look
first I guess we're just gonna use like
the littlest bit perfect not gonna lie I
am a little bit scared and nervous
change up my nose contour but I think
Jonathan definitely knows what he's
talking about so I'm just gonna give
herself a more natural look today ah oh
my god wait I actually love it Jonathan
thank you so much holy crap I thought my
nose was snatched before but how like
this natural bigger the better look I
think it's just the way to go from now
on this next one it comes from Orion's R
and they said your contour blush is
horrible you put way too much blush on
so it looks like you've a red cheek on
your face and then your contours just a
dark brown line on your face it's barely
even blended so you shouldn't even be a
makeup artist because your face makeup
is horrible the only good thing about it
is your highlight thank you
at least I'm doing one thing right oh
yes the haters are all being blinded
right now
well we love a stock sister all right
guys so next we have the bras which I'm
actually really really excited for have
you been following me for a very long
time on Instagram but you know that my
brows have underwent such a major
transformation and it's honestly a lot
because of you guys and a lot of the
hate comments I received at first I just
really could not take the conjuncture
criticism I thought my brows were so so
so beautiful but finally I realized that
there were literally just the worst this
first one comes from Baylin Kibeho and
she says bro if you don't fix your brows
your eye look is so warm and your brow
color is ashy they're gray okay this one
comes from Emily and she says anybody
else think that he should really maybe
trim his eyebrow hair and make them a
little bit thinner they are so super
boxy nothing against him he's so great
but I think he would really look much
better smiley face this one comes from
melancholic Mexican there's a scandal
these eyebrows are way too thick they're
supposed to be thin like skinny legend
Mariah Carey true and finally we have
this one from I hate Aloha and she says
boy I think those eyebrows need to be
closer together okay so I definitely
don't want my brows to look ashy today
that is a major major nono so instead of
my regular brow pencil I grab the Mac
lip pencil in the shade of Burgundy this
was just a little bit more red tone so
hopefully it'll match with the I like
that I do later on and then according to
everyone else they need to be a little
bit more arch a little bit skinnier and
closer together you know we're really
going for that look of like raising your
eyebrows at all times to show everybody
that I'm very very interested in what
they're having to say there we go
super arched definitely a little bit
thinner than normal then bring it right
back down oh my god yes that looks so
much better than normal
according to I hate Ulua they really
should be almost touching because you
Nawroz are very much back in style and
trend so really gonna do that there and
then of course we have to make them
eyebrow twins they can't be sister so I
checked it exactly even well I think
that's the best they've ever looked
okay so pretty good right like we
definitely a little bit of concealer
just to clean them up a little bit
really just got a sister snatch them
oh yes for all you yes that is exactly
what we're going for tonight that it's
so good
well this eyebrow is just a skinny
legend oh my god
Mariah whoo this is how close I am to
losing my mind wow I think this is
finally it since starting my Instagram
account three years ago I've just gotten
so many comments about my eyebrows being
too thick or not arched enough or just
too big and I've had so many brands not
repost me because of it and maybe
finally I'll have a chance in the beauty
real now thank you to everybody who
suggested this today because I love this
so now that our browser hashtag on fleek
I think we are in a really good place to
start out the eye shadow so this comin
comes from Shannon and she says you
always do a half cut crease holy is
there anything else you could do or are
you really just not talented at all
[Music]
No
okay so I really want to add a winged
let's look I feel like it'll just pull
everything super super it together and
thank God we have comments from you guys
telling me how to do it so I don't do it
wrong and this one come from divine bond
dagger and this is on my drive video and
she says sister James your eyeliner
needs to be thicker okay no problem I
can definitely get thicker thank you and
this one comes from Andrew and he says
girl why was your wing so sore
you really should have made a sharp
enough to cut it right so definitely to
listen to Andrew we need to make our
line or really a really long and then
according to it divine we need to make
it really thick so let's bring this just
up Andres really you know we love a
thick sister you know who cares about
the hours of time we spend on blending
our eyeshadow like wing liner is really
aware it's it just really opens up the
eye just frames the face so well I
definitely would say winged liner make
it nice and thick every day Wow I think
they were so right my wings are big
enough and sharp enough to almost fly
away I love that alright so the eye look
is almost complete and I'm literally
loving it so far and her necks it was
going to be a lash it said I'm actually
really really excited for this one
because similar to brows I've always
charcoal just a little bit with lashes
when I first started to do makeup I
would always go to my eye shot and even
still to this day I have very very
sensitive eye so sometimes eyelashes
will come off or they won't sit right
and there's a little bit wonky so I'm
really looking forward to reading your
guys's advice today and hopefully being
able to fix them this coming home from
Samuel and he says no sister the lashes
you chose for this look we're all wrong
they close off your eyes making them
appear smaller you should have used a
way bigger lash that flares outwards and
really lift the eye up rather than
squashing it down
okay so Samuel thinks we need to use a
big lash today which I'm totally down
for I mean I love my Mami's but
sometimes you just gotta be a little bit
extra you know so I grab these three Oh
ones I think they're really gonna do the
job
okay so just put on some glue and now
sam said when we put them on we need to
make sure that the washes really go
upwards so they don't close down the eye
so I'm gonna put this right here in the
inner corner perfect and then it's gonna
pull this tail and right up here oh yeah
only really lift it everything straight
up Wow okay so those are looking up
great but I think they could be a little
bit more lifted so you know what
really get them up there let them up gal
hmm this looks amazing
RFA so this look is almost complete and
our next item is going to be the lipid e
doodahs you know starting from day one
I've learned so many techniques about
over lining and making them look
beautiful of course I've gotten lip
filler but you know what there's always
ways that I can really improve my
technique so this comment comes from
Jessica and she says sister love you but
your over line your lips way too much
they look like they're about to explode
you know what fair no date sometimes I
definitely come in at that I go a little
bit overboard so let's just bring them
back to their normal size whoa oh my god
Jessica girl you are literally so bright
I am actually gonna call my doctor right
now and ask her to dissolve the lip
filler because this just looks the best
hashtag natural beauty is the best
beauty this next one I actually get all
the time it is always a top comment on
my video and you know what I hear you
guys Takaya says sis then lips dry
though Hannah says how you gonna be a
guru and have your lips looking dry as
how sunshine says I feel like his lips
are always so dry the indie said Wow
James's lips are about as dry as his sex
life you got me there
you know what you guys are totally right
nobody likes a crusty lip it is
definitely soso service and not the way
to go let's accept eventually Wow
oh my god so much better alright you
guys oh my god I think we're actually
done with this look today and looking in
the mirror this is by far the best I've
heard looked oh my god I am so glad that
I set my ego aside and just really
listened to everybody who knew exactly
what they were talking about because
clearly this is the result and our last
but final step was going to be Sat
anything in place so we can really just
keep this on all day long and thank God
we have one last comment to really guide
us through the setting spray and that is
from Tegea
and she says that wasn't his friends it
was the full-on shower you need to use
way less setting spray oh okay maybe
maybe if I use less it'll really lock it
in all day long
let's try that's it all right you guys
that is all I have for this video today
this is Venice so much fun to film this
look I mean can we talk about it
literally iconic 1 million likes on
Instagram here we come
on a more serious note obviously this
video was satire and I was just joking
around in a play
and light-hearted manner but if I said
that hate comments never affected me I
would 100% be lying because of him being
honest they do obviously I try my
absolute best to put on a good front for
you guys and always inspire people and
preach positivity but I'm a normal human
being just like you are I have feelings
and sometimes comments really do hurt
before you write something please think
is this necessary to say is this helpful
is this constructive because like my
momma said if you don't have anything
nice to say don't say anything at all on
the contrary at the end of the day
nobody's perfect especially not me I'm
always looking for ways to become a
better person and a better content
creator so if yelling you want to say
leave a comment down below there's so
many ways as followers that you guys can
give us content creators incredibly
helpful advice feedback or constructive
criticism that we can use to help our
channel be better and I love reading
what you guys have to say without you
guys I would not be where I am today so
I'm so so thankful for you guys just
please try to be nice while doing it
it's really not that hard and I promise
you if you're nice about it there's a
way better chance that somebody's
actually gonna listen this happened from
unnecessary comments of people being
mean this is why we don't listen all
right you guys that is like her for this
videos today I really hope you enjoyed
it I had so much fun doing this if you
did don't forget to give it a big thumbs
up down below and chugger in love it
really means a lot and you know what
said this video was just a whole lot of
negativity why don't we share the love
down below in the comment section
let's her up on little sister tryin to
go leave the person that comments it
above you a compliment why not let's
make people diet let's spread the
positivity and happiness we love smiling
sister if you have not already literally
what are you doing with your life click
the big red subscribe button down below
and come to the sister it is a pretty
lit time and don't forget to click that
bow I can't see be notified every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me on a makeup Turner you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter they
both says James Charles and I snapchat
for more a Hennessy site stop his data
Charles that extra eyes after Charles
this videos sister shadow goes to sister
Lexi thank you so much love bro eyes
following it's marine or I love you so
so so much and if you like to be the
next videos sister shadow don't forget
to always reach evidently something go
live on it Twitter alright sisters and
haters so thank you guys so much
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next one bye
[Music]