hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel you
guys i am literally so beyond excited to
sit down and film today's video it is
not
even funny because you guys are gonna
get to be a part of it if you've been
following me on social media for a while
now on my instagram twitter or youtube
and i've seen
my photos you definitely know that i am
no stranger to photoshop and
facetune i really love editing my photos
and i've always been
super honest and transparent about that
with you guys which i think is very very
important but whether it be retouching a
makeup look or sometimes even taking a
simple boring photo and giving it a
full-on transformation into something
crazy i view editing as an art form my
social media accounts are like my
artistic portfolio and i think it is
so much fun adding things to photos that
couldn't actually be achieved with a
camera a few years ago i did a super fun
youtube video where i had you guys send
in your photos and i edited them on
camera but for today's youtube video i
want to send you guys my photos that i
want you
to edit me i'm honestly not sure if i
should be excited or nervous but
let's go ahead and get started
[Music]
okay you guys i am so beyond excited and
also nervous to see what the heck people
are gonna come up with
today when i did this concept a few
years ago i had you guys send in your
selfies and i just edited on the makeup
which is of course super fun but for
this i literally want there to be
no creative limits at all i just took
these
four photos and i cannot wait to see
what the heck you guys transform these
into i included a close-up headshot
selfie just in case my makeup followers
want to add on a fun little makeup look
but i also wanted to do a lot of
full body photos as well whether you
guys turn these into memes put me
literally on the moon or something in
between i am literally so excited to see
how creative you guys can get
so right now i'm going to upload all
four of these photos to my twitter and
then i'm going to wait a few days just
to you know give my fellow artists some
time to truly create masterpieces out of
these photos and then i'll be right back
here to check out what you guys have
created see you in a little bit
hello you guys i am back here in the
sister studio it has only been a few
seconds since you saw me last but it's
actually been about 48 hours since i
have last
filmed and you guys have gone absolutely
crazy
i think at this point the tweet has over
7 000 replies which is so
beyond crazy and i am so excited but
before we jump in i do have one super
quick announcement you may have noticed
the very very cute hoodie that i'm
wearing and also the
less cute makeup look i was trying
really hard to like match them together
but i just don't think that this color
situation was the right decision
anyway i am wearing the brand new
sisters apparel color block collection
which will be launching
next week i am so thrilled to finally
talk about this collection because it
has been in the works for months now it
honestly felt like it was never gonna
actually happen because we have worked
so hard on making these completely
custom
super super cute sets but they are
finally going to be here next
thursday september 24th at 12 p.m
pacific standard time on
sisters.apparel.com
this collection is so different than
anything we've ever done before with
sisters and i really really hope that
you guys love it as much as i do
first of all it is the first time that
we're ever using a different font for
the sister's logo so as you guys can see
it is very like
cute varsity back to school inspired and
it is obviously a color block and it
comes in
four different color ways the one that
i'm wearing right now is the pastel
little set we also have this set right
here which is yellow
black and blue we have another set that
consists of all the vibrant primary
colors
and we also have this super cute purple
set as well i am so beyond excited for
you guys to see every single thing that
is in this collection because it's a
whole lot more than just hoodies and i
know you guys are going to fall in love
i also cannot wait for you guys to see
the campaign images for this because
they are so
so sick make sure you guys are following
me on all my different social media
accounts
especially my instagrams at james
charles and also of course at sisters
apparel so you guys can see the full
collection revealed
this week and all the amazing campaign
images with a few very very special
friends and
guests set an alarm mark your calendars
for thursday september 24th at 12 pm pst
and get ready to sister shop okay on to
the video
my team has gone through and picked
their favorites and now i'm going to see
some of these edits for the first time
i don't know how should we start should
we start with like the first
images the curse images
oh god like good edits are like
sure um this one is from sophie and her
caption says
challenge accepted oh
she actually made a gorgeous makeup look
oh this is like so cute i wish i had
this look on instead first of all it's a
double winged liner which i always love
is gorgeous she also did like a blue
graphic moment
too i don't think i've ever done a look
like that before and the gold glitter
tears are you kidding oh my god sister
sophie's not
this one is from brandon he says i see
why you guys love face tunes so much i
was playing with it on his face
don't know how y'all do it but i really
like it and it reminds me of a certain
tv show
tv show euphoria
whoa that's crazy oh my god you can
literally do so much in face soon
i mean i know best but literally whoa
philly completely changed the lighting
of this photo
that's cool oh my god in the blue
glitter highlighter how do you even do
that oh there's a little
glitter button mama no way on what oh on
face soon too
oh i prefer face tune one still the
thing that i use the most in facebook is
always the tones tool
every shape so definitely prefer the
tones tool in phase two and one the
reshape tool however face soon too
she's gorge also you can edit videos now
video chords that's my best friend mama
okay we've now reached kirk's territory
already this is from victoria
okay i hope you love it that's it yeah
[Music]
that's disgusting cursed this makes me
uncomfortable i'm not really sure what
to say to this
three mouths you should have a lot to
say yeah
oh guys in that photo
okay ooh i we need to get get this way
for me that's gross
this one is from marina and it says i'm
starting to think i have too much time
on my hands
oh god oh my god okay
this is definitely the vibe that i was
hoping to get with
this like whole competition so like this
is gorgeous like this is what i was
hoping for
e.t phone home that was an
awful impression i love also that they
made my arms even skinnier
thanks gal i appreciate it so this is
from elena she said this is so cute
okay
i hate you and elena oh my god
not shrek are you kidding me i was
expecting like me kissing
famous celebrities me kissing uh
all right so this person actually like
facetune face tuned you
okay and like like didn't add anything
or makeup but they said you literally
already look perfect but a before and
after
oh i love lying like that this is one
that i posted okay got it
gorgeous this looks very very similar to
how i would have edited this photo
myself he literally lowered my hairline
which is the first thing that i do in
every single photo
he made my cheekbone like a little bit
more plum on the side
oh my god he even got rid of the five
o'clock shadow honestly pj are really
staffed with this i'm so impressed like
i'm actually
like wow this is one from a familiar
face
and he said it's my favorite picture of
us with a heart
a familiar face you gotta zoom in to see
who did it
louie yeah i thought that he even edited
himself in this photo just to really
send it home
why bring it home it's really bring it
home
really oh wow this is embarrassing okay
well i love that he edited himself to
really
bring it home there you go if i actually
had louis this size he'd be like
he did however make me skinnier and
that's appreciated so
my head kept my head the same size
i wanted you another really good one so
this is what's up okay
i don't even think you can show that on
youtube that's only fans content oh my
god if i made it only fans bella thorne
would literally be shaking in her boots
i don't really
i don't know what to say about this one
yeah
oh my god next one
okay the next one is from um
fat bussy tings me
that's my second twitter account i think
you'll get it immediately why it's so
freaky who does that look like
yeah my father oh
my god that's literally if this laser
away does not open very soon i'm going
to be on my way to this
that makes me so fairly uncomfortable i
don't know if i'll be able to use this
but
i'll just put it in we can't use that
we can't we cannot put that in i think
we can
tech talker will be having a field day
okay this one
is from your very own editor ryan oh i
already saw this i replied back to him
saying he was fired after this one
james did not fire me thank you james
[Music]
of course ryan when it fully download
the image put it into
final cut pro cut me out of the tick
tock and then like edit it all together
at least we know we have a hard working
good editor true this video
i think i should tell the backstory to
it because nobody knows the only reason
that my editor ryan even has this in the
first place is because
somebody posted a video of me singing
this song on tik tok and it went very
very viral now there's been a lot of
questions who is sylvie why is she
bringing me water why is james sitting
in the middle of a crowd of people on
the floor this is a choir song
and i was singing this song to a crowd
of fans
at my first ever meet and greet this was
when i had like a hundred thousand
followers there was like 50 people there
which was like the coolest
thing to happen to me ever at that point
in my life we hung out took pictures
together and just like chatting and then
they were like oh my god we should all
sing together
so i was like oh my god i want to teach
you guys this song
so i sat on the floor and then taught
them all three parts to bring your
little water selfie
unfortunately for me that was the only
part that was caught on camera
none of the performance altogether
actually was although that probably
wasn't
great either so i hope that at this
point sylvie brought the water because
i'm sick of hearing about it bring me a
little while i think you deserve a few
good ones you please
[Music]
oh my god that is
so sick are you literally kidding me the
lip detail is
so so cool where it's like almost
disintegrating into bats oh my god the
cut crease with the shape of bats
even like the fully edited forehead
makes it look even bigger
but so so sick it's freaking baths
it's freaking bad it's freaking bats i
love halloween
oh i like this one a lot this is also a
super creative one
okay this is from gemma jones
[Music]
that might give this video band this is
the original flashlight mary the ball
james which i still don't know who
actually made that but it haunts me to
this day
and i don't even know what this one is
but i'm scared of her with the big eyes
i love that she really added the circle
on the triangle too to really tie it
home
what am i saying ty at home bro
what do you have on your basement okay
that's dark
this is from uh lucas okay this
took so long i really hope you noticed
maybe it can be in the video
[Music]
whoa yeah oh my god wow that's actually
so cool the queen of hearts
almost like this is an edit but like the
way that he was able to edit the makeup
on over top
doesn't look like he just like scrubbed
it on his face too like it actually
looks
even the hair too wow that'll be a fun
halloween moment for halloween
i mean he did such a good job editing it
nobody would ever know oh my god lucas
you sister stop that's so sick oh my
gosh this is from travis i said this is
me unleashing my inner artist
i actually tried also i included finn
and theodore
cute oh my god you're kidding that's so
cute
oh my god i'm obsessed with that like
that looks so accurate it's not even
funny oh my god and like the half-edited
version of me
wow this is so cool i love this the
explanation behind this is you cutting
out the negativity in your life and not
letting terry down while you thrive and
making all your dreams come true i just
constantly want to remind you how far
you come and how proud
of you i am oh that's gorge
wow oh my god the influencer poster the
palette the oh my god
she even edited my clothing into sisters
apparel that's a true sister oh my god
positive comments
oh they're negative comments but it's me
getting rid of them yeah
oh my gosh michelle thank you so much
for making this edit i was literally
already in such a good positive mood
today but that just made my smile so
much
bigger i love you and appreciate the
support so so much
this is a masterpiece
oh my god literally lizzo snake charming
me
that is an edit that i never in a
million years could have imagined
somebody putting together
and it's well executed too she looks so
skinny she they didn't make me look
really skinny
gorgeous so when i first brought this
idea to you of shooting this video and
you're really excited because you watch
a bunch of photoshop youtubers all the
time
all the time every day yes and i know
one of your favorites
is betty productions yes and so
we reached out to him and he said he
would make an edit for you
i'm so scared
yes oh my god
oh my god oh wow i'm literally
speechless this to me is a prime example
of why i consider photo editing like a
full-on art form obviously like
retouching it like this or two very
different feels but like they're still
to me equally as important to making a
full image like this is so sick not only
did he completely move my feet around he
put me underwater he added the light
reflection from the jellyfish i look
like i'm literally glowing
the oh my god this is why i love this
stuff so much
i wish that my skill levels were up to
par with like doing stuff like this
louis thank you for
coordinating that that's so sick okay
well that
was definitely such an incredible and
positive end to this video that
literally just made me so
so so happy obviously i wasn't able to
look through all 7 000 responses but
there were so many amazing incredible
talented artists out there i had so much
fun looking through at these memes these
edits and also these full-on art pieces
thank you so much to every single person
who submitted one who put my
crusty dusted face into photoshop and
made something beautiful out of it
i love you and i appreciate you so much
and i really really hope that you guys
enjoyed this video as
well if you did please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below
and share your love and support also
click that bigger subscribe button and
come join the sisterhood and finally
click that bell icon so you get notified
every time i upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me on my
makeup journey all my social media
accounts will be linked right here
around the screen
and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number for new updates on
videos photos merch and so much more
it is 310-905-8746
this video sister shout out goes to
sister sumi thank you so much love for
always following and supporting i love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always retweet my links
when they go live on
twitter finally before i go don't forget
to set your alarms mark your calendars
and tell your friends about the
assistant's apparel color block
collection
coming next thursday september 24th at
12 p.m pst
on sisters.apparel.com alright you guys
i love you so much thank you for
watching i will see you in the next one
[Music]
bye