hi sisters James Charlton welcome back
to my youtube channel
oh my god you guys for today's new video
I am annoyed but also concerned and also
slightly excited too because I know this
videos gonna be a little bit shady I
knew this was going to happen but I did
not think it was going to be this quick
Before we jump into the video I do want
to give you guys a quick little reminder
just in case you may have forgotten and
it it is December it is the holiday
season it's time for me to give back to
you guys and say thank you for
everything you would do for me and this
entire month I'm doing holiday give a
slave's on every single upload we're
halfway through the month of December
meaning a four amazing sisters have won
so far but in case you guys did not know
this I am giving away more VX James
Charles full PR bags inside that
includes a James X more Fiat 434 Pete's
brush set and a real James Charles
palette one of the assisters apparel
artistry logo honey these are completely
sold out and are never coming back
there's literally only eight left in the
entire world and eight of you sisters
are winning them and finally a brand new
at 2018 a MacBook Air to enter the give
us ladies you must be following me on
all social media platforms so make sure
you click that big red subscribe button
down below and come join this sisterhood
over here over eleven a million sister
strong and also follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both ashamed Charles
and my stop talking work behind seat
sides on this James Charles the next row
asked after Charles also give this video
and all my other December uploads a big
fat thumbs up until your sister love and
support
I'll also finally not least leave any
comment down below for all the official
rules and regulations please don't
forget to read description box down
below so I don't get sister suit and so
you guys know all the correct
information and how you can win one of
these eight holidays that circular slays
like I said for amazing sisters have
already been chosen and there are still
four more including on this video right
now so good luck you guys thank you so
much for all the love and support and
without further ado let's dive into
today is a brand new video
so when I was talking about the PR box
is a few seconds ago you guys just heard
me say that it was a real James chance
for people at now why would that matter
you're wondering well because some very
shady people and companies out there
have decided that since the James
Charles acts Murphy palette and sisters
sold out worldwide and is by far the
most sought after makeup line on this
holiday season and Ulta and morphic
can't keep it in stock that they would
try to keep it in stock and make their
own to try to cash in
the sales absolutely not sense of how I
first sold out a few weeks ago I've been
getting tweets and screenshots literally
every single day from you guys I've
either fake website saying they're
selling the palette and running ads all
over Facebook on all of our social media
of people listing their palette on eBay
for hundreds and hundreds of dollars
which is so ridiculous also people that
are literally emailing you sisters on
YouTube comments saying that they have
Amazon gift cards and different palettes
for you guys to win it is so ridiculous
editors may be so incredibly furious
that there are actually people out there
that are trying to take advantage to you
guys please please please do not fall
for anything the only places where you
guys can buy the palette or a more calm
and Ulta calm and I will always tell you
guys when there's a restock coming the
more of you legal team and my legal team
have been working together very very
closely recently to make sure that this
is taken care of and they've been
sending a cease and desist after cease
and desist of all these online listings
makes your production has stopped
immediately and all the listings are
taken down it is so disrespectful that
these people want to stop my name and
face and hard work on a god knows
whatever product this is to try to sell
it for a few extra dollars so for
today's video I thought if these guys
are trying to a sister scam you and get
you to order their pallets that is
exactly what I would do now I've done a
video like this on my channel a few
years ago when I tested out fake makeup
and to do this I had it over to Santee
alley Santee alley is a very famous and
iconic Street located right here in
downtown Los Angeles who triggered where
they basically sell everything you
possibly imagine well there be a trendy
off-white belt the newest Lima time by a
pair of $10,000 YSL diamond heels by and
by the way I think or whatever beauty
collaboration had just launched you
could definitely find it in the streets
of Santee alley well at least something
close to it I had no idea that was gonna
actually exist yet because obviously
pellet just launched a few weeks ago so
I had it over to Santee alley to see if
anybody had a fake Jacob Charles X
Murphy palette I tried my hardest to
film on the DL because they're very very
strict about their after searching every
Street and talking to every single
makeup vendor in Santee alley for over
two hours literally on my way out there
was
last and that I happened to mess and I
was losing it all but I wanted to at
least give it a shot so I said hello and
he said hola and I said tiene la pelea
de chambre James Charles X Murphy and he
said see you'll think of so low dose and
I said cuánto cuesta and he said Fanta
tolerates that I said Tommy Lowe and
finally after a very very long day and
also an equally as long video intro we
are back home with this the James
Charles acts morphe palette for today's
video we're going to be testing out and
comparing these babies right here the
real version and the fake person I
literally have not even opened this up
yet I wanted to save my first impression
on camera but we're gonna be swatching
them looking at the colors of the
rotation and the shade names the actual
sizes of palette which already are
literally it not the same and I'm gonna
try to put them on my eyes as well
hopefully I don't get an eye infection
or get hurt we have no idea where these
palettes are being produced and their
venom Soleil reports and stories of the
most repulsive ingredients going into
fake makeup such as literal rot feces in
your health news this afternoon makeup
buyers beware sometimes when you spot a
good deal on knockoff brands it really
is too good to be true the Los Angeles
police say they have confiscated
counterfeit makeup that tested positive
for high levels of bacteria and also get
this animal waste I am doing this at my
own risk so please do not try this at
home I wanted to do this video today to
show you guys the dangers of thick
makeup and also to address the scams so
you guys can be smart and not make any
bad purchases but also to see if a
knockoff can compare to literally the
best makeup palette on the marketplace
right now so that further new I already
have my face on let's jump into the
video
[Music]
alright guys let's just jump right into
this I have been dying to open this up
all wording blog and see what the heck
is inside oh my god so first of all the
packaging it clearly not the same of my
head is like 800 percent bigger on this
and also this skin tone situation we
really don't love a sister's candle so
I'm gonna need them to fix that
immediately it's a darker packaging and
also as well
it's literally like an inch smaller and
to me I have a feeling that we might
open this up and it'll be a 35 color
palette as opposed to a 39 color palette
so I don't know what's gonna begin here
looking at the back of the boxes the
note and signatures are exactly the same
except there's a few typos in the fake
version for some reason the H and
Charles is capital and morphe brushes is
spelled wrong let's look at the
ingredients on the back of my palette
there's a huge detailed paragraph of all
the different shades the different
formulas at the different ingredients in
the pressed pigment or the regular
shadows on the back of this palette
there are not but the shade names on
this are safe word charm dominatrix
military fetish androgyny poison and
swallow now I don't know about you guys
but those names definitely are not in
the James Charles ex Murphy palette but
I'll tell you what palette they are in
the jeffree star cosmetics androgyny
palette I'm really not sure how people
still be headed to mix Jeffrey and I on
we look nothing alike and are both
incredibly hard-working and have our own
things going on but at this point I
think I need to open this up you guys
I've been waiting for way too long and I
just need to see what's inside oh I
think it still looks like my palette
here's the real one here is the fake one
I just need to open this up I don't know
why I'm so scared oh my god okay oh wow
well first all this plastic has
literally nothing on it so that's
looking at these two problems back to
each other a lot of these shapes are
completely wrong like literally if
there's fabulous chains left and right
those colors that are wrong but from
afar definitely my palate unleash your
inner honest more like unleash my inner
lawsuit before I jump in and start
playing I think I want to do a few
swatches we have my ring light oh my and
the other ring light okay gross we have
you're kidding and you're kidding this
is little orange okay we have spooky and
spooky oh wow that's odd we have a
social blade and social blade literally
not even the same formula okay we have a
playground and playground you and last I
want to do escape this is a hard one and
escape Oh God
look just looking at these two on the
finger you can already tell we have
escaped and escaped oh so sad okay I'm
gonna go ahead and take this off my arm
and so far so good my skin is not
reacting in any sort of way thank God
I'm gonna put on an eye primer so you
put these shadows to the true test all
right so I just went ahead at night zoom
do you guys add it to do these I look so
you guys can really see it the full
details of what's going on I have no
idea what is about to happen on my
eyelids but hopefully nothing that bad I
do have a holiday parties to go to after
filming this video so I think I
definitely wanna do like a kind of red a
smoky cranberry moment on the eyes but I
was gonna go ahead and play and see what
we can come up with I'm first
underground they're real you're kidding
on em four five six and put this shade
right into the crease using a tapping
motions for maximum pigmentation and
then with a clean em four five six gonna
dip into the same shade on the other
side do the same exact thing Pat this
right on
corner and top it into the crease Wow
alright so I have no idea what's going
on in this outer corner there are
certain areas where the shadow just is
not grabbing - and there's also this
really really strange like line right
here I'm gonna try to tap on some more
pigment see if that all fix it the
pigmentation is also just not really
there I've had a layer that's up many
times it's not look good okay with an
emperor 3/3 brush I'm gonna dip into the
shader code James and I'm gonna place
this right above thought you're kidding
and you set to buff out the edge a
little bit to be honest with you I don't
think I've actually used these two
colors together yet but that's literally
the perfect transition shade oh my gosh
grab me a cleanup 433 I'm gonna dip into
the same shade in the knockoff palette
and use this to blend out this other
edge oh my god I'm really having to
blend this so hard to even get the
shadows to show up what is this line
like dude okay maybe if I try to put
back the you're kidding overtop at
Alltech so just gonna pop this in there
okay that definitely fixed it a little
bit I definitely want to deep it up this
crease so I'm gonna grab an avid four
five six and dip into a boutique the
dark matte cranberry red and layered
this over top and put it in the outer
area all this color is so pretty
and then blending it out with that same
brush that we had at you're kidding on
so on this side I'm gonna go another M
four or five six and dip into the same
shade in this side boutique but before I
even put this on this is my boutique and
this is this boutique so I am gonna have
two different eye looks it's very clear
we're playing a little bit of a game of
one of these things is not like the
other doing the same thing packing the
shade right into the crease just even
doing anything hello whatever I'm four
three three back into the fake you're
kidding I'm gonna see if that blends
anything out a little bit there's two
different looks here I really know what
to do I can't go to a party looking like
this are you literally kidding me the
pigmentation isn't bad and the fake
palate but it's just not the same colors
I think is like the real issue here this
is clearly a lot more dark and smoky and
cranberry whereas we just layer it on
three colors and it all looks like the
same exact shade of bright orange
next under grabbin em 506 and dip into
the shade and Benny and Maya palette
which is kind of like the dark
eggplant e color and pop this right in
this outer V and really darken this up
literally love the shade gonna bring the
X that's right into the crease as well
oh yes that it's so pretty oh well oh my
god another NY bow sex is dipping into
the shade Benny I can already tell that
this one is not nearly as dog here's my
opinion here is the fake one basing this
right in this outer V once again topping
the shade on there that's ad oh my gosh
okay let's add on a lot more what's so
weird is that the shadow is actually
going on and blending nicely and some
spots but it's clinging and won't blend
it all in
others like I've never seen this happen
before what's going on shadow will not
stick right there at all my neck step is
gonna be to cut the crease so we're
gonna do that I'm gonna cut the crease
using a tab 2 to 4 brush and a little
bit of concealer alright so now that the
creases are all caught I want to go in
and I want to layer on some metallic
shades on there for a nice pop of
festive color I'm gonna have it one two
four brush and dip it to the shade
shucks which is the cranberry metallic
red and I'm gonna pack this shade right
on the middle of the lid oh my god I'm
so pretty I don't know why I actually
haven't done a like cranberry red eye
look yet with the palette I literally
have just not had time but this looks so
gorgeous gonna use it and blend it into
the dark cranberry shade over here as
well for a smooth transition clean brush
up in a grab Chuck once again from the
fake palette I don't gonna place this in
the same exact spot on the fake side wow
that's underwhelming okay then I really
take my brush into here talking this
right onto the lid
okay I'm gonna use this to blend out
that outer edge as well and then finally
just to brighten everything up a little
bit in the inner corner I'm gonna grab
another M at 1/2 for this one is clean
and dip it to a mix of the shades
literally and also a little bit of a
sister gonna talk that little concoction
right in the inner corner and blending
it into shucks oh that is so pretty oh
my gosh so for the other eye at once
again doc I mean that 1 to 4 brush I'm
gonna do litter
sister what got you here literally is a
matte shade in this palette so not
really sure how this is gonna work out
well you know we're gonna do it okay
since I do a party to go to after this
and I don't want to look disgusting I'm
just gonna grab a sister because at
least it's a metallic shade and I'm
gonna pop that in here here's what we
have for the real palette is so far
really beautiful and here's what we have
for the think palette is so far not
horrible but definitely not comparable
in any way shape or form to the original
start over the lower lash line just
grabbing you're kidding on an am a four
five six brush and tucking this right
under here and blending it into the
outer edge same thing on the other side
please one oh my god back to the other
eye dropping a little bit of boutique on
a tiny pencil brush and using this to
deepen up the lash line packing the
shade right on there
and same thing on the other eye once
again where is this color like it blends
on to nothing
so that's the eye look all complete I
guess I'm gonna add mascara and lashes
off-camera in just a second but I want
to go ahead and finish out the face
using a few other shades from the
palette like I normally do before I give
my final thoughts although you guys can
probably already guess what they are
like always gonna give my face a light
spritz of the more V prep and set
settings right to prep for highlighter
again we're gonna add a 501 brush and
dipping into a face in my palette a
little bit above the brow bone as always
gonna tuck a little bit of that right
below the brow as well clean em 501 and
dipping into the shade and face I'm
already a little bit scared because the
shame is a lot darker than the one in my
palette but let see how this works
no no absol giving not only isn't nearly
as close as blinding to the other side
but it's also way too dark just like I
thought as you can see when I look
forward you can literally see dark
orange right there where as on the side
nothingjust kintama BAM at last so
finally not least you guys know my
all-time favorite trick with the palette
robbing a blush brush this is the e4 and
to begin to the shade and literally the
metallic bright pink that we have right
on that lid and using this to mix
together the
I am loved stones for a beautiful pop of
pink so pretty and then finally another
84 brush and to begin to you literally
must be laughing oh my little I don't
even want to do this so now you want to
be pigmented no no absolutely not
of all the times this palette had an
opportunity to be pigmented it chooses
right now look are you literally kidding
all right sisters I'm gonna go pop on
some lashes and the lip to finish off
this look and I'll be right back alright
you guys I just popped on some lashes
these are the Lily lashes in the style
so extra Miami has talked a little bit
of glitter liner in the crease just to
distract from the bad shopping going on
on this side and also pops out and Kylie
liquid lipstick in the shade or not pout
to finish up this cranberry smoky clam
all right you guys and I think this is
the final oh the think now nobody has
the same message on ever and in white
the real car literally does not even
have that I am just realizing this right
now as I was saying I think that is this
real person
fake makeup challenge all complete using
my pallets look at the two different
sides of my face there is definitely a
major difference in how the look turned
out I said in the beginning of the video
that I really wanted to eat deep
cranberry smoky glam but perfect for a
holiday party and I was definitely able
to achieve that the less that my face
using the real palette you're kidding
coach Apes and boutique blended so
beautifully in the crease and shook
literally and sister with a pop of
glitter liner overtop blended so
beautifully on the lid for a really
amazing transition now on the other side
of my face I will say that the shadows
were horrible they definitely had a some
sort of pigmentation to them but as you
can tell I definitely did not get a
cranberry smokey eye and this is way
more orange tone and the deep shades
just really did not get as deep as I
wanted them to be and they were
extremely hard to blend there is still a
major patchy area in this outside edge
and whenever I tried up on a metallic
sheen over in this outer corner the
shadow literally disappeared regard to
the actual swatches that you guys saw it
live in the beginning and these colors
definitely do swatch but nowhere near as
beautifully as the colors and the
original pilot do so many of these are
just super super talking at how
like no pigmentation to him it's
honestly just like mmm can't relate I
mean I feel like at this point the
winner of this competition goes without
saying it's pretty obvious I may have a
little bit of a personal bias here but I
am definitely going to declare my
original palette the victor Santee alley
sweetie I am so so so sorry but it just
does not compare in any way shape or
form and normally I would say it's the
thought that counts but myself and the
morphe team put in over a year of work
time love and thought into this palette
and the thought is counting in sales
like I said in the beginning of this
video you guys I am so incredibly
grateful for all your love and support
with the launch of my palette I cannot
believe that it is sold out time and
time and time again I promise you though
it is a permanent item and it will keep
coming back if you guys have not yet
been able to get your hands on it please
be patient and I beg of you please
please please please do not fall for any
of these scams or fake listings about
the palette although it may look very
very similar
you were just not getting the same color
payoff and pigmentation the blend
ability and God knows what ingredients
went into these like I said there have
been so many horrible articles and
findings of the most disgusting things
in these doctory so it is so horrible
that people are taking advantage of you
guys I do not want your sisters
hard-earned money going to God knows
whoever's producing these palettes and
even more importantly I really really do
not want you guys to get hurt please
keep in mind the only place that palette
will ever be available as that ultimate
a locations in a line or barfi source
and online or any other approved morphe
retailers that is it and any launches
you guys will hear directly from me so
make sure you follow me make sure you
have your post notifications on if you
guys want to grab the palette be sister
spark how about being said it is been a
very very long day and I think that that
is all I have for this brand new video
thank you guys so so so much for
watching I really hope you enjoyed and
learned a little bit more about the
world of fake makeup and how to avoid it
getting a sister scammed and I also hope
you enjoyed watching me create this
beautiful cranberry smokey eye on this
side and watching me struggle on this
side and you did enjoy it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below enjoy your sisters support and
love it means so much to me and also hit
that big
subscribe button and come join with his
sister her beer over 11 million sisters
song and I am so incredibly grateful for
every single one of you guys out there
and also click that Bell icon so you can
get a notification every time I upload a
brand new video
if you like to follow me on I'm a
custard you can follow me I'll answer
your Twitter they're both so James
Charles myself have more behind the
scene things have a junior starlet an
extra I asked dr. Charles this videos
sister said I goes to sister Paulina
thank you so much love for always
falling at supporting oil of Olivia so
so so much and if you like weed the next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
always reach view my video lakes when
they go live on Twitter
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching this video don't forget to
enter my sister holiday give a slice you
can win a real James transporting
palette and a ton of other prizes I love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one bye
[Music]
[Applause]