what is this oh my god
not cries cutely on the thumbnail from
the tatty apology video
hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
a few years ago you guys know that i
released my first ever makeup
collaboration the james charles x morphe
palette and thanks to your guys's love
and support it sold out in only a few
minutes flat which was absolutely crazy
because of that though within only a few
days there were fake
knock-off palettes popping up left and
right so i decided to film a video for
my youtube channel
called testing out a fake james charles
palette where i did just
that and a few years later little did i
know it will become one of my most
viewed videos
of all time since that video you guys
have been asking me non-stop to review
more fake palettes but the only problem
is
i haven't released any other makeup
products just yet although there have
not been any new fake palettes there has
been
quite a lot of fake james charles
products that have popped up online over
the course of the past few years
of course you guys know i have my
clothing brand sisters apparel which by
the way thank you so much for all the
love and support on the butterfly
collection but beyond just clothing
there have been
so many crazy products that i have never
actually released and we decided to buy
them all
for today's youtube video i have no idea
what we're going to be looking at today
i have not seen
anything but i am very very nervous and
excited and probably ready to send a
whole lot of cease and desist letters to
my lawyer as well
let's get started
so this is the best of them why are you
starting off with the best one
um just to give you hope oh ripping away
from you
okay are you talking about the best in
terms of production quality are the best
just in terms of the actual item
yes okay so here we go okay i'll put my
hands up can you see my hands on camera
okay
this feels like a piece of clothing can
i open my eyes now yeah
okay what is this oh my god
this t-shirt is the worst quality that
i've ever felt this feels like a bandana
this feels like the motel sticks on exit
or motel six is that what that's what
it's called right
i'm out of touch uh like bed sheet yeah
i would never in a million years do this
this is
hideous also like like they couldn't
have even gotten like a high resolution
image
okay let's try this on i'm so scared
that looks like it's built for someone
that's the body of a fiji water bottle
like oh
oh my gosh this neckline
is disgusting this is literally like an
eight-year-old girl's like
pajama t-shirt they couldn't even get
like all your hair in it
[Music]
and your hair just went right into it oh
that would be good literally the most
disgusting thing you've ever suggested
what is this it was expensive how much
was that well that was at least like 40
bucks
what this is forty dollars i don't think
anything we bought was below thirty
dollars
child anyways see the seven about this
is that people probably
do actually buy that do not buy
literally the only place to buy
james charles officials this is
merchandise at cysterwigs.com i don't
make this video like an actual
commercial for like our brand but like
at this point it should be oh my god do
i dare even like
crop it i don't know i was gonna try to
rip it
[Music]
oh surprisingly it's actually it's
pretty darn full
[Music]
oh should we like write these oh sure
what are the out of ten
zero oh happy halloween oh god can i
open now
oh my god put it on my favorite part is
the nose hair
it's so okay oh my god i need you to
give a good
zoom in oh the nose hairs like
what do you see there's like weird i
wonder if these are punch outs
oh oh
oh there is no mouth hole that's weird
you don't get the top
probably for the better so none of those
tick talkers can do a disgusting
impression of me
hi sisters here happy halloween
[Music]
it bobbles
james charles smile mask celebrity
cutouts
period celebrities i'm a celebrity
okay i'm ready for the next one this is
scary how will we venture into
just one fake sister's apparel item
please i would love to see a fake system
hair lighter
let me just say that this item is out of
this world
oh gosh oh no
yikes literally all they did was take a
picture of the galaxy from google and
blow it up this actually looks like i
put this hoodie into photoshop and then
like put a nice blur on it
and now i'm looking at it somehow that
being said like why would it kind of be
cute to do like a galaxy collection for
sisters apparel
that's not the one no this is not it
this hoodie will not be part of it
like that would be like that would kind
of be everything the inside of this
hoodie feels like a camping tent
like a sleeping bag but not a good one
how much was this
this is trash oh it's also extra what
the oh my god it's like stretch fabric
it might be a tent well this is
definitely fun
i think the worst part about this is
that it was 38 for this piece of trash
and like an actual sister's hoodie
that's good quality and gorgeous
it's 45 like it's only a few dollars
more for the difference between
this and a real one like
i want to make sure that you're covered
on both ends of your body sure
yeah is this a skirt you've got to
kidding me this is the pencil skirt
with this disgusting photo of me on this
from like 2017.
you know what's he oh my god you're the
worst part about this this photo is from
the sister's apparel website they
literally went on our website
stole one of my images from our actual
merch and then went and produced
other merchandise with our photos my
favorite part is the hair cut off on the
back end of the skirt
oh you're probably wondering where's my
hair oh it's right there oh god do i try
this on this is the thumbnail for sure
oh my feet are asleep
let's just go over oh
oh miss teacher i need to stay after
class this has to be a joke
wait that shakes your ass so nicely
oh my gosh
it's a little bit long i would prefer a
little bit more of a
school dress code if you want yeah but
that's okay sure
oh i'm so sorry mr smith i didn't see
that there oh i liked mr smith
obviously different name oh
[Music]
oh i'm so sorry mr rogers i didn't see
you there
[Music]
this is better than all the other ones
so far this is my favorite piece so far
ready for my next item
okay oh i don't
yeah i don't think i could open up the
shirt oh my
literal this is homophobic the fact that
this exists on the
planet earth is in fact homophobic this
photo
is from my old youtube channel this has
to be a thumbnail or a screen
hey guys it's james whoa last year i
thought i was being really organized by
using binders for every class but let me
tell you no one has probably ever had
this on their entire life
you're about to before
middle after a good glob
this is a negative 643 out of ten
negative there's a little sticker to
maybe put on your folder your binder
[Music]
who made this whoever produces is sick
in the head sick
use code james for 10 off a checkout i
mean hey at least some at least
at least a
there she is more womanly
yeah more more lately
[Music]
oh my god is this a literal dress
swear to a baby shower this smells like
um
like stale brownie mix don't smell it no
i was really hoping this was gonna have
like some shade to it right did you
actually think this was gonna have some
shade to it
i mean the skirt was gorge that
is
she walks into class and just says and
she's white man
white just to clarify oh my classes
[Music]
see
yeah get out of my closet i would rate
this a solid eight out of ten the
airflow
great comfortable sure could be a little
bit more
fitted to the body to really show off
and accentuate the features you know but
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna penalize
that some people love a more loose
fitting
look isn't it the penalized
oh this feels weird oh my god
oops not cries cutely on the
thumbnail from the tatty apology video
sure first of all the fabric is canvas
sort of an outdoor pillow a patio pillow
if you will
for perhaps a rocking chair on the front
porch
a hammock show or a hammock crying
cutely in the hammock
outside
oh my god i don't know why is this not
stinging
ready to open
look yeah you i don't want to uh
oh
[Music]
oh my god i feel sick to my stomach
about this
i was literally swelling through getting
images probably two weeks ago you were
all here at the counter
and i was literally talking about this
is the worst paparazzi
that exists ever everything of all this
is disgusting
disgusting and not much better for what
you're wearing now of course
i disagree i think this is very cute
see this all worked out
you know who probably has bought this
online it's done the same thing
no no hey hey
oh sure
okay well i was honestly really enjoying
filming this video today up until that
very last moment that cardboard cutout
completely ruined
everything i think that's all we have
for today's video i honestly had a lot
of fun going through all these fake
items and trying everything on
i would not recommend any of these
products in today's video
the pricing was ridiculously high for
some reason the quality of most of them
is absolute trash
and most importantly i don't know where
any of these items are actually coming
from and if you want to get any official
james charles items the only place to
shop is sisters.apparel.com
if you guys enjoyed today's video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below if you have not already click
that bigger subscribe button down below
and also hit that bell icon so you get
notified whenever i upload brand new
videos if you'd like to keep up with me
on my makeup journey all my social media
accounts are gonna be linked right here
around the screen and also my personal
phone number for updates on new videos
photos merch and so much more
is 310-905-8746 this video takes a
shout-out goes to sister kiana thank you
so much
for always following and supporting i
love you so so so much and if you'd like
to do the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always
reach people links so they go live on
twitter and also turn on my youtube post
notifications
all right you guys thank you for
watching this video today i love you and
i will see you in
the next one
[Music]