hi sisters James Charles hurt and
welcome back to my youtube channel first
today said I have something super super
pro plan that I'm actually literally so
beyond excited for so this is a trend
surfing on YouTube I think by a Sofia
Nygaard and not even sure at this point
I feel like she starts a little every
trend we love a YouTube latch and I get
through my makeup all the time I pick up
all my own products I plan my looks and
I'm gonna throw that all the window
today and let you guys pick my makeup
this is kind of gonna be like one of
those choose your adventure games that
we all ride when we were younger you
know the ones where you like died for
steps in every single time but then
you'd always go back and redo it until
you finally won yeah literally me with
everything in life but every single
aspect of my makeup routine today is
gonna be chosen by you guys from the
products to the styles to the colors
literally everything so this could
either go really really well and I could
look the beautiful and fabulous and
stunning at the end or this could be a
major hardcore sister sabotage but that
is all up to you guys without further
ado I'm gonna hop on my Twitter which if
you don't already follow me and is just
a James Charles go follow me and it's a
pretty lit time turn on post
notifications so you can see all the
scandals before they really begin and
we're gonna be posting all sorts of
polls on there to see what you guys want
me to wear and let's get started alright
so jumping right and I already went
ahead and moisturize my skin off-camera
sorry you guys are not choosing that one
today I need to have a clear skin for
Coachella
she's already breaking out a little bit
so we're leaving that one up to my
discretion but the first step of every
makeup routine is always foundation so
for today's they don't have four
different one so you guys are gonna be
choosing from being at my Holy Grail Too
Faced Born This Way my old holy girl
that I used in literally every single
video for two years straight the Make Up
For Ever Ultra HD stick
did you weigh a full coverage foundation
and the six dollar la girl pro matte
let's post the poll and see what you
guys have to say should I wear today
we're gonna leave this up for five
minutes and see what the results are
alright so it's been a total of eight
minutes now and it looks like it the two
ways from this Wayne foundation is
winning at 38 percent so let's pop her
on I'm just gonna apply this to my face
using a damp Beauty Blender I did just
get a brand new a sister a spray tan and
it is wearing off my face a little bit
so I don't want to see any comments
about me not matching
foundation it to my face first of all I
know I have eyes too and second of all
I'm matching it to my neck Coachella is
definitely coming up and I am so excited
and I am not about to be a Casper the
Friendly Ghost walking around so so just
gotta beat a nun so our foundation is
all owner skin is looking as super
smooth and beautiful and fresh and
that's going to be our concealer so per
today I'm gonna be choosing between two
for concealers the color pop no filter
concealer the brand new k'kaw concealer
the Tarte tape tape concealer and also
the Maybelline fit me concealer and I
also have my setting powders here as
well then I'm gonna have you guys vote
for right away because I definitely do
not have time and between polls because
Assessor is not trying to get crazy
so we have the Laura Mercier translucent
setting powder the Too Faced sweet peach
setting powder and also the Cody or some
powder okay what concealer should I wear
and then what should I set my face let's
give those polls on 5 minutes and see
what you guys have to say so after a few
minutes it looks like the Tarte a shape
tape concealer is a winning so far and
then for setting powder it looks like
the allure Mercier one with a 40% which
is only one percent higher than the
sweet peach whoo
so looks like our tart shave tape is the
clear winner here with a forty to a
percent boat so we're gonna go ahead and
apply that today I'm just gonna apply
this in a triangle right below my eyes
on the sides of my nose really highlight
the center of my face then are just
gonna bounce it in with my damp Beauty
Blender having a good skin day so now
the concealer is all on we are
highlighted we're gonna go ahead and set
that in place using Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder which is so
anyway at 41% Wow so far you guys are
literally picking my everyday makeup
routine it definitely is really really
cool that you guys know my makeup
products that I love and stand by that
well here's the best gonna got my damp
Beauty Blender and pop this right
underneath the eyes
our face is offset in place but we need
to add a little bit more dimension
because we're looking a little bit Flat
Stanley like so I'm gonna choose between
some contours what should i contour my
face way that today question mark we
have the usual very busted crusted
dusted busted rusted Kat Von D shade and
light palette we have the Anasazi
Beverly Hills contour kit we have the
next holiday and contouring palette and
lastly we have the new morphia bron
tours which are bronzer and contour duos
what blush should I wear today I'm gonna
make option number one no blush for a
very bronzy type of look option number
two will be Mac peaches which is my
usual go-to peaches is a very orange
tones I'm also gonna do it Mac dolly mix
which is a bright bright pink shade and
then finally edge away a blush and
highlighting do it in the shade kiss me
oh my god
oh wow okay so so far the contouring
pole literally is almost tied with
everything it's at 24 23 26 and 27
percent let's see which one pulls ahead
so after eight thousand votes the Kat
Von D shade and light palette is winning
with 29 percent and the Mac peaches
blush is winning at forty two percent
which is all by normal products that he
used in an everyday makeup routine so
what I'm thinking I love you guys I
appreciate so much the fact that you
know what all my products are like
that's honestly so so dope
but let's put a twist on this I want the
city to be interesting so from this
point on I'm gonna be picking all the
least voted items from the poll to keep
this good and fresh so new products are
being used so to contour my face I'm
going to use the oddest Asya contouring
kit which has a 23% and then Mac oh God
dolly max I just definitely screwed
myself over which has 11% oh I regret
this I'm gonna grab this middle shade
right here in the palette it is the most
cool tone shade and I'm gonna use that
to start chiseling
out my cheekbones oh that colors pretty
oh my god hello oh we love her she's
good definitely cannot forget to chisel
out
five heads a little bit of work I'm
gonna lightly chisel out mine oh that's
not lightly okay well miss Anasazi huh
she's a pigmented sister I'm guess I'm
not going to blend this out very happily
I'm just gonna pawn this latest that up
the dolly books blush that's enough
that's enough I can work with that
it's for the video it's for the video
it's for the video all right so long my
face is baking in the oven we're gonna
move on to the eyebrows and you guys
know I definitely always use a brow
pencil all the time so I'm a little bit
scared because I haven't feel like if
this is continuing to go how it's been
going that this is gonna win and that
means that another option we're gonna
have to use but regardless let's go
ahead and create the pole so today's
options are going to be the benefit
precisely a brow pencil the iconic
London liquid a brow cushion benefit of
foolproof brow powder which I literally
I don't think I've ever actually used in
my entire life and then the oddest Asya
dip brow pomade so we're a few minutes
into the pool and as of right now the
anasazi dip brow is currently winning at
39% it is at a hot minute since I've
used this baby and as you can see she's
basically a pretty much empty this was
like the number one recipe item for
getting the James Charles block brick
lego sharpie eyebrow a year or two ago
so I'm spooked mcgoofy
to use this today but you know what
we're gonna do it oh wait
that's the winning item no we obviously
use the brow powder no ah okay just
kidding I literally already forgot that
I'm switching things up so the one who
is pulling the least sorry sweetie is
the benefit foolproof brow powder I
don't think I've ever once done my
eyebrows with powder I really don't
enjoy it I feel like that would just
look weird but you know what we're gonna
make this work so I'm gonna grab this
powder and an angle brush and try to
slay this these brows may take me a hot
second to get a snatch and on fleek I'm
a little bit scared so while I'm doing
my brows I'm actually gonna post the
poll for my eyeshadow palettes see your
sisters have plenty of time to vote
we're gonna choose between the Jocelyn
Hill palette from morphe the BH
Cosmetics take me back to at Brazell
palette the anasazi Beverly Hills soft
glam eyeshadow palette
and the brand-new kkw ex mario den
ivanovitch huh as well alright the poll
is up now let's try to slay these brows
I think I may have a slight advantage
here being that I definitely do already
have a lot of brow hair so this is kind
of just like filling in and shaping up
but I literally cannot imagine trying to
use a brow powder first of all that
doesn't have a lot of eyebrow hairs like
Hello I use a brow pencil or a pommy
because I feel like it adds a lot of
pigmentation and it really allows to
shape the brow whereas like powder like
Hello what is it even doing where is she
I feel like brow powder is definitely
for like the type of person that wears
makeup every day but doesn't want to
look like they're wearing makeup
everyday boring cannot relate but I
think that's why I'm having so much
trouble with this because it's like
literally not showing up that I'm used
to like brick block Lego sharpie eyebrow
moment but that's what I'm known for and
that's what I really really love I've
gotten to a point with my brows now
where I actually I'm really happy with
the shape and the amount of hair that I
have I can usually do them with a brow
pencil in less than time that it's at
this point both eyebrows just took me 34
minutes and they still look that I don't
think I will ever ever do that again
once both rows are filled then I'm going
to use as my normal concealer that we
got from before and a flat top brush
just to clean up underneath and then use
that concealer as an eyeshadow primer or
wherever look we decide to do wow I
literally don't even know where to put
this concealer to define the brow
because I can't even see where the
eyebrow is in the first place let's move
on to eyeshadow so the pole has been up
for 20 minutes now and after 15,000
votes the Jaclyn hill paula is number
one with 35% jacqueline lover girl but
that pile has been used on the channel
way too many times so at this point I'm
kind of glad we're doing this twist and
a BH soft lamb is our loser today with
16% of both but she's not loser in my
heart because we're gonna use this
palette to create some type of look and
now I'm gonna run a poll to see it what
style of eyeshadow we should use let's
see what type of eyeshadow look should I
do question mark
let's do cut crease let's see choice
number two could be half cut crease
choice umber three smokey eye choice
ever poker beat halo
let's see what the sisters have to say
okay I clearly play myself because I
wanted to switch up but you sisters are
way too smart and you caught on to the
fact that the everyday stuff was winning
so I'm gonna reverse reverse
and go back to figure you number one
option because I never do halo eyes so
I'm gonna put on a halo eye because 40%
of people want a helo eye this is a mess
but let's be real what James Charles
video isn't a mess I'm gonna start off
our car be in the shade oranges soda and
using that as my transition and popping
that right in my crease so everything
blends nicely together I'm just gonna
use circular windshield wiper motions as
usual but I'm keeping the shadow
actually more a rounded shape but you
guys know I love a good winged out
shadow moment that really lifts up the
eyes but for a sister halo eye I
definitely want to keep it more round
and really accentuate the circular halo
shape next to the morphe m4 33 I'm gonna
grab the shade of burnt orange and I'm
gonna pop that right in the crease once
again making sure to keep the eye shape
really really circular and large we love
a blended sister okay next is the more
defined blending brush I'm gonna dip
into the shade it's Janna right up in
here and use this to it define out the
crease a little bit more and then
finally using a really tiny a tapered
blending brush whoo that's a mouthful
I'm going to dip into the shades
mulberry and a little bit of Cypress
number and just really deepen up the
crease one last time I feel like it's
been a hot minute since I've done like a
darker smoky type of look I think I've
been doing it that's why it looks a lot
recently so holding this video let's
switch it up a little bit make her dark
make her a little bit spooky why not
this outer corner still is looking at
walki though why don't it's not blend
out it is clearly been a hot minute
since I've done a halo eye because I
cannot figure out how to blend this
outer edge to save my life points let's
play on hello so now that we have the
crease I'll blend it out and define I
want to make this into an actual halo
eye so I'm gonna grab my morphe m42 one
brush and a little bit of my concealer
from before and I guess cut the crease
those muscles of your cut crease but
just in the center portion so we can
build out that halo to do the actual
heal the way I'm going to do the same
exact colors that I used in the crease
and the same order as well popping them
right on top of the concealer and I'm
gonna start off with the shade orange
soda and pop that right in the center
but I am gonna leave a little bit of a
strip in but
you know for a shimmer shadow in a
second I'm just packing the shade on
there making sure to get right up to
that line of concealer so we get that
cut halo I type of love I'm gonna grab
the shade see Jana and pop that right
next door next we're gonna use Cypress
Ember on a fluffy pencil brush and pop
this on the inner corner as well as the
outer corner next to the small concealer
brush like this one this is the morphe
at 19 I'm gonna dip into the shade or
right up here called a bronze and I'm
gonna give my brush a good spread of mac
fix+ so it's very very pigmented and
metallic and I'm gonna pop that right in
the center of that little halo so the
upper lip portion of the shadow is
finally Donna thank God I was not too
confident this at first but I'm really
liking the direction that's going now so
let's talk liner do we want to do it we
don't want to do it let's ask the
sisters gonna put choice one no eyeliner
choice number two winged blocked liner
choice number three glitter liner for
this portion and choice number four
would be black and glitter liner let's
see so once this pulls done am i picking
the most voted option now or the least
voted option now this would be a fast I
know what I'm doing Oh while I'm waiting
for the results to come in on the liner
Paul I'm gonna quickly go ahead and do
the eye shadow off-camera on the other
all right I'll be right back to finish
off the look so we are back and both
eyes are currently done and a slave and
as even as I could possibly get them I
always hate doing a halo eyes or eye
shapes like this because my eyes are
very very uneven and always is a little
bit wonky but you know what I'm happy
with where we're at the polls are
running for 20 minutes now and at low
state the results are black and glitter
liner is waiting by 40% let's do it I'm
gonna use the Urban Decay Midnight
Cowboy glitter liner and first pop that
on the center of the lid to really make
that halo eye pop and then I'm also
gonna trace out a really thin line right
at the top of that halo to cut the halo
crease might as well go all out and be a
little bit extra at this point I'm gonna
throw in a black winged liner as well
using the NYX matte liquid liner you
guys did before a glitter liner too so
not only am I gonna put it on the lid
but let's be a little bit extra today I
want to do a double glitter winged liner
I may be regarding that but you know
what go big or go home
I forgot how hard this wants to do oh my
god okay she's on there
oh that was a lot I don't even know if I
like this anymore
whatever too late now oh my god had to
throw in the other I know what okay
honestly it has been a very very very
long time since I have finished my
makeup and looked in the mirror and not
been happy with the result but for some
reason I absolutely hate how this is
turning out I don't know why but you
know what we're just gonna keep trucking
through hopefully it'll come together in
the end but next up is going to be the
eyelashes and at this point go big go
home so today we were choosing between
Lily lashes in the style mikonos house
Elijah is ikonics Lily lashes and the
style Miami's and a good and fresh 301
[Laughter]
you're kidding the poles been going for
10 minutes now and unfortunately my
sister 301 did not win we're gonna pump
on a pair of the Lily lashes Miami's
today I thought I'd wear these all the
time are you guys I love that you know
my makeup routine so well but this video
I had never wanted a video to be over
with more in my entire life I don't know
what its way on right now let me hear
that I just accidentally cut off half
the eyelash you know how I said earlier
that lashes could potentially save this
look I lied I still don't love it but I
will say that it does look significantly
better and less like horrible with a
pair of lashes on and although it's not
my favorite look that I've ever done I
will say that it does kind of look
relatively pretty relatively okay and
maybe can be fixed with a little bit of
sister phase tuned
so I'm trying to stay positive I'm kind
of stay motivated because I want to
finish this video and I'm honestly
having a lot of fun doing this so now
that the eyes are all complete let's
move on to the rest of the face starting
off with highlighter
we're gonna choose between for today
starting off with mary lou manizer from
the balm the Anasazi beverly hills exxon
resi collab Anasazi beverly hills so
hollywood might go to or the jeffree
star cosmetics 24-karat highlighting
palettes the results are in and by an
overwhelming majority the jeffree star
skin frost palette won with 55% of the
boat who i'm going to
myself a good spread of mac fix+ because
I've been having a lot of powder on my
face and I'm gonna dip into the shade
sarcophagus in this palette and get my
glow on oh you're kidding me
I know Geoffrey does not play around
when it comes to his makeup and
pigmentation but that is probably the
brightest highlighter I've ever seen in
my entire life like what the hack I was
going for a more soft and subtle look
today by I guess this is gonna have to
do I'm gonna mix a little bit of the
shade King Tut in with the sarcophagus
for the next cheek so it's not like
overwhelming wow that's insane a whole
I'm gonna pop a little bit of this right
above my brow bones as well you guys
know I love having up here to widen out
my face a little bit and just bring more
attention to this region I feel like it
gives a really really natural and
beautiful like glow from within take a
look even though this palette is not
exactly a glow from within type of the
highlighter clearly also how would you
guys feel about a sister James and
Geoffrey collab I feel like that would
low-key be kind of iconic let me know
I'm actually gonna skip out on
highlighting the inner corners today
because I really want to keep the focus
on the halo eye right in the center of
the eyes and not like in the corners of
the eyes if that makes sense
but I am gonna grab a little bit more of
a sarcophagus mixed with King Tut tap
the excess off the brush then I'm going
to use this to highlight right down the
tip of my nose Oh what from this angle
this look looks really pretty actually
okay maybe this isn't the worst only
from this angle though hmm and last but
certainly not least thank you lord if we
have the Liberty to us and for this at
once again we have four options starting
off with a glossy nude a kind of a brown
a cool tone gray lip a red or a pop of
color and I didn't pick out a color for
pop of color if that one went I'll host
a separate poll again letting everybody
else pick a pop of color let's do it you
guys want the results are in in our last
poll as
a glossy nude honestly not surprised and
it won with 36% out of 10,000 votes in
only nine minutes you guys literally yes
laid this challenge I feel like a purple
or a blue or a green what I've looked
literally so bad at this look and I feel
like at least a glossy nude will kind of
tie everything together even though I
still hate bass you guys
it is currently 436 here in California I
started filming this at 11:30 this
morning it has been five hours now this
has been a crazy wild ride we had a lot
of ups and downs
a few emotional breakdowns on the way
but we are finally done with the
completed look completely chosen by you
guys even though I'm not obsessed with
the finished look today I think that
having you guys pick my makeup routine
and products is one of the most fun
things I've ever done and I really
really really love this challenge I
forgot to say this was slowing the outro
earlier sorry guys I was very very
focused on finishing the video and
getting my makeup off my face but thank
you so much everybody who participated
in that like seriously oh my god it
means so much to me that literally
thousands of you guys we're sitting and
literally waiting for me for five hours
so I found that video to vote on those
polls and to pick which products I would
put my face like that is really really
so cool and just goes to show how
amazing you guys are and obviously we
did it do a little flip flop and I was
making fun of the fact that all my
everyday makeup products were being
picked but that just shows that you guys
that really do care about my videos and
that you pay attention to the products
that I'm using and that I'm loving so
thank you at the most ever and really
meant a lot that you guys wanted to
participate and I love you at the most
ever in the long run this vide was a
little bit of a mess it was all over the
place but I did have so much fun filming
it and I really hope you guys enjoyed
watching if you guys did enjoy it please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and show your support it
really does mean the entire world to me
and also if you have not already make
sure to join the sisterhood it click
that big red subscribe button also click
that Bell icon so you can notified every
time I upload a brand new video if you'd
like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram or
Twitter they're both does James Charles
and my snapchat for more behind the
scenes next up is James Charles that
extra asks after Charles this accessory
shot it goes to sister Donna thank you
so much me for always following it
supporting you I love you literally so
so so much and if you guys like to be at
next video sister shadow make sure
they're always a retweet with any links
and they go live on it Twitter all right
sisters thank you for watching I love
you so much and I will see you
the next one
[Music]