hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel a few
videos ago I did a Q&A and one question
you guys asked was if there were one
youtuber outside of the VT road that you
who collab with who would it be and my
answer to that was Shane Dawson and
Jenna Marbles and today my dreams came
true kind of there was a really crazy
trying to bug out on YouTube right now
we're different people try to follow and
recreate beauty gurus makeup tutorials
this is started by Thomas Humbert who
tried to follow a Jeffrey star makeup
tutorial I will link his video down
below he started this whole thing and
now it is literally blown up this
morning I woke up to a million tweets
because living legend jenna Marbles
decided to follow a James Charles makeup
tutorial I can die happy
I was so absolutely honored to have
Jenna follow one of my makeup tutorials
I was a little bit spooked on not gonna
lie because she chose the Valentine's
Day look from last year I still had my
man but Anna block eyebrows who those
are dark times we did not talk about any
more on this channel but I think she
absolutely killed the look I'm not gonna
lie I was not expecting much but I
really think sister looked so good so
definitely go check out Jenna's video go
show her at the sister love tell her I
sent you and for today's little surprise
video I thought it would be only right
to follow the trend and recreate one of
Jana's makeup tutorials without further
ado I'm gonna throw all my makeup
knowledge down the drain I no longer a
beauty guru and I'm gonna be getting
ready
using a jenna Marbles makeup tutorial
lord help me let's get started
[Music]
there's stuff up on YouTube and we
search the jenna Marbles makeup tutorial
okay so we have the I tried following a
James child link up to trail that's
iconic
we also have jenna Marbles drunk makeup
tutorial from five years ago this has 23
million views hello what am I didn't
happen tutorial to get 23 million views
that sounds the best ever the fact that
there's a drug to trail it's poufy a
little bit you guys know I here on the
James Charles channel we are sober
sisters but if you go like drinking
never experience is you before
[Music]
okay can already tell you I'm not gonna
follow this first step this is not a
good start makeup my partner this is the
line okay let me see if I can find a
normal tutorial okay this is a makeup
tutorial for my vlogs for unskilled
people and today that is what I am let's
try this
I'll like I'm watching two different
people what is going on
same-same okay even though this video
let's take its toll on a toaster oven
she looks great so hopefully i'll be
able to recreate this on me today
that is literally the team
I feel like primer I correct me if I'm
wrong for many of you guys I feel like
primer literally does nothing like every
time I use a primer if anything it just
disrupts the foundation that's actually
on my nose that's why I literally
stopped using it I only use moisturizer
anymore but I feel like primer is the
biggest gimmick in the beauty world like
what does it even do oh my god sisters
that we are doing a full coverage
vanilla cake mix makeup today good lord
that foundation it can cover like
anything like that's enough to cover
like my scandals I don't have the exact
cream foundation that Jenna uses but I
do you have the Krylon TV paint stick
which is equally as full coverage and
also a cream foundation this is
literally what I use for drag makeup but
I guess we're going to use this today
with a brush oh gosh
guess I'm just gonna go right in and
it's oh my god this is so full coverage
my skin is crying oh oh my god flash
like Mary is shaking I do not even
realize how light this foundation was
hello where is the concealer the
concealer not exist yet in 2011
oh hey I don't have that powder but I do
have my Mac Studio Fix Foundation which
is a Mac pressed powder that has some
color to it she is scrubbing that all
over oh okay here we go
[Music]
No oh my god this is not true okay
sisters I don't know who thought love
either coming her marbles in the
background love a dual-purpose that sir
I don't have that brush or dogs that's
chew on them but I do have it my morphe
M 5 to 7 News coach James return office
oh I love the place that she's going
with of all over her face okay I'm gonna
start off on the cheekbones like she did
I noticed he put a lot of this in her
eyelid region up here and also laid
across her cheeks and across her nose oh
my god I can feel the foundation on my
nose crying for help right now you know
okay well okay so she's contouring her
face right okay let's pause and going
right in at the hollows of the cheek
bones to really give that sunken and
sculpted look I like that she actually
described that that is definitely
correct placement and I always do my
contour in my cheeks and as well as
around the face as well that really
highlights the center of your face which
brings attention to it so good job
sister Jenna that is correct
I feel like we have reached the maximum
level of bronzer please yeah okay thank
God okay you guys know I love a good
peach blush okay I don't have that but I
do have a Mac blush and peaches
hopefully there should be a similar
color
so according to like your face shape I
like to blend it in like with my bronzer
a little bit okay me too I think she's
actually doing a really good job of
explaining where to place the products
and how much to put on like how to blend
it out that's awesome good job sister
Jenna from seven years ago you're gonna
be amazed at how frigging easy and I
don't care oh come on I don't care well
I'm not even put it based on my eyes cuz
they don't like me everybody I really
really like this light brown color race
okay so let's say she has a duo palette
of a light light light light light brown
and a slightly darker brown let me go
see what I have okay so I just found
this covergirl true naked eye shadow
palette it basically is like my only
palette that has light tans and browns
if you guys know me you know that I
really don't do a lot of soft makeup so
we're gonna make this work today so try
and find a closer this or that just
really looks natural but make sure for
me because my hey so what say I think
she's doing a really really good job of
actually explaining why she's picking
he's tell it like she's talking about
how she wants light matte cheeks under
her eyelids really bring attention to
her eyes I think this is actually a good
tutorial
sister Jenna do you think iris
everywhere are quaking in this light
brown with this blending brush which is
totally not what you're supposed to use
it for oh really
just about right Oh God I'm gonna take
my empire 33 and dip into this light
brown shade and my nudes palette and I
guess put it all over the eyelid with a
blending brush like genocide this is
definitely not the brush that you would
normally use for this I wouldn't usually
pick something like this a more like a
flat rocker brush to really get that
color and they're particularly good that
color on there but you know what we're
gonna just use a blending brush for
today and like Jenna said we're gonna
put it all over I think this is
literally doing nothing because the
amount of bronzer have I made peace
right no I'm gonna take this darker
brown and I'm taking the same brush and
then clean it and do it into it knocking
up my crease I don't know about the
whole slopping method I can actually do
my I kind of throbbing right now that
definitely does not feel good I'm gonna
stick to my windshield wiper motion but
you do use this I looked at all you can
take a q-tip or whatever but I just go
like this
oh no want to touch up like your temples
now that you've messed them up YouTube
but I don't oh you know what I feel like
this is a terrible joke video oh that is
just not what you're supposed to do as
painful as that was for me to do with as
a beauty guru I am falling of course
Jenna's tutorial I do see so many people
doing that when it comes to fixing up
their eyeshadow a really great technique
you can do if you want to kind of clean
it I'm gonna make it just a little bit
more to find easy to grab a little bit
of concealer under Beauty Blender and
just go right and it kind of just go up
against that edge and really just clean
it up doesn't do a great job of kind of
lightening up that area and defining a
little bit without ripping up all of
your foundation leaving a red spot was
just
spooky and horrible or sometimes if it's
really not looking doc odd you can take
a powder puff or your Beautyblender and
a little bit of setting powder and just
go right under just like that and wipe
it off after a little while just like
baking normally does and that shuttle
will be cleaned up and your foundation
will not be disrupted and completely
gone like it is here poeple hunt I'm a
big fan of gel liners this brush just
came with it you can use any kind of a
liner brush
I'm a fan I'm gonna put this right
before I even start doing this I notice
Jenna is talking at her land to get it
straight across while looking down at
her mirror to try on her liner this is
something that is really really common
for people to do as well but this is
actually a really really bad technique
this thing that can cause really really
bad eye wrinkles which obviously none of
us want ever gonna do a gel liner and
you're having trouble getting it really
really even I would recommend getting a
compact mirror like this and instead of
kind of like looking at your mirror and
trying to get it straight hold your
mirror at a downward angle like this and
hold your brush upwards that'll give you
a really easy access to your eyelid so
you have the whole thing to look at
without having to stretch it which shows
bottom a long run right here in the
corner oh okay was it like this okay so
we're doing a wing I guess as well and
Jenna is definitely right and that when
you draw an eyeliner weighing it you
definitely want to follow the natural
shape of your eye and Jen it is true a
baby weighing today so it's the same
thing that we are going to do if I turn
to the side this is basically hide our
winged eyeliner should look as you can
see it goes right from the bottom and it
follows my eye right up at the shape and
just comes right up into a nice point
and goes right back in to that liner
which is really really flattering for my
eye shape way too many people draw their
winged eyeliner going right up like that
that I let her shape is flattering on
literally nobody please don't - dolly
[Music]
can relate I love a good laugh okay
those look like
ardell demi whispies hold on whoa hello
worst explanation where's the glue
where's the tweezers she's putting this
lash entire lash may add on with her
hand even as a beauty guru who does this
as a job for a living every single day
I still struggle with putting on
eyelashes and it's one of the hardest
parts of makeup and she's just gonna
throw it on there
speed it up like it's nobody's business
I don't think so sister
[Music]
don't I actually just get that on there
are you kidding me okay and lashes are
on let's go into a mascara please tell
me she did not just glue on a pair of
eyelashes about a mascara to blend them
together Oh Jenna she liturgist that
eyebrow in like 20 seconds my eyebrow
process is like 20 minutes for each
eyebrow okay like genocide just gonna go
right in follow the shape
[Music]
tell me where that I broke does not even
look that bad what is going on thank God
thank God okay
whoo I can roll the best
okay I think that's a Maybelline mascara
but this is filmed in 2011 so I don't
even know if that's being unsold anymore
I'm gonna use the Maybelline Big Shot
mascara which is being sold and it's
good not only do I want to teach Jenna
how to do makeup but I also need to
teach her how to do a ton pop
desperately so once again there's
getting a helpful hint when you use
block file it often gives you like a
sultry sexy look but it does make your
eyes look much smaller I like to use a
white like Jenna said make sure I soak
really really big dress attention to
them and gives you like a doll like look
but God Paul John today makeup is very
very expensive but you can definitely
find it cheaper options that is Four
Swords sisters preaching the truth
[Music]
we're not doing web sick oh so I
described the mac lipglass
in the shade it pleased me this is the
lightest pink I could find so that's it
wait a second where's the highlighter or
has a setting spray where's the setting
powder sister
okay sisters I guess we are done here
and this is the completed look for today
looking at this draw beauty guru
standpoint if someone who does makeup
every single day I definitely have
products and techniques that I like to
use and definitely would have loved to
see added to this tutorial but the whole
point of this video is obviously to
throw all my makeup knowledge out the
window and kind of look at this as an
outsider trying to follow a YouTube
tutorial just like all of you sisters
out there I really don't think this
looks that bad and throughout Jenna's
video I actually feel like she did a
really really great job of explaining
every single step she was doing so
everyone could kind of get it no matter
what their skill level really wise
Jenna's video actually included a lot of
really really great tips that beauty
gurus tend to skip over but that would
be super helpful to any beginner makeup
wear such as using a different brush for
bronzing and contouring know what
they're not the same thing using your
natural eye shape as a guide for drawing
your winged liner one of the best tricks
I'd ever learned using mascara to blend
together your falsies with your regular
lashes and of course the pros and cons
of using black and white eyeliner
overall I had so much fun following a
jenna Marbles makeup tutorial today I
know how crazy she can be in her video
sometimes but I think it was really
really cool to see this more chill side
of Jenna just relaxing
I've been subscribed to Jenna for years
now I grew up watching her so to wake up
this morning and see that she recreated
one of my tutorials and has been
watching me and as a true sister was
definitely one of the coolest things
I've ever experienced on YouTube thank
you so much then I hope you're watching
I love you sister although I love this
tutorial please let me do your makeup
and do it right it will be such a huge
honor if you enjoyed today's video and
this jennamarbles inspired layout please
give it a big thumbs up down below it
means the world to me and don't forget
to click that big red subscribe button
down below as well and come join the
sisterhood
also click that Bell icon so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video
if you'd like to follow me on a makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they are both the same
Charles and my snapchat for more I have
the scene size-up is James Charles the
next your ass after Charles this big
shadow ghost assists our lad thank you
so much for your always solving good
supporting you I love you so so so much
and if you'd like to read the next video
sister shadow don't forget that way
Street week video link so they go live
on Twitter alright guys thank you so
much for watching this video thank you
again to jenna Marbles i love you so
much and I will see you in the next one
[Music]
I don't mean all that he ought to do
this Oh
oh my god so much better