did you ever have a thing with noah back
did you actually steal these designs
from teddy fresh jeans are you
subscribed to anybody on only fans
are you actually a virgin did you ever
get more cosmetic surgery on your body
i like some more hi sisters james
charles here and welcome back
to my youtube channel for today's video
i am
a little bit nervous because i'm doing
something that i've never done here
before
on this channel or actually ever in my
life and that is
taking a polygraph test as you guys know
i'm always telling the truth on
social media and um
[Music]
lewis and the team thought it would be a
wonderful fun idea to hook me up and ask
me some really really juicy questions
we have john here you guys may have seen
him before he's done like collaborations
with everybody before huh he's very
famous very professional and the team
and a few
friends and special guests are going to
ask me some very very
juicy questions and i'm going to
probably tell the truth
i am not a very good lie like if i'm
ambling
it's good that little polygon thing is
gonna be flying all around the screen we
have a lot of questions
okay should we get hooked up and ready
to go okay
john i have a question for you and like
crimes why don't they literally just
hook everyone up to a polygraph
chapstick did you do this
yes or no james just solved crime
why not if like okay whatever
okay so john what happens if james lies
when a person lies we can find
changes in their blood sweat and
breathing oh
[Music]
okay james charles dickinson yes should
i start off
really giving it to you sure so today
you launched a sister's apparel
classroom collection
yes
[Applause]
the gals want to know did you actually
steal these designs from teddy fresh no
that's true next question
did you ever have a thing with noah back
no i wish
i can't believe people actually thought
that like that was stupid this is a
video really just bringing it all yeah
[Music]
questions right away um
do you think that you can beat larry in
a fight watch your mouth
uh like what kind of fight physical i
guess
for you physical no but in lawyers and
like court
probably yeah so obviously not i don't
want to fight anybody so like if i was
forced
that's true i still want to see it
okay james charles have you ever done a
collab with someone you didn't like
at the time of recording
no true
there are definitely people that i've
clogged with oh just like after the time
of
recording that's for sure we got that
much yeah are there any beauty
influencers that
doesn't deserve their career yes
true would you like to give names no
james charles yes have you ever stolen a
makeup look
and not given credit
uh yeah
a long a long time ago but now i always
make sure to do it but if there is an
actual look that i see on my floor page
and i
literally am looking at it as i'm
recreating it like to figure out how
they did it for inspiration
i have no problem giving credit oh yeah
james gonna put this one arrest
did you actually say the n word on new
year's eve when we're singing along to
sweden
no you did
[Music]
thank god you're not an idiot your pr
smart
also a lot of people that send me their
like subscription like link for free and
i
always accept it you can do that
yeah i need it too james would you ever
get more cosmetic surgery on your body
i like more uh yes
true i told you guys i wasn't i didn't
feel like i needed to lie
you're can you lie i'm bored
um james yeah we're really close you
like my girly
yes me and my boyfriend together would
you
slide into the end
no i got a good right hook like nobody
knows
no july oh
if brady and larry were never together
would you slide into brady's dx yes
your boyfriend's literally the most
perfect person on the planet
like he looks like he was picked out of
the sims yeah if larry and brady break
up
tomorrow let's say would you then slide
into brady's dm
true okay
sylvia
like they sell weed or drugs no are you
sure
yes you look sucks see some of this is
all just
makeup do you believe that tick tockers
deserve to be as famous as they are
some of them that's for yes or no
interesting would you like to elaborate
yeah i think some of the people that
have become famous from tech talk do
deserve it but i definitely
before tick tock the only way to really
get popular the internet was like
youtube where like twitch which i feel
like definitely requires a lot more
work than how a lot of the big tick
talkers think famous
agree have you ever hooked up with an
influencer's ex
yes true
you're a bad [ __ ] have you ever hooked
up with an influencer with
more than a million combined followers
yes
five million combined followers yes
anyone want to buy 10 million combined
followers
yes
okay am i a talk can you just say yes
[Music]
yes
yes do you believe you're a good singer
um yeah it's true
i don't think i'm the best singer james
charles yeah do you believe the james
charles x morphe palette is the best
palette ever made
no
why i mean i guess that's good for me
but i think better better is a
subjective term
okay well we're deflecting better in
terms of like formula better in terms of
like
more use was your account hacking
just a ploy just so you could leak your
butt picks
no true
but it was a fun part that was
horrifying but i thought might as well
make the most of it
have you ever collabed with someone that
has a bad makeup line out
no you know i'm thinking further
yeah oh see that was an example of me
genuinely thinking that i was giving a
true answer but
that was not true and now i'm realizing
that
technology is crazy do you believe that
you're the hardest working influencer
no
true who per se um
i think logan actually works really hard
i definitely respect his
work ethic uh the difference yeah love
him
i know he's not up there though james
charles has there ever been an outfit
that you've worn to
let's say an important red carpet or
event that you have
hated
which one i'll actually hear you that
often was so good
james have you ever stolen something
you've ever stolen something
like from a store like just anything men
including i
personally like some more thing
are you planning on firing any of your
workers
yes
absolutely not true
i feel like me and drew were like
literally some ways but neither one of
us are each other's type but like if we
were we would have gotten married
yeah we literally have every single
compatibility on
that thing have you ever fantasized
about one of your friends
no so why
what do you consider friend group like
oh
oh no yes i have yeah i thought about it
further yeah definitely
are you into black eyes yes
are you actually a virgin um
and and like oh
you ever hooked up with someone after
getting off the plane and not showering
and him eating your ass
poor child
have you ever
[Music]
do you want to change your last name
yeah
james charles do you think
[Laughter]
larry i cannot answer that question this
word enough of this video
okay let me elaborate do
all right you guys well with that being
said i think we're probably going to
complete that
anyway that is the completion of this
polygraph test thank you so much john
for administering
this to me today how would you say it
like did i perform because i feel like i
told the truth for a lot of the
questions you're an honest person oh
i love that i think you're a little too
honest with your honest too
i definitely had fun and i really hope
that you guys enjoyed this fun
live detector test video and learned a
little bit more about me
if you didn't enjoy it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and share love and support also
click that big subscribe button to come
join the sisterhood and finally click
that bell icon so you can notified every
time i upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me on my
makeup journey all my social media
accounts will be linked right here
around
the screen and if you want to text me on
my personal phone number for new videos
photos merch and so much more it is
three run out 905 8746 this video sister
shout out goes to sister scarlett thank
you so much love for always following
and supporting i love you so
so much and if you would like to do the
next video sister shout out don't forget
to always
reach for the links in the live on
twitter and also turn on my youtube post
notification
all right sisters thank you so much for
watching i love you
and i will see you in the next one bye
[Music]
you