hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so as
you can see today I am rocking this
super super simple but also get super
glam and effective black smoked out
winged liner I freaking love how this
look turned out and it is of course
inspired by the legendary Kim K herself
and this picture that Mario denna
banovic posted on his Instagram I know I
just did a k'kaw Beauty review and a
kendall Jenner inspired look a few weeks
ago but I cannot even begin to explain
when I saw this original picture of my
mouth dropped to the floor it was just
so beautiful and so stunning but also so
simple and effective at the same time I
just needed to recreate it and show you
guys how to do it before we actually get
into this look I have just a little
something for you guys and that is going
to be a giveaway so as you guys know and
if you saw my video from a few weeks ago
the Jacqueline Hill & morphe brushes
collab just launched and it's probably
one of the best palettes of all time
I do actually use this palette in the
video today but obviously I use like my
crusty dusty used version not the brand
new one when the original palette
launched it did end up selling out in
only 45 minutes and that left a ton of
you guys without in your hands so I
thought it would be a perfect giveaway
being that the palette does actually
restock tomorrow morning at 8 a.m.
California time of course you can use
co2 change for 10% off as always you
guys need to get your hands on this
thing but just in case you can't I will
be giving away one of these babies right
here and I'm so freaking excited to tell
you how all you have to do to enter
yourself to win is go give this video a
big thumbs up down below come on go do
it right now sister and then just leave
a comment I need comment whatever you
want to say say hello say this makeup
look looks amazing say what you're
eating for breakfast this morning
I don't really care just leave some
comment that will instantly enter you to
win I'll pick a winner one week from
today and I will contact you by DM to
let you know that you won and ask your
like address and everything and then
I'll of course update the description
and to let you guys know the contest is
closed good luck you guys and back to
the video if you want to see how I
created this smokey winged out Kim
Kardashian inspired makeup look make
sure you keep on watching
alright sir I already went ahead and
primed my face using my benefit total
moisture moisturizer and then my benefit
Porefessional primer as always I'm gonna
put on a headband here because my hair
is looking a real real wonky today and
it's not styling for the life of me so I
kind of just gave up I'm gonna throw in
a hat as soon as possible just bear with
me while I do my base here and I
I will fix this situation in a few
minutes for my foundation today as
always I'm gonna be using my makeup
forever Ultra HD foundation stick in the
shade of y 335 and I'm just gonna put
this all over my face but I'm actually
not going to use too much of it today
and then of course I'm just gonna take
my damp Beauty blender and blend this in
for concealer today we're going to be
using of course Maya tart shaped tape
concealer of the Holy Grail and today
I'm using the shade light I have usually
been using the shade light medium honey
recently but in the photo Kim definitely
has some very very very high contrast
between the rest of her face and her
like t-zone region being her under eyes
in the very center of her forehead so I
do want to recruit that as much as
possible and add that our Vic terno
2010 at Kim K SIA of glam I'm so
freaking excited to see the fact that
she's definitely going back to her like
roots with the full on full coverage
glam
I missed that Kim so much it was by far
my favorite era of hers I do obviously
love the natural face she's in as well
as I've said a million times in the past
few videos but you always got to go back
to your roots at some point
all right so I just went ahead and
quickly set my face and locked it in
place using my Too Faced Born This Way
ethereal setting powder I have a very
very exciting and fun video coming out
in a few weeks from now about setting
powders and the battle between them and
flashback and everything and you can
possibly think of because lord knows I
am the queen of setting powders and
flashback photos so definitely stay
tuned for that coming soon so in the
photo that Mario posted Kim was
definitely super super bronzed and
contoured so of course I want to
recreate that as much as possible
because y'all know I love a good runs in
contoured look so of course I'm gonna
start off like I'm in my benefit hoola
bronzer and my morphe M 570 brush and
you can use code at James for 10% off
your purchase at morphe brushes com I'm
just gonna start chiseling out my
cheekbones and really warming up the
outside edges of my face I am definitely
rubbing a decent amount of this product
when I actually go and I am going pretty
light handed with this brush because I
do want a lot of product on there but I
want to build it up slowly over time
because if we put a lot on there at one
time is just gonna get super super muddy
and obviously we want it to be super
super blended out and nice and beautiful
and bronzy so I am just being a pretty
careful to go nice and slow and just
disperse the color evenly all throughout
my face I'm also going to use this color
to bronze up my forehead as always
I'm also gonna grab my age 80 81 82 Luxy
180 perhaps oh my god and dip it into a
little bit more of hoola bronzer just to
lightly contour my nose I'm actually not
gonna do the very signature snatched
James Charles nose I just want to do a
light contour just a little something
but definitely not super super intense
because it's just gonna look very very
wonky with this look because we do want
to go for that natural more dewy skin
all right so you guys know I'm a very
very loyal more if you stand up but
there's one nod morphing brush that I
have been absolutely obsessive lately
and that is the makeup Shack t89 brush
it's just this fluffy brush and I am
gonna grab this using my Kat Von D shade
and light palette and I'm gonna tip into
it the darkest shade of the contour
palette and I am going to definitely
dust off that brush because I don't want
too much but I've been loving this brush
for just going in the very very very
hollow of my cheek bone right in the
bottom of that contour I feel like it
really defines the contour so well it
also allows you to blend it out so you
don't get that like really really harsh
light but it definitely does look super
super cut and defined and natural and
then of course I'm just gonna go back
into my original M 574 morphe and just
blend that oh and like oh my god look at
how good that looks it looks like a
natural super super defined Angelina
Jolie cheekbone I freaking love these
two brushes together it's a match made
in heaven
I don't want to bake today just because
I do want my skin to be really really
moist and hydrated but the one thing I
am gonna do is guy my Beauty Blender I
just admit to a tiny bit of that setting
powder and just lock in the sides of my
nose just to snatch that nose contour a
little bit and just to hold it in place
because it's already getting oily
because of these studio lights in front
of me and it is very very hot in
California today so I definitely don't
my nose to melt
okay finally I can take this stupid
headband off and replace it with my huh
thank God alright so for blush today you
guys know that I usually use Mac peaches
this is my all-time favorite blush but
for today I'm actually gonna exchange
that and I'm going to be using the Mac
blushes in the shade spring sheen
instead this is actually a very very
similar color to peaches when you put
them next to each other but Spring Sheen
does have a little bit of shimmer to it
which is perfect because we definitely
want that radiant skin look and we are
gonna be using a lot of gold tone
highlighter as well so this will just do
a good job of mending everything
together alright so I just went ahead
and quickly did my brows and my eye
primer off-camera and you guys have seen
me do a million times out there is no
point in including it let's go ahead and
get started well we're all waiting for
and that is the eye shadow so for this I
said a look today I'm gonna use in the
morphe X chocolate Hill eyes shadow
palette now obviously this look is
mostly black land we're just a pinch of
brown and warm tone orange but this
palette is just so freakin bomb and so
pigmented as I'm sure you've heard it
literally everybody and their mothers
say it but it is actually true so if
you're watching this today on Monday the
17th this palette is actually
relaunching and coming back in stock
tomorrow Tuesday the 18th and I know so
many of you guys missed you rich in the
launch it's sold out at only 45 minutes
and I know not a lot of people were able
to get their hands on them which is why
I'm doing the giveaway in the beginning
of the video like to talk about so if
you have not thumbs up this video and
comment it down below definitely go do
that but like I said this will be
restocking tomorrow so if you would like
to try it it goes live at 10:00 a.m. and
you can use code jinx for 10% off your
purchase this palette is something you
need in your collection I am not kidding
when I say it is so beyond good before
we get into the actual liner I do just
want her to find my crease a little bit
and for this I'm gonna grab my morphe
m43 3 brush and dip into the shade
butter and just put this right into the
crease this step is definitely not vital
you can totally skip out and go right to
the liner portion but since I did it
prime my eyelids with some concealer and
not like a transparent primer I do just
want to add a little bit of dimension
back into my eyelid but that's just
personal preference I'm going to take a
quick break from the palette for a
second and I'm gonna grab my Inglot gel
liner in the shade block obviously to
start off this wing and just catch this
out I'm gonna use my sigma e06 winged
liner brush
it has been so long stuck on a winged
liner using a gel liner my hands are
shaking so hardcore / some reason I
don't know why I'm like still nervous to
do this oh my god with this liner I'm
also going to make sure to tight line up
my waterline as well because there's
definitely a very very smoky look going
on alright so I just went ahead and I
tight line off-camera using my edge away
a black pencil clearly that's the
tration was not working out too well and
I do not want to risk anything again and
of course I still managed to somehow
smudge black liner onto my lid but you
know what we're just gonna do with it
we're gonna move on alright so going
back to my tiny little liner brush I'm
gonna dip into the English eyeliner one
last time I'm gonna draw this little
wing in the center corner of the eye
look this is obviously featured in Kim's
look and this is a very very popular
technique in Arabic makeup that just is
so so freakin beautiful I personally
have a very very hard time doing this
because I do have a little bit of skin
that actually covers my inner corner but
I'm just gonna draw over it and hope
that it it works kind of now going back
into Thor female I'm gonna grab my two
one two brush and I'm just gonna dip
into the shade abyss which is just this
black in the bottom corner it is so
freaking pigmented and we were going to
use that shade to smoke out our liner
today
this looks awful okay this literally
looks awful so I'm going to try to take
off the outer wing portion how you asked
I have no idea all right now that the
wing isn't taking up our entire eyelid
let's go ahead and try this again my two
one two once again at dipping into abyss
let's go ahead and smoke out this liner
very very carefully the nerves degree of
my makeup Shakti to brush and I'm just
going to smoke out the edges at once
again and then finally my morphe m56 one
okay honestly for an I we had a
completely performing surgery on and
this really did not turn out that bad
thank God I'm not going to go mighty to
brush and dab back into a best and I'm
going to smoke out the lower lash line
as well I'm just keeping this color
super super close to the lash line
because we do want that smoky effect but
not bringing it down too low because we
don't want to be really really
overpowering and we're essentially
making sure to really concert that color
on at the outer corner and connecting up
to the way to really like circulate and
complete the eye I'm gonna go to the my
m56 one brush and just buff over the
edge to make sure it's not going too low
as you can see this look is actually
super super simple to achieve it just
looks complicated and you definitely to
be careful because the black
I can definitely end up everywhere as
you just saw so just be careful when
you're blending but let's go ahead and
move on to it the lashes so for the
lashes today I definitely do something
very natural in the picture of Kim who's
actually only wearing mascara which
makes me so freakin angry like oh the
fact that anybody can have natural
lashes that good is so beyond me because
unfortunately I cannot relate so for the
lashes today I just want to use the
ardell demi whispies these are a very
brave natural pair I used to use these
on all the girls in my local hometown
when I did their prom makeup they're
just very very beautiful but definitely
are just a little bit of
something-something so I'm just gonna
glue them on of course as always
and then just to blend my regular lashes
with my fake ones together I'm gonna
grab my benefit roller lash mascara and
just play a very very light coat
so both eyes are now complete and of
course the next type is going to be the
glow I know I use this one all the time
but for today I'm using my Anasazi so
Hollywood illuminator this is one of my
all-time faves and for this look we
definitely do want to be super super
gold then I cannot think of a better
gold highlighter than this one and to
play uncle using my morphe EMB 23 brush
oh wow yeah and you guys know normally I
would use my morphe M 501 brush this is
like my go-to highlighter but recently
I've been actually loving using a
smaller brushes of four highlighters to
get like a more precise and confined
highlighter I don't know if you think
I'm getting a board of like the look of
highlighter like everywhere all over the
face i doesn't really love you to look
like a natural natural tiny to find
highlighter moment I don't know personal
preference do whatever you want
oh my god yes this literally looks so
frickin pretty Wow okay this area of my
forehead is actually still my favorite
places the highly on my entire face and
I've been getting a lot of questions
about it lately - everyone's like why
the hell are you highlighting your
forehead I thought you wanted to make it
look smaller and well yes I definitely
do that is for sure when you sweat
obviously this way is going to hit the
light and it's gonna reflect naturally
where the light or where the liquid is
on your face that's just how science
works Wow
so by adding highlighter here and making
that light hit it and catch it it just
helps to kind of further along the look
of that dewy and not your foundation
because not all of us unfortunately can
be blessed with that beautiful glowing
skin but we got to fake it till we make
it for lips today I'm first gonna go
into the dose of colors new lipstick in
the shade
Kim definitely was wearing a glossy lip
as well so I'm gonna layer over top of
the it mac lipglass in the shade
see-through as well and then for one
final pop I'm just gonna layer these
away skinny dip lip topper right in the
center of the bottom lip just for a
little bit of gold glitter realness
oh I almost forgot to highlight my
collarbones as well alright guys and
that is the Kim K inspired arabic black
winged out smokey eye i freaking love
how this lip turn out I think it is so
beautiful in sunny as I said before I
really never ever did these like inner
corner points but I honestly really
really like how it looks today
I'm kind of shook if you guys did enjoy
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not already click
that notification roll because I am now
gonna be posting three videos a week
Lauren Hubley on Mondays Wednesdays and
Fridays I have a ton of amazing videos
and amazing projects and amazing collabs
coming out very very soon so definitely
keep your eyes peeled I am so excited
for this channel to grow and explode
because there's a lot of very very cool
stuff in the works
this week's shout-out goes to sister
Gianna thank you so much girl for always
following and supporting you know I love
you if you would like to be at next
video sister shout out make sure to
always read through my video legs so
they go live on Twitter and that is it
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching this video and I will see you
on Wednesday bye
[Music]