hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I am very excited because
we are doing something that we have not
done in quite a long time but I love to
do and that is a makeup challenge
now this particular challenge has been
requested non-stop in my comments with
lost several videos in a row and I've
actually wanted to do this for so long
so I'm very very excited and this is
what I think I'm going to call it the
LED lights challenge now you're probably
wondering James what the heck are you
talking about and don't worry I'm gonna
explain it to you right now it is a huge
trend for people to buy LED at little
light trips and put them at the top of
their rooms for cool fun lighting
effects and also tik-tok transitions
now speaking of tick-tock this actually
became a trend octave talked a few weeks
ago where basically people were changing
the color of their lights and doing
their makeup in a specific color now
this may not seem too difficult because
we all have our everyday makeup products
that we know and love abut where it gets
very difficult is the eyeshadow portion
I want to show you guys a quick example
because a lot of people were actually
using my palette for this challenge
because there are 39 beautiful rainbow
colors but when you turn on your LED
lights like this it's not so very blue
anymore and now they all look the exact
same so for this challenge today I'm not
beneath my palette because I have it
memorized I'm gonna pick up a random
colorful palette from my makeup
collection and I'm gonna try my best to
do my full face of makeup and a
beautiful eye shadow look using only a
colorful LED lighting and at the end of
this video you and I will find out
together how actually turns out let's
get started
[Music]
okay you guys I just want to talk about
right not only because I'm excited but
also because this is really hurting my
eyes and like messing up my overall
vision like I said in the beginning the
face person is probably gonna be pretty
easy so I'm just gonna speed through
that but let's go ahead and get started
I am first going to color correct using
my bright green dragon beauty color
corrector I'm gonna put it on my beard
area this looks so crazy and this
lighting holy crop and quite let's go
ahead and blend this end just bringing
the excess underneath the eyes or some
nice dark circle coverage now for a
foundation I'm gonna mix together my
noble two which is the Dior air flash
and fenty Pro filter in the shade at 150
foundation matching is already hard for
me in a normal lighting so this lighting
should be a very interesting I know
these two colors mix very well to make
my skin tone but I'm not really sure
what this looks like I'm just gonna
blend it in using my Beauty sponge as
always I mean I have no idea if my
foundations like well this is actually
harder than I even thought
well concealer I'm just gonna grab my
shape tape it in the shade light just
gonna put this in my normal high points
of my face so nigh use the wrong shade
no no this is tripping me out okay I'm
gonna blend it in I'm just going to set
this with powder like always using the
other side of my sponge pressing it in
there to lock it it kind of contours
always easing my anasazi up Beverly
Hills contour kits I do know where the
actual colors are on this palette and I
know that I always use this middle one
but I don't think I can't really tell
how intense this is gonna look I just
think my normal skin oh no I'm Simon
well I'm actually getting nervous about
this okay and I'm just going to contour
my nose as well this might get bad fast
I'm gonna come out of here and have like
the harshest nose contour of our weight
it literally looks like there's nothing
there but I'm also scared of it packing
it on there and then turning the light
back on and looking insane so I'm like
trying to tread lightly here and be
careful don't do contour my forehead
yeah I did not bronze thought that I did
not do okay so lately bronzing a little
bit of blush using the Kylie cosmetics
pink dreams which looks bright yellow
[Music]
look oh my god this is so insane what
the hatch we try to change the color and
see if it looks different like a
different color I'm sure it will right
let's let's try it
whoa oh here I can dip my nose contour
is definitely there I can see that oh oh
I can see the colors a little bit easier
in the blue everything good sneeze we
come stand in here and see if it looks
slow hmm oh I took a block light
oh whoa it's like a block like that when
you're like investigating a crime scene
you're looking for hidden specimens okay
well now looking in this light I can
tell my contour is a little harsh
oh holy crap
for brows Otis could use my Anasazi
eyebrow powder and the shade and medium
brown and I'm just gonna clean my brows
up using a little bit of concealer and a
flat top brush I think this is good it
was definitely harder than I thought but
I think if we flicked the lights back on
right now it would look okay that being
said we're about to move into the eye
shadow portion and this is where it gets
a very very difficult I would love to
say in this blue lighting because it
hurts my head a lot less and I can
actually see a little bit of colors but
this is a makeup challenge
I don't want the speed too easy so let's
go ahead and flip the LED lights you
look at my skin yeah ah oh that is a
harsh contour oh my god did I really
contour things that harsh Princess Fiona
for this videos today I'm going to use
the Stacey at Marie xB perfect cosmetics
carnival palette because in normal
lighting this is a very very beautiful
and pigmented or rainbow palette similar
to mine but I don't have any of the
color positions memorized at all so the
finished result will be colorful could
be good it could be bad on but we're not
gonna find out until then so let's jump
in since we are focus on the eyes for
this challenge I do think it would be
fun it also might really come back to
bite me in the butt to do one eye in the
green lighting and a certain color
combination and then switch the lighting
and do a different color combination in
a different color and then in the end
when we turned the normal light back on
and see which I actually like looks
better and it's like a better color
situation but I have plans to go out to
dinner with my friends after this and
being in public might not be a good idea
so I'm going to of course prime my lids
using a little bit of concealer and I'm
gonna do my left eye first I'm first
gonna grab a four five six brush which
is my custom brush that I created with
morphia let's go James for 10% off and
let's do
to the shade no no idea okay let's do
her suasion I don't know what this color
is
but it looks like it's a lighter color
than a lot of the other ones so at least
that means we'll be able to like put it
in the right place so I'm gonna grab
persuasion and I'm gonna use this brush
that i'm gonna start patting it in my
outer corner in a nice little v-shape
and now I'm gonna grab a and 4-3-3 brush
and let's dip into the color show boat
I'm gonna use show boat to blend out
persuasion I'm gonna next gonna have
another M 4-3-3 brush and dip into the
shade called the height and I was gonna
put this in my inner corner and blending
those together in person the blend of
this looks really really beautiful and
on camera it looks no it looks okay
still but it could look better this is
actually really fun I'm sure I say that
now until I turn the lights back on and
I look like I got hit by a bus now gonna
grab a little bit more of persuasion on
my own four five six brush I'm going to
tuck this underneath my lash line like
this and no grabbing some of showboat on
my other brush and buffing that color
out so now that that is there so there's
this color in this palette
it's called ecstasy and it's looking
like it is lime-green and I'm gonna grab
ecstasy on a pencil brush and I'm going
to press this in my inner corner for a
nice vivid hop the fact that it's not
even showing up on my skin it makes me
think that it probably is actually a
neon green color and I'm just going to
cut my crease using a little bit of a
concealer and a flat top brush I'm gonna
get the shade of peppermint and I'm
gonna give it a nice spread of some
prepping setting spray and then I'm
going to pack this on the lid carefully
packing this color on there making sure
not to mess up my cut crease and I'm
also gonna take the color
backchecked so I'm going to put this
particular color on the lid as well in
this like outer area and that was my
same M 4 or 5 6 brush before diving a
little bit more of persuasion I'm just
going to top this over the edge and make
sure it is nice
blended out alright so I think that is
pretty much one I all complete I have no
idea what that's gonna look like I'm
gonna add of course lashes and mascara
after but for now let's go ahead and
switch the lighting one more time and
move on to the other eye and see what we
can come up with oh no oh God what the
heck what is what I do I look like I
have a black eye this is it looks so
normal and the right thing oh my god
this is so bad
well we have nothing to lose now so
we're just gonna go ahead a Primus other
eyelid so I definitely need some of the
colors in the palette that we didn't use
it the last time so this time I'm gonna
grab the shade
let's try covering the shade of wasted
in this lighting the shade looks like a
light purple so grabbing the shade of
wasted I won't say another M 4 5 6 brush
and putting this in the outer area and
topping this M okay I'm just putting us
in the same type of motion and lightly
blending out the edges as we go next I'm
gonna grab the shade in lust I don't
know this is gonna be what we're gonna
try to blend out wasted using this color
don't be shy put some more ok blending
this out now with another M 4 5 6 brush
let's grab the color lips because our
mmhmm yeah let's go the color left
because it is right next to endless
sometime I think this is gonna be nice
and warm tone as opposed to whatever we
have going on over here
blend it down to the lower lash line as
well for the public art on this eye I'm
gonna grab the shade called pepti in the
bottom of the palette so we're gonna cut
our crease once again okay once you're
gonna grab me another flat brush I'm
gonna dip into let's do the shade of
pink me I know for a fact this one's
gonna be pink because of the name so
thank you Stacy for that one and we're
gonna put this one all over the lid up
just like we did with our last color
keeping it nice and light for the outer
portion I'm gonna get a little bit of
the shade at temptation I'm gonna put
this to blend together that pink talked
and wasted color alright you guys so
that is the shadow portion of both eyes
all complete I'm horrified because this
eye it looked a lot like this I did
before we switch the lighting so I don't
know what's gonna happen when we change
the color next but before we do that I'm
gonna go ahead and apply it lashes and
mascara and then we
we'll finish off this long alright you
guys we are back I popped on lashes and
mascara thank god the only color
involved with those are black so no
surprises there so let's go ahead and do
a highlighter I'm just gonna grab my
highlighting brush and the B probe it
tells that I thought about actually has
highlighters in it so I'm just gonna go
this top one because it looks like it's
the lightest and let's go ahead and just
pop this on look at all the top of the
brows it's always a little bit on the
chin and then my nose highlight as well
okay so our last and final step is going
to be at the lips and I could just go
ahead and grab a nude lip that I have on
my desk because I use them all the time
but this is already a mess okay let's be
real said to get more fun to reach into
my lipstick drawer and just pick out a
random color and see what ends up
happening once again alright so I went
ahead and I picked at this one from
Kylie cosmetics I have not looked at the
actual name but I picked this color
because it looked a little bit different
tone wise than a lot of the other
lipsticks that I knew were nudes in the
drawer so hopefully this will be
something fun that was saying that still
matches with the rest of the look
alright
I think that is this look all complete
I'm gonna go ahead give myself a quick
spritz of my morphia helping set setting
spray to really lock it in place and now
it is time ladies and gentleman after a
very long and scary makeup application
process to turn off our LED lights and
switch back to our normal Beauty
lighting and see what the heck we have
on our face are you guys ready one two
three I'm gonna look down first so my
eyes can adjust back to normal colors
okay okay oh wait a second this is cute
like not good not good but oh my god
wait a second what you know I just far
as I'm wearing green lipstick I have a
nun green lipstick like that's cute
I like none of this the skin doesn't
look that bad and this lip color was
definitely the worst decision out of all
of them otherwise you guys well I think
that is this LED lights makeup challenge
all complete I had a so much fun filming
this today despite the fact that it was
quite the emotional roller coaster all
the way it through I went into this with
very very low expectations because I'm
so used to my beautiful white lighting
and I had a feeling that the colored
lighting was going to be very very
deceiving and oh boy was it in the end
do feel like both looks that we came up
with are kind of cute I had fun and
that's all that matters and I really
really hope you guys enjoyed this as
well if you did it please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
and show your love and support it really
just helped me out so much and also if
any of you guys have LED lights in your
bedroom we'll try out this challenge
turn off your normal lights and turn on
your LED lights and grab your favorite
rainbow eyeshadow palette of course I'm
gonna recommend my palette but you can
use ever you have in your collection and
see what crazy eyeshadow look that you
guys can come up with please tweet me
photos or typing in them I would love it
to see your guys's at creations if
you're not ready make sure you click
that big red subscribe button down below
as well and come join this sisterhood we
were almost 17 million sister strong and
I love to have you and join the family
and also click that Mouse icon so you
could notification every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on our makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram Twitter Facebook intake talk
to elder's James Charles and my snapshot
from our behind the scenes I've stopped
in senior house the next row asked after
Charles you can also text me one-on-one
at my personal phone number three one oh
nine oh five eight seven four six four
all your video updates new photos merch
drops and so much more exclusive info
also I send out a personalized birthday
a voice memo every single day to all my
sisters that have a birthday so it's
kind of late send me a text that I
cannot wait to talk to you guys soon
this video is sister shot at gooses
sister Joe thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting I love you
so so so much and if you'd like to be
the next videos a sister shadow don't
forget to always retweet Avenue is legal
I'm on Twitter and also to my YouTube
post notifications alrighty guys thank
you so much for watching I love you and
I will see you in at the next one bye
[Music]