hi kitty girls
James Charles here and welcome back to
our YouTube channel as you can see under
the day very special guest okay
so for today's video we are doing a
wonderful idea
after you nights ago meeting and we're
sitting and talking and just having a
good and fresh time like the sisters
that we are and we were discussing our
first ever collabs on YouTube you're
talking about their first ever video
that we did together on my channel the
introduction of sister yen which was him
doing my makeup and why not that that he
was brought up in discussion Ian said I
could easily pick out your makeup
products and probably do a good job
because you know make a profession on
that or just like you what exactly makes
me think that I would love to know me
and we did that video did the woman I
did my own makeup I was you for a day
I've said a lot of experience around
makeup now so you know so she's cocky
you love a cocky sister really Dale
honestly I will admit when he entered
his own makeup for the life swap series
he did do a a pretty decent job but
since the first video that we film every
single time I have picked out the
products for Ian to use and put that
much knocked up in front of him every
single step taken care of and walked him
through the actual makeup application
process okay yes but I've had experience
so I remembered the names and like what
you need you think you're everything I
think I remember every product not like
the brands and what type think I know
what you need just don't know who well
that's great it has first today's video
I had the novel idea to have Ian go to
the makeup store with my credit card
puts already scary thought so yeah it's
gonna be picking out all of my makeup
and then I'm going to have to use that
makeup and do it this video concept
really doesn't seem as exciting when you
really lay it down it's gonna be
exciting right now can you quickly list
to me all of the staffs of the makeup
routine okay so we got foundation
concealer setting powder setting spray
nine order oh well no I want them in
order oh I don't know okay keep lying
foundation concealer setting powder
setting spray mascara eyelashes bronzer
eyeshadow
brow gel or pencil and lipstick just
because you have the stops down does not
mean that you know what products to get
or buy shades
oh yeah Shea's another thing let me
guess more like kind of the same like
shades on the face so not really I'll go
like one thing lighter than what I think
works for me okay
so I did like a color coordinated look -
yeah you should probably make sure it
looks nice together I have to worry okay
I forgot to say tail hello I'm going to
a really important event later on
tonight my best friend ooh you're going
to yes this is true but you don't have
to our makeup to it
yeah I'm more important we are going to
a makeup launch tonight and I have to
look very good because this is going to
be pressed there and this is a very
important launch to me because it is my
best friend - melty it she's launching
saline to you on halo Beauty I'm super
proud of her by the tennis videos Oh
it'll already be up so go check it out
problem for talk to you love it smells
you have to wear this look to top these
over yeah so please make it good I mean
I will try alright sister so that
further ado Ian I am putting my full-on
makeup routine and your hands today I'm
gonna call you an uber to Alta I will
not be going this is all on you and wait
what about the special announcement
ah t so you say now we're at the end of
the video end of the video make them
wait
oh no quick marketing going on okay yeah
we do have a special announcement for
the end of this video
stay tuned wait for it it is a good and
fresh sister announce that okay this is
go
[Music]
we are heading to alta to get some
makeup for James I'm gonna try my best
to figure out what he uses on the daily
it's kind of nervous but I forget
something or not get the right shades or
products or brands the makeup products
that I bond James he's gonna be using
for Tottie's event tonight so I have a
lot more pressure on me to get the right
products to make them look a sister
stash for tonight alright guys we just
got the Ulta and I'll walk around and
try to find the products this place is
huge there's everything here so it's
gonna be difficult book let's go yeah
we're gonna find foundation first
foundation where you at that's this
foundation primer we need primer too
don't we Oh God maybe this thing is like
a champagne
what is this one this one's perfect yeah
let's get my brow pencil is there
different shades in these two oh my gosh
sure yeah I think he likes liquid
lipstick so this is nude kisses okay
yeah so we got this so far we got liquid
lipstick brow pencil foundation than a
primer we still need mascara eye shadow
powder and concealer what type of look
is he going for he didn't give me any
ideas he just said buy me makeup sorry
so got the eye shadow I think he's gonna
want to use more like the pinkish tones
it's a matching with the lipstick I'm
smart right now I really should have
looked at his makeup room before I came
here
cuz I don't know any brands that he uses
I haven't even seen concealer anywhere I
know what it was Urban Decay settings
Urban Decay settings retinue it that's a
thing okay
tart shake Cape where you at so I think
concealer has to be lighter than the
foundation to a certain extent if I'm
correct ban medium sand sounds about
right
soft light blend powder it's just hiding
powder I think yeah set in Africa so we
got some setting powder from Becca James
I feel like I'm not getting the right
brands and they're gonna get mad at me
but I'm sorry I'm trying my best here
so mascara the lashes in a highlighter
and I think we're done oh okay okay
mascara maybe he uses this brand burning
it black no matter what's probably think
mascara matters that much especially
he's gonna put lashes on so let me grab
one of these ultra black pigments okay
we got black mascara where is it lashes
at I need some Miami's I don't know what
brand that is but I need my Eunice here
all the washes I don't see Miami's how
do you pick out good eyelashes I don't
know what friends are good I don't know
they seem pretty cheap I honestly don't
know then these are good what about
these
to go with these he's looking about the
right length and James always cuts him
anyways these look good we got brow gel
I think he needs this so I'm gonna throw
that in there welcome James and its new
bronzer it shouldn't be this difficult
what is this okay this is our
highlighter matches with the nation of
the other stuff okay bronzer and I think
we're did smells like peaches maybe
James wants someone else ones like
peaches
now we're getting this two-faced
smells like peaches BAM I think that is
everything I don't know how I did I know
I got all the right products I don't
know about the brands or the colors or
how well it's gonna work together but
we'll see James good luck man okay guys
I picked all the products and now I have
everything he needs but I don't think
it's the right brands but I think he can
make it work James I tried my best man
hopefully you look good tonight how was
I like knew what to get brands or what
shades to get so that was the challenge
wasn't like organized so I was like oh I
need foundation here's all the brands a
foundation we got sort of friends yes
that's me I made it difficult oh my god
what if makeup stores were organized
like my product
that's smart I don't know why it's not
kind of a really good point actually
Wow okay anyway how are you reveal them
to me okay okay so we're gonna start it
off for a primer okay benefit
Porefessional it's a good brand aha
don't use this anymore
bye fine oh great start and then we got
some setting spray okay
urban decay deselect this is a good one
okay this is what I'm scared about the
foundation okay Oh No
you're kidding you know I thought Asian
socks once I here in front of you shed
you just told me yet that is such my
face yeah yeah they'd have to face there
what brand is that yeah they do at all
time okay we're gonna make it work I
made it back to face though you just
told me there was no you have found it
was like peaches all their products do
what okay so this is the Too Faced peach
okay these ones are pretty yeah from
Vegas now I learn logis Lancome
once you're big somebody ain't no really
likes this I think it might be taught to
you oh wow
coincidence okay this is a good one oh
my god oh my god don't do that bad this
is bad the Smashbox cover shot pedal
metal I shut up haha oh Stila
highlighters are actually pretty good
let's go maybe have some tart whatever
that is concealer oh this is their new
one I haven't even tried this yeah oh
yeah get some lip goes okay Laura color
nude kisses
what about that's eyebrow job okay it's
a waterproof eyeliner babes
you might that was very and finally
something that I actually do you is
benefit gimme brow just a free gift that
yes and God the Becca opal highlighter
oh this is actually a good highlighter
we bought three of them
I believe please tell me exciting softly
a blurring powder hopefully I have no
idea I did bad yeah oh my god thanks Ian
thank you so much sweetie windowed here
yeah you can go please go
really tasty good job thanks for
shopping buried today alright guys so
you just left the house to do some more
assists are shopping for tonight's
festivities I have all just products
laid out here in front of me I am
nervous for this because I literally
don't use a single one of these products
in my everyday makeup routine and also
disappointed because evil is very very
convinced that he knew every single
product that I used and it was honestly
getting a little bit excited and really
happy that he felt like he knew my
makeup routine but we are going to make
it work and I appreciate him still
shopping in the first place it's the
thought that counts and I'm going to now
think that I have some sort of talent
and I'm gonna make that thought count
and make this look count because I have
to get ready and I have to go so let's
do this if you've got a long time sister
you would know that I used to use this
primer and literally every single video
but when I would also talk about in
every single video was my foundation
that's slipping off my nose and after a
literal year of trying to fix the
problem I realized that it was this
primer and the ingredients in it that
were causing my foundation to dissipate
on my sister schnoz so that is why I
stopped using this a very very long time
ago but it's still a good primer so I'm
gonna put this on tonight and I am NOT
gonna put it on my nose I'm only gonna
focus this right here in the rankings
that my pores are a little bit there so
for foundation we're gonna be using the
new benefit hello flawless foundation in
the shade I'm so money honey
oh la vache marks that is very me I
don't enjoy the foundation these shade
rains and it launched with was the
sister sad it's just something that I
really like to pearl on this channel and
well benefit does have pretty good brow
products everything else is not good so
I I just want to use that let's do a few
squirts and see how this looks okay
thank God
decent shade match Thank You Ian at
least for the you guys know I really
don't switch out my products that often
but the one thing that I really don't
ever change
is it foundation I've talked about this
before but I use had really bad skin
young credit I'm still a little bit
self-conscious about it and always want
my skin to look very very porcelain a
doll like using a new foundation is
always a little bit of a risky moment
because you never know the type of
coverage or how it's gonna wear or how
it's gonna look throughout the day or
how it's gonna photograph ideally
foundation is just really one of those
things that can totally make or break
your entire makeup look so I would just
rather not risk it
but looks like Ted risking yes that's
good where it's at right now I would not
choose to wear this again but keeping an
open mind I want to finish this look
before I make any comments next step
Taric creaseless concealer I have not
tried this one yet because shape is my
hour late or die I know this one
just launched so let's try this out and
see oh oh my god this is so thick like
me oh my god this concealer is also
yellow
this concealer is pretty much the same
exact shade as my skintone it's just a
little bit more yellow that's a little
bit scary to me as someone who really
likes to have a lot of contrast in their
makeup I guess I'm just got a contour my
face a lot wait
oh my god Ian forgot to get a contract
powder I'm going to be flat for the eye
hold on this is not good
dear Lord and have it please let me not
look flat to this event tonight and
please don't let me take a flash photo
and somebody will say on Twitter and it
go viral and create another beam
actually please do do that I want to
release more roots and make more money
amen now to set this in place I'm gonna
be using the Becca soft light blurring
powder I'm just gonna stop this and -
this is so dark oh my god Ian you're
giving me a racism scandal do I have to
put her to bed with this bonnet Oh
bigger that's already five o'clock the
powder is Occident I have never once
seen this in my entire life but of
course we're witnessing it right now
when we go ahead so glad Burt Brenda
from the apartment tours to be making a
comeback today
you're literally kidding me next up is
going to be contouring but guess what we
don't have
contour maybe this can work as a contour
shade I'm gonna work out this this is
red oh my god my skin is bright yellow
my contour is right and I am going to
die I'll give to take the peach blush
from the middle of this palette and I'm
gonna pop it on for a real and use my
morphe floor brush these coach aims for
10% off wish they had more via alpha
they do have more fuel tie-in you didn't
get a single morphine product I can't
believe I'm contouring my face of the
mob I shadow right now
what has my wave come to okay I'm going
to grab a highlighting brush now this is
the M of 501 and I'm going to open up
the setting spray then I'm gonna dip
into the highlighting shade right here
in the peach oh wait there's another
highlighter we have three highlighters
oh the Becca one the free sample okay
let's do what the peach one mixed
together with Becca opal gonna go the
benefit goof proof brow pencil you got
the shade number 4 thank God that is a
shade that I actually do use oh my god
they look so uneven I never been makeup
again this is fun a PSI
Wow now my brows are all filled in and
looking probably the worst they've ever
looked thank God for benefit gimme brow
so we can set them in place and how they
last all night long
okay it's eyeshadow time we have these
shades we have two mats and one two and
six shimmers why I'm first gonna grab
this mauve shade that I used to
literally contour my face okay
next in to grab an AB 507 brush and this
is where things are gonna get really
tricky because the only other option for
a matte shade in this palette is this
dark brown why I do not know Oh what my
god I am now going to not panic and I'm
going to blend this out okay that looks
okay gonna grab the Becca highlighter as
well on the same approach that I just
used to cut that I'm gonna wet it for a
real one and I'm gonna try it to attempt
to fix this because I am now freaking
out and this is not funny anymore okay
that helped great taking the rosy shade
from the middle of the palette I'm gonna
place that next door next to get this
liner from buxom this is a metallic grey
brown liner it keeps getting worse and
worse
what does this even look like it's
broken great that is what it looks like
I am not using that liner because one
it's broken and I'm Julia sharpen it and
two it already looks bad enough and I
don't want to make it even worse so I'm
gonna fly to Lancome mom's your big
mascara I think this one it's actually
okay I still have not try this but
fingers crossed we'll have one good
moment out of this entire look
I am going to put on an eyelash these
are the islur at vegas night eyelashes
and I will say that a good lash can
really save a lot usually when filming
my videos it is a little bit of a bumpy
road to get to the final product am i
exaggerating my complaining a little bit
yes but is the end result
always redeemable and telling that I'm
proud of yes this is not that I don't
want to say this looks the worse and I
don't know how to fix it because I don't
have any product options to fix eyes
because of this challenge I am gonna go
do the other eye off-camera now because
I'm running very late and I have to walk
out the door in a few short minutes and
my face currently looks probably the
worst it's ever looked so I will be back
in a few short madness to finish off the
rest of the luck thanks BRB ok so we are
back and the other eye is looking
equally as bad so I'm going to take the
Becca highlighter that yeah literally
did not even buy it happen to get for
free
I don't going to reapply this for some
glow - hopefully distract and then we're
going to complete our look and that is
the laura geller nude kisses lip hugging
lip gloss at least the lip matches the
eye
thank you Lord Jesus and heaven above oh
my god
and we're going to finish off this
amazing and lovely makeup look today
that I am so happy with with the Urban
Decay all nighter D slick setting sprays
[Music]
holy a little bit you think
eyelashes really big and wonky doesn't
work yeah face a little creased a little
crusty you can see through your pores
yeah do cat's eye brows a little big
lips a little crusty overall a pretty
awful job on my part
the sad thing is too is that this
doesn't even look that bad on camera so
all the comments are gonna be oh my god
damn stop complaining like do you look
fine it is currently 622 and there is a
car coming to get us for the event and
approximately eight minutes what I don't
know that
yeah you need to get ready tail and I
look like this so that is neither good
nor flash nor fine and I am really
scared we'll see first problem you did
you should have started filming earlier
so it didn't work out well he could have
done an actual look it made me so happy
and so Kaunas an older brother that you
were so confident in your I was calm
well I had trusted you to take out
things that I would wear I know I'm very
thankful that you did this and I'm also
very impressed that you at least knew
all the different steps and it kind of a
guy like three hours you did and you
also missed contouring but most things
are there and the fact that you even
know about makeup in the first place is
enough
so thanks love you love you too and now
I don't know what I'm gonna do so we
need to go if you guys enjoyed this
video today please don't forget to the
big thumbs up down below enjoy your love
and support it really means so much to
me and as well click that big red
subscribe button so you can come join at
the sister and it is a pretty lit time
and I'd love to have you join the family
and also click the bell icon secret
non-friend every time I upload a brand
new video if they follow me on a makeup
journey can thought me into Twitter
they're both the same Charles so I
stopped out for more I'm gonna see
inside stuff its James Charles the
mixture asked after Charles
please tell yourself as I feel like
after all this guys like to follow me on
my social medias
my snapchats and JT 12 instagrams and JT
12 Twitter is Ian JT 12 my YouTube is
the eject
yes I made a YouTube channel go check it
out the first video is great the second
video is the literally horrible so
hopefully back to the special
announcement guys oh yeah brother and
sister whoa you're going into it that
fast
brothers and sisters making a comeback
okay so I'm really excited because when
we originally launched our show and
brother and sister here on YouTube it
was kind of like our trial run with you
guys and literally the support on it was
so insane we had so much fun doing the
series and that was kind of like in the
beginning stages of Vienna coming to LA
spending a lot more time with me and
it's us being together and we had so
much fun doing the episodes too it was
truly like such an amazing bonding
experience for us a lot went on behind
the scenes and Ian was also in school
which made producing the episodes a
little bit of a struggle for Shore but
it's a summertime Ian's back in LA and
we're kind of figuring out what he wants
to do with this career and it's looking
like online school is gonna be a really
amazing option to Meramec which means
brother and sister is officially making
a comeback and we are so pumped they
decided to upload episodes once every
two weeks now to make sure the quality
is on point for you guys I'm super
excited to bring it back it's a great
bonding experience me and James have and
I hope you guys will enjoy it definitely
stay tuned for lots of updates on this
series it should be a very raised to you
by the time this video goes up and we
hope you guys are excited for the
premiere of season 2 this week sister
shadow is sister Lily thank you so much
for we supporting James and we have some
points I love you do you okay if you
like to the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always a retweet
Wendling so they go live on Twitter
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching we need to go the most ever in
the entire world love you and I'll see
you in the next one bye
you
[Music]