hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel today
as you can see I'm done with my favorite
person in the entire world
if you dose off a few weeks ago my
entire family is out here visiting me at
La and I film videos with my parents
which was so much fun
if you guys missed those videos we
should go click right up here because
they are a very very good time but
sister ADA's back we flew men and
today's video we were doing something
very very exciting here in YouTube
there's been a very popular trend going
on right now where people try to follow
other people's makeup tutorials that
have no makeup knowledge and what better
person to try to follow a beauty gurus
makeup tutorial then sister Ian who has
no makeup knowledge so a opposite does
not wear makeup ever but we have them
three videos together on my channel at
this point so how do you think you're
gonna perform today wonderful and
professional now oh he's a professional
anyway coming for the gag yeah okay this
is some high confidence levels that I
did not expect for today's video but you
know what we're gonna roll with this I
love this version of sister Ian so
without further ado I'm gonna step out
ian has my tutorial ready to go trying
to follow he's gonna recreate my lips
today and good luck alright I'm gonna be
doing a white glam today so me watching
Gina's on here from two weeks ago how to
get perfect skin with me
feel very moist these are the Too Faced
Born This Way in the color warm nude
just feels like peanut butter like I
said before pretty cold and we're gonna
put all over my face
hopefully it comes out decently James
always says don't miss the neck or you
get some flashback Mary situations I'm
not trying to have that so cuz we're
gonna do the neck we're gonna do my ears
apparently that's part of your face no
makeup my ears forever
alright now that I have all my
foundation done I'm gonna continue the
video and see what the next step is I
already get our concealer and put it
under our eyes cuz that's what James is
doing these good makeup fashion the
shave new concealer so my all-time
favorites because it's Kate apparently
will cover our whole face with a hold on
[Music]
Wow feel beautiful but it blends out
beautifully that's a very very hydrating
to the perfect look to it absolutely
love all right and get the Beauty
Blender and we're gonna blend this all
win this thing is things to go it does
everything
the beforee 20 blender my undereyes to
get rid of the crease thing is I'm gonna
have my setting powder not there ready
my personal favorite is actually a
mixture of the laura mercier okay making
mixing zone arrange the sign just take
all right I'm gonna use the Beauty
Blender and push those creases up and
try not to be too hard as opposed to my
favorite makeup tricks that I have ever
learned today and truly likes bridge Oh
get the mac fix+
drop and pick up the fan we're gonna
spray myself with this morphe m45 brush
and i too many steps i came and found
the brush the m-52 7 brush but I guess
that works
contour my cheekbones or something like
that or bronze my cheekbones i think
it's called i'm using the morphe m 405
brush use KO james for 10% off we're
also gonna be using the Anastasia
Beverly Hills contour kit the light to
medium I'm gonna grab the palette I'm
gonna dip it into this I will do two
lines on top of my nose
if you're someone like me you're trying
to kind of fool beyond your nose looks a
lot smaller you definitely do not want
to follow your non sono save in the
situation and the contours where you
wish your nose all right we're gonna
move on so I just really like to kind of
reinforce that later on while the face
is still really really fresh and kind of
do it because it does everything we knew
the nose hollow because if you put the
completely from the effect of the pitch
smells but if you put it just on these
honeys tip of the nose range or right in
between those two contour lines it's
really gonna further afield lose it and
make it look like her that was spread
just literally like wow moving on
better saw her face we went to a lightly
baked earth base but make on face man
once again using my camp you under and
dipping into them right on the sides of
my nose to enforce the highlights which
once again further the illusion of a
pinched and snatched nose and when I
wipe this mall in a little while it's
gonna kind of brighten up that entire
area and just clean up the contour what
just makes it look a little bit more
defined it a little bit more copped it
fetched I got a white beer to grow and
meet only being sixty and I could really
grow a full beard so kind
what the saying goes browser not twins
they're sisters wait a second why is
this brown pencil pink I'm gonna hold my
pencil vertically into my face and I'm
gonna use a very very light pressure and
just lightly place my pencil I just kind
of flick it upwards to create
natural-looking hair strokes all right I
think this eyebrow looks okay I'm gonna
be a lazy piece like James and do the
old one off camera I'll be right back
all right I gotta find a brush I really
am I guess I'm concealer some shape tape
concealer get a little bit on with that
brush and then I'm just gonna go right
in and start cleaning up that brow very
very carefully all right I think I did
my concealer pretty well moving on
mushroom [ __ ] close one eye and open
the other so I'm not sure I'm gonna do
this part
[Music]
you know another I don't have lashes
this guy's really easy eyelashes I'm
gonna start by bringing this one in
starting right at the root of the lash
almost in my upper waterline and just oh
boy I need to focus hold on
[Music]
well we have to fix this somehow I'm
gonna see if I could fix my mistake and
we need some concealer and some setting
powder do you wear this mascara
[Music]
this isn't good they're fully made worse
I'm gonna get some same pattern see if I
can fix it not sure if I can we're using
the LM a new boo sue using the new
bounce um Bella BAE lashes this is gonna
be the worst part of the whole video cuz
I want to stab my own eyes third off
fake eyelashes Jim there's like 34 ads
on this video I'm pretty sure you can
afford some lashes train I think I think
James did he cut these for me I don't
trust myself with a pair of scissors
where I did James's makeup he said I put
his lashes on perfectly but I'm not too
sure how long we better do mine I'm
gonna glue my lashes see how this works
out this glue dries pretty quickly and
it goes on blue so once it turns clear
you know it's ready to apply and I'm
gonna place the lash on top of my lid no
[Music]
yes
don't know how I did that but I think
it's on I got to deal with one now we're
just not gonna work out - I can already
guess alright I had the glue pot in this
lash I'm gonna see if I can get to try a
little bit I'm gonna attempt to from
other lash out
[Music]
wonderful
alright I guess I actually did it I'm a
makeup genius I saw the few tips in
check to show you guys to make your lips
look more plump just the thing
well first look I'm here for you guys
today is slightly over lining your lips
went over linear lips I always like to
start at the Cupid's bow just kind of
build now let's take the people always
make when they're over lining is that
they keep over lining the entire top lip
alright so looking in one mouthful
lipstick right that's at our very lips I
think you should have plenty go there do
lipstick with the lip liner for that
natural ombre look never do that again
think I forgot to wipe off the bake so
I'm gonna do that now please I James I
think I'm done yeah come on and see
close your eyes low open your eyes in
three two you've gotta be kidding me
what is going on right now
okay literally looking your face right
note you look so Bom and so smudged
how did you find following tutorials
today I mean we have film like three
videos of you doing makeup on me to
definitely help put you tutorial
definitely help me even more go really
yeah so don't you think there was like a
like good information in there yeah
definitely help me love that I think
Megha velvet looks hard from the outside
a little bit of practice anyone can do
it I mean got pressured like yeah after
only doing makeup literally three times
total in his entire life somehow managed
to put this on his face play my toys
dude oh so sorry he's a pro Ian all
jokes aside I do want to say actually
thank you for doing this video today I
know you hate this and do not want to do
it but it does mean a lot to me that
throughout filming these videos you have
actually like been paying attention and
kept up this makeup knowledge and you're
willing to do this so that means a lot
thanks broski I'm really really proud of
you because you look honestly really
really good you guys better give this
video a big thumbs up
I'm never doing it again in my life oh
yeah I'm take as Mega Ball no I have a
little bit of a surprise for you what
come on guys why is there a camera crew
in here well not only are you following
my makeup tutorial today but you're also
gonna be living it to hit my life today
No uh-huh oh no no no no no I'm already
getting stared at about five minutes now
you're styling at their face I need you
to slice with your eyes stop if you're a
true sis or not only do I love makeup on
I also love music I think the time has
come for sister Annie try a song you
think yeah you're having fun of this
don't even behind what did I sign up for