my sister's James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see he said I'm done with a
very very special guest
[Music]
it's called me brother in from now how
about you don't tell me what to do with
my youtube channel okay continue thank
you sorry for today's video we're doing
something you would probably never guess
you would see on a makeup channel but
life is full of surprises and hello hi
here we are
so a few days ago I had a dream
we're not making news there King Joe I
spent about this a lot but my brain goes
a little bit to sister speedy I'm always
thinking and I come up with generally
some of the craziest ideas ever in the
entire world and a few weeks ago I
literally had a dream and I swear to God
I cannot make this up that all of the
beauty gurus in the beauty community
were in The Hunger Games you oh you
think I would lose the Hunger Games yes
are you kidding me Jeffrey's no incline
boys it was me and Jeffrey were the file
too and I ended up stabbing him but I
will say I was running from him for the
majority of the finale of the game he
actually plays a really really popular
game right now that is kind of like a
similar situation to the Hunger Games
called fortnight four days of free
battle royale game when you jump out of
a bus and land find weapons and it's
basic a fight to the death between 100
people you can build structures find
weapons get potions to recharge your
health it's pretty interesting that's
not the most fun ever it is so this
isn't happening at very often but
today's video is sponsored by Epic Games
so showing us is fine this is something
that really meant a lot to en I know he
was literally it so excited about this
and I've been hearing so much about for
tonight I have not played it before I
will admit what incident teach me how to
play it today not gonna lie I'm a little
bit excited about this I think this is
gonna be so much fun hopefully I don't
get sisters thought within the first 60
seconds if you go into a diner - yes I
am
like inside for tonight it's free to
download and it's available on all
different gaming
from the Xbox picks for a computer
iPhone the full shebang so wherever you
want to play it you can totally play it
and don't forget to check the
description box down below for the link
to download so without further ado it
ends gonna teach me how to play
fortnight I'm gonna twerk it for a real
one until two towers and slay some
sisters and I'm calling it right now I'm
getting a big darrell absolutely not
not without attitude don't be rude
alright let's go yeah that's right let's
go okay where do I go stop stop what's
so Red Lion to toe to toe with her I'm
gonna be destroyed angry no yes I don't
want to press X as soon as you drop and
get that gun Barbie what is that I have
to go oh are you gonna think of that I
don't condone gun violence you're gonna
pick up that booth okay you interrupted
my psi okay I don't condone gun violence
um you know I'm just saying I don't want
to push on towards the floor break that
oh it's the good and beefy one Oh a
sister's secret mmm oh here we go
gonna surprise him sneak attack
why are you screaming so not close at
all whatsoever
looks pretty close to me roll the clap
press B
B I heard you oh there's the ramp right
there don't even have to build look at
that look at me saving resources and
saving the planet dude
dude not me gonna hit my ball what I did
that not hurt a lot my ears hurt you
just scream I'm like a personal problem
now is that a golf car okay let me write
it for a real one
go go go go go let go wasn't feeling
like we're never feeling I gotta get
away get away get away you know that's
gonna win every day day attitude or not
oh wow you're the past press press X
princess I am let's go I'm just gonna
drive the entire time and see how long I
can last without dying that's a
challenge playing 40 in a golf cart
until I die a challenge just did it
right now you welcome ninja and every
other fortnight gamer not only mine died
of pioneering the beauty community but
also the gaming community better watch
out
tensho yeah Wow oh really picking up the
speed now look at this spooky maze Oh
oh my gosh we try to solve that what if
we just break the mate once in there
okay means you're gonna die
you missed how I missed every single
bullet matter oh I definitely hit him so
what one thing you're not gonna want to
do is stand on top of a building
and do nothing take some what's in here
why would you let me die like that if he
knew that was gonna happen you idiot
that's mad funny I'm never gonna be a
pro gamer with a help like this boom get
out the way oh yeah bar shoot me there
you go should go to the desert
coach hello begin somebody a party is so
funny Oh kind of pretty mr. sunset this
will be good for golden our makeup
selfie okay so I'm sorry I'm going
learning about the sunset in selfies
your point for tonight you're going to
battle this is war alright even a war I
still need to up to Instagram where my
followers will die where's the chest
okay I can't so bad if you don't kill
this kid James I'm bubbly
you are so awful at the game he's
playing on my he's lying on his phone
it's like any video game name from their
head and are above yeah but I was
focused on shooting you just shot at the
floor to hear what's here I have no idea
this little town it's hotel and be
tomato quiet village tomato town
hey so tomatoes there's a oh that good
already
it's been three seconds I can't wash
this anymore I'm actually gaining this
game is too far I'm not gonna play in
these games so I can actually show you
how to play for night I know how to play
for night clearly you do not walk the
plank oh there's a gun stop screaming in
my ear oh no oh my god since you're so
bad you are annoying and rude I mean or
give me bad advice you just have to go
get that gonna look what happened I died
I'm not gonna look this whole game
what's gonna be fly that oh thank you I
need a gun there's only one room in this
house what the heck bad planning about
architecture can't relate
oh my god
I don't understand ah no oh you're
sliding smatphone
oh I don't know what's gonna die oh wow
do have my teachers trying to make me
die and that's it live on camera we have
proof Ian's jeopardy is a horrible
brother tell this videos my brothers had
to kill me question mark exhalation
point star traumatizing star clickbait
star fades sorry it just happened star
oh he's right there that was so good
it's lying on the map what can you speak
your being away oh it's going faster
than I can run oh I'm gonna die
I am beg no no why wouldn't you tell me
this ed you're certain tol I have the
one game I gonna kill it I'm gonna die
from a storm why you're not funny you're
the worst oh let's go sister suicide
there you go
kill myself till the storm cut it gotcha
I will not be a pawn in this games games
oh my god dude if you die from this kid
James why can't I run
that's right
Toph could me you didn't have a gun why
are you so happy cuz I'm the queen of
fortnight he's right there I see him en
why are you wrong me cuz he's killing me
you don't run you shoot back my time to
all my problems you suck that's when I
get a victory Royale you can't get a
kill barely oh how really whip it for a
real one
right this one nice should go right here
- retail row ah oh my god let's do some
sister shopping look at these houses
look kind of fun let's go to the rich
people house maybe they have a chest
life hack rich people usually have a
valuable thing so you can steal them
maybe don't do that actually
Oh oh wow
look at me being the cleanup for tonight
who called it me you just all witness
not oh my god it's a blue button oh it's
a grenade launcher Oh fun great the
bathtub haha guys goes over the mirror
break the mirror oh oh my god oh my god
we're even were they oh right here here
let me in oh I've been here for three
seconds that was homophobic oh no I had
the first one here oh here we go here we
go here we go it's game time ladies No
here you go you got you you're just bad
okay
it's um there's nothing wrong with the
game you're just bad I don't appreciate
you being an unsupportive sister yeah
I'm trying to be supportive but you're
really not
I'm just making fun of a game it's not
the game you're just bad you're right
I'm sorry for tonight thank you for
sponsoring this video what is this it's
a bush get it it's a bush yes you do
yes you do I don't enjoy me yes you want
don't enjoy what get the bush please
what is it gonna do to me oh you have
got to be kidding me
oh I'm one with my people
oh he doesn't see me oh my gosh No do
anything oh oh my god I am literally a
bus where's the person Oh what was that
how did I just fly oh my got a fine bush
kind of a speedy but oh oh oh my god I'm
literally walking Bush this is the Oh oh
my god I can go be a bush in the forest
hey everybody here's Posey oh my oh
there's only 24 people laughed I'm
probably gonna win this one I feel
and your Bush yeah but no one can see me
I'm in disguise just like last week's
YouTube video which if you haven't seen
it yet click right up here to go check
it out look at me being queen of promo
so good then it stopped what the spooky
music I'm trying to focus is where
there's a person out there to your left
just less you know to your left this
person right there is it a common the
entrance would be this way oh my god but
I go I would wait we're gonna go help me
we're knocking Victor Royale why I've
been playing full night for a very long
time I have like five then you stalk
okay you can see here and play full name
for us I'm gonna try to give it to
around no sister sad you see Center
footage of me getting a picture al but
just say it's me
I'm scam everybody yeah Queen of odd
name alright guys that's enough for
tonight for today James is absolutely
awful at the game made it farther than
you did you ran around in a bush and hit
and got one kill what did I place 14 I
cannot to do please 34 with two kills
not aggressive talk to anyone it's all
but one it's about being aggressive in
getting kills 14th okay moving on you're
not good at the game there you're not
good at the game okay we're done here
even though I only got one victory rail
today so hard I had so much fun playing
this game and I definitely want to keep
playing for tight as soon as I get into
a house the better Wi-Fi thanks to Ethan
a Grayson for letting us play this game
at their house today and also major
thank you to forte and Epic Games for
sauntering today's video I know this
meant a lot to Ian he loves Forte I now
also love for tonight a lot even though
I'm not the best at it and this was so
much fun to do and don't forget to check
out fortnight for free and download it
by clicking the link in the description
box below if you guys did enjoy it
make sure it the thumbs up button if you
haven't already subscribe down below and
click the Beltline console you notified
every time I upload a brand new video if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
torn you can follow me on instagram at
Twitter they're both just a James
Charles and my snapchat for more about
how the teen side stuff is genius
Charles the next RS after Charles Ford
to follow me on social media all them
are Ian JD twelve this video is at
sister shadow Costa sister Emily thank
you so much for your always falling at
the party nor I love you literally it's
so so so much and if you'd like to be
the next videos sister shout out don't
forget to always reach me per bit early
so they go live on Twitter alright guys
thank you so much for watching thanks
for watching us sister Xu and slay this
fortnight game from today and we'll see
you in the next one