hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel in
case you notice everything you might
look a little bit different right now I
slightly changed my setup and my letting
a little bit
I made the lights a lot less bright and
added a lot more diffusion so now I'll
hopefully be able to open my eyes and
not blink and close them every 3 seconds
come on camera I've got so many comments
about it I know it's annoying
you guys have no idea how much frickin
light was surrounding me in my previous
video so hopefully you guys like this
whole lot better but let me know a
sister is working on it anyways for
today's that I have something very very
fun plan that I'm actually so excited to
try out I've been seeing so many
youtubers lately doing videos testing
out mixing their different products
I saw Sophia [ __ ] testing up mixing her
foundation first and then she tested out
mixing her liquid lipsticks to get a
funky color so for today's video I'm
trying something a little bit different
and I'm gonna mix together all of my
setting powders if you guys been a
longtime sister you know that setting
powder is a little bit of a touchy
subject for me when I first started
doing my makeup I use the Cote air
somehow too religiously and we all know
how that turned out so this one is
slowly made its way out of my routine
now I use the Laura Mercier translucent
setting powder in almost every single
video but I've tried out so many
different powders in between some of the
remotes have mattify some of them are
meant to brighten some of them prevent
creases but overall the whole purpose of
them is that they set the face in place
today I'm gonna be mixing together all
my setting powders they have in my
collection both my favorites and the
ones that have given me a little bit of
trouble in the past and this empty
setting powder container we're gonna mix
them all together and then we're gonna
set my face in place that actually kind
of hurt I'm really not sure how this is
gonna turn out just on my first thoughts
I am assuming that it's probably gonna
be ridiculously dry like it's a hair
desert level I do have my setting spray
just in case everything gets a little
bit too serious or my face is like you
know cracking off because won't be that
big of a surprise but who knows I also
feel like I probably I'm gonna get
pretty bad a flashback today hopefully
Mary will not come back to play I do
have to wear this makeup to an event
later on tonight but I'll be taking you
guys with me to show the full thing I'll
also be taking a lot of photos so
hopefully none of them turn out too bad
anyways all being said if you'd like to
see all my setting powders being mixed
together put them to the test
will it work will it fail will flash
like Mary make an iconic appearance keep
on watching
[Music]
so before I actually go into my
foundation today my first step is gonna
be to go into the touch of water cream
which is my all-time favorite
moisturizer as I was just talking about
obviously the whole point of setting
powder is to dry foundation down and sat
waiting in place and I definitely do not
want to be the Sahara Desert
today my skin is just arting to clear up
a little bit so I'm trying to protect it
therefore I need to be really really
hydrated before I suck all the moisture
out for foundations today I'm gonna grab
my all-time favorite my makeup for ever
ultra HD stick and this is in the shade
of Y 335 I am using a stick shade that's
slightly darker than my normal shade for
them I do have a bad feeling this is
gonna give me a really bad a flashback
today so I'm trying to combat that as
much as possible then I'm just gonna add
a few drops of the Giorgio Armani
luminous of Foundation and use this to
kind of blend that foundation out this
is a very very dewy foundation and once
again we're trying to add the most
amount of moisture possible then just to
brighten quickly I'm gonna use my shape
gave concealer in the shade up light
stand as usual so now that we have my
foundation and concealer all in place
let's go ahead and mix all these setting
powders together I have an empty tub
right here that is ready for this
concoction the first part I want to add
is my all-time favorite which is my
Laura Mercier I have some one the top of
the jar right here so I'm just going to
pour that in and then I'm just gonna
like a little bit of a tap just make
sure we have enough in there next I'm
going to add the two phase two peach
perfect setting powder whoo that is a
mouthful this one smells literally so
good and actually smells like real
peaches I love this one as well the only
thing is this is a little bit orange but
that may help with combating like dark
circles especially under the eyes and in
the beard area so this could be a good
addition I'm just gonna tap a little bit
of that powder in there next one to add
a little bit of the beauty bakery flower
setting powder I've actually never tried
this one out but I've heard amazing
amazing things about it so hopefully
it'll be just as good for me next comes
in powders that I either don't like as
much don't sit well on my skin or gave
me flashback our burst can afford a
little bit of the RCM A&O color powder I
did not like this one as much it clung
to my skin a pretty bad oh my god
and also did way too much brightening so
who next will be the tarte smooth
operator Amazonian clay finishing powder
neck's is gonna be one of my all-time
least favorite setting powders which is
the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD setting
powder listen I love makeup forever they
are an amazing team they have a lot of
amazing products I use their foundation
in every single look but this powder is
just really not a good one at all I know
it does give it very very bad flashbacks
so I'm probably gonna have to stay away
from this app chat tonight I'm just
gonna pour a little of this one in and
last but certainly not least we all know
this one mmm yes we do that's enough
so that is all seven of our setting
powders mixed together today I am very
very scared for this but I'm gonna put
the cap back on and we're going to shake
it up sick sick sick
Oh shake shake shake shake your powder
shake your powder I need to stop so
looking at the powder in the jar it
definitely looks like a normal setting
powder although it does look a little
bit chunky I'm really not sure if that's
because I just shook it to mix it
together or if it's because the foreign
laws are the powder aren't mixing
together hopefully it's not option
number two but I guess we're gonna find
out in a short second also the color
looks pretty normal as well but I will
say it does look a little bit more
orange than normal the Cody are some
powder and that two-faced peach powder
are both slightly orange II peachy tone
and hopefully that doesn't affect my
color shade they can be look like an
oompa loompa then I'm just gonna go
right into my Beauty sponge dip right
into this powder and set my face that's
really matte whoa then of course you
guys might like to rock it on the nose
choice any water oh my god I was I think
I like to really really pocket on the
nose that's always the one thing on my
face that gets oily the fastest this
feels like a normal setting powder to
apply but I'm not kidding when I say
that I can literally like taste the
peach in my mouth I don't know if I put
too much of the peach powder and Orvis
just actually that strong but regardless
I do like that setting powder so
hopefully it's working in my favor
things were definitely getting a little
peachy up here in the sister studio so
looking close up with my skin in the
mirror I look very very matte there's
like
not a single trace of Oh oh my god okay
not only do I look mad but I also feel
mad - holy crap
looking clothes everybody knows wherever
there is a - spots right here with the
foundation there's a little bit worn off
there were two little specks of setting
powder that wouldn't go away and I'm
assuming that's from the RCM a powder
because I remember that happening a lot
when I use this powder and like stuck to
my foundation and when I rubbed it away
now I'm left with a little bit of
discoloration right here so hopefully
I'll be able to fix that when it comes
to the most contouring later on but I
knew I didn't like this powder before we
make my face I'm just gonna go in and
I'm going to contour and bronze my face
normally using my Kat Von D shade and
light palette and my benefit hoola
bronzer
as always once we're onto is it of
course we have to bake our face so I'm
gonna get my blending sponge once again
for morphe and dip into our custom M
powder concoction right up in here and
we're going to turn on the oven at 350
degrees and bake it up the point of
baking is not only to prevent creases
but it's also to brighten and add a
definition to makeup so with the
addition of the makeup forever setting
powder which heavily has a lot of flash
like and a lot of lightness and also the
RCM a color powder which is white
hopefully this will do a really really
great job with that and not make me look
disgusting
while we are baking at 350 degrees in
the oven I'm gonna go ahead and quickly
do my eyebrows off camera just to save
some time always some eyebrows were all
saved in place it has been about 20
minutes now so let's go ahead and wipe
off the bake and see how this powder
actually held up a hole so far so good
everything is still really really
Merritt and set in place and it does
look a little bit brighter if you see
like underneath this contour but I feel
like the true test is definitely the
nose contour so let's wipe this off as
well obvious I mean to me it looks like
my normal nose contour I mean I did tell
you guys I lost my nose contouring brush
so things in that department and general
have been a little bit wonky but over
life like it looks really really good
it didn't cling on to my skin at all
which is the thing that I was very very
worried about everything looks really
nice bright side play so so far I
actually have no complaints
I'm gonna give my face a light misting
of the Scandinavian makeup finishing
spray just to make all the powders kind
of melt together because lord knows we
have a lot of it on right now I'm gonna
go ahead and do the eyes and the rest my
face off-camera and then I'll be right
back with the finished look then we'll
put the setting powder concoction to the
true test and see our seven powders mix
together sister approved we'll have to
find out
and only a few hours later this is the
finished that I came up with today I
came up with this purpley half cut
crease and I added a winged liner as
well I haven't done purple or a wing in
such a long time and honestly I just
felt like I was missing something in my
life I needed that purple smokiness that
cut winged liner and I am in love with
on this look turned out just in case
you're wondering I catered it using the
brand new morphe 15 and palette this is
Dean bytes thinner palette from the
holiday collection and it is so so
stunning friendly Randy you can use code
James for 10% off all morphe products
and the Holiday Collection I would
definitely recommend this so look at my
face in the mirror I am very very matte
there was no question about that
literally dewy skin never heard of her I
have literally no shine anywhere on my
face except for obviously the place I
put highlighter but I feel like even my
highlighter today is not shining as
bright as normal because we layer it on
so much powder before hand honestly my
face feels really really secure like I
said earlier it even feels matte like
it's super super dry so honestly I feel
like this may last for a very very long
time
but I have literally no idea we're gonna
put that to the test
so I'm gonna go get change this outfit
is a little bit dusty if I do say so
myself I'm gonna put on a hat and jacket
because I have a birthday dinner tonight
over in Malibu to celebrate sister
Patrick stars birthday I love him so
much and we're gonna be wearing this
makeup all night will it flash oh oh my
god before I leave let me take a flash
test right now before we actually leave
the studio that's your test it didn't
flash back not even gonna lie I'm a
little bit shocked right now I a hundred
and fifty percent thought we were gonna
have a flash like merry situation
tonight I was really really ready to
take a whole lot of snapshots how's the
internet go crazy once again only to use
it for video promo for this video but
this is not a bad thing that being said
even though it's not flashing back now
and may flashbacks later on as the
powder wears down and we make it creases
so like I just think before I got
sidetracked
I'm gonna go quickly get dressed for the
event tonight and I'm gonna head out and
I'll make sure to keep you guys posted
all throughout the night with lots of
updates with my sisters and friends will
this mixture of the seven most popular
setting powders stay looking amazing
like it does right now
or will it get crazy and Crocky and
gross and cakey you'll have to find out
okay
sisters we're here at Nobu I have
sisters carrot and crispy and Sydney I'm
gonna ask all of you individually what
do you think about my skin right now
I think you look very good he looks very
snatched skin let's put together a
little more matte than usual very matte
full coverage personally I love here
with sister Yoli glow the woman who
slays my skin all the time Yoli what do
you think about my skin right now like
what does it look like I approve so this
is a powder that emphasizes texture you
guys in achieving an amazing job because
it's really emphasizing oh and you don't
set your makeup
how about it'll look by the end of the
night you look really mad Mary
oh it's actually pretty effects your
head guys I'm with the woman at the our
sister sorry I have a question for you
okay what do you think with my skin
right now she's full cover she's bad I
like it does it look good yeah but it's
good I mixed together every single
setting powder that I own and today not
my powder [ __ ] I need you to read yeah
foxes December 4th even ah master hobble
darling thank you thank you babe
hello sisters and back home from the
birthday event that was literally so
much fun I have reading on right now
because it was literally so cold outside
I'm actually so happy that it's finally
getting cold in LA I thought I was gonna
be summer all year round but wintertime
is coming and it's currently 11:47 p.m.
meaning I've had this makeup on for just
over seven hours now which is crazy
because guys this looks so good I did
not touch up once tonight this is the
first time since I started wearing
makeup and going to events that I did
not bring a beauty blender with me to
even like do some touch-ups or to powder
my face and this still looks so bomb I
can't frickin believe how mad it looks -
like there's literally no oil at all
like not even on my nose and you guys
know so chef James's nose is usually a
problem place everybody that I asked out
my skin tonight said that it looked
really really smooth really really good
really really full-coverage and really
really mapped I mean obviously we did
mixed together 7 powders to set my face
today I hate to say it because I
honestly really thought this is gonna be
a complete joke but as you saw not a
single one had flashback my skin looks
smooth it still looks smooth it's still
dry it's still not guys I think I just
found my new favorite makeup trick this
is obviously the first time that I've
ever mixed setting powders but after
trying this trick out I honestly do
think I'm gonna make it a custom
concoction to use for everyday use I'll
probably end up mixing my Laura Mercier
my Too Faced peach perfect and then a
little bit of the Cody err some powder
because these are my all-time favorites
I don't know about the are CMA or the
maker for everyone because these do get
pretty bad flash like and this was a
little bit clingy and I think that I'm
gonna have to test out the Beauty bakery
one a little bit more as well because
obviously I've never actually used this
on its own so I definitely want to see
how it actually wears before I put it
into the baked concoction but you
see convicted setting powders I think is
a really really cool thing that I can't
believe it actually never thought of
obviously the whole point of mixing them
is like to get the best of all worlds of
all the different setting powders so I
really really like this check and
definitely recommend to you guys if you
guys have a bunch of setting powders mix
them together try out your favorites and
definitely let me know how they wear
throughout the day
did they crack do they look Matt I want
to hear the team because I am so shocked
at the results of this and I definitely
want to keep doing this alright guys let
us all I hope of this video today I
really hope you enjoyed it and if you
want me to mix together any other makeup
products definitely let me know this was
so much fun to do if you have not
already made sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below
thank you so much for 2 million
subscribers I have not got a chance to
thank you guys yea we're literally
almost at 2.1 million which is so so
crazy the sisters are growing so so fast
so make sure to join the sisterhood
click that little bell icon as well so
you can be notified every time I upload
a brand new video if you'd like to
follow me I like makeup journey you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for what we're heading c-types
up is James Charles an extra ask after
Charles this week sister shadow goes to
Kendra thank you so much for you for
always following in supporting I love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be next video sister shout out make
sure to always reach you if I do like
something go live on Twitter alright
sisters it is getting very rarely I
definitely need my beauty rest so I'm
gonna take this makeup off and head to
bed but thank you so much for watching I
love you so much and I will see you in
at the next one bye
[Music]