hi sisters jean-charles here welcome
back to my apartment come on you guys oh
my god I am literally so beyond excited
for today's YouTube video if you guys
have been a true sister subscriber you
would know that since day one I'm moving
to Los Angeles in to this apartment
I've been saying I'm gonna do an
apartment tour and guess what I have not
done an apartment door I've been here
for about a year and a half now I like
it I definitely do not love it and that
is why I wanted to do the apartment tour
today because I'm gonna show you guys my
little sister suite my sister shelter
but I'm Carly in the market for a sister
sanctuary which will be a house
hopefully in the very very near future
it has been a huge goal of mine I really
really love architecture interior design
it's when I fear things in the entire
world I feel like I've done a pretty
pretty decent job at this apartment and
I'm not gonna be here for much longer so
I'm gonna show you guys what I've done
with the place I'm really really proud
of it and I hope you guys enjoy it too
[Music]
so as soon as you walk into the sister
shelter we have the kitchen which is
probably by far the least used place of
the entire house but of course we do
have our regular stove our microwave
where I cook ramen in our dishwasher
which does not get used very often
because we have paper plates
and then over here we have this like
weird little breakfast nook cabinet
situation on this wall I really really
love burning candles the sister sense of
down panel I can sometimes be a little
bit so stir spooky so I definitely loved
light candle then I have my little Bowl
that house my earpods my wallet and my
keys because I'm always losing I miss
placing them so I figured might as well
just put them there on my toaster oven
if I ever cook avocado toast and then
just a coffee machine it so I can make
my coffee in the morning with of course
my good morning sisters mug for Lima
home so although we don't do a lot of
cooking it you guys know I definitely do
- a lot of eating that is for sure I am
definitely a foodie i order from so many
restaurants in LA and I'm always having
friends over here so having a really
really nice dining set up for all my
friends and family to eat while they're
together is a very very important part
of this house disclaimer most of this
furniture and this property is actually
from Ikea the city was not hashtag
sponsored but at hashtag should be
because when I buy my sister sanctuary
in case you did not know real estate in
Los Angeles
exactly in the cheapest so a Cicero is
going to be broke so IKEA if you want to
hit a girl up I'd love to have you
furnished the new sister's house when I
get it regardless I just have these
place settings on here that I got from
CV to this cute little bench so a bunch
of people can sit on here and we can
sister squeeze wow so many good sister
fruits that I like I said I definitely
have had a huge interested in interior
design since I've been very very little
I'm a huge fan of Pinterest
I literally have boards and boards and
boards and boards of different
inspiration photos and these chairs have
actually been on my like a wish list
since I was literally like 11 or 12
years old swear to god I'm not kidding
so the second that I moved into this
house I ordered a ton of these chairs
they are super super comfortable and I
use them for a dining purposes above the
13 people we have two very very large
hanging light pendants when I moved in
here we literally had to get a 20-foot
ladder and climb all the way up to the
sister ceiling to install these light
but I love love love how they look and
it was definitely very much worth it and
I'm definitely not climbing up there
again when I move out so hopefully the
next tenants like these lights and then
finally on the wall we just have these
two posters which I absolutely love
once again from Ikea the first one is
from Andy Warhol from the Modena musi in
Stockholm Sweden this has been a huge I
don't my voice let's forever I have a
bunch of them all throughout my
apartment I really really love Andy
Warhol as well I think he's a very very
inspiring artist and then my favorite
quote of all time work smarter not
harder
that is like my all-time a favorite
quote to live by I say all the time it
is my phone wallpaper connected to the
dining room was actually obviously the
kitchen it but also the living room and
the office where I get all of my work
done throughout the day so along this
wall we have a bathroom right over here
which we don't need to go into this is
why I sister you don't need to see that
along this wall we have our office and
this is probably one of my favorite
walls in the entire house because this
is where I'm spending most of my time so
I really want to make sure it was super
super cute and a space that inspired me
so once again I have my little table
from Ikea and of course the Alex drawers
of course you guys know with my job we
have to say very very connected all
throughout the day it is vital to the
existence of me and all your sisters out
there so this is where all the work gets
done we have my huge iMac which I love
love love working and editing on we have
my phone charger an Apple watch charger
and then my laptop for work on the go
and then my sister I've had which I
always used for taking notes sketching
things down and just planning out
different video concepts when decorating
I knew I wanted to put the desk there
but that
left a very very large and kind of
awkward wall space that I knew I needed
to fill so I feel like a pretty good
design tip queen of HGTV and spill it
with a very very large buck face and
lots of different decor pieces and that
is exactly what I did I have a printer
right next my computer so I can print
out any files or contracts that I need
you to sign some different books my
favorite youtubers I have a few
different awards this is from the Shorty
Awards when I want it for break out
youtuber last year Thank You sisters for
always being the absolute best of course
I have this little ampersand because I'm
an internet relatable team and then once
again to some little plants here and
there to keep everything alive so
obviously all my work gets done in my
office but if we move just right over
here to the living room and this is
where all the fun that starts to happen
I'm actually very proud of how this room
turned out because decorating it was a
little bit of a challenge when I moved
in here obviously a lot of the walls are
white on the inside but all the outside
walls because this was a cornered unit
are made out of brick which makes
decorating it so incredibly hard because
not very many things match with burnt
orange a red tones I try to convince a
building's help me paint it white they
would not budge I don't blame them it's
still a little bit sister selfie about
it but I feel like I did my absolute
best so of course we just have this very
very large and extremely comfy couch
from Ikea we have lots of different gray
at white and black throw pillows to add
just a little personal Flair and to make
light here a lot more comfortable
I've taken a so many sister siestas
that's a nap in Spanish I'm so cheesy up
in this couch of course in the middle of
the living room we have this little like
coffee table that I got once again from
Ikea and I'm not having like a full-on
meal and if I'm having more of a little
bit of a lazy day I'll sometimes eat on
here or put my feet up if you may have
noticed in this apartment I actually do
not have a TV and that is because
instead of a TV I have a projector which
is probably literally the best decision
that I ever made in my entire life I
have it right under here on the bottom
shelf and it projects right over to here
a big screen that pulls down right above
my office I actually really really love
having a projector instead of a TV
because it relies on the lack of light
obviously work hello
so it forces me to get my work done
during the day because I can't use it
and then at night once they have
everything done and I'm hanging out with
friends I can always pull this down
watch on Netflix on my Apple TV
I also have an Xbox down here which I
got for the sole purpose of playing a
black ops zombies literally the queen
event and a Wii which literally hello
and nostalgic memories I will crush you
in Mario Kart if you ever come over and
that is a promise moving right along we
probably have the part of the apartment
that you guys have seen the absolute
most from a snapchat and Instagram
stories and that is the sister selfie
mirror I literally love this huge
oversized mirror once again from Ikea
the lighting is literally the best here
because it's actually in the corner of
the apartment so there's light coming
from both this window and this window
which makes my highlight reflect on both
sides which is literally so good so
fresh as you can see I definitely have a
lot of plants in here I really really
love the look of greenery and plants but
they're all fake because literally every
plant or flower that I've ever owned in
my entire life has died and then last
but certainly not least we just have my
little keyboard sitting here on the
floor it's so sad looking literally one
of the first things that I buy when I
get my new sister sanctuary is going to
be a huge huge huge professional
beautiful grand piano I literally cannot
wait but for right now we'll just have
to deal with this keyboard that I got
from Amazon but whenever I want to learn
to practice a new song that I'm loving
or at work on something myself who knows
what the future holds in case you missed
it which I really don't know how you
would because it is up sleek huge right
smack that Woodinville the living room
it's just insanely beautiful spiral
staircase which I am literally so in
love with and is actually one of the
main reasons I caught this apartment in
the first place when I was growing up
for some reason I've always had a huge
infatuation first tile staircases I
always just thought they were so cool
and I'm gonna miss this a lot when I
move out but this apartment is actually
two different stories so of course we
have the bottom level the living room
with the kitchen the filming room and
the closet which we're gonna get into a
little bit later and I'm so excited to
show you guys but upstairs we have of
the loft and that is where I get my
sister sleep so let's go up there I've
actually never fallen down this thank
God but several of my friends have sorry
who's loved you the most the main
problem with the upstairs area is that
there's no window up here which is so
beyond fresh shooting I only have one
little string of lights above my bed
which do very very little and it also
gets really really hot up here too
because obviously we're on the second
floor and heat rises it can sometimes be
a little bit sisters sweaty at night but
I still do love this base I think having
a
locked bedroom is so cool because
obviously we have the railings and I get
to look over everything kind of see the
full apartment which is such an insane a
beautiful view and if I ever have a home
intruder I can Scizor spot them before I
die of course we have my bed at right
here in the middle with some white bed
teeth just to match the aesthetic we
have a little bit of a blanket once
again for the LA winters if it gets cold
those little table lamp that I have next
to my bed I really really love this it's
just super cute and it's bendable so I
can kind of move it in any direction
that I want it to a large Jay painting
because I'm doing like I said I don't
really put that much time up here anyway
just to a sister sleep and occasionally
sisters talk and then moving down the
sister style staircase of course we have
a dis door right here which leads to the
closet I'm gonna save this room for last
because by far the best of the entire
house and I am so excited to show you
guys that but if we walk right across
the living room and dining room we get
to this door right here which you guys
may have seen in videos a few times but
I've never really given you the Grand
Tour and this is where all the magic
happens
the sister studio I'm so good at as soon
as you walk in in the main space once
again we have a very very large
bookshelf we just have a few different
knickknacks some picture frames these
pictures of me my best friend Laura and
the entire world we have this little
poster that my mom made me saying makeup
is my art you guys are gonna say that in
every video at this point before we get
a few different candles at different
plants some storage items we have my
Amazon Alexa so I can always listen to
music while I'm getting glam hashtag now
sponsored by Amazon's go ahead a sister
up I love to do a brand deal with you
guys and then down at the bottom we just
have a bunch of different equipment from
audio recording stuff to SD cards
batteries different cords different
chargers different lenses different
cameras this is like my videographers
dream area of the house and she keeps
everything there so you can say it's
super organized and get ready whenever
we're being issued during the day I've
been moving this way once again we have
the dream studio and for some reason not
a lot of GD gurus like to show this I
think it's because getting a perfect
lighting setup is obviously a very very
difficult thing it took me a lot of
trial and error and a lot of different
really really ugly looking videos but I
finally have a setup that I am super
proud of so this is kind of what it
looks like this camera and lens and
lighting setup not gonna lie was
extraordinarily expensive it really bit
my bank account for a hot minute but
I've been saving up for it for a very
very long time and like I said having my
video quality be the absolute best I
could be for you guys or something it's
always been it very very important to me
so it was down
worth the investment clearly all this
equipment together isn't exactly the
prettiest it's definitely pretty pretty
cluttered and busy in here but all these
items work very very nicely together
so when I sit down I feel me using a
video this is what it looks like and
like I said this is taking me years to
get to this quality but I am finally so
beyond happy with the camera quality of
my youtube videos and this is what you
guys see and every single sister James
Channel video when I'm actually sitting
down to film this is what the general
setup looks like right in front of me I
have my makeup table once again from
Ikea I have a trash bin below for all my
last crises and my makeup wipes that I
use and my drawer here I just have a
bunch of different mix-match stuff from
it different handheld mirrors fixed paws
some makeup lights and of course all my
little tools like my tweezers my beauty
blenders or little scissors to cut my
lashes I of course my makeup brushes
over here I have this big standing
mirror right here on the corner of the
table that isn't in the camera frame but
I can definitely still see myself and
then on the other side we have this
beautiful TV monitor which is suspended
from one of the light poles and this
actually is connected to my camera so
I'm able to see myself live and make
sure that my angles are good the
lighting is good and to see if it stops
recording so this is kind of how
everything works together to really
create our really really awesome YouTube
video right above me when I'm filming a
video I have this boom microphone and
this catches all the sisters sound and
then behind the one I feel of course
have my backdrop so you guys know why
YouTube videos are always stoned at home
too based all on a white wall and over
here we have the holy grail closet tada
the makeup you guys have definitely seen
some vlog style clips of this kind of
general makeup storage area and I was
originally planning on doing a full on
like makeup collection tour because it's
like every beauty guru ever and the
entire broth has done that but I
literally got to the point where my
collection was completely overflowing
which was definitely not cute at all so
I actually went through and got rid of
and by got rid of I mean donated like
90% of my makeup collection and now I
kind of only had my like favorite
products that I reached for on an
everyday basis and it honestly feels so
so so good so I think I can just kind of
go over in general what I have of course
I have that setting space up here
Beauty blenders lashes different skin
care foundations tanners powders blushes
and bronzers concealers and he dragged
or like more art type makeup looks
glitters more glitters liners brows
highlighters lip liners and a regular
lipsticks liquid lipsticks lip glosses
some single eyeshadows
and makeup cleansing wipes down here I
have ISIL up health and down here I have
more excess lashes for a beauty guru I
feel like this is a very very small
collection and for me
having everything nicely organized and
all together makes it so easy for me to
pick out makeup before I'm doing a look
before I'm filming or if I'm putting
something together so I really really
love the system that I have going on
thank you to its sister desi Perkins for
the organization tips she did a full
video on her beauty room tour and this
is literally it's so insanely helpful
and these make organizing everything so
incredibly easy and really really easily
accessible on this top shelf I have at
various different wigs from whenever I'm
feeling Maya and dragged fantasy and
want to go from a brother to a true
sister these are so fun and they're just
displayed on these little styrofoam
heads and then right next to it the
makeup storage I have my youtube
subscriber plaques which are probably my
most prized possession of all time I
cannot wait to get a house and display
this literally in the front
walk-in hallway to say yes that's me but
I'm so proud of these and I keep these
where I see them every single day in the
make up filming room I love this room
I'm here majority of my time so I really
wanted to make it really really special
and really really cute obviously but I
think it's finally time to move on to it
the last room of the house if you follow
me this way out right across the
apartment we have probably my favorite
room in the entire house oh this is the
walk-in closet the first thing that you
see when you walk in is of course this
huge holding rocker right here and on
here is all the items from sisters
apparel displayed a loud and proud
obviously fans know you can get all your
sister's merch and gear as sisters -
apparel calm right here on this wall
once again we have another large selfie
mirror if I put on a new outfit at ways
like to stay here and pose in front of
it and see if it looks good on me if it
frames the body well if the fine is
looking good or flat it's usually
looking flat but I can see it right here
I custom designed this entire storage
unit from Ikea once again not sponsored
but literally so good they actually have
a thing on their website where you can
put in the dimensions of your room with
walls and doors and everything and
design a full-on closet storage thing so
this is actually what I was able to come
up with and I am literally so happy with
it so proud it just stores everything so
efficiently and I'm able to organize
that really really well so and then I
only have this beautiful leather pouf
which is great for sitting on if I have
any friends over if I have my stylist or
designer over helping with outfits they
can sit right here and sometimes because
the bow
was right there I'll come out of the
shower and fall asleep on here
butt-naked it's very very comfortable
that was probably too much information
you didn't need to know that regardless
the poof I think I ordered this from
Amazon I believe and then of course a
just little carpets what's sisters soft
right here the first storage area I have
our shoes and like I said I really
really love shoes starting at the top I
have all my boots from my wire cells my
Louboutins some timberlands some Yeezys
that runs different mix-and-match shoes
for the most part they're all adidas I
absolutely love adidas you guys know
where it literally all the time from
shoes shirts and jackets everything and
then of course we have my everyday go to
the Balenciaga switch you can see me
wear it almost every single picture I'm
sorry they're really really comfortable
and they're super cute we have a cute
little sister's poster and then I feel
like her bag I think literally every
beauty guru ever has like 80 million
Chanel bags little purses
do you are a Louie Vuitton and the top
traders have some accessories I don't
really wear that many of them so I don't
have this drawer like very very fall but
definitely nice just to have them just
in case my earrings you guys always see
me wear the same one of my little lock
knuckles that I always wear from Louie
Vuitton and then of course my bracelets
that are way too expensive but I've
saved up for my entire life and I've
definitely been a beauty guru staple
item that everybody has so I don't
really have them in accessories but
anything that I have is stored right up
in here this deck story have my hats
which is actually thank God our drawer
that I don't really touch that much
anymore like I said if you've been
following me since day one a little you
sad the ugliest man bun and they have
terrible and these faithful hats were
glued to my head I just loved the way I
looked in them most of because I hated
the way I looked
I hope moving back a little bit here's
where I have all of my like more formal
pieces or my moral long pieces so I have
all my different jumpsuits you guys know
I love a good jumper that I feel so good
so powerful so like street wear ninja
type of look when I have a good jump
suit on so I have my graduation jumpsuit
my sister jumpsuit and a few other ones
my overalls are all up in here I have my
Coachella looks for archival purposes
you need to get them framed out I have
all my different suit jackets for want
to go to fancy events I literally hate
wearing suits so I don't really have too
many of them but I have a black a red
and a blue it's just in case whatever
the color coat is and then a few
different white dress shirts as well so
moving on to this wall right over here
we have my more every day at casual
stuff that I'm playing from all the time
this is mostly like shirts
sweatshirts jackets and hoodies
obviously you guys have seen a general
theme with me I don't really like to
dress up that often but I can still rock
a really really beautiful it's lame look
and make it sophisticated with a
sweatshirt
it just works trust me obviously you
guys can see that I have a very very
strict color scheme when it comes to my
outfit being white and black and gray
okay see I'll throw in a little bit of
color which is all stored in this drawer
right over here but that is very very
few and far in between so so doing over
here we have all the white and gray
pieces once again mostly sweaters I have
my underwear and socks drawer over here
what you definitely do not need to see
and then just some various different
t-shirts which are not very organized
but they're there just in case I want
them I really love this middle section
this is where I keep all of my different
jackets and kind of like more heavy
pieces so I have like 87 million
different denim jackets I absolutely
love them and a few different pieces
that are custom made by one of my fan
pages salads our illustration he paints
my face on the back of jackets hello
that is the coolest thing in the entire
world I love these so so so much I
always keep them right there in case I
want to once again so promo a little bit
because something wrong with that some
green or camo jacket and then a whole
lot of some block farmer jackets some
cropped jacket some adidas jackets
champion Chanel YSL everything is kind
of in there if it's an outerwear type of
piece in this top drawer I have my
sister shorts when it gets hot in LA I
don't really have that many pairs them
because I just don't really like the way
I look in shorts but I just found these
recently which I feel a little it's so
cute and how loud they're like boyfriend
Schwartz but you know what's not cute
the fact that I don't have a boyfriend
and the second drawer down I have all my
pants and I've been obsessed with
getting really really cool pants
recently for some reason I don't know
why it's just so fun I literally used to
wear black skinny jeans every single day
I probably have like 30 pairs of just
blocks and jeans literally or right here
they're all from Laura's boutique use
code days for 10% off they fit amazingly
but I was just getting so bored of them
and I looked the exact same every single
day I've been trying to spice it up a
lot recently and then in this drawer we
just have my sweat shorts which I would
wear if I was ever gonna work out which
I'm not let's be real so the stores
probably completely who's this and then
a few different two-piece sets and then
finally on the bottom we have my like
sweat pants slash casual pants type of
drawer I love this Shore this is where I
keep all my adidas track pants that I
wear all the time and some different
Corp and pieces that I've been upset
- recently as you can see I definitely
like a very very casual item I like to
be very very comfortable while still
spicing up the office somehow and then
finally last but not least the last
section of the closet is all the way in
the back or right here and this is where
I keep all of my block pieces and I know
it looks a little bit barren right now
almost everything is in the wash
I picked a very very bad time to fill my
closet tour but you know what we're
gonna make it work obviously you guys
know that I wear a hold on a block so
this section is literally usually like
filled to the freakin brim but there's
just some really cool pieces out here
like about geography a few different
crystal pieces that I haven't worn yet
some unreleased this is apparel items
what could that be I don't know and then
just some fun pieces like this a furry
jacket but for the most part I think
that's actually it for the closet tour
like I said I definitely will go more in
depth in a future video when I move into
the new house but that's everything I
think we're done already sisters I think
that is it for this apartment tour today
I really really hope you guys enjoyed it
I know I've been saying that I was gonna
do one since moving in here literally a
year and a half ago but I just honestly
I've never gotten time to it I'm always
working I always have boxes and people
over every single day so it's placed a
little bit messy but I figured it was
finally time since I'm leaving it very
very soon
to kind of set everything up make it
look really really cute and show you
guys what I've been able to do with the
place over the past year I'm really
really happy with how it turned out and
I really hope you guys liked it as well
and got some inspiration and design at
tips I know that I'm so beyond blessed
to be living alone in the middle of Los
Angeles California and this huge
beautiful apartment I literally pinch
myself every single day because it feels
like I'm in a walking a magazine in this
life is a dream and I don't want this
thing off as bragging in any way shape
or form this would literally not be
possible if it was not for you guys so
thank you for all your love and support
and for everything you guys have changed
my life truly for the better and I
absolutely love you guys so so so much
and I hope you like this apartment tour
like I was thing beforehand - I've been
saving my money for a very very long
time now and I'm super close to being
able to buy a house I'm so beyond
excited there's been a goal of mine
since I was like literally three years
old I cannot wait to decorate I was
thinking to it that I really wanted to
look at full-on decorating and moving in
threes to the new house when I get that
so definitely comment down below and
tell me if you want that but if you guys
did enjoy it don't forget to go to big
thumbs up down below and show your
support it would really mean a lot to me
if you've not ready make sure to click
the subscribe button as well and join
the sisterhood it is a pretty lit time
we are five million sisters strong so
thank you guys once again for that
youtubers changing a bunch of things on
their algorithm which is literally so
beyond annoying and I know I've been
getting so many tweets and comments from
you guys say that you're missing the
video
don't miss the videos I want you guys to
see them office they put a lot of work
and love into them and they're pretty
good if I do say so myself so make sure
to put that bad notification icon if you
guys like to follow me on my makeup
trend you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both the same Charles my
snapshot for more my huntys I thought
was genius Charles an extra ass after
Charles this video sister shout out goes
to sister Talia thank you so much ray
boys following it supporting you I love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to retweet videos they go
live on a Twitter all right sisters
thank you so much watching this video
today I hope it was worth the wait
I love you and I will see you in the
next one