with your eyes I know we've got a crazy
fun day so far but it's not in the
bureau's sometimes we have to do a lot
of different events so tonight we're
going to a party
the links are gonna be they're gonna be
leggings it's a sister cinched leg look
I love us darshana leg look it's not my
sister I overdo the change you have to
win change I'm not posting a picture
this is the traditional Jean thought
would be a good look for sister yeah
know where your crop top dude Oh weird
this crock-pot Pepsi crop top for you
roars no this one's a little bit of
print and I think it's masculine with
the red
be the same so many pairs a chain
pantsuit because they're cute and trendy
holy and we can put you in this good
Michael Costello jumpsuit this is the
James iconic everyone will know it's
James when they walk in when you're in
this looks like it fits though it looks
like a bit like it would fit actually
really nice and cinched we love a cinch
sister yes we do oh my G bunchy overall
oh dude why is the waist here no this is
an overlap it's like it's like straight
put those with no shirt no sure yeah I'm
just not gonna wear a shirt to an event
she proposed my wife Sal your wife L
boots farmer I don't think you'll like
the YSL bomber oh it's like shine oh I'm
scared of a huge ad jeans have like one
pair of jeans you can wear as a surface
or short wait we should put them in the
flash like Mary dress what is that diff
iconic classic Mary dress what started
my entire career hello yeah with no
pants love you couldn't look for sister
and maybe a pair of heels too perhaps
this will be the last outfit that we're
gonna put me in and I'm just an overall
with nothing under it I feel like you
look good are you guys wearing a shirt
so are you today okay so I need some
accessories probably since early a baton
because James needs more fringe at all
times also a and Gucci belt cuz again
rich oh okay yeah this is a good one for
you and then maybe something could he
drink you Sonny is this iconic I think
it's a good look for you okay you ready
come on out sister can I not wear this
ever again in my life please okay ready
for number two yes please come out and
share we love a cinch sister can't
really breathe that's the point I
actually love all those looks on you're
not gonna lie
we like the masculine touch it'd be easy
you don't get an option go purely for
the loss outfit come on out sister oh
this is literally james on instagram i'm
really been watching myself right now
i'm scared
yeah this looks so good on you what's
going on I'm scared do you like this
outfit No
out of the three of those good and fresh
sisterhood you late the bottle alright
definitely not the adidas dress with
heels cuz I like this cuz the crop top
so I guess the overall
[Music]
these are
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my gosh wherever you you mean the
world to me oh my god oh my god sis
you're here it's so nice to meet you
do you like my time okay they come in
ten minutes
wait
[Music]
[Applause]
to much taller sister James dad knows it
so time yeah yesterday sister James are
so much more broad sister James today
[Music]
we love you and we're so great thank you
thank you for giving me co James for 10%
off oh my god that was one of the
craziest days of my entire life I take
my makeup off now yeah please
you found the kind Thanks that's the
best feeling in the world I know this is
something that you really did not want
to do this morning when I proposed the
idea to you but did you end up actually
having a good day tonight
I mean it's pretty interesting to see
like what you go through every day and
like your life and all the people you
know it's really a lot of people think
youtubers do nothing but that's not
really true
I mean James's day was extremely busy
and it was pretty stressful actually
behind the scenes stuff that no one
actually sees is probably the most
stressful part I give him a lot of
credit for doing his job so well oh
sweet of you I know you did not want to
do this like and this lady's bad oh not
at all actually not at all but it really
did mean a lot to me that you were
willing to like be such a true sister
and a true sister and live my life with
me today let's do it Peaks intense what
was your favorite part and what was your
least favorite part of the day my
favorite part was probably the event
Kosar interesting to me all these makeup
artists I've never really met before and
at least favorite part was probably just
singing because I can't sing for my wife
you didn't mind the eyelashes or the
nails oh yeah well that was awful too so
even a lot of today was makeup tailored
we did go to a photo shoot post on
Instagram do some comments you applied
to a few business emails as well and
they went to an event so could you see
yourself living a life like this in the
future like
you tuber cuz we do a lot of the stuff
yeah I can definitely see myself being a
youtuber but probably not makeup base
but it was really nice to see all the
hard work that paid off at the end of
the day and I feel very accomplished
finally my face is nice and clean it
feels good to be back it's brother Ian
oh yeah thank you so much for doing this
video with me today like I said I know
you hated it but it really did mean a
lot that you're willing to indulge my
crazy but fun sister life so thanks bro
if you guys enjoyed this little mini
series with sister yet please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below I had so much fun something this
is him honestly I'm so happy to have
such an amazing brother in my life and I
really really do truly love Padma you
guys better like this video I did not go
through all his work for nothing
who's giving it you to like you heard
the man give it a big thumbs up down
below and subscribe if you have not
ready yet to join the sisterhood we were
a pretty wet time if you like to follow
me and I make up to her you can follow
me on Instagram and Twitter they're both
the same Charles and my snapchat for
more on behind the scenes things up is
James Joslin extra ask after Charles all
my social medias are Ian JT 12 hit this
is we have a huge surprise for you you
guys me and Ian have had so much fun
dubbing these past two days together
that we have decided to start a brand
new show here if I YouTube channel Club
the chains and show and the first ever
episode will be airing this upcoming
Sunday April 1st I am so pumped it'll be
a weekly thing on my channel so I hope
you guys are the most excited ever I'm
so excited to be working super close
with my favorite person in the entire
world sister in so hopefully you guys
will check that out this coming week and
we hope you guys are excited just as
much as we are we love you guys so much
thank you for watching and we will see
you in at the next one bye
[Music]