hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel
today's video I'm so excited to bring
you guys a brand new episode of beauty
battles those who of my favorite people
on the planet the ones that gave birth
to me sister mother Charles and sister
father Charles welcome to our channel
brother oh my god so my entire family
because they right now LA and on my
channel I do a really awesome series
called Beauty battles where I have two
different people both take one half of
my face with all the same makeup
products and they are challenged to see
who is the better ME way and being that
these two people came together to give
birth to me I makeup guru I figured what
better way to test out who I really got
the makeup knowledge from my dad or my
mom then have them do an episode of
Beauty battles so that is exactly what
we're gonna do today how do we feel
about this are we excited excited I am
excited I'm a little nervous because
although I wear makeup every day your
father is a much better artist than I am
yeah so I was gonna say that too I think
that the playing field is definitely
actually even in this situation at my
mom wears makeup every day and as the
true sister she watches all my YouTube
videos she's always the first person
text me every single time I upload be
like great for you you can't drink on
camera I didn't I definitely think she
has that makeup knowledge but my dad is
far more creative far more artsy I think
like we said this could be anybody's
game at this point
without further ado if you'd like to see
my parents a battle to see who was the
better anyway and learned about me and
my childhood and our crazy family keep
on watching okay so for today's video I
picked this look out for you guys to try
to recreate today it's really simple
sure I'm gonna take the Tarte shape tape
you're doing this first
[Applause]
so tutored Assessors and I asked you
guys to send in questions for my parents
answer about me and my childhood and
growing up with me and sister Ian so are
you guys ready for a quick little Q &
slay sure why are you pushing it you're
pushing his face I'm just holding my
thing gently and you're like I'm trying
to would you keep moving it around the
first question is from Jenna and she
said huh see you guys
how did y'all react when James wanted to
start doing makeup I just was confused
at first because I've never seen boys
wear makeup so whatever my first thought
was that perhaps he was transgender
which would have been totally fine but
that was a whole new unfamiliar area for
me and I was nervous for him and I was
nervous for myself because I knew things
would change but once we realized that
James was comfortable with himself we
were comfortable with him and we were
very supportive and still are with what
he's doing yeah for sure it was nothing
like a rough patch in our family and
everybody was kind of confused but I
kind of like try to explain to them as
best as I possibly could that I was
comfortable my gender identity I just
wanted to do this to kind of express
myself and of course like once I started
like gaining followers and getting
paychecks and stuff it became more of a
reality that like I wanted to do I was
like something serious other than just a
little hobby after school going back
even further though we asked what was
your guys's reaction to James being gay
you're gay I don't know do you have the
better side or do I I'm not sure I got
no better Oh Nicole asks how was the
family decision of James not going to
college and if he did go what would you
have liked him to study architecture
interior design fashion design I think
that would have been his forte actually
the whole College thing happened rather
quickly in my mind he was
I believe yes that he would have studied
something in the creative arts field and
I was still determined that he was gonna
go to college up until the very last
second okay so I actually have a
follow-up question for you two I was in
high school working really hard in doing
well on my grades but kind of last
second I kind of hit you guys with hey
I'm graduating early and moving to
California not going to college do you
have any advice as parents to any other
parents out there who may be watching
with their kids about college and for
those kids who might not feel like
college is the right path for them
obviously each individual each
circumstances obviously each person each
individual we're gonna be here okay I'm
glad I promise go ahead
so obviously each individual is unique
each situation is unique we you answer a
smartypants
if your son or daughter's got good
grades and they've been working hard and
if they want to go to school let him go
to school if they don't want to go to
school you're in the dream for about 80
grand a year so what kind of from that
standard life on a budget by budgetary
I'm asked what's the most embarrassing
thing sister James said as a child
t-ball sitting at the second base line
braiding the second baseman's hair
that's embarrassing
she looks great Gabriella looked amazing
she did look great but we ran a t-ball
game priorities I didn't think the
baseball field or the infield was
exactly the place to be braiding
Gabriella's hair that's what did it for
me that's what I knew something was a
little different well what do you think
I do remember that situation I also it's
so cute how you're like actually trying
so hard for every question I think it's
cute that's why it's funny just be
natural you're doing fine
your egg looks good it's nowhere near as
dirty as mine
I draw how is James are coming a big
influencer at /pha mass changed her
guys's lives I think the major change is
him just not being with us all the time
because he's living in California but it
is very surreal for me when we are here
visiting him or when we were in New York
City a couple months ago people
recognized him stopped him and want an
autograph or a picture and to me to us
I'm sure he's just James and to the
world he's James Charles and it's kind
of cool to see that everybody just loves
him but yes it definitely is a little
scary a little scary as well so you guys
mention the last question helps
sometimes a little bit scarier for the
world to kind of like know me so this
question comes from Nicole and she asks
mama and father Charles how do you guys
feel about the hate James gets for
anything as a fan it always makes me so
mad but I'd like to know how you feel
it's it's terrible and because he's a
new quote-unquote celebrity we are not
used to this and I do I admit that I do
read the comments and it just breaks my
heart that there's so many people that
are so honest
people that are unique if you don't like
what somebody does or what somebody
believes in then that's okay but don't
don't be mean don't be cruel and it just
breaks my heart people are for the most
part that's why I don't participate in
any of that online stuff because as a
father you only have a couple of
responsibilities in your life one main
one is to make sure that your kids are
safe his safety has always been a
priority to me that's what scares the
hell out of me because just a lot of
time and that's always scared me school
bus I'm grateful for all his fans that
follow and protect him and support him
because it gives me strength to know
that there's plenty of people out there
that don't feel the way those selected
few do so I'll be so down this one is
for you and in a lot of cases when it
comes to boys and beauty we
unfortunately see a lot of like horror
stories online about their fathers not
being supportive from sister Kalina Papa
Charles what was it like building
James's glam room and the basement I put
a mirror up and some makeup lights and
tried to do the best I could to give him
what he wanted his glam room used to be
my office it was so I had to move out of
my office pretty much which was no big
deal but that's what I do I build stuff
so it was no problem I had fun that was
I think a really cool experience to be
able to bond with my dad because we've
always been really close we boys built
stuff together but obviously like we
were talking about before makeup was
definitely a really rough patch for our
family when we kind of started off so
that was a really awesome just
experience that we had together because
it really showed that like they were
beginning to be way more supportive and
helped me in my career it was clearly
obvious that he was dedicating a lot of
time with a lot of energy to it and it
was gonna be something that he was going
to pursue so it just made sense to take
it to the next level and give him a
better area to work and a different
setup so that's what we tried to do next
I'm going to use the morphe 35o palette
for some color on the eyes use code
James for tempers
that's right it daddy's awfully
concerned about his shadow worry about
daddy shadow
Karolina asked what was one thing you
didn't allow James to do it but he did
it anyway
wear makeup to school I would have to
say everything eyeliner
oh god this goes on top of your eyes
right yeah I guess I don't have a steady
hand oh well that was pretty good I
think
don't be looking at mom what's now you
were nope nope you're looking at mine to
see what I'm doing
where's that go do it on the bottom I
don't know I don't know if I want to put
this on your waterline am I gonna hurt
you I'm not putting the stick into the
why for Christ's sake it's this that's
not right is that right well why would I
push stick on your I do I going on
underneath your I know goes no no I'm
gonna put something in your eye it makes
them look pretty that's okay they look
fine I'm doing his eyebrows next I'm
gonna fill in the brows wisps don't you
very competitive I am are you looking at
okay brows know this family is a funny
subject because thank God you got my dad
for us because I know they're horrible
they're links have anything of her yeah
I just put in a little line at the end I
don't know you should put them together
you shouldn't put a more together
yeah you should start like right here
okay that right there yeah so I need to
put little hair you actually 100%
correct Oh get me up in the morning when
you're ready to do your eyes I'm super
excited because I've only done my mom's
makeup I think twice every time I do it
she complains because it always looks
too much but you know what I think
sister Christie is ready for a full glam
makeover something you guys want to see
that give this video a big thumbs up
down below I'm gonna
your eyebrows I need some tips on how to
look prettier that's you already look
beautiful you saw your makeup game could
be a little better I'm sure it's a
snatched snatched that's a good word
yeah it's nan does this involve glue on
your eye that goes on the bottom of the
top all right so I've never worn false
eyelashes before so I'm not sure if you
put mascara on and then the lashes and I
know after you the lashes you always put
the mascara on to blend them together I
have no idea how to do this hey I think
I did it
I'm going to put this on and try not to
glue James's eyes shut
wouldn't be the first time Kim asked
what is your guys's favorite makeup look
that I've ever done my favorite is the
solar eclipse it was my idea but it also
was a very creative very cool look that
did well I believe to reveal its it okay
love marketing well Burnett there's been
a number of them I like the one with the
hand that was when he first started this
colleton yeah the skull that's like two
years ago
I know I just got that once one of my
favorite ones I thought was really cool
and I also liked the one with the matrix
that you the color matrix on your little
I thought that was extremely intense I
thought looks like my old yeah those
were some of my favorites when I was
younger and still had time to do a lot
of those creative looks I would go to
school all day for eight hours and then
go home and do my homework and then go
to work at my frozen yogurt shop and
then sometimes go home and finish my
homework or if it was a really late
night sometimes do a makeup look and my
mom always goes to sleep at like 6 p.m.
so I'd I don't always be the one awake
so he was at 11:30 midnight is he come
upstairs to say what do you think so he
would always be the one to do the lux
before they would go live okay this
question is from sister Sebastian and he
asks what were the options for James
when he found out you were pregnant
question is that what were the name
options for Jason he found out your hip
fracture if James was a girl he was
going to be named Chloe and he was named
James Charles James after his grandpa
who passed away two years before he was
born and Charles is my dad's middle name
so hence James Charles I know you like
to have a full lip oops so I know you
over lined them oops oops going on oh so
[Laughter]
sorry I'm pounding on the Beautyblender
yeah I had a little bit of a ooh I do
now as well now I'm gonna go in with the
liquid it I have mine Oprah liquid
lipstick oh oh
[Laughter]
stay on your side oh I'm gonna like do
the corner of his mouth no no put the
mushroom on there you just don't look
very you're like how's it go oh yeah you
could do that oh my god okay sorry last
step I believe today's setting spray oh
that's very close
I think my mom and dad have completed
their beauty battle for today I have not
seen the finished result yeah I'm a
little bit spooked mcboot my dad just
did me the honors of cleaning my mirror
for me or are you gonna rotate it to
ready yeah one two three
tada trusting look we got going on here
well let's go through I feel like the
base for both sides looking mediocre at
best
you both powdered after which is great
cuz nobody wants a wet face all day long
yeah nobody wants a wet face you all
done no no I think da definitely took
the Ilyich home really the lash is a
place on more accurately oh my hat my
lighting jamya lash right I don't know
looking at it I would say no daddy
didn't do the waterline no don't you
like mine I didn't want I was afraid I
knew I didn't want to put any I didn't
feel comfortable putting his pencil on
his I forgot this is the finished makeup
look today I am so thankful to have two
extremely amazing and supportive parents
that love me and love what I do so thank
you guys for having me up Sedalia I will
be a very very honored to walk outside
of this makeup look on my face maybe I
don't know about this I really hope you
guys enjoy this videos today and learn a
little bit more about us as a family we
are crazy
somebody please send me an email about a
reality TV show we will definitely come
on its first tour if you guys didn't
like it please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and subscribe
if you have not already
we just hit literally three million
subscribers last night which is so it's
like literally blows my mind thank you
guys so much for the constant support
and love always you all mean so much to
me I never in a thousand years thought
we would ever be at three million
subscribers so this is so crazy and
unreal so from me and my family to you
sisters out there thank you so much and
if you haven't already click that
subscribe button subscribe comforter The
Sisterhood we are pretty lit it's a good
time I promise if you'd like to follow
me on my makeup already can follow me
answer which better table just James
Charles at my snapchat for more behind
the scenes I stopped a shame Charles
that extra s after Charles my dad does
not have any social media accounts
please do not go looking for him but my
mom John is fine if you'd like to follow
my mom her thing is Christy be
team up on her thing down below she
always post pictures of median and she
always comments and likes back too so if
you guys ever want to talk to her she's
there and she's great so she wants to
talk to me you could talk to her this
video sister shot it goes to sister
Gabby thank you so much baby for always
falling in supporting I literally love
you so much
and if you guys like to be the next
video sister shadow make sure to always
retrieve it at links to go live on
Twitter alright stationers think you
start watching this video we love you so
much and we will see you in the next one
bye
use code James for 10% off you know if I
had to on my fly away it's all the rest
no it's not I don't know I never used
one of these things before I'm not a
diva what you got to do this one sound
what no you gotta say it if you don't
say it it won't open
you're making me feel insecure whap
yours is more better greased or
something then I can't honey I don't
know what I'm doing wrong yeah you're
doing it but you're not teaching me how
to do it myself
sorry
well editor he said cuz I don't think
I'm gonna be able to figure it out did
you do it again trying to god
come on go to any guy try it again try
it again one more time
Wow Wow