hi sir welcome back to our YouTube
channel as you can see I'm obviously not
a mineral makeup studio a very expensive
penthouse suite and all figures with all
my best friends does my YouTube video
light we need to early go to five crops
it's the morning we just so hot but I
definitely am going to be getting the
lamp resistivity so I just figured might
as well just be approved you could sit
and do anything if I don't do this very
often a lot of course applies now
moisturizer to begin with some touch a
water paint okay
surprise not become baby there goes my
all-time favorite looks together to of
shades of right now being a new and
natural beige just because my sticks
element sucks
recently I've been doing ok that's a
really good things happened and I've
also had some really bad things happen
so emotionally I was down and I don't
know probably the biggest project of my
entire life and I'm so excited about it
and then it's like something stupid
this is not stupid I promise can I say
honey please do important in my life
was there a good approach there hi
have a great day thank you my life was
there contact I'm just so cool my
parents flew in product um as I first
have seen I mean literally like six
months
mr. Feeny was there of course even the
grace through there all seasons
apartment somewhere I don't know where
there was just one of those products
that you know it's going to be so much
work but that you like want to work on
but you don't agree in school you don't
feel like the dumb assignments and
that's a thing you always like want to
die every time but when you get like
your product that you actually really
wanted to work on like a poster or
something or refined
nothing else is fine just know that I'm
working already so our three guys that I
don't know that is active recently on
the social media that cell but it's all
good self and I promise
whether you guys seal everything is it'd
be really probably just because you know
please if some of these sisters are
already starting to theorize what's
going on and what the tea is a chef
starter that's okay I'm just really cool
that you guys are so supportive of me
even when I'm out there you know that
working for you you know that I'm
correcting the grind is real
[Music]
so this is going to be a great first
Oklahoma stories of you're one of those
people that's like c'mon you choose make
too much money it's a fine name on the
wall boy please click off because your
life if you notice right here milestones
so the first of the blue bricks that was
different than what's on my head and
they two-lane subscribers and it was a
huge huge deal for me and the love
bracelet came I think I think it three
million so I believe all the time I'm
sorry they might sleep with them I do
not take them home because there's
obviously they don't want to lose that
and they also be lost do they have very
important sentimental value I bought
them because of you guys and you guys
are special to me and these are writers
of you have to say that sounds this one
is just include with a nail bracelet
it's a literally still have to get
awfully I really gonna spray tan I have
so much trouble actually removing it
from my rest but for some reason I'm
excited certainly any physical activity
pepper which is very often it flies off
literally was that right for in
Australia doing how we agree but one of
the most like all acts and things I
practice the law and ladies
oh so the guy I'm joining to get rather
than you guys can't stay nice and
recently what was i you're like there
was just in town
mr. beetles here MEAP Anna get along
really well together for now shall we
dig under / - we're fine then we go to
Cannes which they were sorry your
California really
that's looting the entire world Kansas
watching us and please it's not to be
this is hashtag let's talk about hashtag
should I be if you're not going Canyon
that is a pretty cool it crosswalk I'll
say every time that I go there there
that leaves a line of authority cars in
the drops a car and another copy is
there in his car he blue flings open the
door there's a Hazen sternly and oh my
god with my launcher videos Taylor all
the time the pregnancy gotcha born as a
kid of course something apart we asked
him to hold my stove oh he I'm inside
has baseball ha something coming can you
please hold my soda so I can you look on
their hand - what
and so he helped myself and I
not even knowing the caves adventure
right but the story doesn't end there
because we tried back to lower which is
like the 30 minutes waiting for cans and
we walk into her permit and you guys
have probably notices until the club
videos anymore remember on insert of why
I can't believe sit still easily if I'm
sitting so I would be jiggling something
will be playing something or like
tapping something and for me one of the
easiest things to play with are the two
priests about me I'll sit there and I'll
spin them around and I'll jiggle around
as soon as it's go to Laura's house I'm
just sitting in a car for 30 minutes so
I need a little little jiggle to my
breasts and guess what isn't there
Mike's dollar party you just include
mail bracelet that has a knock off fly
off so I started crying
my god I literally just lost every slack
and okay let's figure it out let's find
it like Ron emission Nelson stars
so our first instinct of courses tool
injures car we go it's not there's a
nice price ok let me show up hold here
and there's never a time line I'm like
line that this actually happened luckily
for me
- had a twenty people take a photo with
me at a public restaurant where migrants
are proudly showing bingo thank you
sister she being the best so we start
running through the people and I not
thinking like okay into the fall once
it's like disappear
was literally just happened oh sweet
girl be apparently stealing your a today
okay actually I'll talk about it I don't
know anything nothing is mine you know
James is my friend if we use some of the
similar techniques yeah cuz they're good
techniques
don't say anything do I'm just keep
loving him in this world we need like
support love it like that because
everyone's really mean his side of the
car the story the inspired winner to be
signing his half through the car window
is also bracelet that was super super
points mean did you know once the team
so I'm freaking out gonna figure what we
can do still looking for the photos and
about one girl outside of the restaurant
we did a full body photo I remember
let's say hypothetically something with
me I'm literally looking through the
parking lot or the bracelet 30-minute
Dantes that would mean likes going me
the ground wahoo the bronzing obviously
all the parking lot and what was so
sucks and that was a lot of people right
near the parking spot of the where we've
ha I think you see it's a sprinkler that
looks like a nail and this one girl
literally is like the Cartier just
include bracelet oh no no as soon as she
said I'm like whoa doc don't do what
that brings it wasn't way too
bad-looking never the wait the first 30
minutes forgot about fart I'm like Soph
I'm super upset
we're finally alone fix them call Lauren
obviously looking through our time
photos like waiting to see if anything
appears we posted me in her mom outside
of the restaurant and if you zoomed in
on my rest the race that was already not
there sound like great
what are just out there on face and burn
30 minutes and looking for Glee said
that literally was not even there
so that's grades I'm now thinking keeper
either loss a loss in the
it's literally like somewhere else and
all the sudden drew my best friend is
literally like James what you're
fighting with again
did your glasses fly off my no sister
eyes were in contact and using James
your bracelets at your house when you
were punching I thought it was your
glasses how the drugs wearing contacts
you think the race looked at your house
so we let me drive all the way home 40
minutes from Haines
there was somebody speeding down the
freeway we're all it was right on it
isn't there you know house we spread to
the corner and the little behold there
was a croc in my mirror and guess what
sitting you're getting on my floor and
you crack your mirror over the last two
hours the ballpark you based on you mean
so ii listening to be accused of of
ceiling at the port and so because the
buses are ever looking for it thank you
all they're thankful to loving blows so
sorry about how I almost lost my
bracelet and then didn't lose every cell
because it was the wrong desert shower
on this turn you're a great story
you're amazing James even those flaws in
your perfect you guys are gonna want to
do this next one this is like so
literally you guys know I'm usually
commentating on Everest public's really
flirting for a real long another two
months away
and the husband is literally since your
paintings had which nobody ever taught
me I'll say that right now and now that
relationship is over for literally and
the craziest or exact same reason ever
licked I've had some pretty intense boys
stories this one's hot okay tell you
because why not
probably James who's a little blinded by
the love what would you think someone's
like so beautiful perfectly appreciate
how I have Accra know that was going on
by knew something was involved are very
interesting like how it all comes
together big fresh titles would be Oh
Mac I think that actually happened it
was money ever
and you look really good together go now
long we should they pardon the girl here
and I'm going to get 30 in 15 minutes I
think like police spend it on me already
at everyone so beautiful crushing John
no stereotypes
but I must look so uneven side
[Music]
anyone look jeans this is eyelash glue
guys I'm not exposing look at that crust
about the hospice it's been abuse a
me
[Applause]
[Music]
weapons do we skin like emerald a
wide-mouthed they're finished mr.
Layton's ammo glamour perfect for
gambling away and sisters away you've
got a Las Vegas Genesis my best friends
in the entire world I definitely need
some time to myself in something you
should have some positivity and good
people in my life after everything that
it's kind of today please give it a
thumbs up down below
definitely the comments won't tell me if
you actually like the silent video I
don't do this very often but it is so
much easier than just a regular style
video and it's it's a kind of gel giggle
and talk to you very simply in all my
life
but inside that I don't have to do the
opposite because I'm so busy working
which I know definitely has its pros and
cons but just know that it's running
time for you guys and you join a family
and also bleep about life right now
become a brand new video
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
dirty Bobby's answer you're much better
that will just save more seats up
yourself dr. Charles sister to Rica
thank you so much Laura is falling and
supporting and loving literally is so so
so much and we're gonna go live on it's
better I love you so much I'll see you
at the next one
[Music]