[Music]
hi sisters jean-charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel so today is
Friday October 26 between Halloween is
coming up in a few short days and am i
excited absolutely have you done
anything to prepare no I think I'm
literally RSVP'd for 9 Halloween parties
over the course of the next 4 days and I
have a costume for not a single one of
them so that's really really good as you
can tell I'm doing amazing sweetie work
today's video I originally had planned
on doing a last-minute Halloween makeup
ideas tutorial video but upon planning
it out I got very bored considering I
feel like there's been a tutorial for
every different Halloween look at least
87 million different times and also um I
was feeling lazy today I know you how to
do at least one Halloween makeup just
her or else she was literally all kill
me so speaking of books that have been
done 87 million times today I'm gonna
teach you how to be a mermaid now listen
hear me out I know you guys have
probably seen a million different rings
before but it is still one of the most
requested looks every single season and
apparently I've actually never done them
before according to my Instagram makeup
and YouTube history which is actually
it's so crazy
so if I'm gonna do mermaid you guys know
I'm gonna go big or go home I am
definitely not gonna toss on some teal I
said I would call it a day I have a
beautiful eye look planned I have some
special effects planned and we're just
gonna look like I just crawled out of
the depths of the sea
ready to slay Halloween season 10
without further ado let's get started
[Music]
hi sisters at James house here and
welcome back to my DIY okay so before we
actually get to the makeup application
portion of this mermaid on the face I do
have like any kind of scale I do that I
want to do on the neck inspired by
Channing Judith you guys may remember
that name that is our see the artist
that did my amazing transformation for
my beauty con series she is so
incredibly talented and that is actually
how I found her or that series was the
picture that she posted on Twitter of
mermaids killed on somebody's leg that
she did with special effects and I want
to do my best to recreate the same exact
thing on my night today but on a budget
and make it really really easy for you
guys all we're going to need is two
things a hot glue gun I got this other
Castro for a whopping 11 dollars glue
stick got these for three dollars now
these are fun glue sticks because
they're glittery can you see that great
I thought these would be really easy for
the marina boat since I have green
sparkle in them and we're gonna add a
green sparkle on top anyway so saving
ourselves some time if you're under the
age of 13 don't do this unless you have
a parents help I don't want to get sued
for one of you burning yourselves with a
clue so this has been a PS I thank you
for coming to my talk I can't find
parchment paper most because I forgot to
buy it so what we're gonna do is take
this classic green sheet and hope that I
don't burn it and stick at the glue
stick in the glue gun
basically what I'm gonna do is take the
glue stack and take this sheet and I'm
going to just squeeze it real good and
just put a dollop of glue on there and
kind of the shape of a mermaid scale
kind of just like that and I'm gonna
give the gun a good twirl to get that
straight off and then sit there first
like that because in case you didn't
know hot glue is very hot once again
thank you this is what a fuse bag so
once this is how to second to cool down
I'm gonna take my clean finger and I'm
going to lately press on the glue and
flatten out a little bit right before it
fully hardens and you'll notice that the
glue is slightly moldable so you can
kind of form it into the shape of a
scale to say thoughts kind of like round
and flat like that is literally it so
we're just gonna make like a lot of them
[Music]
so once you have like a lot done final
here to do is describe a pair of it
really sharp tweezers I'm gonna use this
[Music]
oh this is not playing well
oh my god the next thing this dope turns
out my face is gonna burn down am I
crazy
you saw that oh it's right here oh no so
as always I always like to start off my
foundation at first I'm gonna grab my
Too Faced Born This Way Foundation if
this photos in the shade natural beige
and I'm gonna tell you right now the
shade is far Tanner than I am we're
going for a mermaid look okay we're
gonna be tan and I'm also gonna grab a
little bit of the Mac strobe cream and
gold light as well
I know desi Perkins actually just
uploaded a mermaid tutorial and her look
was so incredibly beautiful and inspired
me to do a little bit more of a glowy
look for today just gonna grab my beauty
sponge and mix that together on the back
of my hand and then just plop it right
on there and blend it
and then with the access foundation on
the back of my hand I'm just gonna take
an m4 3:9 and I'm going to really dip
into that and blend down my neck one to
avoid getting a million comments saying
that my foundation doesn't match because
I know and two because you guys just saw
me making those skills earlier and those
are going to be going on my neck later
on in the video so I definitely need
everything to blend together seamlessly
next I'm just gonna grab a concealer
this is the Attar shave tape as always
and apply this to the high points of my
face to cover up my under eye bags and
also just to add some more dimension
just because I really like how the
attention goes right down to the center
and just really makes everything look
super pretty from products that I'm
actually gonna use two different ones
the first one begin the regular Laura
Mercier translucent setting powder this
is so my all-time favorites and also the
brand-new Laura Mercier glow translucent
powder I haven't really tried this
without yet but I do all my stay to be
very very dewy today so first
impressions time I'm gonna dip my Beauty
Blender into the regular powder and use
this to set right underneath my eyeballs
just because I really need to set this
in place and also just right on top of
the Dinos bridge as well in the center
of the forehead just to get those
creases gone to contour today I was
gonna go buy a before Oh fire brush usko
J's for 10% off and dip into my
anastacio contouring a kit and just dip
into this middle cool tone shade right
open here I do already normally tend to
go a little bit harsh with the contour
just because I really like the way my
face looks when it's really tough
loadout
but for today I do actually want to go
even a little bit harsher than normal
especially with the bronzer because this
is obviously a mermaid sunkissed kind of
type of look and the next undergo am
about five to seven brushes is just a
beefy big a bronzer brush and dip into
this kind of more a caramel shade or
right next door to that one and I'm
gonna use this to blend together my
contour and normal skin tones I'm gonna
save the blush and highlight for a
little bit later on I'm mostly because
I'm not exactly sure what combination
I'm gonna be feeling when it comes to
the eye look so for right now what I am
going to do is it for once not baked
because I definitely don't want to look
at any more powder than I are do I
really want that dewy look so I'm going
to grab my mac fix+ of gold light as you
can see this bottle has definitely had
quite the usage this is like one of my
favorite makeup products
early in the entire world it is just so
pretty and it is just like fix+ butter
does have a slight glitter in it that
just reflects so nicely on the skin I'm
gonna get myself a quick sister spreads
I'm gonna do a rose quickly using the
Anasazi eyebrow was in the shade and
medium brown air pencil all time and I'm
gonna do these a little bit more like
fluffy and a wispy than normal I
definitely don't want them to be like
normal James Charles Instagram brow I
want a little bit more of like a
underwater wet moment does that make
sense
you'll see okay sorry line I literally
filled them in exactly and like I'd
normally do but and then it's gonna grab
the anasazi clear gel after that and I'm
going to go right through and kind of
brush those hairs upwards to kind of get
rid of a little bit of that brow pencil
to really make them a little bit more
light and fluffy and just to make them
look spiky by Seljuk at brow hello I
kind of like low-key don't even want to
conceal under Neath my eyebrows but I
also feel like I need to it's cleaner
really really lightly go right
underneath that brow not even really to
clean it up just to literally cover over
the foundations I'm just gonna pull that
concealer right down onto the eyelid to
prime for eyeshadow so that is the face
all done and now I get to move on to my
all-time favorite part always which is
going to be the eyes and for its today's
like I actually have a really fun look
picked out from an artist that I fall on
Instagram her name is Gabrielle with two
axes and is this like neon green to dark
blue kind of cut crease with the glitter
liner look that she has going on it is
so crazy so intense but it's like it's
going to look absolutely perfect with
this mermaid lips today and we're gonna
attempt hopefully hate to make this look
good so I'm first gonna start off with
any fluffy brush this is the Emma 5:13
and just dip into a neon bright green
shade and I'm gonna pop this right in at
the inner corner right here just
starting by topping it in so it's super
super pigmented
and then I'm just going to lightly blend
out those edges to make sure those edges
have blended out on an m4 33 I'm just
gonna dip into a bright yellow shade and
a tiny bit of that green as well and
just go right over the edge
that's too yellow I'm just kidding going
back into the green on another I'm 433
I'm gonna dupe into a light teal shade
and place that right next door
focusing this color right above my
natural crease with any excess I'm just
going to lightly blend this up going
back into that green take sure we didn't
lose any of it with the same exact brush
on the teal I'm going to dip into more
of that tail shade and I'm going to use
this color to form that outer V starting
off by just kind of stamping that shade
on there and then of course going in
after to blend it out and my outer
corner I'm just gonna take a little bit
more of a fluffy packing brush and dip
into a darker blue I don't know places
right in the outer V and just pack it on
there and I'm just putting that shade
right up into the crease
okay sorry hello I am back the camera
just accidentally stopped recording it
has only been over a year since I filmed
this tutorial so sorry about that
once this shadow was all planned out the
way I liked it I'm just gonna go ahead
and cut my crease using a a small
concealer brush and some shave tape on
the back of my hand this is gonna have
so far I'm gonna grab a small pocket
brushes the a matte one to four and just
pack on a light teal shade I mean like
Hello right on the inner corner just
packing the shade on there right on top
of the concealer being super careful not
to get it over the line it's okay if the
shade doesn't purposely touch that cut
crease as well because they had to be
using a liquid liner in a few short
minutes just to line out the crease and
then without saving that brush I'm just
gonna dip into more of a that metallic
like aqua shade literally oops I had
literally don't know how to do tutorials
and I'm just gonna place that right or
that kind of line between it the light
teal and dark blue just to blend them
together I'm just kind of patting it on
there and then using a slight like
back-and-forth rubbing motion to blend
at the same time so for the inner corner
little liner I actually don't have like
a sky blue liquid liner so what I am
going to do is use this white liner from
I don't even know what Brendan says my
friend hey-zeus gave me this one but
this brand it's just a really good white
liner mixed with literally the tiniest
bit of the ofra liquid lipstick in the
shade on my beach now I think I'm going
to use the yellow liner I'm going to
follow that line and wing it out just
like that oh my god pretty okay and then
once that later is dry I'm just gonna
grab the Urban Decay glitter liner in
the shade a Midnight Cowboy and go right
over top of that yellow so I think for
the liner I'm once again gonna grab a
little bit more concealer on the back of
my hand and yet another tiny brush this
one is the morphe at 19 and I'm going to
cut the lid kind of like again I guess
but like only in the liner area using a
really tiny pocket brush I'm just gonna
tap on that metallic teal shade from
before right onto that concealer carving
a little bit of the peaches and cream
and glitter makeup base on the e30 7
brushes just a tiny little brush and
just packing that right on top of the
liner Ivor's gonna pack on a gold
pigment right on the inner corner then
just placing got some chunkier glitter
that I found at the craft store right in
the center just gonna go the Urban Decay
Midnight Cowboy liner one last high and
pop it over top of that inner corner so
that is the upper eyelid all complete
and I'm actually really happy how that
turned out
didn't really have too much confidence
myself not gonna lie but kind of looking
good and fresh so I'm gonna finish out
the eye now using the amp or three three
and first dip into that same aqua shade
from before and start placing this on at
the lower lash line making sure to
connect to in from that outer V region
and then go in the deep blue shade on em
506 and just tucking that right up into
the outer corner and pumping it up into
the lash line as well any time use a
little bit of green or right in that
inner corner I'm gonna use the Tarte
press payment in the shade at top yacht
to highlight my brow bone and inner
corner to finish off the light in my
waterline I'm gonna put the Tarte
claypot in the shade of blue moon right
up in there and then four locks I'm
gonna pop on a pair of Yas Queen from
Lily lashes these are brand new and they
are literally Miami's except one time as
long as
the other this is everything that I've
ever needed in a lodge all right sisters
and that is one I of this mermaid look
all complete I'm gonna go in and if they
want off camera quickly they save some
time because that literally just took me
an hour half I'll be right back to
finish out the rest of this hug we're
back it's been another hour but I am
still going strong kind of those Lea's
all complete and low-key like hello I
snap like this looks so pretty I
absolutely I'm obsessed of how this
turned out thank you so much to
Gabrielle for the inspiration at today
but let's move on to it the rest of the
face to finish up this mermaid look so
to put on my blush and highlight and
like everything else today I wanted to
grab a pair of a fishnet tights because
that creates a whole like scale effect
and I forgot to buy them so instead I
have to use my very very expensive at
Swarovski crystal tights that I wore to
Drakon I'm very annoyed about this and
I'm going to try not to ruin them a
little bit on us that literally barely
did anything you're kidding you can see
it but like that is not okay so this
gift obviously did not work but it's
okay because we're gonna have scales on
our neck later on light hopin it spot I
do want to add something to my face so I
picked out these half little pearls that
I want to stick on kind of fun oh my god
doing things those nails are so hard
I put one right up in here and one right
on that one too okay so that is pretty
much the face all complete I think I'm
going to add on the Anasazi Beverly
Hills liquid lipstick in the shade
insomniac as a base and I'm gonna pop on
a little bit of the Mac reflex in the
shaded teal right on the center all
right you guys see that it already
sensors I'm just gonna finish this off
once again with a little bit of the
mac's fix+
gold setting spray and that is pretty
much this look all complete so you could
totally stop here throw in a wig some
seashells a cute little bra and a
mermaid tail and call it today but this
is the James Charles youtube channel and
you guys don't really take it a step
further so I want to add some special
effects to the mix I'm first gonna start
by over my makeup forever flash palette
you can use this or like literally any
face paint it does not matter okay
totally what I'm actually gonna start by
doing is scraping my liquid latex from
Ben Nye and a roll of toilet paper now
special effects is very very complicated
but I'm a beginner and I do definitely
want to learn more there may or may not
be a video on that coming very very soon
but for now this is all you're gonna
need I'm gonna pour a little bit of it
out into this little hole in my lash
thing just for easy access and then just
using a disposable cross buns I'm just
going to start by applying this to my
neck I'm gonna focus in on little areas
at a time as well because it does dry it
pretty quickly
so literally that's all I need then I'm
gonna grab just a sheet of toilet paper
I'm going to shred it up into little
pieces and I'm gonna lay it right on the
skin and then once I does on that I'm
just gonna go back in with a little bit
more on the brush basically what we're
doing here is creating like a second
layer of skin over top of the area that
I want to have the scales on so once the
latex is completely dry I can actually
peel up a hole in the middle and it'll
look like my skin is like ripping there
are a lot of different ways you can
actually achieve this look as well I
think Channing and her original photo
used
scar wax which I do have it right here
you can like mold this kind of like clay
on the skin but it's definitely a lot
more work and it's for people who really
know what they're doing and
That's not me
well unsexy she's all on there I'm just
gonna take another bag a glob of liquid
latex on the spine and I'm just gonna go
lightly over the entire surface just
kind of brush it to make it smooth and
then with that access product I'm just
gonna go around and really really
lightly and kind of feather the look of
latex now on the edges obviously it is
going to try obviously we're gonna put
foundation over it to fix the color but
we want the actual formula and the
texture to blend with the skin as much
as possible
I'm just gonna let this dry down for a
few minutes I'll be right back what does
pretty much fine I'm just gonna grab a
fluffy brush and some translucent powder
and just tap that right on the surface
just to make sure everything is in place
and nothing is still wet by accident
and if you're doing this at home as well
your neck should feel really really
tight right now that's okay it's a good
thing then I'm just gonna grab once
again at my Too Faced Born This Way
Foundation and my own for 3:9 and I'm
just going to stipple that and then just
going to powder that once again okay so
now comes the fun part where this stops
looking like a gross scary rash and
starts looking like mermaid scales so
I'm just gonna grab my tiny little
scissors that I use with my lashes now
be careful during this time please do
not cut yourself but I'm just going to
lightly go in and start picking at the
center of the latex now once you're in
you should be able to start cutting so
crazy okay and you're basically just
gonna cut out a big hole right around
this entire area and then once you have
that oval I'm just gonna cut little slit
into the edges to kind of like ruffle
them off a little bit
you
kind of lightly tug on it as well now
I'm going to grab my m2 g4 brush and my
make up forever flash palette and I'm
gonna dip into the teal blue and green
shades and it's kind of mixed them all
together and plopped them right in there
then it's gonna grab a little bit of
block kind of a lot a bit of block
honestly I don't it's going to use this
and shove it right in the outer edges
just to create some more dimension and
to make it look like it's an actual hole
[Music]
so finally now we get to all the hot
glue scales we literally spent two hours
making today half of which are now
missing inside of my stove can't wait to
burn my house down to apply this I'm
just gonna grab some Kryolan at Spiricom
as you can see mine has clearly been
through quite a lot at this point still
works just as well basically this is
just kind of like insanely strong glue
and all you do is put it right on the
area it's gonna wait for it to dry a
little bit and then stick on some sister
scales
[Music]
you
you guys about liquid latex on them like
without do anything once that is all dry
and set in place thank God
I guess the answer is to use liquid
latex and not Spiricom we're learning
together now I went to gravel once again
that same little brush and just too big
into the makeup Rover flash palette I'm
just going to grab a mixture of those
colors and we're going to stipple them
over top of the skills just to bring
some of that color back since the tan is
clearly not what we're looking for a
little bit of reflex teal right up in
there I should put some little glitters
in there too just for funsies Oh Katie
already sisters and that is this under
the sea a mermaid look all complete yeah
I did for this look came very very last
second and I have not done a tutorial in
a very very long time I definitely
apologize if the city was a little bit
of a mess but then again so is every
single James Charles video and in the
end it sounds of looking okay I am Heike
in love with how the face makeup turned
out this I and this glitter liner is
serving me mermaid or realness I am
obsessive it thank you so much to
Cambrian for inspiring me on this look
today that's what the Ark so special
effects not the best but I still think
it gets the point across I definitely
need more practice I literally have not
done it in over a year now but can
always get better
that's the fun of makeup overall though
I really hope you guys enjoy this little
under the sea mermaid and makeup
tutorial I've seen so many beautiful
mermaids over my past several years in
the makeup community I think it was
finally my time to give my classic James
Charles take on such an iconic look at I
really hope you guys liked it if you did
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and show your
sister support it really means so much
to me and also if you guys choose to
recreate this look for Halloween and you
decide to be a mermaid definitely tag me
on Instagram I cannot wait to see all of
your guys's beautiful faces if you have
not ready don't forget to click that big
red subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we are nine million
sisters strong oh my god and also click
that Bell icon so you can get a
notification every time I upload a brand
new video if you like to follow me on my
makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both does
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes I've stuff is Danis
Carl's an extra s offer Charles oh by
the way as well for all my loyal and
amazing scissors out there
sistahs the panel has a brand new line
launching two day at the same exact kind
of this video is up and live oh my god
you guys we have choc pants and a
matching track jacket and also a
matching prop Tony as well so you can
like get the pants and
choose-your-own-adventure
fur to the top we have a cropped
windbreakers we have booty shorts coming
out and we also have industrial belt as
well which are of course inspired by the
iconic off white belt they say sisters
they are custom and so incredible you
guys this line is something that I've
been working on for so long and I'm so
incredibly proud of and I hope you
choose to go check it Oh sisters -
apparel calm or shop using the link in
my description down below this video
sister said i-gos - sister Haley thank
you so much love for always valued
supporting you I love you literally so
so so much by the way at major shout out
to you for your cute sisters peeling
hoodie and your iconic and beyond school
look so amazing if you'd like to be the
next videos that sister shadow don't
forget to always a treat you're visiting
us think alive on Twitter all right
sisters thank you so much Arts in this
video today happy Halloween I love you
and I also see you in at the next
by
[Music]