hello sisters and welcome to messy
makeup trivia the game show where no
matter who wins we all lose let's meet
today's special guests our first
contestant left his eyebrows in 2018 and
apparently all of his friends - please
welcome Jeffrey star our next guest is
back and better than ever with a will
get there one day
please welcome James Charles our last
guest has been around forever but
somehow has not had a scandal so we've
got literally nothing joining us in the
studio after filming her 87th video this
week alone Totti west brom hi sisters
team Charles here and welcome back to my
youtube channel as you guys can see -
the Internet's who very brilliant
specialist is right every star yeah you
guys for today's video I am so beyond
excited because after hundreds and
thousands of comments we are finally
coming back to you with a brand new
episode of messy makeup trivia in case
you're not familiar with messy and
makeup trivia it is a game show that we
play here on this YouTube channel where
I basically team up with two close
friends in the beauty industry and talk
to you and Jeffrey have both been major
inspirations and friends to me it's end
day one and we're basically to be
quizzed on all things beauty industry
now could be anything even though this
is not my channel I do not know what
they are promise yes absolutely swear to
God
thank you promise really I never had any
say in these they're completely done by
my friend
off camera completely so I have no idea
this is gonna be equally as competition
I love it a competition and I'm ready to
win what do we win okay so I'll let me
give you the rules sister yo Harold
merged yeah yeah what's the grand prize
oh my we've in a full sweat suit my
shopping spree at Marshall's yeah I
already had a shopping spree at
Jeffrey's yeah you did raid my closet I
love that okay so what do we win tell us
tell us so basically here's how it works
we're gonna go through our major
proteins and getting money together huh
girl all things life beauty updates but
while we do so before every single step
there's going to be wanna question one
juicy T and gossip question about the
makeup community make them history
people in it who knows and they didn't
have to impress our buzzers so whoever
buzzes in first according to our
producers in the back
okay that's answer the question first
and for each question there is what we
like to call a sister sabotage that this
thing could be a challenge
it could be a challenge this was just
like makeup trivia not like oh no it's a
game show we're going to be yeah what's
the first one and I'm a little shook cuz
yeah [ __ ] can hit the fan at the sign
your moment yeah so basically if you
answer it there's sister Shantha Tosh if
you get it right you get to choose one
of your two contestants and give them
the sabotage but if you get it wrong you
have to take it for yourself and
basically in the end the viewers the
sisters decide by telling us who they
think looks the best
it's basically a large harsh right but
they're pretty fair judges I will say I
will they love to read me this girl if I
look ugly so you guys are and your guys
are fine migrated section awesome listen
I'm ready I don't know I'm okay let's do
it let's just dive right in
okay okay well I feel like we have so
many things to talk about and catch up
on and just get clams without further
ado are you guys ready we're ready let's
go BAM
[Music]
[Applause]
question number one says no one was born
being Pro beauty guru what is the name
of the oldest makeup tutorial currently
public on your own channel wait I still
cover types blue brown serpent makeup to
turn oh my god you know it's really
crazy I remember that yeah oh wait okay
yeah
it was disgusting with that for a moment
let's not we should pause the video and
watch it
I just did a video few months ago
reacting to it for the first time I had
not looked back at it until that it's
cool though it's cool to see the growth
I don't know what mine is I think that
maybe no but okay titles and mine was
Pelle the five dollar drugstore blue
beautiful it's been a long journey for
all three of us okay what's my sister
nervous oh that's not even Bob okay
that's like starting off slow okay
that's like not even not Bob I feel like
either one of you guys it's not that bad
it's not that bad
hmm Geoffrey like us I'll take one for
the team
yeah sure no only thing is do you guys
have a dry Beauty sponge for me yeah
this was already wet yeah
Wow cheater I came wet say always are we
putting on our foundation yet yes yeah
so now what's going on I can't wait I
don't care what's wet or dry oh this
feels weird
okay gross screaming OH even I'm so
lover finally all together filming this
video actually gets been talked about
for so long oh right yeah I get on it
don't give me that look behind the
camera
oh my god okay this dry good or bad I
feel like I'm like hitting my face with
a piece of wood oh okay good or bad um
I'm not sure I guess let's to go and get
to the contours of my face I thought a
dry Beauty sponge was gonna be really
hellacious I'm ready to move forward
yes ready okay question number two says
Fenty Beauty helped revolutionize what
it meant for brands to be inclusive yeah
name two foundation launches that
weren't very inclusive in their first
launch
tart f fe f i all i think of this lemare
but it's not it's not that it's a tart
and you know I will argue this though
okay can we have like like messy spill
debate we got we can have a debate but
go ahead
how many shades did they come out with
they came out with 40 since I did do a
review on it yes okay but listen
they came out with 40 and there was
about 25 shades of the same shade
mystery which is why their foundation
range was a flop and they then had to
apologize an add 10 later so they did
add more but six months later no this is
the wrong group to have this
conversation
six months later if you're that brand
and you ever have that much money you
better bring in honey and they swap for
you but the formulas sickening and James
one so here we go again
I love concealer and I'm a brave I know
oh shoot I'm gonna get it on this one I
just I just have a feeling I would take
this for myself
Oh what do you think white concealer
sometimes it's fun to make it really
nice to highlight
yeah probably don't wanna
no ma'am i won I hope they talk to you I
feel you tougher usually close to what I
really do look natural at me no you're
fine all right what concealer are you
using miss thing I'm using your favorite
or fee in shade invisible it is not
called invisible is it stop it I'm going
with a little thin team I'm using Miss
born this way again okay I really like
this concealer oh my god oh my god you
look amazing lot more full coverage than
I had imagined this is my first time
trying the morphe concealer oh okay yeah
amazing then there's me using the same
products for the last two years
hey if you love it you love it and I
kind of like that about you I mean you
are loyal I do too like and then when
you introduce something that you really
really love it's they're like oh [ __ ]
you must really like it yeah this is
true sister star I have a question for
you
well we're getting glam here okay
obviously is my first official music
over here on my youtube channel yes
there is so much fun literally when I
figure products of all time I don't know
you have a history of music as well you
just tweeted okay say that you are in
the sister studio working with oh wow I
really do I was like you know what I'm
gonna announce to the world that I might
be a little so it's the 10 year
anniversary of my very first album
called beauty killer and I felt like it
was time to come back and just say hi to
everyone there was someone in the studio
that people are gonna be like any clue
that he has usually I'll give you a hint
off camera but I'm really scared let's
just say that they have won a few
Grammys oh I'm finally able to do
everything I couldn't do and I was
signed and
you have the freedom now I had no
freedom back and now I can do everything
on my own terms so I'm like you know
what I just want to have some fun so
that's really exciting
congratulations sister thank you hi
she's back
also we were talking about I think it's
time for James to do some original music
I want to see you were doing a music
video meet Ellie well that would be sick
I mean I really want to like so badly
music is definitely on my calendar and
to-do list for 2019 I just think I'd
surely need to work on the finding the
right team and group of people to work
with it like see the vision and like see
the potential just because I could
imagine him doing anything his first
ever like oh yeah cuz I loved the cover
like love love the covers so much what
kind of forgetting that you have a voice
too
I do I know can we sense a Christmas
album coming I want you and your James
to do like a yeah I reckon oh my god no
he cannot sing well Hansie were in
Hawaii for her wedding
we sang her on the piano together I have
video I have video footage
[Music]
I showed my James my husband James the
cover that you did and he was like wow
it is crazy to see and in like a short
period of time how much you've grown
like this polished video of you at the
piano and then flashing back to that
video at our wedding
yeah it was like the coolest oh yes sure
I just have my face really badly I'm
melting at the moment all right this
indie Brown marketed itself more
luxurious audience OH
Oh 360 no reason why I know that is
because it was traumatizing to use and
that's how I got kicked off the peerless
oh I actually thoroughly enjoyed the
brushes but they were way too overpriced
there were a few of them that ever there
was a big good one yeah there were no
clumps at all you're just the package
you're gonna cry it was just a little
just a silver it was brave you know it
was promising it's a great honor to the
other side it was pretty men what's the
sabotage oh my god I think I would die
to see James do that that is so iconic
we both do it and just a little fingers
ready can I have some of them oh well
that looks good you my travel pessimist
and you wear tires on it
let me just set this concealer oh my god
perfect eight
I'm so perfect oh my does this is
disgusting don't worry I'll get a good
gal sure I do actually as a matter of
fact I'll be rubbing this off all right
Q I'm feeling sad continue to wait a few
more minutes my nose trigger Oh getting
brave don't be bitter it's also very
graphic on a good note you're making us
look more attractive I love to do more
charity I know I'm just honestly I need
a brush in my head immediately let's
move on to the next play and what is the
next step well this is our promotes a
healthy immune system minimizes fine
lines and wrinkles it has a great
fighting enzyme that is true and it
minimizes fine lines and wrinkles what
do you want to take my pink contour nose
like no Jeffrey is gonna love that too
much you just watch
if you moments later oh my god are you
kidding me looks so stupid you don't you
really don't you really even read not
till I don't look stupid no I'm just
going with like some blush on my nose
like a little freckle yeah what do you
think is gonna be like a pretty the next
trend like the freckle thing is like a
thing for a minute I think being honest
and nice what are you guys most hated
about 2019 in the PD community got it
thanks for coming ah I'm just sitting
here thinking about what I'm most
excited for I don't know I'm really
excited for what you two have going on
I also just love watching what made a
really bad choice
I can feel revenge on its way I feel
like you correctly oh we're doing
eyebrows now oh whoa
do I get to shave someone's oh that is
not funny you know is that the stuff
batons shaving I love a good sister
shave question five says there is
nothing more inspiring than hearing the
stories of people who made their dreams
reality
name three beauty brands ce o--'s
co-founders or president Linda Murphy
Claudia So Ra and listen I'm decease Wow
that was bad
Linda morphine or Vienna anastacio and
Marlena makeup geek BAM
thank all the time I ran out Ross I
would have been getting some attention
now and that's the last thing that I
need so at least I have a 50/50 chance
of knock what is it I'm nervous I feel
beautiful right now so bring it my
makeup thank you
you must use black for your eyebrows and
no oh listen listen I need to see you
with black eyebrows I feel like look I
feel like James already had his moment
oh I saw the picture of James from three
years ago think once again this is my
video
he already had his moment he's grown and
blossomed and until until what he is
today I will take the black eyebrows um
so what should I use eyeliner eyeliner
have one hour no please no I'm blocked
oh how about I could do morphe gel liner
[Music]
good in glot oh that's my jolly good
Morpheus too late Joanne or use code
answer time for softer purchase I'm just
excited to see talk to you anyway I
already hate it so much I was having a
good attitude it just left so talk to
you while you're doing your a little
challenge I thought I would ask you a
little question she said wait Britta
so today is Friday and this game is
being uploaded by the way also on
Fridays we were paying everybody just
thought I would um you didn't upload
yesterday or on Tuesday for those of you
who do not know miss Tati over here
major inspiration to me an amazing
friend as well but she's been uploading
five days a week on her channel for the
past how many years five years cannot
really we'll never be able to relate
don't understand how that even works but
you just recently announced that you
were done doing that and you wanted to
take a step back which i think is so
incredible I've seen you went behind the
scenes in your work ethic it's literally
unmatched I would die if I had to
produce five videos a week watching the
video as like both a fan and a friend I
think was very very emotional but I'm
surely everybody at home watching that
it's been such crimes like would love to
know more about like why I'm like how it
feels to even be like taking a little
bit of a step back - thank you you
already feel that is the sweetest um
yeah I do you know it was really
exciting is getting a text saying hey
let's film together and actually being
able to be like yeah yeah let's do it
and half the time and half the time
because normally I would shift from like
filming to Halo back to filming going
through edits posting like it was just a
24/7 thing
and I mentioned in the video that James
and I are trying to have a baby we want
a family so you know maybe Westbrook is
I'll be the god sister god sister is
hopefully on the way the challenge with
that and like being hormonal and like
emotional and going through that and
five days a week I was like none of them
yeah I need to like de-stress be happy
and more joyful about it and honestly
the craziest thing about it is I'm
already feeling more refreshed and happy
to film and more creative and I'm like
wow that happened so fast like I was so
scared of it and then it was the best
choice ever be real for a minute I am
excited to actually be able to hang out
with you more I don't mean our I know I
think like really I got so sucked into
that schedule and and that was like my
main commitment and I really felt truly
in my heart but if I stopped or slowed
down everything would fall apart I'll
stop you thought I'm just gonna ask how
does it be back band on your I could cry
right now because I've never felt more
connected and more like in love with my
subscribers and like they are being
incredible and it makes me like want to
make better videos and like you know
rest and be better as a person and a
better role model like it's just all
good things so I live I am so good and
I'm so grateful definitely got some
foundation oh my god stop
must be nice cannot relate once this is
worn and shown insane girl we put her in
the archives we wave at her once a month
and say thank you for your time when
you're making your drop to Goodwill
yeah right there I'm like oh my god w
bro I know okay I know whoa I don't have
it formed
oh okay so what's next I shot oh
I shot isn't it
okay question number six says was it a
highlighter
was it an eyeshadow or was it pencil led
what is the name of the jeffree star
cosmetics black highlighter I have no
idea
onyx ice unfair advantage where's my
affair Oh what's the sabotage yeah I can
breathe a little bit of fresh air today
what oh wow like fees no oh oh wow who
wants that challenge I'll let you to
pick don't make eye contact they look
Brown okay oh no ma'am
oh no sweet the face butchers are right
there yeah yeah you know what's the best
part about all these brushes
girls cartoons for 10% off Norfolk oh
it's actually James Charles or James
James James 10% Oh same my - I love that
code works really well actually it's get
to the 10% every time every summer times
even on federal holidays doesn't matter
the weather are we using your palette
looks she has been okay with me but just
see what you see on my I love it's been
loved and just it's ready for me okay
great I'm right I'm down okay
well I'll be rubbing my beautiful
eyeshadow brushes Jeffrey why don't we
share okay great we just have so many to
choose from it's crazy I'm just gonna go
in and do some pink in honor of this
little going on today just gonna play a
little bit of skip in the crease
hopefully it doesn't stain me I have
lots of things to do tomorrow okay
are you priming your lids with that
brush that's genius like a quick it
worked
see efficient efficient I'm learning new
things got lucky Geoffrey what can we be
expecting from jeffree star cosmetics in
2019 whoa okay so we all I know you have
your favorite concealer but I do have
concealers coming to you really yeah Oh
new concealers and setting powders are
launching maybe in the next month or two
Oh - do I get a sneak peak I would love
for you I just want you to review them
okay like you weren't my friend and give
me a full wear test I'm kind of over
people thinking that you can't do like a
real biased review with your friends
like listen I get it I love what I might
know let's talk about that well I
obviously that video meant a lot to me
as like a friend but as a viewer I
thought it was so cool to literally
watch you sit there and say this is a
biased review and I think you know of
course the pds about it but for the most
part I did feel like a lot of the
comments were really really positive
this was an important moment for you it
was an important launch like I was not
gonna be the person you know being that
we are so close now I have history with
you to tear it apart and I knew that I
was gonna be a little bit biased so like
I felt why not just say that but
honestly like through and through as far
as palettes that I do reach for I do
reach for this quite a bit
voila and that always says something to
me when you have access to so much to
really see like what you're really
reaching for hmm just because I like the
versatility of it I don't do a lot of
bright so I kind of stay in the neutral
zone but then I like having like okay
yeah that's a creative or it has
something a little bit of something for
everybody yeah do you guys have a hard
time when you film to not like move
around to do your makeup because I'm
someone that like will tilt my chin all
the way up and you'll see me like lean
back and I do like professional
okay over here doing my makeup yoga do a
little challenge coming over there
oh that was actually really sickening
like I live for and I love it already
hit powder room about it yeah everywhere
everywhere oh my god I wasn't even
Salvatore so they literally disgust of
my eye makeup you have got to be kidding
me
well being friends with James Charles he
he really said oh my god I'll be free I
thought you were kidding
no you're not
[Music]
okay hi we're back
Wow really really beautiful isolate you
know we've really kind of died oh my
gosh mini blips highlight don't get too
excited there's always opportunities for
oh yeah vertical really gone okay I'm
ready we're ready
oh wow okay good okay number seven
obsessed the past year was sorry
laura-leigh I already forgot that's
happening okay what do we got oh that's
cute I can do that I can do that
blindfolded let's talk just getting a
real brave bird box have a seat let's
give this with the jeans okay
I'm not worried okay well actually
started highlighting with a pencil brush
my nose because of you that's your trick
that I am like the facetune the nose but
in real life yeah covered up my palate
again a little bit of face this is the
first shade I literally ever have had on
his face
look at the pencil brush mo man I think
it's sick Oh yep looks amazing yeah I
mean everybody's looking really
beautiful at this point I feel like we
need like immigrants question and
sabotage just like Relling get it going
where's getting too hard to - is the
winner number 8 James house Morphy of
Bremen Rock yeah why did we all have
amnesia okay oh well hopefully the
jeffree star cosmetics line has lots of
colors that she's way too sure do and
now what are we gonna do for this one
you chose a neutral eye and you have a
pink oh my god like I feel like there's
not many I think what about like a nice
bold ombre moment with green on the else
no let's do yellow let's do yellow on
the outside agree to the Venus flytrap
this is like sickening look at that look
at the monitor it's so stunning that's
one word to describe a queen bee loves
to be layered dental comes in oh my
skittle all right now let me take karma
such an inspirational shade from last
year that is wrong oh I love it
don't I do you're a liar I love that
it's like dysentery green it's what
later all right
Oh Oh what um I've been sabotaged
how are you Jeffrey how are you think
with your new love I honestly am living
for it I think everyone's gonna start
doing this once this some is that you
think
yeah the new Beauty Tony has a nineteen
we're starting our own region in Georgia
let's roll right what it's just setting
spray okay so this is the last question
I don't know
number nine says unique content is hard
to find on YouTube nowadays this ca
about the perimeter made quite its mark
last year how many total views has
secret lab has directly start a
docu-series by Shane Dawson received
since being uploaded five months ago
Oh 87 million 104 million 116 million
yes there is no James Charles biasing in
this fight
oh I don't wish this on anyone
that's hot oh my god it's Cooper I don't
care you can spring what's in there I'm
so yeah what what the hi it's toilet
water oh hey that is not funny I mean
disgusting okay so who do you want
we're sending over here where's this
belly no there's no Oh No
what was that it wasn't a face looks
like that my makeup looks good we saw
are we done yes we're done we're done
Jeffrey's done I think we all like
Tucker salvage horse doesn't really ran
like we all well I hope you guys through
this episode of messy and make up Travie
I think we all they're really really
good but it's up to you guys leave us a
comment down below and let us know who
you think killed this the most whose
look do you think looks the best out of
all three of us to be honest I think we
all look sickening but it's up to you
guys to of course choose the winner of
today's challenge and also let me know
who you want to compete next if you guys
enjoyed this video today please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and show your sister support and
love it truly means so much to me and
also click that subscribe button as well
and come join this sisterhood we were
almost 14 million sisters song have you
enjoyed the fail
and also click that Bell icon so you can
get a notification every time I upload a
grand nuit video if you like to follow
me on our makeup tourney could follow me
on Instagram or Twitter there pull to
st. Charles my snapchat for presents
eats that's up to you Charles the next
rest after Charles that's the past I
think I'd ever sad really wasn't I
understood you to well for you what can
I find both of you guys alright you guys
so if you would like to follow me then
I've made my way into at the description
box which makes me feel very good and
thank you for having me here I'm also
going to encourage you guys to check out
halo beauty haha
know how do you have skin push their
skin that can look good with any makeup
situation go check it out and yeah and
if you want to subscribe to me cool like
you can join my humble family of 5
million I love that alright if you guys
want to follow me everything will be
linked down below it's just my name
Jeffrey star for everything this videos
sisters how that goes to to serve
Brandon thank you so much love for
always falling and supporting you know I
love you so so so much and if you would
ho blue the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to always reach it
religiously go live on Twitter and
eternal my post notifications BAM
alright thank you guys so much for
watching today's a video I had an
amazing time thank you for having us
James
thank you yeah thank you for being the
best friends litter in the entire world
and being role models and it sparing me
and just being real ones in the beauty I
love you guys too I love you guys all
I'm watching it thank you so much for
watching this videos today we love you
and I will see you in the next one
[Music]