hi sister James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel first of all
you guys happy new year welcome to 2019
kind of fine kind of fresh so your whole
thing about your words so the past three
years on my u2 journey has been quite
the wild roller coaster but throughout
all of it I've had the same a close
group of friends literally through
everything now we were starting off the
brand-new year still you guys obviously
all met my friends within the YouTube
community but I've never really firmly
introduced you guys to like these best
friends of mine and these are like my
family basically that's putting your
pretty much together every single day
we're in a group chat that talks way too
often all day long a little too much a
little too we also have Victor who's
Laura's fiance who was in dotty videos
and also Eldon Cassie's amazing husband
here's Malvina this is the familia this
is the kitty girls and we are all
together and I'm so blessed to have all
them in my life on we been through so
much together and for today's video I
just thought it'd be so much fun to kind
of sit down and repose him okay you guys
asked us all the questions anything you
wanted to know with anything juicy or
fresh or fun and then we're gonna answer
them and we have none of us know what
the questions are including me including
James so this is gonna be kind of fun
yeah I guess this is like yeah
[Laughter]
Oh cute simple person easy option okay
so I met Cassie first out of the group
James and then I met Laura at work we
wait Victor how many followers to James
half at the time like a thousand
followers
Oh kind of further on yeah yeah cuz I
met James through our mutual friend Cade
I'm at hey Zeus first that I met Cassie
when I went to LA for the first time so
we went to Buffalo Wild Wings all
together
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
well we got so much it together the
first night yeah do you remember when we
went to go pick up James and he said
he'll be ready in five minutes a really
sweaty dream I came to California I went
to a guy's house and Twitter and I
didn't have like any crush on him at all
so I was really really nervous to be
there and really slept in the same bag
however I was like uncomfortable so I
wanted to sleep in like full Club pants
and a sweatshirt and like how like eight
blankets out of a woke up with like
literally his sole gross I like hot like
from their entire rest of the way like
fixing ham and then that leads into the
same story of us going to the event that
we met up with yeah and that's what we
met in contact yeah horrible what's your
first emotion because we have a mutual
friend Daisy and I was going to the
two-faced warehouse and Daisy's going to
Loras and we were like okay I'll bring
you to two-face if you can read Laura's
so that I was like mine was normal I
only met James like a year and a half
ago yeah yeah like right like a couple
months before Christmas of last year
because the nice thing was is that he
live in downtown only a couple blocks
from me as to where everyone else here
kind of lives further away so me and
James would hang out a lot because
like within like a five-minute walk from
each other we started hanging out like
literally everything every single day I
guess we both made YouTube videos and
then I would help James then he would
help me and you only had like I don't
know how many subscribers at the time
you had just like hit over a million I
say yeah and I'm the same one in scream
cuz you're answering YouTube are kind of
always the same yeah so it's just like
also that but I feel like my first
impression was just normal
yeah just a normal meeting of a person
like it wasn't anything weird that's
what everyone thinks I mean Laura have
sex all the time and realize that we
love a tional II jump in we're talking
weird he likes to pick his bellybutton
and smelly oh no it's fine do you ever
know well you got - my lady
[Laughter]
why do you smell you have to keep
smelling a relationship me definitely
not me no no because guess guess what
store happens to be selling a whole lot
of one pieces attractive lately miss
Laura's boutique suppose the head of the
fashion don't ever use for jeans for 10%
off that's right I used to wear I used
to wear jumpsuits alternative out of me
and say that I always like jumping out
of my clothes I wasn't jumping out of a
plane
[Laughter]
and it looked really good on me so I was
like yeah I was ahead of the time sorry
I can't help myself
I'm just too fashionable whenever I'm
getting rid of clothes Cassio emerged I
love a good throw by our source full per
se yeah vintage I know why I know I know
I know he can he just likes the
challenge so he goes for the ones that
don't want him secretly but they can't
come out yeah I know what it is also
James is a very much of a person that's
like I need it now
right now suck it so it's not even like
oh let's date for like a couple of weeks
and you can come over to my house after
like a month like a normal relationship
it's like you're cool I'm probably gonna
do something and then yeah yeah yeah
maybe miyamura we could talk again I
think you just want someone so quickly
that maybe maybe they get turned off by
it and they're also straight yeah well
yeah I mean I'm supposed to answer them
you're gonna have to so he must be
talking about the other stuff I like
what I like I like everyone in here for
different reasons well I don't know I
have no knees who's the longest mean
cause you have like are we shared like
such a passion for makeup that we always
like get to work on that together me
more are just dumb I've had so many
crazy memories
the intruder together almost every
single day so Teresa pick one you can't
[Music]
oh I'm scared tweet them pretending to
be friends he doesn't like someone he
will not be back and I'm let them know
he doesn't like them too oh yeah I want
to give him free cloud I think I'm like
in a pretty good place than most people
in the community I know but I definitely
like a little awkwardly way to like you
know what I mean like I won't talk to
anybody if I don't like that you're also
the most famous of all so yeah like you
don't even there's not even anyone but
to me that does not matter our follower
count doesn't it does today no I always
ask him to check us out so fun to see so
like I'm always like James what's your
artistic I don't know I've been checked
in a couple days that's Olivia I do it's
not a numbers game for me like I don't
really care yeah but it is fun you
trying to know your red charlie mine
didn't even exceed the hundred dollar
threshold you should cry Laura so like I
was obviously already friends Lacaze and
hey-zeus and we like we face name all
the time but when I started really
coming to California often for different
shoots or different like bookings I
started talking with Laura and her
family because they were nice enough to
let me literally live with them and take
Laura's brother's room for six months on
and off and we just got like really
really close I obviously moved from New
York so I don't really have family here
so Laura stylet became
like my family and they were it was just
so kind and so welcoming and they were
always there for me and then obviously I
met drew to work together almost every
single day and same thing with Alden and
Victor Victor nails are obviously cold
or straight man and like it's just cool
to like have their support and love to
is just like when it comes to security
and protection it always just like being
there to defend us and stuff especially
like being in the industry for three
years now like I've got so many amazing
people but I've also met so many
horrible people and I've been involved
like with so much and like they have
just always been by my side through
everything no matter what and they get
and they're with me and like they just
know my true intention so like just know
you come for James you come it's just
really cool to have like such an amazing
group of people around me at all times
that I can really really rely on like if
I had not had these guys like I probably
would not be here today like I would not
be as emotionally strong I would
definitely like you be a stripper we do
take it personal so whenever we see hate
comments we really do they learn to talk
about the hate James may not see it but
we reply what can we save like no no
just be a bigger person yeah so he
inspires us to be better people at the
end of the day I think it's you like
social media can look so crazy from the
outside like when you're not really
involved in it it's kind of hard to like
really understand like what's going on
and it's easy to make assumptions or
like generalize things or like say
people are copy or like scandals and
stuff I know influence just always say
like oh you don't you don't really know
what it's like until you're in it but
like the reality is like you really
don't you have no idea what it's like
and what goes on behind the scenes and
the emotional pressure that goes on and
like for me it's it's hard because like
I can't really talk about it with a lot
of people because it could come across
as really egotistical as ungrateful when
in reality it's like it can be really
hard sometimes so like it's been great
to how these guys around me because they
do get it not only how they see me grow
and experience it but they're also like
they witness it to look at it's not as
crazy when you're seeing it happen
firsthand I guess you've seen some crazy
stuff happened
three things he was coke coke honest I
see a broken phone is Twitter coca-cola
if you actually had a gas what would be
things like seriously like if okay
seriously I'm not like I'm really really
getting dropped off the helicopter
plummeting down to the staff James would
bring with him his phone a solar paneled
phone charger and no because you can't
get by on a coke a Chili's gift card my
straw for his coconut oh yeah my
favorite is a red hoodie because it just
sounds a lot in my shade Wow Wow that's
daddy you the darker one there's a
lighter drink socially wow that's one I
name my favorite out of a sister apparel
collection is the artistry hoodie which
unfortunately I'm not wearing the least
favorite eyeshadow is probably probably
cool my neighbor is probably the nude
swirl anyone that you just
yeah and Whaley's here probably the
white the white and the nude waiting for
this one Wow forget any car park that
where he's like wait hold on to snapchat
no let's walk to the car because it
echoes very well yeah at a car park yes
like a parking lot you will take any
advantage at any time to see yeah you
hate so many no God no that one that I
don't like the most you sing bachelor or
something oh don't be rude I don't even
know it but like I've heard it so many
times it's firmly can you sing yeah
death of a bachelor
[Music]
at the moment me in this clot of people
might not know but also know at the same
time that James litter has the most fans
ever like it's not you go to the mall
it's like the malls gonna shut down
probably not it's not even like oh three
people come up it's like 87 people run
there's like tackle no they tell them to
say no because it causes like a yeah and
you guys don't know this but a lot of
times when we go places we actually
don't upload our snaps or our stories
until today because it's that crazy yeah
it's crazy that we hope to LA but I'm
really grateful that you guys like get
it yeah totally and we love you guys
like don't get don't take it wrong like
we love you guys so much
obviously like James is where he is
today because of you but at the end of
the day like he's a human being and you
just have to respect his privacy also
you know like driving through the house
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
email reputation stadium tour probably
30 car garage yeah probably
one car for all of us I really think
he's gonna transform it to something
else like he'll still be doing makeup
but I feel like you'll be doing like all
those people will comment and be like oh
you guys just our friends with James
because of like he like this and this
and this oh the thing about the car
Oh number one people would say oh I
forget what it's exactly about but like
oh you can tell it they're only friends
with James because of this I just love
when people actually bring that up when
they're like oh they're just friends of
him because of XY and Z like I'm just
like at least some friends so gotcha
[Applause]
the truest friends are very happy being
behind the camera so yeah I've been
trying to be on camera for like three
years
[Laughter]
welcome back to my channel I don't care
yeah we're not ya know like obviously we
appreciate everything that James has
done for us and we all have like our
different paths like we all kind of do
different things but it's just so cool
that you know James does want to put us
on this channel but at the end of the
day like we've been behind the scenes
for so many years that it's sometimes
like real me and Laura we're at the Mall
of America meeting great but for the
grand opening for Morphy and it was
literally so surreal to see that many
people in person like I've never seen
that many people in my life in one place
and I was so surreal like I just it was
crazy long I feel like also like oh yeah
I'm not your job so it's not your job to
put us in your video yeah like you're
clapping with people that are mutually
benefiting both of your guys's career us
being here it's not really like
benefiting your career like a can in a
way personal canta do you know what I
mean but and like in a way that like we
don't have to be on your video like yeah
you can do what you want with your own
videos
yeah watch this video morning with
breakfast Alden remember we have
sleepovers
I'll do it except every single morning
cooks us all breakfast boys delicious
and then for dinner it depends on who's
here see they're all dinner mama Laura
Cassie so we can see sometimes it's
[Music]
really actually I think he's always been
like super generous and like kind and
wanting everyone around him to girl he
doesn't show us there's my camera but he
does a lot for us behind the scenes
obviously because of him like Laura's
boutique that a lot bigger and I will
forever be grateful for him because
he'll be like oh do you guys want Lauren
sporty clothes like he tells us friends
sometimes and I like yeah so super like
confident and like not giving one fling
what anyone things around him like I say
he literally walks into a household and
he's he will take his pants off
he goes to sleep gnosis unto you so if
he's ready to out they're gonna
come on he's gonna be stinging the whole
time
[Music]
so the same person he like wanted to say
something he would tweet it like Hamas
but like now he like takes a step back
it's like I mean there sometimes we're
like you gotta have to say something but
he's definitely known which ones to
fight back in fact he's also telling you
as a little brother what not to tweet
yeah oh yeah he's a good anything drops
bourbon convert every street boy yeah
I'm gonna be hard working thank you 19
year old with f9 blending brushes we
were like this is the first ever have
like a real pro like Tex 24/7 like
FaceTime I don't all the time okay so
then basically James and this guy did
wanted to find him all the time pushing
by him out to like oh and then he kept
pushing it back because he had to do
like his like work or whatever which was
like a lie basically so James facetimed
one of his friends and
complain to them about how like this
relationship wasn't working and blah
blah blah blah and like they're not
coming out here to see him and then
basically that person told James that
they had a friend as well which James
actually knows this right having good
friends with good friends with this
person like talk to them on occasion but
never happened to bring this up to that
person that they have also been in a
relationship with this person for two
years
not just like recently but I've been
simultaneously talking and sending the
same exact like good morning talks
FaceTime call same exact watch both of
that for the whole time that you have
you were talking him but of course he
was actually talking to the other person
for a lot longer so me and my friend our
boy friend just texted him the photo
that he had I think my favorite one for
sure was like seeing like the behind the
scenes of like a whole pallet we
actually probably already had it all
[Music]
on the tomato project
yeah I was there when you're making the
Photoshop file yeah yeah no like Suniya
actually come to life and like you guys
like buying in like seeing the
screenshots and everything it's just so
like seeing it still to this day like I
walked to the brand ma James's face like
oh yeah and seeing that looks that you
guys would create with it like for us as
artists like it's just insane to see
what you guys come up with with the
pouts I mean there's literally every
color of the rainbow in there but it's
just it blows my mind I don't say the
launch party simply will I think like
taking the family photo too is like were
together all the time in Suffolk in the
family group so like just to have like a
photo like of all of us together like
all in white looking really nice and
chic and fun and fresh spring thanks to
Eldon kasi for Christmas crying for a
role I know
alright sisters I think that is all we
have for this little like sister family
sister so thank you guys all so much for
being on my channel today I feel like I
have so many amazing people on my
channel and I figured it was only right
to store on 2019 with the people that
have been with me and starting out every
single year to say so
I really hope your sisters at home like
this video as well if you did please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below cherry assist and support and
love I would love to do more videos than
these guys let us know if you want to do
more and let us know if you want to be
on a TV show because
[Applause]
and like we are women that looks
original if you guys wanna call follow
any of them you can check out his ooze
Dru caste Laura and vector and Eldon
behind the camera although socials will
be linked down below they're my favorite
people in the entire world and they've
been with me through so much and I am so
incredibly grateful to have all them in
real life and like I said I don't if
you've not ready don't forget to click
that big red subscribe button down below
swim through the system every year over
twelve merely a sister's so I'm going to
have you join the family and also click
that felt like one so you could get a
little vacation every time I upload a
brand new video
if you look follow me on there make up
turn you can fill me up in serum on
Twitter they're both sisters Charles and
they stop talking so uh this videos
sisters how they posted sister Rhonda
not sister Rhonda who literally
clarified a in her Twitter week so will
be the absolute lowest girl thank you so
much for always falling in supporting
and if you at home like through the next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
always reach me to make something go
live on Twitter all right you guys I
think that is all I have for this video
today thank you so much for watching and
happy of 2019
this year it's going to be so incredibly
lit and I am so grateful to be spending
it with such amazing people around me we
love you guys and we will see you in the
next one
[Music]