hi sisters James Charles sir and welcome
back to my youtube channel oh my god I
cannot even begin to say to you guys how
much I have missed sitting down and
talking to you in filming makeup videos
holy crap it feels so good to be sitting
here today hello how are you how was
your week I hope it was phenomenal happy
Friday and I am super excited for
today's a brand new video this is
officially my first makeup video in the
new studio in the new house we literally
spent like eight million hours putting
together the whole lighting setup which
I will show you guys in the house for
video coming up probably next month but
you have taught me know in the comments
down below I look how I sound do you
live for it do I look busted hopefully
the quality looks good and you guys will
be able to enjoy it the video today
because I have a really exciting one
plan right now there's this really cool
try not to talk going around that I have
been dying to try where you have your
friends draw your makeup looks basically
I'm gonna open up my snapchat and send a
bunch my it close influencer friends a
sister selfie and then they're gonna
send one a bat and on top of that
selfies are going to draw the makeup
look of their dreams I'm going to
screenshot it and then try my best to
recreate their drawing on my face using
makeup let's get started
[Music]
all right so first I have to go ahead
and top to a bunch of my up friends send
me a selfie it back and draw me a makeup
look for my YouTube video I'm gonna send
this help me - lets do a disarray let's
do a B Roberts first short oh my god
shall have a really good one let's do
Avani charlie'd Emilio duh
Dixie D'Amelio as well let's do david
dobrik but be so good
let's do Nicki - somewhere else she may
have a good one Larry I'm gonna send
them the sister selfie and I will come
back to you guys once I have up somewhat
drawing responses how about you guys we
are back almost everybody has responded
at this point my snapchat notifications
are going on crazy this does not happen
to me very often so kind of fun let's go
ahead and see it well my friends came up
with the most recent one it was Dixie
let's see it looks like Dixie created
this like Sun and Moon type of look cute
next we have larai oh he gave us full
detail all the way screenshot this okay
hostile pink smokey eye nose contour the
ours
maybe the house nose contour the house
I'm talking about a sin B or no sign
then little hearts on the cheeks and
then nude lip Abby Roberts oh my god a
little Gucci moment of course I knew
that would come through with this
seconding look this is so cool to be
honest Gucci's by far my least favorite
of the designer brands literally the
most bucks
I miss Roberts I think is onto something
this is so cool she even gave us two
options if I didn't like the Gucci one
Abby also did a block with a green flame
okay honestly as much as I hate Gucci I
think I'm gonna do it the first one cuz
is super super cool Charlie sent us this
gorgeous sunset linear or smokey eye
with a nice white
squiggle Picasso could never honestly
okay what is awesome gonna do oh oh my
god why did she sound a little like a
rainstorm of lightning bolt to Rainbow
moment right oh my god I'm saying I
definitely wanna do this one oh my god
thank you girl Nikki sent us Oh a little
purple polka dot moment that's super
cool okay thank you Nikki David
responded David sang
oh my god gridlock James David what like
why lots of ugly not least we also have
Avanti who was a queen of makeup so I'm
sure hers will be really cute oh and of
course I was right
okay so bonnie did this like a purple
green and black cheetah print i think
this is super cool okay oh my gosh thank
you to all my friends who submitted a
look I think after looking at through
these I'm gonna do a four or also study
over don't take me 18 at million years
to film and I think I want to do a
vonlee's Addison's
Abbey's or the 3 a's and then oh my gosh
okay okay you guys so out of the four
looks i think i'm gonna start off with
the easiest one which it's really not
even easy at all but it's Abby's and
Gucci look so I'm going to zoom you in a
little bit and we're going to get
started okay I'm first starting off a
little bit of concealer on my eyelid to
act as my eye a shadow base as always
and then I'm gonna set that in place and
draw that like brown a wing it using the
shader punch me from my palette while
I'm working on this eye as well I want
to take a brief moment to dis brag about
Abbey Roberts and how literally proud I
am of her if you guys don't follow me on
instagram for a long time now which if
you don't
hello wouldn't even doing you absolution
um I used to do these things probably
like two years ago called sister Sunday
takeovers were basically every single
weekend
I looked for incredibly talented but
like unknown small influencers and I
asked them to film videos creating a
makeup blog and then I posted it on my
stories and like gave them a bunch of
definite try to help them grow their
pages it was a really fun way to just
showcase a smaller artist which
obviously we were now doing in a much
bigger way with instant influencer which
is amazing but the first ever person
that did it take over on my account like
two years ago when she had I think it
was like thirty four thousand followers
was Abby Roberts like that's how we got
started and now because of tik-tok Abby
just hit I think 10 million absolutely
insane and so well deserved I mean if
you guys look at any of Abby's content
she is literally one of the most
talented people in the entire world I am
still inspired by her every single day
so watching her like rise I just been
incredible and I'm just so grateful that
I got to be part of it in a smallest way
like oh she's just super super cool so
now using this red liner I'm going to
draw in
that line is so messy oh I have not done
makeup in like a weeks
you're almost done all I have left is to
add the Gucci logo now I'll be also put
a little bit of yellow in the inner
corner so I'm going to plop this into
here and hope that it doesn't ruin the
entire thing I think the finish off this
arm is gonna add a little bit of punch
me on the lower lash line just to tie it
together all right you guys that is one
of these at Gucci is all complete but I
saw a whole nother eyeball to do I'm
gonna try my best to do this quickly
off-camera and I'll be right back with
the finished love all right you guys
well it took me a little bit but I
finally matched the lips to the eyes and
I think with that being said that is
this Gucci I inspired by my good friend
Abby Roberts all completes right now
it's probably the only time in my entire
life that I wish I had one of the lovely
Gucci tracksuit to take a photo and win
this look because like 50 would pull it
really all together but nonetheless it
turned out so cute
thank you so much Abby for sending this
in and after hours to work we're gonna
wipe this off and move on to the next
one
all right you guys we're back with a
clean base ready to go for a look at
number two and I want to go on to
Addison's look next she created this
like a gorgeous fun thunderstorm with a
rainbow at the end like this is really
symbolizing you know the past year in my
life it's been a storm and now there's
rainbows coming out of it cuz it's over
with okay so to start this look I'm
first gonna grab a little bit of like a
white concealer and just apply it to the
lids I think I want to make the clouds
very like abstract ask okay so we've got
the morphe 35o palette which is all the
pastels and grab this nice little blue
shade right up in here and now we're
just going to loosely just you know pop
this shade right onto the canvas this
looks like I just lay down a nice pastel
blue layer onto the eye I am aware that
it looks patchy that wasn't doctor on
purpose sheer Jam but now we're going to
add a nice cloud outline now we're gonna
add some nice further fluffs into the
clouds still looks like blues adding in
some nice white highlight to do this
fluffy cloud now we're gonna add in the
nice lightning bolt so I'm just going to
give it this nice Suva beauty hydra
liner and the shade a dance party in a
spread there's gonna draw in some nice
lightning balls ups oops that was the
wrong direction so now we're gonna add
in the nice and rain drops like August
and put on her
don't hold on ice rain drop what it's
coming out at the sky I should probably
out in the rain bottle I'm basically
just gonna have a bunch of impermeable
paints or liquid lipsticks and drawn
purple blue green yellow orange Oh
[Music]
literally four hours later that is this
pop art stormy day look by Addison Raya
all complete I definitely think the pop
art like comic twist was 1,000,000% the
way to go and I love love love how this
turned oh thank you so much Addison for
sending this and do you like a cute
little stormy luck where or where is
there phone right now
oh yeah thank you for sending it in have
a good night and now after four hours of
work I'm gonna wipe it all off and move
on to the next block all right you guys
we are back with a clean base on and
we're ready for look number three which
is going to be a Von Teese that fun
colored cheetah print look I think this
one's actually going to be it relatively
easy so let's just go ahead and dive
right in I'm first gonna use just a
purple base I happen to have this dose
of color is that matte liquid lipstick
lying around and out on the basic color
I want to talk a little bit about Imani
because literally she's one of the
nicest people in the entire world I love
her I mean obviously if you're like a
fan or tik-tok you know who a Bonnie is
she is huge on the app she is so much
fun and despondent that I see people
that I've literally never met but the
reason she actually blew up on Tech Talk
was because of these are really really
cool like crazy a clown but he owes it
and she blew up because she's actually a
really really talented makeup artists as
well he also signed out while I'm on the
topic if you guys want to see a collab
between me and Emani it's actually
during like Halloween time but something
with crazy clowns please let me know
because I feel like that would be so
much fun and it was so crazy because the
first thing that I ever actually met her
I asked her if I could send her some
merch and she told me that she already
literally had like all the collection
and when I came home to brag about how
excited I was to meet everybody and how
amazing they all were my assistant was
like James we've actually posted her on
the sistas apparel account like years
ago before she blew up which was
crazy I didn't even know that so Avani
is a true sister now that we have that
all on I'm just gonna grab the shade
hello single flame palette and you
sisters have that shadow in place or
though what now that we have that liquid
lipstick all in place on my eyelid I'm
gonna grab the show you to single from I
am how I thought I'm gonna use that to
set it in place
once that set in place I'm just gonna
use a little bit of my foundation just
to clean up that line and make it super
sharp so now that the base is all on I'm
basically just kind of start adding
these like cheetah I said is this this
cheetah print right big cat big Hobbit
print but I'm gonna use a block liquid
liner this is the only one that I could
find laying around kind of little just
gonna draw on like random little shapes
this one could be a little bit like
wonky a little bit big there you go sure
sure
and now just a tiny liner brush I'm just
gonna grab me a little bit of green
liquid up SEC and I'm going to just add
on like that outside well I don't even
know how do you describe cheetah print
just like the outside blocks out of
usenet local is like I'm actually gonna
grab the anasazi at Nora bina liquid
liner because the formula of using bomb
oh yeah that's what we need I think I'm
just gonna go in with a little bit more
block and just clean up some of the
areas that like got a little bit of
messy but I think this is okay actually
also just for fun that all popped really
accentuate the green features we have
all round here I'm just gonna take a
little bit of that access electric liner
and put it in my waterline which mind
you it's not eye safe so just don't
follow along
beauty is pain is what they do say all
right you guys this is actually turning
out to be a pretty easy maybe I
should've done through this one first
when I was filming earlier on how could
I cover a few minutes and do it the one
off camera and I'll be right back with
the finished look I'll race you guys and
this is a body's 90s rugrats cheetah
print makeup look all completes to be
completely honest aiya literally hate
animal print and this color combination
is saying that I would normally it'd
never go for her but I am so so so glad
that Avani sent this in because I think
this look turned out so cute do you like
it I really like 90s and Rugrats cheetah
print inspired your boyfriend is a
cancer gonna post right now okay love
you - thank you so much - a bunny for
sending this look and now it is time to
wipe this off and start over one final
time okay we are back the base is still
on somehow okay a taking my makeup on
and off four times today not an but
David's look is actually really cute we
put together this like very emoji
inspired a starry night type of makeup
look so I'm gonna do my absolute best to
recreate it and I think the first step
is going to be creating a regular block
a smoky eye what's gonna grab a cream
eyeliner this one happens to be from
Sigma I'm gonna use this as like a base
instead of using like a concealer for
the eyeshadow that will stick on top and
now I'm just using a small fluffy brush
and a little bit of spooky a front of
the palette I'm going to start by a
buffing out those edges now that the
block is along I'm gonna go ahead and
draw these stars as Wow okay so we're
just gonna draw star first now we're
gonna need to draw with a nice starry
trail that really goes around the
eyeball okay so now I'm gonna use a
little bit of eye shadow to add a
dimension into the stars just like on
the actual emoji having a tiny little
detail brush like this one this is the
morphe e39 I'm just gonna dip into being
and try to add some dimension oh my god
there's supposed to be other little
stars
[Music]
okay okay my creativity got a motivation
gone energy at gone I'm going to cut and
do something to the other eye off-camera
I've literally never been more excited
to be done with a huge video in my
entire career oh my gosh you guys
finally that is this starry night by
david dobrik call completes although I
did get lazy and didn't exactly do the
entire eye off-camera I at this point
after eight hours after I'm just gonna
do my outro while I'm taking a come on
after eight hours like I'm I'm had
enough but this has got a lot more
personal that I wanted it to be but you
know what
I guess that's YouTube welcome to my
channel I really really hope that you
guys enjoy this crazy video of me are
recreating it my friends that makeup
looks at they drew for me I had so much
fun doing this although this was a very
very long and excruciating a film day if
you guys didn't tour them but please
don't forget to give this video a big
thumbs up down below and also Lumia
comment let me know whose look was you
are a favorite if you guys don't follow
me on my makeup journey all my social
media links will be right around the
screen right here and my phone number if
you want to text me for updates on it
and do photos videos perks and exclusive
updates and more my number is three one
oh nine oh five eight seven four six
this video sister shadow goes to sister
Pablo thank you so much loves always
falling and supporting I love you so so
so much and if you'd like to be the next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
always reach buidlings legal I'm on
Twitter and also turn to my you to a
post notifications well I'm pretty sure
that's all I have for this video today I
can't think of anything else that I want
to say thank you so much for watching I
love you and I will see you guys in the
next one bye
why can't we ever do that at the same
time
[Music]