hi sisters James Charles Sturt and
welcome back to my youtube channel first
today's YouTube video I am absolutely
terrified because we are doing a
reaction video what you don't do very
often but it's what we're reacting to
and that I'm scared about and that is my
drunk makeup video by the time this
video right here that you're watching is
live you guys have already seen that
video if you have not definitely click
right up here I hope that you guys loved
it hope you enjoyed it I hope you got a
good lob but today's the day that I'm
filming this I have not only not seen it
yet but I also literally remember
nothing from the night that we filmed it
because I completely blocked to sit down
watch it for the first time and react to
myself getting drunk also for the first
time my friends that unfortunately had
to be with me during the night a film
that you're all sitting in the room
ready to react to much as well but we
also have a very special guest to
today's video they're supposed to come
in what am I looking at the camera to
cover the camera okay my sister Christie
B is currently in town and are you
excited to react to this video today
yeah I am really worried because I've
never seen you know you were dying to
Barnaby to get drunk for a very long
time not drunk yeah no I just wanted to
to you drinks and yes you're very
intense and everybody knows so being in
here to drink you would just relax a
little bit and see if you relaxed no
your birthday
[Music]
just to clarify as well okay so I filled
the intro to this video completely sober
and then we went downstairs took a shot
or fine and then came back up to start
filming the video because I wanted to be
a little bit tipsy what we first started
but it didn't kick in quite a while know
that look that was looser
that's the teaser for what's wrong hi
sisters James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel if you can
describe me for a while on my social
media platforms you've heard me talk
openly about the fact that I do not
drink alcohol it's just not really my
thing I never went to parties in high
school and I've just never really
thought they need to but that being said
today that is how I never that's not all
I never went to a party I know all the
time did you ever think that I was going
out with friends and was lying to you
about where I was no I always knew that
you were I think this would be a good
time to tell you if I never did go out
but I actually do that I know I believe
you have my brand-new bottle of Don
Julio 1942 and
just sleep like Drew was also blocked
outputs are on the floor - yeah he was
on the floor directly left everyone went
to bed before we even finished filming
this like watching this box I remember
parts here and there a video nothing I
think this is okay I really thought I
was yelling a lot okay this looks
disgusting
breakfast lunch and dinner
oh can you suck Oh head why would you do
that I don't think yeah looks good right
I'm gonna make a furnace look
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
three two one this is okay nice this is
my finished trunk makeup tutorial we're
actually done with the video
and you call me back upstairs and yelled
at me so that I could film you just
doing the Debbie wear anything with
maestro behind scene size-up is there
Charles to make sure yeah I know bleep
up my telephone but Louis took my phone
so I don't send many boys and he's to
protect messages my phone our video you
were you were funny you weren't doing
text you were having fun you always so
high strong and so intense so you think
I should get drunk more often no no no
honestly that was not as bad as I
thought it was going to be but
regardless okay I do not plan on
drinking it anytime soon
to me and the moment I guess was clearly
a great time but the next morning I woke
up over the day I started to feel a
little bit nauseous and I didn't feel
the best okay but I definitely do not
have like a full hangover but regardless
okay it was not worth it I don't
remember my 21st birthday and buckle in
suck thank y'all for a great great time
and for taking care of me because that
kind of gotten real bad real fast and
thank all of y'all I love you sisters
for watching today's video and the drunk
video if you guys enjoy it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up and
leave me a comment let me know what was
your favorite moment in the video and if
you are above the age of 21
what is your drink of choice that could
be a fun question of the day I got if
you've not ready we she's like my big
red subscribe button and come join it
this sisterhood and we're 19 million a
sister song and I'd love to have you in
the family and also put that back on so
you can open every time I upload a brand
new video
Brian don't put that in there know if
you like slow and beyond that make up
dirty you can call me at scripts letter
to Facebook all the same Charles
myself from over ninety thousand miles
and my actual personal phone number
right here I like the one for Maya but
text updates on new videos photos mercs
and exclusive information it is three
one oh nine two five eight seven at four
six if you want to follow her and see
very embarrassing photos from
in childhood and the occasional update
its Christie b19 yeah this video is such
a shot that goes to sister Ruby thank
you so much love for always falling in
supporting we love you so so so much and
a few at home watch would like to be the
next videos sisters don't forget always
reach me putting links and also to my
youtube post edification all right you
guys thank you so much this video today
we love you
[Music]
[Applause]