hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so it
is officially October I am so excited
for the fall and for all the cute little
pumpkin spice lattes and sweaters but
most importantly I don't care what day
of the month it is this month is
Halloween the entire bar I definitely
plan on doing a ton of different
Halloween looks for you guys so
definitely make comment down below and
tell me what you want to see me do for
this Halloween but for today's look our
very first one I did this half face neon
light up skull inspired makeup look and
I am honestly it's so so hard to be how
it turned out I think it just looked so
so sick it definitely was not the
easiest makeup look I've never done it
took a very long time and a lot of
concentration but I feel like it's not
that hard you just have to be a really
really patient and be willing to take
your time - something that I definitely
struggle with but hey we came with okay
today by the waves today's look is
inspired by the wigs and makeup manager
on Instagram she does so many beautiful
and stunning skeleton makeup books do
you guys have to check her out all right
all that being said happy Halloween
everybody grab your Piketty drink at
ease and let's get started
[Music]
alright guys so I already went ahead and
I primed my face off-camera as always
using my favorite moisturizer but before
we actually go in with the makeup I want
to pry my lips and for today's video I
partnered with Yoos to show you guys
their brand new crystal lip balm
basically this lip balm acts as like a
moisturizing primer underneath the
makeup and it just wax for you so it
feels super super lately on the lips
which is great because we're gonna be
putting a lot of makeup on today so we
don't want it to feel very very heavy
and it also can needs a lot of natural
ingredients like shea butter and coconut
oil which makes for a really really long
lasting hydrating feeling which is so so
good like I said everybody putting on a
lot of face paint and
and liner onto my lips today which is
not saying that I normally do and it
tends to get really really really dry so
this is just gonna make sure those lips
last all day long and are super super
comfortable to wear so now that we are
all primed and ready to go like I said
we were gonna be wearing a lot a lot a
lot of makeup today so I'm gonna quickly
go ahead and do my base up camera as
well as my eyebrows to save some time
and then I'll be right back to sur off
the eyes okay so jumping bright and I
have my base already completely on it
this video is obviously gonna be focused
on the eye makeup and the skeleton
portion so I figured might as well just
save some time and for my eyes today I'm
gonna start off using my morphe 35o
palette I use this palette so much in
all my videos you guys have heard me say
this a million times but it is surely my
all-time favorite palette for a color
looks and I'm gonna be using all these
of blue shades in the left-hand row I'm
gonna start off by carving an M 4-3-3
bet and typing into this light blue
shade up in here and use that to start a
transition shade I'm going in with a
very very light hand because a blue eye
shadow does tend to be very hard to
blend out and I do want this to look
good obviously I mean duh so I'm just
gonna blend this very very carefully
making sure that this doesn't get too
high up into like the brow increase
region and just keeping the shadow
mostly concentrated in the crease I am
taking what's left of that shadow on the
brush and just winging it out as well
there's obviously gonna be a lot going
on in the mouth region with all the
skeleton makeup so I definitely make
sure it's balanced on the eye portion
and this is gonna be a lot of dimension
a lot of different colors going on it so
I feel like weighing this out and making
the shadows really really blown out and
wide with a lot of different shades and
dimension is just going to like really
even off this low neck so I'm gonna grab
an AB 5:07 brush and dip into this
darker blue shade in the top left hand
and use that to darken up the crease in
the outer corner
then I'm just gonna grab my own 4-3-3
that I had that light blue shade on and
use this to lightly buff over those
edges make sure everything is super
blended out copy that same M 507 brush
that I used for this blue I'm gonna dip
into this darker blue shade in the
bottom and use this to deepen it up even
more at this point you guys have low
base you may do a million half cut
creases I was reading through this
pretty quickly just because there is
gonna be a lot of work and color going
into the bottom half of the face being
the skull so just follow along the best
you possibly can or watch another two
turtle on a half cup crease I'm
basically just doing a full on blue one
and then guard my M 506 I'm gonna dip
into the slightest bit of black from the
bottom of the palette and I mean slight
you need to be so careful here can't
even tell you how many times I've messed
up an entire look with black shadow so
only grab a little bit and then once
again going with the next darkest blue
shade and using that to blend it oh now
that the shadows are all laid out and
blended and decide now I am so happy
because the blue shadows for me are
usually really really tricky but today
this looks so good and blended so thank
God the makeup cards are in my paper
today but moving on normally to cut my
crease I would use my a tarp shaped a
concealer as all of you guys know but
that has a tan base obviously so instead
I'm gonna use my Kat Von D lock-it
concealer in the shade whiteout today
just because I want this a cut crease to
be like white as opposed to like a tan
color so you can overlay it with a
glitter in a second
and then I'm just going to set that
concealer in place using my sugar pill
single shadow in the shade taco and then
finally for an extra pop I'm gonna grab
my Mac reflux teal and my morphe M two
to four brush and I'm gonna spritz it
using some fix+ and then pack a little
bit of this on to the later purchase a
nice pop of blue for the lower lash then
I'm gonna grab at 5:07 and dip into the
medium blue shade in the top and just
start to buff out the lower lash you
guys always know when it comes to doing
a half cut creases I always like to
bring this shadow in the very inner
corner on the lower lash line forward as
opposed to following my natural eye
shape this is a very drag technique but
I love how it makes my eyes look a lot
more open and wide driving my original
I'm four three three brush I'm gonna use
this to buff out that bottom edge and
then finally I'm gonna grab an M 213 and
dip this in the absolute darkest blue
and then just push this right into the
lashes so that is what I all complete
obviously I'm gonna add a mascara and
lashes towards the end of the look but
everything else is gonna take me a
long-ass time and I don't want to have
to deal with these charcoal up wearing
lashes for the next several hours so I'm
gonna go ahead and do the other eye
off-camera quickly and I'll be right
back to start off the skeleton and then
we'll put on the lashes and stuff later
on now we get to move on to the fun part
of this tutorial and that is the half
base skeleton look next in occur have
any white eyeliner pencil this one is
from a morphe in the shade
coconut and I'm gonna start sketching
out the highlights of a skull
I have a picture pulled up on my phone
right here that I'm looking at a lot of
times when you do skeleton makeup you
usually start with black to do like the
shadows but instead today we're focusing
on the highlight so really make sure
your toning into the light and the
darkness up the photo to really make
sure we achieve this effect correctly
okay so my camera died and I didn't
catch it I mean imagine that we really
surprised at this point but what I did
is I started off with my two top front
teeth and sketched those in and then
just started out from there making my
teeth get smaller and smaller as I get
out to the molars out of the corner and
then I'm just gonna do the same exact
thing on my bottom lip and then taking a
break from the mouth from one second
then just gonna trace my cheekbone
if you make a mistake it's okay don't
worry about it that's why we're starting
off with this white eyeliner basically
this entire top line that I just made
was completely wrong so I'm just going
to grab my Beauty Blender and quickly
try to go over as best as I can
but it's gonna be hidden in a few
seconds anyway because of the shadow and
stuff that were gonna be putting on
there so I'm gonna go ahead and redraw
that now and then finally placing one
really long line to trace up my jawline
and yes I am definitely being a lot more
sharp and chiseled than normal
definitely does not hurt to fool the eye
a little bit then I'm gonna start to
sketch in my nose and then remember
normally I know when we do a skull we
usually focus on the shadows first being
in the Blackshades flat first today we
need to do the whites first just make
sure we get those highlights all in
place before we place the shadows later
on so just kind of think the opposite of
what you would normally sketch so I'm
just kind of sketching a white outline
of where the nose would normally be if
that makes sense now I'm just going to
quickly go ahead and mirror that same
exact white lines on the other side I
just went ahead and I drew out all the
lines and once again don't worry if it's
not perfect you can always fix anything
up with concealer and we're about to
blend the crap out of it anyway so this
is just to get a rough baseline but now
that everything is roughly on I'm gonna
remember three threes that I use for my
eye crease and back into my at 35 beat
palette you guessed it and dip into this
bright blue shade and serve to blend out
all those white lines I'm also gonna
grab a clean m5 13 brush or any big
fluffy brush and just go over those
edges to make sure they're not too
intense then I'm just gonna go ahead and
repeat this for literally every single
white line that I've already drawn okay
so this way we're looking absolutely
ridiculous trust me I know it's gonna
get better in a second don't worry
there's a lot of layering that needs to
really go into this look to make sure it
looks really really realistic what I'm
gonna do is grab a slightly domed hacker
brush into the same Indian blue shade
once again and I pack this on into the
same exact areas tracing over where
those white lines were originally and
this is just gonna help add a lot more
to bend into the white lines once we add
them in next I'm gonna do the same exact
thing on the nose and the teeth as well
but I'm gonna use my m14 and I'm just a
tiny fluffy pencil brush and said just
make sure it's more defined
okay so now that we have all the blue in
place next we're gonna go in with the
black and this is where we have to be
really really careful and really precise
or else is gonna start looking a really
messy and really wonky real fast I'm
gonna start out by Gary Miami 506 brush
which is that same brush we used in
black to deepen up the crease and I'm
gonna dip it right back into the black
with a 35 B I'm gonna start to really
lightly fill in these areas in between
the blue where there is no light what
I'm gonna do next grab ie
37 brush and dip once again into that
black shade and use this to add it to
mention into the teeth region because
using a faulty brush in there would be a
disaster alright and now that the block
is all in place I told you guys this is
gonna be a long one I'm gonna go Miami
five thirteen which is my blending brush
to blend that blue out and I'm gonna dip
this into the teal and I'm gonna get a
lot of it on there and I'm gonna go
right over top of those lines one more
time to blend together the blue and the
black this step is basically to
eliminate any tan skin left showing in
this region okay so now that we have the
black and blue in place finally our last
step is going to be to add the
highlights which makes this like
actually neon and today I'm gonna be
using the white mixed liquid liner I'm
gonna be super careful here because this
took a lot of time but all I'm gonna do
is just trace a thin white line right
over the center most bluest point of all
the blue lines and that's going to
create that neon sign effect
just for an action little touch because
at this point why not I'm gonna grab an
Emma for for one or just any fluffy
blending brush and dip the tiniest bit
into the Mac reflux teal spreads a
little bit of it with some fix+
and then just tap this pigment right
over top of those highlighted areas
finally to finish off the hook I'm gonna
pop on the new bounce of lashes in the
style dragon Lee and you can use code
James for 20% off all their lashes all
right sisters and that is this hot faced
neon skeleton makeup all complete I
absolutely love how this turned out it
has been so long since I've done
Halloween makeup I mean yeah it's been a
year just like everyone else but you get
what I mean
I'm so excited to be finally back in the
game I love October and Halloween season
so so so much and I cannot wait to do
more tutorials for you guys definitely
make a comment down below tell me what
you want to see me do at this Halloween
season and I'd be happy to start
planning for some tutorials if you guys
did enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below if you have not already we are so
close to 2 million subscribers click
that little bell icon as well to be
notified every time I upload a new video
if you like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter and they are both just James
Charles and my snapchat from Marblehead
and since I stuff is James Charles that
extra s after Charles if you are a new
sister or you are already in the
sisterhood I love you so much don't
forget to check out sisters - apparel
comm for all your sisters apparel gear
and all the cutest hoodies in the entire
world
this week's sister shout-out goes to
Amber thank you so much girl for always
falling in supporting you and I love you
so much and if you would like to be at
next week's shadow make sure to always
reach eat my video links and they go
live on Twitter all right sisters I've
been filming for a total of 6 hours now
I need to wipe this off and go to bed I
hope you guys enjoyed this video I love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one bye
[Music]