hi guys this is James Charles welcome
back to my youtube channel today I'm
here with a very special guest
hi I'm Rachel Rachel our CEO Beauty
legend of YouTube if you don't know her
you should check her channel you
probably already have but we're here
today and we're gonna be doing the no
mirror makeup challenge we're gonna go
from this to this
but back to this if you want to see her
created those looks that we just showed
yeah let's keep on watching okay I'm
gonna start off for crying red nose like
I always do well we were like really
talking about this what are you I'm not
going to he's gonna talk about oh wow
okay sister I don't pry my nose put it
in my face
well when your oily like me you have to
do those things
okay thanks I can already feel like this
is watching chewing oh so we'd like to
give each other heads and suffered no no
okay thank you sister Laura for the
Empire I'm gonna use my benefit
Porefessional primer Wow
she's coming quick I'm gonna need you
not to rush please I went to say over at
Rachel's house a few weeks ago and I met
her mom for a brief like five minutes
and now it's like Oh James oh is that
the boy who did your makeup that's all I
am to her as just a blending brush okay
I'm gonna go do my makeup for everstik
foundation oh wow this feels now that
I'm not looking at this this feels
disgusting like now that I'm not
watching this like go on look I feel
very rose oh we all might happy to come
up Juanita here time I have won wow
that's really real of you thank you I
know
oh no so funny sorry homie and Rachel
Matt because pretty good friends oh I
love me too oh no but we met at a Knicks
party I saw Rachel walking by she saw me
I was like oh my god your makeup looks
really good what foundation you wearing
and then right from there that was it so
I try out that same tape yeah
was this the same car that you used I
got so gonna be using the sharp hey
Seeley thank ya
James Chavez cover would sing gay
English speaker I feel like what I'm
doing this like I can never stop
blending like I feel like I could take
care of it yeah counting this
Beautyblender in the same place for like
45 minutes and I would still look in
your after but no [ __ ] what are you
doing
what that's not even cheating I didn't
say it was cheating silence Lavazza
friction okay I'm now gonna take my
morphe r7 brush to my Kat Von D shade on
a palette and I'm going to bronze my
facial rims you're going so hard losing
okay now I'm gonna contour my nose good
lord
I don't do it should I even try to
conjure yeah you just use that brush
with a highlighter oh please you've
gotta live in place yes and this is the
morphe friend 501 girl sister use code
James yeah yeah that's a good man right
there I think you know your friend
watches your videos
is the point I'm I'm gonna use my morphe
e29 it's rubbed off in my Anasazi on
dipbrow and the shade number evany and
shaved number Mme
I'm gonna use the this benefit eyebrow
pencil so didn't mean I don't suddenly
the eyebrows can say it literally they
can say unfilled
Oh everybody's gonna be really bad luck
over laughing at me
this is really bad I'm not gonna use
some concealer and a pencil brush to try
to clean whatever is going on oh I think
that consider just went too high and now
now we're gonna I want you to prime my
eyelids I think I'm gonna go for a
purple look okay I don't know I'm gonna
start off with some red as a transition
shade judging this color and I'm gonna
use that as my crease color all think oh
that was a good one
James Charles guys making everyone feel
untalented consumers I give up
I'm putting hashtag and my crease you
look good once I line it Oh No thank you
I'm gonna take my m4 for one and I'm
gonna take the shade at transition and
hashtag mixed together and then blend
that in the crease this is with my
already just so that what the [ __ ]
apparently not people to see also makes
me forget Oh
alright this once or twice
that's some way to get glitter ah I'm
not gonna grab the well the 35b
and my m56 - I'm gonna dip into the dark
purple and the light purple ashley
mixing them together oh my god that's
what I could've done when I was like I
need to come it in between these two you
didn't think about that
imagine I'll pour it into the lid oh oh
wow okay did you get it today no part of
it I don't think I can depend wondering
what every single color looks like
that's how long it takes me James put on
eye shadow
oh wow listen more sister please anyway
I went to [ __ ] burning right now my
eyes are burning doesn't stop after it
dries taking a little bit of black
eyeshadow I'm blending it by the lines
so that my line doesn't look as stupid
I'm gonna take the Kat Von D tattoo
liner in trooper and I'm gonna try to
sketch on the wing no oh and I already
made a dot it's too late
I don't know where to go with that
okay I'm gonna curl my eyelashes now
before I do mascara me too
oh god this is actually what's scary Oh
her smile in common it just in case
anybody was wondering oh my god I'm
gonna use the Mac soft and gentle
highlighter and my morphe m5a1 rush
which Rachel stole and I know cannot
find no puss on it yeah I'm going to
finish off by setting my face go steal
Rachel's
it says in the bottle to spray one to
two times
hold a wine tell okay are you ready to
see ourselves okay oh I'm not that
actually oh this oh your eyeshadow
honestly does not look bad okay so like
my base I'm honestly like pretty happy
with like my foundation concealer
contour highlighter it looks pretty bomb
what isn't so great this I I now
understand why six people entered the
room it started creeping up this
definitely needs some help
alright guys and that is the completed
video we are so beyond done I just gave
instagramers everywhere a second hand
embarrassed that I want this off so that
is that on that to say the least
I really really hope you guys enjoy this
video and if you did don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not already I post
videos every single week and they are a
pretty good time if I do say so myself
can you relax if you like to follow me
on my makeup you can follow my Twitter
Instagram they're both James Charles and
you can follow my snapchat for more
personal behind the scenes they're just
touching baby stuff which is James
Charles with an extra ass after Charles
and you guys want to follow me I'm a
beauty 101 on everything a living legend
don't go check her out
alright guys thank you so much for
watching we both love you we'll see you
next time okay we love you so much
goodbye