hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 channel
TGIF you guys I hope everyone had an
absolute incredible week and that
everyone is smiling and ready for the
weekend ahead of us I spent my entire
week on set working on several really
really exciting projects and have been
up since the crack of dawn all the way
until the wee hours of the morning and
let me tell you I am beyond exhausted
but it is all for a good cause and I'm
so excited for you guys to see what
we've been working on that being said
for this week's video I wanted you to
sign just a little bit more chill so I
can kind of relax and enjoy it the
weekend after a long week of work but
still make it super super fun I'd buy
the title of this video you guys already
know that it is going to be a
never-before-seen footage and bloopers
video oh my gosh you guys we have
literally been saving the absolute best
moments that were not able to make it to
camera over the past I think like 7 to 8
months since the last video some of the
clips in this video are beyond crazy
this will definitely be demonetized but
at least you guys will have a very good
laugh so grab your pen get a drink at
ease and grab your socks they get ready
to laugh until you cry at butt butt
Subaru Quinn's League before we show
Clips today's video I have a very very
special announcement that I want to tell
you guys about and that is that I'm
gonna be flying one of your sisters out
to LA for a full glam makeover I am so
excited to announce that I've teamed up
with omae's to give one of you sisters
the glam day of your dreams that means
flights to LA for you and a friend hotel
accommodations and also a $1,000 makeup
shopping spree and after a full time
makeover by me and whatever look you
want you can enter twin for free
or you can also donate to enter and the
best part about this entire thing is
that it's all for charity and every
single donation directly supports two
incredible incredible causes listen and
also the National Center for transgender
equality now if you guys are not
familiar with them at glisten is an
incredible organization that basically
works to ensure that all members of
school communities are respected and
valued regardless of their gender
identities or expressions and also the
NCTE is an incredible organization that
basically works on at changing policies
and society to help promote
understanding and acceptance of
transgender people the work that these
two organizations do for members of the
lgbtq+ community is extremely extremely
important and obviously I am very very
passionate about these issues and I know
that a lot of you guys watching my
videos are very very passionate about
them too and I'm so excited to help out
and are really really fun
that being said if you in a friend want
to come to LA and have a fun sister
shopping spree with me head on over to
omae's comm slash James right now for
all the information on how you can enter
to win remember that by donating your
supporting to amazing causes and
hopefully I will see you guys very very
soon finally time for some bloopers and
never-before-seen footage Oh God
[Music]
hi sisters
James Charlie just Buckley hands I don't
even I love a good sparkly head welcome
back to this [ __ ] off [ __ ] hey Horace
hi sisters I'm all caffeined up now hi
sisters James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel hi sisters
James Charles here and welcome back to
toy-u channel
hi sisters [ __ ] took [ __ ] here and eat
this Bousema
[Applause]
welcome to my youtube channel now if you
guys remember in my last now if you guys
remember in the last video that was
uploaded what was there k now if you
guys were in the last oh my god honestly
Beverly Hills me I am so sorry I miss
you the most
I promise I'll be dark for you oh so
okay so for today's video
I thought B stands for beefy which
basically just means like big or thick
you couldn't describe do you not you
really don't know what I'm talking over
now
oh my god I thought it'd be really
really fun to kind of bring in the new
year I thought it'd be a really fun way
to introduce everybody so for I know the
best I haven't wanted to you know do any
collabs I'm so famous and so talented
Picasso is dad yes way too soon you
don't hand Milan Omo whoa whoa no we
shouldn't you know papi 2019 this year's
about to be a legend I am so glad we
lost to have such an amazing people
[Laughter]
liner but this time to on the eyes and
that is lip like rude at this at this
point at this point at this point
finding my favorite at this point
finding my parrot fun at this point
finding my perfect foundation Shane has
kind of been atones at this point
been a challenge that I gave up on a
very brave at this point finding my
perfect foundation chain has been a
challenge that I gave up on a very very
long time ago because I simply gone I
just drank coffee though I'm sorry for
my coffee but next I have the milk
makeup a blur liquid a foundation and
this one is in the shade one nope
hello Thomas James over Arden Kiki
Louis [ __ ] you if you for that of the
[ __ ] movers their wedding this job
sister shadow is this busty mom huh
Debbie get out of the close-up a whole
night off that looks old Lucy on Gabriel
wait James Dean's it's just like a chic
minimal cakes like just as is pull it
back more yeah if you don't get out of
the clothes on it won't even poke ass
there you go okay it's [ __ ] folks in
value blue dduba dduba dduba die I could
see you definitely being like an
elementary school teacher okay I'm so
very very long lower eyelashes I was a
very very long lower lash eyelash I have
some very very long lower lower
eyelashes and taking it and listening
and taking in the constructive criticism
oh my god biking professional I got too
close I need to get aside you're kidding
us literally the best a shadow in the
world yeah Louis did not put that in oh
my god I got a ma I Oh
I clicked on the screen shop a girl who
had made her I clicked on a screen shot
of a girl who had made her brother I
clicked on a screen shot of a girl who
had made her a little I flicked on the
screen shot up a girl who had made her
little brother jock and I I clicked on a
screen shot of a girl talking about how
she had made her new hey alright you
guys we are I'll say everybody's
individual channels will be linked down
below and then used to set again if you
guys want to see us all together like
check out my channel on Mondays
Wednesdays and Fridays oh yeah
I don't want to say that make me sound
weird doesn't need the push but thanks
all white sauce is except for alfredo
are disgusting disgusting
Lucchese is range gross what so gross
hey Olli
oh no anyways good I know it's not my
I'm so sorry what about a crystal dildo
that's gross where I'm from they had a
train that used to like run through our
town and there was also a river going
through it and we used to climb up on
the train tracks where the bridge was
that went over the river and climb under
the train tracks so the train tracks are
like here and your face is like here and
then let the train go oh sorry
and I picked out this look by my really
good friend it brought and I picked out
this look by my really good friend by a
brick hell it is like this bleep but for
this video I do want to challenge myself
so I picked out this look by my really
good friend friend I'm having to leave
[Music]
and cut [ __ ] see Anna think of leather
brown do anything for that bra bra
rise and shine but I'm going home so the
first one of the alphabet is a a nurse
the first total the Alpha is a in R and
in oh my god so the first letter of the
alphabet is a and in our sister
dictionary a stands for acrylics and it
goes it goes how soggy the house baki
the house is my water it's lightly
dusted P it stands for pressed [ __ ]
so as much as I would absolutely love so
as much as I would absolutely love to
race these videos videos so as much as I
would absolutely love [ __ ] QRS TUV
wxy NZ how's up with this law likewise
no so this is definitely gonna be a
winner for the part that the Wow
obviously you guys know I don't really
do reviews that often on this YouTube
channel I'm definitely a person that
sticks with the same maker products in
every single video I mean if it ain't
broke don't fix it broke don't fix that
that was not there anything to use there
what if I were to eat my entire routine
ain't broke so I'm not gonna fix that
unfortunately I couldn't cope
I could why can I not enunciate
unfortunately I could not go with
anything from the letter box okay set in
place okay
I said it too late
all right sirs you don't say that okay
you could we done
okay yeah thumbnail dinner oh yeah there
we go
I'm [ __ ] done oh my god God blast oh
wow
God thank you Lord Jesus that having
[ __ ] a mob okay
I'm going to my ow oh okay
but finally
[Laughter]