[Music]
a beer
hey guys it's James Charles welcome back
to my channel so I know it has been a
hot minute since I bought cells in the
video if you've been follow me on my
other social media platforms but you're
totally shot if you don't you know that
I've had some amazing things going on
recently that have totally taken up all
my time but in a very very good way if
you missed it I am officially the first
male covergirl and there will be a video
on that with all your questions and all
the details and behind the scenes
footage coming soon so make sure you
definitely stay tuned now that
everything is kind of calmed down at
least a little bit and I am a back home
I finally have some time to sit down and
film for you guys and get back into the
Halloween groove today I decided to film
this super drag super glam a Playboy
bunny inspired look I absolutely love
how this turned out I posted it on my
instigator day and everybody was
commenting asked me to film it so of
course I had to sit down and teach you
guys how to do this look full credit and
inspiration for this look goes to jubu
or instagram will be right here she is
so talented and she did this first so
this is inspired by her also this video
is a collaboration with one of my best
friends in the entire world
Tina helada or tutorials by Tina she's a
15 year old makeup artist and she is
beyond talented so we decided to team up
and do two different styles so Tina
decided to do a more toned town glam and
definitely easier version of this look
if you want to see how she created hers
make sure you click right here tell her
Jane sent you she is amazing as for my
look cover we always got to be extra 8
up on this channel you guys know that I
never do anything toned down so this is
the look I came up with this dry glam
inspired a Playboy bunny and if you want
to see how I created it make sure you
keep on watching
hi guys to begin this tutorial today I'm
gonna start off by covering my brows now
this technique is definitely not the
easiest thing in the world so if you
Argan do this for Halloween please make
sure you practice beforehand it can be
very very tricky I'm just using a
regular glue stick and a brushing all
the glue into my brow hairs and then
combing every hair up with a spoolie on
the end of a brow brush to really make
sure they are flat to my face and every
hair is separated and going upwards then
I'm just going to take a damp towel and
kind of go over the edges of the glue to
blend them into my skin sometimes it can
be a pretty textured and lumpy so like I
said we really want to make sure these
are flat to create a new layer of skin
then I'm just going to do the same thing
on the
bro and once that is coated in dry I'm
just gonna continue to lay our glue and
then finding it letting it dry it
between three or four times depending on
how thick your actual brows are until
you get the desired coverage to where
you feel they are good then I'm going to
set my brow hairs in place using Kody
airspun this is my favorite setting
powder and just a regular powder puff to
really press that powder in there once
again to make sure they are very very
flat and not textured then I'm using my
morphe 48 brush to brush away the excess
hairs
now to begin covering the brows I'm
going to use my Mac painterly paint-pot
this Paint Pot is super super pigmented
I'm just brushing it on with the morphe
r32 brush to really pack that color on
there I love this because it really
covers the texture and the color of the
brows which can be very very hard if you
have huge ass caterpillar brows like I
do so I would definitely recommend this
step then I'm gonna prime my face using
a benefit professional you guys know I
love this primer this entire tutorial is
gonna be very very out of order I
apologize this is just kind of the way I
did things and it worked out pretty well
so follow along if you choose or just do
whatever you want and then using that
same Paint Pot actually to start to
paint my nose now this technique was
recommended to me by a follower and you
guys always know that I complain about
foundations something off my nose so
this technique has really saved the lane
of my nose contour and really helps
everything to stay in place all day long
it doesn't wear out then I'm just using
a damp Beauty Blender to kind of blend
over the edges of the nose and the
eyebrow cover I'm then just gonna start
my regular foundation routine as always
is my makeup over Ultra HD foundation
stick I'm just gonna put this all over
my face including my brows and my nose
we really want to make sure there is
even coverage and no discoloration and
then I'm just gonna blend that in very
very carefully using my morphe 439
foundation brush this is one of my
favorite foundation brushes ever it is
so great and you can use code James for
10% off all morphe brushes and products
you guys know I absolutely love them and
stand behind them 100% so you should
definitely check them out if you have
not already and then I'm just going into
my Too Faced Born This Way concealer to
put it in the high points on my face and
then blending that out with the damp
Beauty Blender to really get everything
it's snatched then you look absolutely
horrifying and you get to make this face
in the mirror and at this point you are
ready to set your face once again I'm
using a Kody era spot and a powder puff
just to pack it on I'm starting off in
the kind of baked areas like the
eyebrows and then on
the eyes and then I'm just going in and
just kind of slopping this everywhere to
really make sure I am a full face matte
and definitely not oily or wet anywhere
to begin sketching out the eye of the
bunny I'm using my makeup forever flash
palette the white shade obviously and my
morphe m15 a brush to begin kind of
drawing it in place where I want it I'm
going to draw a line upwards problem at
the corner of my eye and then from the
inner corner of my nose and then kind of
connect it sort of similar to the way we
draw a cut crease just a lot bigger and
more draggy if that makes any sense I'm
really making sure to pack a lot of
product on there because we want this
white to be super opaque obviously we
can go over and clean it up later on in
the future and then I'm gonna take the
anasazi liquid lipstick shades in pure
Hollywood and blush mixing them together
on an angled brush and sketching that
right over the white line we just drew
this is gonna be kind of the I guess
eyebrow of the bunny I don't really know
what it is but it looks cute so we
decided to do it and it was in the
original book by jubu as I said before
so I really really loved what she did
and I wanted to recreate it as
accurately as possible I'm just
following the same exact shape as the
white line that I created below while
making it a lot thicker and then a
tapering it off in the inner corner to
create that classic drag effect I'm not
gonna use my morphe amma 4-3-3 brush and
the anasazi a single shadow and shade
babycakes and kind of said that liquid
lipstick in place I know it will dry but
I really want to make sure this is super
super exactly there and where we needed
to be and the nurse going back over with
my m15 e as I said before from morphe
and the same white shade to really make
sure those lines are opaque and very
very sharp and defined then to begin the
upper fur of the eye on once again using
the same brush same shape same color
from the flash palette and I'm just
going to follow that pink line exactly
but I'm going to start sketching in some
fur this time I'm really making sure to
pack a lot of product on there this
product while they are great can be very
very wet so sometimes I find that it can
kind of drag the foundation along with
it so really make sure you're putting a
lot of product on there so when you drag
out the fur you're not dragging out the
foundation with you and your fur remains
white and super clean to set the fern
place I'm going to be using my Ben Nye
super wet face powder on a flat to find
a Russian just packing this right into
the fur to make sure it is dry and super
opaque and white and then one of my
and while mega liner in white it is a
super precise and thin liner which I
love and I'm just using this to draw in
some more furs and some tiny little
hairs this adds a lot more dimension to
the look which previously was not
possible with the flash palette and then
using this tiny Mac definer brush in my
Kat Von D shade and light palette I'm
using the shade all the way to the left
to add in some shadowing to the cut
crease I'm just placing the shade
lightly underneath the white lines that
we created earlier on the cut crease so
above the top line as well as the lower
line where the liner will be in a second
this just creates some more dimension
and kind of looks like it's like a mask
that is popping off my face so I really
like how it looks for the liner today
I'm gonna be using my Kat Von D trooper
liner this liner is super precise and
thin so I really do love it and I use it
all the time which you guys know this
liner today was giving me a lot of
trouble I ended up redoing it and fixing
it like five or ten times I don't know
why I'm not used to making liner this
big but it is a dried look so you got to
do what you got to do and then I'm going
back in once again with that mega liner
from Wet n Wild and just sketching in
some more hairs over top of that pink
area I am however keeping these hairs a
little bit smaller than the previous
ones because we are gonna be adding some
glitter whoa who doesn't love glitter me
actually I really don't like glitter
because it's dirty and once you get
glitter in your life you literally never
can get glitter out but that's aside
from the point under stating my makeup
forever mist and fix spray and then some
dollar-store glitter on my morphe I'm at
242 brush and just packing this right
onto the pink area this adds a lot of
texture and dimension let's be real it's
pretty so you got included the glitter
for a drag look to finish off this I am
then going back into the white from the
frost palette and filling in my
waterline as well as a lower lash line
and then to shading once again with that
mock brush and the Kat Von D shade and
light palette add some final dimension
and that completes one eye of this bunny
look going to go ahead and do the other
one off Cara then we can go ahead and
finish off the rest of the face for my
lashes today I'm puffing on a violet
boss lashes in the style I to hose you
guys know that I absolutely love these I
always wear these for my bigger look
such as like cut creases and drag books
they're just perfect and mice and wispy
for my lower lashes I'm popping on
janessa my Rx lashes in the style of
thrive zero ones these are really just
gonna help to open my eye and kind of
further that whole drag effect and I'm
just popping those on or right below the
white and the
line I'm then going in and starting to
contour my face is my morphe and 435
brush and my Kat Von D shade and light
palette I'm not going to help you
because we are going to be covering a
lot of the face with some more fur but I
am going to go pretty heavy on my jaw
line even though we are cute Playboy
bunny we still want to be as snatched as
how as always so I am a packing on the
bronzer and really making sure to chisel
out my jaw and then just gonna go in and
quickly bake my contour with my echo
tiara spot and a powder puff like I said
before not focusing too hard because we
are going to be covering a lot of it in
fur next I'm just going with my morphe M
509 brush and a little bit of blush we
are gonna be using a pink highlighter
today from the Anasazi at moonchild
palette so this just really helps blend
everything together and make sure that
glow is super pink and of course I'm
using a pink heart from ABH moonchild
like I said then you start the facial
fur I'm just going into the white color
from the makeup rubber flash palette
same thing as before and that definer
brush and just sketching it where I want
the facial fur oh my god this voiceovers
literally such a mess it is so late at
night and I want to get this video oh
and I feel like I'm barely speaking
English anymore please bear with me once
I have that in place I'm then just going
back in and starting to fill that in and
similar to it defer above the eyebrows
I'm really making sure to put a lot of
that product on there because sometimes
it does move around so we want to make
sure we have white fur and not like
off-white skin color type fur then for
the nose I'm just using the same mixture
from before or those two liquid
lipsticks from ABH they are blush and
pure Hollywood and I'm just sketching
out the nose with a tiny angled definer
brush and I'm just going from Nashville
to Nashville and then filling the tip of
the nose in and then a similar to the
pink up crease I'm setting that with the
Anasazi eye shadow and babycakes for my
lips today I'm going to be using Anasazi
Lucca lipstick in the shade a pure
Hollywood it just to fill in my top lip
I am over drawing a little bit but
making sure not to go overboard and then
I'm going to set that in place in my
Anasazi on babycakes single shadow as
well as setting the bottom lip would
that been my super white powder to make
sure those two colors did not transfer
onto each other to finish off I'm going
into my morphe and to 50.0 liner brush
and some black gel liner to draw a thin
line from the tip of the nose down to
the Cupid's bow and then finishing off
with some dots where the bunny's
whiskers would go alright guys and that
it's a completed drag Playboy bunny
inspired makeup
if you guys decide to try out this
awesome look and you do on yourself
please make sure to tag me on my social
media and follow me as well it's a good
time and I would love to see all your a
beautiful bunny faces as always if you
guys did enjoy this video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and subscribe if you haven't
already it is a good time and there are
lots of really awesome things coming
soon alright guys thank you so much for
watching and I will see you next time
bye he just thought trying to be funny
that's clearly not