hi guys it's James welcome back to my
Channel today I'm going to read makeup
on big apiaries hi guys it's James off
the back to my channel as you can see I
have a very special Gotham e my BFF been
redoing makeup on here today we created
this tutorial with a pop of color in the
inner corner I have the same look on
we're twinsies with our makeup and our
chrome nails we're gonna go ahead and
get started all the products will be
listed below as well as any coupon codes
if you want to say about money and make
sure you stay tuned at the end because
we are gonna be doing a video on vent
channel as well so make sure you go
check that out
ready a SHINee unbend I'm gonna using my
makeup forever Ultra HD foundation stick
this is like my Holy Grail as you guys
know thank God were the same shade
because he doesn't have a good
foundation and this is what I brought so
am I pretty
yeah so what you're doing that means
this is like what you do every day
no I'm so easy I do makeup for events
and events only Oh ever that ain't me I
was gonna say everybody makeup just fair
photo but that's it I see this is where
the abuse happens I don't feel like
caked out yes I feel good yeah that's
gonna change okay I'm also gonna get on
his ears to turn for me my ears yeah you
don't put my patient under ears no
that's mistake number one if your I
don't have that I need to take a picture
look at it the next time I grant ears
will be bright red so for concealer and
highlighting today I'll be using my Too
Faced Born This Way concealer unban and
this is the shade light/medium this is
where we mix in the flour the eggs and
the baking soda a cup of olive oil the
water and
economics these don't feel to imagine
like a completely baseless diversion
I've let it go
so now they're just I don't know how you
have the patience for this there's my
use my Beauty Blender I'm just saying
they give up just enough time for it how
long did you make up here to take you
[Music]
mine takes me two hours and that's what
happens yeah this is the market you 59
brush to be used by coatings for a 10%
off all my products like as a Meyer oh
you know what I've been doing since I
got these nails okay so I'm not gonna go
into contraband stays using my Kat Von D
shade and light palette it's a great set
I'm missing out the clothes because I
use them all I'm going to dip into this
middle shade I'm gonna love being a
beauty guru and i'm gonna use my morphe
m-52 3 brush so I'm just gonna go and
really lightly and make sure to blend
upwards I'm also gonna contour
underneath the jaw line get more defined
you're a real man I'm so excited about
this I'm actually wanting you to do n
make up for a very long time I know I've
been actually watching your videos for
like 17 years now oh my god yeah that's
my baby video I'm also going to contour
my seven head that's my joke - 19 ahem
yeah and we like to minimize that too so
you have a 19 head which is when you
have a forehead the size of an album are
those 19 that was contrary saw oh it's
like we twenty minutes of film break but
you finally like one of my jokes yeah I
do like the same I like every day yeah
we know literary art we did asking for
suggestions and for people they reward
people both me and tree debris second
please something other than red because
that's the only you traders
that I could just steal now I'm going to
use the same powder from before and a
powder puff to bake BAM we're gonna put
on the oven at 350 it seemed we've
already made all the cake that's all
mixed in the ball we'd like to use the
little machine thing your than the mixer
mix our packet like you're going on a
vacation for two weeks I'm just gonna
take my own associate dip brow in dark
brown and kind of fill these in using my
benefit cosmetics brow brush people ask
me all the time what I used to feel
underground so I'm like uh question
though do you hate like when you tweeze
your eyebrows do you hate the pain yeah
I cry every single time cuz I'm this is
really weird
I said this said they told it can be
funny like it was a dirty thing it's not
I like the pain what's the fastest
you've ever done you're like traditional
makeup that you do ten minutes you've
done that ten minute phase yeah I had a
Skype call with a really really big
company for a future project and they're
like yeah you need to have your makeup
ventas we're gonna record it and that
was like 20 minutes beforehand luckily
my mom is not that great so I knew I
could kind of like yes I just what do
you set the brow with benefit give me
brow gel mistake number three yeah once
you do your powder and cream it's really
good to set the brow hairs in place with
some type of gel just sello the hair
same place doing the day where you want
them to be wow we just did one brow and
one eye off-camera to save you guys a
million years of having to watch this
Matt didn't do it the other one now on
camera I did a little bit of ballooning
in a corner to match my yellow in the
inner corner now we're twins for the
blue in the inner part say are we using
my morphe 35o palette this palette is
phenomenal for all color looks it's my
go-to and we're gonna use thing these
two sheets right here I'm gonna use my
morphe m5 19 brush and just pack on a
little bit of that blue in the inner
corner and then blend it out and see
where we go from there to like to have
eyelids I'm never taking my morphe I'm
431 pencil brush it's super tiny
I'm gonna use my Anasazi at moonchild
glow ket in blue eyes
[Music]
yo listen up here's the story a battle
date of god that new world a shade was
good unless as good as the shading of
this contour i'm nominees like hot Von D
tattoo liner in trooper to do the other
wing we're gonna pray that we can make
these even oh my god they mat Wow I
think we just like did open-heart
surgery and it worked that's how happy
I'm like reading it right now like am I
ready suffered lashes today I will be
using my Eschete eyelashes in the siwash
Napolitan to how am I suppose it got let
me be a real be new Hoover for five
seconds okay so I just put some wheel on
this box I'm gonna do then I actually
think could not even put on lashes until
very recently if he's going on like
Instagram feed
the first like maybe 20 looks that I
posted all had the last edited on the
bat is hey something with the brush tool
like because I cannot figure out how to
put the one I glued my eye shop for
sometimes I come in hey you kidding no
now Ben is lining his upper waterline or
thought associate darkside liner this
just helps make like the liner and
lashes they blend all together and look
nice we did this off-camera and I tried
to do it and it was a disaster to
steadily so that's it that's doing it
it's a glass it does not say the most
about another one with the eyes we're
gonna go ahead and wipe off the bake and
continue on reverses the face and finish
off a couple have swirls done so much
like watch it risin cosmetologist messes
passionate I will rise my ass
gloomy it recorded your last bag like
from today now we're going to go ahead
and highlight the best part my favorite
part and we're going to use Anasazi SSL
Hollywood illuminator and my morphe m5a1
brush oh my god it looks so good oh oh
my drag maybe I don't know my drag name
would be this understood get it or miss
yeah the drug so just actually got it
like so for love so yeah I'm gonna be
going in with you a lip gloss and papaya
I think that's how you pronounce it no
way yeah and there we go we're all set
thank God it's over
Wow thanks so much for watching if you
do this video please make sure to give
it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you haven't already I'll be
posting videos every once in a while
whenever I'm not lazy enough we're also
we're doing makeup roulette over on
Ben's Channel yeah that's gonna be fun
is there gonna ruin all the makeup week
Justin and also if you're one of many
people watching this video subscribe to
James he's awesome follies Instagram and
that's the scared to bed if you have it
because he's also really funny you say
unsubscribe to me no I'm gonna fight
yeah we love you guys thank you so much
for watching and we will see you next
time bye