hi sisters James Turrell Sood welcome
back it's my youtube channel if you're
thinking wow James you look not good I
would be thinking yes it's currently
6:00 in the morning and I just rolled
out of bed and sat down I filmed a video
after going to bed at 4 a.m. last night
filming a video so that's um fun and
fresh today I'm doing something crazy
that I'm actually very very very nervous
for and I am going to tell you about
that throughout the year in the beauty
community we have a few huge major
events called beauty conventions there's
a lot of them that go by different names
but overall they have the same kind of
purpose of connecting smaller
influencers and big brands to allow them
to network together sell products do
demos do classes for influencers to make
appearances and they're usually pretty
fun I remember a few years ago and I had
only 50,000 followers begging and
pleading my parents let me use all of my
saved up money to fly to California to
go to generation Beauty I had followers
but no fans yet no brands had any idea
who I was no influences knew who I was I
remember my makeup looked literally the
absolute worst and as my first time
meeting all the major influencers I
snuck into the crater cocktail party so
I got to meet so many people and take
photos and it was honestly such a cool
experience and it's also the first time
that ever got on PR list because of you
guys know and how fast this sisterhood
is growing I don't really go to beauty
conventions that often anymore for a lot
of reasons but spoiler alert I'm going
to win today so I'm going to keep those
reasons to myself because I don't wanna
get yelled at
after this video even though I
personally choose to not go to these
conventions much anymore it has been
several years since I've attended one
the industry is ever-changing and it's
been a very very long time since I've
been able to interact with fans
different Beauty influencer people
different brands and I'm kind of curious
as to how these conventions are running
are they going smoothly after Tana Khan
I feel like anything would be going
smoothly in comparison to that but I
really want to get the inside scoop see
how people are feeling about the
industry right now who they like who
they don't like what brands they like
which brands they don't like so for
today's video I thought I'd doing this a
few weeks ago and I can't believe this
is actually coming to life but I hired
an extremely talented special effects
artists you guys are going to me in a
few short minutes and today I am get
fully professionally transformed into a
completely different human being and I'm
going to be sneaking into beautycon and
interviewing a ton of people about the
makeup industry you guys I'd like to
introduce you to my very very special
guest today this is joining welcome to
our Channel are you excited I am really
excited but also really nervous okay
because this is a huge transformation
John explained like briefly what we're
really doing okay so James contacted me
for this super secret sister makeover
and he basically wanted to be in
disguise to go to beauty con yes and we
decided to do something like an older 30
year-old male very masculine so he's
gonna have a beard he's gonna have
facial features that change with the
prosthetics he's going to have a wig on
we'll do something with the brows will
change wardrobe and he will be a new man
oh my god
how long would you this process is gonna
take usually special effects makeup
artists have like three or four people
working on one person they still can
take up to five hours five to six hours
eight hours the more pieces the longer
it takes to apply how many pieces do you
have today
um I think we have five what do you
think it's gonna be the hardest aspect
of it successfully pulling off this
sister secret surprise I would say your
face but we have that under control yeah
that's girls have it covered yes I think
the next biggest challenge would be just
staying in character and keeping your
mannerisms in check yeah oh yeah I'm
gonna have to say hey guys for all the
clips today which is gonna be a
challenge already I have to really focus
on slowing my words down I also have to
try to go from being like a 98 percent
gay man to a like roughly 32% gay man or
I'm out we already went ahead and took
off all my jewelry earlier on
which was very emotionally hard for me
oh she stuck oh oh hello hey take off my
cardi doesn't look I can never do this
with nails this limb you didn't have to
use a screwdriver for so please don't
ever try to rob me or cut my hand off on
the streets because even if you do you
won't be able to get it so gotcha with
that one I'd literally don't think I've
taken this bracelet off since I bought
it
what the heck righty-tighty lefty-loosey
right yes right Lefty
oh there we go oh Jesus it's early my
hand is shaking what the head unscrew oh
oh no I only took six hours for no
reason do you think it's solid gold
sister's necklace I'll give it away
oh hey Katie girls what have my producer
Kelly taking off my neck last cuz it's
stuck on my body
wow that was easy yeah well it's
official ladies I officially am worth
$0.00 as a human being so know your luck
dear oh okay ladies it's a fish little
guy especially where $0.00 as a human
being so that's really fun and fresh but
I want to offer such as a good
personality good personality
coincidentally as well this week has
also been one of the most stressful of
my entire life so I may or may not have
bitten off all of my acrylic nails which
is actually great for this video because
I think that may be a very intense
giveaway I'll give you go down well I
have a million questions that I want to
ask you tanning I am so sated for this
food today I think you are so talented
and I'm putting my face in your hands
I'm very very nervous I'm not even gonna
lie it not because I don't trust you
because I don't trust myself so we have
five hours ahead of us I think we need
to buckle up get ready to go get ready
to his sister's secret surprise
everybody and should we get started on
this transformation
so a few nights ago Channing came over
to my apartment for the first time ever
and made a life cast a life cast of my
face which was um probably hmm
one of the scariest and worst hours of
my entire life but they're doing that
she was able to actually make a full
plate of a wonderful prosthetics that
are gonna be glued on and we'll roll the
footage right now and show you guys how
that process went because I'm sure
you're just going to love watching these
suckers walk us through your process
like what are we doing I am looking
right at home look like at West
Hollywood trash can it's silicone body
double it's what I'm gonna use to laughs
cast him it'll come free from like all
his hair I don't have to use a release
and it's it's a lot quicker and it lasts
a lot longer so if James wants to make
multiple life casts of himself he can
this is very good cover no guys please
try not to make me laugh once I explain
okay
it kind of feels like cold oh my god
I'm getting claustrophobic just looking
at you these might be the best 30
minutes in my entire life
we can legit talk about him and him not
even talk back to us so after this I
will take it and I'm gonna pour a stone
in it that we use to make live cast and
from there I'll start sculpting the
prosthetic pieces and from that I'll
make a mold of those and I'll pour them
in more silicone and then they'll be
ready to go on oh that's so weird I
don't like that I feel like that's
really squishy and I hope the sister
slice under James's nose okay so now I'm
gonna take plaster bandages and make a
shell for the silicone mold and it just
protects it yes so this is the hardest
part of doing it cuz now it's gonna be
stiff where he can't move at all and I'm
sure he feels it like the difference do
you feel genius warm it's warm you can
feel it he's heard me knock on him like
20 times now but I'm making sure it's
okay hmm
wait now start moving your face around
this is your face really beautiful
no what's the dot by Dudley was like
very uncomfortable especially with like
everybody's saying funny things I want
to laugh so bad but it wasn't like pop
up so I'm gonna start by cleansing the
skin to get rid of any dirt oil all of
those things stops from sticking and
then I'm taking a skin protectant to put
on you it's gonna be like damaging to my
skin at all no if you remove it
correctly then it's totally safe
a lot of fun so yes starting out I'm
using pros aid transfers which are kind
of like the same as tattoos you wet the
back of the paper like literally a
temporary tattoo and then you just blend
the edges off with alcohol for head well
you have a lot of space to work with
so what like are you interested in
special effects like in the first place
and the tricks that they pull love that
for you or less yes yeah I feel like the
lot so if you a definite giveaway most
30 year-old straight men don't exactly
have a viola Juvederm until floods but
you know what we're not judging here wow
I look like I just gave a really good
sister stock since the designs are so
small you may not think that like
they'll do much yeah to the overall look
but once you see it come together you'll
realize like oh it took that little
amount mm-hmm to change a feature uh-huh
this is low-key really relaxing I don't
want to fall asleep research any you're
saying you loved horror movies that's
kind of what you got you know special
effects what are some of your favorite
horror movies that you've seen
I love all the Saw movies I figured you
would like those yeah yeah it's just
like the thing that inspires me is the
fact that you can literally just take
someone a regular human and turn them
into this like creature this monster so
now I'm going to take silicon
encapsulated pieces and apply them to
James I'm gonna start with his chin Oh
God
so these are the pieces that Channing
came over a few days ago to premake oh I
know you're not giving me a double
chattering bruda just kind of like with
the pros aid transfers these blend off
with alcohol as well well probably the
first and only time alcohol will be
featured on the James Charles YouTube
channel I'm a sober sister
my butt chin has gone oh now know about
of jaw clenching her face didn't can fix
this that's my worst nightmare Oh No
oh my god you've got to be kidding me
so Channing how long did you actually go
to cosmetic school for but they take you
through everything so quickly which i
think is a good thing
yeah are you a fast learner I am same
that was my biggest thing in school
would be like I would learn the lesson
once and then they'd keep going through
it and reviewing and I was like oh my
god so now I'm gonna put on cheek pieces
for James what is this gonna do to the
jawline of my cheekbones and it's gonna
round it off it's not gonna be as
structured okay out of all the things
that you've learned how to do what's
been your hardest like transformation or
like special effect yeah I'm so in
school
in the special effects class we have to
like sculpt and make our own monster and
that was probably the hardest thing that
I've ever done
really yeah cuz start to finish it was
like a four week process for weeks holy
crop everything in school is pretty much
like that I kind of rather than be that
way because I think it just prepares you
more how would you compare like this
transformation type to like the stuff
that you're doing in school like the
monster Soph
[Music]
this is more difficult in the fact that
it's like realism right a monster you
can just be like as creative and crazy
as you want this is like all about
making sure you paint it right making
sure your edges are blended really
nicely so this is harder whoa I don't
know why I'm so nervous for this hello
everybody my name is Tom and welcome to
Beauty Cod that's not like a man no
that's still okay I could be a really
gay bad it bros its mark question right
now and let's see do both and pretend
that you're asking a question hey who
would you say your favorite influencers
and Oh No
who would you say right now are your
favorite influencers in the beauty
community and who is your least favorite
that still sounded like me huh
I love this
have a pop in the middle I face I think
this is the finished look right here
guys so right now I'm taking bondo which
is just like a thickened adhesive to
help blend the edges of the prosthetic
into the skin better so is this like the
final set before we get to the painting
yeah okay guys we just had breakfast and
we are back and we're ready to start
painting this is where actually it gets
like real and it starts to like look
like a real person hello hi and I took
my wig off because Mama's hot and she's
working love okay so now I'm gonna start
painting with alcohol paints and the
reason why we use alcohol paints is
because there's still translucent so it
makes it look like skin like you're not
taking a bunch of product on you can
still have translucency with it so how
many layers of paint would you typically
do for this you just build them up until
it gets to like a skin tone type of base
like it's a multiple layered thing like
you can't just go in one or two layers
so now I'm going to take the beer that I
made and apply it with spirit gum I'm so
not gonna be a bad I'm so excited I'm
gonna be a bad
oh my god hey brothers what's my name
Stephen eight years of races and
brushing my teeth about to go down the
drain alright guys I guess this is the
transformation all complete so I'm gonna
go put on my Braille outfit it's gonna
go put on my bro alpha and get changed
and get ready for my first ever
interview super excited major thank you
to sister Channing for participating in
this video today bro I think you
absolutely killed it this transformation
is insane I don't even recognize myself
and I feel like we're gonna kill this
challenge today so please go show
Channing some love on her Instagram it's
makeup by sea Judith and I'll leave all
of her social links down below she's the
sister sweetest and you guys better go
sister support her thanks for having me
on your channel welcome sister sister
out so now my face in here a complete
but we still have a whole lot left to do
so let's go to the closet we just
finished the first part of the
transformation and brother Ian hasn't
seen me yet so I think we need to go
sister surprise him
what what's up bro kind of good great
perfect love that for us brother drew
here so my best friends in the entire
world he's a fashion blogger here on
YouTube call them over today because I
need a bro outfit for this bro interview
so let's head into the closet no homo
what do you think talking like this all
day is gonna be horrible
oh just talk like normal for now you're
fine okay bro I wasn't even coming over
here for this thank you / - watch your
face now you're treating my often bro
what about beats yeah Oh second aim yes
some sisters flex flex are for sure in
here they're in the back the gray ones
oh these mine I think I mean are these
mine perfect
why are they so low wasted button down
over here mm-hmm
maybe yeah yeah then tuck it in Merle
and we're no belt not no that's too
trendy you were this Australia sisters
good I invite a buck in Australia here
for today's interview a beauty : job you
really do the parts of the Caribbean
episode of breaking Amish this one does
look right here
but some bros welcome to beauty con ha
ha ha
Cruz like your favorite influencer right
now I love James Charles it's pretty
funny we're on the way right now to
beautycon and I'm not even gonna lie
like I'm feeling really really nervous
right now I never ever get nervous to
like be in front of people but I think
I'm nervous because like this is not
like me I'd have to like ah I'd have to
like play a part I guess I'm just
confirmed because I really want to see
the sisters and stuff but it can like
these conventions can be a major safety
hazard and I'm just praying that we
don't get caught because if we do it's
literally over and this whole entire
thing is ruined at this point I think
Channing did literally such a phenomenal
job I don't think it's gonna be the face
that's gonna be an issue if anything I
think it'll be the voice or like if I
slip up on my man voice or like my
mannerisms I speak with my hands so much
like so so so much my stomach kind of
feels like right now and I think it's
because I'm getting the feeling of how I
used to get when I first went to these
conventions as if I'm not important
because there's me a million people
there and it's like it's very
overwhelming they're always very very
crowded and very very packed and like
everybody's super stater to see the
people that they love and the brands
they love but normally now when I can
walk into an event or a convention I
have a full team of people around me
that are protecting me that are making
sure I'm led to the right places getting
like you know what I mean like I'm very
coordinated at these type of events and
this were literally walking in of course
hopefully they won't be able to see it's
me but it's still kind of like that same
feeling of like oh I don't really know
what is gonna happen I'm not really sure
how that's gonna go if I'm being
completely honest I'm just a little bit
nervous I just want this to go well we
just got here we have to find the
entrance now I don't really know where
we're going
I'm very scared I'm gonna be honest but
let's get this over with
[Applause]
hi guys my name is Stephen Bock well and
today I'm reporting live from beautycon
at Los Angeles my name is Stephen can I
ask you a few questions for glitter glam
magazine
I'm feeling it not good I'm literally
freaking out and I don't know why I've
never been like that's all having a
video before I don't know why I'm so
scared
cut the cameras I think we need to go
home today kind of reminded me exactly
why I stopped going to those