hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back today the very very special
guest Lorraine
so we had a meeting last day of my team
and came up with a bunch of video ideas
right and my team really wanted me to do
a prank calls video hang I called videos
I don't like prank videos I don't like
putting call videos I was literally the
kid growing up that like would actually
start freaking out if like one of the
students got on the cup fight with the
teacher or started talking back or like
would be like I'm noxious and loud
you're gonna be what okay like I wasn't
ever gonna tell him this but so every
when you attacked fans on Twitter
because people kept calling you oh my
god I don't need to do I had it a lot of
people do I know my number got leaves
for weeks anyway I have been fighting
Luis and Trevor I don't really I don't -
I don't want to film this I cannot do it
I cannot do it and then I thought okay
well if I'm going to be forced into
doing this video against my will I might
as well invite somebody over that I know
actually it can be funny and it wouldn't
have a problem so basically what we're
gonna do is call makeup store so Ulta
Sephora morphe and we're gonna ask them
about me this is so stupid I don't want
to feel I guess we're supposed to ask
about myself my palette will not to
burst your bubble but you have a very
distinct voice that's okay so that's
what I'm scared of - honking man boys
hey you got one like hey yo hey yo
what's good I just wanted to see if you
had any James Charles pallets it's all
my girls that's Noah maybe like hey it's
Brendan gonna freak oh okay well why
don't we just get started you can make
the first call okay whoa period I had to
do it Oh
[Music]
so you're gonna [ __ ] her this is your
channel because I'm horrified just r67
is that what it is to block the number
right star 67 wait what stores hello hey
so my girlfriend has been talking about
some Jaime Charlie James Charles I
believe it is and she wants his palette
you guys have it in stock question so is
there any other palette you prefer over
the James Charles palette so you like
James Charles can I ask you a question
if I said I was next to James Charles
right now would you go crazy or soy just
kidding on the mix of James Charles I
just go say I'm literally shaking I
don't know I know I don't know why I
hate this so hard
he says eyes oh she's focus focus are
[Laughter]
you actually you actually shaking I
don't know I don't know what I just
don't like doing how you have 20 million
subscribers and you shaking over there
what if she was like no he's the most
disgusting youtuber but she didn't
though
well what if she did and then I would be
like listen sure so he call her back
then yeah
hello is this the same associate that
was speaking to about the James Charles
Pelle one second hi sister hello okay
next we should try a more feast or
what's the voice amusing hi hey girl hey
girl hey girl I'm just wondering if you
guys have any the James Charles pallets
and stop oh you have both okay that's
really yeah my daughter's just been
asking a lot about it and I really
wanted to grab one for her birthday
coming up is the pallet good oh that
sounds like literally perfect for her
you know as a mother I'm always just
trying to look out for my daughter and
like make sure that you know she's
watching good things online like do you
know a lot about James Charles sure okay
good to know I know I don't think so
that's okay you too oh my god I'm so
sorry
so nervous yes he's a good oh my god we
should call him or feed that I've been
to for a meet and greet
[Music]
[Laughter]
James you shoulda said hi no I don't
like doing that
that's too scary okay now that I'm not
about to have a phone we should do one
where we like double-team but we should
do our we like have a storyline together
should you be my BAE you know what's
good
hey yo I'm just calling to see if y'all
got the James Charles pilot in stock I
don't really know my girls been talking
about it for the past few weeks now and
I've been wanting to get it for her for
anniversary hello whoo why are you
talking to my boyfriend
I was right
okay so you know as the mother I'm just
trying to make sure my daughter's always
watching good content online you think
he's a good role model absolutely not I
saw the booty pics on my Twitter page
was that fat James your ass is kind of
fat hides wall I'm just calling to see
if you had the James Charles pallet in
stock oh yeah both I don't know there
was two my granddaughter has been asking
for it for her 13th birthday for weeks
now and I've been trying to get it do
you like the palette always it you know
as a grandma I'm always just trying to
make sure that my my granddaughter's are
watching good content online do you know
what much about James Charles oh why not
hello cut the Kim's I can't believe she
hung up okay let's do another one
your turn stop unfortunately we don't
carry the James I mean I don't know I'm
just one of the workers here I don't
know that that's why you're not having
it you know as a mother I'm just trying
to make sure that my daughters are
watching good positive content online do
you know anything about James Charles do
you think he's a good role model
this part of the lobby oh my oh my oh
yeah I really appreciate that do you
know um where I could find the pallet
role model absolutely not I saw some
booty pick something Twitter page
oh my god let's call Hawaii cuz they're
three hours behind okay Aloha babe um so
I'm currently traveling from Los Angeles
[Music]
[Applause]
so you're like eco-friendly Aloha babe
thinks is that what is the longer Yahoo
strangers voice okay okay I'm making
that second
[Music]
okay um one second my boyfriend wants to
ask you a quick question
hi sister James here hi love were
literally we're filming a video right
now where were you prank call a buncha
different make up stars literally I I
had no I appreciate that literally so
much all the information you just gave
was like the best ever I'm like I had to
pop in and to say like she's a bad oh my
god well we ended on a positive note but
that has got to be the worst right not
worst hilariously the worst video ever
fail well I was going to but I don't
think it'll be bad but I think that that
was the most uncomfortable that I've
ever been filming a video yeah yeah he
was lucky shaking I don't know like I
feel like it's taking me so long to like
become so confident with myself that as
soon as they have like portray a
character and then also whilst like
pranking somebody I'm like fooling them
it just makes me feel dirty
yeah although this is awful for me Larry
I had a great time I don't want to leave
Fox News video and honestly I would not
have been able to do this if it were not
for you so I really really appreciate it
and if you guys enjoyed it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below enjoy your love and support it
really just helped us how it's so so so
much and then leave us a comment down
below and let me know if you guys want
me to do another calling video should I
prank all of them oh my god did our
minds
I have the mind of a mastermind what's
that well if you want to fall be able to
make up journey all my social media
accounts will be linked right here
around the screen if you want to text me
on my personal phone number right here
for any updates on new videos photos
merch and so much more whenever is three
one oh nine oh five eight seven four six
make sure you guys go check out the
write out all of his socials as well cuz
content is hilarious it's this all day
long with no
panic attacks little also if you have
not already please it make sure you hit
that subscribe button right down below
because we are so so close to 20 million
sisters it's not even funny I cannot
believe that that sentence just came out
of my mouth for you guys and also click
that notification bell so you get
notified every time I upload a brand new
video I have something very very special
plans in honor of 20 million it's coming
in a few weeks
what is it this video situation auto
costa sister carnie thank you so much
love for always following its wording
and i love you so so so much and if you
like to be the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to always reach we would
relay something live on twitter and also
her my you see my post notifications
I'll write you guys I think that is all
we have for this video today at thank
God Oh much and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]