I sisters James Carl's here and welcome
back to my youtube channel as you can
see today I joined in a a very very
special guest who's just laying here
with me at the beauty room let's move up
with this morning and in LA it is a
pouring rain which honestly I love I
love a good rainy day and it's just so
calm and comfortable since it is pouring
rain today we were not able to take him
on his at normal morning walk and we
honestly didn't even want him to be
brilliant outside much today because he
got soaking wet we had a little airy
give him a shower but in order to do
something fun that with Finnegan today I
thought we would do a video that has not
even requested and since we got him a
few months ago and that is a puppy it
picks my makeup well honestly he's not
even really a puppy at this point I
think he's like 18 weeks old
oh my god it's not like one of those
moms it's like oh my god how old is your
baby and they're like oh little Juliet
is 36 months old and you're like three
Melissa your baby's three super-quick
pub date for everybody that's been
asking he is now 18 weeks old he is
growing insanely fast it's not even
funny he has fully trained that both
potty training and just like kind of
everything in general he can safely go
up and down the stairs now that you guys
for all the tips and advice on the first
30 about that he sees me every night he
loves everybody and everybody loves him
and is so obsessed he's such a blessing
to our life and we absolutely are so
grateful that we got him and if you guys
want to see more pup dates and more
phone as a finna make sure you follow my
Instagram over X Ben Charles well that
being said if Finn is fully trained and
to see me in the studio at many
different times doing different makeup
looks but what will you pick out for my
makeup routine I honestly have no idea I
don't even know if he's gonna cooperate
and pick anything to regain right
but regardless let's jump right into
this video and see what look we can come
up with it what the hell pardon Oh papa
right here let's get started
[Music]
then come okay good boy hey sit stay
stay
okay for the end you have four three
foundations okay treats one two three
what what you want I want the bag there
we go okay Finnegan for powder you have
three options baby so then again oh oh
he wants the Jacqueline he'll luminous a
car do you have that little rotation you
did right there I never taught I said
this could either be really good or be
my skin literally look okay one two
three
come here sit good boy okay okay no okay
fifteen complete
he's bored or any hello are you kidding
up for contouring thin again we have the
Anasazi Beverly Hills contour palette
and we also have the dragon Beauty face
palette by our good friend Nikita
now speaking of scandalous that's this
one but she loves to snatch it up so
then again what do you want everyone to
take a good luck yeah you really want
sickness all of the artists what - what
what do you want oh oh oh hey
honest idea he's a classic okay now for
blush we have pink or peach you get to
pet you know peeps pink oh no you won't
see you instead oh oh my CT was he's lit
just think all I know I'll go to
okay now for brows and again we have all
Anasazi products but three very
different methods he's boring okay so we
have Anasazi brow ways we have battle
powder would you never do and approach
out Coenen huh okay little rap this Hawk
said he's taking you all day like go to
favorite really dunno were you so well
that was it is o one rap video and she
thinks she's an MC hi sisters now
Finnegan from last year we have three
lovely options pick your favorite
mascara sweetie good boy okay benefit
roller lash
he realized again like making sure he
picks the right one I'm looking keep
sticking one that's in this position for
some reason okay what you need to switch
that hey now for lashes we have to pick
out the lash it's going to go with this
makeup looking we have three very
different options check your laps oh
wait hold on now stay here no big
retreat pic now I know that you see
these three lovely treats in front of
you which one do you want me with
experiment concluded it's not just the
right position okay you do know what
you're doing he really wanted look I
think
okay for a high later today Finnegan we
have the brand-new what more for you
Finnegan
actually let's really cool
okay the more px Manny anyway
glam palettes good choice I'm excited to
play with that one to a theme so the ice
unfortunate are everything gets fine and
now it's gonna have a pick between a few
different palettes but ultimately then
that look is still kind of up to me
based on the clothes in the palette so
instead we decided to blow up the
channels explore came in Carla into the
James Charles X Murphy large pathway
that's funny so we're gonna let then
again pick the colors are the actual
look today come on are you kidding oh
okay
he picked Daddy a nice dark forest green
good for the holiday season
okay okay a little bit of social blame
for a nice lighter green oh okay with to
Cola socialblade and Donny for a nice
lovely festive blue and green luck beste
for what holiday birthday why
so now it is time for on the lips and
fin is easy okay
[Applause]
there's no truant hey blue new red and
brown I got to choose about Twitter and
blue he's kept the pink honestly good
taste I would get the pink as well I
think you gotta go with Finnegan's first
choice mm-hmm this could be gone
[Music]
alright you guys let's just shall write
and a fan that definitely picked a lot
of my go-to favorite products but I
think he was also trying to challenge me
as one of my fellow subscribers that is
tired of using the same products over
and over again so let's just do this and
have a really good time our first moment
that pen picked is our foundation and
that is the Dior Eric last foundation I
forgot how do you apply this that's my I
play put this in the back of a mirror
actually Sharon's gonna bond this right
and alright you guys so this place
already on it this foundation is looking
at really a really beautiful or conceal
I'm gonna go to my Tarte shape tape this
is my Holy Grail favorite and pin and
pin I was gonna say pin did pick this
one Vindictus 100k then will literally
sit outside at the studio door crying
until you let him in and then once he's
in here he will want to leave
approximately 30 seconds later all right
now Jocelin the my system of this all
over I'm really concerned what I'm gonna
do is grab me a little bit of a regular
setting powder just put right underneath
the original a little bit of Dijon
Cosmetics luminous powder in
do me do me too me too me like that's
gonna grab a fluffy brush and I guess
like put this on here I was really
scared that by applying this with a
brush it was going to really get very
very like shining shimmering splendid
effect on the skin but it definitely
it's not it is still setting everything
in plates but it does have a really nice
like shy you're kidding
I definitely looking forward to playing
this a little bit more and seeing what
it's capable of but so far
holy waiting yeah cool we are looking a
very flat and I desperately want to add
some contour back to the face so I'm
going to grab the Anasazi Beverly Hills
at contour palette that Finn so kindly
selected and that Bryce just going to
grab my actually mac-11 3us brush and
I'm just going to grab the kind of light
shade in the light banana shade and use
a little bit of this to highlight the
center of my face then I was gonna grab
my morphe am at 405 brush use code after
10% and dip into the middle cool telenet
shade of this palette I think the shade
is actually called fawn if I remember
correctly it's gonna use a little bit of
this dish as well my cheekbones my
forehead look a little bit smaller
especially with my hair in the growing
back recovery up process that's honestly
been the most frustrating thing of like
this whole hair journey I feel like I've
talked about this a million times
already but you guys know that I used to
have like my little curly hair where I
would like kind of swoop over the
forehead and give the illusion of like a
tiny here
hairline yeah can't do that anymore so
that's been really on my mind to get it
then lastly cover um five to seven I'm
just gonna dip into the warmer tone
shade away in this left-hand corner and
I'm going to use this to kind of warm up
my face a little bit timewe nose contour
brussels gonna use a mix of these two
colors and chisel out the nose as well
or even a sofa blush to fit picked my
go-to favorite Mac peaches he only had
two options it was either pink or peach
instead of divid with my evil brush and
not a little bit of a color back into my
cheek region just for a nice little wash
already base and I would have time for
brows and fana did pick the Anasazi
Beverly Hills brow is in the shade and
medium brown that being said you guys to
me do this a million times I'm going to
do this off camera quickly and I'll be
right back to do it the eyeshadow
portion because that's what it's gonna
start getting a little questionable ah
so the brows are all on and now that
means it is time for the eyeshadow
portion now the colors that Finnegan
chose for this look today
I would say it wouldn't be my first
choice of eyeshadow colors to use we
have socialblade daddy Cola and acapella
and then tune okay I'm gonna survive I'm
gonna have what four five six brush and
dip into a daddy and I'm going to place
this into the crease and now I'm going
to grab and then four three three brush
dip into a social blade which is our
bright green shade and I'm going to use
this and like just barely blend out the
edge of that daddy can I have an m4 for
one and dip into tune and use this to
just buff out that green pitch have
another girl what kind of look that I
wanted to do for this and I really have
to come to the collusion that the red
lip is going to mess it up later on so
we're just gonna cut the crease and hope
for the best
I will change out the lip for the
Instagram photo now on this cut crease
I'm going to grab a sigma e27 brush and
just dip into it Cola and I'm gonna
place this right in this outer corner
over top with this concealer and this is
going to blend nicely into Daddy and
then with a flat brush I'm going to grab
acapella and I'm gonna place that in the
middle of the lid this looks so pretty
and it's gonna get completely ruined by
a red lip I cannot get that oh it's
never for the lower lashline it's gonna
be super easy I'm just gonna first grab
Miami four five six once again and dip
into a little bit of dotty and I'm just
gonna run this right up along my lash
line and connecting it to the outer
corner and then finally a little bit of
a tune to tie it all together just to
make this look a little bit more sultry
I'm just gonna grab a liquid a black
liner and I'm just going to add a little
bit of a wing Finn did not pick this but
I'm making the executive decision that
it needs it
next I was going to be at the mascara
which Finn picked the benefit roller
lash this used to be my literal all-time
holy grail favorite mascara and I've
honestly been using it again and I kind
of like miss it a little bit so I'm just
gonna use it today you know send a text
to it at 3m you up question okay and
then ridiger of our ardell demi wispies
recently just for funsies i've been
trying to practice
more like natural glam a type of makeup
and a lot of sovereignty makeup artists
actually use these on their clients
really don't want a crazy
look so I'm not gonna rush them they're
also very very affordable so let's see
if we can at least like this look look
good I'm definitely not mad at it and I
want to use these again when it comes
like a natural glam and see how they
look but for this particular look I
wouldn't choose them okay so that is one
I add this look all complete I'm loving
how this is looking so far I'm gonna go
the other one off camera quickly and
then we'll come back and do the rest of
the look which might not look so
beautiful
in the end all right you guys we are
back and both eyes are now complete and
it's time to move on to the rest of the
face the next step I'm very very excited
for and that is going to be high leaders
we are going to be using the brand new
morphe x-man EMU a glam palette
congratulations Manny on this palette I
am so proud of you and so grateful to
call you a friend this palette is
beautiful if you guys know what this is
obviously very very true to Manny's
brand I love that he's kind of running
with the copper eye and nude lip
literally if you guys been around since
day one when I first started on social
media
in the beginning I got a Twitter fight
with Manny because I called him out for
only to cuff her eyes and nude lips it
was so stupid it was a huge mistake and
it came from a really really big place
of entitlement when I was really really
uh and I'm very grateful that men and
they were able to work it out and now
I'm so lucky to call her my closest
friends in the community just wanted to
kind of share that little story time
because we've literally both grown so
much and I am very very happy for him
that being said we're gonna test out the
highlighters today so I'm gonna grab the
shade no butt and we're going to pop it
on the cheekbone
oh yeah that's for Tess beautiful coulda
grabbed this on my pencil brush as well
and use this to highlight my nose all
right you guys now it's time for the
last step of a sec which is of course
going to be at the lipstick fan
picked the Fenty beauteous Sun and let
paint in the color uncensored which is a
beautiful red color I love this lipstick
but I did not like this lipstick for
this look like this is just not a red
lip look we're just gonna go ahead and
apply it so Dinah this looks so bad oh
my god this is the ugliest combination
are you kidding all right the look is
done what do you think do you like it
hello he said I regret the red/black do
you want to keep hanging on oh yeah okay
I'm just good you're gonna say right
you're then are you guys well I think
that is this makeup picked by my puppy a
Finnegan Hall complete I am really
really happy with how this makeup look
turned out today aside from of course
red lip I think this foundation in
powder combo looks stunning on the skin
and I think that the color actually
ended up being really really good in the
end so I'm really pumped to keep using
this I love manis highlighter I love
this I looked at Finn it picked out for
me I was little bit scared at first but
thank you so much for this beautiful
color combination the red lip of course
was not my favorite Thank You Finn for
picking my makeup today though if you
guys enjoyed this videos today with a
little Fanta please don't forget to go
to big thumbs up down below enjoy your
love and support it really doesn't mean
so much to me and also if you have not
ready it make sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood I would love to
have you in the family and finally click
that Bell icon so you'll get a
notification every time I upload a brand
new video if you like to follow me on my
makeup dirty you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter
tik-tok and twitch I think it's
everything just team Charles and my
snapchat and world behind see if it's up
there James Charles the next rise after
Charles Fitts video sisters how that
goes through sister Laxus thank you so
much love for always falling in
supporting you know I love you and your
profile picture
very very much and if you'd like to the
next videos sister shadows don't forget
to always reach me Twitter links when
they go live on Twitter all right you
guys thank you so much watching this
videos today I love you and I will see
you in the next one look cozy bye
[Music]