[Music]
[Applause]
hi sisters James Charles Yura and
welcome back to my channel
[Music]
getting straight into playing this video
is when we're going to be very long son
John I want to take up any more of your
time on this intro it has been far too
long since I have like the silent kind
of just chatting with you guys so sooner
you're excited to sit down with them a
little bit of a chit chat with me a
style video I asked you guys on Twitter
to send me a bunch of questions about
like my life makeup whatever you wanted
to know Under the Sun so today I thought
I wouldn't sit down and just talk to you
guys I put together this brown winged
owl smokey situation and I decided to
pair it with this blue a periwinkle
custom lip color and honestly you really
really love how it turned out I also
brought back at the fake freckles which
I have not worn in a long paralytically
time and I forgot to put on a half of
this video so this is definitely a very
very weird type of situation for me to
be in I don't exactly feel like myself
but honestly I really really like
sitting down and talking to you guys so
if you want to just chill relax and hear
some questions being answered about me
and see how to create this definitely
strange and unique makeup look
make sure you keep on watching oh hello
everybody I am currently a barefaced
well no I'm not because I'm putting out
a primer but the hair is shaved
I got a fade on the size thank God it
was looking a little manly before not
gonna lie right now I'm currently
rocking the pepper from American Horror
Story look but you know what we're just
gonna move on and probably put on a hat
as soon as humanly possible I feel like
it's been literally months inside like
it's not that I talked to you guys I've
been it so really busy with my move to
LA and just so many different things
going on and I've been really really
slacking on YouTube and kind of every
social media lately so I'm so excited
now that everything is like kind of
settled down a little bit and I am back
and ready to kill it I really wanted to
sit down today and do a little bit of
like a chip shot get ready with me a Q&A
style video it's been far too long since
I have like just talked to you guys and
nothing like a really really serious
in-depth tutorial so I really do miss
that a few days ago I had tweeted on my
Twitter I just want to focus on you guys
I'm communicating
um there because I really feel like I
don't talk to you guys enough and that
is something that I definitely want to
change so if you don't want me on
Twitter definitely go follow me I've
been tweeting a ton of you bear that the
infalling when two people as well I
don't know why I didn't do this sooner
but hey it's never too late to be bad a
shitty influencer right I'm gonna be
blending this foundation away good tone
my next today as you can see a sister
spread hen is looking a little splotchy
I have an appointment later on this week
perfect in time for Coachella this
weekend I am so freaking excited and I
hope that I'll be seeing a ton of you
sisters there it'll be me and Laura and
hey-zeus and Victor all going together
it's gonna be such a good time so if you
see me and you better freaking say hi I
honestly have no idea what I'm gonna be
wearing yet so i'm horrified but
hopefully i figure something out because
the last thing that everybody wants to
see is me naked trust me
earlier on Twitter when I was planning
on what I want to do for this video when
I decided I was going to leave a little
chitchat Q&A style video I'd tweet it
out asking for questions and stuff like
that you guys no need to talk about so
I'm going to be answering them as I do
my glam today the first question is from
Mac and she asked if you could do what
one Kardashian's makeup who would you
choose and why well I think I would have
to choose obviously a sister Kim just
because she is a living legend and I
have a personal bias to her because I
had the honor and blessing of meeting
her she was so frickin nice literally an
angel sent from above so I asked Lee
loved her and would love to have her up
one day but maybe Lee after Mario dies
because that's his job and I do not want
to compete with a legend
Zoi house where do you think your life
would be if you never picked up a makeup
brush and not oh wow that's honestly
such a hard question because I genuinely
have no idea just a year ago I was not
even doing this and now I'm living in
Angeles with amazing friends and amazing
people and doing what I love and am able
to make a career out of it this all has
happened so quickly for me and I've
loved every single moment of it but I
probably would still be sitting in a
high school classroom learning every
single day chase asked what is your
skincare routine and how do you get rid
of weird spots and pimples on your face
that's a really good question chase and
that is a question that I get asked all
the time and unfortunately my answer for
you guys is literally just wash my face
in the shower I know that sounds like
complete but I swear to God I
do
literally no skincare what just
definitely gonna come to bite me in the
ass later on I definitely want to do
some like research into finding good
skin care products soon is just not
something that I've really like really
cared about in the past and I don't
really know why that it's either I used
to have very very very bad acne people
it's good when I was like in fifth sixth
and seventh grade but it kind of like
just went away and I really had to deal
with it it's weird too because with me
when I don't wear makeup for a few days
then I'll start to break out I'm
definitely not the person to ask when it
comes to skincare advice I'm so sorry
Brandon asks what is one thing you love
about your career and one thing that you
hope to do in the future
answering this while doing my nose
contours already it's killing me because
y'all know this takes a lot of focus but
I'm gonna do my best
how about favorite thing about my career
is just getting to me all of you guys I
know that's like so chase that's what
everybody says but it truly does like oh
my god if you guys ask any of my friends
if I'm having a shitty day you have no
idea how much it'll like instantly turn
around as soon as I see one of you guys
like in public or something even just
like getting happy tweets from you guys
just truly just makes my day you have no
idea how cool it is to just know that
you have like an entire platform of
people from all around the world
watching you and supporting you loving
you it when times get tough and trust me
they do for everybody it's really just
like nice to be able to just get support
from you guys and hear all the nice
things you have to say that's definitely
by far my favorite part of my job as in
the future I really don't know what the
future holds I have a lot of ideas and
I would love to work on I'll see you
guys know that I love to sing so I
really want to do a more musical stuff
in the future but that's hard as well
because like producing and directing and
blah blah blah so I'm trying to work on
that as if I have nothing immediately
planned but the second I do have
something and you guys know it'll be the
first people to know so just keep your
eyes open but there's a lot of cool
stuff in the works coming soo that I
have the scenes for now I'm just gonna
focus on YouTube and seven just having a
good ass time Nicole said cereal then
milk or milk of M cereal well Nicole I
have news for you I don't drink milk so
cereal then more cereal dry as seer
house do you before doing a more
creative looks or more glam looks for me
the answer to this question is extremely
obvious but I think a lot of you guys
might think differently and that is for
sure
creative looks 150 percent honestly I
hate doing glam looks literally more
than anything in the entire world I
don't know why I feel like they're just
so boring we've all seen the same with
Ron Sophie I have 50 million times yet
here we are I've gotta do a
bronze smokey eye in about ten minutes
when I finish do brows creative
avant-garde out there makeup looks got
me to where I am today
they got me all my followers and they
are truly what I enjoy most about makeup
I love putting a ton of really crazy
stuff on my face it's like creating art
honestly but one thing that sucks about
them is that those books can take up to
like five six or even seven hours
depending on how complicated they really
are so it was much easier than Wiener do
back home when I was like still just
starting off now it's much harder for me
because I'm just so busy and I have
something on every single day it's
really hard to get five or six or seven
hours free but I really am trying to get
back into it I've been trying to set
aside some time recently and I've been
like panning a lot of things on
Pinterest and like saving a lot of
pictures for inspiration so definitely
keep your eyes peeled because I really
really want to get back into career
stuff soon but yeah I definitely prefer
a creative makeup looks over going on it
any day of the week Nicole asked James
what is your opinion on
well Nicole if you couldn't tell about
my thirsty Instagram comments on their
pages almost every single day or my
tweet to them or my idioms to them
asking them to country the face I
haven't lovable for them and I'm very
very open to a brother-husbands style oh
my god this joke is already going down I
love the Dolans ones that I want them
both to punch me in the face and then
make out with me if that answers your
question
Haley asked attending VidCon you asked
question mark unfortunately no I will
not be attending VidCon this year I'm so
freaking sad because I really really did
want to go but I just found out a few
weeks ago after I had already booked my
tickets to VidCon that is the same
weekend as my graduation back in New
York across the country so unfortunately
I'll not be a bit calm but I'll be at
playlist live in Orlando in a a few
weeks I am so freaking excited so if you
are going to that I will be there
my meet-and-greet just kind of knows I
think I'm competing great number of 20
on Saturday don't quote me on that but
definitely check it out get some tickets
I can't wait to meet all of you sisters
I've asked how do you like living alone
in your new apartment and are you gonna
do it in a permit or soon it is very
weird and yes absolutely I have been
working for the past few weeks actually
on an apartment tour video I'm working
with a graphic designer to kind of make
like an HGTV style thing it's gonna be a
big production this sounds weird but I
promise when you see the apartment or
video you guys are going to be shocked
to the frickin core I do plan on doing a
either two or three part series of it
I'm not on a percent sure yet but it is
gonna be a big thing on my channel that
I'm very very excited for so please stay
tuned and one of those videos will be
like a Q&A on living alone and how I
like decorated it and how I handled the
boob so I'm not going to answer that for
right now
stay tuned it'll be coming within the
next few weeks but I'm like officially
done decorating and fully like
settled on and I'm gonna so pretty busy
lately and I was just traveling and now
I'm going to a hotel this weekend and I
just had a friend sing with me so
there's gonna walk going on I will be
done soon I promise
I want these videos to be like really
good so it just be patient they're
coming
Gio asked what is your favorite pool of
all time
whoo I feel like I should really say
something from like one of the scissors
Apparel's hoodies but honestly it's
probably work smarter and not harder I
think that's something that like I
always apply it to my life and I feel
like it's a really really good quote to
like live by yeah that's kind of how
like that's how I like to work every
single day and like make sure that I'm
doing the best I possibly can
work smarter not harder or it's not that
deep Victoria asks how do you cope with
all the negativity you receive I truly
admire you for sticking to career
instead of taking a break Thank You
Victoria that really does mean a lot to
me I think it's something that you
really have to learn to deal with as a
social-media influencer and it's
something that is really like it's
really really hard to kind of like grasp
the fact that when you do this job and
you have this lifestyle
everybody's gonna be watching everything
that you do and I think that even now
today being where I am it's still
something for me that is really really
scary to think about and something that
I honestly don't even like wanna think
about at the end of the day if people
are talking about you and mentioning
your name and wasting their time talking
about you not only is that free
publicity and free press but that means
that you're successful so when I see all
these negative tweets about me I just
try to keep in mind the fact that like
okay these people are talking about me
and day in and day out because I have a
name for myself and because I've gotten
myself to where I am today it's a really
like kind of twisted way to look at it
and it's kind of sad that I like it even
has to be that way but that's the
reality of the job that I have a very
very thing before I am and I'm so
thankful that I have
you guys because if it was not for you
guys I definitely would have quit a very
very long time ago but I have so many
amazing sisters out there that are all
loving my work and loving the things
that I do and that is truly what keeps
me going the negativity that all social
media influencers get is definitely like
the number one downside to having this
job it honestly can make some days so
beyond miserable a lot of people will
seem to think that oh like your
social-media influencer you make all the
money in the world you have all these
friends and you get to do fun things and
well yeah some of that is sure I
definitely have a lot of friends and
gets do a lot of cool things and I
definitely am making a study and kama
817 which I am so thankful for I would
never take for granite money does not
buy happiness there's no amount of money
that anybody can in the bank account
that makes them happy take it from me as
someone who has a lot more money than
most seventeen year olds I definitely
still go to bed upset many nights out of
the week it's just something you have to
learn to cope with and that sucks to say
but you didn't have to think about the
positive and think about what you're
gonna do next to get through it and how
you gonna handle this situation yeah
Kristine asked how and why did you come
out well Christina came out of the
closet when I was 12 years old and the
way I came out is definitely a little
unique and different to say the least so
I plan on doing a story time video about
it eventually please stay tuned I
promise it will come out just right now
it's still a little bit too soon but the
second I turn 18 we can talk about it oh
that sounds weird I've been asked what
is your dream car by the way I love you
and I'm in love with my sweater from
sistas apparel ah thank you sister Ellen
I love you too girl my dream car that's
actually a really really hard question
up until recently I've never actually
been like a car person even still I'm
kind of not now that I live in downtown
in LA I don't actually have a car I then
rank everywhere because I have up my
credits from and you guys using at my
code shout out to all of you for that
but I'm actually thinking about buying a
car in this summer and I definitely I'm
looking at a lot of
options but I'm really leaning towards a
cheap they are really really cute and
they're not too expensive either well
apparently they're awful on gas mileage
so I generally have no idea but my dream
dream card is probably like a g-wagen
all those in the next few years I will
have a matte white g-wagen in my
driveway on my modern at California
mountain Homa but as of right now a
sister is dealing with her tubers Sarah
what is your go-to order at Chipotle my
order is exactly the same and at this
point all the workers at my local
Chipotle and know me so I don't know if
that's like cool or really really sad
but either way my order is a burrito
bowl with white rice no beans chicken
and then a mild salsa lettuce cheese
guac yes I know it's extra and then
oh wait that's it then I was going to
sign up chip symbolic as well and a
fountain drink for the road and my total
is a 1589 sometimes they gave me the
sisters discount all right I'm gonna do
the other eye off-camera really quickly
then I'll be back and we can finish off
the rest of the face with more questions
I just want to take up anywhere every
time because I feel like this video is
already getting very very very long so
BRB so I just wanted to finish my eyes
off camera just to it save a little bit
of time so you continue on with the Q&A
I use the black liner for the upper
waterline and a nude liner for the lower
waterline of course I had a pop on my
house lashes like products for the
lashes today and I just bend them
together with the benefit roller lash
mascara eight and ass we're to get the
idea of calling your fans as sisters
this is actually one question that I get
asked all the time and I don't think
I've ever actually adjust it in a video
before so this is like a good time to
answer I guess I personally hate the
word like fans more than anything in the
world I think it is so incredibly tacky
and ugly to call like followers and
supporters the fans who I just I don't
know why I just really don't like it
sisters are so started this past
Halloween
you guys do not see my Halloween costume
I was a little bit of like a dead deer
type of situation it was a very very
intricate costume but you guys know me I
always need my baseball hat on Laurens
dad basically helped me cut holes in a
leather hat but it was where so I could
put antlers Stuart's second where the
antlers and the hat at the same time
loading me being extra as helper and no
reason at all
but I was super super appreciative and
he literally pulled it together out of
nowhere so I was like damn super
impressed and when he handed me the hat
I don't know why but I just said thank
you sister Marco don't know where it
came from don't know like why it came
out my mouth because I had never like
said it before but and then I was just
thinking like what should I call my
followers because I adored fans then I
was like you know what I already called
my best friends which are basing with my
family sisters so why not call and you
guys sisters as well just because like I
like to look at you guys's kind of like
my family and close friends as well so
that's why you were all sisters Anne
Tolley said if you were going to go to
college what would you study this is a
great pressure that I actually get asked
all the time and it's honestly something
that I'm not really quite sure the
answer uh when I was applying to
colleges and looking at colleges I was
looking at different majors and
specifically like marketing and a social
media stuff
obviously I wanted to do something that
was going to be your focus towards so
that was gonna help me with my career
later on but obviously a lot of the
class I was looking at the different
schools it seemed very very like
outdated and just seemed like they
weren't gonna be very much help to me
basically however once who I asked about
like lessons that they had in their
social media marketing class and the
moment basically told me one of the main
things that they focus on is like
finding your target audience which yes
is a very important part of marketing
and she was like well one of the biggest
lessons we learned is how to find your
age group so basically if you're going
to be targeting older people you want to
go on Facebook and if you want to get
the young kids you're gonna want to go
on Instagram and I was like there's a
lesson on that and she's like yeah it's
a huge part of the program when I heard
that for the first time that is when I
knew that college definitely it was not
gonna be for me I definitely do not
claim to be an expo to anything I
believe there was always so much to
learn but I am definitely a very very
hands-on person taking a class on a
concept that I've literally known and
and then executing throughout my social
media career since like age 7 when I ran
a Club Penguin blog should not be a
lesson that I need to take in a college
setting where I'm paying several several
several several several thousand dollars
my parents money that they don't even
have in the first place so at that point
it was like a unanimous decision between
me my family that college definitely was
not gonna be for me and they were on
board and now I'm here in Los Angeles
and I'm learning more every single day
being like Anza and doing stuff like
that and marketing every single day with
my manager that I would ever learn in a
college classroom setting so I feel like
I definitely made it the right decision
definitely look into it and definitely
do a lot of good research before you
made the decision as well because I
believe education is a super SuperDuper
important I graduated high school a
super high average and I'm very very
proud of it but I definitely think it
was right for me and my family to not
continue on but definitely do some
research and decide what's best for your
situation for how later today I'm going
to pop on the Eclipse highlighter from a
jeffree star cosmetics this is in a
collaboration with many of you I I am
I'm so freaking oops I am oh my god oh
wow okay how are you doing today the for
the lips today I was originally planning
on this one from Anastasio which now
looking at it on the camera would look
really pretty so I really hope that I
don't regret this but I'm gonna go to
the anasazi lip hell up today I'm going
to custom mix the color somebody mixing
the shades primary five which is blue
primary one which is white and then a
little bit of nine which is purple
speak' a periwinkle color this is the
combination of the three colors that I'm
gonna go for today I hope that I don't
regret this but I guess let's go ahead
and put on
ah okay I really like this color this
would have been a really good
alternative hello to finish off this
look of course I'm going to set my face
using my Urban Decay oil slick setting
spray and then use my pal I'm just going
to dry that setting spray into my face
to lock everything in place and to just
make everything kind of melt into the
skin and finally Zoe asked James could
this be your last question yes sister
we are done all right guys and this is
the completed look that we put together
I really really hope you enjoyed this
little chitchat get ready with me like I
said before it's been a far too long
since I've been able to sit down and
kind of just chat with you guys I am so
looking forward to being more active on
snapchat and Twitter make sure you
follow me over there if you have not
already I cannot wait to like interact
with all of you sisters that follow you
guys tweet you you know the drill if you
did enjoy this salad video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below subscribe if you have not already
show me the love on this video because I
would love to do what more videos of
this style on this channel if you'd like
to follow me on my makeup journey you
can follow me on Instagram and Twitter
that they are both just James Charles
and my snapshot and you know from work
behind the scenes type stuff James
Charles and extra ass after Charles all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching and I will see you in the next
one bye
[Music]