hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I was
looking at my calendar a few days ago
because I'm doing some traveling
very very soon which I'm very excited
about and I noticed that we were at the
end of September which means October is
coming up sister's goofy month a
favorite time of the entire year
literally cannot wait but that also
means that my anniversary of the first
time that I ever put on makeup is coming
up in a few days and oh my god I am
literally so excited it is about to be
our three year sister bursary I
literally cannot believe this is do my
job for three years now I pinch myself
every single day and it's literally so
cool and I thought for our three year
anniversary we should do something very
very fun and good and fresh and special
I'm working on one other video right now
that you guys will see in a few short
weeks but it required me to go way back
in time and open up the history books on
both my Instagram and my youtube channel
and through doing this I came across my
first ever youtube video which I
literally have erased from my mind if
you've been a longtime subscriber you
know that I have changed drastically so
for today's video I want to react to
this video and see what has changed I
know I've gotten way more comfortable on
camera my talking speed is probably
multiplied by literally a million at
this point and I also would love to try
to recreate the look and kind of
modernize and see how I would do the
same exact look in today's makeup skills
I am praying that my makeup has gotten
way way way better oh yeah
James 2016 Sharpie eyebrows there's no
way I could even lose at this foolproof
plan without further ado let's pull up
the first ever video and take a trip
down memory lane okay this video is
titled blue brown serpent before I even
finish that sentence literally why
makeup tutorial from Jade Charles Beauty
have you been around since day one that
was very original Instagram name before
I got James Charles this has five
hundred eighty-three thousand views oh
not bad
and as posted two years ago
[Music]
oh okay pause ah a second synonym
already horrified I forgot that I oh my
god
okay okay before I had this really
beautiful good and fresh hair that I
loved I used to have a man dime and it
was bad disgusting and horrible and
cutting that off was probably one of the
best decisions I've ever made in my
entire life
so in this video I am rocking gray man
bun which was a bad choice
sixteen-year-old makeup artist from New
York and I run the Instagram page to
change her on Beauty lately sisters
another thing yet either
this is so weird oh my god they're
talking so slow hi guys my name is James
I'm a 16 year old makeup artist from New
York and I run the Instagram page J
Charles Beauty I don't even think I
could talk about that now if I tried for
an entire video
[Music]
you know everything about this paused
who the man but being tied up and
besides not being shaved looks gross the
eyebrows are taking up half of my
already very large forehead I would love
to know where I got trio chrome from
because the only color that I'm seeing
here is green but then again that could
be the fact that I was literally using
one light to shoot this video that cost
me $50 from Amazon my nose because of
the contour looks like it's about a good
inch thick so we love that and my top
lip is not there oh my god I forgot I
look filler oh my god this is why make
sure to keep on watching hi guys I'm
gonna be starting off today using my
benefit Porefessional primer I've been
million little bumps and pores all over
my face so doing this would really help
me smooth everything out and get an even
foundation application next I'm going
into my la girl pro color corrector
concealer
she's just a color correcting shadow and
my aya literally cannot even tell you
the last time I color corrected my face
I think there were so many makeup trends
one of them being color correcting that
we're like so big at one point that now
literally nobody talked throughout if
you don't have this problem obviously
don't color products because this is not
pumpkin glam but if you're like me and
you get negative 15 hours to sleep this
might be for you I also get a solid 18 a
green color corrector also from Le girl
and then blended it out with my Beauty
Blender or its use the full coverage
foundation HD Ultra foundation in the
shade Y 255 and just putting a bunch of
little dots all over my face obviously
we're gonna blend these out later on but
it just helps create a really even
application that is yellow that is
literally yellow nothing has changed I
still can't match my foundation but good
lord we want a smooth transition and the
last thing we need is Moses parting the
foundation see on your face oh my god I
literally thought I was
YouTube's next comedian what is going on
I'm using my la girl Pro concealer in
the shade porcelain woah my face in the
middle of my forehead in the middle of
my chin on my moustache area and just
one line down the center of my nose this
will just make all the high points of my
face to stand out and then once again a
blending out with my Beauty Blender now
I'm setting my entire face using Cody
Cody or some powder let me tell you
great powder if you need to literally
lock in your makeup for the next eight
years this is what created flash like
Mary that's all I need to say on that I
don't think I need to elaborate any
further reduce crease edge that's before
I had a coupon code Oh gonna put it in
there now use go James for 10% off oh my
god I didn't even have code James then
this is so crazy here is control of this
color usually comes in the contour
palette but I actually deep hot in it
and just put it in my Z palette with all
my other contour and highlight shades
once again I'm just putting everyone's e
palettes were a thing and everybody used
to have like their little custom shadows
and their pal that they bring everywhere
does anybody even still do that Oh
nobody uses deepal because they had
their scandal moving on oops still hated
the fun still hated the Fife at that and
today nothing has changed whoo at least
we found one similarity next to further
defined my contour I'm using the same
brushes before and make up a cocoa bear
it isn't eyeshadow but I never use blush
and I look so this really helps I just
warm everything up if you've been in the
make up community for a very long time
you were probably very familiar with
makeup geek shadows because everybody
had pretty much their entire line makeup
geek shadows are some of the first ones
that I ever ordered what I started doing
makeup the shadow that I just used Coco
bear was one of my all-time favorites
for brown smokey eyes and I just used it
to contour my face I know you can't
really tell because the lighting is the
worst I'm already looking yellow because
the foundation my contour is orange of
course the angles are gonna turn out
that that when your brows look that ugly
oh my god I cannot believe that these
eyebrows literally were once mine they
still are not perfect now like they
could I'm sure be a whole lot better
with the amount of hate comments that I
got on my eyebrows on a daily basis
which was an alarming amount for any
sixteen-year-old kid to be dealing with
I don't know how it took me that long to
fix them the first day of convention I
ever went to I waited in line for over
an hour to the meet and greet for
anasazi Beverly Hills and she had been
following me and she was like oh my god
James I recognize you and I was
literally fangirling so excited and she
literally looked me right in the eyes
and said you need your eyebrows they're
horrible like I swear to god I wish I
was kidding and in that moment I had
such a big ego at this time I was like
oh please and she literally sat there I
was like no you really need to tweeze
off like the entire bottom portion and
like lift them up and I was like oh
please lady they look fine
I've actually if I had listened sooner
we wouldn't have you know how to deal
with this issue
although the hate sucked at the time
thank you honestly truly for the bottom
of my heart to everyone who ever left a
hate comment on my eyebrows I needed
this like
that's what they look like right there
this entire look I use my morphe 35o
palette I'm using my Murphy I'm four for
one and once again just a medium brown
tone from the 35k palette I'm putting
that in the inner and outer views of the
eyes and then just taking whatever
excess product is left and coming in
windshield wipers just to find that
crease okay honestly not gonna like my
tutorial skills back then although it
may not have looked pretty we're pretty
decent like I will say no I definitely
get a lot of comments complaining that I
skipped through everything which I
definitely do but like how did you good
to have a good explaining everything
here making sure it's like eventually
all the right angles
good job sixteen year old me in the
waterline I'm just going in with the
Italia deluxe I pencil in turquoise I
got this at the morphe store if you
don't have this eye pencil you can
easily just do black it's really up to
you but I wanted another pop of color on
the bottom I actually lost the clip but
I did use the NYX jumbo eye pencil in
black bean just so mimic the halo effect
that we have going on on the upper lid
and then once I did that I'm just going
back under the lower lash line couple
end everything out and connect it back
up to the top that was the longest
sentence I've ever heard my entire life
oh my god
queen of run-on sentences the speech
patterns really have not changed and
sinus I'm just going to burn mascara
benefit roller lash it's so good and
makes my lashes look so on and not
clumpy so I would definitely recommend I
stole my cameras today I use the
Blackmagic lashes in siren I include my
eye shot what I try to do on camera so
definitely not going to do that again
anyway lesson learned
that is true I talked about this a few
times before but when I first started
doing makeup
I could not glue on eyelashes to save my
life probably because my eyebrows were
taking up half of my eye so I literally
could get no room in there and every
time that I tried I glued my eye shot
wish I was kidding
not so highly I'm just approaching my
brush again
sex+ to make it super to find and then
mixing these two colors for my Anasazi
aglow camp now we pack that highly on
like there's no tomorrow
remember the goal is that your toilet
can be seen from space and that you
blind everybody walking by okay we get a
sweetie
I always highlight my cheekbones the tip
of my nose and my cupids though just
because I think it looks cute
I am scared at the size of a brush I
just use to highlight my nose oh my god
this is why my nose looks like it is an
inch wide for my lips today I'm using
Oprah Brooklyn you guys always ask what
liquid lipsticks I like best and they're
definitely Oprah the formulation is so
good and they don't dry crusty and girls
like so many other brands do true I
still stand by this and I love the
overlook a lipstick they're by far my
favorite formula of all time also keep
the coupon code must have been over
first
this one was code J Charles but now it's
Co James it gets you 30% still to this
day my poor top left where was I even
putting the left stack at this point
like as an option last step I went ahead
and I added Houdini all over my lips
just for a cool Jerome effect
oh and that guy's is the finished look
if you enjoyed this tutorial and I will
see you soon with a new video
[Music]
well that was seven minutes of my life
that I will never get back looking back
at these videos for me is literally so
crazy I cannot believe it's already been
almost three years since I started doing
this like it feels like it was yesterday
but at the same time this person feels
foreign like who literally who is she
like the gray hair the man Vaughn the
big nose contour the non-existent topped
lamp the eyebrows like wow I'm really
thankful for both the positivity and
also the negativity on YouTube over the
past few years because it's made me a
way more confident person a way more
comfortable person a way happier person
and also I won't say this with
confidence
oh hey better-looking person as well
thank God for this cologne personality
aside though the makeup in this video
I'm horrified I actually don't think
there was a single product or technique
honestly that I still use my everyday
makeup routine now that we've gotten
watching this out of the way thank God I
have all my favorite makeup products
here that I now use on an everyday at
daily basis and I want to try to
recreate this same exact look that
actually make it look really really bomb
really really beautiful and hopefully
actually show up and look nice and a
good studio setup so let's get clean
alright so starting off my routine today
I am NOT going to be color correcting I
have probably not color corrected it
honestly probably since that video so
for a foundation today I'm gonna go to
the Born This Way Foundation from Too
Faced you guys know this is my all time
a holy girl favourite in the original
video I was using the Make Up For Ever
Ultra HD liquid foundation which I
actually think is kind of funny because
if you know me and even around for a
very very long time you know that before
born this way I was actually using the
makeup forever stick foundation and that
was kind of like my Holy Grail that I
used forever so I don't even know why I
was using the liquid version in that
video because I generally cannot ever
remember liking that but guess I did so
end up on the sin I was gonna be using
the morphe Cod or highlighting sponge I
absolutely love this one if you want to
get this these Co J's for 10% off
putting it in now since I apparently
couldn't
three years ago cuz had a good shade
match I still can't tell what are you
three years later I still don't know how
to match my foundation once AI
foundation all over my actual face I'm
gonna grab just a big fluffy foundation
brush and dip into the same color and
this one this all down my neck
apparently I did not know how to
two years ago despite the fact that I
literally made a joke about Moses
parting the foundation see still
couldn't match it so I'm gonna make sure
that no matter what color my face is
today my neck is the same shade for good
suitors today and no surprises here I'm
just going to get my shape tape
concealer this one's gonna be in the
shade affair and I also have the shade
light natural to mix together as well
because this one is a little bit light
definitely do not want to be rushed back
Mary that is for sure I think in the
original video I was using the LA girl
Pro concealer I actually still like that
concealer a lot but shaving peepers
definitely a lot more full coverage the
one thing that I probably changed the
most and like my makeup process aside
for my eyebrows of course it's probably
my base routine which I'm really really
thankful for I used to use a super super
full coverage foundation and super full
coverage concealer and then pack it on
with Cody or some powder which looked
really nice of course for like Instagram
pictures which is literally the only
thing that I was doing but once I
actually started wearing makeup out
though and like actually being in the
real world and taking selfies and
looking in mirrors I quickly realized
how disgusting it looked because it was
so incredibly cakey and the one change
that I really made now is I definitely
prefer a really really light coverage
foundation but just a more full coverage
concealer so I can really focus the
coverage in the areas that I need it and
actually like my normal skin shine
through I've worked really really hard
to clear out my skin and have a good
skin and definite like to show it off
and I think it's just a lot better a lot
more natural as well so definitely like
my base routine now a million times more
all right so everything is blended in
but I'm looking a little bit light
hi mr. spooked first or I want to set my
face in place and add some dimension
back as quickly as possible so first
today I'm gonna go to the Too Faced
peach perfect setting powder
I'll let the Cody air some powder it's
actually not ridiculously drying it's
definitely more of like a light coverage
powder I actually really liked the fact
that this kind of wears down a little
bit throughout the day call me crazy but
my favorite time of like makeup is
probably two to three hours after wear
but it's still looking really really
beautiful but by that time some of your
like natural oils have kind of seeped
through you know that sounds really
gross I just like it to look a little
bit more worn and I feel like it looks
much more natural and it kind of gets
rid of that like vanilla cake mix type
of look
so this powder is definitely my all-time
favorite to achieve that look before I
actually move on to the next time I'm
gonna grab the morphe preppin set
setting spray I really really love this
because it has such a fine mist so I
always use this in-between of the stuff
so a makeup routine whenever I apply a
lot of powder just kind of lock
everything more in place add a little
bit of hydration back and that really
prevents the cakiness that the other
14:1 of different so next I'm going to
contour my face and guess what I'm not
gonna use an orange eyeshadow today I
have with me my Anasazi Beverly Hills
contour kit
I do have an orange in here but this I
use for blush so I'm just gonna got my
morphe emma 405 brush end up into this
cool tone right here on the bottom
corner i don't gonna use this to it just
chisel out my features i'm gonna go in
with a little bit of a light hand with
this as well i know by sound me recalled
the contour in the video i ended up
looking like okay but i remember taking
so many photos a long time ago where my
contour literally looked like a is
strike down my cheekbones it was so ugly
probably because i was using a dark
burnt orange eyeshadow for that but i
just wanna use a light hand and really
use this contour to chisel out my
natural features and not literally
create new ones because that's not the
point and it really does not look good
ever definitely still gonna better - the
5head though definitely a contour out my
jaw line as well the one thing that i
noticed in that video oh my god by java
like definitely looked better two years
ago that it did now how did that even
happen that is literally so unfair I'm
calling the police
I'm not gonna grab the m-52 7 which is a
bigger fluffy brush and dip into this
kind of more a warm tone caramel shade
right next door and I'm gonna use this
it's kind of like a bronze or show you
just one together my natural skin tone
and my contour eventually nose color I'm
gonna grab my JD weighty 182 brush and
dip into that middle shade in the
contour palette once again if you've
been around for a long time you would
know that my nose contour has really had
a quite the dirty
clearly with this video I don't know how
to do it period so that was great and
scary then I got really really good at
it and now actually recently I haven't
even been compromised nose as much and
I've really learned to embrace it a
little bit more kind of fun I love that
journey regardless I'm so good at
contour today and I'm gonna make it not
look an inch long because that looked
about it so let's do that
I'm gonna make sure to place those two
contour lines pretty close together and
blend them out and when it comes to
highlighting them later I'm not going to
use a big Brush so hopefully that'll
help the illusion actually exists next
of course you guys know comes a blush
and first I'm going to be using the Mac
blush and the shaded peaches funny
enough in this video and actually for a
majority of my makeup career I do not
use a blush because I said that I didn't
like it for the longest time I really
felt as though like my cheekbones were
for some reason too high and
couldn't fit blush on there I really
don't know where this thought process
came from it was truly so so so stupid
but in my head at what I first started
doing makeup the only blush clothes that
existed was bright pink which I hated
so finding peaches for me was like a
full-on like Holy Grail revival moment
and now I love blush once again before I
move on to the next time I'm just gonna
do a light spread of the morphe prepping
settings right before we move on to the
next time I am still going to bake my
face but I'm just gonna bake it lightly
as opposed to using a powder puff and
iris pilot like before I'm just gonna
grab my same Beauty Blender and dip into
at the peach setting powder and just
place a slightly underneath any areas
that I have contour just to bring some
of the highlights back by using a Beauty
Blender I'm really melting the product
into the skin which is actually so much
better when it comes to creasing and
bringing highlights back as opposed to a
powder puff which Lauder just makes the
powder sit right on top
well that bakes in place on my face love
all those rhymes that just happen right
there
next I'm gonna move on to my brows now
and you guys know just like the original
video I still to this day usually skip
the brow process and do them off camera
because I don't like the angles of it
but you know what
in honor of today's video I thought I'd
be so much fun to celebrate my borough
transformation god bless and do a little
bit of a brow routine for you guys
because I have not done one in a very
very long time so why not
to start off eyebrows today I'm gonna
use my Anasazi a brow is in the shade
and medium brown I really like using a
brow pencil mainly because a dip brow is
what got me into the whole and James
Charles brick sharpie brow from before
but that's my fault for using it way too
heavy-handed but that's why I really
like a pencil because you can either use
it really really lightly to create those
little hair light strokes in the front
of the brow or you can actually really
press down and layer on and give it a
much more defined look you really get
the best of both worlds so I'm gonna go
right in and I'm gonna first it up by
using a spoolie and just to brush the
hairs upwards to see where my actual
brow is and then I'd like to go in and
start with the tail first
I'm honestly really not sure why
probably because my original brow tail
literally used to end like here and I'm
like triggered over it so I always had
to make sure that it's in the right
place at first before I anything else
gets put on there but I just like to
draw that little point then follow it up
to the top that I always like to define
the lower arch and bring it in I'm
holding the pencil so lightly when I do
this as well literally applying like no
pressure at all once I get to the front
of the brow I'm just going to flick the
pencil upward to kind of create the
illusion
hair strokes I always like to put the
hair strokes in place at first and it's
okay if it looks a little bit messy of
course I had to go to the concealer
after and clean everything once the
bottom of the brow is all taken care of
and is truly all smooth sailing from
here I really just like to get that over
with first because once again it can
really make her break the brow and I
definitely did not want to go back to it
straight bra from before so then once
that's all in place I literally just
take the pencil and I kind of follow
from this area right here that is really
dense and I literally just start to draw
and it's super super light hair strokes
and I'm filling in as I go as well and
then all I do literally once I get right
here it's just cool like that's so that
is the brow all filled in and it's
looking pretty good so far but it
definitely needs to be cleaned up quite
a lot so next I'm just gonna grab that
same exact concealer from before and put
a little dollop on the back of my hand
and then just grabbing my super flat mac
242 brush I'm gonna dip right in and I'm
gonna use this to clean up the bottom of
my brow for me my brush automatically
goes right to the arch and I always pull
it right underneath the tail and then
with any excess product I just bring
that right down to the front oh there we
go see stunty the Nerds gonna use any
excess product on that brush and tap it
into my eyelid to act as an eyelid
primer to get it ready for eyeshadow I'm
just gonna grab my morphe e 20 brush and
dip into it once again at that same
exact setting powder and just lightly
place this right on top when it comes to
the setting powder just like my face I'm
actually not gonna like we set it in
there just because I shadows tend to
stick better and be a lot more pigmented
when they're kind of blended over
something a little bit tacky and now we
were officially ready to recreate this
blue green brown trio chrome serpent
okay so for the eyeshadow look today I
don't actually have like a clear image
of what I want to do which is pretty
rare for me I usually have like a vision
and then just go right in but being that
the original look was so bad and also so
poorly documented because the lighting I
don't even know what this was supposed
to look like so what I'm just gonna like
throw something together that would
remind me now of like serpent
well even like why would know why I got
that I think I'm just gonna start off
doing this I look in the same order as
the original video and see where it goes
I'm gonna start off by grabbing my
morphe m4 33
stepping into a light cool tone brown
shade and is putting that right in the
crease I'm just going to blend this very
very lightly I'm gonna grab that I'm
five-eleven
and put more of that on there because I
have a feeling that this is gonna get
pretty dark now I'm gonna grab at the m4
33 again and tip into a little bit of a
darker tone Brown I'm gonna place that
in the crease to add a little bit more
dimension into this I literally don't
know what I want to do it for this
eyeshadow look I know in the original it
looked like I was using a like teal aqua
metallic shade all over the lid and then
I put like a metallic light green in the
center but then I called it blue
somewhere there was blue in the
waterline and it's going in pretty
lightly and using back and forth motions
using the excess product that's still
left on this brush just make sure that
there's an even transition between it
that light brown and the darker brown
shade it's looking at pretty good so far
but I don't really know what I'm doing
so I'm gonna go the ab 178 brush it's
that I just a tiny little concealer
brush and dip into a metallic like aqua
watery looking shade oh that's pretty
ot that looks good okay okay okay okay
no places over here as well I guess I'm
just gonna fill this into a layer of the
blue over top I'm just gonna mix
together a dark blue and a dark green
and put this right up in here to blend
this together because I don't want this
halo eye to be like really really cut so
this whole mix that brown and the blue
together I really should've done this
before placing that metallic shade on
there because now this metallic sheen is
gonna get in the crease but everybody
makes mistakes and this original look
was one of them so before I move on to
us let's halo eye I'm gonna grab that
dark brown shade again and just go right
over that little area because that
blending is scary
oh that looks way better great moving on
let's forget about that please okay so
now I need to make the halo eye look
like an actual halo eye duh so I'm gonna
grab an e 37 it's actually a little
liner brush I know most people like to
use a little pocket brush for their halo
eyes but for some reason I have like
this weird flap of skin that covers my
inner corner really rude really annoying
do not ask for it to be there but I
really need to like tuck shadow into
that region so what I'm gonna do is grab
the
blue in the dark green once again that I
just used to darken the crease and place
that right up in there I'm gonna pull
that right and on top of that metallic
shade oh yeah this looks good and we're
just gonna pull that color combo into
like a v-shape in the outer corner you
guys know I love really waiting out my
shadow even honestly if we're like
around looks like a halo eye I'll still
wing it out just a little bit for some
reason round
eye looks just really it's not flat on
my face shape so just kind of wing it
out for a real one then we got that dark
brown once again and I'm going to go
over that outer edge and blend that
because it's already looking ugly and I
don't want to make it look any worse I'm
now gonna grab my NAT 2 4 brush and I'm
gonna dip into a lighter aqua shade and
I'm gonna put this after spritzing it
right on the center of the layer to
further accentuate the halo moment okay
now I'm happy where the woowoo god bless
okay so I'm gonna leave the shadow how
it is because at this point I am
horrified at making this look worse I
cannot have my three year anniversary
video be equally as bad as the first one
so what I am going to do though is grab
the Urban Decay liner in the shade of
distortion and it's like this bluey
green purple glitter moment it's a
serpent and I'm just gonna put this
glitter right on that cut crease moment
to really make it shine and I'm gonna
pull that right down as well right into
the center of that halo eye I'm gonna
grab this powder brush and dust off the
fallout because there's a lot of it for
some reason now for the lower lash line
I think I'm going to mimic the halo onto
the lower lash line as well it's been a
long day I'm first gonna grab but this
brush is the M 149 and I'm going to tap
into the dark blue and green shades once
again and put those right up against the
lash and then I was gonna use that same
fluffy brush from before and grab the
light brown shade and go right below
that lightly just connecting at that
outer V a transition color right into
deep blue just to tie everything
together
could I put the same aqua shade on the
lower lash line as well then it's gonna
place that teal shade right
in the middle then just got me a little
bit of the mermaid's pigment from
peaches makeup one of my all-time
favorite brands when it comes to colitas
and pigments and popping up right in the
center oh that's pretty
Wow one thing goes right whoa okay so
next I want to highlight my brow bone
and the inner corner just to add more
dimension to this eye look so it'll
really tart pigment in the shade of top
yacht I absolutely love this for
highlighting it's literally one of the
brightest things I've ever seen in my
entire life and I'm going to place that
right in there oh so pretty okay then
right on the brow bone for lashes of
course you guys should know at this
point I'm gonna use my all-time
favorites Lily lashes in the style on
Miami you can use code James for 15% off
your purchase Lily as well but I'm going
to trim them first to avoid the whole
wonky loss situation and gluing my eye
shot because that is not fun um so what
I'm gonna do is just grab these with a
pair of tweezers and I'm gonna cut off a
spike from each end just so they fit my
eyes a little bit better then I'm gonna
apply a light layer of the duo of brush
on and glue and then while that's
getting tacky I'm gonna pop on a really
light coat of the Mac extended play out
mascara and then looking at my we're
from right below I'm gonna hold this
lash up and I'm gonna plop it right onto
my lash line finishing it off with a
little bit of mascara right on the lower
lash line that was quite the journey
there is lots of bumps in the road but
we got there in the end are we looking
the best No
are we looking okay that's for you to
decide but regardless that is one blue
green and brown trio chrome serpent I
complete I'm not going through the other
one off camera so I don't literally die
in the next few minutes but I'll be
right back to finish how threats of this
block be right back
let's go ahead and finish the rest of
this look before I decide that I hate it
again our first finisher left by just
wiping away this bake that's been
sitting here for like literally eight
hours now while I finished those eyes
I'm also going to wipe off the excess
underneath my
oddballs as well so next was going to be
our highlighter but before we do that
once again I'm gonna grab my trusty at
prepping set setting spray and just meld
everything together and this also is
gonna be the highlighter stick a whole
lot more too so we get that really
blinding glow and for my hair today I'm
gonna grab not a large brush this is the
a 501 great highlighter brush that won't
ruin my entire face that makeup and I'm
just going to dip into my highlighter
pop that right on the cheekbone and now
for the nose highlight what I'm going to
do is not grab a large fluffy brush this
is the e36 it is a tiny pencil brush and
I'm going to use this to highlight the
tip of my nose Wow look at that so tiny
so beautiful and not an inch wide
that is how I notice how it's supposed
to look okay so far less if we have the
lips now in my original video I did a
chocolate brown lip with a green and
blue pigment over top sorry we're not
doing that today because that looked
disgusting so what I'm going to do
instead is take a lip that is much more
flattering to this look and nude I'm
gonna start by lining them using my
all-time favorite lip liner this is from
colour-pop X I love sonic e in the shade
curvy and then over top I'm gonna grab
the anasazi liquid lipstick in the shade
it stripped and just put that right in
the middle and while I definitely do not
want to put on a blue green pigment what
I am gonna do just to finish off the lip
today is out on a tiny bit of gloss
right in the center just to give it a
little bit more a dimension all right
you guys we're gonna finish it off with
some sister settings Mary one last time
just to lock everything in place and
finally that is the completed blue brown
green serpent
a child
[Music]
three hours later I had finally been
able to show you guys three years for
skill improvement and I really really
hope you guys enjoyed this videos today
this look was quite a little bit of a
roller coaster to go through but then
again the original luck was really
neither good nor fresh so I still feel
like in the end we came up with a really
really beautiful look and I actually
like how this turned out
a hot I really hope you guys enjoyed
this video too and a little trip down
memory lane
I cannot believe I've been doing this
job for three long years but you guys
truly do such an amazing job at always
making me feel like I just started
yesterday I mean seriously the same time
fives are having fun I think really
really applies here thank you for making
the last three years so amazing and so
memorable
thank you guys always for all your
constant love and support it truly means
so much to me and it does not go
unnoticed if you enjoyed this little
trip down memory lane and you also like
my updated version of my circuit makeup
look please don't forget to give this
video a big thumbs up down below and
also come subscribe and join this
sisterhood by taking that big red button
down below and like the belt icon so you
can get a notification every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me and I makeup tourney can
follow me on Instagram or Twitter they
are both the same Charles and my
snapshot for more but I haven't seen
sites up it seems Charles to the next
row asked after Charles this videos
sister shout out goes to sister Carly
thank you so much love froy's following
in supporting you I love you literally
so so so much and if you would like to
the next videos sister shout out don't
forget to always a retweet my video
links and they go live on Twitter all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching this video today
thank you and Leslie for the last three
years of my life I love you and I'll see
you in the next one
[Music]