hi sisters James hi sisters James
Charles here and welcome back to our
YouTube channel jumping right to the
point of this video because it's
probably going to be a quite a long one
if you guys did not know over on my
Instagram which is just James Charles if
you did not follow me come to him the
Instagram sisterhood it's where I got my
start and I post a lot of a really bomb
selfies over there but every single
Sunday on my Instagram story I pick
weina really talented and creative
artists to take over my Ivy story and
give you guys a tutorial I am so blessed
to have a job where I get to share my
artwork with the world and inspire you
guys I've been having so much fun with
lurking and creepily stalking on your
guys's Instagram pages and I have
literally been so beyond shocked at how
much talent we have in this sisterhood
and I have been getting so much
inspiration from you guys some of you
guys are literally some of the most
incredible makeup artists I have ever
seen it but for today's video I asked
some of you guys to tweet me your
favorite makeup looks that you've ever
done on yourself and I'm gonna do my
best and matching your crazy talent
levels and recreated them on my face I
think it'll be really fun to see how our
different styles compare and it also
will be quite a little bit of a
challenge because I will say that I
picked three pretty awesome looks for
this first video I definitely wanna do
more of these in the future so if you
guys ever post our makeup books and
you're just feeling it so proud of it
please tweet it to me tied me I want to
see all your guys's crazy beautiful art
but without further ado keep on watching
it you never know your luck may be in
this video let's get started the first
thing I want to try to recreate today is
this one which is sent in by Rocio seja
if you guys do not know who she is you
have to check her out an Instagram but
she does the most beautiful colourful
looks I've ever seen in her talent level
is literally unreal you have to go check
her out she was with me and the benefit
broad competition so she definitely has
a special place in my heart but let's be
real a girl can blend and this is
definitely gonna be a really really hard
challenge one she tweeted me this she
literally said good luck sister so
challenge accepted so after looking at
all of Rho cos work I noticed that the
one thing she hasn't common with all of
her looks like the little stamp of Rocio
approval is she has a little star here
on the inner corner and I know that she
does this using a sticker so I want you
to start today to look for star stickers
and these foam glitter stars with the
only thing I could find this is probably
gonna get really messy and really
annoying but
it's gonna go ahead and I'm gonna pop
one of these right on my inner corner
hello
let's try that again what that is
definitely a way to bigger stars and
sister Rose here we usually use this but
you know what
so the colors did her luck today are
obviously a rainbow so I figured the
best palate to use for this would be the
morphine 35b it has all colors of the
rainbow I love this palette and you can
use code James for 10% off I'm gonna
grab it M 4-3-3 brush and dip into this
bright yellow shade down in here I'm
gonna start by packing that into the
inner corner she also always brings her
shadow all the way up to her brow bone
as well and kind of almost blends into
her brows but I feel like I have a lot
more eyelid space in rocío so I'm just
gonna keep it more concentrated towards
the crease region I'm next time I go to
another clean and 4-3-3 brush and dip
into this shade right here and I'm gonna
pack this right here kind of in the
center of the eyelid her rainbow colors
are literally always so incredibly
pigmented and boy I have no idea what
the heck she does to get her shadow I
was like this I always have to build
them up so intensely I'm gonna go back
into the some more yellow and make sure
that those two colors are really
seamlessly blended together I'm mixing
to grab another clean and 4-3-3 and dip
into this bright blue shade right up in
this corner here and pop that right next
to the green a few weeks ago I did a
favorite brushes haul on my incertum
stories which is still highlighted by
the way so if you want to go check that
out
how'd it rich my tensor time and go look
at all my favorite brushes and of course
you get your discount but when I was
talking about blending brushes I of
course mentioned the m4a3 which you guys
saw was like my all-time favorite brush
and I said that I had 27 of these so
many people were like why the hell do
you need 27 of the same eyeshadow brush
well I already used three so far this is
why our next to go with a matte 514 and
dip into this bright purple shade and
use just to finish off my little outer V
how did she get her shadows to be so
pigmented I'm next to have a little bit
of my Mac select cover-up concealer and
I Mac 252 brush and I'm just going to
carve out a little bit of like a halo
eye type situation next I grab this
bright teal shade on a flat Packer brush
and I'm going to stretch it with some
mac fix+ to make that shadow
super duper intense and we're going to
pack that right on the center of that
little halo eye we just carved out
I'm gonna use those thing instead colors
I did before and create the same that
pattern of the rainbow just inside of
that little halo eye we carved out when
applying the shadows I'm more padding
and tapping them into place as opposed
to kind of like souping them and like
brushing them on in circular motions I
really want these clothes to be the most
pigmented they can possibly be and we're
gonna achieve that by packing them on
and then to really make that halo eye
pop I'm gonna grab the Mac reflex teal
and pop that right on the center I think
this came out like okay
damn Rocio has talent I did not think it
was gonna be this hard for the lower
lash that I'm gonna grab another fluffy
brush and go in with the bright red
shade and I'm gonna pop that right on at
the outer corner and then some orange
right in the middle of that lower lash
line
and then going back into the inner
corner with some of that yellow to
finish off the lower lash line at
Rainbow and last certainly not least for
the shadow portion of this look I'm
gonna go a just done some packing brush
from morphe and the sugar pills single
shadow in the shade taco this is
probably the most pigmented white eye
shadow there is this one is so so so
bomb I'm gonna dip right in it to that
shade and get a whole lot on the brush
and hopefully fingers crossed that this
foam star sticker works I'm gonna pop
this right here for my final reveal I
really hope this worked I'm gonna grab
some tweezers and I'm going to peel off
the star that is probably the worst I've
ever seen for once this is not my fault
I blame this one on the sticker and then
to finish off the stuff today I'm gonna
pop on the makeup shock lashes in the
style onyx
I know roseola loves these and uses
these all the time
okay guys that is what I all complete
I'm gonna go ahead and do the one
off-camera quickly and I'll be right
back with the finished roasty oh say hot
look okay that's that about one hour now
I am finished the other eye and I am
back with the completed look and I just
want to say good lord in heaven about
this was literally so hard to do like I
already had an immense amount of respect
for Rocio before as an artist but trying
to actually recreate her I'm a little
shocked right now this look is not my
best looking at the original picture her
blending work is impeccable her colors
are beyond pigmented and her crease is
so costly perfectly there's like a nice
bright
Shyne right in the middle and of course
her star on the inner corner is looking
perfect I think I got the entire look
the star was actually at the hardest
part but like I said blaming it on the
stickers I tried to outline it with some
white eyeliner to make it look a little
bit more defined but it is really not
looking the best major applause for her
and hats off because she's such a
talented artist like I said if you guys
do not know who she is or if you've not
seen her work before please go check her
out for a far far far better and more
talented version of this and yeah that
is the Rose feel look all complete okay
guys so the first thing I want to
recreate today was sent in by an artist
I follow on Twitter by the name of Ivy
kongu she is so incredibly talented and
so beautiful when she sent this that I
literally at guard I think I have a
really fun way to kind of put my own
twist on this when I saw this I just
thought it was so stunning the shadows
are so bright and pigmented and the
contrast between the shadows and her
skin color literally like so incredibly
beautiful so I'm gonna try my best to do
Ivies injustice and put my own sister
James twist on her look today okay so
I'm first gonna start by grabbing my
morphe M 513 fluffy brush and my
radioactive pigment from melt cosmetics
these shadows are so incredibly
pigmented and I really want this look to
be very very bright and vibrant so just
gonna take this on my brush and I'm
gonna pop this right on this inner
corner area I'm really gonna press that
shadow in there because we are going to
be covering out the crease so this can
be a little bit messy I just want these
colors to be extremely extremely vibrant
I'm next gotta good with my morphe i'ma
4-3-3 brush and dip into this bright
purple shade right up in here I'm gonna
use this to put it in my outer crease
and shape out an outer V as well once
again I'm gonna start off by really
packing this color in there and pressing
it end to make the colors super super
pigmented and then kind of go in
afterwards and blend them together I am
gonna be adding a winged liner so to
kind of follow through with that shape
I'm just gonna take that brush and I'm
going to press it right in on that outer
corner to kind of create that v-shape
and then just connect it up to that
crease region just like that before we
go in and blend out the edges because
they're looking a little bit wonky at
this point I'm going to take a little
bit more of that purple on the same
exact brush and packed it on the outer
lid just to get ready for the base of
that half-cooked crease
looking at Ivy's photo she definitely
has a very very high contrast in that
look so to add a little bit more
contrast to my look today I'm gonna go
my morphe I'm a 506 brush and dip into
it the black and the bottom
35b and i just a little bit of that in
the outer V be sure to not go crazy I'm
just gonna wiggle a little bit of the
shadow into that outer corner and kind
of pull it out just do your slightest
bit just to add some more dimension and
that is plenty enough and I'm gonna go
back in with Maya I'm four three three
brush that I just used with that purple
shade dip into a little bit more purple
and then just go right over that edge so
to make sure that the block doesn't get
everywhere to carve out the half cut
crease I'm gonna use my steel out liquid
metals and the shade rose gold retro
this one is a little bit more orange
tone that I would have liked but I'm
gonna layer over top of it using the
Urban Decay glitter liner in this shade
grind to make it a little bit more pinky
I'm gonna dip back into that radioactive
pigment using another m4 3:3 brush and
I'm gonna go right over that edge
between the purple and the shadow we
just put down and then going back into
some more purple on the outer corner and
then like I said going into that urban
decay at glitter liner to make it more
pink other than that crease is cut for
the gods and all dried out I'm gonna add
a lilac liquid liner today using the la
splash Pro artist liner in the shade
psychedelic this purple isn't as bright
as I want it to be so I'm gonna grab the
Makeup Forever aqua XL liner and this is
in the shade I don't even know it's the
light purple and I'm gonna go over top
of that with this I don't know what was
going on here but I was definitely
having some liner troubles I just
finished up the wing using that Makeup
Forever aqua XL liner and then use some
concealer to clean up below it because
it was getting a little bit messy but
for lust I'm gonna pop on something nice
and light and simple which of course you
guys know my Lily lashes in the style
Miami these are like at this point kind
of the only eye lashes I wear but
they're just so pretty and they'll fit
perfectly with this look because clearly
we want to show off what's going on on
the eyelid but my lower lash line roots
gonna go that same exact a dark purple
shade on my I'm 4-3-3 brush and pop this
in the outer corner right up against
that lash line then popping that pink
shade right on the inner corner to
connect it back up and then taking my
Abbot 1 v 1 brush and dipping into this
dark purple shade right down here I'm
mixing it with the slightest bit a black
I'm going to use this to connect
the outer corner up to the wing I'm
really hugging the shade right up
against that lashline because I don't
want everything to get too dark and
muddy and then just pulling this right
up against that lilac little wing I
really want my eyes to look big and have
a lot of attention drawn to them so I'm
next I grab my benefit high brow pencil
which is a pink like wax pencil this is
normally for highlighting your brows but
I'm pretty sure it's isafe don't quote
me on that
maybe don't have this at home but I'm
just gonna pop this right on the lower
lashline to really open my eyes and make
them look huge okay guys that is one eye
all complete for right now I definitely
have a few more things that I want to
add to this look but I'm gonna do the
other one off camera quickly to save
some time and I'll be right back all
right sighs design back with the
finished look but I'm honestly loving
how this looks so far sister I have you
put little hearts right here to kind of
fit together like the whole love theme
but we're gonna take it one step further
so I grab these like little glitter
hearts that I found in my clitoris we're
gonna even have these but I'm gonna pop
a little bit of these right underneath
my eyes to be like kind of a glitter to
your type of situation I'm just gonna
apply this using the violet Voss glitter
adhesive and just put a little bit of
this right up in here then just rushing
those on using up my finger and then
finally to finish off this look today
I'm going to add some heart freckles
using some different shades of pink and
purple liquid lipstick all from Oprah
these are in the shades of Laguna Beach
Las Vegas Panama and mocha and this
isn't forever I looked at I saw Nikita
drag and do it she looked so cute so I'm
gonna do it myself as well today
okay so honestly this look kind of got
real intense real fast I'm honestly not
sure if I'm loving the heart freckles
but you know what
I made the decision it is way too late
so we're gonna rock them now and I
finished off this look I'm just going to
go on in the ofra liquid lipstick in
Laguna Beach right guys and that is this
lovesick look inspired by sister ivy
kongu all complete this definitely was
not exactly what I envisioned it
originally but I am definitely really
proud of how this came out I think that
the eye look is literally so sunny I
definitely want to do a lot more looks
using this like pasta eyeliner I think
it's such a nice stark contrast from the
usual black liquid liner I'm honestly
like those looks really really bomb and
I hope you guys really really liked it
too and sister Ivy if you're watching I
hope I did you proud let's move on to
the next transformation okay so the next
thing I want to recreate today is this
one from it make drew on it hello Vicki
there you go Mick drew on Twitter the
next look I want to recreate today is
this one which was sent in by it Mick
drew on Twitter it is like this cool
tone or brown cut crease with a pop of
light blue in the inner corner I think
it is so stunning and so beautiful and
I've actually not done a cut crease at a
hot minute so I'm gonna do it this look
today please leave Nora my nose baking
as well I've had to take off part of my
makeup like three times out there at the
point of this video to try to do all
these looks and one day this has been a
really intense but assisters nose needs
to be snatched no matter what so just
roll with me here okay so when Drew's
look she definitely knows like all whole
Tom Browns and I actually don't have a
single palette that's like all cool
tones I definitely need to get that so
if you know of any lettuce sister no but
I'm gonna be using the morphe 39a today
because I feel like they're like you
cool tone Browns up in here we're gonna
make it work I'm first gonna start my
carving Miami 513 which is a fluffy
blending brush and dipping into this
light brown
cool tool in transition shade and
putting this in the shape of a cut
crease when I do my cut crease I like to
keep the shadows focused kind of above
the lid just for a more lifted and
really really large eye look but you can
obviously place your shadows wherever
your heart desires
I'm gonna grab a slightly smaller
blending brush this is the M 4-3-3 you
guys know I have like literally a
million of these in my collection in it
they're so good and I'm gonna dip into
this slightly darker brown shade it
right up in here and use this to it to
find out the crease a little bit more
I'm just gonna play says once again in
that same shape following my natural
crease and
pulling it out towards the end screw
that cut crease shape that we all know
and love to finish off the shadow
portion already on my m56 too and dip
into this kind of slightly warm tone of
cranberry dark brown up in here and I'm
gonna pop this just the slightest bit in
the crease I really like using this to
just get the slightest bit of definition
in cut creases and stuff like that
because you're able to kind of put the
color on and bonds it out at the same
time without putting it everywhere now
that we have the general shape and
blending of the cut crease all complete
I wonder grabbed as any folk harbors
concealer this is the max I like to
cover up and I'm gonna be using the Mac
252 brush I just found this from
Mitchell and Stacy Maria I'm doing an
Instagram and I have been obsessed with
this brush recently and I'm just gonna
use this to carve out my crease okay so
don't do what I just did and rush
through the carving of the crease
because it clearly this is not the shape
that we're going for today I was
definitely a way too confident and that
crease cutting situation so let's try
this again
I used to be literally so good at cut
crease is what is going on right now
okay doing this cut crease that I just
humbled me right off it has been a way
too long since I've done one clearly it
is showing in this work here this is not
my best status for sure but we're gonna
keep on talking and hopefully those will
come together at the end I'm gonna grab
a tiny brush just like this I dip into
the same dark brown shade and start
sketching out my wing just like a
regular wing liner I'm gonna pull this
right up out from the outer corner I'm
gonna pull the shade a little bit under
the lower lash line as well does because
we are obviously gonna be putting shadow
there so that helps get the wing shape
nice and correct I'm gonna use this same
shadow to lately pack on the shape of a
winged liner and not making this too
thick because we're gonna be doing a
little bit of an ombre waiting today
grabbing our original transition shade
I'm gonna grab a small fluffy brush just
like this one and lightly go over the
edge to kind of buff and blend it out so
we have an ombre a wing so that is the
ombre smoky liner all complete but
clearly it got a little bit messy so I'm
gonna go Miami four three two you guys
know this is my favorite concealer brush
for doing under the brows but it's also
great because it's flat so I'm gonna
grab just a little bit more of that
concealer and I'm going to lightly go
over that edge and cut out the
there we go now we're talking since we
already went ahead and put a little bit
of that darkness on the lower lash line
it from before all I'm gonna do is grab
my original transition sheet on a fluffy
brush and just bring that right under
the lower lash line connecting it up top
to that wing and just finishing it off
for the pop-up blue in the inner corner
I'm gonna grab my morphia 35 B palette
and just any old fluffy brush this one
will do this happens to be another 33
I'm gonna dip it right into right here
and just pop this right in the inner
corner I'm not gonna put too much blue
here because we definitely want to do a
light base so the pigment really picks
up that blue sheen and then finally for
that pop in the inner corner I'm gonna
grab my Mac reflex teal this is my
all-time favorite glitter slosh penguins
I don't even know what this would be
considered but whatever it doesn't
matter I'm gonna pop that right in the
inner corner that is what I'm talking
about oh my god this is so pretty
I love this then I'm just gonna pop on a
wispy pair of lashes all right sister
status one eye all complete I feel like
for the amount of issues we were having
earlier on we somehow managed to pull it
together this is looking so beautiful so
far but I'm gonna go in and do the other
one off camera quickly and I'll be right
back with the finished look all right
guys I am back with the other eye all
complete this one was much easier to do
off camera thank God I don't know what
was going on here but I think we
definitely pulled this together to
finish off the look I decided some more
glow and some more highlighter anasazi
yeah so Hollywood as always and then I
paired the lip with Anasazi Ashtyn
liquid lipstick and this is the
completed look inspired by it make Dru
Marquez and those are all three looks
complete for the day whoo my face has
had way too much makeup on but honestly
filming this that has been so much fun I
really enjoyed looking through all the
different pictures that you guys
submitted to me honestly it some of you
guys are so beyond talented and I'm so
excited for more instagrams sister
takeovers in the future and I definitely
want to do more videos like these so if
you guys did enjoy it please don't
forget to make a thumbs up down below
and like I said earlier if you ever
create a make a book that you were so
proud of tag me in it tweet it to me at
hashtag James Charles so I can take a
look if you have not already made sure
to click that big red subscribe button
down below so you can join the
sisterhood and click that Bell icon so
you can be notified every time I upload
a brand new video if you'd like to
follow me on my makeup turn you can
follow me on Instagram or Twitter
they're both is James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes I'm
self is James Charles the next row ask
after Charles
this big sister shadow goes to sister
crab thank you so much maybe for always
falling in supporting and I love you so
much and if you would like to be the
next video sisters no doubt it makes the
detroit free tweet video links when they
go live on a twitter all right guys
thank you so much watching this video
today i really hope you enjoyed it all
of you guys are so beyond talented i am
literally shaking in my boots y'all
they're coming for my career but i love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]