hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as we
all know Instagram was one of the
biggest social media apps in the entire
world obviously though I've been using
Instagram way more than normal recently
because of their new filters now when
Instagram first released arrays I feel
like not many people really care about
that because the filters on there
weren't that great at all so we had all
had snapped out for the last like
several several years snapchat gave us
the dog filter the skin soothing filter
and also the flower crown filter I mean
truly what else more could you really
need well apparently the answer to that
is quite a lot because recently
Instagram but took the crown out of the
ability for users on the app to actually
submit their own face filters and oh my
god it was quite the game-changer over
the last few months there have been a
ton of filters to go a very very viral
on Instagram because of how cute they
are
and I found myself wanting to open up my
stories to take selfies literally all
the time so for today's video I thought
it'd be a really cool challenge to try
to create Instagram filters in real life
using makeup like this one this one and
this one so if you guys want to see how
I created these looks keep on watching
[Music]
all right you guys something right into
today's video as you can see I already
pretty much have my entire base are that
most of these filters are based on like
either eyeshadow looks or just different
art things on the base they're going to
add on top of this but if you do want to
see how I created this base make sure
you like right up here and check out my
new updated makeup routine I've been
using a lot of new products and a lot of
techniques and I go super in-depth so
make sure you guys check that out if you
want to get to this stage before we
actually throw on the filters out of all
the filters that I've seen recently one
of my favorite ones to use myself is
this one which is called a blue
butterflies by a girl as you guys can
see it smooth out the skin add some full
crackles and also some cute little blue
butterflies at different places on the
face and it makes the lips a little bit
more plump so I'm going to try to
recreate this one using makeup the first
thing that we're gonna do for this
makeup look is to add on some faux up
freckles so I'm just gonna take a tiny
little liner brush so this is the m25
0-0 and a little bit of a brow powder
and just add on some cute little dots
I've done a few different videos on fake
freckles before on my channel but just
to recap I'm using it different varying
pressures all throughout some of the
freckles are a little bit more pigmented
and some look like they are more
underneath the skin it'd be more natural
obviously better then it's going to top
anything in as well fake freckles are my
favourite steps to do in any makeup
routine and they look so cute but I will
say they are pretty challenging to do it
definitely takes quite a lot of practice
to get them to look real and natural so
it's all about different techniques and
seeing what works best for your skin
tone and then just on top I'm gonna take
a little fluffy brush and dip into that
same little brow shade a tub of any
excess product and then just kind of
lately like splotch this into what the
area this just adds back a little bit
more dimension into it the freckles and
kind of gives them more like sunkissed
look now I'm going to zoom you guys in
and we're gonna draw a butterfly all
right you guys so I took a photo myself
with this filter which obviously is okay
but I just went ahead and zoom to end so
that way I'm able to kind of use the own
filter as a reference when it comes to
drawing this on so I'm just gonna first
start off with a tiny little brush and I
guess try butterfly so the first one
it's like on the cheekbone like right
here so I'm scared okay
here making a little bit thicker at the
top and it is at the bottom usually for
me I prefer the opposite but
[Music]
that's a really bad joke sorry but I'm
gonna draw the two little wings Oh No
this might be a lot harder than I
thought it was guys oh oh okay and I'm
just gonna kinda mirror that on the
other side that looks so bad maybe if
it's colored it won't look like as awful
now just gonna grab some liquid lipstick
colors on the back of my hand I'm going
to start mixing together the different
tones for this butterfly and I'm just
gonna you know start filling this in and
really hope that it comes together
because right now it's not looking great
first I'm mixing together a super light
sky-blue tone and I'm going to put that
in the wings just like this the good
thing about like with up sticks too is
that they do what dry down so I won't
have to set them with eyeshadow
hopefully I'm even gonna take a little
bit of white as well and put that at the
very very like edges of the wings to
hopefully make a little bit brighter
then I'm gonna use a deeper blue tone or
that same little liner brush and put
this towards the middle of the butterfly
to create that like illusion of a shadow
as if the wings are opening grabbing
even darker blue shade I'm just gonna
add a little bit more dimension into the
very inner parts and also connecting and
like that wing up just like that because
it'll be a shadow in the middle okay
that doesn't look that bad I didn't
think I wanted to set this with shadow
but I honestly think I'm going to just
because some of the liquid lipstick is
like a little bit shiny still and I
really want to make sure it's fully and
matte so I'm just gonna go out at the
mini palette and grabbing a little bit
of a playground on a flat brush having a
little bit of a flashback just to
highlight yes okay now doing that same
exact thing a book and I use the little
bits the co-op's adding in some
dimension in the wings right up against
the edges of the butterfly and then
creating some super thin little fine
strokes like that into the body as well
it was good now I need to use a tiny
liner to outline the butterfly it's so
better got Maya tomforde liner I'm gonna
carefully outline this and also create
the shapes that are inside the witness
okay dot you can't tell me that's not
cute that is cute and now last but
finally not least I'm going
to add a few more super tiny dots about
light blue just on the bottom Horsemen
of that wing okay that's cute that is
cute that looks good right all right you
guys didn't think that is one of the
butterflies all complete I was
definitely a little bit nervous at first
but I think this is one of those type of
art pieces that definitely takes a lot
of like layering to get to the final
result and I think it looks pretty cute
I'm gonna speed through and add two more
than John's with my face then we'll come
back to finish off this look all right
you guys these are all three of the
butterflies all completes and I think
this looks so cute I'm literally
obsessed at this and very much Randy of
the blue a butterfly look from the
campaign last year and now our brand new
intro graphics um you could definitely
stop right here but I want to keep going
to turn this kind of hold filter into a
look I'm just gonna add on a subtle
little blue winged liner just kind of
like weighing up my eyes out so grabbing
this wider brush this is the ambit 213
and I'm gonna dip into a little bit of a
playground on this brush and I'm just
going to kind of smudge just on my lash
line in the shape of a wing but not
worrying about it being too defined
focusing at majority of this color on
the outer portion of my eyelid to really
focus on pulling it upwards okay with
any extra healthy Russian was going to
lightly buff out that edge because I do
not want it to be a super defined line
and now I'm just going to grab a an
angled brush and dip into a cola the
dark blue shade of the pallet once again
and use this to make a little bit more
of like a defined weighing one thing I'm
just really pushing the shadow into with
the lash line and I'm only gonna focus
this color on that outer corner and wing
and then you guys know what my little
new trick just gonna spritz that brush
and get any excess shadow on there wet
pinch it together so it's super sharp
and then create a tiny little line right
in that inner corner yes oh my gosh
that's okay actually I'm happy I did
this oh yeah then with my little
concealer brush from my foundation
beforehand describing a tiny little bit
of concealer cleaning up that wing oh my
gosh I just applied some mascara using
my Mac extended Piatt and I'm just gonna
pop on my pair of Lily lashes at Miami
flares wow this is a pretty when they
snap all right both hands now complete
and we are so close at the end we only
have one step left and that is of course
the lips now the Instagram filters for
some reason always like to make the lips
like NASA
and I feel like it's only appropriate to
a follow suit so I'm going to grab my
irregular lip liner which is pervy from
colour-pop and I'm going to go a little
bit crazy you could do over lining today
because actually okay no it does well
no it's crazy imagine I come back the
next video like my sister's Jane Charles
her local dog to each other I was
popping on some lipstick and finally
gonna top this off some gloss all right
you guys and this is the blue butterfly
at filter by agar on Instagram all
complete I am obsessed with how this
left turn out I honestly would have no
problem walking out like this in public
a little details on the butterflies were
a little bit challenging at first but I
think we definitely got the hang of it I
think that you guys could easily
replicate this at home if you do
definitely tweet me a photo and make
sure you tag gege as well for credit of
course but now it is time to move on to
the next love the next filter that I
really want to use today is one that
I've been seeing out quite a lot
recently and that is a cloudy day by
Brian now I really like this one because
it is a little bit more simplistic
there's no like crazy reshaping like
some of the other filters but it is
super cute with just some white clouds
on the cheeks which should be pretty
easy to recreate with makeup and then I
have a really fun idea for the eye
shadow look as well alright eBay so
literally all we're gonna need for this
look is a white cream paint or liquid
lipstick or white concealer literally
anything that you have in your
collection and then also a white
eyeshadow today of course I can be using
the morphe axioms Charles the shade
flashback and the palette because it is
super super pigmented and also a little
concealer brush this is the morphe m22
for literally what i'm gonna do is just
take a little bit of this concealer on
this brush but I'm going to go in and
you see a little bit of like a little
nice little hump and then with the
excess concealer I'm just going to
carefully blend
downwards just like that and I'm going
to put another hump right over here and
then you look a little bit right in here
move a little bit over here as well
literally like that took me three
seconds flat now with a little fluffy
brush I'm just going to grab a little
bit of flash back and just set that
concealer in place and then also use it
to kind of buff out that bottom edge
because we do want these clouds to look
very very fluffy and soft on the face we
don't want them to look like they're
like very sharp or anything coming up a
little bit more concealer then do
another one
maybe right over here bboogle for a
smaller ones huh
they went over here to a really tiny one
that's so cute a little cloud floating
in the end okay with any excess powder
I'm just gonna put a little bit more
flash Brown kind of around the cloud
region it just what like looks like I
don't know it's like floating in the sky
or something now I just wanna add a
little bit of dimension to these clouds
so I'm actually gonna pick up the brand
new at morphe at 35 i palette this just
came in the mail this morning and i
opened it right away because this
palette is so beautiful oh my god it is
literally all I see beautiful pastel
shades I'm obsessed this I cannot wait
to create looks with this and this look
today I'm little just gonna be using
this gray shade so you definitely don't
have to use this if you don't want to
just how does he send it next to me but
if you guys do wonder check this out I
would definitely recommend and of course
you can use coaching whisper 10% off I'm
just gonna use the light gray shade to
add some dimensions and between link the
little humps of the clouds okay so that
is pretty much the filter of this
already complete I think it looks super
cute now for the
I had a sneeze coming in that laughs are
you kidding me
Jesus for the eye portion of the slug I
really want to create a white smokey eye
now I'm not sure if this is gonna look
ridiculous but we are going to try it so
I'm just gonna grab a little bit more of
that white concealer and I'm gonna put
it on my eyelid aside from like a cut
crease I don't think I've ever actually
done anything with a white eyeshadow
before which is crazy to think about but
I have wanted to for a very very long
time
so this could look really really cool or
really stupid but I guess we're gonna
find out in a second
honestly that's cool that is cool okay
so I just looked at my last short I just
found these para from Daddy B lashes by
a jenny 69 I love her the absolute most
and the sale is called IG and I think
this is actually perfect for this look I
really like Miami's obviously but I
think they're a little bit too intense
whereas this will look nice and like I
almost want to say like this is really a
girl anime style makeup look so what
this is like very cartoony which I think
will be good I just layered on some
flash back from my palette over top of
the white shade from the other palette
that I was using and literally look at
how much better that looks not to like
to my own horn or anything but to to it
we've handed that alright you guys so
this is pretty much half of the face of
this cloud look all complete I'm gonna
speed through the other half and we'll
be right back to finish off the rest of
the face Wow oh my god this is cute okay
now for our last and final step of this
makeup look I think I just want to put
on like a look at a little ombre oh my
god I'm gonna give a little bit of this
red gloss you know talking about oh that
is everything oh look at that
okay now let's gonna grab a little bit
of the Fenty beauty gloss in the shade
of fussy alright the guys like I said
super super simple that is this a cloudy
day filter by Brian all complete oh my
gosh I love how this one turned out it
was very easy to recreate I think that
you guys could definitely do this at
home I think this look is very light and
gellick almost euphoric if you will this
is a very lucky for his style and makeup
look I like this I definitely wanna try
out more looks with my eye shadow in the
future as well let me know what you guys
think if you recreate this make sure you
tag me and the original creator but
let's move on to our last and final
filter okay I somehow managed to get all
the clouds and the white makeup off my
face and we are back to my normal base
ready for the final filter isn't popular
as I miss Kylie Jenner and it ends this
one which is called a cherry on the cake
by Barbara balance
now as you guys can see there's
definitely more of that like crazy
reshaping a fact that we had in filter
number one so we can do that again at
with those hips and this look these ones
were crazy we have a whole lot of pinky
tone blush which I've been loving
recently some pink eyeliner and then
also two super cute cherries on the
cheekbones which we can draw on with
some liquid lipsticks again there
shouldn't be too hard one to recreate
and I think it looks really awesome so
let's just jump right in alright you
guys so for the first step of this
filter I want to go ahead and add the
pinky toe in a blush all over the face
I'm gonna use this blush from that
called dolly mix and just this little
cute chocolate hill blush brush I wonder
do this first just because blush is one
of those things that tends to kind of
wear off during the makeup application
process and I don't want it to go away
so we're gonna load this on there
great we're just gonna can I bring it up
to my temple just a little bit as well
why not might as well fade it up there
does it have a little bit of blush on
the nose as well let's see oh yeah it
goes all the way up geez like the entire
face is pink I mean I love blush but
this is a little bit excessive what
about on the nose why not
alright now I'm gonna go ahead and add
the highlighter so just taking nm5 whole
one brush I'm gonna dip into literally
from the palette and you guys know I use
this all the time as a blush shade to
mix together at my blush and highlighter
because it's kind of like a pinky peach
orange each eye on it but it also has a
beautiful pink reflect just so I'm gonna
put this on my cheekbones give it a
little spritz oh look at that that is a
gorgeous and then just to intensify that
pink glow a little bit I'm gonna throw
it way back to the og a beauty guru days
to the anasazi Beverly Hills moon child
pellet this was the first palette that I
picked up that have the pink highlighter
in it as you can see it has clearly been
through quite a lot it is so beautiful
is that enough blush question oh my god
I then just super quickly I'm gonna add
on a few of faux freckles to this look
just because it does have them in the
original filter and I want to stay true
to it let's draw some cherries so to
draw the cherries once again I'm gonna
use a liquid lipstick and for this I'm
just gonna grab the Kylie in the shade
the after party matte but of course you
guys can use any red that you want too I
like this one because it is definitely
more of like a pinky tone red then an
orange E tone red I'm really sticking a
true with the color scheme that we
clearly have going on right now I wish
there was like
where that I could like stamp this on my
face I wonder oh my god let me try to do
this okay if I use like a bottom of the
lipstick it like rub this in there is
this cheating and I'm now going to try
to stamp this this might be a really bad
decision but it also could be good okay
well that was a flaw there we go and now
I'm just going to I mean I guess I'm
just gonna like literally do oh gosh I
mean there we go some lovely four
circles all right now I'm having a flat
brush I'm gonna dip into the shade at
you're kidding from the palette or any
other bright red shadow that you may
have just to you know really make the
staining that we're about to get even
worse and we're going to set that red
liquid lipstick in please just to make
sure it doesn't move or smudge around
okay no in this filter the cherries are
actually completely flat and just like
one-dimensional or I guess
two-dimensional hello but y'all know me
I like to go above and beyond so I just
want to take a little shader brush and
dip into a little bit of boutique which
is the maroon shade from the palette and
I'm just gonna add a little bit of
shading to the cherries just so they're
not like one solid color cuz that's kind
of boring I'm also gonna take that same
brush that we use the white on in the
last look for the clouds and grab a
little bit of flash back maybe a little
bit of pink a tea drink a tea as well to
the palate then I'm gonna use this to
add some highlights in to the opposite
corner of the charities now we have to
add on the little stems so I'm just
going to grab a green liquid lipstick
and then just connect the two together
then I'm just going to draw on the
little leaves as well and then I'm just
gonna set this in place using a little
bit of a social blade from the palette
now I'm going to use a block liner and
outline everything this is so hard
oh okay so now I'm gonna draw the little
face details that they have on the
filter
time for the final details we add in the
white liner I mean could be better could
be worse
period alright now just let me know I'll
just put some nice pink highlight in my
inner corner perhaps some skip from the
palette to start off this a lovely oops
that's bright I hated my palettes to
purchase to want a little inner corner
glow in there perhaps a little bit of
literally I definitely donate that
that's okay great now we're gonna add a
little bit of a brow bone highlight for
lashes today I'm just gonna pop all up
my Lily lashes in the style Miami
regular not the flare this time we are
now on to the last step which is of
course the ellipse personally I would
love to just leave this look right here
I think this looks super cute I'm very
very happy with it so far I don't want
to do the whole like big lip thing but
I'm gonna respect the artist so we're
just gonna go true to the filter and
we're gonna over draw the living crap
out of my lips once again
alright sisters at last with finally not
least and that is our cherry on the cake
by a Barbra mite so it's a filter look
all completes I think out of the three
filters that this one was definitely the
most challenging it just because getting
the circles be nice and round getting
the kind of cherries in the right place
but in the end I do think this one is
the cutest little changes on my face but
I think the simplistic inner corner
definitely turned out really really good
but I'm definitely looking forward to
hearing what you guys have to say once
again if you read this one that make
sure you tie me in the original artist
[Music]
thank you guys so much for watching
there's recreating Instagram filters
using only makeup video I had it's so
much fun doing this and I think all
these turned out so cute definitely give
it a big thumbs up down below if you
enjoyed it and leave me a comment let me
know which filter was your favorite
wasn't one of the three that I created
or do you have another Instagram filter
that you love and that you want me to
recreate definitely let me know because
I would love to do a video like this in
the future this was so much fun and I
really hope that you guys enjoyed it as
much as I dance if you have not ready
make sure you click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood I would love to have
you in the family I'd also like that
belt like hugs so you can notified every
time I upload a brand new video if you
like to follow me on my makeup journey
can follow me on Instagram Twitter tic
toc and Facebook Geraldo same Charles
and Mary snapchat for behind the scenes
I'm Thomas James Charles an extra ass
after Charles this videos sister shout
out goes to sister Abbie thank you so
much lip for always falling in
supporting I love you so so so much and
at you at home watching you like to the
next videos a sister shadow don't forget
to always read tweet with it at least
legal live on Twitter and also turn on
my YouTube at post notifications thank
you so much watching this video today I
love you all so much and I will see you
in the next one bye
[Music]