hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 channel you guys I am
literally in such a good mood tonight
and I'm so excited to be sitting out if
I'll be this video because this morning
my palette restocked for the first time
since the initial launch on more feet
calm you guys know we sold it out when
the leave few hours the first time and
once again and his sister sold out
worldwide which literally like my mind
is blown and I am so beyond grateful for
all of your guys's love and support and
I never in a million years would have
even expected to have the opportunity to
make a makeup product let alone do it
with morphe you make it literally the
best in the entire world and how the
demand and reaction just be so kindly
positive that it sells out not once but
twice like holy crap obviously the goal
this palette was to inspire people and
make people want to go on to their
comfort zones and play with color and I
will confidently say that we are
definitely doing that some of the looks
that I am seeing from this palette are
like mind-blowing the Tala is unreal and
that is what brings me to today's new
video if you guys been around for a
while you would know that I have a
little series that I do here on this
channel called arere creating my
followers makeup looks now i believed on
that two of these videos in the past so
far but they are truly one of my
all-time favorite series to film because
of the fact that what they are so much
fun and I get to be a super super
creative with my makeup but too I get to
shout out really amazing artists that I
believe have so much talent and deserve
a bigger platform and that is exactly
what we're going to be doing in today is
a brand new video for today's video I
want to recreate three of them three to
them with not as still sex three of them
that I selected that I just think are so
incredibly cool I want to challenge
myself and I want to show you guys at
home that approaches the palette as well
the true possibilities that the looks
that you can create super quick before
we jump into the video you guys don't
forget that I'm doing my entire month of
holiday give a slave's every single
upload during the month of December I'll
be giving away a PR package including
the palette and my brush set and
artistry collection hoodie that has been
a sold out on sisters a palette and it's
never coming back and as well a brand
new 2018 Apple MacBook Air oh my body
literally the give us play of the
century all you have to do to enter is
me following me on all my social media
platforms including this YouTube channel
make sure you hit the subscribe button
it's like
so you never missed an upload and you
were able to enter into all the holiday
give us ladies this month also be
following me on my Instagram and Twitter
there bolsters James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scene
size-up has changed hours that extra ask
after Charles give this video and all my
other December uploads a big thumbs up
and show your sister's support and
finally leave a comment down below and
tell me literally anything in the entire
world if you love the makeup looks which
one is going to be your favorite later
on after you're finished watching what
you want for christmas literally
anything just leave me a comment and
they'll be one winner randomly chosen
per video and every single winner will
be announced in the description box of
the next video totalling to eight
winners total for all the information
and official rules on entering up please
don't forget to read the description box
down below for more details but you know
I think that is it you guys good luck
and now on to the video
[Music]
are you guys even screenshotting
literally hundreds and hundreds of lux
as you guys are posting loads with the
palette and I also tweeted asking for a
bunch of different artists to submit
looks like they've done this well just
the case I missed any and I picked out
three to do for today's video that I
think are gonna be so much fun and I'm
so excited for this first one because I
picked up this iconic look by makeup by
Raquel oh my god look at how pretty this
is it is just a warm toned brown smokey
eye but she added this beautiful pop of
yellow in the inner corner Brickhouse
one way all-time favorite artist to
follow right now she is literally 16
years old and she's been doing so many
incredible looks using the palette like
oh my god that blending work is insane I
invited her to my launch party and she
was just so incredibly sweet and is so
talented she reminds me a lot of myself
from a few years ago and I think she's
gonna go very very far in this industry
so please go check her out and show your
social support and love as always I
figured this look would be perfect to do
first and today is a brand video because
so many people have been requesting a
glam look from me which I totally get
obviously I've been focusing a lot on
the rainbow colors because that's kind
of the point of the palette but I did
put in a ton of beautiful neutral and
warm tone shades and there as well
perfect for everybody who doesn't feel
as comfortable wearing those crazy
colors on their eyelids and just want
something a little bit more wearable on
an everyday basis
this look is gonna be perfect because it
is a typical glam look but it still adds
a little bit of a pop of color for those
you who just want to dip your toes in
but don't feel comfortable going all the
way I'm gonna start off my drop of Miami
won 7-3 brush and dipping it to my back
Paint Pot in the shade of painterly
and using this to a prime my eyelids so
opening up the palette we're gonna be
mainly focusing on at the middle row of
bigger pans right here obviously we are
gonna add a pop of color later on but I
firmly did all these shades perfect for
creating any warm tone smokey eye and
that is exactly what we were doing today
I'm gonna first so if I can get a matte
four or five six brush and dipping into
the shade and no beans and this is the
warm tone of brown in the palette and
I'm just gonna pop the shade right onto
my eyelid I'm nicer than have another m4
fine
ruslan dip into a 10% off and I'm just
gonna place this shade right above that
no beans color and just blend it lightly
upwards just kind of chopping that shade
on there first and then using light
little circular motions just to blend
out that Brown edge moving right up the
line I'm resting up in a mat 4-3-3 brush
and dip into the shader code James a
right next door and same exact thing I'm
gonna use this color to go right over
that edge and start blending a little
bit more upwards just using light
circular motions and then finally with
an eye before for one I'm gonna dip into
the shade of two and they're just a
little bit of family as well and use
this to blend out that final edge will
be gone to the lower lash then I'm gonna
take the same I'm four five six brush
and the shade and no beads and just tuck
this right up in there bringing it all
the way across the lower lash line and
also making sure to connect it up with
that outer V on the upper lash line as
well
I cannot stand in smoky eyes when the
lower and upper lash line are not
connected I think it looks really really
messy so just put that collar there plug
in the same exact color order next
undergrad about ten percent off and
blend that edge out and blend this right
below no beans and then coat James and
then finally five honey in tune to
highlight the brow bone are gonna grab a
little bit of a face on just a flat top
little brush and give it a quick spritz
of the oven set setting spray and just
pop that right up in there I'm gonna
grab my tiny bit of five money on just
that same and four for one brush and go
over that because that was a little much
so that is the brown smokey I literally
already complete using the entire
mineral of the palette like I said you
guys I picked these colors for a reason
it is so easy to create the most
beautiful
chocolatey warm tone I look ever I'm
obsessed with how this turned out now
you could totally stop here but I do
want to add it just a little bit of a
pop of color you guys it is so much fun
to do so I'm trying to decide that
because in Raquel's original photo she
had a pop of yellow in the inner corner
which was so beyond a stunning like I
was obsessed with it but sister Kylie
recently posted a picture where she had
a pop of a pink in the inner corner and
it was so beyond sunny
I feel like inner corner colors is
becoming a major ten right now so I
think just to switch things up a little
bit because I have been doing a lot of
yellow recently I want to do a pop of
pink so to do a pop of color
for three one this is a little pencil
brush that comes in the brush set and
dip into the bright neon pink shade a
called skip no I do want to give you a
fair warning you guys if this pink shade
is insanely pigmented and if you have a
sensitive skin it may or may not cause
staining so be careful I'm just gonna
pop this shade right here I'm just
popping it right in that inner corner
and then using any excess that's left on
the brush to kind of lightly blend it
into the kind of transition shades that
we had going on around the eye I'm not
going to a matte five six to in a tiny
little bit more of skip but really top
off the access and just use this to
Crabb fluffily fluffily watch this is a
fluffy brush I'm scared just blend out
the address gonna dip into a little bit
of pink kitty drink a tea to help me
blend this out as well next for that pop
of glow I'm gonna dip into the shade of
litter leaves in that same little pencil
brush I absolutely love this color that
is one of my favorites from the palette
I'm gonna give this a good spread of the
morphe prepping setting spray and just
tap that right in the center just to
really make that shadow pop I'm just
gonna have a tiny little bit of a liquid
at glitter and they tiny little pencil
brush and dot dot right over top and
lastly probably not least I'm going to
line my waterline using the Makeup
Forever aqua oxalic color pencil in the
shade pink
you definitely could skip this step if
you don't feel comfortable putting a
pink and your waterline I know some
people may think that that would look
sickly you can definitely do a nude or a
block and said if you want a more smoky
look but for me personally I really
really like when the pop of color just
continues in if you like it really pulls
the whole eye look together
alright that is officially one eye all
complete I'm gonna go ahead and do that
one off camera quickly and I'll be right
back with the finished look I just
finished up the other bronze smokey eye
and I decided the pink looks a very very
beautiful but not our of Raquel's
original photo I do want to add a pop of
yellow in the inner corner just because
the look was literally too pretty not to
recreate and also to show you guys that
you can do this with literally any of
the color I mean a purple would be so
sunny with this a blue a green like
literally anything would look so pretty
with this so I was gonna do it the pop
of yellow
to grab a little bit of pee on a pencil
brush same exact technique is the pink
just popping the shade right in there oh
my god so pigmented like the pink Center
was gonna grab a fluffy brush and just
have been to a little bit that same a
shade B and just Suzi is to lightly buff
out the edges of that yellow and make
sure it's evenly diffused into both the
regular skin around the area and also
into the orange of the smoky eye just
like the other side kind of got me a
little bit of regulate on a tiny little
pencil brush and give it a quick spritz
I'll sum up prep insect and use this to
highlight right on that inner corner
carving some more Beach make sure that's
nice and blend it out then carving a
little bit of a liquid glitter obviously
this one is it gold this time and
packing about right over top then I'm
gonna finish this yellow eye off with
just a yellow pencil liner this one is
from NYX gonna pop on a quick color of
mascaras in the Mac extended fight for
laughs today I'm gonna pop on the Lily
lashes and the style oh they are not
Miami's for once but they are very very
similar these ones are actually just
longer on the end so these are gonna be
perfect for an eye look like this where
we really want to focus it on the inner
corner and you can still always use code
James for 15% off so those are both
lines all complete I thought that was
gonna look crazy having two different
colors in the inner corner but kind of
like living for this little strawberry
banana lemonade but we have going on it
right now I'm gonna go ahead and brush
off any excess powder that we still on
at the face so we can move on to the
highlight can give my face a quick
spritz of the prep and settings right so
the highlighter has something to adhere
to and to kind of melt some of the
excess powder into the skin that on an
AM 501 I'm gonna dip into the shade of
face and just go right yeah a little bit
right above with the brow bone as always
Jim and then with that second m-43 one
from the brush set just a tiny little
dot on the tip of the nose and one lie
right down the center then finally my e4
brush I'm gonna dip into the shade it
literally the same color that I use on
my little pink inner corner you guys all
have been loving the shader recently for
blending together my highlight and blush
like I said in the beginning of the
video lips are already on for obvious
reasons and you guys I think that is the
first look inspired by a makeup by
raquel i'll complete
[Music]
I had that so much finally recreate this
look if I recount like it's kind of
rather too looks today like I said
before had such an easy go to warm tones
folky out using the middle row of the
palette this is exactly when I created
it and of course we got to do a little
puff of color as well just if it would
be whole unleash your inner artist theme
I think this is the perfect look for any
beginner makeup wear who wants to just
dip their toes into color but it's a
comfortable going all the way yet but
speaking of going all the way we have
two more looks to do so that further ado
let's jump on to luck number two alright
it is day number three I filming this
video but this is going to be look
number two I just wanted to say that
because of my hair it just got cut but
in the next that was going to go back to
long and really really gross this has
been a vest filming but we're gonna get
it done together
you and I so let's move on to the lock
so for the first think we definitely
kept it pretty simple glam still adding
a pop of color but a really really great
look for the everyday it girl on the go
but for look number two obviously that
says the artistry palette and it is a
full rainbow palette so for this look
you guys know how to throw in something
there with a whole lot of color so I
found this look by Lauren Bettles it is
this beautiful like rainbow cloud cut
crease with lots of glitter different
stars and I'm obsessed with how this
turned out oh my god I think it is so
pretty you guys know I don't get to play
with glitter that often on this YouTube
channel because I really really don't
like it but I feel like she used this
very very wisely in this stuff but I
also have a few other ideas up my sleeve
but I think I want to add to this look
to really tie it together as well so
without further ado let's jump in
so first let us rather than the inner
corner in that little crease moment and
obviously we're gonna cut out the cloud
later on but I'm first gonna cover to
m45 sex and dip into the shade Cola
which is the deep matte blue of the
palette and I'm just gonna pack Col up
right inside of that like inner crease
area and I'm gonna bring it out a little
bit farther to what I do cut crease is I
usually actually cut out right on the
crease line because I have this really
annoying flap of skin that like covers
my inner corner and seems like such a
stupid thing but you have no idea how
difficult it makes so many makeup looks
especially creases but with this cloud I
do want to kind of bring that in a
little
more so I'm going to take that into
consideration next article all I'm gonna
take a little bit of a daddy on the same
exact brush and place the shade as well
right next to it on the crease in the
crease why don't I just next to daddy
I'm gonna take it beyond an m4 3/3 brush
and places right there padding on the
color first and then blending it upwards
I'm gonna grab a little bit of you're
kidding on an M 4 5 6 brush as well and
put that in here I'm gonna add it
obviously in a lot more clutter that's
multiple of these all together but I
just want to kind of get the situation
started just like good amount of
everything out
I'm gonna grab escape I don't employ 5 6
brush and put this over here at least
and I need to go back into like all the
transitional colors to blend all this
together so it doesn't look disgusting
like this so what I'm going to do is
grab a fluffy brush and dip into it
single and I'm gonna use this and go
right over the edge of this red and
purple to diffuse these two colors
together and to blend out this outer
edge adding in some more of your kidding
a little bit more of B gonna buff out
that Daddy using a bit of social blade
and then finally a little bit of
playground just to buff out that inner
corner to cut the crease and create this
little cloud shape I'm gonna grab the
morphe white concealer and I'm going to
put this on the back of my hand okay so
I'm gonna grab it the 19 brush this one
is not in my brush set when I was making
the brush size and not exactly
anticipated doing a cloud cut crease so
sorry about that but I make this work
lump number one pretty good love if I do
say so myself I'm not gonna lie cut it
down kind of good kind of fresh kind of
funky kind of clouded London were three
one more little lump okay this is good
okay so now I'm gonna grab the N 1 2 4
this is my all-time favorite brush
you're packing on shades and I'm first
gonna grab a little bit of love that I'm
gonna pack this right over top of that
like outer edge I'm gonna grab your
kidding on a tiny little pencil brush
some basically gonna like keep laying on
these colors in the same rainbow we're
going back into the eyelid but I'm gonna
leave more and more white space
basically this is like rainbow liner
almost next to the red I want to place a
little bit of or so I'm gonna grab a
little bit of Rustad put this like right
there just coming actually gonna do five
one eight finally gonna grab a little
bit of a yellow on that same brush I'm
gonna pack that right here nothing to
pack on some white put a little bit of
flash back right on top of everything
well I've been silent for almost this
entire video telling you know I'm
struggling for a real long okay I'm
gonna do the lower lash line now
something easy and nice so I need to
first put on some more single with at
home for my sex and really bring this
all the way into the lash we're gonna
kind of pull this down pretty far too
because I am gonna be awning glitter and
then just taking a little bit of
playground on this same brush from
before as well and tucking this right
next door and I'm gonna bring this right
open to the inner corner as well I'm
just lightly feathering out those edges
now I'm going to take a little bit of
black very carefully on a tiny little
pocket brush I'm gonna put this right up
against that lower lash line nice and
smoked for a real one okay that is
looking really beautiful so you guys
remember in the first look a few minutes
ago I talked about how I always like my
inner corner highlight and my waterline
to always notch could I feel like it
makes the whole look up he said so I
wanna do the same thing here I'm gonna
have a huge pop of white in the inner
corner so I'm gonna grab a little bit of
that morphe white concealer on a just
liner brush I'm gonna top it off so it
kind of dries down a little bit but I'm
gonna tuck this I'm gonna take a little
bit of a concealer as well just to
sketch in a new lower lash line in the
inner corner
just gonna grab a little bit of Flash
buckle on a pencil brush and I'm going
to pop this right on the inner corner
just to blend out that harsh edge heart
harsh just to blend out that harsh to
blend out that harsh edge that's right
what is wrong with me oh the little
stars and stuff forgot about that okay
first I'm just our back garden by NYX
white liquid liner and I'm just gonna
sketch in a few little stars in the
rainbow Porsche let's do like a little a
moment right out here
notice for some little stars I'm gonna
pop on a glitter in the inner corner but
I'm just gonna take a little bit more of
that liquid liner and add in some dot
right on that white shade this is what I
like to do a lot too when it comes to
putting a bright highlight in the inner
corner because sometimes those are in
glitters or pigments they only shine a
super super bright if the light is
heading in but obviously depending on
your lighting it you can't always do
that so what I like to do is sometimes
take a white ladder and put a ton of
little dots here it's almost like mimic
the look of glitter because that way you
can still layer glitter over top of it
but even if the light doesn't hit it
it'll still be white now I just want to
take a few different chunky glitters
let's see oh I should do like little
star drips first huh I'm gonna grab my
liner brush and dip into the shade a
single and then I'm going to I guess
just like drip this down for a real one
I'm gonna take a little bit of brother
he's not same little brush now I'm gonna
pop on some glitter okay so have a few
different chunky glitters that I'm gonna
use today and they're often the brand in
your dreams on insert I don't want to
tip that or it's gonna fall everywhere
I'm gonna die but they're super dope
when they have a lot of chunky glitter I
feel like for some reason chunky glitter
is like impossible to find but it's not
the only glitter that I ever used cuz
you guys are I hate glitter period so
we're gonna put it on I don't get to put
it on using the peaches and glitter
adhesive
lots of filing at least I have a few of
these tiny little stars there's I do not
know how far I can tell that before it's
gonna fall
but they're shaped like stars I promise
thank you to my sister Burrell Co for
letting me borrow them could I go all
these little stars on to the bottom of
each little like drip as if they're like
stars that have fallen out of the sky so
cute oh my god so that is what I all
complete it I am obsessed with this this
is literally one of my favorite looks I
have ever ever done and it's also one of
the longest times I've ever spent on an
eye I'm gonna quickly cut and go off
camera to the other eye and hopefully
not take four hours and I'll be right
back with the finished look okay so
alright doc I decided on the other eye
off-camera this did in fact take me
another several hours which is just
lovely but it's done and that's all that
matters and I feel so beautiful I just
popped on a pair of Lily lashes in this
house so extra Miami get a new scope
James for 15% off your purchase and
that's going to move on to it the rest
of the face for the highly unscientific
my face a quick spread of the more via
prep insect siding spray this is my
literal all-time favorite and then grab
the shade of face from the palette and
then just grabbing literally on a knee
for brush you guys thought this my
all-time favorite combination and
putting this right over top just to mix
the highlight and blush together finally
for lips might go to a nude combination
and then just topping it off with some
gloss and finally finishing this look
off of the mac fix+
gold late edition for a little inner
glow okay I know literally four hours
later this is look number two inspired
by sister Lauren battles all complete I
went to this lips today knowing it was
gonna be challenging and it definitely
was but it took so much longer than
expected now you guys know I love it
just sitting down and playing with
makeup but this took us so much time in
patience and precision cutting this
crease making sure all the whites and
all the closure blended together but
that being said literally four hours of
work later I think every single bit of
that was worth it because I am obsessed
with how this lecture now I think it is
literally one of the most beautiful
looks I have ever had on my face like
are you literally kidding
hello you guys all better go double tap
this Instagram picture once it goes live
oh my god but thank you so much to
Lauren for sharing this look with me and
for supporting me of my palette it means
that so so so much this literally goes
to show that you can do anything with
this palette if you guys decide to
recreate this look at home do not forget
to type Lauren for makeup credit and
also tag me so I can see all of your
face beautiful looks as well or that
further ado let's move on to the next
one
alright so finally on to the last look
of the video and I'm a little bit
nervous with this one I'm not gonna lie
I'm assuming if you saw the thumbnail
this is probably what you clicked on
this video which is why I kept it for
last
queen of marketing I'm gonna be
recruiting this look today from LA via
done prints one of my really good
friends Jose Jose is an incredibly
talented makeup artists but also truly
one of the nicest influencers I have
ever met
to this tank such a sweetheart I
absolutely love him the most but that
being said I am very very nervous for
this look that I am because this whole
makeup look is actually inspired by a
Marcelo con to photo who is an iconic
photographer now if you're not familiar
with like makeup community history this
whole look and effect actually went
viral several years ago by a photo edit
that Marcelo con 2 did know I've
actually shot with him before his work
is literally insane one of the coolest
photographers of all time and he's very
very known for doing it digital effects
now I know for a fact that this original
photo that Marcelo did it was completely
added it on and Jose did it with makeup
and what I saw Marcelo's photo a few
years ago I've always wanted to recreate
it but I just generally never thought it
would be possible using makeup because
the colors are so vibrant but sister
Hosea managed to do and to make it even
better he used my palette so I figured
for the last look today I would try my
absolute best to recreate this if it
turns out great amazing if it turns out
god at least it's the last look and you
guys would have already clicked off the
video early on ok so I think looking at
this photo and also at this really great
condition to charles palette i think i
want to start with the highlights and
kind of build
backwards with the colors ok so I think
our first thing I got my own 433 brush
and open to the shade of playground
which is this like teal blue
um this is this is my better side just
gonna put this like right oh my gosh
who's no going back now
then I'm gonna bring it like up to the
nose but I'm not gonna do is start
freaking out okay we're gonna make this
positive and I need some more up here
too I'm gonna layer obviously a lot more
on but I think this is a good start now
I'm gonna grab another M for three three
and dip into the shade single and I'm
gonna use this like below the blues so
like right here maybe you're gonna have
a little bit of a brother on a M 5:19
news up to kind of blend together the
blue and purple I'm just placing colors
on here randomly so I don't even know if
this is supposed to the K your tutorial
or what's going on I'm assuming there's
gonna be a lot of phase two needed to
like bring this to life you know what
that's okay you know I do love I got a
face to the moment I am the queen of
Phase two so you can definitely make it
work
I didn't that brother shade in between a
playground and a single definitely makes
it look way way way better but still not
good oh I forgot my brow bone I'll do
that in a second okay I need to put more
things here I've done some single up
here next to the blue can add a little
more purple here I'm gonna go to the
shade love that and a little bit more of
a fluffy brush and use this to not blend
out the edges of that purple oh yes yes
cess the chief just called and this this
is that that was so annoying a little
bit of love that in the inner nose area
I feel like during these videos and
these table looks they always get super
super discouraged when it doesn't look
perfect right away but in the end
usually happy with that right now
definitely at that stage where it looks
not good I'm not going to give up and
hopefully it looks okay by the time that
I finish this at this point I think
that's gonna be out anything that's
gonna say this look it's going to be the
highlight and like the white so I'm
gonna grab an M at four five six and the
shade hello
there's like the bright metallic I see a
baby blue from the pellets I'm gonna
give it a nice spread of some puppets up
because I definitely do you want this to
be like very very metallic and I'm gonna
start placing this color on the high
points
this is kind of coming together they're
not gonna lie gonna pop a little bit of
hello right on that inner corner on the
tip of the nose also down the nose
bridge and on the brow bone as well now
I want to take another one of the m45
six brushes is different to the shade
ring light once I get that metallic
pearl I want to give that a spread of
prep inside and put that like even more
in the middle this is exactly what we
need okay
oh I should definitely some on my ear
mm-hmm definitely in my ear and Jose's
personal photo he does have a winged
liner on now I fully already have lashes
on because I was too lazy to take them
off before I started this look for some
reason and now I'm gonna be really lazy
I'm gonna try to do my wing liner over
top of my lash days is this going to
work
probably not am I going to try
absolutely oh my god I am the queen of
savings time
look at that wing you oh my god I would
normally literally never do waiting this
thick but Jose's wing was large and in
charge today gal so we're gonna match it
I'll do it on the other eye too even
though there isn't gonna be anything
over there I guess then I just make my
Wayne die literally literally perfectly
even I'd like to and Jose's virginal
look he does have the lower lashline
smoked out with block you guys know I
don't really like putting block on my
waterline but we are going to do it
today I'm gonna dip into the shade of
spooky on my time at 5:08 brush and just
go right in there oh my god I should
have just left that how it was
oh I'm gonna use the Urban Decay glide
on pencil in the shade at zero which is
the block when I put this in my
I guess last I'm gonna pop on a black
line with lipstick this is Oprah in the
shade of the Bronx whose coach a misters
30% off whenever I do black lips I have
the tendency to over line them way too
much oh that is not good mascara all
right you guys I think this is the final
look final of be done print inspired by
Marcelo con tu foto all complete I'm
really not sure how much better I can
get this to look up considering the
original was not even actual makeup and
it was a digitally edited photo where
literally anything is possible
considering that I think we did okay
today I think it looks definitely decent
with a little bit of facetune though
this will be good and fresh and with all
that being said I think those are all
three looks all complete I really hope
you guys enjoyed watching me a recreate
or at least try to recreate these three
makeup looks on my face today
oh my god when I saw these three looks
from the original artist I was so
excited and I just wanted to play and
sit down with the palette which is
exactly the point of why I made this in
the first place these artists blew my
mind and even if the last look didn't
exactly come out quite as planned I
definitely had so much fun challenging
myself tonight and I felt equally it's
beautiful in all three looks
if you sisters at home decide to
recreate any of these makeup looks make
sure to like the original artist for
credit and also time me so I get to see
it as well if you happened to pick up
the James house ex Murphy palette before
its sister sold oh please tell me all
your makeup looks I cannot wait to see
you guys playing with color and being
creative and unleashing your inner
artists if you enjoyed this video so
they please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below come share your
sisters support it means so so so much
to me and also if you have not already
don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood we are over 11
million sisters shortly we were going so
fast on my brain cannot even keep up and
all stuff like that Bell icon so you and
get a notification every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on i makeup Turner you can follow me on
Instagram or Twitter their posters
change charts my stop shop for more
behind the scenes item is James Charles
the next ask after Charles since videos
sisters thought I'd go sister
ten thank you so much love for always a
following in supporting oil every
literally it's so so so much and if you
like to be the next videos a sister
shout out don't forget to always retweet
my video looks like a live on Twitter
alright since there's that as I have for
today's video thank you so so so much
for watching do not forget to follow all
the rules so you can be entered to win
this video is called and I give a slave
I love you so much
[Music]
[Applause]