hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I
have a little turtle luck on today
because it is getting a little bit
chilly here in LA it is the Christmas
holiday season I mean it's really not
that cold but I'm trying the hardest I
possibly can and this is the most
Christmassy outfit that I have so a
sister is trying up in here I currently
have to get ready for a very very fun
video that I'm filming later on today
but the makeup look that I have to wear
is very very boring a look that you guys
have seen me do literally a million
times so you guys know when it comes to
doing those looks
I will never film them without making a
fun twist a few months ago I did a super
fun video called singing my makeup
routine methought my best friends
Anthony we picked seven of the most
numerous pop songs at the time and I
improv my way through them it was
definitely interesting to say the least
and if you have not yet checked out the
video make sure to click right up here
and go check it out it was one of the
most fun videos I've ever done and today
you guys love it so so much that I
decided to do again Christmas edition I
have one of my best friends behind the
camera blade today Gabe ugh you guys
know her as Dee soprano from flashback
and if you have no idea what I'm talking
about
flashback cousin acapella group that I
sing in music plays a very very huge
role in my life and I've been skiing
forever I'm definitely not the best at
it but I do enjoy it so for today
Gaber picked seven of the most serious
and most popular holiday songs she
arranged them on the piano and if you
would like to see me and prod my way
through my makeup routine holiday
edition keep on watching I guess so okay
I'm beating my face gonna meet a guy
it's our first aid gotta be looking fly
just kidding I'm sick oh ho forever
alone I'm trying to mingle so straight
boys can come home with me foundation
foundation we're covering our face got
lotsa supplements and pimples do we
raise fund a Sunday we're
covering our face Carlos also publishes
in pimples to e raise we got there
okay X all winter wonderland
okay set your face pack the powder bake
your face slop it harder laura mercier
Too Faced Born This Way are makeups
gonna stay on a long house easy already
okay what is that why excuse me I want
to chisel out my cheekbones tap on D
shade + light will do gotta look
snatched can't be looking flat you gave
I didn't ask for your favorite oh my god
yes can't wait
[Music]
gonna slay my brows there is just one
thing I need precisely my brow pencil
I'll sponsor straight or
feathery first we draw the bottom line
there filling to save some time conceal
and clean or to baby now my brows the
gray
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry Briah what song is that oh that's
cold
yeah really
to see those shadows blending and
pigments flying at you come on it's time
for smokey or natural aura sultry are
calling you horribly and by soon I mean
right now I don't even know the song to
be fair alright so in the spirit of
giving yes okay okay what are we doing
mary did you know okay I got this song
hard song
[Music]
maybe did you know that my Eider can be
seen from space look at that glow how it
shines so bright right upon my face did
you know the truth in your brush will
make it shine more bright this
highlighter I'm using wish
[Music]
[Applause]
mary did you know
[Music]
we really gotta go baby my face ain't
done you're going way too slow baby my
face ain't done we're gonna be so late
baby my baby my Asti - stop acting like
standards gonna bring me a boy under the
tree that's gonna rush they throwing
make up 14 because we all know that's
not happening
all right status and that is the
completed look and that means that it's
only hard for this little holiday
Christmas singing my makeup routine
video this was so much fun to do I
personally love Christmas and I feel
like so what if you guys do too but I
think everybody knows and loves
Christmas you think but not that many
people like actually no Christmas music
like I definitely struggled on a lot of
these songs as you guys just witness to
but definitely comment down below and
tell me which song was your favorite if
you guys absolutely love this video
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below it is definitely
the season of giving so give us this to
your thumbs up speaking of the season of
giving it has been just over one year
now since I really started to blow up on
social media we have literally gained so
many millions of followers and only one
year it is so beyond crazy you guys
we're already to two million YouTube
subscribers almost the 3 million
Instagram like I just love you guys so
much you seriously do mean the world to
me and I would not be here today without
you guys so sister wants to give back
because I love you sisters so so so much
I've officially decided to do 12 Days of
Giveaways not only will the prize
packages include tons and tons of your
all-time favorite makeup products and
the most popular items from 2017 but
there will also be some very very big
ticket items towards the end of the
gibbehh slaves including the brand new
iPhone acts like I told you guys in the
iPhone X video if you'd like to enter
the 12 days of sister Christmas campus
lace make sure to give this video a big
thumbs up down below and then just leave
me a comment down below tell me your
name your age where you're from and the
one thing that you want for Christmas is
here you must be subscribed to my
youtube channel so if you have not
already make sure to click that big red
button down below to subscribe join the
sisterhood and then also click that
Ballack on so you can be notified every
time I upload a brand new video you're
also going to want to add me on snapchat
which is James Charles the next row
asked after Charles because
why you to schedule isn't exactly the
most consistent let's be real all the
prize packages and winners one week
after they originally announced will be
posted on my snap story this week sister
shot echoes - sister meet thank you so
much for your always falling in
supporting and I love you so so so much
and if you'd like to be at next video
sister shout out make sure to always
retailer video links and they go live on
Twitter all right sisters that is all I
have for this video today thank you so
so much for watching and good luck in
the 12 days of Christmas give us life if
you do decide to enter I love you guys
so much happy holidays and I will see
you in the next one
[Music]