[Music]
it's like 50 degrees no I knew I forgot
something
we're going to Australia hope we don't
get hypothermia well how long do we have
until that happens I mean I really would
not be on the trip if it was not me
Laurel don't attack me we're on the way
we'll be there soon here we go
Wow look at me being amazing vlogger
bloggers are shaking Casey nice I found
dad Casey and is doing just fine
yeah moment of truth once again we go
from LA to Brisbane boarding at a gate
157 comments boarding at 11:20 tonight
the nicest nothing
oh my treasure for the record I didn't
lose my boarding pass
James walk test usually I'm going a
little bit and we're here he's yelling
at me so James
[Music]
it's your work yeah what you're singing
tomorrow yet Oh baby it's a knob where
you down to the bottom of Australia had
to mr. James here welcome back to
Australia all right you guys hello
sister bird so we're currently on the
Gold Coast here at paradise country and
I'm about to meet koalas hello literally
never been more excited in my entire
life
they're all currently sleeping
apparently they can only work for 30
minutes a day for three days straight
then they need a day off like hello I
need to be whatever that level is right
now it's so soft it feels like a little
weight goal don't they
hello 'test is 15 oh yeah we came like
human years yeah yeah unfortunately that
the numbers on doing to do so because of
habitat destruction people cut down
trees to make houses these are the guys
that dip out higher ranking so she's
she'll be like okay you guys so what we
just got the calls they're all so cute
I'm literally gonna crying right now but
now we're meeting the sister kangaroos
and they're all so majestic and
beautiful and they're all sleeping I've
noticed every single animal here is
sleeping like goals hello new thought in
my life right now but I have this sister
right here I have some food and I think
I want to try to feed it so I would film
that what noise do they like
are you going sister you got a hit you
belly that's cured yeah too late to post
an Instagram picture this time is all
just really nothing at my head
[Applause]
very special guest hosts with me today
she's an influencer and James his best
friend Laura mulatto thank you for
holding down the fort with me today hi
thanks for having me I'm very excited
host welcome James Charles hi sisters
I'm so excited to be here
[Music]
good morning sisters it is a day two
here in Australia and I am a week alive
I literally woke up at 6 a.m. today
because of the jetlag apparently a bunch
of your sisters were camping out last
night so I really hope you guys are all
awake alive safe and warm and I'm just
so excited I'm currently getting ready I
have Laura over there who's the entire
world she never leaves her house and I
convinced her to come and see me since
I'm here in Australia and I literally
looked up to her forever like this is so
exciting for me and we're just gonna go
and slay this me together
[Music]
successors here I'm alive
[Applause]
[Music]
walking in my heart is pounding thank
you by then I was like oh my god this is
this is nuts it was nothing right when
it wasn't really state hasn't told my
ears were like yeah it was like static
yeah a lot it was like the sky at that
level what doesn't cool yeah it's an
affair said that this is the largest
turnout I've ever had okay
[Music]
it helped oh my god that was that was so
would say you guys you guys are so crazy
in the both in both what I love you too
mom ever there how to be more several
thousand people there like you guys come
through every time it's so much fun you
guys are all so sweet
we have the best meeting greets always
because you guys are just like normal
humans and you just get anything oh I
love you also wants to keep call the
love and support oh my god holy crap
you're kidding
[Music]
is that embarrassing if I tweet saying
like what song should I sing at my own
show I literally don't know what I'm
doing later on Oh your sisters whoa what
the hell we just did five million on
Instagram
[Music]
[Applause]
is pretty much impossible to master the
art of makeup and to become a celebrity
doing so within a year but that is
exactly what James Charles has achieved
he's done before at the age of 18
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah oh my God look at all like real it
love the lollipop you're kidding
this is so cool fan I don't think I've
ever think in the entire row like that I
will take time to like do that hello I'm
doing I'm getting too old for amusement
park ride tomorrow
[Music]
that was absolute horrible
I enjoyed not a single hole with that my
stomach feels like it is in my throat
right now if you go all good this is the
biggest drop drop let's do it you don't
worry and this current element love them
so far but right now the chaperone
turned around it was like James himself
is so scary and she scared me you guys
this is my chance so we just said that
ride three times now um it was really
let not gonna lie but now I am soaking
wet from talked about him to my brand
new clothes that I just bought yesterday
that were several hundred dollars that's
great
we kept rewriting over over again
because there's the camera at the top
just like every rise that takes your
photo and by the second time around we
figured out where the camera was so we
wanted to create an Instagram meme out
of it because y'all know it that's what
I'm known for starting a meme anyway
guys for clothes none of us are looking
so we have no idea where the camera
actually was oh wow yeah you're kidding
now I'll play the helicopter tour
[Music]
oh my god my face
me either Wow we learned which leg
forward Oh see much better hurry wow
this is a good good
we are in Surfers Paradise here on the
Gold Coast and I thought I would stand
here today and let a bunch of strangers
do my makeup I'm scared
hopefully Border Patrol doesn't get me
good I love being robbed I'm keeping us
much time with you as I possibly can I'm
Jonathan is she off today whoa currently
here at a prison about to go on for the
second shot of the tornado yep so beyond
excited we just got back from the
sisters of VIP a little Q&A and female
session you guys like all the brothers
and sisters perks so nice and so sweet
the show is gonna be super super awsome
I'm finally wearing our merch thank God
finally got here after Australian
Customs was such a mess but I feel crazy
night we didn't have to do this show go
to Rome I literally had to bed and then
wake up 3 in the morning to go to the
airport for our Sydney show tomorrow
morning it's gonna be a lot but we're
gonna make it through I love you sisters
and the show
[Applause]
[Music]
to go check out the brandy video is an
extreme uh translation
see you soon
70 sisters I've morning sisters our
Sydney show a wonderful three hours of
sleep you know what gives me a lot of
inspiration with what I do every day and
gives me a lot of confidence he's just
like my favorite youtuber and I just
really love him he's so good at making
his really positive I do love his
approach other times I just loved him so
much he's so good at makeup and he's
such a big inspiration his house is so
talented I didn't like makeup before I
like
Dean's are so funny and he's so good at
makeup and it just makes me
I love James because he doesn't care
what anyone thinks about him he does
what he loves and
I love James because his makeup looks so
unique I really like James because he's
a nice personality he's really funny
informative he just explains everything
really well I really love James I really
love his personality and I just can't
wait to see him alright well Michael is
12 years old sorry and she has just
become so good at makeup from watching
his videos he's a very big fixture in
our smiles
[Applause]
[Music]
the past 12 days that I spent down honor
for my Australian sisters for have truly
been some of the best days of my entire
life
and a trip that I will literally never
forget I cannot even begin to thank you
guys for the me out of love and support
that I was showing a while I was there
but more importantly probably mount of
fun that I had I am definitely a little
bit of a self-proclaimed workaholic and
I'm very proud to a minute but unless
you've happened to catch me at your
local Starbucks or Chipotle I really
haven't had that many opportunities to
see you guys face to face to hug you it
to hear your stories and just to thank
you for what you've done for me and this
tour has really been an amazing
opportunity to go and I'm so so so
thankful that I get to connect with you
guys every single day I pinch myself
because my job doesn't even feel real
and I'm so glad that I get to do what I
do
so Australian sisters I love you so much
all around the world sisters I love you
guys so much as well and you hopefully
will be seeing me very very soon this
trip and tour has inspired me to wanna
travel so hopefully I'll be in the city
near you guys very very soon you'll
obviously we'll have to keep posted but
thank you guys for allowing me to do
what I do every single day you guys have
changed my life truly for the better
thank you guys for watching this little
behind-the-scenes Australians location I
really really hope you guys enjoyed it
and if you did please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
share your support it really means the
entire world to me also leave me a
comment down below and tell me where you
want to see me travel next this tours
inspire me so much and like I said I
really want to go international with you
guys if you have not ready don't forget
to the big red subscribe button down
below and come join the sisterhood it is
a pretty lit time we are officially over
5 million sisters so thank you guys once
again so so so much for everything and
also put that bow notification icon so
you can notify every time I upload a
brand new video all right sisters thank
you so much for watching I love you and
I will see you in the next one get a
mate
[Music]