today I'm doing something crazy that I'm
actually very very very nervous for I
hired and extremely talented special
effects artists you guys are going to me
in a few short minutes I'm putting my
face in your hands oh wow I just gave a
really good sister sauce oh I know
you're not gonna be a double chance
that's my worst nightmare I don't know
why I'm so nervous for this
know what's up rose welcome to Jersey
club we're on the way right now to
beautycon and I'm not even gonna lie
like I'm feeling really really nervous
right now I never ever get nervous and
I'm just praying that we don't get
caught this if we do it's we just got
here we have to find the entrance now I
don't really know where we're going I'm
very scared if I'm gonna be honest but
let's get this over with
we can also ask around maybe this way
yeah I'm silly staring at everyone just
make sure that they don't make something
even worse I'm very nervous I don't get
nervous why am i nervous I'm so nervous
he's so hot hey kid you're all okay the
only reason why oh I'm a mess
the only reason why I recognized him as
because he literally sent me a snapchat
like this earlier and I was like holy
hit you
and then like I recognized you from you
don't look like you at all I'm dying oh
we're not here you never saw
we've officially gotten here to beauty
pod and I'm freaking about check out
hello miss Rob beauty bye Christy can I
ask you a quick question
[Music]
my name is Stephen I know right so good
do you mind if I ask you a few questions
for a magazine interview glitter glam
magazine we're new it's a startup
company on Twitter right now what brands
and like people are you really excited
to see here today at beautycon I'm
really excited for flower beauty I love
drew Barrymore I do - she's so funny
did you see Drew Barrymore's video
nikkietutorials wow it's a pretty good
video other than Nikki who were other
influences that you enjoy watching how
many followers you on Instagram have 56
that's so crazy I only have like 739 I
think when I checked last night or
something that's so cool that's really
what you think maybe you could give me a
shout out when the interview goes live
of course really do you mind if I ask
you guys a few questions for glitter
Glamour magazine have you heard of our
magazine before I think I have yeah yeah
you probably have it's pretty big Orion
Orion Carlotto hi my name is um Stephen
Brock well from glitter glam magazine I
was wondering if I could ask you a few
questions
yeah you remind me of somebody who
excuse me LOI hi my name is Steven with
glitter glam magazine I would love I can
ask you a few questions
would you say I love you first
like two seconds excuse me excuse me
amber hi my name is Steven with a
glitter glam magazine I was wondering if
I could ask you a few questions
[Laughter]
my name is Steven
brockmore with I have changed my last
name I think four times now doesn't
makeup look at at least honestly I would
have never known for like at least a
solid probably three minutes until I was
like wait I watched a lot of games for
our tutorials are nothing to who that is
but that name is not some familiar I've
only heard of Jeffery saw and Patrick
Starr
James Charles and man number one here
real mother cube hello Lauren Lauren hi
my name is Stephen Bock well with
leather glam magazine I was wondering if
I could ask you a few questions how did
you put in three seconds your voice and
you knew my name straightaway I was like
yeah very much hello Ruben my name is
Stephen block with glitter glam magazine
nice to meet you nice to meet you
I've heard about your work before I saw
you on LN you're very talented
yeah is this your first time at
beautycon here in Los Angeles
yes it is that's amazing I love your
makeup you look fantastic thank you so
when did you start doing makeup and I
asked and I think I was an 8 8 years old
you've been doing Blom for five years
yeah because I watch like DIY videos and
then like I saw like a DIY foundation so
I know makeup that's pretty incredible
as a boy in makeup who were like your
biggest inspiration I love James Charles
Geoffrey start to shore
I love Gabriel Zamora and everyone I
love that who do you think is the best
youtuber in the community right now okay
James house is killing it though like oh
my god this views like like his video
ideas are sick yeah literally just take
it out long hello Nikita dragon hi um my
name is Stephen can I ask you a few
questions for glitter glam magazine
you can't do that you you can't I can't
ask you questions from glitter glam
magazine we're a very big publication
right now on YouTube
a sister I'm a I'm a very big fan of
your Laura why I would just love to know
like are you excited for Beauty call in
Los Angeles today I'm performing
tomorrow that's really awesome I will be
there thank you so much sister
should I not know I was trying to act
very diva is that your team wants to
talk to me that's pretty good it was I
think a Mayan good disguise
good we've seen only a few people so far
almost all the man figured it out
eventually I need to just grow the balls
and go up to strangers I think
I'm literally freaking out and I don't
know why I I've never been like that's
all having a video before I don't know
why I'm so scared
I have no problem going up to all these
youtubers that I know and trying to fool
them but I don't know why I cannot go up
to some that I don't know right now but
normally I feel like if it was me I
could go up to anybody this video is
getting really deep really fast for some
reason which I was not expecting and I'm
kind of scared maybe this wasn't the
best idea I feel really stupid now Kelly
I don't wanna film anymore no I think we
need to go home I think we thought the
car was addicted to go home
so I just got home I just took a shower
I am now back to regular old sister
James and today's video took a turn the
head I was really not expecting it to
take but it's definitely one that I
think I want to sit down and talk about
before I say anything about what kind of
just went on I first want to say a major
major thank you - Channing Judith who
was my special effects artist for
today's video she is literally so
incredibly talented and one of the
nicest people I've ever met in the
entire world yes of course today's video
did not exactly work out like I wanted
it to but it had a no correlation to the
makeup whatsoever at all it was my own
personal issues that we'll get into in a
second and I just want to say thank you
to her for taking the time out of her
day to make those prosthetics to mold my
face to apply that that took five hours
this morning and it was truly one of the
coolest processes and makeup that I've
ever been a part of and actually got me
so into special effects makeup I
definitely wanna do more research and
learn a lot about it but major shadows -
Channing and I also want to say a major
thank you as well - beautycon for their
entire team for not only hooking me and
my team up with talent passes very very
last second and also for letting us film
that was super super awesome and this
concept was something that I really
wanted to do was super excited about so
I was really happy that they were
supportive of me as a creator to allow
me to do that in their convention today
all that being said I don't really talk
about my feelings that often on YouTube
I am very much an open book but usually
an open book of positivity and
creativity and marketing and all sorts
of things I've talked about all the time
in my videos but it's not very often
that you guys see me being vulnerable
and the truth is that I don't really
like being a vulnerable I myself have
never before suffered with anxiety I
know a lot about it because a lot of
really important people in my life have
it of course I've been nervous and I've
been anxious for different things
happening but I've never really suffered
with true anxiety and today I think what
I had was an anxiety attack and I'm
still really confused about it I'm still
a little bit shaken up I'm still sister
shock there's not
time for jokes sorry but that's just how
I cope with these type of things and I
just wanted to sit down and kind of talk
to you guys about it because for the
past two or so hours on the way home
from beautycon to getting on transformed
to then taking a shower including myself
up I've been thinking a lot about why
today went how it did and how I feel
about it
and I think I've actually been able to
successfully kind of like really dig
into why I was sort of nerve-wracking
and I just wanted to talk to you guys
about it in case anybody else has a
similar situation a similar scenario
because the city was supposed to start
off for a very light-hearted a super
positive I wanted to start off by going
into the convention and and having
different influencers that seeing if my
friends recognized me and then
eventually going to bunch of the
different brands talking to brands on
who their influencers that they love
working with were asking if I myself
Steve could be on PR lists I really
wanted to go into the public area
beautycon didn't really talk to fans but
for some reason when I walked into just
the backstage kind of like talent area I
something came over me and I was even
experiencing this in the car on the way
there I was really really nervous but
something came over me once I walked in
that was like a feeling probably the
most similar feeling that I've ever
experienced this and was when I landed
in Africa after the Ebola scandal like I
saying beauty Khanna was in on this
video I had told them a few days ago
that I was going to do this they gave me
the okay which I was super appreciative
of the first step of my video of course
was to talk to different influencers
that I knew because all of them know me
very very very well all then pretty much
caught on quickly which was funny but
also was a little bit disheartening
because I really really tried to hide
myself almost every single of them said
that it was my boys that gave it away
which of course me and Jenny were
talking about earlier we knew is this
gonna be anything that was gonna give it
away it will be my voice let's be real
the space can be transformed but the
Salang s voice is not going anywhere no
matter how much I try to change it no
matter how much I deepen it no matter
what country I try to pretend like I'm
from it's me and it gave it away pretty
quickly which already kind of put me in
a weirdest mood going into it I got a
little bit discouraged but I was so
ready to go super excited I think it's
kind of got a little bit awkward and
escalated for me personally once I sat
down and talked to my really good friend
Nikita dragon now me and Nikita have
been friends for literally three years
now she
probably one of the first influences I
ever met I remember going to my first
ever gem duty like I was talking about
in the last video and Nikita was so
sweet to me she invited me to her
birthday party that night and I couldn't
go because I was underage but she was
just super super welcoming and Nikita
and I have grown really really close
over the past few years we tell each
other everything I know her family so
what I went up to her I'd actually made
eye contact with Naheed his mom and she
kind of made a face like I know this
person but I don't know this person so I
was like Shh so she knew something was
up and when I went to sit down with her
Nikita I know figured it out right away
but Nikita if you know her is very
playful she loves drama she loves acting
she's super super funny so when I sat
down with her to ask her if I could
interview her she was like oh yes of
course and she knew exactly what was
going on but her management team was
like oh no we're not doing any questions
right now and Nikita's assistant was
also right there and she sought me a
super super nasty look because I knew
Nikita knew what was going on I kept
talking to her and because I'm so close
to Nikita I was getting closer to her
and asking her questions even though
both her manager team and her assistant
told me to stop which is totally my
fault for not realizing like Hello
they're not supposed to know that it's
me looking at now I am so glad that that
happened because I was a very very
creepy looking busted crusted dusted man
asking very very forceful questions
which should not be happening to anybody
in the entire world and I'm really
really glad that Nikita had a publicist
and a security guard there to be like
get out of here Krause
we're now stopped talking to my client
but in the moment because I myself was
still James in a different body per se
it was a very very uncomfortable moment
for me of course once things started
escalating and Nikita told them what was
going on and we all laughed about it and
it was fine but it still kind of left a
weird feeling in my stomach and after
Nikita I moved on to a few different
smaller influencers that I have seen on
my explore page and that I know by name
but I've never really met in person and
don't have like a close relationship
with that that make sense
I was ardent control but these
conversations is what really masses my
head really badly and made me want to
leave so bad and kind of ruin the whole
thing of course I was able to pull a few
people who didn't quite catch on at
first and a Rubens mate who's another
really little boy and makeup was
literally saying the sweetest things
about me I need to not even realize I
literally adore him he is so sweet and
that made my day so so so much but
unfortunately his conversation was
probably the first one
out of all the influences that I talked
to after that and they were not like
that at all I'm not including I need the
footage in this video because the point
of this was not to expose anybody or
start drama it was literally a
light-hearted video that unfortunately
had a turn
but like 90% of the influencers that I
went up to trying to ask interview
questions with were so beyond rude and
so nasty and me it definitely was a
little bit of an ego trip which I will
100% admit because me as someone who was
already scared to this video in the
first place was walking around a beauty
convention with a camera woman and a
writer and a microphone and that was it
while a lot of these fellow influencers
that had like 100,000 followers that
have talked so poorly about me in the
past but I still want to interview
because I thought it would be good for
the video had full security teams around
them which I found a little bit strange
and when I went up to them trying to ask
them if they would do the interview it
was either the info to themselves being
very very nasty and keep in mind gasps
of course I'm like crusty just did
busted old man asking a young kid to do
an interview it's okay to say no I do
not blame them but it could have been a
simple no thank you I don't have time
right now but it's easier than being
really really nasty or their security
guard which they definitely do not need
being also nasty as well it was just a
weird situation I'm gonna be honest when
I'm saying this and I know that I get a
lot of comments about this so I kind of
want to explain where I'm coming from
because I never address this and I
always just delete the comments cuz I
find it annoying but I do understand why
this experiment was a major ego check
for me but also a confidence check for
me and my confidence comes from my work
which has built my reputation when I
first when the beauty industry a few
years ago I was a boy of course and I
was also sixteen years old so because of
that a lot of people already didn't take
me seriously and those are factors
obviously that I cannot control but
there's also a lot of things that I
could control that were my own fault
that kind of ruined my reputation in the
industry very very early on I got
involved with a lot of drama I fought
with a lot of different influencers of
course now that I'm okay with but a lot
of influencers and because
that a lot of influencers of course work
very closely with brands which you guys
all know so I lost out on a lot of huge
branded opportunities and I also had of
course we all know those a lot of
scandals as well so despite the fact
that I was gaining followers pretty
quickly from viral posts I didn't
exactly have the best reputation
internally and although I was getting
hate online what I truly care about is
the people around me and that's always
than have a person that I'd been on
Twitter and Instagram when I was first
starting off there were so many
influencers that I was once really close
friends with and then the next day on
Twitter they'd be tweeting about how I
was a horrible person because they saw
scandal and they wanted to join in and
be a part of that bandwagon or so many
parties that I would go to and talk to
people that I thought were my friend and
then they would end up talking about me
badly on snapchat that same night behind
my back well I guess not behind my back
in front of millions of people I guess
early on I did not I just didn't have
the best experience coming into the
industry and it's something that I've
had to kind of deal with and fix those
relationships and also build back my
reputation through hard work over the
past three years a long time ago when I
kind of have this like a reality check
of oh my god James you're getting into
so much drama like stop I had really had
to make a mental note to get away from
it and stop saying things about people
and stop talking about other people and
stop being shady and rude it's just
unnecessary and one of my ways to kind
of cope with that and to fix it was to
kind of take a step back from the beauty
community and really focus on my true
friends outside of the industry and not
really attend many events and not do
that many brand deals anymore and that's
kind of the way that I have ruled for
the past probably year or so I'm just
like really private with my team and the
people that I love the most but today
kind of reminded me exactly why I
stopped going to those events because
just the feeling and the air and the
attitude and the egos and the
entitlement from some of the people you
can just tell that it's just a I don't
even know how to explain it to you grace
it's just a feeling that you get you
just feel like you're not wanted in a
room and that your presence to somebody
else is not taken seriously for their
sake I just hope that like myself they
realize how ugly it is and will try to
turn that around because take it from me
as someone who has been down that path
you will have to do a lot of work to fix
that one day and that work is not fun
because of both things that I couldn't
control
my age but also things that were
hundred-percent my faults such as my
scandals and also my dramatic attitude
in the beginning I've had to work twice
as hard as everybody else for the past
three years to build up a reputation to
show people that I'm not a horrible kid
and to show people that I do have talent
and that I want to work hard and that I
deserve to be where I am today and I
know that I always preach this as well
like move silently and let her success
speak for herself but I will admit that
that's always a battle that I've had a
fight internally and I of course do
always catch myself and I try to stay
humble and I try to really put my ego
aside but it's not really me thinking
that I'm the best and thinking that like
I'm the queen it's me defending that
position because of the fact that I had
so many things working against me when I
first started and I think that that
saying that I really realized today and
saying that I kind of need to get over
in my existence to really not depend on
my reputation because at the end of the
day I love what I do and I worked so
hard for what I do and they'll always be
people following and supporting me no
matter what and I think this has been a
really great you go check for me because
I quickly realized that today was
triggered for me because it wasn't me
James Charles is confident I love myself
I am so happy around my fans and around
strangers I can be bubbly I can be
myself I am not ashamed of that and I
love Who I am and I can talk to anybody
and that's why I do my shaders doing
makeup videos because they're so much
fun and they get to travel in new places
and experience new people and also me
you says his along the way but for some
reason today having to play a different
persona and to kind of hide everything
that I've worked over the past few years
to show people was so weird and I could
not do it and it was literally like
taking my persona of talking fast of
using their hands and having their nails
on and having their Julia that they've
worked hours and hours and hours of
sleepless nights for and being able to
wear a full face of makeup and sow their
hair really nicely and have cute clothes
and also not having to throw that all
away to having nobody know who I am have
nobody know what I've worked for what I
stand for and having to be a totally
different person who was literally polar
opposite of myself
I I could not do it it it was weird
and I felt generally trapped under all
that makeup and all that hair and that
beard and I felt like I was literally
becoming Steve who nobody knew and a lot
of people were tweeting very very poorly
and it kind of brought me back to how I
was feeling in the beginning of the
industry feeling very very unwelcomed
feeling unliked feeling unwanted and my
brain started running at a million miles
per hour and that's kind of where the
anxiety attack came from and that's why
I needed to get out of that situation
and get that makeup off and come back as
me and not because I needed to feel
famous or because I needed the attention
but because I have worked so hard over
the past few years to fix myself I'm not
even gonna stop talking because it's
Aaron I have worked so hard to decks
that reputation and really show people
my true colors and show people that I am
a good person and show people that I do
have so much love in my heart and I know
that that should come across naturally
and it's not saying that I should worry
about or care about but I can't sit here
pretend like at something that is
bothering to me because it really is I
do care about how people think of me and
how people look at me and I wish I could
say that I did it I'm sure we all do and
I do have a very very thick skin that I
have had to build because I was forced
to grow up in an industry very very
quickly but at the end of the day it
still does get to me from time to time
and it's something that I've had to deal
with it's been a constant battle
internally and a lot of the battle was a
hundred percent my fault and I know that
and I'm okay with that
but it's been a hard battle to fight and
it's been a battle that I finally felt
like within the past few months I
started to win and today all the sudden
I went back to square one and it was
like losing the battle altogether at the
end of the day although this experience
was very very hard for me to go through
I think I learned three very very
valuable lessons one being I myself now
need to really fight this internal
battle more than ever of not only
letting my success really speak for
herself and not having to worry about my
reputation but really not letting my
confidence come from my work
really looking back at today I'm not
realizing that I do have a major issue
of that and a lot of my confidence does
come from the fact that I've had a fight
to get to where I am today and it feels
like a battle that I finally won and
whenever you win of course you feel
really really powerful you feel great
and you feel just on top of the world
and that's what I've been feeling the
past few months because you guys are
always so supportive of me and you guys
are really enjoying my content and that
makes me so proud as a content creator
and I feel like we've won that battle
together but I don't want my internal
confidence to come from that battle
I need that confidence to come from
self-love and that's something that I
will be working on definitely after
filming this video today because that's
bad and it shouldn't be that way too
I kind of really experienced a lesson
that I had learned many many years ago
very very early on that I thought
everybody else was on the same page as
but I was clearly wrong and that is that
no matter who you're talking to you
always need to be polite no matter who
they are what they look like what their
size is what their color is what their
makeup looks like what their hair looks
like because you never know who you're
really talking to it you never know who
so much related to be never know who
someone's working with and you never
know what opportunities or what
friendship someone could bring you in
the future and as it influencer in the
space take me out of the equation
because I would say the same thing to
any other smaller influencer there were
a lot of really small influencers today
that I have loved and I thought were so
talented and that were so incredibly
rude and those people relationship with
me that could be very valuable to them
or it could be a really great friend to
them I love making new friends I'm a
pretty good person if I do say so myself
and I've done the same thing early on to
a lot of different people and I ruined a
lot of relationships and friendships and
reputations being my own that I had a
fix for a very very long time so I
really hope that that's a lesson that a
lot of people were able to take from
this video because it's a valuable one
and you should always treat people how
you want to be treated that's something
that I have really taught myself to live
by within the past few years of the
beauty community because it's a
dog-eat-dog world and at the end of the
day you just need to be supportive of
everyone because we're all in the same
business that we're all fighting
together and last but finally not least
three I learned that I should never ever
in my entire life love
facial hair grow out to a full beard
because it looks the absolute worst all
right guys I think that is all I have
for this video silly I hope you enjoyed
this kind of more like one on one
conversation I don't really do this very
often and like I was saying it's because
I don't really like coming across as
vulnerable
I like being really positive I like
inspiring you guys I like making you
guys happy and this stuff for me is
saying that I don't really talking about
but at the end of the day if it could
help anybody that's why I want to talk
about it and I really hope you guys were
able to learn stuff lesson from this
video because lord knows I did that I
would definitely be taking with me and I
hope you enjoyed it I want to say
another thank you to Channing who is a
little he's so talented please go check
her out I'm gonna leave all of her links
in the description box below show her
some love she did such an amazing job on
the transformation I also want to thank
you t-con for letting me attend today
they were all so sweet and I want to
thank you guys for following and
supporting me since day one
from the drama to the internal battle of
having to work my way up to where I am
today and it really means a lot that you
guys have been with me through all that
and have seen through me and I've seen
my intentions and my love and my passion
for what I do so thank you guys oh I
don't wanna start crying
ah what the heck
thank you um thank you guys for watching
today's video I love you and I guess I
will see you in the next one bye
[Music]
you