good eye sisters James talks here
welcome back to my youtube channel that
was good in frosh
so for today's video I thought it'd be
so much fun to do something that we are
seated over in my homeland which is Los
Angeles such as strangers they make up
on Hollywood Boulevard but clearly we
are not in Hollywood or on a boulevard
we are in Surfers Paradise here on the
Gold Coast and I thought I would stand
here today and let a bunch of strangers
do my makeup so last video I know there
were a ton of sisters hopefully there'll
be a lot of sisters here today hopefully
I'll also go to get cleaned up by some
really hot surfer dudes as well with
some washboard abs in six-packs that we
can find in the water as you can see the
ocean is very clear today so the chances
of that
like my relationship life are looking
very very slim we tied it to this
yesterday and for some reason the world
was just really really a gun stuff this
could either go really really good or
really really bad doo doo doo doo doo
doo doo
it's accordingly we die here on the Gold
Coast and none of the sisters are
showing off hello sister Siegel would
you like to do my glom and they're
having the best luck there's a lot of
birds here ah did we leave the brushes
in the hotel
I knew this video is also to happen
today you're kidding again this morning
and hopefully I'll be able to get fully
glam will I look great well I like a
busted crusted must have dusted rusted
you guys are gonna have to find out and
let's get glam I know you well love me
being the Queen a member here guys this
is sister Kiki hello she was the number
one person in line at my pack fair
meeting great a few days ago there was a
7,000 people there and this sister 23
hours why sure that did not seem too
confident
Oh walk me through be a beauty guru okay
no it's very early in the morning but
there's a lot of people here in school
uniforms did you skip school today yeah
that's a dedicated sister they're not
mistakes that's me when I'm talking to
my PR team after I have another scandal
I get everywhere girl can't forget to
blend on the neck looking beautiful
always oh thanks girl disagreed love you
the most ever thank you for waiting in
line for 23 hours god bless you alright
guys so next let's move on to our next
up what's going to be concealer what is
your name Zara how old are you 11 you
want to do my concealer today yes have
you ever worn makeup in your entire life
yes love a glam sisters are put on my
concealer yes gofal oh sorry
this is taut shape type contour
concealer so we're just gonna put it
under the eyes does your mom bring you
here yeah I made it
wow this is like a dream come true I
can't tell you
you're so cute I literally love with you
right now we're done with a concealer
already I'm scared
who your favorite beauty gurus to watch
online what class would you be in school
right now missing I'm some primary
school so I'd probably be missing on my
spelling test
maybe semester spelling us either yeah
yeah yeah who cares I'm stalling as long
as you can tell James Charles and the
word sister we're good can you spell
sister yes I st thank god we're good I
learned while being in Australia that
there's a hole in the ozone layer right
above this country and that's really sad
so I need to powder myself before I'm
out hi sister hi what is your name
nice to meet you since I love your
freckles Thanks are you also supposed to
be in school right now yeah wow I love
all of you guys okay do you want to
powder me up yeah I do it walk us
through what you're doing that's it oh
I'm scared okay a quick glam sister
thanks girl
okay so next we have to contour who
wants it shows on my face out nice to
meet you what is your name Cooper our
sister Cooper do you want to come to my
face today do you know how to contour
okay love that are you also in school
today wow this is good I'm gonna get a
lawsuit from all the Australian schools
coming at me have you ever worn makeup
before would you ever do makeup do you
think love died what's your like
favorite part about makeup thank you
sister Cooper you were literally at the
bust okay guys so now we were all snot
and ready to go so now I think we need
to do like blush and baking
perhaps hi sister oh my god you are
literally beautiful nice to meet you
thank you oh my god well do you think
you cannot blush me and then baked my
face today sure myself but you know
first time for everything I love that we
happen to get everybody who doesn't wear
makeup everybody's just so beautiful
here give me three Australian slang
things that I like need to know I've
learned that nobody says shrimp on a
Bobby why is that like to go to American
like Australian things oh sure I'm on Oh
mommy I'm like what even is that shrimp
isn't even a thing here it's prawns
now you want to bake me up yeah okay
bake me girl do you wanna have somebody
else do baking yeah give someone else do
you want to make me up we love baking do
you have three Australian slang terms
not really we're baking the oven yeah
what degree would you guys don't have
degrees oh wait yes you do
interesting Celsius what's your unit of
measurement Celsius wow you're really
good eyebrows I feel like I trust you
with my brows come here what is your
name you're really good in fresh
eyebrows thank you do you think you can
fill in minds today well everyone's
letting me down I'll show you to love
themselves this has been a PSA we have
everything you could possibly need right
here
eyebrows who uses powder in their
eyebrows like I say I look good I guess
I'll give you that one walk us through
your routine okay brush the mouth always
got a sister spoolie first what is
Vegemite okay Vegemite is a spread that
you put on bread or toast you don't eat
it with a spoon you just spread it on
bread without shading it Ethan agree son
yes what does it taste like interesting
what are other Australian foods that I
need to try
I've already in 86 packs of Tim Tams
they're really good in frost I'm gonna
like smuggle million boxes back with me
hopefully Border Patrol doesn't get me
good you have to be confident you can do
that you have to say I love the
prostatitis pond James Charles's face
there we go that's all we need thanks
mister okay let's move on to the sister
eyeshadow now hello sister you haven't
really
I shadow on I feel like I trust you to
do mine today okay okay well sister
Sophie I want you to let me up tonight
what kind of looked you want to go for
what pants do you have I have the john
the morphe 35o I want to have you do one
eye and then have somebody else try to
match it I use code that's right that's
what I thought thank you uh-huh thing to
do honestly everything here's been
absolutely amazing the day we landed
from the plane I got to go see all the
classic Australian animals and they were
so cute yeah I got to me a koala and
hold one and he was literally the cutest
I miss him I want to adopt a koala I
think right now and smuggle in dr.
America I'll be very friend upon and
then I also got to be the kangaroo and
he was also so sweet I was scared of
getting kicked the entire time but it
was good I don't think in general
everything here is so beautiful also I
don't really get to do that many like me
great stuff just cause I'm always
filming and working so like the fact
that I'm here on tour is so beyond
excited because it's just like I get to
meet everybody and say hi yeah across
the world hello so fun are you doing
this entire look with one brush we love
a recycling Queen a soft light pink on
the I just had soft ah the lips is
coming back we're done I love you the
most in the entire world
oh thanks gross should we oughta bring
Leonard here I'll look do you think what
is your name Dylan are you confident
ability to give me a good impression 20%
confident oh thank god we needed okay so
I'm gonna start in the middle of the eye
and I'm gonna drag it up and out because
the eye shadow is already really winging
at so we'll follow that contour we love
a beauty guru do you have a cup on a
daily basis yeah so I wait makeup only
when I really do like Instagram looks
same stuff like that so I haven't gotten
makeup not so much like everyday glam
say mom oh my god not twinning sisters
James and Dylan what would you say is
the best no-carb anywhere
I love being robbed what would you say
is the best way for gay hookups in
Australia
definitely grind up I disagree I don't
know me my manager Vernon grinder the
entire weekend have not had any luck we
where are they I have no idea I'm from
Melbourne I flew out today what but now
I'm gonna start on the inner core not
make it really thin and gradually get
thicker so it matches the outside
thank you sister all right so now we
have one eye all complete and okay let's
see if we can find someone else to do
with the other half of my face talena oh
my god do you think you can match the
other half of my eyeshadow do you do
makeup yes okay great we love this
confidence level look like me up now you
can match the other eye if you want or
you can do your own brush true size or
have you ever used more people before I
can tell that Yorkshire are desks are
you self-taught makeup from like
watching videos are like what how are
you guys me honestly with everything I
love this squatting that I'm doing right
now for coming for my career
Oh Shelly it's so clean I've noticed
America cannot really unfortunately
that Sun is so bright oh wait this guy's
so pretty looking now one thing that I
need to do before I leave Australia what
is that
so I've been trying with absolutely zero
la tried tinder tinder does not like me
they were deleted my account three times
done hello surfer daddy come here would
you like to be in my video hello hey
going I'm amazing now how are you what's
your name
Nick hi sister knack will you put on my
eyelashes today I'll give it a go
you think you could figure out how to
put on my lashes it will be a bit of a
battle we love a good battle no this is
your job have you ever done makeup in
your entire life you don't need it
you're kind of hot
have you ever watched a beauty video in
your entire life sadly no I can tell
okay
like help me through I guess I mean I do
love doing charity work and you're kind
of hot so I guess we can today and then
we also have some glue you hold this if
you glue this wrong you could make me
fall blind so no pressure so Nick what
do you do play cricket actually I think
I've got the hardest job here so if I
can put ashes on I can do any type of
makeup then I love straight people you
still had a hard time getting my last
glue open and people say beauty isn't
hard try to put it right next to my
eyelashes like right on top good I don't
know you tell me nope you're on duty
neck
I'm keeping us much time with you as I
possibly can are we done I think so
are you stressed I can see a bead of
sweat running down your nose right now
it's not a lot on the street people
thank you sister deck that was great
work so the eyes are all complete hello
beautiful what is your name Ivana do you
want to do my mascara today I'm gonna be
like a koala bear already sleeping in
the tree thank you
really you're welcome I love doing
charity work no I'm like one of the best
weeks of my entire life what is your
favorite and least favorite thing about
Australia I love the web app because
it's like pretty much always sunny yeah
what's your everything about earlier I
don't - your internet connection it
sucks it's the worst maybe it's just the
hotels you've been singer Wi-Fi and the
service
dottie Nick do with the lashes he's
pretty good okay good
Thank You long okay guys we're almost
done so now we have to move on to the
glow nice to meet you what is your name
Malika that's a Briton or her
her life your eyes are so pretty well
how does the glam look so far we love
that adjective okay let's go that's a
pair in the world I'm being attacked
that's right
bonuses are talking pop I want to be
brighter than the Sun that's shining
through the broken ozone layer here what
is like the legal working age in
Australia 14 nine months what 14 and 9
months die is the weirdest number I've
ever heard in my entire life 14 why nine
months I never highly be there before
there's gonna be a shining sister done
so we're pretty much all glam I still
have not seen anything but we have a few
more steps to do before we were all
complete starting with the lipid II
doodahs let's find somebody to get them
good
hi sister what is her name Lydia Lydia
you're so cute you wanna do my lipstick
today um yes thank you alright guys so
that means we're all done but our last
step is going to be some sister settings
ready to lock up all in place and
hopefully not melt under this very very
bright and blinding Sun which has been
obstructing my vision for this entire
video so that's been great
hello what is your name Dominic Dominic
you're very nice to meet you your
tattoos are nice too
do you want to finish off my makeup
today yeah were you from Germany is this
your first time in Australia yes what
first them where do you think I am from
Los Angeles have you ever been there
before
would you like to go yeah you should
come back with us yeah yes we'll
definitely take you with us pal I love
that okay don't you wanna finish me off
today holy love good whoa I'm done for
that as well something that gave me a
good and fresh spray with this yes no on
me on you yes yes yeah
yes daddy
yeah we love that well yeah sure yeah
yeah it's totally good I'm probably a
little bit what right now in both ways
if you know what I'm saying here you
want to give yourself a good spreads to
know okay thank you
I'm literally dripping wet Dominic got
me go ahead all right sister so that is
the glam all completely we had a bunch
of scissors of course they always come
through no matter where we are in the
world
a few changers and also a few really
really hot guys I literally am in love
with Australia but I think it is time
for the grand Ruby all Casimir please
ready three two one Oh literally this
scan looks great well you guys this is
really good the whale eye liner is
taking off we love the winged eyeliner
thanks guys with a little bit of face
and I feel like this could definitely be
Instagram ready this is really good and
fries ready for the glow where is that
the Sun is too bright there we go
we love how this turned out even sister
Nick did a really good job of being a DA
Dinkley on my eyelashes
even though sister Dominic almost
probably melted the glue off with the
amount of X plus that he just use but
it's okay we love hot boys here on the
team's channel to youtube channel
alright you guys notice all I have for
this video today I literally had so much
fun doing this I am literally I love
about Shelly it needs to come back asap
definitely become a double and tell me
where you want to see me get glammed by
a bunch of strangers and hopefully as
lawyers a bunch of sisters next if you
guys enjoy this video today please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below subscribe if you have not already
come during the sister does the pretty
lit time it's like that Bell icon so you
can notified every time I upload a brand
new video
apparently YouTube is changing their
algorithm where videos are not in order
anymore of course so don't forget to
notified once again every time hundred
to video if you like to follow me on I
make up turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both the
same Charles my snapshot from aura
behind see myself is James Charles so
that actually asked after Charles this
dinner sisters how that goes to sister
Trinity thank you so much pain for
installing it's for you I love you so so
so much and if you like to be the next
videos sister shadow don't forget toys
we treat Billings I go live on Twitter
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching this video today I love you so
much and I will see you in the next one
bye
[Music]