hi sisters James Charles here welcome
back to my youtube channel you guys for
today's video I'm done to the very very
special guests Jacque Liddell for
today's video we're gonna be having a
really fine a competition that we've
never actually done before on this
channel or basically we're just gonna
sit and talk and by the end of it we're
gonna see whichever video is made first
Java Hill annoying James Charles for two
minutes straight or vice versa so
without further to go but alters this
guy's this club means so much to me and
I'm super said I do sitting with
Jacqueline today she's a huge role model
of mine and now I'm supposed to call her
a friend and as well we have very very
different styles in the beauty world so
I figured it would only be right to do a
s style soft today with sister
Jacqueline if you guys didn't know if
that is it is a series that you hear my
YouTube channel where I pick what my
favorite beauty gurus and we swap makeup
bags and give each other one of our
iconic looks and challenge each other a
little bit and talk about the community
it drama life and everything in between
so without further ado let's get our
style you talked so fast that sometimes
I'm just like like your brain just like
fun you get a lot of information in a
short period of time I feel like you're
on 1.5 speed I'm having my first ever
pinky drink at eat how do you feel give
us a review it's really sweet but good
right I feel like I'm gonna have massive
gasps I'm just waiting for the explosive
diarrhea that's the search are basically
we're gonna start off I selected a luck
of mine that I want chocolate to
recreate and I packed up all of my glam
goodies in my makeup bag and I'm getting
to give this to her I have my makeup bag
which is much bigger than his because
I'm out of town for two weeks so we saw
each other luckily picked out one dog
well all my looks are the same so I
didn't think it'd be too difficult
[Music]
literally is like a red smokey eye leave
no lipstick Nick did that one it's
literally it's a red blown-out smokey
eye okay yes a good and fresh copper
shimmer like a little bit of a cut
crease but more than anything just like
really intense like
like I bring like the orange I got buff
it down lig into my blush like major
like okay down for that okay
so this look that I picked out for you
is one that I think brass represents me
obviously that you probably would
never do but I really want to see this
on your eyes today because you have the
perfect eye shape for this I picked out
my rainbow cut crease oh my gosh which I
think will be really good it's also
Pride Month so that's my month oh my god
I think it'll be good that's a hearty
beautiful okay so we have our looks all
picked out and ready to go oh Jesus
Christ oh my god Jocelyn why it's like
800 pounds I'm gonna start off with the
chocolates do your skin forever
foundation I've never what do you use
for Prime in this bag except for the
touch SLE canvas which I lost so for
your foundation you have worn this way
I've never used this foundation in my
life what this foundation sells a
cleaning supply is kind of what's your
nationality why is I have so many things
but I want to ask you and then I want to
talk to you about today what got you
started into my god and to make up or
into YouTube makeup I guess my mom is
being such a beauty girl my mom has
always been obsessed with makeup and
fashion and hair and like she just hid
her vanity every single night before she
washed her face and played with her
makeup and I'm so burned watch her she
just vehicle I'm just teaching myself
new techniques and she played makeup
like an hour every single night and then
she wash her face and go to bed and so I
just watched her do it and I was like I
love this he's got interested in it
but it's so cool and why did you start
YouTube I started doing YouTube because
everyone on instagram has asked me for
after my Instagram page started gaining
followers but I started doing makeup and
predominantly because of this right here
sitting next to me every single time you
say that I still don't believe you and I
think it's so cool yeah sort of all the
growth that you've had and being so
young and having this incredible success
so quickly but you are still able to
like sit here and give credit to
somebody
I think the humble of you and so cool of
you because most people when they get to
like your stature they would not even
remember that and they would be like oh
well I did this on my
you know what I'm saying and I think
it's really cool like you still sit here
to say that about me and that really
like it's very humbling for me and it
inspires me I remember literally being
like 11 12 13 not doing makeup yacht but
watching all the beauty tutorials and
like Jacqueline was like the main one
that I would always watch like when you
were sitting on your floor still working
it back and the way I just number like
everything you'd put on your eyelids
because you have like the best eye shape
ever
I literally really I need that product
right now I was like I don't even wear
makeup what am i doing when I did
surgery makeup eventually you were like
the first beauty guru ever noticed me I
remember it vividly I remember actually
where I was sitting I was at my mom's
house and I was having dinner with my
family and it was a Sunday night like I
remember it perfectly and literally and
I reached out to him and I was like you
are so incredibly talented like I just
stalked your page for the past 20
minutes straight I can't get over it
like I did a green eye like I remember
that and tried my one that you did and I
was shocked by it I was just like oh my
god this kid is so talented and you
barely even had any photos and you had
5,000 followers and I was like oh my
gosh like he's gonna grow so much and I
was like you're so talented he was like
oh my god I'm screaming right now I
can't leave what you're talking I'm
freaking out like it was so sweet he was
so nice and then I screenshotted his
Instagram and I sent it to Linda the
owner of Moorefield like you've got to
check this guy out and you've got to
start sending him PR and so she did and
he freaked out he's like I'm crying
right now oh my god like it was I was so
sad that's like Oh James for 10% off
exists that's why it exists so you guys
actually can hate me for him always
shoving his coat down your throat I'm
gonna spread my face with the morphe
preference that sprite use Cote mister
can resolve a little bit I'm dry
encrusted you're gonna do that before
you go on with your under eye yeah on a
real note though like you obviously have
been in the industry for a long time
doing makeup forever so you've seen a
lot of things change what would you say
has been like your favorite makeup trend
that's like happened that it's like now
a really big thing and what's like your
favorite makeup lift Eve ever done oh my
gosh okay so as far as trend I would say
when Kim Kardashian and Mario posted
that picture of all that yellow and her
in her t-zone yeah I remember like that
was so iconic and there were articles
everywhere and everyone was like oh my
gosh what is this trend
dad was like my favorite moment and make
a pissed Sri as I've been around for as
an adult like witness like firsthand
because that changed my makeup routine
and it's something that we all utilize
now like we all put like light
and light powder in the center of our
face to really bring like everything
forward and create that heart shape yep
like that ideal face shape if you will
and that's all because of Kim and Mario
which is why no matter how much people
talk bad about Kim I'm always like she's
Shawn is really she's a legend when it
comes to this industry big time I'm
trying to think of my favorite makeup
look that I've done I can't even decide
let's just skip that and say it my
favorite look of yours you'd like a fire
and ice look a long time ago okay so let
me ask you and do not even pretend like
be honest how long does it take you to
truly do your makeup like not just your
doing like a quick beat which what is a
quick beat just to be honest I probably
like a quick beat like get ready like I
would take like an hour but like give me
an hour and a half just be like really
safe like I saw you're gonna sit down
and like really like go in on your face
now not like you're creative like it
looks like an event like just like yeah
evening look like how long is that gonna
take you like three hours whole devote
to it are you serious
yeah why sister James I am sugar but
it's fun for me like I like oh I get it
I love it yeah I don't really like to
sit down only have to do makeup when I'm
rushed of course like it'll come out by
literally and I'm not using this words
like sorry I cut you off that's what
I've known before I can see the videos I
get all excited I cut you off about 7:00
it's just gonna there's gonna be viral
videos of Jacqueline interrupting James
for five minutes straight I can see it
now can't we I don't personally know now
obviously I'm sure there's people out
there but I don't personally know
anybody who works as hard on their
content as you do like I cannot believe
how much work you put into your content
it shakes me like you will work on one
video for weeks months like you'll have
a concept and like you will focus so
much on it and like put so much effort
yeah that video that we're planning that
right in for over a year now and we're
like just finally now getting an
intuition it's crazy like you really
like you know what happens you guys
three years I've had this work be4 brush
to use cocaine for 10% off and it
finally just hit the bat after three
years I've washed this probably eighty
seven times oh don't lie you're dirty
even we wash it twice you're probably
right I'm not gonna lie don't mind me my
brows okay I'm gonna do some champagne a
pop OH
oh my god that launch party for this was
the first thing that we ever Matt I know
is that so crazy
it really is I still have those photos
on my phone oh my god I'm gonna pull
them right now I'm scared scared oh my
gosh my eyebrows took up half of my face
eyebrows are so big and even realized
how big they were back then it looks
like you got a no shop there queen of
contouring honestly I mean when you
don't have makeup on it looks the same
but when you make the final little like
you have a nose job yeah you gotten so
good at it I want you to do my makeup
give me a nose job and freckles speaking
of me doing your makeup obviously i
speedy guru is a weed or i'll make up
all the time but occasionally I know you
have gotten your makeup done who would
you say are like your favorite artist to
work with well Nicole who was known as
lipstick NIC you know I'm gonna be
honest is the only person who's ever
even done my makeup oh really mm-hmm
because I love her style so much we see
eye to eye she really gets my vision I
just love her so much but I would love
for re al to do my makeup yes oh I don't
have it or makeup too I don't love to
get me makeup done by hush as well
oh love to okay sister her oh Sh
I feel like those two people both like
get my vibe completely mm-hmm who are
your favorite artists well for like I
looks I really love a lot of the UK
artists so oh my god Marie I really want
Arielle doing makeup as well I think
he's so talented
I want Mario do eye makeup oh my gosh
why I didn't think about Mario I'm so
excited
next to it just crawling I was like hi
oh you use the brown to fine arch of
your brows ha yes I hate that to my
brother right now because I do not like
this thing I just don't like skinny
little ones I think I can't get the job
done dad's what she who likes a good ski
little one no we don't discriminate here
on the channel I asked you this earlier
like no don't tell me cuz I wanted you
to tell me on camera what is your sign
oh I'm a Gemini are you water earth fire
I don't know well I like some egg
I like the ground that I stand on her
not to be in the air and I would prefer
also not to be burned but I love a good
campfire so I need to know now hey
that's great my face idea isn't working
right now that's when you know that you
look alright
Oh kinda I'm finally moving on to eyes
now I think the Lord in heaven above
eighty seven years later enough my
eyebrows are finally even John we were
talking earlier how like you took a much
needed mental break for a while yes
yes as a close friend of you you didn't
need that very much so and now you're
kind of like slowly easing your weight
back into YouTube when you obviously got
on the platform for a very long time now
where do you think the industry and the
makeup communities kind of had it
because I feel like right now it's in a
little bit of like a rough moment it is
it's hard for creators right now yeah
it's way harder than it used to be and
like with all like the algorithm changes
like it's so different and it's so like
saturated now with so much content and
so much incredible content and so many
incredible artists and like it's a lot
to like be successful in this industry
now it was so much easier and so much
more simple back in the day people used
to just want makeup tutorials like
that's all they wanted and they feel
like now so many people are like okay we
know how to do makeup now like we want
more and they want like really
entertaining videos that have to do with
beauty and I think that's why your
channel is so incredibly successful
because you put so much effort into
doing that and it's very difficult to do
the kind of videos did you do but you
make it happen
where is I feel like my followers if I
don't do like makeup tutorials they get
upset yeah we want the makeup because
that's what I'm known for
yeah you know but I feel like that's
very rare like do you think you'll
forever do tutorials like do you want to
keep doing that well in that sense so
like you haven't here for a long time
your followers do love tutorials but do
you think you wanna branch out more and
they kind of join in with that like oh
absolutely
I would definitely love to do like
different content
once my editor and videographer moves
down he moves down mid-july I definitely
wanna be like branch out cuz now I like
have someone to actually warn me and not
just a tripod the things can be totally
different and I have a lot of ideas yeah
I'm really excited to actually branch
out and try new things for sure but I
can't wait for like the rebound
chocolate hell sister-sister sparkles
it's such an easy one you still gonna I
literally blow my own thought I don't
mind me I go yeah I usually pull that
out I am that's what I'm doing it I'll
pull it out farther I definitely took
this out a little bit far but you know
what
okay I'm gonna put Block in my waterline
now which if you guys are a true sister
you know I absolutely hate doing it oh
my god this is so dark and smoky and
spooky chuckling I feel you can blow
he's seeing a little bit oh no I can't
but I feel like I feel like Hardy's
thinking like it because you will like
include some sense of it in the edges of
your video sometimes I think you could I
have a long power but I don't have a
good voice can you match pets
I don't know I'm never tried like if I
sing oh we love a vocalist a singing
sister try to sing sober and not kiyose
like mom I'm so sorry I'm not so bad
anymore so you can't sing
what's your favorite song first of all I
know it's typical but like Ariana Grande
no tears left to cry so good has
literally been like mm-hmm
can you sing up my life
[Music]
you could say so different from me do
you literally use the word sister like
your normal life all the time
no the brand but like just like when
you're hanging out your friends yes I'm
using my own mascara because I'm Sam
yeah that's not something we should swap
oh my god if we swapped oh my God my
induction I would literally kill you
that's how many so many times I always
get sisters dies I'd be like not I did
my first time my second eyes gonna go
really fast yeah it always does how do
we feel about this I love it now
using a lot of blush I'm using docklands
lashes what's our flutter intoxicating
talks of hearing my favorite lashes mean
terrible ever really ever interesting
and I am using Lily lashes and the style
Miami which is a lash I would never ever
choose to wear myself just because this
style is so pretty it's beautiful
I love Lily lashes so much but this
style like my subscribers will know I
never ever ever wear lashes Apple
separates you I never realized I have
separation on them really ever alright
guys so Jocelyn and I both have one eye
done on camera we're gonna go ahead and
do the one off-camera
chitchat spell some sister tea and we'll
be right back to finish off the rest of
our lungs we're back bullfights are all
complete how do you feel so far I feel
like I don't match but I'm fine with
that we love it we love that this eye
stands out so much more than this one I
feel like like this eye all around
stands out more yeah
I'm look yeah ooh and I never do like
blues and purples on myself ever no I
like my I like this just brings more
attention to it oh good Queen of the
game is happy pride
right okay I'm gonna grab the morphe a
blush palette which one do you like out
of this I always use this one this one
or that one you really love a good blush
oh my god I'm obsessed with blush I
apply blush like four times over and
over today well how do we have in your
bag Oh put on too much blood No
you need to go heavy love pink cheeked
okay what how did you bring serious oh
did you forget it no no I understand
yeah so you what makes you love this one
so much it's just really pretty in gold
and I think a lot of gold highlighter is
either too silvery or like too orange
yeah hello
so she's like the perfect like middle
shade but who's to say that there won't
be a better one coming out of enjoy I'm
gonna highlight once again for the
second time something pop I'm
highlighting to the heavens I'm
literally having my entire face I'm just
like okay I'm ready for lips I was going
over my foundation lips cuz I just don't
care we love a crusty sister we really
do honestly truly I'm using James
Charles
lipstick right now which is kind of like
decimated we're like almost making out
that's kind of hot so sister sexy okay
chocolate I know well I'm doing my lipid
you do does I have one last question for
you that I think I'm really excited to
hear your answer for how can I help you
obviously time this on a really really
positive note you inspired me as we were
talking earlier to like join this entity
in the first place and you truly I feel
like have been such a pioneer and
someone who like for fronted the makeup
on the internet revolution so this club
meant a lot to me and I have one
question for you would be what piece of
advice would you give to any young girls
or boys out there who want experiment
with makeup or who may want to be like a
beauty influencer one day I would say as
far as advice to you know someone
wanting to get started in this industry
or just loving makeup girl or boy is to
honestly not be intimidated by all the
incredible artists out there because
especially now with how many amazing
artists aren't Instagram like when I was
younger I didn't have social media to
run to like it was like the beauty
magazines and what you saw on TV and now
it's like you just like turn on your
phone and it's everywhere and it's such
an incredible makeup and then on top of
like the photo shop in the face tuning
and some of it is so over the top and
they're completely doing their their
makeup literally with Photoshop and bass
tuned and it doesn't look like that at
all in person so and to not be
intimidated by someone who has been
doing makeup for years you know like us
when we started we all had moments of
absolute suckage I think even you like
starting off you were so incredible just
right out the gate and that's extremely
rare but still when I see you do looks
now compared to when you started on my
whoa oh my gosh luck marry we've all had
makeup I didn't realize how much better
you could get like you're blending has
gotten better your contour has gotten
better your everything is gone better
you know you know you were so incredible
just starting off I personally did not
start off great like I've always had a
knack for I've always loved it you know
I was self-taught but like I used to be
very harsh literally a lot of harsh
lines I would just say to not be
intimidated by everybody else who has
been practicing for a long time and
working really hard at their artistry so
definitely not to be intimidated there
are so many talented artists out there
and I'm always exerting for a new talent
and for a new and upcoming artists that
you can help out or support or like Paul
or just like to check out and get
inspiration in general and one thing I
see all the time are people who are so
incredibly talented but I often times
see a lot of people that like have the
best talent but just complaining on
Twitter all day long about them not
getting recognized or they're not making
it are them not getting brand deals and
stuff you have to be focused on the
talent but what's really gonna get you
to the top is your personality there was
a moment on YouTube where like everyone
was copying everyone like whoever was
getting views everybody was trying to
act like that person just being yourself
don't think that you have to like overdo
it because someone who is getting tons
of views is acting that way
you know just honest to god being
yourself no matter what that looks like
don't know if you think that you're
weird or you're different we've all felt
that way and most people on YouTube
actually ran to this as an outlet
because they weren't accepted and
because they felt weird and because they
felt different and then on camera me
personally I'm speaking for myself I
couldn't believe that so many people
loved me like I could not believe it so
many people that wanted to hang out with
me and actually liked me and still to
this day when I do mean greets and
thousands of people show up I'm always
that what for me no matter how famous
anybody gets it's always the same
feeling every time it's always like the
whoa you never really said yeah so yeah
just be confident in yourself and just
be you no matter what I'm literally
gonna drench myself it's like you have
no idea I'm so ready make sure you guys
use code Jack Attack and all capo or
sweetie oh no that's awesome that's Cole
James Cole James for 10% off your
purchase that's great J t-shirt but
they're still gonna use Kojak they're
still gonna use containers that's why
mine's been the number one selling code
alright guys those are both looks for
this sister's style swap all complete
not gonna lie I do feel very very
beautiful I was
sister shucks in the beginning but I
love how this turned out how do you feel
I'm actually so shocked by how much I
like this eye right here that's the
thing that I can't stop staring at my
like I'm definitely inspired to start
wearing more like greens and blues cuz I
really never wear no clothes I love this
like this is very common for me but I'm
like why don't I start doing this kind
of stuff in it I love it I know I'm
really glad that you got me out of my
comfort zone so I saw this like I was
like it's so not me but I really I love
it Jacqueline I have not put block in my
waterlines and like a good yeah I know
I've never seen like this in my life no
he looks so in the viewfinder I can't
stop staring at you like I might be
looking at me I think I got that little
troll next it a little colorful troll
but you look so just like mm-hmm like
like I said I was a little bit spooked
to do this but I feel so beautiful and
you look the best ever in the entire
world
thank you for answering me literally
since day one I know I said them
beforehand but I'm literally not kidding
like you're the reason I already make up
in the first place and this cloud meant
the opposite world peso thank you for
even being here oh he's so sweet no
matter what the internet says he's very
sweet
oh no she's Kojak attack for everything
like I don't care where are you at
you're buying Tampax just try and if you
did it please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up and down below and scram
you have not ready come join the system
also please go subscribe to joseline
Hale she's a living legend a beauty
community everything that she puts on
her face you're gonna want to buy so be
careful but definitely go check her out
over on Jacqueline's head all we are
going to be eating is a mukbang always
long apparently so yeah I can't wait to
yeah I'm very excited if you like to
follow me on our makeup turn you can pop
me to Instagram and Twitter they're both
just a my snapshot from art behind see
if I sell ACA Charles the next rise
after Charles you can follow me on all
social zazz Jacqueline Hill and snapchat
is Jacqueline R Hill this video sister
Shawna closes sister Elora thank you so
much for your forties following its
already know I love you literally so so
so much and if you like to be the next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
always a retweet riveting still go live
on Twitter all right sisters I love you
so much thank you for watching and I
will see you in the next one bye guys
[Music]