okay hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back
to my youtube channel i know i'm not in
my normal studio setup i really just
wanted to pull up the vlog camera super
quickly and document this just in case
this video does become
a reality if this video is being
uploaded and you read the title down
below you already know what's happening
but we have decided to get a best friend
for
finnegan
[Music]
okay you guys so we are currently in the
car on the way to go meet the puppy we
have obviously lewis in the back we have
eldon driving the vehicle
thank god we've already been in the car
for about 30 minutes we have another
basically hour
to go because of la traffic it's also
kind of far away but we are literally so
beyond excited louis and i have been
talking about wanting to get another dog
for quite a long time now
luis was the one who really brought up
the idea several months ago
and i was into the idea but i kept
putting it off because
we were obviously renovating the new
house and the last thing that i wanted
to do
was adopt a new puppy in a construction
zone because that would be a disaster
and very
unsafe period but we are officially in
the new house we've gotten settled we
filmed the house for a video so i feel
like it's
honestly a good time to bring another
dogger to the family yeah
finn's also been what's the word uh
clinging oh my god so i
think it'd be really good um no we love
it and he'll also
feel really excited being able to play
with someone and keep up that energy
that he has we also researched the dogs
that would the breeds that would work
best
yeah okay let's talk about that okay so
a lot of people in our lives have french
ball dogs including alvin and cassie
two two of them and kawa and we love
love love them so much and we actually
were really interested in getting a
frenchie as well
but alvin was actually telling us about
their legs and their
like spine because going up and down
stairs a lot is not good for them since
their bodies are so short yeah
and obviously we've already done three
years in the house three levels do we
actually yeah 41 why did you count that
because it's a lot of stairs that's
obviously our main priorities that
obviously the dog has to
you know fit in with finn to be real i'm
not really concerned with it honestly
finn
has literally gotten along with every
dog he's ever come in contact with
he's the sweetest but ultimately we
decided that the breed we really wanted
to bring into the family was a lab labs
are super easy to train they're very
friendly family dogs which is
very important for us just like with
finn we still have people over all the
time
anyway we have about a 45 minute drive
still to go so
i will obviously keep you guys posted
and pull the camera whenever we get
closer to meeting our new puppy
but yeah see you guys soon
oh my god oh my gosh
he's adorable hi
hey big guy oh my gosh little boop on
the camera
do we need him i think we do
he's so sweet oh the bracelet's going
right for the bracelets
expensive taste yeah
yeah oh he's walking himself
hi big guy little prancer
all right you guys we are here at the
pet store my mask is matching the new
puppy and we're gonna go inside and get
him some
supplies oh hi big guy
i remember when we first got ben he was
pretty chill on the ride home
but if you guys watch our videos you
know the finn does not like the car so
i'm really really hoping that with this
pupper we're able to
kind of like warm it up to him a little
bit sooner that goes for a lot of things
too the pool
is one of those things like our
opportunity to do everything like even
better
than we did with finn
hey you guys so the puppy's first trip
to the pet store is complete we got him
a bed a bunch of different toys and a
little crate as well
he did pee on me slightly in the store
but you know what it's okay
accidents happen and now we have a very
very long drive home ahead of us
how old is he uh eight weeks so you're
bringing them home right now
yes congratulations
thanks guys your grandparents again what
is it a male or female it's a boy
he's so tired he's pretty calm actually
he's really calm hello
[Music]
okay you guys we've officially made it
home the pepper literally slept
all the way and now we are about to
bring him inside and introduce him to
finn
i should go in first and be on finn's
side yeah and i definitely think so
you can bring him in and drop him down
okay why don't you go in we'll
let him smell me okay here we go hey big
guy
oh my god oh my god he smells him oh my
god he's losing his mind
i really think that it's gonna be okay
finn is obviously such a good little
angel he's the sweetest everybody
oh my goodness he has been like our baby
for a year now and i
just don't know how he's going to react
having somebody else getting attention
oh my goodness are you excited good
point good boy
set go forward good boy stay stay okay
stay
okay
[Music]
me oh sure finn how do you feel about
this so far he is so cute
oh my god finn just really really wants
to play what the problem is he doesn't
know how big he is
it's crazy because alvin's two french
bulldogs are the ones that usually are
playing with finn but they are like
literal tasmanian devils just like
zooming everywhere bumping into each
other like head first like crazy
so finn's not used to like playing
gently oh he's really climbing those
stairs
very athletic oh
my god hey
good boy okay you guys the puppy's
having his first
meal little finn is watching from the
background being a good little boy
hi snooper we have the food that he was
already eating then we also have the
same brand that finn
um is usually on we mix in a little bit
of uh finn's brand into his
so we can ease him in so the guys are on
the same food he just took a little
nap and fell asleep on me while i was
watching a new episode of rupaul's drag
race at vegas review which is
so entertaining by the way i hope that
that doesn't mess up his sleeping
schedule because
i remember the first night with finn was
a nightmare
fingers crossed that it'll be all good
i'll play a little bit more tonight
before we go to bed and then he will
knock out and be ready to go again
tomorrow morning now it is time for our
dinner
trevor just lovely wet and go hello
what's our shot called crossroads it's a
nice vegan restaurant and normally i
don't love vegan food to be honest with
you but we went a few nights ago for
trevor's birthday dinner and it was
so good oh my god it was literally some
of the best food that i've ever eaten
it's bad oh did you finish your food oh
my god
oh no no that's finn's bowl no no sir
okay so end of day one he's got finn's
precious cow
he's not having it getting along really
well they're much calmer
than they were in the beginning right
finn
he's eating his ass we all would if we
could
[Music]
he's brave he's like running right into
thin so
like is this even real oh my god
this was such an amazing and beautiful
day i am so excited that we actually
ended up getting him
wow the next day last night i did the
unthinkable
i had the pup sleep with me in my bed
because he's
so cute and so cuddly and he's been
really good about his potty training so
i wanted to see if he'd be able to
do it oh my gosh i wanted to see if he'd
be able to do it and spend the whole
night with me in bed and not go to the
bathroom and he did he's such a good boy
he is however a very very um like a
squirmish sleeper so we did wake up a
few different times in the middle of the
night just because he kept like
re-adjusting himself which was
a little annoying but other than that
you did a good job baby you did a good
job
[Applause]
this is not an optional assignment
he's so cute in fin
what oh do you want a bath now
or you just want to join the party i
think we need to make a double bath
you did this you did this
war oh no oh no
oh no oh oh
oh oh okay so obviously i talked about
how finn is like extremely attached to
lewis and i he's very very just
protective and loving but he's also not
an aggressive dog
literally at all like we've never even
heard finn growl like out of anger since
we got him which is
great but with the puppy the puppy's
obviously in his teething face because
he's only a few weeks old and he keeps
like biting me and lewis and i've
noticed whenever he starts like biting
me and i'll like say no
like just like push him away a little
bit finn will like come
walk in the middle of myself and the
puppy so the puppy like can't
get to me to bite me which is like i
think finn protecting me it really seems
like finn
is like honestly helping train the pup
which is like
makes my heart so happy and also like
the best thing that could have ever
happened
next time that that is like happening
i'll try to get it on camera because i
really would love
the input of you guys like anybody else
who has dogs out there to explain what's
going on i could be really overthinking
this but
i think finn is really like handling
this super super well
the next day all right you guys you've
been having a rough day with this little
one
so far he has not been the best angel
but i want to try and take him
swimming and see how that goes finn
hates the water and we're reading online
to see if it was safe for him we found
out that it's okay to start introducing
puppies to water around eight weeks
which is exactly how old he is
and my thought process is that hopefully
if we get him introduced to water
earlier on
he might like it labs and gold
retrievers are both really good natural
swimmers
so let's see hot tub is not on for
anyone wondering
we're not cooking him
oh my god he's good yeah that was really
good it's okay
oh i know you don't want to join we know
you can't tell if he likes it or not
he's like willingly swimming how do we
get our dogs to light the water can
somebody leave us a comment down below
and tell us how to warm our dogs up to
the water
finn's literally horrified and like this
one seems to be okay but i don't think
he's loving it oh he's not thrilled
maybe if you like hold his like
rib cage area and he can just practice
the motion finn's loving us he's getting
treats for doing nothing
hopefully whenever we're in the pool if
we just take the puppy in for a little
bit he'll get used to it and we'll enjoy
it and we'll definitely give you guys a
puff date on the swimming
hi you all watching the vmas you're
watching the video music world all
together as a lovely family
oh please don't bite me ouch ouch kind
of kisses instead
are you giving me kisses you're gonna
bite me because i'll find you back oh
you do not want that breath in your
mouth
the next day hello you guys so this
morning i had a cute little vlog clip of
me waking up with the pepper
he slept perfectly last night did not go
to the bathroom was an angel
and i have not filmed anything yet today
because um i've literally spent the
entire day
with this one trying to fix him because
oh boy the excitement that i had for how
well he was behaved
last night quickly diminished when he
decided to pee inside of the house
four different times today not once not
twice not thrice but
it's only two o'clock as well we are
super frustrated and also just confused
because for the past few days he's been
doing such a good job of using the
bathroom outside waiting for the door to
open but i don't know what it is
now he needs to go for redemption every
main character needs a redemption arc
lauren knows they've had mine so why is
he being so bad today
that is the name of a cartoon character
boy so the other dog has to match that
which is why i think theo is the perfect
name
terrible is such a good name a very
exotic
foreign boy hot chiseled boy what yeah
and theo is the same body harley's a
great name and
he's a girl of dogs harley leonardo
leonardo's really good
i love the ninja turtles and leonardo
dicaprio i'm sure you guys enjoy
everyone listen hi here we go leo harley
scout no yep what were mine
girl don't do it it's not worth it i'm
not gonna do it girl
i was just thinking about it i'm not
gonna do it
i did it perfect
good boy thank you all right you guys
well i think that is everything that we
have for today's new video i'm so glad
that we got to introduce this little
baby right here to all of you guys and
he's now officially part of the family
it has been an insane past couple of
days he definitely has quite a lot of
work to do
finn this little angel right here was
definitely quite a lot easier but i'm
always down for a challenge and
that just means he's gonna be a very
very strong spirited individual
also before this video is over one week
ago was the house tour part two video
and the announcement of the one hundred
thousand dollar giveaway we had such an
amazing time reading all of your guys's
comments and it was really
really really hard to pick all of our
winners but in the end we did select our
five sisters who are going to be taking
home the 20 000 and those names are
going to be listed right here on
the screen all five winners have been
contacted privately and thank you so
much again to every single person who
entered
we'll be doing more giveaways in the
future very very soon so make sure you
follow turn on notifications and get
ready for anything else we may have
planned
off our sleeves and don't forget to give
this video a big thumbs up down below
click the bigger subscribe button and
also click that bell icon so you get
notified every time i upload a brand new
video if you guys follow me on my makeup
journey all my social media accounts are
gonna be linked right here around the
screen
and also if you want to text me on my
personal phone number for new updates on
videos photos merge and so much more it
is 200-905-8746
this video sister shout out goes to
sister jenny thank you so much love for
always following and supporting i love
you so so much and if you like to the
next video sister shout out don't forget
to always retweet my video links when
they go live on twitter and also to my
youtube post notifications
all right you guys thank you so much for
watching today's video i love you so
much and we
will see you in the next one bye
[Music]
you