hello sisters to use penalty and welcome
back to my channel I thought I would do
the intro to this video a little bit
more up along as hell because literally
the entire team is downstairs getting
ready for today's sister holiday party
and I am so beyond excited I just want
to take a brief moment talk to you guys
and also just saying thank you for those
of you guys who may miss to a few needs
to go on my snapchat and Instagram
stories I announced that I was hosting
my first ever sisters holiday party and
that 25 you guys were going to win an
invite and that day is finally here I
have wanted to host an event where I was
able to invite you guys for so so long
now and have just never worked out for a
million different reasons but this
Christmas party was the first time were
actually stuck and the whole team was on
board and excited and were able to make
it work that being said I don't wanna
make this too long say it's going to be
so much fun the 25 sisters are on the
way I can already hear some people
downstairs so the party is about to be
started it's going to be a super fun day
of to celebrating the holidays lift sec
nick my really my friend who owns about
beauty percent of view for artists to do
touch-ups on the girls while they are
here we're gonna be playing at christmas
games and then we're gonna finish off
the night by playing a white elephant
but instead of everybody bringing their
own gifts I bought all the guests and
let me tell you they are so let everyone
is gonna be walking out of here with an
amazing new Christmas gift and hopefully
amazing at memories I love doing these
things to do highest you guys literally
mean the entire road Smith this year has
been obviously very tough for me for a
lot of different reasons and I am just
so grateful that I still get to do
things like this and spend time with you
guys one-on-one because you are the
reason that I am here I love you and
without further ado okay let's get party
[Music]
hi girls here and welcome to the first
ever official sisters holiday party all
25 sisters are downstairs and probably
ready to go let's go inside everybody
[Applause]
beautiful
happy holidays hos okay first of all
thank you guys so much for coming today
it means the opposite world to me I have
wanted to do an event like this for so
long now and we have just not been able
to actually make it work I would not be
here today if it were not for all of you
guys and for obviously everyone in
general so you all mean the absolute
world to me and I'm so grateful for your
constant love and support and I just
want to do something fun to just get to
chill with you guys so today's gonna be
super super let thank you guys
[Music]
all right you guys have work to be doing
a gingerbread house building competition
we're gonna put you guys in season two
we will have one hour to build the best
Gendron house that you possibly can he's
the only Talos Internet and the end of
one hour you'll compare them and the
winners will receive a very special gift
at the end of the night okay so if you
guys want to get up the next 60 minutes
to meet your newest friend introduce
yourselves but also remember this is the
competition so you want your hosts look
as good as possible because the winner
will be getting some very some friends
is okay 60 minutes on the clock
ready set go
yeah jingle bell sound that's also dear
frosty snowman is all around town while
chopping brandy
okay interview around how do we feel
what's your inspiration for the house
tell me all about it
a winter wonderland I love that a winter
wonderland with an open back so the snow
falls down yeah okay our dog we're gonna
be done you're gonna make going climb
down the chimney had the speed of light
while we're dancing around the Christmas
tree hug and kiss in the shoe
what inspired you to make the the sour
patch shingles different colors on their
house immigration status 7 to 9 climb
down the chimney at the speed of light
while we're dancing around the Christmas
[Music]
on the top I think that's a Los Angeles
alright
[Music]
all right you guys so what is about to
be time for white elephant probably the
most lit Christmas cave there ever was
so we're going to bring everybody up on
your way I have this little Christmas
hat and you're going to pick a number so
person number one goes up and they open
up their very first gift and they have
to show the crowd the gift person number
two gets to go up in the either can
decide if they want to steal person
number ones gift or open up a gift from
the tree you have to decide first you
can't like open up into I don't want
this one I'm gonna take this person's
inside each item has a steal limit of
only twice so why don't we all come up
and we can give the gifts thank you guys
so much all for coming today and
seriously means so much getting to sit
down with all of you guys have fun I'm
making the different houses and I got to
know so many of you today as well and
just hearing your stories about your
guys's lies and everything in your
makeup journeys and how you started
following me it it really like it hits
home and you guys are the reason why
you're here today I don't wanna get
emotional it's okay I'm just gonna stop
talking before I start crying but this
way elephant is the fun way to get back
to you guys like I said there are gifts
for everybody here and they're all
really really exciting so I hope that
you guys are excited and happy about
them and yeah this is just a little
thank-you from me to you thank you for
being the absolute best and first as one
of you through everything okay number
one who has a space let's go okay so
pick whatever your heart desires
okay alright number two so this is an
amazing gift for my good friends over at
morphe it is a full box of a ton of
different products so gonna make a
little makeup goodie bag oh yeah just
going for the Big Daddy
[Music]
I know a lot of you guys love makeup and
a lot of advisers Hawkins news today
about wanting to start doing YouTube
videos I wanted to start doing this so
we thought including a camera will be a
really cool item so things are heating
up now okay who is at number eight okay
who is number nine nine okay are you
gonna steal somebody's or your number 17
[Music]
that's the name of the game Oh so we
have to Mickey and Minnie ears and also
two whole day passes to Disney ok
numbered next oh so this is a printer
for your phone and also has little
puller things too
so you can print any of your iPhone
pictures out and like is everywhere okay
what is it locked
all the time
you just clearly know you have very good
taste yeah
no Disney yeah does he locked okay so
now lock the finally not least we have
our beautiful miss number one who was
the victim of thievery and betrayal
8,000 times in the thing so you can
either keep what you have or you can
perform one final steal such a good
smoker
alright everybody well that completes
why Alison I hope that you all love your
gifts thank you all for being honest and
thank you all for being good sports
happy holidays everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
okay guys just a few quick things first
of all once again thank you for
everything with my elephant on top of
your white elephant gift everybody will
be going home with a mini palette and
mini brush thanks guys because what was
the first of our sisters holiday at
party I had a literally the best night
of my entire life
I am so grateful to everybody that can't
everybody just headed out right now and
we were working on it breaking down all
this beautiful decor once again thank
you to it looting designer for a
cleanness it looked so beautiful and
thank you so much to the 25 sisters
shoot about today I you whatever you
like okay I'm not even gonna stop
talking I let me feel like crying I'm so
grateful that I get to do things like
this and interact with my fans and just
give back in such a fun way like this
couldn't have gotten any better and I'm
so grateful that now all of you guys get
to watch us and I get to watch us and
look back at it this is something that I
definitely you know I definitely want to
do it more even outside of LA I think
this would be so much fun and just
getting to hug everybody and say hi and
give kiss and just like spend time
together and just like everything about
this was incredible and I'm really glad
that happened and I'm really glad that
this video happened and now I'm saying
the same thing again I'm sorry she goes
to this videos today please don't forget
to go to big this is disgusting if you
guys enjoyed this video is today please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and show your love and
support it really means so much to me
and if you have not already make sure
you click that big red subscribe button
as well and come join at this sisterhood
I would love to have you in the family
and also make sure you click that big
bell down below so you giving each and
every time
I put a brand new video if they follow
me and I make up journey you can follow
me on Instagram Twitter and TechTalk are
all just a James Charles and my fat
check from our behind the same times
have is Dana's Charles the next row ass
you guys want to make sure you fall
because we never know we're going to do
one of these again we're going to be the
first ones to be educated
this videos sister shot across the
sister Hayden thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting I love you
so so so much and if you at home like to
the next videos a sister shout out don't
forget to always retweet Vanilla's gonna
go live on Twitter and also to my
youtube at post notifications my
eyeliner is now running because of my
tears all right you guys well that is
all I have for today's video thank you
so much for watching I love you so much
happy holidays and I will see you in the
next one bye
[Music]