hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
normally in the beginning of each video
I say that I'm very excited but no cap
for this video I am too nervous not
excited in this latest pin that is
because we were doing something that is
a little bit triggering to me the past
like few weeks on YouTube I've been
watching a lot of nostalgic content for
some reason I don't know what it is but
like the whole recommendation system has
they given me a lot of things from my
childhood I've been watching poptropica
tutorials for some reason Mario Kart
videos tumblr theme coding videos like
everything that I used to do when I was
like 10 years old it's all coming back
to me and what are my really good
friends Larry a few days ago uploaded a
video where he went on omegle no hits
you don't know I've never been on a
before omegle it's basically a website
where you can log on and you can video
chat or text strangers for free and if
you're thinking to yourself well that
sounds kind of dangerous you're
absolutely right and I would definitely
not recommend doing this um if you see
my coming out video you would know why
this is very triggering to me and if you
haven't seen that video don't worry
about it nothing said for today's
YouTube video I thought I would log on
back to amigo for the first time in like
10 years and I would ask strangers to
pick my makeup routine I truly have no
idea who we're about to meet on this
website today from what I remember a few
years ago it was either our musicians
playing their songs or other tumblr kids
that all have the same muffle emo
haircut as I did
or like Autobots or a lot of really
nasty old naked men so for the sake of
both my eyes and yours I am sincerely
praying that we will meet a whole lot of
sisters that are able to help me pick my
makeup routine but without further ado
let's log on and find out
[Music]
all right you guys I just want to get
the self-worth and come jump right and
as you can see I already have my brows
on and I also call it crack - just a
tiny little bit so we're gonna start off
with our first step being a foundation
okay here we go
[Music]
hey hi bro what's up and if someone can
abuse you up what I don't like I'm gala
beef okay
oh she left me so rude nobody wants to
talk hello coming up anywhere have
people on omegle help me pick my makeup
routines you guys want to be in it
okay for foundation today or should I
use the fancy Beauty Foundation or
perhaps the Dior air flash or maybe the
Anasazi Beverly Hills Foundation or a
mix or the mix of all three yes okay
perhaps I'll do that well thank you guys
for helping me pick I'm gonna head off
and put this on and thank you guys for
being in the video I have been up a fun
night they're so sweet oh my god oh
that's gonna keep going alright so you
guys heard the girls for foundations
names we're gonna mix together I guess
all three of these that one coming so
we're gonna take this your AirFloss from
the shade 100 and which is the my go to
recently a little Fenty beauty in the
shade 150 just really squirt it in there
and then a little bit of the Anasazi
Beverly Hills actual let me give this a
little jiggle jiggle as well and the
shade 200 W I don't know how this shade
combination is gonna actually look just
gonna paint us on using a foundation
brush I was gonna go ahead and blend
this and use my dunno in Cola buns oh
I'm actually not loving how the three of
these together are looking this is a
little bit like a wall of it cakey
wow my skin looks really bad what the
heck okay our foundation that's all on
and we are on to step number two my name
is James what's your name my name is
Michael where do you live Marco I've
progressed you went a little bit of
Brazil so bad I have a question for you
okay I'm doing my makeup right now do
you wanna be in my youtube video and
tell me what to put on next oh okay so
I'm gonna do concealer you have four
options okay okay you can either do that
it's called tarp shape tape do a full
coverage makeup forever HD or fancy
beauty it's almost the same they all
look the same but they perform a little
bit differently ready so let's try the
first one
the Thar shape tape this one yeah that's
the best one hey thank you so much Marc
I hope you have an amazing time tonight
all right you guys our good friend Marco
Brazil ended up choosing art art shape
tape I'm not sure if he knew it like he
was a true makeup lover or if he just
had one too and he drinks the man but
we're gonna go ahead and apply this just
like normal on a real note though he was
so fun
Margo just seems like the a person that
just like enjoys life you know Marco is
just a copy to be alive and like that's
the energy that we need in 2020 all
right you guys our concealer is all on
in our face is looking a little bit
better right now but we really need to
set it in place so let's go ahead and
log back on or our setting powder
oh hi sister
do really beautiful nice to meet you I'm
filming a video right now where I have
people on omegle help me pick my makeup
routine you want to help me out so I
need your help picking a a setting
powder okay should we go with and you
can tell me either the laura mercier
translucent setting powder a cult
classic of course we also have the Too
Faced peach perfect palette and then
also the frente Beauty butter powder the
Laura Mercier okay thanks girl I'll go
ahead and apply that right now thank you
oh she already lost all right you guys
so I'm just going to give you a quick
little touch-up before we go ahead and
set our face in place using it the Laura
Mercier translucent setting powder like
sister Sarah recommended that is
literally so cool that we're just on
this random spooky website and she
literally had the palette sitting right
there that are so cool like oh my god
okay our base is all on but with this
foundation combination I am not loving
how my skin is looking it is very flat
little bit pale and very keikis so I am
very much hoping but the next few steps
of powder and contour
which is more powder which I think isn't
gonna help but you know what we're just
gonna move on to our next step we need
to add some dimension so let's see what
we got your biggest fan oh my god thanks
girl wait really is that you I don't
like a YouTube video can we be in it do
you want to be yes are you true sisters
or are you making fun of me at the
beginning no I do you guys much makeup
videos okay that's your first time it
looks really bump good job okay you guys
help me out here with this video okay I
need help choosing a contouring palette
because my face is looking very flat
right now okay so shall I use the Nikita
dragon dragon Beauty face palette okay
the morphe 8l contouring palette or
should I just go to the benefit hoola
bronzer morphe working the more you one
and what should they do for tempers that
off
Oh coach James very well thank you guys
for helping out with your video and I
really appreciate it
joy you're naive yeah oh you guys so
according to Madeline and Sophia we're
gonna grab the morphe 8l palette as well
if the morphe emma 405 brush and we're
gonna dip into the shade of donut and
use this to add some dimension at back
my face I don't even know why I didn't
think about this but literally in the
beginning of this video I mentioned how
so many people on this website either
have fake cameras to either like
advertise nasty websites or like literal
catfish video so I didn't think of the
fact that people would probably think
that I was fake while being on here that
is so funny that not only literally
thought I was recording but obviously I
am real I'm not being said it assigned
to move on to our next step
I'm just hiding to move on to our I
thought a portion of this look this
should be interesting
oh my god do you guys wanna help you my
routine then yeah it's time for me to
put on an eye shadow law get fully glam
so I need your guys's help to pick what
look I should actually do to that okay
maybe do one I have my palette right
here do you guys want to like pick
colors from it or you can like tell me
something something that you think I
should do a look inspired by oh my god
how do you make up new content all the
time okay great cuz I don't know do
something inspired by like a hero like
someone you look up to okay - my idols
are definite like my mom and my dad and
they have two of the taste in the power
happy and then skip maybe like a pink in
like yellow yeah do you think that's
cute yeah well thank you guys helped me
picked out that so sweet yeah you guys -
thank you for the love all right you
guys someone's Hannah and Sarah had a
really cute idea of having me do a
makeup look inspired by somebody that I
look up to now to people that I love the
absolute most and they have afraid me to
be Who I am today
or my mama and my father sister Christy
and skip because I met them many times
in YouTube videos and on drunk stars I
thought it'd be really cute to me we'd
do a look inspired by them with a be my
mom shade and skip might oops
and skip my dad shade which now has a
large gouge in it this will be a cute
little lemonade look so let's see what
we can come up with a few months ago on
my end
right after I finished watching at
euphoria and amazing show by the way
can't wait for season two I did a look
inspired by luck said to me and
like this beautiful pink and yellow
sunset look and I think that I probably
should recreate something similar so I'm
going to grab the first a pencil brush
and just dipping into a little bit of B
and I'm gonna pop this right in my inner
corner and now for the outer corner I'm
gonna grab a Tama four five six brush
and dip into it a little bit of love
that which is the darker pink shade and
I'm gonna start shaping up my outer V
and then with the M 4-3-3 I'm just gonna
dip into skip and use this to buff out
the edges okay it's gonna start talking
that underneath the eye as well maybe
should I grab a little bit of literally
on the lid I could look actually really
pretty oh yeah
all right you guys this is one I
inspired by at my parents who are true
my idols all complete I love this idea
so so so much thank you again that to
Montana and Sarah I'm gonna go to the
old one off camera quickly add on some
mascara and then we'll be back on line
to have somebody pick our up lashes all
right you guys we are back bullfights
are all complete I'd let me just say I
am literally obsessed with this I look I
cannot stop staring at the monitor it
literally looks so cute I am so excited
to finish off this look let's log back
on and pick some lashes hi how are you
guys hi hi oh service Charles did you
really
I forget the store I got it okay bye
thank you liar I'm currently filming a
video where I have people at home a go
help me pick my makeup do you guys wanna
help out I need your help picking an
eyelash to add on to this lock okay
your options are going to be we have
Lily lodged in the sail Miami this is
like a fun light fluffy lashed okay we
have Lily lashes in the style so extra
Miami and we also have Miami Flair it
gets longer on the outside so it's a
very nice life snatched
luck all right babe
yes okay why do you why do you think
that one
whenever you sends this thing yeah
probably is that okay hallo bah thank
you guys I appreciate are you kidding
Wow why is such a real one for picking
this eyelash this is really what I was
hoping for
let's give some pie later on I'm telling
it YouTube video do you guys want to
help me pick up my highlighter for my
video so you guys I have this fun little
sunset look on right now so I need a
really beautiful highlighter just tie it
all together
okay so I'm gonna let you guys pick
whatever one you want of course we could
use our highlighter shade from the
palette which is called face so Jocelyn
Hale cosmetics highlighters - some fun
ones from colour-pop we have trouble
understanding my skin any quick Pat
other my feet are both asleep oh my god
okay I'm not really sure what to do oh
oh oh my god I forgot how fun this was
that could literally cause a spaceship
to crash alright you guys with our
highlighter being all on and ready to go
we are on to our last and final step
which is of course going to be the lips
but since we've been doing strangers for
the entirety of this video I do at least
want to give an opportunity to some of
the really hardcore sisters to get a
line and say hello so I actually just
put out a tweet so for our last step
we're gonna log on and try to find some
hardcore sisters to pick out our lip
combination how are you hi I love you so
much you're beautiful oh thank you love
your beautiful as well
okay so I'm filming a YouTube video
right now and you want to help me
definitely
I'm doing full-face to make up here on
omegle my only step left is going to be
a website so I want you to pick any
brand any shade any color you want to
finish off the suck you can be as
creative or as simple as you want you
have like a lipstick is like the same
color as like the purple in your eye or
purple I hope this one shade of purple
do you like this one yes I love it hope
you have an amazing night alright you
guys so to finish this look up once and
for all we're gonna be using the shade
called las vegas from Ulfric cosmetics i
have loved to look with the sick formula
as you guys know and this is a bright
purple shade I'm actually really excited
because I definitely wanted to do
something a little bit more fun and then
a classic nude and this will be perfect
with this look
alright you guys as always finishing off
this look with a little bit of cup and
setting spray from morphe and that is
this look selected completely by
strangers on omegle a hug completes
obviously I had no idea how this luck
was going to turn out today it could
have ended a very very poorly but I feel
like the people of omegle came together
and honestly created a masterpiece
because this look is so cute I do want
to say Ranger thank you to every single
person who said hello or who
participated in today's video I
obviously couldn't include all the
footage because we've been literally
sitting here talking to strangers for
the last like 5 hours but reckon all
this it means the opposite worlds meet
and if you guys at home watching enjoy
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and show
your love and support it really helps me
out and also leave me a comment down
below and let me know if you guys
enjoyed this video if you want me to do
more of this in the future if you like
to follow me on my makeup turn again
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
tik-tok and Facebook all to shame
Charles and I snapchat for more about
him the teen signs up is James Charles
the next ask after Charles Fitts videos
sister Sara Costa sister Victoria thank
you so much love for always following in
supporting I love you so so so much and
if you like to be the next videos the
sisters now that don't forget always
retweet buidling so they go live on
Twitter and also to them on YouTube
posts implications
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching this video today I love you and
I will see you in the next one bye oh my
god it's real in charge
what's up Bros is it actually how are
you guys are you happy yeah your gems
Charles can you play the saxophone for
me go again why not you don't even play
the saxophone now I don't
hi sisters oh my god for those you guys
who don't know this is Debbie also known
as Oh Tom Mary on Instagram I literally
love you the absolute most oh that was a
dark disgusting
[Music]