hi guys this is James Charles welcome
back to our YouTube channel today I'm
joined with a very special guest
hello I'm Ricky Dillon what's up nothing
we just finish oh yeah this is a mess
well so say I'm excited to sit down and
film a collab video we did a little chit
chat get ready with us we are about an
hour and a half late to an event right
now so we kind of like Zippity duped up
sped right through this yeah I'm like
taught Ricky what's one of the make up
road because he said try not make up
recently I don't know what to do and he
taught me today yes so gonna see how we
created these looks and to just enjoy
our conversation they're definitely
interesting to say the least make sure
you keep on watching so we're in first
off by priming our faces and I'm going
to use the benefit Porefessional primer
yeah yeah alright let you look my neck
okay you love that phrase don't you I
really do honey when you say it give me
good brows but I'm learning that and I'm
so hit or miss I like doing really well
a long time and then they'll be horrible
then I could like what am i video
visually they were so bad for people all
the comments were like what happened
there's eyebrows in like the next video
they looked good
okay so check in the court is showing
what's the question I don't know what
should I do this too if you want to yeah
will the person is stored they matched
it with me so if it's not right then
it's their fault that look right that
color does actually count it up and down
okay
okay how does that blend it out though
you just happen in oh yeah oh wow woah
shook an iconic invention I'm shooked
the gold is ticket and every nook and
cranny possible without raising your
forehead but also get creases and then
we'll be crusty your crusty
thank you we're great one-two concealer
okay
conceal don't I make that joke every
time I do a video bad joke that's what
my brain goes to sing frozen to
them about the site that's unfamiliar Oh
fun fact about my eyes they water really
easily
Oh suddenly this corporation just
actually got yeah I mean I'm like fine
but like if you see while rescuing out
this is like quite a task
well that's when you're texting you're
like oh how I'm just gonna take like an
hour oh it's this jacket man there's
nothing useful like video to take like
two minutes that's very very basic I
just it's just like you want like you
want to leave even out your skin tone
and everything about you right so like
when you do your makeup in supper you do
highlighting and contouring you want to
add as much contrast to your face as
possible all right it's like when you
put on your foundation obviously it's
like one color if it's like full cover
so you don't really be like Flat Stanley
so like have my videos
okay self-drive go I mean yeah this is
close all the cheekbones right but sure
it actually you think it was nice of
doing it I truly do like I like a good
sneeze me she loves yeah I do huh it's
like the best bodily function by far
right so wait what are you putting this
so like this I'm gonna die gret below oh
wow never never never never never
anyways goes like on the cheek bones
anyone upwards I thought that how it
goes the cheekbones yeah so I thought
bronzer where do you think frogs are
those I think it okay like what hold on
like in know what no no the whole point
okay so you're gonna bronzer like here
and blend upwards and then you want this
part to be the wall yeah that's enough
that makes your cheekbones okay I sunk
it in that's what you want you wanna
like have snaps cheekbones
do it for me okay likewise okay okay I'm
gonna hats right I do I do it right
there I don't blend I just kinda like
yeah like look you want this thing right
here
and this often go I'm talking but this
this is one situation where it will go
actually below yes yeah I do guys know
how to get below like a shadow then I'll
make your drawing stronger okay and then
same thing on the forehead forehead
before yeah actually you only need to
give a small forehead anyway it must be
nice cannot really unfortunately but
like yeah actually see the bed oh it's
pretty bad so bad okay let me try it out
so yeah
whoa what okay tap that off I rubbed it
like twice yeah see all this
whoa okay who's that enough yeah now try
it lightly light top there you go that's
it no do it again
there you go okay some art I love a nail
thing literally make us wear makeup like
it's over like I I person talking to
answer mark hinkel's to you I do really
I come on really I know it really does
help a lot of people but like for me I
just cannot help but start like cracking
up beauty stuff it's like littering all
like tapping all rubbing like so they
might good to do it as a mouth like a
daily basis just about everyday makeup
routine so I think maybe that sound like
I'm you twit at this point but again I
don't like go watching it but I stumble
upon it I get that like it's like the
pimple popping videos I'm backing into
that really I'm Asha oh love me a good
blockhead oh god now that we've
conquered and bronze we're going to go
ahead and bake our faces but is the job
technique so yes I know because I watch
that grace I don't know how to do
anything okay so we're gonna get a whole
oh I love beta you do what kind of
possible Chris a lot left and right you
know they came Oh
no matter what be careful cause it's
like okay so okay we're gonna let this
set for we're done
oh yeah okay guys ready to go okay
notice they were gonna let this set why
don't I just go just got too serious too
fast we're gonna let this set for a like
a few minutes and I'm going to come back
and we're going to start off on eyebrows
and then finish off so we are be we're
gonna star on it great I like the we're
gonna get started on the brows we're and
oh gosh right now we are currently 37
minutes late furnace up recovering Hey
okay so I'm gonna do one of Ricky's bros
before him and we're gonna see how
stature you can make it and then it's
gonna match it while I do mine let's do
this one okay concealer
okay ever worried about making it
perfect right away we can always fix it
we're not to do I'm gonna try to match
it I might end up having two different
looking eyebrows oh okay yeah I'm
learning I'm gonna start with my Anasazi
dip brow and my morphe e 29 and I'm
going to begin sketching out my brows
what's your favorite part makeup to do
my favorite part is probably um I shadow
it's like it's really fun and it's like
something new true but I do my face it's
always the exact same video so it kind
of gets boring
um how does this look you drew this
round really really low whereas so that
makes your brow looks tiny which makes
them like you're constantly throwing
see how this rod is like more arched it
like looks more like it snatched in like
so how do i what do I do
conceal under okay like hold them here
this is this is beauty so you have to
hold your head up hold them your down so
you can look in the mirror okay
and now that you can see what's going on
in this region your forehead is
increasing so it must does in the mirror
look at yourself but keep your head up
but look down a division
this is hard but I just like chop that
off it's so ugly if that's no I like it
it's cute in the button but like I'll
take it down later yeah but what does it
do which it kind of flops over it's so
gross
well I haven't been washing yet I'm
gonna now use my e45 to blend in my eye
concealer of this stuff and rekha gonna
do the same thing I was about to say
that he said before it couldn't yes
taking a deeper voice weirdest things
you do you doing you're pretty good whoa
you're gonna hit it you need your
awareness things are like so um being
that we are now an hour late for our bed
I'm just going to do some mascara no
eyeshadow today and unfortunately but we
totally do want to do eyeshadow and
Ricky does need to learn because this is
makeup education school with Charles so
if you want to see us do eyeshadow in
the future definitely checking us today
we're gonna do on his channel but also
give this video a big thumbs up down
below because we can totally do another
video in the future
well I'll have to check first my
calendar but pencil in summer I'll see
what I can do yeah my video we're
definitely going crazy like with
eyeshadows go check it out totally check
it out I'm hopefully gonna pop on some
fake lashes these are Lily laughs in the
style and Miami's Montebourg oh yeah she
likes inhales a bird yeah it's funny I
love this idea really I was really it's
a horror horrible do you like horrible
movie I heard there was more hold on no
other horror movie you're not wrong I
need to hate the man out on the house I
loved it I would picture you as being a
not horror they two years ago never now
I love it I like like paranormal stuff
yeah me too yeah let's do it
okay now we're gonna highlight for
almost some people take this brush cool
okay we're gonna dip into Anastasio some
Holly
she's a little shattered and cracked but
she still works so what I'm deaf into
here yep
now this is something you're actually
gonna want a really proud because we
want them having to be blinding people
oh right okay let's see if you turned oh
I had the Kat Von D everlasting set yeah
what comes I do I was going to say I'm
going to do a nude far down do I go how
far your heart desires if I live so
really too big I'm learning my corner of
the video without learning your isn't
that you gave messy I'm always writing
like crazy color so it's always nice to
like just take a break and lack your
like take your clothes off me nude
great yeah I guess I don't really have
any lip gloss on me I don't know where
it went but in that case we are done but
I all right guys and that is the
completed look I really really hope you
enjoyed this video if you do that don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and describe you have not already
I post videos every single week did you
have fun
I had a blast literally like I keep
saying I'm learning but I you guys learn
stuff today that's always fun for me to
be able to like teach people to make
them every single day so follow me on my
makeup journey don't forget to follow my
Instagram and Twitter they are both just
James Charles and then you can add my
snapchat for more personal behind the
scenes type stuff which is James trust
in the next u.s. after Charles well we
really did that gonna check me out on my
channel is Ricky doing it's a good time
yeah yes but I have a link that sees
your folks last week you know and my
Twitter would be P Dillon am I just
gonna forget ill and check out amazing
amazing you were watching him for so
long so this is
like fun for me also we did a video over
on Ricky's channel we did this crazy
conceptual look perfect for holiday
wintery cold season so make sure you go
check it out it'll be a good time yes
all right guys thank you so much for
watching and we'll see you next time