hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so if
he wants to go I did a video on my
channel called testing a fake makeup
where I went down to Santee alley and if
you are an alley native you know that
that is like the holy grail of all fake
products and all I can knock off or
really really cheap goods and I did a
video testing out fake makeup products
where I did like knockoffs of all like
high-end name-brand stuff you guys
absolutely love that video and there's
one of the most dude on my entire
channel so thank you for that and I got
so many comments ask me to do it again
and what are the main comments that I
got in the video as well as that I
should have gotten the real versions of
all the fake products and tested them
out half and half which I was like oh
yeah that would've been a really smart
idea so today I'm coming at you with a
part two of testing fake makeup I have a
ton of new products that I do not try
out in the last video the real versions
and the fake versions as well so we're
gonna do half and half and compare how
the real products compared to the fake
ones so yeah without further ado let's
go ahead and get started so I actually
don't have any base products that test
out for you guys the only foundation
that I've ever seen a fake version of is
the Mac one that I used in last video
but what I do have is a knockoff Beauty
Blender that I found so I'm gonna go
ahead and use a knockoff Beauty Blender
and a real Beauty Blender on different
sides of my face using my regular
foundation and we're gonna see how they
actually apply if they apply the same if
they're different so yeah what I find
weirdest about this knockoff Beauty
Blender is the fact that it comes in a
plastic package that literally says the
original Beauty Blender and I've had at
many Beauty blenders in the past and
this is literally the same exact plastic
packaging that the regular Beauty
Blender has come in which is very very
suspicious but if you take the actual
sponge out it is definitely a different
shade of pink a different shape as well
this one is slightly more fat and the
texture is completely different Oh God
alright so these are both completely
soaked and then wrung out this is
obviously the fake one it has not
changed in size in the slightest and
this is the real Beauty Blender which is
now like probably doubled in size so I'm
gonna grab my Too Faced Born This Way
Foundation which is only a longtime
favorites right now and just pump a
little bit on the back of my hand and
then we're going to apply it so this is
literally incredibly hard and not like
remotely comfortable in the slightest
you know makeup gurus are always coming
and I'm beating my face like I am
literally having to beat my face at this
product I'm gonna go ahead and now grab
my real Beauty Blender into the Born
This Way Foundation and do the rest of
my face oh so much better so the non
Beauty Blender i bought at Sanchi alley
for a total of nine dollars and the real
Beauty Blender retails at like most
makeup stores for I think $20 obviously
you are saving money by getting the fake
version but clearly it is not really
working out that well for me you have to
blend it out really really really hard
and just soak up a lot of projects as
well so ultimately at the end of the day
you're just losing money because you are
using more your foundation and I'm
assuming your concealer when we get to
that stuff in a second which I am
literally horrified for but literally to
spend the extra $11 if you have it of
course and get the real version because
it pays off so much better so like I
said with the foundation I didn't find
any base dupes so I'm gonna go ahead and
use the Tarte shaped tip concealer in
the shade light/medium on both sides
then we're just gonna use the different
Beauty blenders to blend them out
I'm literally hitting myself so hard to
actually like blend out and distribute
this product which is not what I want to
be doing right now using the original
issue so much more effortless and not as
violent alright so now that the base is
all on our next step is going to be to
powder and once again you guys know that
I love my Beauty Blender for this so I
just have my regular Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder and I'm gonna
first got my knocked off Beauty Blender
and dip into the powder and I am so
horrified for this one being first gonna
do my nose on the fake half Oh God
normally when I do with my regular
Beauty Blender it really helps to melt
the powder into the skin which creates a
really flawless finish I am definitely
not achieving that with this sponge at
all which is why I'm getting like a lot
of excess and residue powder on my nose
under my eyes as you can see posh like
Mary is trying to come back today and we
are not about to have that happen so I
face is aweso and I am currently baking
at 350 degrees to my face locked in
place and all snapped and ready to go
and of course the next step along always
baking is my eyebrows and I do have a
knockout product for those and that is
the Anastasia brow definer now I did
have a bra definer in the same exact
shade and I got dark brown and the fake
one but I just put on a trip and
happened to leave mine there so I had to
improvise and instead of using the brow
definer today I'm gonna use the
Broadway's they are both in the shade of
dark brown I figured the actual shaper
the product doesn't really matter that
much I'm just gonna compare it to color
the price and the firm tool and how they
actually look on the brows you guys get
the point my dumb master shouldn't have
lost their product in the first place
let's go ahead and swatch it on my hand
to actually see how the colors compare
so this is the dark brown brown define
our oh wow okay so the forma is super
super soft as you can see it just broke
off almost instantly swatching this on
my hand I'm gonna try that again so as
you guys can see I just went ahead and
applied the real of dark brown for about
from honest Asya and the fake dark brown
is actually darker Brown and the real
dark brown from actually I besides you
know this is a mess that you guys should
understand what I'm saying at this point
and the real dark brown is actually a
lot more gray toned and the fake dark
brown as well this is a definitely has a
more red undertone so this is definitely
look like more realistic brown hairs on
the real side but let's go ahead and
apply the fake version to the left side
and the real version to the right side
like we did with the Beauty blenders and
let's see which one actually applies it
better when I'm instantly noticing right
away - is that the point on the fake oh
my god ow the point of the actual like
tip of the product is not nearly as
sharp or defined despite the fact that
it is the Anasazi a brow definer as the
original version I'm applying these
lines and they're coming out very very
thick and usually I'm able to get a very
very sharp edge which makes my brow look
super super chiseled out but as you can
see looking at the tail right here it is
not chiseled out in the slightest it
looks very very messy oh you're kidding
No okay this eyebrows will be like
throwback to original Jade Charles
Beauty Instagram block eyebrows this
looks the worst normally I would go
ahead and do my other brow and then
conceal after but either way cannot
stand to look at this any longer I'm
gonna grab some charts shaved and just
fixed up with my morphe for anything you
brush as always because this is looking
I don't think I've ever had to work at
fixing an eyebrow that badly ever like
in my entire life as a makeup artist
that took like at least 30 minutes to do
this one eyebrow and that should never
ever be the case like I get something to
finish my entire makeup routine in 30
minutes if I'm really going fast so that
was awful I definitely would not
recommend this wanna be asked brow
definer from
Anasazi of Beverly Hills I think this is
a total of 14 dollars at Santee alley
and I think the regular one retails for
21 dollars so definitely would not
recommend her at all come with the
original because you don't want to end
up with a block eyebrow from the
original J Charles Beauty on Instagram
those are dark days and we are so glad
to be away from them let's not go back I
think today for the first time ever my
right eyebrow is my better brow today
I don't know this fake bride a finer
just really did not do it for me but the
original brow was came to slay and came
to safe today let's go ahead and move on
from the brows thank god we've been on
the step for way too long and move on to
the eye shadow so for the eyes today
we're gonna be using one palette that I
absolutely stand by interviews many
times on this channel and that is the
morphe brushes collaboration with Jaclyn
hill the real version is in this hand
and is $38 at morphe brushes dot-com or
if you news code change for 10% off and
then there's the fake version which I
got at San cially for a total of $12 so
I definitely price different but let's
put it actually see if the quality is
different because let's be real they're
probably gonna be a lot of the colors do
look very very similar but there are
some huge noticeable differences such as
this shade right here I mean this is a
shimmery Bravo highlighting how it and
this is like literally a bright awesome
neon chartreuse color which is
definitely not even close to what it is
supposed to be this gold shade and the
fake version is nowhere near to the gold
in the original wide this dark brown
shape in the original color which is a
brownie red undertone is loading another
black in the fake palate so oh yeah so
this one obviously is the real version
is much more pigmented and the color is
much deeper and more defined as well
whereas the fake version definitely is
not nearly as shimmery as the real one
it did honestly swatch much farther than
I was expected it's not like awful by
any means but clearly the original
palette is a lot better this is the brow
bone highlighting shade which is
absolutely stunning I love this color
and this is the brow bone highlighting
shade from the fake palette which is
that I just pale rusty dusty looking
chalk so first go strong with my morphe
m5 13 brush and dipped into this warm
torn orange shade right here in the fake
palate and as I start off by décima in
the crease oh that is not pigmented and
then using a clean version of the same
brush I'm going to go to the same exact
shade corresponding in the original
chocolate palette and do the same thing
already as you can see the original
palette has a lot more pigment and
payoff and is blending up very very
nicely next intagram IM poor 3/3 brushes
my all-time favorite fluffy brush for
creases and smokey eyes and there's a
gif light brown shade from the pink I'm
gonna pop this on the lid the shadow is
definitely not letting out as well as
the first edited I honestly thought that
I might be struck to the core and have a
better version in the end which I was a
little bit spooked about but this shadow
is nowhere near blending up very well as
you can see it's looking a super super
she and this like outer crease region
I'm gonna go ahead and grab some more
pigment onto the brush and really pack
it on there to try to create a more
uniform color but this is now looking as
free as I was expecting it to look well
I wasn't expecting it to look good but
then I was a little bit shocked and now
I'm unsure you get the point I'm gonna
grab my other M 4-3-3 brush and dip into
the same exact shade corresponding from
the real version of the chocolate
palette and put that on the other lid
next underground Miami
5:07 brush and dip into this dark brown
shade in the bottom half of the palette
and use this too deep enough to smokey
eye for being fake shadows honestly
these have a ton of pigmentation and are
going on a super nicely but they're just
not blending out like in the slightest
this literally looks the worst ever like
that is not how a smokey eye should be
blunt action okay so my camera decided I
didn't catch it in time but I just use
my morphe m14 line pencil brush and
dipped it into this blue shade in both
the fake version and the real version
and apply them and they are definitely
looking very very different the real
version is a lot more blue and a lot
more pigmented whereas the fake person
is a lot more green tone and is nowhere
near as pigmented as the real version
there is no sparkle to this whatsoever
so definitely the real version is a lot
better maxilla gonna have an e at 19
brush and dip into the brow bone
highlight
with just this right that's yellow and
the top corner Oh God oh no not did
absolutely nothing okay let's try that
again using the same exact brush the
clean version and dip into the real
problem shaking ah there we go
at least that definite looks a whole lot
better than that musty crusty dusty
yellow that literally looks like nothing
so that's good at least alright so those
are both smoky is all complete from the
fake palette I was honestly really
surprised to see that the shadows were
pretty pigmented but as you could see
they really do not blend out at all
there is so much passion is going on
especially out in this outer corner from
the dark brown shade that just did not
want to blend at all and this blue shade
on the lower lash line is nowhere near
as pigmented as the real version wears
on this side of the smokey eye is
definitely a lot more blown oh and
blended it is a more nutritional smokey
eye whereas on this side somehow it
became bright ass orange which I do not
want their arse a nice blue pop of color
on the lower lash line which actually
shows up and the highlights are also
there as well and not looking talky and
invisible whereas on this side they're
gone the real version is obviously a lot
more expensive but you're paying for
quality pigmentation and blend ability
which this palette obviously does not
have so if you're gonna buy heading out
of the - same theme as everything else
so far oh this video by the real version
spend a little bit more money and get a
great house product moving on for the
Highlanders today we're gonna be using
the iconic Kylie cosmetics watts at and
this is the real version and this is the
fake version when you open them up the
pan sizes are obviously a whole lot
bigger and the real version than the
fake version and for the most part the
colors actually look pretty similar
except for the thought that
do-not-disturb was obviously a whole lot
more bright pink and the fake version
then in the real version to do a swatch
comparison I'm gonna grab a privacy
pleat on my pointer finger and then I'm
gonna grab it on my middle finger on the
other hand
whoa okay so privacy please from the
original Kelly Paula is ridiculously
penguin said I've actually never tried
these calendars out before this promise
actually my baby Amanda and things still
thank you to her for letting me borrow
it and then the privacy please from the
big Charlie Paula is a lot less
pigmented as you can see and definitely
nowhere near as a metallic or reflected
as the original it is just kind of like
white satin finished kind of like more
like an eyeshadow rather than an actual
highlighter this is really really
stunning oh that was really
underwhelming place oh there's literally
just like no pigmentation in this
whatever this is after three different
dips into the highlighter and as you can
see this claw is a little sad as you can
see for literally just one dip into the
original palette it is a whole lot more
pigmented a lot more blending the highly
is a lot more sparkly as well but I
honestly really really like how this
looks
whereas on the fake side we get nothing
obviously I can't believe put my nose in
half so I'm just gonna use the real
version on my nose so it doesn't look
the worst Papa oh well that is a
blinding highly oh my gosh whoa okay so
now that the blow is all complete I
guess kinda sorta our last steps it is
gonna be the lipid II doodahs and I
think I have the funniest comparison yet
and those are the k'kaw creme lipsticks
from Kylie cosmetics and yeah this is
what we got oh my god oh wait the the
colors the most nude light shade in the
real version is literally like bright
ass orange this looks like Anastacio
Ashton liquid lipstick in the fake
version was good and apply these and see
what they actually look like next to
each other oh it smells like paint it
literally smells like acrylic paint this
is probably so unsafe but I'm gonna go
out and apply this shade camee to the
fake side of my lips
okay so the actual chemi smells like
nothing which is great I'm gonna go
ahead and apply the real version on to
the real half of my face you get the
point right now so I know that's like
k'kaw cream liquid lipsticks are
supposed to not dry down obviously the
real version is still like a white
looking whereas the fake version have
dried down completely matte but even
just formula aside though if you're
gonna disrespect a brand and all the
hours and money that they put into a
product by copying them like can we at
least try to get the color like
relatively similar I mean like what is
that okay so normally my last step and
obviously beaches at my face in place
but this just looks the worst ever so I
definitely do not want to keep this
makeup on for any longer and that is my
full face of like us half face of fake
makeup part two I'll complete I really
really hope you guys know this video and
definitely become a down below and tell
me what side of the face you think looks
better after testing out all these
products I'm definitely gonna have to
say that the real side of makeup
definitely is my winner here a lot of
these fake makeup products cannot even
close to compare to the real versions
listen I know the low price tags can
sometimes be really really appealing to
you grant or on a budget
trust me I get it makeup can sometimes
be so so expensive but by putting all
these fake products on today I am taking
a huge risk a lot of times these fake
products are nowhere near the same
chemical composition as the real
versions they can sometimes contain a
really really harmful and bad chemicals
to your essence put on your face then
you're not just inhale and like your
lips or your eyes so if you can
definitely some of the action money's to
get the real versions I mean it's gonna
pay off in a frontal on peg rotational
makeup in general so I definitely not
recommend any of these products at all
alright sisters if you guys enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give a big thumbs up down below I
definitely would like to turn this
testing fake makeup videos into like a
full-on
series where I go to Santee alley and
just get fake products all the time I
mean these guys are really freaking
quick anytime that there's a new release
they always have them like
instantaneously so I would love to keep
up with that and show you guys the
comparisons between the real and the
fake because I think it is very very
interesting to learn as a consumer and
as well by giving a thumbs up and lets
me know that you liked it so definitely
share the love down below if you have
not already make sure to click that big
red subscribe button and click that
little bell icon to turn on
notifications we are so close to 2
million subscribers on here which is so
crazy oh my god
join the sisterhood I promise it is a
wonderful time if you'd like to follow
me and I make up dirty can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind-the-scenes fun type of stuff is
James Ross that extra ass actor Charles
this week Tata goes to sister jazz thank
you so much girl for always falling in
supporting you know I love you so much
and if you would like to be at next
week's sister shout out make sure to
always follow me on Twitter and snapchat
and retweet my video links and they go
live don't forget to check out sisters -
apparel calm as well for all the sisters
March my official calling land there's
this kind of really cute stuff on there
which you should definitely check out
and yeah I think that is all I have for
today's video thank you guys so much for
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next one
[Music]