hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys all know last Friday was the
season 1 finale of my reality
competition show instant influencer our
first ever instant influencer is before
I say anything about this video at all I
first just want to say a major major
thank you this project since day one has
been such a dream of mine come true and
to actually put it out into the world
has been some of the most fun weeks of
my entire life and the fact that you
guys loved it and supported it as much
as you did literally means the entire
world I like at a loss for words
although season one has unfortunately
come to an end I feel like this is truly
the beginning of an amazing journey for
the past few weeks every Tuesday after
into influencer episodes we've been
uploading a YouTube video that somehow
correlates to the last week's challenge
and today's video is actually no
different when we found out the enca
influencer was gonna become a reality at
several several months ago lewiston i
actually decided to film every single
step of the way so for today's video I
want to give you guys a
behind-the-scenes look of what it
actually took to put together a real
reality TV show I do want to warn you
okay there's obviously going to be a
whole lot of spoilers in today's video
so if you have not yet got a chance to
check out the finale or literally any of
the series I'm gonna link the full
playlist and to influence are right up
here go on a binging spree now that
they're all lie but without further ado
if you guys want to learn about the show
see some behind the scenes footage and
see what I actually took to make this
dream a reality
keep on watching
[Music]
production is very populations we have
fun project for both me and Louis as
well potentially exciting to learn from
professionals we've done this a while
aside I think LOV your role
[Music]
which is scary
okay James what are we doing artisan
videos to be on influencer the first
time saying hi indigo how are you good
and you I am doing an absolutely amazing
I'm calling to let you know that
congratulations sister you've made that
period my sister on to the show is one
of our contestants
oh my god I can't believe I'm talking oh
hi sister how are you I'm good sister
Jane I have some very very special news
for you you've officially made it onto
the show thank you so much oh my god oh
he was so excited that his skin also
looked so good - really - how are you is
real my heart is racing so fast right
now I cannot believe this
have some pretty special boots for you
you've officially made it onto the show
oh this is gonna change my life forever
James you understand like I I made a
Facebook post I mean when he became the
first cover boy I said I want to be a
cover boy one day I always I told my the
itis
ever since I was little I always I
looked up to I just oh I always want to
be different and I can't believe I'm
talking to you right now this is unreal
thank you so much James thank you so
much thank you I'll talk to you soon
he's literally so sweet you can just
tell it like he wants this so pretty
exciting news for you that you are
officially one of the six people on the
show oh my god it just means like a lot
oh my god she's the cutest I'm obsessed
with her oh shoot she's like seriously
oh my god I love her hi love how are you
good how are you good I do have some
pretty good news for you oh my god
because you are officially one of the
six contestants for the show thank you
so much okay bye hi all right you guys
we've officially called all six of our
contestants before the show they're all
such incredible artists with Amazing
Race
I cannot wait to learn more about that
but more importantly I cannot wait to
see what makeup looks they bring to the
first day of shooting it that defines
good morning and it's currently 626 in
the morning and I have full glam side
without some for it is day one of
shooting and we're on the way to center
right now and so dark you can't even see
it's still dark outside left we were
pulling up to the YouTube faces right
now it is literally a barren wasteland
nobody see art as they should have been
you should be sleeping right now so we
are awake and if they didn't say
[Music]
we're getting very close I'm getting
really nervous TT v qh
people don't say hello you guys and
welcome to instant influencer lights
what they called you guys to tell you
that you made the show we actually gave
in your first on compactor challenge
okay so we just got our first official
cut it's going very very well it's very
weird for me to like be so produce
because we're so used to doing our
YouTube videos and having full control
over everything that we saying
everything the review and all the angles
and all the way to get what's happened
it's like we kind of know what we're
gonna say just play something puffing
stuff but how do you like a four scrub
just like really really odd all the
contestants looks was absolutely insane
I am it's so pleasantly surprised at all
Abed and I need to pee really badly and
think about who I think should win this
we're almost at the end of day one I'm
in my brand new customer
I don't know the nation that the
conditions have done there anything
together
merciless walking seems to do some
touching this is where it gets
interesting but before that I want to
introduce you but before that I want to
introduce my introduce but before that I
want to quickly introduce our guest
judges for you guys so we're about to
about day one we're on the final shot up
the dates and that man's revealing the
winner and loser obstinate episode I'm
really really nervous I'm excited to
tell the winner that she literally I
went against Paris and Avila for this
decision but I feel if I got that Kalyn
it deserves this and Oh next I want you
to go buy her product and that's what
the channel is all about so hopefully
our Vina doesn't hate me and hopefully
don't think somehow I really nervous for
the elimination I'm not looking forward
to that do what I got to do this is the
bowl that I signed up for so let's do it
unfortunately say after the judges
deliberation at your video was not our
favor of the day and you have been
eliminated
how do you feel I don't know expect the
people to be emotional so I don't know
maybe maybe I'm not surprised but I that
was so hard and just like saga always
how much she wanted how much was
clutched that being said it's like a
quarter of the positives everybody was
here for a reason and the other girl who
did wine itself just like has to be done
it sucks but I just hope that she's able
to understand where we're coming from
it states here but it's currently six of
five of the warning you're going to work
with all the contestants here at the
hotel and whisper it because everyone
else is still sleeping
but we're going to first understand that
they're doing by could get ready
challenge this is going to be or crazy
hopefully nobody punches me I hope if
I'm doing somebody are throwing about if
I don't cover this hour so
[Music]
what is your guys's fastest I leave how
to get ready for something Betty why
don't you have to get up for school or
make up to school I think I did like
three times total and it wasn't because
I was too scared or I'm confident if
they want to wake up early enough to
actually get glam yeah
okay number two through thirty minute
makeup challenge and stone very very
early but I am awake in more lines and
such a know the sisters wrong okay that
means while Ashley starting everybody
else will be chillin on the couch
thinking hopefully I thought the look
that you're gonna do what 15 minutes
less time that Ashley has Ashley your
time starts right now
[Music]
everything I'm sorry Benny
but I'm getting that pink wig
sorry buddy unfortunately in comparison
to the other contestants today the
Justin I have decided their luck was the
week it was very hard self critiquing
from software challenge today but I
think it's important as artists to know
when you do not before to abandon stop I
really thought he was like I couldn't
follow him on Instagram as soon as we
finish probably because this he's
everything himself I'm really grateful
that you took it so well and he isn't
gonna competition a quick waste of the
day so far as you guys can see I mean I
call it the moment gosh see how
everything kind of works out in today's
elimination challenge if I truly don't
know it's validation challenge we've had
a bunch of people on set with us and
hopefully it was a really good
experience we're gonna find out though
going to be judging when it comes to
actually watching the videos so let's
have it you walk so fast
[Music]
I'm barely breathing
it's a souvenir from yesterday or could
it be the fact he's a big man you guys
wanna see his favorite snack you're
gonna have to go to his channel because
that's what this is all about get over
there so I want to like know more about
like your start hey guys today we have a
very special guest okay we all agreed
[Music]
unfortunately out of the cloud videos
today the others really shined and okay
yours was the weakest video and I have
to send you home very very well it just
it feels so real now because we're down
to the final three obviously this prize
is
st. and I have no idea who's ended up
getting it and the next week's challenge
I'm just really proud of Gabriel there's
such a huge audience out there of makeup
artists and that's my makeup artists
that want to learn there are and I think
you could be an incredible resource for
artistry and the diver I learned so much
so you should definitely go check them
out
now it is time to go say hi to the three
finalists and then lap our
semi-finalists
it's been a good day you guys we
officially wrapped oh you can see your
breath that's all called out we are
officially wrapped on a day number three
of the show a whole leg go ahead it's
coming together self well we are
shooting the finale of the show tomorrow
just crazy to think about already tell
you by yourself ass but I've been so
much fun and I cannot wait to go home
and get some rest
I genuinely cannot wait for you guys to
see the show you are going to be
obsessed Oh morning you're actually
shooting the like intro opening the
scene to the entire series which is
river being at last I open script we
have this really fun idea where
basically we do the entire intro in like
one take but that's through like walking
through the entire set thinking
different positions or shows I hope
it'll be so sick and action
hi sisters James Charles here and today
I have something extra special for you
as you know last year I started the
search to find the next Beauty
influencer literally thousands if you
answered the call and I was blown away
by what I saw right well hey I think we
have potential to be a beauty superstar
there'll be a few special guests and
it's hon of surprises but in the end
only one can become an instant
influencer coming after we finish
majority of this and you are a tonight
what I basically means a lot of four
contestants actually hit on to set the
tone of a show while going through and
like speak at nothing as if the
competitors are actually standing in
order to make sure that you get clean
tastes we've actually been enjoy
successful so far getting really good
how I don't we said are you guys know
this but it sounded just kind of a
precaution safety photographers today so
let's go say let's go alright the great
it is the end of day at number four I do
my final anomaly I would do a scroll
with this revenue with others but this
beautiful books and the competition okay
Lauren eating my toenails I feel so bad
it's a literal torture I have beautiful
ones got on it and I forgot but
ultimately came down to consistency
throughout the competition and who I
think has what it takes to be a beauty
superstar our first ever instant
influencer is
Asli this is a out-of-body experience
like I want I am the person in the
middle sir I have to tell you because we
have to go sign off and make your
wedding video but very efficient days I
appreciate everything everyone's done
all the curve balls and getting
everything's done we've done a lot of
great stuff in the can and all your
efforts all departments very appreciated
I think this young man sitting in front
of me for all of us that have done
pilots and first seasons of shows I know
I have and I crush before all of you
have never seen somebody nail it cause
it's important for him to know because
this is different than what he does
every day that's what we do and he
killed it so and Raveena as well as been
amazing
all right you guys and it's a person
that is officially around and it's
officially Iraq on insta influencer
season live this project has been one of
the most fulfilling things that I had
ever gone to work on at my career I'm so
proud of the final outcome and I really
hope that you guys at home enjoyed
watching this but just we enjoy how to
get together and I really hope they get
to do this again at first season 2 but
that is ultimately up to you guys I
really hope you enjoyed the show and you
would go behind the scenes look at what
it took to create it it was a whole lot
of work and so many people were part of
this so I obviously am a thank you to
everybody who is on the casting crew and
I'm proud of myself I thought this was
so much fun and I really hope that you
guys loved it if you did please offer
give a big thumbs up down below until
your love and support it really helps me
out
it helps to show a lot - if you have not
ready to forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come for
the sisterhood for more fun content
coming soon I can't promise you that
it's a super high quality production as
this but promise the videos are very
very funny I'd love to have you and the
family today sister Charlotte goes to
Ashley the winner of the competition
she worked her bomb the past few weeks
that I am so gonna be proud of her you
guys have to go at check her hours
before I go if you have not yet seen all
four episodes of instant influencer and
season one you can click right up here
for a full playlist already guys that is
all I have for today's video I love you
and I will see you in the next one bye
[Music]