hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel today
we're in the studio I made my little
sister's a bathrobe available now and
sisters Esther Perel calm and of course
is going to be getting ready but for
today today I wanted to do something a
little bit different if you've been
watching my channel for a while it is
definitely no secret let's be real hope
that I had my holy grail beauty products
that I pretty much use all the time I
definitely get a lot of comments about
it people ask me to use new things and
I'm not even gonna lie to you guys at
this point I'm honestly getting a little
bit bored too I want to switch it up I
want to try out some new things and I
figured out a really fun way to do that
we'll be testing celebrity makeup hacks
now so my favorite videos in the entire
world are the vogue beauty secrets
series I'm sure you guys have seen them
in your recommended feed on your YouTube
homepage they always pop up for me and I
have watched so many them and personally
I really really love the vogue beauty
secrets videos because they're kind of
like a fun chill intimate inside look
into what the glamour routines of these
celebrities look like on an actual
everyday basis obviously over the course
of their careers they are used to
sitting in a glam chair and working with
different artists so from doing that
they obviously pick up a lot of tips and
tricks and wealth of knowledge from all
these artists and it's really cool to
see it what they picked up and also what
they've implemented into their daily
routines if that really works for them
so last night I was bench watching a ton
of the videos I took notes on a bunch of
my favorite tips and checks froy they
were celebrities I got in my bathrobe I
did try to film this video in my
bathroom I thought it'd be so much cuter
but I could not figure out how to get
the lighting and the camera angle all
correct if anybody works at Vogue and
wants to inform me so we can do a part
two to this video please let me know but
yeah we're it's gonna get glam and
chitchat and if you guys want to see
some celebrity at makeup hacks keep on
watching
[Music]
all right defense before you even put on
a stitch of makeup skincare is super
super important obviously Asda probably
my favorite video of the entire series
is from an 80s supermodel named joan
severance I love her video because she
is so happy and so upbeat and she talks
about all different age defying a beauty
secrets she just says that she wants to
feel beautiful no matter what age she is
and I am freaking love that as a
supermodel clearly she knows good tips
and techniques and even though I'm only
20 I would love to look like her when I
get older so I'm gonna test out her
routine today and she is using a peel
off gel mask as her first step
i'm joan severance and i'm gonna share
some beauty secrets of mine with you
today this is what you take some of this
and glops down the throat and look good
my throat so that's that and now we wait
for it to dry my skin looks right now oh
my god I wish it could actually look
like this on a daily basis this looks so
freaking cool it literally looks like
those Instagram filters that has like
the okay then it's lower there's a
little bit of bulk filter that has the
Bogue logo above your head with your
skin like this it's meant to be in this
vogue video okay that's everything
oh yes oh wow this is good big chunk
this is it that I heard thing that I've
ever done
oh that looks so nasty wow that was so
good I'm gonna quickly wash my face with
water to get off any excess and we're
gonna move on to the next step all right
okay so my next type is just going to be
applying some moisturizer and today I'm
using the old Hendricks in @ci
frightening at gel cream I love this one
and I did a campaign to them a few
months ago I'm never losing it her sense
it isn't bomb health and the next step
is going to be from one of my favorite
models in the entire world Ashley Graham
now in her video after she puts on her a
moisturizer she uses a roller to roll
her skin in I'm gonna be honest with you
guys I've literally never used one of
these before in my entire life I think
even Ashley in her video is like
sometimes I wonder why I are rolling my
face sometimes I wonder why I'm rolling
too but basically it gets the blood
flowing throughout your face that helps
deep up everything because
like a lymphatic massage our state's
pains that really really well so I'm
just going to go ahead and get deep
huffing you know you see all these
people rolling all the time you wonder
why they're rolling sometimes I wonder
why I'm rolling too but I know it's for
the contour it's for the deep huffing
and my skin nice and tight already best
another why skin prep is all done
normally next I'd go to the foundation
but almost literally every single person
that filmed one of these videos did
their eyebrows first which if you know
me you would know is not exactly my
personal favorite technique I just
really like to have my full base on and
then put the eyebrows overtop because I
feel like it's so hard to just carve
them out and just get everything around
them but that being said there's no it
specific way that you have to do makeup
so I'm gonna try it for today and we're
gonna see how it goes
fingers crossed first I start with my
brows I never used to be good at brows
Jordan was always like used to do my
brows I conceal right underneath to
shape the brow and then I actually hmm
well alright okay so the eyebrows are
both odd and I would do that there
looking like okay I honestly will say I
do like how they don't look as like
intense and bold because the fact that
there's no like foundation in powder and
everything underneath them so it's
really just like my skin and the hair
which looks really good but I did have a
lot of trouble getting them even without
kind of like the rest my face to work
off of so I'm not sure maybe I'll
practice this technique more in the
future but regardless let's go ahead and
move on to our next step which is
finally going to be our foundation and
this next tab keeping in the Kardashian
family is from Courtney and she applies
her foundation with her hand now this
tip may seem a little bit crazy for
those of you guys who are like me it's a
group with beauty gurus and have Beauty
blenders and morphe Beauty sponges and
literally everything in between
but the reality is is that a lot of
people use at their hands for their
foundation and a lot of celebrity makeup
artists swear by using their fingers in
their hands because the natural heat of
the body does a really good job of kind
of blending everything in and making it
look smooth I don't like doing this
because I have a very very weird like
phobia of getting makeup on my fingers
and nails I don't know what it is I
literally keep makeup wipes right next
to me at all times and I clean
my hands so often I'll do my makeup and
my little bit crazy or does everybody
else do this like I just do not like the
feeling of having makeup on my fingers
and just makes me feel like the process
is in a dirty and phimka gross that my
nails are good we're gonna do it today
an honor of sister Courtney it might
work out but I don't have any complaints
I'm ready to clean up after I apply this
with my hands I also do my skin before
my eyes I think I told Kendall about
this too using my hands first of all was
not as nasty as I thought it was going
to be I just clean it afterwards and I
was completely fine at the nails are all
good and I did not freak out and I will
admit that using my hands that kind of
low-key Heike made me feel like one of
those supermodels that just like rubs
everything on and gets clam in five
minutes and somehow it looks really chic
like it does look very very beautiful
but sees my fingers took way way longer
than it does when you think it's fun so
who knows I might use this again in the
future and I'm on a time crunch though
absolutely not but that being said to
each their own and now I decide to move
on to the next step and that is from
Taylor hill and normally my next MOV
concealer but Taylor hill likes to use a
powder brush and set pretty much her
entire face with a little bit of powder
before her concealer now as you guys
know they're obviously no rules to
makeup but kind of one of the more
unspoken suggestions is that it's not
really great to put creams or liquids
overtop of powder because they don't
waste much well without being sad if
it's working for we're gonna test it out
today that is the beauty of this video
so I'm just gonna grab my little setting
powder mixture and a fluffy brush and
I'm just going to lightly set my face
and please next I'm just gonna use a
little bit of powder I put powder all
over my face next is concealer sometimes
I use brushes but for the most part like
if it's more natural the makeup I like
to use my hands because I feel like it
blends the product better I mean that
worked really well cool I am pleasantly
surprised with the result of Miss Taylor
Hills a technique I think my skin is
looking a beautiful to concealer blend
it out to one
and I am loving this so far that being
said that my face is looking a little
bit flat and I am definitely ready to
add in some more dimension with some
contour today I'm gonna be following it
tonight
EKOS fun fact a few weeks ago on Twitter
I tweeted her thing she was beautiful
and to your pilot said that I was also
beautiful and I was very excited about
it so I think it's safe to say we're
both fans of each other which is kind of
everything I'm just gonna grab my normal
contouring I'm brush and dip into my
narwhal contour shade at least for the
cheekbones and forehead portion but I'm
gonna go soft kind of to it I like to
just follow my natural curves for her
contour differentiates on her nose
contour instead of tonight doing a
superest notched nose like I personally
her fur she actually contours like a
little ball on the tip of her nose and
gives that like that button look which I
actually already have I normally try to
hide it so let's try it out for my nose
I like to create like a little button
no do a little circle at the point at
the I don't know whatever that's hot
then I use my finger and I go right here
to give it like a cute little all right
you guys said this next up comes from
Emily radda radda chomsky right at
akatsuki Hirata - I don't want to get
dried from restaurants in her last name
her Instagram was Amerada she's a
beautiful supermodel and this is her
five-minute date night look now at
Emily's video she used a cream a
highlighting stick pretty much like all
over her face TIFF I'm going to be
honest I don't think this technique
would really work for a lot of people
who don't look perfect like her for
example media but I'm definitely down to
try this out and see what ends up
looking like a little bit of highlighter
I just take the stick a little bit on
the nose put on my lip
into the eye yeah and realizing that my
skin looks so pretty I'm not a sweetie
I'm so sorry that I doubted you even for
a moment
like what first Shore going to be using
this technique in the future I don't
think this technique would really work
okay so the next time is going to be of
course I showed up unfortunately not
many of the celebrities actually put on
eye shadow looks in their videos which
definitely sucks so one trick that a lot
of people did use however is using their
bronze are in contour to really chisel
out of their eyelids which I actually do
all the time when it comes to my
everyday glam so we're going to do that
inspired by a kendall Jenner I learn a
lot from being on set I usually just
take my bronzer and do it by phone I may
have like a little bit crazy
using the brush hair on my eyelid look I
am just not used to this whole natural
glam type of situation but this does
gonna show that using a few different
shades of brown can create a really
really stunning I look even if it is it
very simplistic
and I think this looks gorgeous we're
about to move on to our next step which
is going to be eyeliner well my favorite
people of all time elect said to me at
from a euphoria did her book video and
she's like taste like my style icon
right now and she did a very very
beautiful block wing on both the outside
and inside of her eyes so I'm gonna
follow her techniques today so I see
this Pat McGrath pen I start at the on
the outer I like a really like pointed
so I kind of just start like that and
then I always get a q-tip and
[Music]
no that is a fail okay this is the first
step so far that has been a fail oh it
sucks to say what this is the first
technique of this video that did
absolutely not work for me putting on
the winged liner it was super easy but I
did kind of mess up a little bit and I
wanted to follow Alexus technique of
kind of licking a cotton swab a cotton
swab if you are a fast refresh watch I
tried it sucking on the q-tip cleaning
up eyeliner to fix it all did was just
drag the actual ink like everywhere it
did not look at it from nation I had to
go back and conceal any way to fix it up
so definitely will not be trying that
one again regardless Alexa looks
beautiful I really love this winged
liner and the inner corner points I
really like this technique and might try
this more often because it very much
gives you that like snatched pull back
feline cat table book which I'm done for
any day of the week but that being said
that is pretty much this I look all
complete super simple super cute I'm
gonna go in and do the mascara and
lashes off camera because everyone is
pretty much dead regular lashes mascara
I'll be right back to continue on with
these tips and tricks so that this point
the look is pretty much almost complete
we only have the lips left and it is
still looking at so beautiful now before
I actually gonna put on any lip products
I want to take one tip from Josefina
scrubber who's a Victoria's Secret model
huh she's still beautiful and that is to
scrub your lips with a tooth brush
before actually putting on a lip product
to exfoliate get rid of any of those
disgusting Krusty's and also plum I love
to brush my lips it was always a little
bit of a dead skin on them and it makes
them swallow a little bit more okay my
lips are definitely tingly I don't know
it's actually being a plunked but this
toothbrush is very very like dense so it
like definitely did a good job look like
roughening up Phillips it did do its job
of exfoliating it I honestly might
continue to use this for me whenever I'm
actually doing my makeup routine I
always it wait to brush my teeth until
right before I do my lipstick so if I am
doing my makeup routine next time and I
go into the bathroom to wash my teeth
before doing lipstick maybe I'll go
ahead and brush my lips beforehand kind
of fun now for lips I took one more
check from Ashley Graham's video but
before she actually goes in with the
lips she actually takes a dark brown
eyeliner pencil and re like dark and
slash shades in her moles to accentuate
them which i think is super super cool
obviously you guys seen my face without
makeup on and I have quite a lot of
moles all around so I'm not really sure
how this is going to
but I'm gonna try it now I also like to
color in there's this like amazing
eyeliner and I don't use it on my eyes I
use it on my mole I love to color in my
malls and make them darker oh no oh no
this was a just did a bad thing
this is that's the Little Dipper oh my
god it looked so cute when Ashley did it
why does it look so stupid on me
first of all I feel like I use a shade
that was definitely too dark like her
looks nice and cute and natural like it
still kind of poke into the foundation
this looks like literal connect the dots
like this is not okay I'm gonna cheat
the system a little bit and grab some
test powder and kind of fix this because
this is bad well not what I will
definitely not be doing again I think
this is a good learning lesson that
everything can be okay in moderation and
this was not moderated I should have
used the later brown brow pencil first
or I should not have done all of my
moles because this just looks billy
stupid that being said I think it looks
really cute on Ashley and I definitely
want to try this again be using a better
technique and kind of reaccelerating
them because I do love my moles never
leave before putting on our new lipstick
Ashley talked about using a brown
eyebrow pencil to lightly contour out
your lips before putting on a nude
lipstick overtop this is my eyebrow
pencil that I use for my lips and it
just kind of contours your lips they do
the rest of my finger
alright you go ahead with the lipstick
all odd and contoured things too miss
Ashley Graham I'm just gonna apply a
little bit of some setting it's ready to
lock this all in place and I think that
is this makeup tutorial and using all
celebrity and makeup hacks all complete
I had so much fun binge watching all
these boat videos last night and bed it
was literally 3:00 in the morning and I
wanted to get up and do a makeup look so
badly I was just feeling so inspired and
I think this is a really good way for me
to kind of break out of my shell stop
using the same products over and over
and over again because I know that you
guys are really bored and I really feel
like that I picked up so if any new at
tips techniques and products that I
definitely want to integrate my beauty
routine and I really hope that you guys
enjoyed this video as well and feel like
you learned something new if you date it
please don't forget to give a big thumbs
up down below and share your love and
support it really means a lot and also
leave me a comment let me know what was
your favorite new a beauty tip or
technique uh if you like mine and I
cannot believe that about to say this
was actually Kourtney's applying it the
foundation with your hands and then
Taylor Hills like light powder and
concealer trick call me crazy but I feel
like my skin looks so beautiful and just
like dewy and fresh right now I really
want to test this out a whole lot more
and just go for bora and natural clam
looks but definitely looking forward to
hearing what you guys have to say as Wow
if you've not ready make sure you click
that big red subscribe button down below
and come join this sisterhood I would
love to have you in the family and I'll
stuff like that belt like um so you
can't refuse every time I upload a brand
new video if they can follow me and I
may come to rdp follow me on Instagram
Twitter and tik-tok or I'll just Gino
Charles and my snapchat for more I
haven't seen signs up and seniors
Charles that extra ask after Charles
this videos sister shadow goes to sister
Kylie thank you so much love for always
falling in supporting all of you
literally so so so much and if you at
home watching my sweet the next videos
sister shout out atrophic it's always
reach route of Italy's when they go live
on Twitter and also to my YouTube post
notifications
alright you guys thank you so much
watching this video today I love you and
I will see you in the next one bye
[Music]