hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my channel since the
very very start of my Instagram feed and
following in general my brows have
always been something that are very very
controversial and always that widely
talked about people either love my bushy
defined brows or they hate them with a
passion and they describe them as things
like Lego or caterpillars but either way
they're still talking about them which
in PR sense is very very good rather to
what people think though my brows have
changed very very drastically from the
start of my Instagram career they've
gotten much more natural still large and
in charge but much less sharp II like so
for today's video I thought I would sit
down and do it update a brow routine
because I don't think I've ever actually
done one on this channel before and I
get so many questions every single video
asked me how I do my brows because for
the most part I do usually do them
off-camera
to save time so that being said if you
want to see how I get my very very
natural yet bushy large enough charts
and defined brows make sure you keep on
watching alright so I already went ahead
it and I did my base up camera that
being my foundation concealer powdered
my entire face did a little bit of
contour and highlight just so doesn't
look too weird and then baked my face as
well and then it wiped it off I do this
in every single video and then my next
step would usually be my eyebrows which
I usually do off-camera just to save
time but like I was saying today we were
going to be doing my brow routine which
is what I do in every single look
whether or not it's on camera my brows
have changed so drastically since the
beginning of my Instagram career so I
thought it would be absolutely perfect
to sit down today and team up with
Benefit Cosmetics they give you guys an
updated brow routine just shot off my
brows today I'm just gonna grab the
benefit process in my eyebrow pencil and
I'm just gonna shake off the bottom end
to use the spoolie and I'm actually just
going to start by brushing through via
bra Harris and brush them all kind of
upwards just to see kind of how big
and bushy eyebrows we are just to get a
good idea of where underneath filling in
and what areas and don't need as much
first product I'm going to go ahead with
is the Bravo conditioning primer and I'm
just going to take the top off and I'm
going to do this a few million times and
I'm just gonna run it through the brow
hairs just like a primer for your face
this is a primer for your brow hair so
it just gets them nice and ready to pull
product and really ensures that your
brows will last all day long
and it also makes like I said before
your brows as full as possible so you
get a good idea of where you should be
putting the product and getting your
brows on fleek and I'm just gonna go on
the back and let's we'll leave one more
time just to evenly distribute that
product through the brow hairs and once
again it push the hair
if you have any straight brown hair this
would be a perfect time to grab your
tweezers and pluck them up before we get
too far into the filling in and the rest
of the brow routine
I'm just really carefully plucking out
any stray hairs that I know are not
going to be in I do get asked all the
time - like who does your eyebrows only
loudly but you get them done and I
actually do my brows completely myself
I've been tweezing my own brows for a
very very long time and I do consider
myself pretty good at it at this point I
also taste a lot of my friends brows as
well and have made some fantastic brow
transformations if I do say so myself
but I really do like tweezing my brow I
would not trust anybody else to wax or
the red now I'm just way too scared and
obviously as a beauty - I have a very
very distinct style of what I like my
brows to look like but if you are
someone who wants to get them through or
tweeze please do this is definitely not
like an easy thing to do in any way
shape or form and if you don't trust
yourself please leave it to a
professional because I've seen stories
my poor mom is someone who actually had
definitely overlooked her broadly she
was younger and now she regrets it all
the time and she's always asking me to
draw in her brows for her which I always
do a course but the poor girl barely has
any eyebrows left so definitely be
careful when you're plucking and go to
professional if you don't trust your
self home to actually fill in and shape
the brows that I'm gonna be using once
again deep resizing my brow pencil in
the shade number 4
I like oops I like the tip of this
because it is super super tiny and
defined so it really lets me get really
really light and defined lines and in
this front area - I can really sketch in
those tiny hairs and make it look
realistic I don't like to start off my
brows like kind of sketching out the
bottom line so I'm just going to start
on the front here and I'm going to
really really really lightly it'd be
good to shape out the
as you guys can see my brother's really
do not have that much of an arch either
so when I'm in this inner corner I
really like to start kind of low and
pull it up at an angle creating more of
an arch effect that isn't really there
and then of course if I make any
mistakes or anything looks too harsh
I'll just switch over to the spoolie end
and I'll comb really lightly over it
just to it
Oh throughout this entire video I'm
going to using this spoolie and this a
lot just kind of switching back and
forth back and forth to get the perfect
results when I get to the outer corner
I'm going to take it the Pens lit number
two really lightly flick it out towards
the end just like when it comes to
shaping your browser obviously gonna
want to do what works best for your face
shape but I find for me personally the I
really like to say eyebrows that goes up
and then kind of out I don't really like
when my brows go down I feel like I have
like a very very tall face so I like to
kind of widen it as much as possible so
by pulling this brow out towards like
this area rather than towards the bottom
of my cyber I get a much like wider more
masculine effect I guess but do whatever
works best for you I'm not grabbing that
pencil I'm going to start defining the
tail so I'm just drawing a line
connecting it right down to that point
then like I said it grimy that's fully
to just blend forward and food
traditions like I said I'd really to
fake a little bit of an arch on my brow
I'm like before once again thank God
those old brow days are over I'm going
to what start by grabbing the pencil and
I'm going to really lightly sketch a
horn line if anything I like the of
bottom some eyebrows to be a little bit
to find it but I don't like the top to
be super defined well because that's
when we get into like the Lego Sharpie
style borrow that they used to have and
that style is over up done with pencil
never wants to get again when it comes
to the inner corner of the brow I really
like the hairs to be very very wispy
looking and I like there to be a natural
ombre from the front to the tip of the
brow this part obviously being a whole
lot darker I'm just guessing in a few
tiny little hairs really really lightly
in the front here just to kind of give
it a little bit of shape but not doing
any real filling and and then once again
describing these spoolie on the end of
the precisely my brow pencil and just
brushing through the brow hairs to kind
of brush them up in the right direction
and the blend through the product and
making sure that there is no area where
it is very very concentrated you know
any sparse area that we don't want any
it's are four areas either the goal is
to have that nice but still defined what
that brought us all a roughly put in
place my next up is gonna be to grab my
favorite concealer watch it right now
with the tarik tape tape and just put a
little bit on the back of my hand and
then we're just going to clean up that
brow I'm gonna really let they follow
the line that I sketched in using the
brow pencil and like I said before it
does not need to be a perfect because
now at the time we get to clean up any
mistakes
regardless of what products steps or
techniques you use and your brow routine
I feel like this is one set that is
absolutely by all no matter who you are
or what your shape is or like but your
style is and like just cleaning up via
bottom of the brows makes it look so
much more defined makes them with a
whole lot cleaner and I would definitely
recommend you to do that if you don't
already do it now that the brow is all
smashed and defined my last and final
step it's going to be to go in to be a
benefit gimme brow gel in the shade and
number three I absolutely love this brow
gel because the wand is so freakin tiny
so you can really get in on the hangers
and make sure you're not gonna make any
mistakes I can't even tell you how many
times I've gotten my brows to look so
frickin good
and then I've bought into the brow gel
and just got like one brown line or
smudge little get the worst thing in the
entire world so like I said I really
really do it like this wand just like
they couldn't see that under the brows I
really really really good at brow gel
it's an absolute necessity I need it
good or protein just because as the day
goes on and your sweat cons hard to
remove product and the hairs are gonna
start to move around so this challenge
is really in terms of the hair stay
locked in place in the market what
alright guys I just draw in some lashes
and a quick gloss and that is the
completed look and video for today my
brow style has changed so much since
beginning my Instagram feed thank God
but oh so much fun today to teach you
guys how I get my natural but still
defined brows using only a few products
if you did enjoyed this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and scram you have not
already I post two videos a week on
Mondays and Fridays that I would love to
have you join the sisterhood if you'd
like to follow me on a makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both just James Charles
and my snapchat nu now for more of a
sudden seems types fr James Charles the
next row asked after Charles all right
sisters thank you so much for watching
and I will see you in the next one bye
[Music]