[Music]
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so I
am currently on set right now for my
campaign video and photo shoot for my
sister collection with morphe oh my god
a few days ago now we posted our
official reveal video upload my talent
and my brush collection that I have
created over the past several months and
oh my god you guys I cannot even begin
to explain how thankful and grateful I
am for all of your feedback and support
this launch is literally going to wake
makeup history I'm so glad that I got to
partner with Murphy because creating
this collection has been so much fun and
so incredible they have truly given me
so much artistic freedom to really
create the collection that I wanted
forever as an artist and also as well I
got to produce my very own commercial
for the entire collection which was so
much fun if you guys have not yet seen
my reveal be to make sure it's like
right up here for the full on commercial
and full review of the collection the
palette all the swatches the prices
every single brush that is in this brush
set it's a pretty good and beefy video
and it's gonna have all the information
that you're gonna want to know before
you actually get the collection for
today's the do I want it to do a
tutorial and one of the looks for my
campaign commercial and that is the
image that is on all packaging for my
palette this iconic unleash your inner
artist look hello flaming I am obsessed
with this look I love this and
ironically enough as well we honestly
shot the packaging photos for the
palette over six months ago now and
somehow this look happened to become a
trend in the big community a few months
ago which I thought was so so so funny
so major sound us to all the artists out
there for giving me a little bit of
promo before my product was even out Co
but in reality great minds do think
alike and I thought this is just be so
much fun to just thank you guys for all
your love and support and to give you
guys a cute little easy tutorial on this
campaign look today so that further ado
let's jump into this first ever tutorial
using my palette my brushes my
collection with morphe and let's unleash
our inner artists
[Music]
so my face is already completely on
because we just thought the music slips
for the commercial this morning about
I'm just going to uh oh ouch pop off my
lashes and add my look on top of this
I'm first gonna go up in 4 3 3 brush and
dip into the shade escape and I'm going
to pop this right on the outer corner
and start Tilly and like imagine it's
gonna be like a Hello the outer V I
normally don't apply shadows like this
either but my goal for creating this
palette was to create really really
pigmented and fully matte eyeshadows
because it's saying that I've wanted in
my kit as an artist literally since
starting in the makeup game and of
course it's been a lot of really really
bomb talent but one of the problems with
propellants I feel like is that they all
look so beautiful inside the actual
palette but a lot of the shadows don't
actually apply that pigmented onto the
skin but I really wanted to create a
really pigmented really bomb and really
really bright rainbow colors and through
doing that some of the matte shades are
either matte or some of them are
actually pressed pigments which means
you just have to work with them in a
little bit of a different way and that
means packing on that shadow first next
thing we have another M 4-3-3 brush and
dip into the shade single which is that
lighter purple shade and I'm gonna use
this too lightly diffuse out the edges
I'm just gonna tuck that right into the
crease as well moving on we're gonna
come back to that in a little bath now
that the Purple's all place on the outer
corner and it's all set in place I'm
just going to grab an Emma four-for-one
brush and dip into B which is the bright
yellow shade this is by far the best
bright yellow shadow I have ever tried
look at this ready hello oh my god like
literally you're kidding me
and I was gonna pop this right on my
inner corner kind of letting into the
nose contour as well I just pull
something right into that crease region
next I'm going to grab another and 4-3-3
brush this is why I love this brush
that's so so so much because they're
multiples of many of the different eye
brushes which make it so perfect for
doing rainbow looks like this you don't
have to wash your brushes in the middle
of them and you also don't have to buy a
million-two them from the website you
get them all at once in the brush kit so
good it's so fresh so helpful I went to
this shade right into the bright red
which is called you're kidding
why is it called that you're gonna find
out when I put this on you're kidding
look at the pigmentation oh my god that
is like a true true true rad rad as all
of the shades that I was most excited
about but also most nervous about
because firm leading a bright red shadow
is really really hard and I also feel
like it's something that is always
missing from every single palette I feel
like every read either reads a burnt
orange or magenta and I was like now I
want red like is it that hard and it was
apparently I was wrong but we did it and
it looks bomb know that same exact brush
I'm gonna dip into the shade of five on
eight which is the bright light orange
color
I'm obsessed with this orange it is so
neon so cool and I'm going to just blend
the yellow and red shades together so
now I'm going to take my favorite brush
of this entire collection this ladies
and gentlemen is the M 4 5 6 so you're
probably thinking that's just another
fuzzy batch no it's not you guys know
the Emperor 33 is my ride-or-die okay I
literally have 36 of these in my makeup
collection and they all are covered and
dirty and a million different eye shadow
colors I love this brush I could
literally do an entire shadow look with
this brush but now we have the M 4 5 6
which is literally a brush that I have
wanted to create since I started working
with morphe so many years ago it is
literally the m-43 threes babies sister
it is the same exact brush just half the
size now this brush is going to be so
perfect for those of you out there who
have a smaller eyes and still want to
create that beautiful blended look or if
you people like me who have big eyes but
like to do kind of detailed rainbow
intricate blending looks this brush is
perfect because it still blows
everything out but you can really get
right in those crease regions to just
blend in to fuse that color without
getting it everywhere so I'm gonna dip
this brush into the shade skip which is
the bright neon pink and I'm gonna use
this to connect the red and diffuse out
the edge of the purple if you ever need
to fix any blending describe your atom
at 4 or 5 6 the perfect tiny blending
brush and just go right back in there
NextEra grab by other at four five six
that comes into the collection and dip
into the shade escape this is the darker
purple shade I'm gonna pop this right in
the outer V to start creating some
dimension I'm just gonna put a little
bit more of that single shade into the
crease for some more dimension to for my
auto color I'm gonna grab my IVA 506
brush from the brush tat I love this
tiny brush for blending out the outer V
and dip into a little bit of the shade
of spooky deep blonde shade in the
palette I'm gonna be very very careful
cuz I don't want to add too much just
kind of patting that on there and
lightly blending it out and then going
back into the M four five six
and there's escape so this is looking
messy right now we're obviously going to
clean it up do not worry so now we're at
the stage where I want to cut the crease
and lay down the rest of the shadows so
I'm going to grab an damnit two to four
brush this is my favorite concealer and
just a thick white concealer and I'm
just gonna go right in on the inner
corner cutting my crease a little bit
bigger than normal and then governing to
n43 one this is the little pencil brush
from the kit I'm gonna grab a tiny bit
more of that concealer on the paint
brush I just got a little bit off and
I'm gonna go in and actually diffuse out
those edges because I don't want this to
be a crease I want it to be like a paper
cut crease now we're gonna have a one 6x
brush and dip into the white shade in
the palette which is a flashback based
on the most iconic internet meme of all
time I really wanted to make a super
pigmented white eye shadow because I
feel like these are really really really
hard to find and I also decided to place
it in the middle row as well because a
lot of you guys love using white when it
comes to either track or theater or just
avant-garde looks in general I will say
confidently non bias as well this is by
far the best most pigmented white
eyeshadow I have ever tried or seen I
swear to God you could either put it on
once purchased a light little wash of
white or the shadow does layer up and
you can literally make it like bright
white that's what I wait so good once
that why I said it I'm just gonna take
my original fluffy brushes and just go
lightly over those edges to even diffuse
it a little bit more now to fix this
whole moment in here because this is
obviously not the tea I'm gonna add some
blue
my ab12 for brush this is just a tiny
little packing brush and dip into the
shade acappella which is our metallic
blue shade and I'm gonna give it a
little bit of a spritz using the morphe
preppin set I'm gonna pack this shade
right on here that are dirty I'm four
five six I'm gonna grab the shade at
kolob which is our dark blue matte shade
I'm obsessed with this color it is
obviously named after Pepsi my favorite
soda just pop it right in there to make
sure the purple and blue are blended
together and then going back in and
blending this edge and on that same
brush the next under grab the shade
hello and pop that right in the middle
of that dark blue and the white just to
add some more dimension to the lid I'm
gonna use the peaches and cream at
glitter base and a few different
glitters that I have this one is from in
your dreams as well as from peaches and
this one is from the craft store and I'm
just gonna pack that right over top of
the white driving a little bit of that
chunkier glitter from in your dream just
gonna pop that on just lightly dabbing
that on as well I do want to show the
glitter reflex but I don't want my
eyelid to literally feel crusty because
that's the worst feeling in the entire
world and then just finally some super
chunky pieces probably the craft store
just here and there now I definitely
have a little bit of fallout that is for
sure so I'm gonna grab the e48 brush I
love this brush for under-eye powder
ever is going to dust that all away and
pray that it actually goes away good
smells my palate is pigmented then to
finish off the upper lash center it's
gonna grab me a liquid black liner and
just go right over that to hide with the
wash that we're gonna put on it a little
bit the lower lash line for this look is
actually going to be pretty easy just
slopping on some colors I'm first gonna
grab a I'm a four five six that has a
little bit of the excess purple shade on
it interested one more time into it
single and I'm gonna use this to blend
together this outer corner with my am
one two four brush dipping into the
shade of brother deeper ice blue shade I
love this color it is obviously named
after sister Yan I'm just going to pop
this right up against that lower lash
there next to the purple this is another
one of those shades that was really hard
to formulate so you definitely want back
the shades on there and then with the
m15 - this is a tiny brush but I love
this for buffing out the lower lash line
I'm gonna dip into the bright green
shade which is called socialblade in
honor of all of you guys and my crazy
growth throughout this past year gotta
stay green always and I'm going to pop
this right next to that blue
and also creating a faux inner corner as
well now gonna go to the a before two
one brush intimate ooh a little bit more
of that white concealer and I'm gonna
use this to create a new lower lash line
using a tiny little liner brush was
gonna dip into the darker green shade
which is called
daddy and honor of my best friend
Laura's husband Victor you guys in the
him in ton of videos now it's gonna line
are right up against the white over top
of the green area just a little bit more
dimension and then using that same brush
gonna dip into Cola and do the same
thing in the blue and then the same
thing would escape in the purple using a
tiny bit more of that peaches glitter
glue I'm just going to pop some right on
top of that way as well just so
everything is like flowing nicely
together just gonna pop on a quick coat
of a mascara and then just popping on a
wispy lash and then it's gonna pop on a
little lash spike right in the middle of
the lower lash line it just for funsies
alright you guys and that is one eye of
this unleash your inner earnest campaign
look all complete I'm gonna go do the
other one off-camera quickly to save
some time and I'll be right back to
finish off the rest of this look oh
we're back I just finished both eyes
that I'm looking at so beautiful I
literally love this look of so so so
much but we're not even close to being
done yet because now I have to turn
myself into the whole blank canvas
unleash your inner artist imagine this
is the paintbrush moment so I'm gonna
paint a lot of my face and body white so
I'm gonna get my fresh makeup wipe oh
okay it's definitely this way yeah okay
I'm gonna take a brush makeup wipe and
I'm going to basically like wipe off
this area because I'm gonna put white
there and it's not gonna mix alright
well I don't want it to mix with the
foundation or else that'll be tan
instead of white to paint my face right
I'm going to use the Kryolan aqua color
what is this pan thing I'm gonna give it
a good spread so using the morphe prep
and set this is water activated but fun
fact this does actually work too so it
used hojae's for 10% off
[Music]
that looks beautiful
no one does an everyday makeup look I
think so is it the grocery store maybe
mm-hmm I always love a putting makeup on
my ears too I feel like every time I do
like more creative looks like this I
always try to incorporate it and I
always get weird comments be like oh my
god why don't you put on this ear but
like it just pulls the entire piece
together like your ears are part of your
face and it also low-key tickles and
kind of feels got to him I'm just gonna
grab a tiny bit of foundation on the
back of my hand and with that savings
like fan brush I'm just gonna go like
over just like I did with the white some
of those edges just to kind of bring
back for the foundation and make it
truly look like it is being painted on
now I decide to make my entire body
white okay let's do it
[Music]
then you get the entire Murphy team to
help you make yourself life all right
you guys a nice oh that's weird look
that is the finished unleash your inner
artist look for my Murphy XG and Charles
campaign all complete I had the idea
with this look so long ago and I had so
much fun to conceptualize and get
designing it and finally putting it into
place on my face today I hope you guys
really enjoyed this video and I cannot
wait to see all of you recreated this
luck with your palettes as well you can
get my iconic palette with 39 shades for
only thirty and nine dollars it has a
full a beautiful rainbow and lots of
other clan shades as well perfect to
create literally any look you could
possibly imagine and my brush set as
well which retails for hundred and
forty-nine dollars
it's a two hundred $18 value that has so
many brushes it comes in a custom morphe
X James Charles hubby case a perfect for
traveling a contour and blending sponge
for those of you who don't like
foundation brushes and 34 of my all-time
favorite brushes including duplicates of
meting my favorite eye brushes as well
so you can create any single look
without having to clean in between the
perfect brush set to unleash your inner
artist oh and also don't forget to use
code days for 10% off your entire
purchase if you enjoy this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and show your
sisters support and love it means so
much to me and also click that big red
subscribe button down below it's all
income from the sisterhood we are almost
10 million sisters strong oh my god oh
also click the bow mic on so you can get
a notification every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on my makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both the
same Charles and my snapchat more by the
seaside self its James Charles the next
rise after Charles yes they do a sister
so that goes to sister Kenz and thank
you so much love we're always falling in
supporting no I love you literally it's
so so so much and if you liked read the
next videos sister shout out don't
forget to always retweet my middle east
like a lion on Twitter but also shout
out to every single person out there
following me and supporting me whether
you join yesterday or three years ago I
am so thankful for all your guys's kind
about this collection I've been working
on this for so long now and this has
been a project that I wanted to do it's
an enjoyed in the makeup community and I
can finally say that it is here and I am
so proud of the products that we are
putting out and I can that way for all
you guys to have them in your hands all
that being said Thank You sisters so
much for watching this videos today I
love you
[Music]
unleash your inner artist