hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
happy 2020 you guys oh my god I could
not believe it the new year is finally
here it is about time everyone had a
super happy healthy but most importantly
safe holiday season
personally I spent my night doing
absolutely nothing which was incredible
wouldn't change anything ten out of ten
would recommend I played Mario Kart did
a few different makeup look hung out
with a bunch of old friends and also met
a ton of new friends and honestly you
guys I don't want to jinx anything
because I'm just only not in my life
right now but twenty twenty so far has
been treating me very very well and I
really hope it's been the same for you
guys I truly feel like this is going to
be our year I'm just like I'm feeling
the energy and the vibes like all
together but I am very very stated to
all the projects all the fun things that
we have coming for 2020 I thought it'd
be really really fun to just sit down
together do a little bit of a chit chat
get ready to me there's been a lot of
things happening in my life resent that
I want to catch you guys up on and also
I've pretty much like completely changed
my everyday on makeup routine I
literally have so many new things so
what are you techniques on new products
this is a very wearable everyday to have
makeup look but elevate it to the next
level and I think you guys are not so
gonna love this so if you guys want to
get ready to lean and see my updated
makeup routine talk a little bit about
2019 but more importantly talk about
2020 and all the fun things coming soon
keep on watching
[Music]
before we jump right in did anybody
notice the new graphics on the channel
control I am literally obsessive how
they turned out I thought it'd be really
fun to go into 20/20 with a few new
things on it - the videos they get to my
good friend of Michael who designed it
he does all the youtuber intros and he's
literally so talented make sure you guys
check them out and also leave me a
comment down below if you notice
anything else okay time to jump in so
one of my favorite things that I did
over the holiday break was getting a
tattoo a face tattoo okay no I did not
get anything crazy I know I uploaded one
at robbing my makeup routine but I'm not
a soundcloud rapper just yeah I want
obviously keep you guys posted my
sisters but I did get my eyebrows a
microplane and spoiler alert I am
obsessed with the result I'm gonna tell
you guys about it while I go ahead and
conceal my brows which is now the first
type of a makeup routine I know there's
video footage of me out there saying
that I would never do my eyebrows first
I just really like to have my full base
on and then put the eyebrows overtop
because I feel like it's so hard to just
carve them out and just get everything
but after trying this technique out and
my celebrity makeup hacks video and
getting them done I will honestly say
this is like the best decision that I've
ever made a my makeup routine that now
takes me at like literally 30 minutes
lasts and I am obsessed with how they
turned out I came across this micro
bleeding artist by the name of brown jam
and I was so shocked by her work because
it was much different than like the
typical kind of like chainin and a
blocky and micro bleeding that a lot of
people kind of had when it first became
like a thing and it was very focused I'm
just like tiny little thin hair strokes
I was so good and I was so shocked by it
that I literally commented on her post
and was like this is the best microbe
winning that I've ever seen I didn't
think anything of it and I just went to
bed but the next morning I woke up and
check my Instagram Deion's and she
actually me and her name was Jeanne but
she was living in Scotland and I was
talking to her about micro bleeding and
she's like oh my god I would love to do
your brows one day and I was like yeah
I'll let you know if I'm ever overseas
and she's like oh I will literally come
to LA and do them for you if you want I
was like oh my god no way like I'd kind
of be down low key and she's literally
like okay let me know I'll book a flight
like now and I was like okay kind of
down and then she was here so long story
short Janine
flew all the way here from a Scotland -
micro blade my eyebrows and I am
obsessed with the results she did
literally the best job guru Sai brows
look amazing as well
she's oops I'm gonna leave Janine's
links down below
none of the eyebrows are all outlined
and blended out I know it looks a little
bit crazy right now
this
like look right I was literally the
reasoning for me not wanting to do this
step beforehand but I now realized that
it is way easier to clean up later on so
if you're watching this and you two are
an eye brows before foundation hater
like I was just bear with me because
it'll come together later on and who
knows maybe you'll change your routine
as well because I'm loving this anyway
okay while that concealer is drying down
a little bit I'm just gonna grab a
little bit of the dragon Beauty color
corrector just like always and put this
on my beard area this step has not
changed I still want to cover up my
beard and five o'clock shadow such as I
possibly can so now while this is right
now I'm gonna go ahead and do my skin
private before foundation someone's
gonna got my touch-up water cream and a
little fluffy brush I'm just going to
brush this on my skin and I'm actually
going to avoid my nose area because my
nose gets really really oily and I've
noticed that not moisturizing it
honestly helps the foundation stay a
little bit better and then with the
touch s self canvas primer I'm just
gonna grab a flat foundation brush this
is the morphe M at 7:07 hues good things
for 10% off I'm just going to grab a
little bit of this and applied this area
to my central cheek area kind of which
is where I have like a bigger pores to
fill this in and smooth this out and
then finally I know this is very
dramatic but like I said has been
working well for me recently I'm gonna
grab the event a beauty troop matte
primer and put a little bit of this onto
my finger and I'm just going to apply
this primer to my nose to keep it true
matte like it says in the name and
that's it
alright now that all that prep work is
done and out of the way we are finally
ready to learn to foundation and for
today I'm gonna using a brand new one
and that is the Dior Eric lash
foundation now I honestly have no clue
why I didn't pick this up until recently
but I'm very fresh to do myself that I
did it because the formula is so bomb
and also what the undertones are like
perfect the shade is 1n and literally
okay like you're looking so good this is
for my face ready for this no I ain't
ready for this okay ready literally by
skin tone that's literally my skin tone
oh my god we have essentially found the
color that is for me like this is 2020
is gonna be my year I'm matching
foundation I'm actually just gonna spray
this on the back of my assisters easier
so I can dip into it like a palette
because the fumes are slightly toxic
what not talks like to please don't sue
me
good to breathe it all so I'm just
putting this into my skin using the Juno
and kala
microfiber sponge and it's like this
like weird fuzzy type of a sponge but it
does such a good job of blending the
foundation into at my skin all right now
that we have the base all on moving on
to concealer nothing has changed
so I'm gonna grab my tart shape tape and
this one is in the shade light okay so
while glad it's all together I thought
it'd be kind of fun to do a quick 2019
recap and when I say quick I do mean
quick okay choose a 19 was a mess but
there were some amazing things that we
did in this past year so let's talk
about them so starting off the year in
January my first days of 2019 were
actually spent in a Tennessee way that
the Cimorelli girls we got to spend New
Year's together and then we recorded the
never enough cover that is now the
second most viewed video on my channel
of all time which is so wild to think
about I love those girls so so so much
and I got to see them a few times to
2019 which is actually amazing and then
later on in the month of January I went
to the UK for the first time ever which
was so much fun I'm going to the UK was
on my bucket list for literally so long
and we were finally able to make it
happen I got a chance to open up the
morphe store in the bullring mall and
I'm Birmingham and it was one of the
best days of my entire life
over 10,000 sister showed up for the
meeting greet it was insane and then we
had February which I feel like was a
really really good month of YouTube
content we had a lot of really good
clubs and interview with jenna Marbles
the flog squad one also the house tour
with mr. King which was one of my
favorite products that I've ever worked
on we also had the Valentine's Day a
single look which of course segue to
2020 single unfortunately for me but who
knows and then I also attended the Bratz
challenge in 2019 which was my favorite
YouTube challenges probably ever the
makeup books that came out of that were
crazy while we talk about March I'm just
going to skip my face using the laura
mercier translucent setting powder
marked was actually another really
amazing month when it came to a content
on the channel
I got to put my linguistic skills to the
test for the makeup tutorial in espanol
which was so much fun and we actually
found out a few weeks ago in the YouTube
rewind that that video was the number
one most liked beauty video of 2019
which is ridiculous to think about
considering the amount of beauty content
that was released this year by -
nonetheless I am so grateful for and I'm
still though that you guys loved it to
contour gonna grab my Anasazi contour
palette and Maya morphe m 405 brush to
chisel out my face while I talk about
the
month which is April we started off the
month by doing something actually I'm
really fond up with the fenomena Buick
Fashion Show that is paired with one of
the designers from the Fidelma program
anyway we have custom up and I got to
walk down the runway which was such a
cool experience one I got to learn a lot
more about being a runway model which I
read had a lot of respect for models to
begin with but after actually doing it
it's very very challenging I will say -
I got to be a model for an amazing
designer Danny 3 a lot of my friends
were involved which made it even more
fun drew Laura and Nikita also walked
the runway in a beautiful outfit and for
your girl needed some redemption because
my laughs oh my walk that walk oh my
goodness it was diabolical
also April is always my favorite event
of the entire year which is Coachella
now I'm not gonna go into too much
detail about this for very obvious
bittersweet reasons but on a positive
note I've had to see ariana grande and
black pink and Billy Eilish all her fur
alive and they are three of my favorite
artists of all times that was so much
fun I got to hang out all my best
friends and my outputs were sickening oh
my god they caused quite a ruckus and
stir on social media I will say it but
honestly I was kind of the point of them
my bunch looked phenomenal I just had
like the best time running around the
festival my literal butt cheeks hanging
out it's crazy that is to say I just
felt so confident and so free and I
think that's honestly the point of
Coachella as a whole so I'm very excited
to see what this year's outfits have to
offer now the next month of the year is
May and obviously we know the two things
that happen at that month first being at
the Met Gala I got to work with
Alexander Wang who's with me
they were designers of all time for my
safety pen top and I just felt so cool
being there but also just like so
nervous and overwhelmed as well because
that was one of the first times that
they ever had youtubers at an event like
that which was obviously a major
breakthrough and like the social media
space I was there without Lilly Singh
and Liza Koshi who I have so much
respect for it's not even funny the
onset of the Met Gala in May of course
we all know I also had my birthday
taking a super quick pause from the
recap I just wanna quickly show you guys
saying that I've been doing a lot
recently during my nose at contour stop
just cover a little bit of concealer on
the back of my hand and a fluffy a dense
brush I'm just going to pop this
concealer into my eyelid and then just
really quickly set that into a place my
contouring process on my face in my nose
is pretty much the exact same which is
why I skipped through it because you
guys said to me do it literally a
million times but there is one thing
that I do a little bit differently so
I'm gonna take my fluffy blending
I'd give it to my same kind of like
bronzy contouring shade and then I like
to take this fluffy brush and at the top
of my nose contour okay I'm not talking
about like the skinny horse because we
still wanted to be very very sad but in
this lake
kind of round area in between the nose
and your eyebrow who was going to run
this color right up into here blending
it into the front of the eyebrow but I'm
also going to take the excess of that
color and blend it through the crease
and then pull it up towards my temple as
you can see between this eyelid and this
eyelid there is a noticeable difference
this one has a little bit more shadow in
here and with this kind of like lion
flagging up and out like that I just
kind of like pulls the eye upwards for
is this eye is just completely flat so I
think it just adds a really nice
definition into the eyelid it pulls
everything up nicely and it gives the
nose contour sling to kind of blend into
instead of just doing like two Brown
lines on the side of your nose
definitely recommend trying this out if
you guys have never before before I move
on to the brows in the eyes I do want to
add a little bit of dimension into the
face so I'm just gonna grab this pinky
tone up blush from Mac eye for the
longest time hated pinky tone blushes
but I've really been liking it more
pinky tone blushes recently I believe
they look very very useful and cute
stepping back into my Anasazi contour
palette with my this brush I'm just
gonna dip into the lighter shade and use
this to highlight underneath my eyes so
the next month was Jude which was
honestly a pretty quiet month for me but
I wouldn't have wanted it any other way
it was a much-needed time of healing
positivity and just relaxation and being
around the people that I love the most
and doing the things that I love the
most so I didn't do a whole lot but it
did end up with a really really positive
no which I'm gonna talk about while I do
my eyebrows starting off I got to sing
at the national anthem with to my best
friends Zoe and Anthony at a charity
basketball game at the Staples Center
which was I don't even know the words
that I have to explain how incredible
that opportunity was
[Applause]
and it was just exactly what I needed
and during that time so that was saying
that I'm really really grateful for and
then literally a from that game we drove
directly to the airport and then flew to
in New York on a red-eye because the
next day I was walking in the Pride
Parade with The Trevor Project it's
really crazy to think about because I've
been out as a gay man since I was 12
years old which is almost half of my
life and I grew up in New York and then
moved to LA three years ago which are
two of the most accepting places like
literally in the entire world but for
some reason I was never able to attend
any pride events there was always
something on my calendar going on where
I couldn't go so this is my first Pride
ever but it was so much fun oh my god it
just really made me so grateful and
proud to be part of my community and I
am very much looking forward to making
sure my calendar is cleared for future
pride events all right you guys I just
do in doing so I can focus on the eyes
super quickly like I said we are not
doing any eyeshadow with this look but I
do want to pop on it just a slight
little wing just to kind of a further
pull up the faith and essentially
everything is so what I'm gonna do first
is grab my morphe MFI hold a brush and
just dip back into my contour palette
from before and tip into the darkest
brown shade in the corner and just gonna
create a little wing at the outer corner
of my eye using this color it's looking
that looks really bad because we're
gonna blow into that in a second anyway
but I'm basically just topping this
shade and the shapeable wing now with
that same broad brush from before and
that same brow powder actually I'm just
going to dip back into that dark brown
shade and I'm gonna use this color and
be it much more careful and go right up
against the lash line and create a
little bit more of a defined way I
really like using the brow powder for
this because it has pigment to it but
it's not like a super super opaque
eyeshadow so you actually have time to
layer up a little bit another trick that
I've been doing a lot recently is taking
that same a brow powder and that angled
brush and creating a very tiny line at
the inner corner point of my eye
pulling the upwards following the shape
of Lian natural lid and as you can see
this just elongate my eyes a little bit
and really furthers that like I thought
and the loss of that is just gonna be
grabbing a little bit more of my amound
ation on a little brush and I'm just
going to clean up the bottom of that
wing for a super sharp
July for me was actually a pretty good
month not a whole lot happened to be
quite honest it was the middle of summer
and we were honestly just going to have
a good time but it was gonna like to
start to me getting back into like my
normal day-to-day routine again which
was pretty awesome this summer because
of pewdiepie making a bunch of Minecraft
videos the Minecraft community on
YouTube really like skyrocketed once
again and kind of revived the game which
was a really amazing for me because
despite the fact that I love makeup I
actually speak you Jay more as a kid
which a lot of you guys know about
minecraft was a huge huge hobby of mine
and growing up especially the Hunger
Games so when the Minecraft Monday's
tournament was announced I was all-in
and so excited to get to play it was a
really cool thing for me to be part of
it I'm honestly so grateful for the
experience and I was so pleasantly
surprised by how nice and how kind and
how welcoming and how funny everyone in
the gaming world was when it came to me
playing in the tournament I just had the
best time I looked forward to it every
single week I'm so sad that it ended I
genuinely missed the community that we
built up but if it ever comes back y'all
know that I'll be ready to slay and who
knows maybe in 2020 I'll sort of gaming
channel probably not but let me know if
you guys want to see more of that
content now next comes August and during
this month I mean probably one of the
biggest mistakes of my entire year which
was please shank my head it obviously
made for a very very ending YouTube
video one of the funniest I think we've
ever posted I loved the way that I
looked with platinum hair the after
effects are Berber not so great because
after a few months it started to get
really damaged and I tried to bleed to
intone it I think one too many times and
then eventually one morning I took a
shower and went to wash my hair and
realized that my hair that was falling
out of my head so that was a really
really unfortunate discovery that I have
now been dealing with the repercussions
of ever since but it's been about three
months now of hair regrowth and
obviously I'm dr. Brown I'm feeling way
better and much more confident now but
unless I'm wearing a wig I will probably
have brown hair for majority of 2020
letting you guys know right now also for
lashes today I just popped on a pair of
Lily lashes and the style Miami flares
you can use coach James for 15% off of
those lashes Lily or if anybody from
your team is watching this please help
me a full box of these desperately need
them like a look at how pretty that is
hello
alright you guys those are both eyes all
complete and we were almost another
makeup routine I'm just gonna go ahead
my mom any excess powder that we have
left on the face while we finish up the
rest of the year September was quite a
jam-packed moment it started off with
learning how to dance with Abby Lee
Miller or at least trying 200mw Lee
Miller I also got the opportunity to go
back to New York for a fashion week in
September which was so much fun I am
very much looking forward to doing more
fashion related things and trying to up
my style in 2020 at the end of September
I finally got to meet my new best friend
for a light and that is when we adopted
our Golden Retriever puppy which we
named Finnegan
I haven't thinking about adopting a
puppy since I moved into this new house
which is over a year ago now but it's a
temper at the time I finally felt right
we weren't traveling we were home and I
was finally kind of getting everything
back together during the month of
September I was obviously still posting
YouTube videos and Instagram photos and
stuff and try my best to put on a smile
for the camera because I would be
completely lying if I said that I was
happy during that month because I was
not at all and I was still really trying
hard to just get everything back
together working with mental health and
obviously Finnegan doesn't know this but
he helped me is so much during that time
period just having somebody an animal to
hog in to cuddle with at night and just
working on training him and welcoming
into the home it made me so much happier
and really helped my mood and just
seeing how he's crawling so much over
the past days I forgot his huge now has
just been a major major light in my life
when I really needed most so yeah he's
like I said my new best friend and I'm
so was so glad that we finally finally
made the move and adopted him because
it's been like the best decision that
I've ever ever made whoo next up as we
all know comes October which is that
spooky season of my favorite time of the
entire year that we started out this
month with quite a bang with the James
house ex Murphy at mini how much which I
just used my hair in a blush like I said
in there until they do this was not
supposed to be anything crazy or
groundbreaking for 2019 in the makeup
community this is truly for the hardcore
fans the lovers of the original palette
they wanted something more small and
travel friendly and I think we
definitely delivered that along with an
incredible campaign that I got to work
with the wigs and makeup my other job
November was honestly a really really
fun month as well I got to go to Las
Vegas Nevada for an Ulta ex Murphy meet
and greet which was so much fun I will
forever remember that me in Greek
because of how nice every single person
that I met was the time flew by so fast
as I was generally just styling and the
entire time I also went back home to
upstate New York for at Thanksgiving
which was an experience and a half to
say at the least we also launched the
sisters apparel holiday collection which
really amazing and I'm so grateful for
your guys to support odd and then
finally we ended off the month with an
announcement that I've been waiting
three years to make and that was that I
got the opportunity to produce my very
own reality competition show on one set
of YouTube for the beauty community now
we've been working on it since that
announcement non-stop and the filming
actually starts in a few weeks from now
which is huh so what I would think about
there are still so many things to get
done so I've been scrambling behind the
scenes to work on everything but it's
been such a fun and incredible process
and I know that you guys are going to
absolutely love it and it's gonna be
something so positive for 2020 which is
the exact vibes that we're going for
we're putting out into the universe it's
gonna be amazing so I hope that you guys
are excited just as much as I am and
finally December was a month for you
guys we started off by going to
Nashville Tennessee from Norfolk meeting
Green I also got to do with my favorite
things that I've ever done as an
influencer which is hostess sisters at
Christmas party we rented out a house
here in LA and invited a 25 of you guys
to come celebrate the holidays we made
gingerbread houses together we
celebrated we ain't amazing food and we
finished off the month of course of the
holiday season
I spent my Christmas with my closest
friends and family to eat absolutely
nothing and I wouldn't have wanted it
any other way super quick signed up
speaking of the palette from earlier I
just want to say a quick thank you to
every single person that we photos of
you guys opening up either the mini
palette or the original on Christmas
morning it made me smile and cry all day
long and I'm just getting teary-eyed
thinking about it right now
but over a year after the original
palette released you guys are still
asking for and are still excited to see
under the tree and I just wanted to
bring them up because it really made me
smile
anyway after Christmas of course comes
in New Year's and now we are here in the
year of 2020 2019 was a really large
year for me and although it was filled
with a lot of ups and a really really
big down I am very grateful to be here
and to still be alive and like I said
the past few weeks have been some of the
happiest that I've been so long that
just feels really really really good to
be able to sit on camera and say it with
confidence and to not be lying and
smiling just to keep the show going I am
so excited for this year that things
that I have coming and the friends that
they have rally right now and the
projects that we're working on this is
so ugly the vibes in general it's
already been amazing despite the fact
that Charles is over produce checking on
the
say of the year and I'm just so grateful
to have all of you guys by my side for
another amazing year it's going to be
good the vibes are already positive and
I really hope that you guys had it Jesus
Christ James like yeah the final step of
this makeup routine is crying it really
helps lock everything into place I'm
just really grateful I'm grateful to be
here I'm grateful for you guys it's
gonna be the amazing year and I'm so
excited to spend with every single one
of you guys the toppings that I'm gonna
set my face the place that before I
start crying anymore this makeup video
has been quite enough I really really
hope you guys know this video I had so
much fun filming and I'm obsessed and
how this luck turned out like I said
this has been like my go-to every day at
makeup glam recently I have been using a
lot of new products a lot of new
techniques but honestly this look has
been making me feel so beautiful so
confident and so snatched I really hope
you guys enjoyed this video at the recap
and also learning about my new updated
makeup routine this look makes me feel
so confident and just so like beautiful
and natural despite the fact that I have
a lot of makeup on I really like this
and I really hope you guys picked up
some new techniques as well if you did
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and show your love and
support it really does help me out and
mean so so so much to me and also leave
me a comment down below and let me know
what your new year's resolution is I
feel like it'll be really cool to learn
about what you guys want to do this here
I have a lot of things that I'm gonna
work on that maybe I'll share with you
later on but yeah looking forward to
reading them and also make sure you
click the big red subscribe button and
come join this sisterhood I would love
to have you in the family so you could
be a part of all the new exciting things
that we have coming up this year click
that button and also click that Bell
icon so you'll get notifications every
time I upload a brand new video if you
like to follow me on my makeup turn you
can follow me on Instagram or Twitter
Facebook and tik-tok we're all just
James Charles and their snapchat for
behind it seems like it's James Charles
an extra ask after Charles if you like
the mirror that I was using in this
video or if you want to check out any
other sisters items make sure you guys
go to sisters - apparel dot-com to shop
all your sisters and gear and merch this
videos sister shout out the first of
2028 goes to sister Seth thank you so
much love for always the following in
support you know I love you literally is
so so so much and if you at home watch
your like to be the next videos sister
shout out don't forget to always reach
we could really go live on Twitter and
also to them on YouTube at post
notifications all right you guys that is
all I have for today for any video thank
you so much for watching I love you so
much I'll see you in the next one bye
[Music]