hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video we're doing something that
you guys have been at literally begging
for it requesting for a comforting about
four years now and that is the zodiac
makeup challenge now I have not been
ignoring you I am actually been putting
this video on and I'm going to tell you
why please don't kill me in the comments
but I don't exactly believe in astrology
I know okay I might be probably the only
person in all of Los Angeles California
that does not believe in this I don't
really believe and like anything and I
feel like basing life decisions on stars
that sky is a little bit weird but a few
weeks ago I was talking to my good
friend at noir Vina who's the president
and creative director of Anasazi Beverly
Hills and she was telling me how I am
like the most Gemini Gemini she's ever
met
and this really sparked my brain because
I had no idea what any of that meant
so I called my mom I asked my birth
certificate and the time and location of
my birth I put it in at the co star app
and then sort of doing a whole lot of
research and I will admit to you live on
camera right now that I was shook
because some of the things in my
horoscope were extremely accurate to
what I'm actually feeling and going
through in my life so for today's video
I thought it'd be super fun to sit down
play what's the makeup of course we did
some research I'm about to find out how
being a Gemini affects my relationships
my friendships my communication skills
my artistry and a personality my
business and literally everything else
and maybe by the end of this video I'll
be a believer in astrology
let's get started
[Music]
alright you guys jumping right into this
as you can see I actually already have a
full face to makeup on
don't worry that's about to change very
very quickly like I said I am NOT very
educated on astrology or being a Gemini
at all but the one stereotype that I
have heard a million different times is
that Gemini's are two-faced personally
okay I feel like I am NOT two-faced if I
love you I love you and you're gonna
know and if I don't like you I am NOT
that a person to go out of my way to
fake it like people also definitely know
we're gonna learn more about this in the
video setting to see how this actually
like affects our decisions as Gemini's
but I do have a super cool idea for this
make a book tonight and that is going to
be representing at the two different
ways that you guys see me as an
influencer on 1/2 my face I'm gonna keep
it natural and this look that I have on
right now and that is kind of like my
day to day it go to glam it's almost
like my off-camera look that you guys
don't always get to see whereas on this
side I really want to represent my
youtube personality the over-the-top
kind of like on brand James Charles that
you guys all know and love colorful
bright unapologetic but overall just
confidence on this side so let's go
ahead and jump in alright so as I take
off this side of my face Luis is going
to read me of my daily horoscopes today
ready to receive your blessings you
might be disappointed by the way your
surroundings react to new things coming
your way
self-awareness is the key to
understanding any relationship issues
these days is bad some tea instead of
thinking about ways of others think
about your own decisions and choices
that legend here and think about the
change you wish to make to your own
so this is really saying think about how
my own actions are affecting it
situations rather than how others are
affecting situations mm-hmm see this
it's like things like this that makes me
a little skeptical about this because
like that was the most general statement
ever like Oh think about yourself anyway
okay I mean I think I think a lot about
myself I do always love a bit this
makeup look today at by the way is going
to be inspired by a Taylor Graham MUA on
Twitter and since we're gonna be talking
I want to tell you guys I'm gonna be
using the morphe 35o icy fantasy palette
this is their new pastel collaboration
with pony it is so beautiful and you can
use code aims for 10% off just draw
great strength gentle gentle
[Music]
I definitely feel like I'm extremely
adaptable like you can put me in any new
environment or any situation and I will
always try my best to succeed I wouldn't
say however that I am very gentle I
guess it does depend on the situation
though on who I'm talking to like with
my friends and the ones that I love I'm
not very gentle but that's always like
out of tough love and like wanting
everybody around me to be the best
versions of themselves but I will say I
am good at giving advice and like
helping other people out and in those
situations I mean one more time tall
okay so now if this is says you're
nervous
oh I strongly disagree with that
inconsistent disagree indecisive
oh that's too nervous I do not think I'm
nervous at all I do not get nervous
rarely ever I do that's a recent thing
though yeah but overall I would not say
that I'm a nervous person I don't think
that's the case
oops then it's a little blurb about when
you like it dislike you like music books
magazine and chiming with anybody and
short trips around town that is so
accurate it's not even funny that is so
that is T Gemini dislikes being alone
being young repetition and y'all team
huh that's T I hate being alone
literally that's what Lewis loves of me
I always have friends over every single
day I always have to film with somebody
in the room I love having people over
I hate repetition I literally get so
bored doing the same thing I always have
to be doing something new let's keep
going this is fine that have strong
opinions and personalities and they
often need to be the center of attention
they are a highly versatile love a good
argument but will often butt heads with
those who opinions differ from their own
it takes a lot to hold a Gemini's
attention span though once they find
their passion they go in all the way
Gemini is the sign of kindred spirit
energy
Gemini loves a dynamic duo and is always
seeking their other oh my god they that
is a full entire that is a whole entire
Drive I mean it's true literally like I
like I said I do enjoy company I love
being around my friends and I also
really what am I not Gemini's are
changeable and open mind that makes them
excellent artists especially writers and
journalists and their skills and
flexibility makes them shine and trade
driving and team sports driving try
Meghan oh that's a lie
team sports well I definitely am not
good at sports but when it comes to team
activities I definitely am a team player
I love a good healthy competition so
although I might not be the strongest
player on the team I will be a motivated
player on the team which is equally as
important Tara versatile
yep I'm loving side born
wish to experience everything there is
out there you know it makes their
character inspiring and never bored oh
that's like this is like very accurate
let's go like more in-depth Oh God
unless it's good Oprah with fun and
always ready for an intellectual
challenge
Gemini's see love first through
communication and verbal contact and
yeah as important as physical contact
yeah partner oh but go to yes when these
two combine obstacles all seem to fail
they are always ready to flirt a Gemini
go spend a lot of time with different
lovers until they find the right one who
is able to match their energy uh-huh and
when they find the right person a lover
a friend and someone to talk to combined
in one it will be faithful and
determined to always treasure their
heart I that is literally me like that's
me the paragraph I value communication
more than anything there was one guy
that I talked to and I'm not gonna go
into specifics because he's a very nice
person
but I was talking to you for a good
moment he was like 6-3 so insanely ha
beautiful face beautiful body really
really great outgoing personality I
truly thought that I was going to be
with him for a hot minute but
unfortunately when he flew home the
communication like completely dropped
out of the window and it went from like
talking every single day and spending a
week together to literally waiting 10
hours for a text message reply and I
tried to fix it and I tried to fix it
and I tried to fix it but I ultimately
realized that I could not change how a
person thinks or how they communicates
and that relationship really made me
realize that I value communication and
openness and honesty it's so incredibly
much the biggest challenge for any
Gemini's love life is to find an emotion
that lacks especially as they get older
and realize they are already in a
repetitive mode of superficial and
disappointing bonds their personality
doesn't allow much depth before they are
on a mission to spread information not
to dig into them and find mistakes holes
or resolutions they look at life from a
relative perspective of you
being the one to circle the Sun moving
forwards and backwards from earth one of
you never certain of their own direction
the one thing I really made sense with
their personality doesn't allow much
depth I don't think it's your
personality but just situation you're
right there's it's not your personality
because I do have a lot to me but I
don't think I like talking about it much
I'm not a very like vulnerable person I
don't like going to in debt they're
talking about my shark those are my
feelings my situation and my career does
make it very difficult for me to kind of
get in depth in relationships and
unfortunately I've had far more bad
experiences with people that weren't
talking to me for the right intentions
then good so it is kind of like made me
build up my wall even higher they tend
to make a gazillion friends people
information so Gemini's like to procure
a large garden of contacts Lincoln
called on that said the emotional
requirements of maintaining
relationships and swiftly overwhelm them
and then honestly they just cut out the
dead boy away so true
I love talking to people I love making
new friends I'm a very very social
person but there's a lot of people that
I have to keep up with on a daily basis
in terms of my best friends my team that
I work with a different business
contacts that were currently working on
projects but sometimes I do tend to
overlook other conversations like there
have been definitely times where friends
from my old high school or friends that
I was with when I like first started
social media that will come to me like
well I feel like you really forgot about
me and it sucks to hear that because
that was never the intention but it just
kind of does for me happen naturally
because I move on very very quickly and
just like start new friendships that
socks that is definitely true though all
right let's do a little bit of career in
constantly of intellectual stimulation
this is just like literally reading
fulfill the most suitable job for a
Gemini has to be challenging to their
brain there are skillful inventive and
often very smart with a need for a
dynamic working environment and lots of
social contacts I met in the office oh
my god it's a so little bit real of like
come on if they were created for
multitasking problem-solving and
bringing new ideas
to life they need a workplace yeah I
mean that's like hit that hit the hammer
hurt Vinay I think that hits the nail on
the head I do this job because I like
being mentally stimulated I've talked
about this a million different times and
I'm my own boss which is the blessing
and that way I get to make sure that I
am NOT on a routine thing every single
day wow this is crazy
it says that mercury is a planet which
is associated with speed and geminis
think fast
eat fast move fast and talk to us oh
yeah they change their mind fast so much
so that they can even meet themselves
coming back around the other way this
can make them seem erratic because they
don't stick to their opinions or
commitments Wow the speed thing I mean
yeah let's be real I literally am the
fastest talker probably on YouTube aside
from Trisha Paytas or Joe Joey well what
should be a competition one day I'm up
Donny see what the cool people I will
say that I have somebody who sticks by
my opinions if I have an opinion I am
pretty out of it on it unless I
presented with good information and
reasoning to switch that Gemini man is
enthusiastic and full of life never
disappointing with dull moments he is
adventurous humorous and this makes him
the perfect partner if a person is
energetic and dynamic and search for
some laughter and
yeah Joe my men are naturally chatty and
flirtatious and you can meet them at
public gatherings conferences and
traffic jams that's a weird thing to say
you will never catch a traffic jam
because I will not be in a car this man
is impossible to cling to and need a
partner who gives him enough freedom and
space followed by mental stimulation of
variety yeah that's definitely that's a
I cannot deal with clinginess I hate
clinginess I don't like flirting to
begin with I like doing the flirting I
like a man who's like gonna bully me a
little bit like a morning gonna like not
like I'm learning pumpkin pie I like
your style shining so bright today I
wonder what could be causing that okay
for our last hopper we're talking about
the future right
Oh God until December 18 2020
why is this looks specific what's gonna
happen on that day oh gosh okay there
continues to be a wonderful refreshing
focus on your private world for intimate
life a possible deepening of a
relationship or an increased
understanding of your inner workings a
boost in your relationship with yourself
your intimate life enlarges and expands
bringing you more joy and your
discoveries I am definitely a man this
year it's in the stars written in the
stop during this cycle you learn to
embrace interchange in order to feel
more empowered there may be more
opportunities to find support financial
and/or emotional but you should be wary
of living on credit and borrowing too
heavily for the future during this
year-long transit it is time to grab
opportunities that help you feel
empowered and on top of your life
otherwise it's a strong period for
opening yourself up to others
you're not confident about your
emotional depths this is a period when
you can quite successfully purge
yourself of some of your inner demons
guilt and buried psychological problems
while there can be some reality checks
at times it's powerful time for
psychological oh oh my god so that's a
really good thing is coming a lot of
self-reflection I've already done a lot
of that so I am a clean a self
reflection at this point its tingly 2020
is gonna be a really good year for us
that's a really good way to end off this
zodiac video all right you guys well I
think that is this Gemini two-faced look
all complete I had it so much fun doing
the zodiac makeup challenge today I went
into this not believing in astrology
literally in any way shape or form but
coming out of this challenge today after
being a ride for fill in the best way
possible I feel like I might be a
believer and I definitely want to learn
a whole lot more don't worry I'm not
gonna start basing all my life decision
on stars I am very much a believer in
living in the moment but after this my
eyes have definitely been open to a
whole new world if you enjoyed this
video today please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and also
if you guys wanna try out this zodiac
makeup challenge definitely tag me I
would love to see what looks you guys
come up with inspired by your zodiac
signs are you believer do you like this
step or were you like me beforehand
where you don't believe in any of it
leave me a comment down below and let me
know if you have not already make sure
you click that bicker at this good
button and come join this sisterhood I
would love to have you in the family and
also collect that belt like on so you'll
be notified each and every time I upload
a brand new video if you like to follow
me on my makeup tourney can follow me
Instagram Twitter tik-tok and Facebook
all just Charles and my snapchat more by
the teen sex happens James Charles the
next ask after Charles this video is
sisters how that goes to its sister
daddy
thank you so much love for always
falling in supporting I love you so so
so much and if you at home would like to
be the next videos sister shut up don't
forget to always reach meet web videos
and they go live on Twitter and all
sorts it on my youtube at post
notifications
I'll write you guys thank you so much
for watching this video today I love you
and your horoscope says that you will
see me in the next line
[Music]