hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel a few
weeks ago if you guys are familiar with
the tech world apple held their annual
event where basically every year they
announce their new
products their new way of how they're
all going to get us to spend thousands
and thousands of dollars
should i say that it's not funny should
i say that
every year there's always a new iphone
this year however they did not announce
that which honestly i'm a little bit
annoyed about but what did launch
is ios 14 and oh my god i think it's
been a pretty long time since any of the
apple updates really caused like an
excitement or like a splash
in society but i will say apple really
did sister snap with ios 14 because
there are so many really
really cool exciting features that i
have been loving so far especially
the ability to customize your home
screen i've already seen
so many people across all different
social media platforms posting
screenshots
and getting creative with their home
screens now mine still looks really
really boring i will show you guys it's
literally just my regular apps and i
added a fun little calendar widget so i
can see what's going with my day and i
really want to figure out how i can
customize my own home screen
but until then i thought it'd be so much
fun to sit down take a look at what you
guys have created and do
my makeup inspired by your ios 14
home screen
okay you guys i'm super excited to get
started and just sit down and play with
makeup today i tweeted earlier asking
you to send me screenshots of your ios
14 home screens and i am
so jealous of how some of them are
looking so far and the first home screen
that i want to show you guys is from
chloe and hers looks like
this looking at chloe's home screen i'm
definitely noticing a few things right
off the bat it is very cute it's very
bright and it's also very
soft which is definitely giving me a lot
of inspiration for a fun makeup look to
combine all these elements in her
background she has these orange
butterflies and there's a user on
twitter that i follow named lauren her
at is raggedy royal
she had this whole like butterfly eye
look trend which could be really really
fun to do and
all of her app icons are pink and
glittery which i normally
don't love her makeup looks you guys
have heard me talk about this but i feel
like i have a really good idea of how i
could pull
all these elements into a fun look so
let's go ahead and see what we can come
up with
okay you guys so for the first step as
always i'm just going to grab a little
bit of concealer and put this on my
eyelid to act as my
rhymer and then we're just going to go
right in with our shadows so i think i'm
going to start
first by grabbing actually let me not
use my palette for once i'm going to
grab the
perfect cosmetics like stacy marie
carnival palette and i'm going to dip
into this shade up here called
slow burn it's just a really pretty like
burnt orange color and i'm going to
pack this in the outer corner now that
that's laid down i'm just going to grab
a little fluffy brush
and dip into honestly maybe a little bit
of a 518 and just blend that out if i
was gonna do this look myself i would
honestly probably start off with a much
darker color just because i really like
high contrast but chloe's home screen is
so
soft that i honestly feel like this will
be perfect i really want to match
chloe's muted pink tones as much as i
possibly can
so i'm gonna grab the shade mary from my
palette on an m456 and use this color
to further like the crease
[Music]
um just put this here and i'm gonna grab
some pinkity
drinkity just on a fluffy brush and
blend out that
mary and i'm just gonna use a little
flat top concealer brush and some more
concealer to cut
my crease now i'm just gonna grab a
little bit of sister which is like the
metallic
champagne shade i'm just gonna pack this
right onto
the lid i'm also gonna use the shade to
highlight the inner corner as well
why does this look so patchy down here
it's a pumpkin patch
yeah what is going on i guess it won't
really matter to be honest because it'll
be covered in
a butterfly anyway there we go that's
the shape that i'm going for
okay now i'm gonna apply some nice
glitter adhesive oh god i
hate hate using glitter it's just gross
like once you put on glitter you're
stuck with it for the next
roughly three to four business days okay
so just mark
a general note that i'm noticing i'm
just not feeling a lot of enthusiasm as
i'm looking at the screen so i think
that might read across
the audience are you still filming yes
and that looks okay okay so now that the
overall shapes and glitter are all on
there it is time to add our butterfly
design so it's going to take my nice
liquid liner and i'm going to just do a
regular
wing okay now i'm just going to draw a
gigantic wing basically
and i'm just going to add in the little
lines okay so now the same thing on the
little
lower wing situation okay and now the
last step of this
butterfly eye is just take a little bit
of white eyeliner
and add in the dots oh hey
oh no hey oh he just peed
like the most p i've ever actually seen
great
mascara time all right you guys so this
is one eye of this look all complete i'm
gonna cut into the other one off camera
quickly and i'll be right back with the
finished
look i matched the other eye off camera
added a ton
of this beautiful baby pink blush some
pink highlighter and just did a cute
little ombre glossy lip and i think that
is this
soft pink butterfly look inspired by
chloe's home screen
all complete i really love how this look
turned out today the soft orange and
pink tones work so beautifully together
and remind me so much of the fall season
coming soon and even though the
butterflies on the eye
do look like a really really vibrant
statement piece they were actually
really really easy to do and i think
this look was super
super cool thank you once again to chloe
for suggesting it to me and i think it
is now time to move on to
the next one yo yo
this one that i have picked out is by
leah sencore
and she sent me these screenshots of her
phone now as you guys can see it's very
like purple very periwinkle which is by
far my favorite color in the entire
world
and it's very just like common calming
yes is it weird to say like this would
remind me of like that lavender like
pillow spray that would like put you to
sleep relaxation
calming down ending off the day on a
positive
beautiful note vibes
sure i don't do makeup looks with this
color very often so i'm definitely
excited for this and as you guys can see
on her little
widget smith app she has it's like this
very like purpley pinky
sky with little planets and stars like
drawn in as a cartoon over top which i
think is so
so cute so i'm going to use that as my
source of inspiration for this makeup
look today
as always i'm just going to take a
little bit of my concealer and use it as
my eye
shadow base that i am using a really
light shade this time just because
since we're working with pastels we want
them to really pop
first i'm just going to grab a little
fluffy brush and just use some different
shades of purple
uh maybe a little bit of single which i
still
am it's the subtle depression yeah i'm
not having a good day today you guys
i'm single just really really single
today
now i'm just going to take my morphe 35i
palette and dip into the nice
pastel purple shade i love love love
this color eyeshadow now i'm going to
take this nice pastel pink and really
just
you know plop this in there warm it up
and give some
pink clouds that looks like [ __ ] okay
now i'm just gonna take a little bit of
white
i mean that looks like [ __ ] wow you can
really tell that i'm not having a good
day huh oh my god
oh sorry guys not every day can be a
good one
now i'm just gonna start drawing in some
nice planets that's
saturn
shall we cut or just keep rolling no
let's just keep rolling
who knows maybe something great will
come out of this tell us
really shitty it just seems like every
time that i find somebody great
it's like three seconds later they're
not but it's also like
if it's not gonna work it's not gonna
work i mean i think by constantly saying
that at least
forever and all that you put that out
there that's what comes back to you
i know it's just really hard to think
otherwise with all this like stupid [ __ ]
that i've
dealt with to finish off the eyes i'm
just going to apply a little coat of
mascara since we did the white liner and
then also all the little white drawings
i honestly don't want to do a full lash
because this is going to cover up all
the work that we just did
for my lips today of course i'm going to
match it right to it the eye so i'm
going to grab the ofra las vegas
liquid lipstick all right you guys will
know that the lips are all on and
matching the eyes very very perfectly
i think that completes this pastel skies
look inspired by leah's ios 14 home
screen
honestly this might be one of the first
times while doing these like recreating
art videos that i haven't been in love
with the final
look usually i'm like obsessed with them
but honestly this time i don't really
know
leah's home screen in the color scheme
is so so cute and i feel like i had a
really good vision for this look in my
head but i honestly just feel like i
didn't do the best job executing it i
think the colors are really cute i think
like the white liner idea
was really really cute as well but i
just feel like this could have been a
lot better but i don't really know what
i would have done
to change it i would love to see how you
would recreate this and hopefully do it
a whole lot better than mine
it's a cute idea so regardless i hope
you guys enjoyed this look and now it is
time to wipe it off and move on to
the next one okay so when i tweeted it
so when i tweeted you guys asking to
send me photos of your home screens
there was a million different themes and
aesthetics
but i did notice that there was one
style in particular that a ton of
different people were using
and that was neon icons i picked out
this photo from autumn
diane as you guys can see she has a very
like billy eilish green
and black neon inspired lock screen
which i think looks super
super cool so i thought that this would
be a really fun trend to pull into
a makeup look basically what i'm
envisioning for this look today is a
graphic liner that looks like it's like
a neon
light against like a black backdrop
normally i would lay down the black
first but i'm definitely concerned about
putting a collar over top of black
whatever let's just try and see what
happens i guess just placing the shadow
in the general area where i want it to
be
obviously we're going to blend that out
but i don't want to go too crazy with
the block just yet because
i mean y'all already know looks like a
like a literal drag queen eyeliner
okay now i'm just taking a little bit
more of that black i'm going to use this
on a fluffy brush to diffuse out these
edges
very very very very carefully put this
on the lower lash line as well
so now basically what i'm going to do is
grab a little bit more of this white
liner you see lots of white liner in
this video i don't know why that ended
up happening that way but
basically i'm just going to grab a
little liner brush and sketch out
like the graphic liner that i want to do
but i'm actually for ones
not going to worry about it being too
precise because we're going to blend it
out and now i'm just going to grab
a little fluffy brush i saw a ton of
people doing a green
nia but i also saw a lot of people doing
blue so maybe i'll actually do like an
ombre of the two colors do you think
that'd be cool yeah i'm just gonna grab
some shadows just like this and i'm
going to pack that
right on top of that white liner just
like this
that looks so cool oh that actually does
look kind of cool
oh period now i'll just switch it over
to a little bit of teal in the middle
i'm just gonna place a little bit of
that green neon shade right in the inner
corner because we'll place a highlighter
there later on so now that we have the
colors kind of messily
placed on there and like i said this
mess kind of was on purpose because this
is basically going to be like the glow
of the neon we don't want this to look
like the actual light just yet that's
going to be what happens right
now with a tiny little liner brush and a
little bit more white liner i'm going to
go in with a
second layer in that same general shape
but this time i'm going to be much more
precise
with my line oh i definitely want to add
in that color to my
lash line oh my kind of fun wow that
actually turned out really good
we love her off the juice cody guppy
tripping
all right you guys well that was fast i
think that is one eye of this neon look
all complete i was definitely worried
about this technique at first but i
think that i got it down
pretty fast and i am loving how this is
looking at so far i'm gonna go ahead
i'm gonna go ahead and do the other one
off camera quickly and i'll be right
back with the finished
look okay you guys the lips are on and i
think that they added such a cool like
punk vibe to this makeup look and i
think that is this neon look inspired by
diane's home screen all complete when i
first saw people using neon icons in
their home screen
right away i knew the makeup look that i
wanted to create and spoiler alert it
was
this one but i wasn't sure how i was
actually going to achieve that just
because sometimes layering on a bright
colors over top of black is like
literally impossible
but i think that we nailed the technique
and this looks so so
so cool i've seen a lot of people do
this neon liner before so i'm absolutely
not taking credit but i would love to
see what you guys can come up with after
seeing this technique with all that
being said i have been down in the
studio for hours now voting this video
and i think that it is time to bring
this one to a close i had
so much fun recreating these three very
different makeup looks from these three
very very different ios 14 home screens
and i'm definitely looking forward to
hearing in the comments down below which
look was your favorite and how you've
customized your home screen
if you guys enjoyed this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and show your love
and support
also if you've not already click that
bigger subscribe button to come join the
sisterhood and finally click that bell
icon so you get notified every time i
upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me on my
makeup journey all my social media
accounts are gonna be linked right here
around the screen
and if you wanna text me on my personal
phone number for updates on new videos
photos merge and so much more
my number is
this video sister 310-905-8746 out goes
to sister kevia thank you so much love
for always following and supporting i
love you so so so much and if you would
like to be the next video's sister
shadow don't forget to always retweet my
video links when they go live on
twitter all right you guys thank you so
much for watching this video today i
love you and i will see you in
the next one bye