we made it this is oh
hey yo good morning okay what's popping
you guys it is 5
19 in the 5 20 in the morning right now
just got out of the shower still my
towel actually
and i'm freaking hype dude let's go wake
the boys up lights are going
on good morning brandon
wake up no what the [ __ ] bro
no bro don't make me take my towel off
bro i'll do it
yeah oh he's in my boxes oh god you're
so good i'm vlogging bro
oh what the [ __ ] good morning bro
oh what the [ __ ] wow jesus what do you
what you do go to hawaii bro
what up kong it's a young doggy bro
buddy i found out you can't come to
hawaii because they think you have
diseases or something yeah guys since
hawaii is an island they won't let me
bring kong without paying like ten
thousand dollars
i'm already spending way too much money
on this [ __ ] train okay guys i gotta
keep getting ready
[Applause]
goodbye maverick ayla's gonna take care
of you while i'm going okay
what the [ __ ] i made a mistake hi
there's the real maverick hi buddy hey
how are you
i know ayla's gonna take care of you
while i'm going okay i love you too
going to hawaii going to hawaii
going to hawaii and evan's got a big
dick hey
have you ever even been to hawaii no no
i have one splashback
yeah fun times man anyways we are on our
way to the airport all i gotta say is
are you
good girl bro are you even good bro we
are traveling with other people our
friends sonia and colt
and my cast mate and future ex-wife
chloe bennett but i got one question is
where they at no
where they at bro where are they at bro
where they at bro evan do you see him
bro
i can't see anything whoa mom i can be
here mom
please call somebody
[Music]
what's your magazine what is this
trump's america are you good bro joey
bennett's reading what are you
psychology today the laws of attraction
this is my favorite the crossword
puzzles grandma chloe
in the house everyone where's your seat
chloe
it's like kind of in the back i like to
humble myself i sit in economy right
where were you sitting
economy no she's in first class she got
first class tickets i'm not gonna lie
bro i wish i had a first class to get
what
can i get a picture oh chloe bennett's
right there
bye chloe course you can young lady
what's your name kayla
same in the tunnel i'm going down bro
sorry
everybody you guys don't know what you
signed up for going on a trip with lp
what's
are you in the logang that's my phone go
to give chloe a high five and then just
dab on her so hard
why'd you hit that door why did you hit
him it must be nice being rich chloe man
yo that was sick bro
hell yeah no this is good you're right
there we're right here yo bro this is
the roster brendan evan
cole
[Music]
there he is that's my boy over there
hello oh great guys look it's the wing
if the plane catches on fire i'll be the
first to know can i not say that out
loud not on a plane
okay guys we're about to take off and we
just found out they might not be
shipping our bags
on this plane uh okay it's gonna be
interesting to see how that plays out
also are you good bro okay bro
okay it's definitely not good bro
[Music]
[Applause]
if somebody told me that love wasn't
real
what kind of thing guys so we got about
two hours left
i'm now on evan's lap we're gonna have
some really heavy snuggles these next
two days got this rice krispie treat do
you want it hey that's
that's true also the real reason why i'm
here uh chloe came to visit
how's actually not first class that's
cause we're not there chloe that's when
we're not there
this one should place it down
oh jesus are you good bro why am i still
here i don't know
what are you doing this has been the
most lenient flight ever we've been able
to do anything let's just hope
this airline didn't forget our bags
because they don't have to talk first
steps into hawaii
oh bro where's chloe bennett is that
chloe bennett
sonja
cole mom
how do you feel about the bag situation
if the bags aren't here they're going to
be pissed she hugged her bag before we
left
she said please make it no you did not
no you hugged your bag
i hugged evan and said the same thing
but my boy made it if their bags aren't
here
no literally bro
they're gonna freak out
calm before the storm right all the
dudes are just in a line we're not even
looking for our bags we're just watching
to see if their bags are coming cold
your bag made it yeah
she's more excited to see her bag than
to come to hawaii
oh no i don't think chloe's bag arrived
my bag did not arrive
ah no did your bag arrive no and it has
my dwarf pills in it where's my leg
what the [ __ ] dwarf pills make me stay
in the door
we need the doorbell so this is the
follow camera following chloe bennett
she's looking for her bags right now
she's running now
oh son of a [ __ ] man thanks for that
companionship chloe did anything you
could just buy your own merch
it's true link in description get your
maverick merch what we got boys
no oh man what do we do yo
while we were waiting to get our bags
the girls got some for me chloe chloe
yes chloe lamey let me or like you gonna
get like
let me oh
i appreciate your hard work i'm glad we
all got laid by
chloe bennett
look at this vehicle bro
dang dude what an interesting start to
hawaii no bags it's raining
not enough big enough hungry i'm hungry
i'm hungry
so we get food then and then go to the
house yeah
oh man look at us getting food wow so
cool
okay enough of that
guys we are at the house we spent like
way too much money on this house let's
go check this bad boy out yeah yeah
[Music]
it's a villa it's a villa it's not even
a house
yo this is this is why it's expensive
yeah
yo call me drake
[Music]
i'm not gonna lie there's no ac
bro dude i'm gonna sweat my dick off bro
i asked the guy
i was like you know is there air it was
the air conditioning he goes oh this
house doesn't have any
i'm worried about the girls bro i i know
they're like oh
um good choice logan guys i'm not a [ __ ]
dog
okay i don't know what i'm doing why was
i put in charge of this honest
honest opinion um no air conditioning i
know
we started we spent so much money on
this we're splitting this house it
it's so much fun we were in a hot car so
like like between
logan and chloe like some clogan type
[ __ ] like
would you like are we staying here so
guys obviously this is incredible but
what's better than a pool
a bull with a floatie oh no don't fall
off
bro you're [ __ ] up
bro it's hot outside it's on the house
but as long as we have each other
so we're gonna figure uh this out and
exactly what we're doing
you guys know me when i go on trips or
whatever like they need to be like
top-notch so i have a hawaii expert
coming his name is
his name is sam he's the legend on the
island but yeah
what the [ __ ] are you doing when did you
get there bro
these next four days are gonna be
absolutely crazy man like who knows
i might be like jake paul by the time
i'm done with this video
also i just want to point out uh we
don't even have a bathing suit yet yeah
still going shorts dude what did my boy
want a man
i got you bro just give me one second
count to one and
done that's my boy with that little man
that doesn't feel like a man i suck at
everything dude oh my gosh there's so
many activities we can do here guys we
could sharpen knives
i'm so sick guys you can play
hide-and-go-seek where's evan dude
yeah yeah tell me guys we're gonna eat
later
[Music]
that's mine oh yeah sorry
did you put ice in my butt thank you bro
i don't know if you missed a memo
but the house has no air conditioning so
this feels really refreshing
guys good news our legend is here sam
potter
what's up bro nice to meet you good high
five right now that's a friendship
this is the vlog logan paul club all
right so
the man sam do you have plans for us bro
i got some plans like you got top-notch
plans or like like
pop notch plans first when you get
hydrated son
he's got coconuts what are you doing
i swear to god you're you're the guy in
the movies that every girl
cheats on their husband with that's you
dude before we came to this trip
i was like damn like chloe bennett you
know clogan type thing
i'm kind of falling in love with sam i
think what would it be slogan
slogan slogan what's yours taste like
that sweet [ __ ] are you gonna put that
in there is that going in there yeah
it'll be squeaked i mean
i don't think so no i'm sorry for all
the kids watching my vlogs
i don't say the word often i don't like
it but like he goes was it he just set
me up that was a classic
real good it's not it was my fault yo
sam what's in that tree bro yo what's in
the trees
oh there's a song about this mama say no
play this is a snow day
climb up the tall tree pick that papaya
maybe it's not a song i don't know
[Music]
mama
this is dope papaya
we are about to finish off the night by
going cliff jumping yo yo
let's see what's going on here we got
the classic thing drinking the hand well
you're also carrying chips
you're a walking mess you're a walking
mess wait hold on is this going down
you're riding in here
wait what really oh but if i'm [ __ ]
doing that hell yeah
this is the move bro why he's sick come
on chloe we got places to be and cliffs
that need to be jumped let's go
colt i appreciate his like half
enthusiasm to be in my vlog he at least
made a noise for me
[Music]
oh good fun that's what that was sam is
this spot like
litmus level like what would you say
wow that was hot hi dude okay so just
reading this uh danger sign here what
you need to know before you enter
the first one many people have drawn
here good thing i'm not a people
i'm a vlogger dude you know being from
hollywood you know being an actor
vlogger it's not often you get to
[ __ ] me go outside and go actually
experience nature
again so when i do go i i make sure to
say [ __ ] me as many times as possible
is it over there sam also convenient how
you just popped out of the bushes bro we
made it
this is oh
[Music]
hello gang we made it to the spot as you
can see
hawaii as always looking beautiful the
sun is setting right there
not gonna lie i took some fire pictures
myself my instagram's at logan paul if
you want to follow me there i don't know
what it is
about like views like this maybe it's
maybe it's because i'm around my friends
i'm just in a really just happy relaxed
place right now but you guys know this
about me i work
really really hard no i don't want to
say that i
i do but i enjoy it that's the thing for
me luckily i have found what i love to
do like genuinely love to do and i get
to do it every day and the fact that you
guys
um like it literally means the world to
me i encourage you guys as always to
keep pushing to find
what it is that you love so every day
you can wake up knowing you want to work
hard but you don't have to work
mavericks change the world baby crazy
crazy inspirational anyway
guys that is the vlog if you are not
subscribed make sure to subscribe these
next couple days are gonna be crazy this
landscape is incredible and yeah guys i
will see you tomorrow uh as usual take
it easy if i plop
that was weird
[Music]
you