let's chop of 2005 that's not my cat you
want to say hello to maverick he's my
bird okay to jungle animals meeting for
the first time and they're not so
natural habitat oh you know we got a cat
in our house right now oh hey Judy I got
a cat apparently needs help and Jesus
through things and maverick merch oh
snap oh that reminds me the favorite
hoodie is back bro his back in stock he
farted he farted he smells so bad I told
you it's worse than yours
I know anyways guys the favorite hoodie
is Becca Logan Paul that cop slash opera
link description my shoe we couldn't do
any better
you guys know maverick bottoms dropping
in like two days or so we are about to
change the merch game forever like be
like this isn't even March anymore this
is the pair and you guys haven't even
seen these these are the athletic
version of the Maverick shorts we're
like Joe oh oh good look the point is
it's going down we got everything just
just be ready bro November 1st now in
the meantime let's uh figure out what we
do with this
it's just my shower you know I'm so yeah
I'm not really sure what you're doing in
there
what are you doing what are you trying
to take a bath dude he's athletic I
think he belongs in this bathtub yeah
do want this wrong me love that wrong me
do this I could be dead probably not
might have to stick with karma yeah oh
speaking of there's a cat in the house
you got a new brother it's a bad idea to
introduce them while he's eating raw
meat
he might mistaken for food this is why
we call him calling the Savage this is
crazy this is very dangerous for you
that is a big guy hey you're new to the
house just give us a little sidebar I
love you and I don't want you to die
okay so you put that tongue inside your
mouth there you go and collect yourself
now if you're watching this vlog and
you're a little confused
uh hi my name's Logan Paul welcome to
the low game if you're not subscribed
subscribe button for me in the face stab
you with the night head yet subscribe to
the strongest family any of you yeah
okay we're gonna go to Hollywood right
now um regarding the tiger thing look I
know I'm dope okay but I can't take you
to Hollywood mr. tiger I just can't
[Music]
[Applause]
and I still pay for it at least for a
year and I said like five months left
let's cost ten thousand dollars per
month to live here and I'm not living
here do you do the math for me fifty
thousand dollars off the window fifty
thousand dollars
I'm a milk it I have on a--throw
stepladders I'm gonna do it it's all I
need obviously we got the machete and
food take this up before
I'm not joking someone was dying like
I've never seen you with that much
emotion and we can't give them a please
oh it takes 14 to 16 weeks you get them
how much is it gonna cost to get
redone misheard Anil I guess for me
$400,000 100% that's 40,000 seriously
though I've made the sacrifice like my
well-being and money out of my pocket is
not as important as making content for
you guys like that's why I do this stuff
so just I hope you can join my your
lives are above mine currently y'all
know me can i buy this today yeah I'm
nice I'm actually gonna buy the horse so
yeah you guys know I'm obsessed with
this store this is where I bought the
purple chair which I'm in love with so
this couch is apparently like a sofa
version of the chair it might be ugly I
don't know but I might see and I have to
have it I act on my instincts sometimes
oh this is fancy bro it's just weird
that's why I like it really weird it's
like me and sofa form if this goes in
the office right and I'm in my purple
chair like what's up dude billion dollar
deals right now and someone's just
laying here like yeah dude for sure sign
the contract drop the mic that's almost
rap do you like this place Judi does it
make you oh no honey honey look look I
don't know what he's worth knockoff
maverick Gaga Brian he needs helping
Jesus I could help you
this shirt bro thank you bro you got it
he's a baby the bad is better it's the
maverick crap
now you remember but you're good to go
my brother hey spread the love baby
I'm on the phone Judy I'm doing business
please this girl she's been whining
about coffee for five minutes I'm not
doing it right
and that's how you do it I'm this house
I'm not sorry
who did you coffee Judy Jesus don't
touch me
your basic your basic thorough your
basic that reminds me if you guys saw
yesterday's vlog we made the world's
biggest pumpkin spice latte and that is
a fact however the pumpkin is starting
to rot right so I figured what better
way to clean it up than to kind of just
like lift it like all the way up to the
top of the forklift and then just
looking drop it relatable okay so I'm
looking at this giant pumpkin
yesterday we uh we filled it up with
milk and made a giant pumpkin spice
latte so that bro there's still like how
many gallons thirty over twenty right so
there's just a skin liquid and coffee
and hay in it now so we're like if we're
on the forklift and the thing falls
while we're in the street that's the
kind of thing that like I would get
kicked out of the neighborhood for so I
hope that doesn't happen it might not
even fall it might just fall apart yeah
like it's rotting and everything but
lucky for us i don't use my brain often
but today i'm going to at the end of the
street boy did we get lucky there are
two trash cans broke just posted cuz so
we're just gonna drive down the street
dump it in the trash can from about
maybe like 50 feet and hopefully no one
calls the cops a thanks neighbor bad
ideas and this is one of them
go forward looks like you lined up this
is the hardest part about
not so much milk and liquid in there bro
it's dripping milk
doesn't look suspicious at all no not at
all I'm like I'm gonna extend the arm to
raise it up
she's talking to the homeowner right now
trying to convince her to let us dump it
in her dumpster and look I'm not gonna
cry over spilled milk okay
amazing thank you new neighbors yeah
okay I can't believe that worked
I'm not lying my neighbors are awesome
so yo if you're a neighbor and you're
watching this video like I love you guys
I can't wait to meet all of you thank
you for putting up with me I'm here's
the thing I'm crazy but I'm also
respected so anyways let's uh drop a
pumpkin and hopefully actually make it
let's drop a 2005 hook
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it worked pretty good
it smells like coffee it does not like
something coffee oh my god all the
pumpkin spice is like flowing out of it
dude it's smoking with pumpkin spice
yeah yeah this is the cleanup Oh gross
bro don't mess up my favorite hoodie no
ball that come shopping so I bought the
horn I got it it makes me horny good
stuff ready to wanna come up here bro
check that it like fits on my arm is a
good investment how you doing today but
you got your copy so stop complaining
okay look hang a lot of good stuff today
started with the tiger right then move
some stuff and drop the pumpkin these
are all good things
thank you ma'am tomorrow's a big day for
o'maverick bottoms are dropping like no
joke no joke these are the comfy shorts
and joggers I've ever worn I cannot wait
to see people just mopping through the
streets looking sexy in their maverick
bottoms son no one's doing it they can't
do what they can't compete with the
squad the logging - maverick favor
hoodies back as you guys know Logan Paul
Keim slash shop or link in description
and subscribe if you're not a part of
the low game cuz we're Linden we are
horny apparently anyways Logan I love
yarn out see you tomorrow
I just
Oh
[Music]