[Music]
son of a [ __ ] oh my god guys we're
watching yesterday's vlog as you guys
know Evans dog Aria passed away sad bro
she was so cute so innocent and now so
dead let's go see how he's doing
second a yoga Monica Loki I was not
did you watch my blog for master yet huh
the good news is we're wearing matching
bottoms thanks for that input anyways
bro you know I love you we all love you
[Music]
so I'm angry because I have to leave in
my Blandy it's cooking why they called
Lydia first yeah are they trying to give
Evan a gift a gift you call them and say
instead of giving me a bill or even a
condolence gift how about you guys give
me my [ __ ] dog back I know this sad
dog stuff and also making eye contact
with Kong while we're talking about this
is awkward
oh no honey no honey no so yeah guys
rest in peace are ya it is sad I think
as more time progresses the will get
stronger and I hate to keep harping on
it in a better place now um okay you
don't you don't know that factually but
I hear you bro she was a puppy she was
innocent yeah but like
sure she went to heaven like she
couldn't went to hell you don't know
what do you think she's not even not
spend enough time with her to actually
know who Aria was you she could have
been doing naughty things we're not
looking you have no idea you're assuming
and when you assume you make an ass of
you and me for all I know is you can
still be alive or in troubie I'm
especially type G oh this is dead oh
good so try to tell me Tupac's dead you
yes yeah brother
anyway yeah I'm I'm going to help bro I
know for a fact wherever I end up I'm
gonna make his soul it bro
I'm gonna pick up my vlog camera go hey
yo good morning little guy was pop and
the rest is history
anyway you guys know I did a movie
called the thinning last year
boy got yoked I worked out so hard for
them and it's actually don't movie it's
on YouTube read most of you seen it if
you haven't seen it oh you got watch it
because the next week I start the first
day on the sequel to the thing against
the thinning tubes on the thinning new
world order guys I cannot wait for this
movie bro
it is so badass my character Blake ready
music G and we're headed actually to set
right now I'm sorry about me in general
what year is the pinning seven it takes
place in 2040 bro okay no we're gonna be
wearing bro this could be that new Gucci
bro this is the classic Blake Reddy from
the first thinning bruh this is like
this is the outfit and my favorite part
watch closely to my boobs good stuff it
all fit high fashion movies acting you
know how anyways guys I have a problem
okay so at the house when I wake up in
the morning Kong starts barking it like
7:00 a.m. it's so loud and obnoxious
this little dogs no granite I still love
the dog but he wants to be Oh God we're
out here I'll see you bro I leave tag me
at Logan home I see everything
anyways I still love Kong it's just he
wants to be let out right and it's like
7 a.m. bro I'm going to better like to
lay on Oh buenos so I thought there's
got to be a way where we can make some
sort of pulley system we're on the
balcony we have a wire run from the
second floor to the middle of the yard
and kind of just like sling Kong down
there and some sort of basket so then I
don't have to leave my room right like
it might not work Kong could die and
fall but
you just got home and I parked and I
realized this is hilarious too big
bigger that's amazing I love it like
this is the angle bro we're doing it
right here at America
I'm getting distracted I'm back to the
UH pulley system and I can barely make a
bowl of cereal guys having ended here is
like having three nipples that third
nipple is just so perfect and out with a
little bit of a game do you you could be
my dad my dad daddy are you splitting
this no way I'm eating the whole thing
this is incredible is losing weight
well no hungry have any made one plate
for me and that's it so you guys can
just show clip stop now he just runs
around with no direction yo Frank that's
not how was you I just feel like you're
acting irrationally yeah hold on do we
actually get do we take on various son
of a [ __ ] I'll come back to the house
[Music]
God didn't notice the thing oh that
doors open bro that's how he got out
there's a visual offense before he keeps
running away Frank guess what I'm
building broke now pulley systems we got
uh you know a thing that goes under the
little horse you go back and forth I got
a thing that goes into the little horse
you go back and forth on building a
spaceship Oh tell me that's not perfect
sometimes in life these things happen
Joe I'm not an engineer I was majoring
in that before I dropped out of college
I'm just a vlogger boy the idea is to
cork this into the ground the ground to
screw this into the ground and then run
the line to the house oh it's about how
hard you get back how hard you get how
are you girls getting you for once in my
life I use my brain and this is leverage
you see this think it's actually torque
its torque is what I said bro that's in
their daddy movie car just as much as
that's in here I'm out here no this is
good Oh
because he's sad about REO and he's
lashing out no it's like 2 feet short
bro are you kidding me right now it was
so close it was so close I think we move
that closer yeah yeah look at us using
our brains Wow mom you're proud - but
we're in business
don't jump Kong oh you know don't jump
stay right there
I want what do you mean look at him dog
he can't you know make that fall hyung
he's a maverick bro you can do anything
or you just say no my boys right no no
Ling you should let it kill your whole
family bro you could get away right
that's so much more so much less
important three point two an Instagram
here we go
yogi you're crazy it was nice intention
using the most precision accurate
engineering no gang we have concocted a
Kong pulley system Oh oh my gosh she's
gonna have to go slow yo just really
slow but look look the bucket stable bro
like we got four lines I'm tilting it
right now it's really hard to tilt or
tip any direction Kong we'll be safe in
there I'm just curious how he's gonna
get out of the bucket once we actually
get him to the ground obviously I'm not
a complete idiot so we're gonna do a
little test just calling me when I'm
vlogging what do you want
Evan testing to see if my dog won't die
too soon I didn't mean it like that I
didn't mean like that like I'm sorry I
didn't mean like that what are you doing
what point is it like why don't I just
walk downstairs like oh we're gonna
double we're gonna dump them in the hot
tub hey buddy
just gonna do a little swap here i oh
you gonna do okay it's your big day
so chill
Oh God
[Music]
amazing
the garlic you go
believe that word I'm an engineering
roots coming into play okay low gang
that is the vlog I want to give a quick
anti shout out to Los Angeles we're
getting dark so early you son of a [ __ ]
makes it really hard to do epic vlogs
like ideally we put a GoPro inside here
right tomorrow you got something to look
forward to if you're not subscribed make
sure you subscribe join the Logie the
showings fastest best ever sexiest
family on YouTube ad format to subscribe
button in the face for me if you have
not yet gotten your merger maverick
merch aka you haven't joined the
revolution of Mavericks the people who
are oh the people who are gonna change
the world by being different by being
unique by being passionate do so Logan
Paul that cop slash opera link in
description the hottest merch in a game
yeah it always feels good to use my
brain to make me be more lazy ok guys
love y'all see you tomorrow
what's up dude now ready to love it Oh
daikon / aht urghan pop icon's not sure
you'll ever so many to movement its
revolution the game