come on Adam ah Logan Logan what are you
doing what are you doing up there can
you toss me the camera so I can take
that's a toss bro yeah cuz I got one leg
here and one leg here and they're both
really slippery I'm good children I'm a
savage and a maverick okay what's
happening today as you guys know
yesterday we got that literally this is
the largest pumpkin in California that's
a regular-sized pumpkin and that's a
2,000 pound pumpkin and then you have a
choch ball or on a forklift anyways we
do have as you know this forklift but
I'm honestly thinking about buying one
of these like right look the point is we
have decisions to make outfit on oh
speaking of decisions guys some adulting
I just got this new house I gotta get
furniture kind of an exciting process
you know making the house the designer
said this I'm making the house a home oh
yeah we are going to get our furniture
today but I'm wondering like since we do
have the pumpkin guys thinking today is
gonna be the 24 hour overnight challenge
in the pumpkin crazy cut yesterday after
the vlog ended I spent literally three
hours just sitting on the inside of the
pumpkin and carving it out not easy
flashback is work boots
also hi neighbors again my name is Logan
Paul and if you were not a part of the
low game make sure to subscribe we are
these strongest family on the internet
and that is a fact
so smack that subscribe button in the
face for me yo I'm sayin house we have
so much stuff going on I guess I'm
putting a studio in that room to build
the tree house in the back bro we're
painting the gym that's happening this
week we have a freak the biggest pumpkin
in California Oh
oh I didn't use my brain uh okay the
guys who dropped it off told me to put
ice in it to preserve it and I did the
bags were open and it melted yeah I'm
not trying to sleep in water look here's
the thing I don't know what I like until
like I see it actually in the house I've
never designed a house I literally I
hired someone to brush my teeth for me
in the morning I did I hired someone to
brush my teeth for me in the morning
because I can't do myself
turn right I'm voguing series a joke I
brush my own teeth but you see what I'm
saying no gang it's not something I'm
good at which is weird
good at everything oh these are their
guys bro we're in the magic shop right
now and I'm just looking around I don't
think we showed this last time but
there's a fat Buddha over here bro what
does it mean like is there some magical
stuff I get like more survivors yeah
it's a magical they'd love to have to go
down oh I'll take 500 it's my big day
yeah baby you know I love this one so
they this could be my girlfriend one day
I don't know how like the whole like sex
thing would work would I'll figure it
out yo okay so I really like this color
it's nice - vibrant we could say it's
very out here like me yo I don't think
I'd put this in the house but maybe my
school boys
there's denim on the side dude denim
denim denim denim denim denim yeah maybe
so you know how we talked about me uh
Brendan you know spending trying to
spend less money and make more money
how's it going not good not good I'm
okay with spending money on stuff that
will increase my quality of life that
helps me think
that helps me be creative and just be an
overall happy person so finding my life
away and these guys are gonna make my
exterior look as I just wrote down the
day here I realized here tomorrow's my
dad's birth
now I need a Bible so do you have
anything here I could buy I'm kidding
what do you like he would love this
he loves high five Oh like like he's
from Ohio pretty like hunter outdoorsy
like a skull with horns I liked it
because my dad's a star oh my god I
could do everything is just lining up or
scissoring I'll take one one very
special one for a very special man who
gave birth to had sex with my mom then
she gave birth to me my dad ah I'm so
out here I'm such a good son Los Angeles
am sure it takes uh whoa Jesus no you
guys see it's heavy no I'm sure Jake is
gonna go like way above and beyond and
be like an overachiever I love my
parents I'm gonna buy my dad a gift for
clickbait uh-huh
forget you Jake cuz I'm the better son I
even made a rap line about I think you
kind of saucy cuz I'm the favorite son
I'm a maverick you're a psycho I'm just
getting by baking of Mavericks did you
get your merch at the hottest stopped is
merch in the game no you're good dancing
the universe every single day maverick
merch
Logan Paul that cops last shot or link
in description join the revolution Oh
we came to pre-order the iPhone we're
doing the VIP experience only right here
on Verizon for hope you guys follow me
on instagram at Logan Paul that's how
you plug Ralph I have been posting
stories a lot recently it's cuz my front
cameras broke yeah it's broken so this
new iPhone is really gonna help me on my
Instagram game again at Logan Paul if
you couldn't get any better I'm talking
toast
bro I'm about to drop a hundred dollars
on a toast I had this issue the other
day had Eggo waffles couldn't toast them
it's a sexy toaster bro
racket put it in the back thank you
route oh just me Ralph and a toaster
and a toaster more furniture I love this
you know what stuff like this makes it
fun like look back that ass up I'm sorry
for making love to your furnace so we're
putting a theater in the garage look at
some stuff like this yeah this is it
what colors do you have this in
different colors honey honey herm is the
man okay this is Aston Martin furniture
made in Italy we have Mercedes sofa bed
for you hilarious not the piece of metal
itself but the contents within so this
is actually all the footage from the no
handlebars music video I'm interested
you oh man it's greasy
brother this thing is like peeing on me
oh I'm not good bro that's the box
before right and they trusted you with
that yeah yeah we have to upload the
footage so we came to the other YouTube
space see look look mama made it to
YouTube space laughs yeah the Wi-Fi
speeds are much faster than we have at
home I have bad news so here look
remember I said the things like leaking
okay so so that's a liquid liquids and
technology don't mix Logan I know I also
remembered I have a shampoo in my
backpack and I just like I hope it
didn't burst opens like oh honey oh my
god why do you have shampoo in your
backpack not the Yeti backpack you can
get on low calm slash shot actually but
this happens to be far too often we
think I would learn no I'm just so in
about 21 hours the footage will be with
you guys know the best editor in the
game because we don't do things
half-assed no handle bars will be
underway oh my gosh oh just right now
mark this down when the video drops just
plan on liking it just just slap a like
right in the face okay I think we go
back home and try to
sleep overnight in a pumpkin haha okay
I'm here with the big boy okay I'm about
to attempt to sleep in the biggest
pumpkin in California overnight Muir
sounds like coyotes really uh-huh I mean
like hopefully I don't that doesn't
happen when I'm sleeping inside that you
know I look at Brendan he's like staring
off in the distance how about some of
these coyotes I heard what I heard
oh Jesus so we got that I have a
megaphone here in case I need anything
like died neighbors a one-issue we still
haven't figured out yet is the water
thing Logan why did you check for holes
you're an idiot I was recommended to cut
a hole in the bottom so that's what I'm
gonna do oh yeah looking at drains look
at that dry first off look at this yo yo
I'm going in where I got pillows I put a
blanket down I put the toaster on the
inside I have a feeling it's gonna get
like kind of cold in there so I got the
warmest piece of clothing that I know
maverick March of course take the cannon
cuz I'm about to sleep overnight and the
biggest pumpkin in the state of
California yo it's not bad it looks kind
of cozy in there it actually is bro it's
a good thing I'm not claustrophobic ace
like there's an emergency like uh yeah
okay can you order me some pizza okay so
I'm gonna give you a quick house tour
we've got a bunch of cool stuff in here
we got a toaster as you guys know GoPro
cause vlog line we got our legs which
are kind of over here in this area
megaphone so I can yell at Lydia and the
pizza man and then this is like kind of
where I'm staying this little pillow
area as you can see this the hole right
there oh man I actually don't mind being
in a tight spot and to be honest this is
like kind of comfortable um
dad dad dad forgot he's here also why
you staying at Jake's house cuz there's
not enough room for two in the pumpkin
oh that's your give you a hug I can't
come out I gotta say otherwise the
challenges Mel's like a pumpkin it's a
big weight you brought this tomorrow
we're you gonna pee
no same hold at the electrical outlets
going through that no sue it rots yeah
that's why I had to do this tonight they
said it was gonna smell really bad by
Tuesday which is when Evan gets back you
love it I love it I did make that myself
but I'm a vlogger thanks Logan that's my
gift to you I don't know what you're
gonna do with that I just I know you're
like oh well it was fun having you as my
dad I will go back to my challenge okay
so dad left it's always nice seeing pop
happy fun don't know his age I'm just
gonna go with a hundreth birthday dad
prize do you uh made it this far
everyone go wish my dad at Greg Paul 63
a happy birthday on Instagram okay I
think I'm just gonna watch YouTube chill
Pizza kids guy beats a good guy
[ __ ] why it's guy gets here yeah that
should be interesting
hello hi there Logan your pizza's here
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay so I got this pizzas hot oh boy
he's nine times better when you're
inside a pumpkin we got freaking we got
a toaster bro we can make this oh god I
don't know
Oh like burnt cheese I think that makes
sense I guess cuz I burned the pizza
right guys I'm actually not even hungry
'ln eats out here for that coyotes
animal rights animals are important too
I'm gonna try to like go to sleep for a
little bit and just pass the time
because the toaster too and pull this up
and try and get some sleep for a little
bit cuz there's not a lot to do Garrity
no one on YouTube has ever done this
that's a maverick bro who stuff people
don't do I live for the title game it's
like it's not crazy late maybe like 10
10 p.m. and I've been out here for a
minute my plan is to catch her a couple
Z's right now I probably wake up in the
middle of the night just because like
I've been in scenarios like this before
we were like in a tight spot something
that's not the most comfortable thing
but you like to force yourself so your
body just naturally like wakes up out of
discomfort oh snap try to get
comfortable
oh okay this isn't bad it's it's also
much warmer than I expected it to be
we even got extra room like I could have
kept the toaster in here but yeah I
definitely fit in the pumpkin I'm about
to go to sleep I said this GoPro up time
last time go
oh hi how you doing okay it's the
morning I'm still in the pumpkin but I'm
not gonna lie to you I woke up in the
middle of the night like I thought I was
check the phone and my brother's ex
music yo come out it's dad's birthday
well go to the club I want to stay in
this pumpkin but then again it's a
[ __ ] pumpkin and while this is dope
yo it is not comfortable in here I'm not
gonna lie oops I went out for a second
with brother Jacob all flashback which
is leave and finish the challenge 706
a.m. it's time to make this official
that was that was cool how was something
in the toaster - is wet
this can't toast anything okay that was
an experience for sure now low gang that
is dumb I hope you guys enjoyed that
that was very uncomfortable for me my
knees hurt Oh God
I'm asleep in a pumpkin if I need you
for you so subscribe you were not part
of the strongest family on the internet
cuz we do epic lychees like tomorrow we
might do a little something today I
guess we might do a little something
like that who knows we'll see and copier
maverick merch it's the hottest stuff
this merch in the game I'm not gonna lie
if I did not have my maverick merch with
me when I was inside the pumpkin as it
probably would have died for real yeah
that's important you get your metal
merchants all the time slash opera link
in description
I just
at stake