it's my 24th birthday tomorrow
[Applause]
casein I said my birthday with me haha
I'm not subscribed make sure to
subscribe
o-genki notifications ahahaha you guys
know we're doing a one-for-one giveaway
on these maverick retro hoodies a
birthday drop it's a two-year
anniversary of the brand for this drop
I'm done being a boy and so you get one
and give one to a child in need Logan
Paul calm /sha we got a fun ass walk
today it's gonna get crazy but first
it's time to wake up
hi turn 24 tomorrow boys have arranged
for something extremely extremely
special 24 tomorrow you're just sick we
do a little something crazy we're gonna
do 24 things 24 times Z 24 thing 24
times each it's gonna get Loco let's
start off with some a little familiar 24
plates yeah
[Music]
everyone good yo Oh God alright next
yeah
24-second handstand surrounded by 24
master Oh
Wow okay what else
twenty-four seconds of cold cryotherapy
liquid nitrogen on me gonna add we're
gonna freeze your testicles oh yeah
negative 320 degrees on your ball size
so worst-case scenario is laughs aw
if I didn't have my penis roll I would
be a lot more productive oh wow feels
great god this actually feels so good oh
wow oh my god it feels so good on my
face if I get a rack keep going
those dopes how you feeling chief wahoo
merch is still hot like huh /op maybe
you know the joke okay it's next
challenge I'm gonna compliment 24
youtubers Jake Paul I think you're the
better-looking Paul brother mr. beast
you are the most hardworking and
creative person on this platform Casey
Neistat
hey Matt you really you really did it
bro you're a sick guy and I know that
sounds sarcastic I mean it I just beauty
by t-series and gosh on you and you're
still number one in my eyes Liza Koshi
you are one of the most talented people
on this platform stay golden david
dobrik uh gotta be honest bro I am
jealous of how funny and creative you
are and also that you're friends with
the Jenners damn it tan ammonia if you
had a tan akan 2.0 I'd be the first to
purchase a ticket Shane Dawson I know
you didn't ejaculate on that cat and
congrats on the engagement must be nice
being in love Tipu yo you're killing it
bro and congrats on the new girlfriend
phase rug you are the most genuine kid
ever and I wish you health wellness and
riches for the rest of your life
jason nash i think you're the funniest
member of the vlog squad and i kinda
wish that you were my dad keemstar
unfortunately i think you're gonna be
around on this platform longer than any
of us
rice gum great content great girlfriend
great and
gee all-around awesome dude you keep it
100 100% of the time
stay real myyy guys ninja you made
gaming cool and you revolutionize the
space and I cannot wait until you have a
ninja baby life of Mack the ASMR girl
you are so popular and cool that our
podcast with you is actually the number
one viewed podcast on the channel Jojo
see WA you are the most vibrant
energetic colorful person that I know
it's just too bad that I can't see any
of those colors wah bah zorrito you're
my Mexican brother me Amano you're one
of the few people using social media for
good and I love you dude te amo me amigo
que si [ __ ] you [ __ ]
yes theory keep seeking discomfort guys
so you got balls the size of grapefruits
jenna Marbles you are alleged you're an
OG and I hope to have you on my podcast
one man Robbie Davidson thank you for
helping me prove that there is no earth
Philip DeFranco Philly be without you
we'd never jump right into it ace family
y'all are y'all are adorable it's just
incredible I hope that my family can be
as half as cute as you guys one day
rocket twins you are some crazy
Australian boys you're also one of the
most talented people on the platform and
I think you'll be directing big-budget
feature films one day I think it was 24
I think oh no we'll take it
[Applause]
[Music]
24 inches in no what do you have one for
me I'm not sure if it's a medieval
torture thing you put them on your ankle
and then you do like a pull-up to put
your hook your leg did not expect these
are great all right I'm gonna go do some
Ironman not cool why would anyone use
these ever
oh thanks Susie he rock next challenge
my roommates are gonna punch me 24 times
I need y'all to me up for real I'll
leave some to Steve all those extra
hours that he missed any problems you
had with me
take them out now I don't got a problem
with you y'all really coming with that
smoke hey how you do this is how you
doing Joe Weller take notes my guy wow
you are today
[Music]
for this birthday it looks like she
looks like you love me man I haven't
felt this good in a long time I'm gonna
listen to ksi music for 24 minutes
straight oh this was gonna be hard
oh my god this is actually tortious core
breach that one's messed up okay I'm
glad that's over
this one's stupid I'm gonna take 24
peoples to the back oh my god oh he's
gonna hurt so bad this is the cheapest
on the head they don't actually have any
cheaper so it's not dope there's gonna
hurt like a [ __ ] but I'm turning 24 so
it's all good I actually want you to
oh the world I'm done
that's a welt I did it no no
[Music]
this one is stupid this was a dumb one
I'll call you to say you don't feel pain
yeah I don't know I'll son I'm really
feeling oh ha ha
I've been doing some thinking and now
that I'm 24 I'm getting smarter huh
and I'm not gonna finish this challenge
tag responsibility really got you yeah
that's what I mean lady but I've always
wanted to get shot with pay poles but
damn I think it's gonna hurt that bad
turn it 24 is rough dude it's just
taking a toll on pickup 24 pieces of
trash 24 marshmallow 24 burps got 24
slices of cucumber I don't know
[Music]
boys come around here and they litter in
my neighborhood
don't litter guys it's not good for this
planet we live on it
[Music]
yeah
okay next challenge I got $24 here for
24 random people go give away some
frickin money there's can I get 24 bucks
oh you want this remember when you hit
me earlier
suck my model I'm so curious to see how
people will react $24 do you want $24 my
24th birthday
okay good thanks my friend here's 24
bucks
alright hey I see you coming over here
thank you you spend it on drugs
[Music]
yes was getting bands with strangers
you'll always take their money
that's not 24 bucks I have to do is get
in my pants thank you you have a good
day kids nor done this before feels oh
yes I feel this weird like tingly
feeling thank you yes money
[Music]
take my money there's nothing you can do
about it original on a date with some
honey's robust impressing bro thank you
I got you go yeah
take my money if you want it [ __ ]
through I'm not here to beat you up
simply give you this money
it's my 24th birthday I'm doing some
good deed no strings attached what are
we doing right now come on there you go
what about you lady I saw you in
stranger things yeah I'm gonna talk
about you see money you take it see
money she's gone
sorry about that let me tell you
something if someone offers you money
you take it holy Sh it has been a crazy
painful day but a good one nonetheless
here this vlog is long I hope you guys
like it y'all know I'm doing a get one
get one sale of all that got slashed
shop this channel do make a difference
when we can so I could buy a hoodie on
the site or anything we will give one to
a kid in need let's do this
new retro hoodies just dropped 1821
oh my god all right look bro
fabulous yeah maverick babies my boys
the hottest softest thickest merch in
the game I'll feel like a husky kid I
feel like a chubby little boy
come on alive we're all feeling like I
kind of live though I listen want to
look like me one day no problems over
local pawn shop you could be this hey
listen guys we did 23 things but we do
have one more thing to do probably the
most important thing about being 24
actually turning 24 my god I am
exhausted I'm also 24 now thanks man
thanks I feel different
my crotch is tingling I might be seven
problem hey B check make sure you guys
subscribe if you're not subscribed joins
a little Gang Gang Gang skirt thank you
guys I love you every year you make my
life is so amazing it's so special and
I'm excited to grow with you guys also
you guys you know we just dropped the
new maverick retro hoodie get one give
one on the website so you buy a piece of
merch and give one to a kid in need
Logan Paul calm /op we're making an
impact this year mark my words I love
you guys and I will see you tomorrow
take these
[Music]
the media is gonna run with it Logan
Paul makes his mother shoot him with a
paintball gun I'd be like
[Music]