you probably think you know me after all
I pretty much lived my whole life on
camera
you've been inside my house you see me
doing crazy [ __ ] you know my friends my
family
you see me at the top and you've
definitely seen me fall
but the truth is you don't really know
me
way to go way to go you don't know
what's inside my heart and you don't
know how hard I'm prepared to work or
how far I'm prepared to go to achieve my
goals you have no idea what I'm capable
of
but you're about to find out
I saw a digital camera in a magazine
when I was like 9 News $150 can afford
that I'm nine years old and when I mowed
lawns I snowboard driveways I had a
birthday party so my friends were giving
me money I remember one of my friends
brought me $20 in pennies it's actually
him right there you're an [ __ ]
$20 in pennies
for some reason I like the aesthetic of
capturing something on a screen from 10
to 18 we made videos Jacob I and then
Vaughn came out and we happen to pop off
on that these uh stupid little six
second videos
hey who woulda guessed good night 88
[Music]
Logan's ability to story tell in such a
short form medium was super impressive
flipping that switch to go to YouTube it
just took off from there he's fast this
channel that will reach a million
subscribers people were living
vicariously through him watching
billions of hours of content I st. Logan
as the biggest entertainer in the world
not a country that you can go in today
without him being known we're talking
the biggest platform in the entire world
Logan is number one for video views I
started on vine and then I became a
youtuber and
a boxer this is weird and so I'm curious
what I was like off-camera compared to
now yeah you know hello closed my house
is listed on Google Maps as a maverick
house hey so this was a little out of
the ordinary I don't know how these
things get in there I can assure you I'm
not manually putting my address into
Google notion this house is a magnet for
crazies it's not just who knocks on the
door though we're sort of like a frat
house but we're the most successful frat
house in the world a chef cooking
full-time those guys coming in world
class box or anything that you could
possibly imagine
as far as training rest recovery
scheduling to create a championship
boxing team we're doing that the first
case I fight watching him train and the
passion that he has for the sport I
think surprised him as much as it
surprised everyone else for me I'm a
long time boxing fan the rematch is kind
of the most exciting part of the whole
thing the intensity is just it's just
higher than it's ever been
everyone is stressed I'm stressed the
chef is stressed it's not the same when
you wake up and it's fight camp
good morning champ we wake up every
single day to boxing coaching Eliot 8:00
in the morning
let's go champ look at him champ look at
him you got him
it's the champ Shannon - Shannon Briggs
two-time heavyweight champion of the
world and guess what let's don't I go to
sleep every night nightmares about let's
go just go champ by bringing in Shannon
the stakes jumped up astronomically
right the energy changes with Shannon
he's just a powerful motivating energy
force and a two-time heavyweight world
champion that is extremely intelligent
animated I'm working loading like a
heavyweight champion but this is a
dangerous business and I tell them that
every day listen you can play football
play baseball but everything is you
can't play boxing this is the hurt
business man
this [ __ ] is real Shannon is a great
coach because here's a great fighter
he's been in the ring he is that warrior
when he's screaming at you and telling
you to do something look that rope
you know it's from the point of view of
hey I've done this before and by the way
it works
[Music]
this is the only reason I'm able to work
out as hard as I am I sort of God this
is it's better than cryotherapy it's
better than any massages any
anti-inflammatories this thing the ice
bath is a miracle chamber I've never
done ice dam I hate being cold
it's like 38 degrees today I mean this
is hella cliche but this shit's all
mental I mean it really is if you can
like go somewhere else for the first 90
seconds you're in here and separate
yourself from your body like pull your
soul out and extract it you can get over
it I think we're gonna peak right when
the fight Khans Shanna calls it baking a
cake dudes baking a cake and he wants to
make sure it's cooked to perfection
oh wait mine's got this boat right now
if any youtuber wants it you can come
get it say someone tweeted me like okay
this guy KS eyes like Jake Paul Logan
Paul I knew kiss that was like a popular
youtuber some like whoa what's going on
here it allowed Logan to focus all of
his attention on a positive pursuit that
didn't have the residue of Japan on it
I've made a severe and continuous lapse
of my judgment and I don't expect to be
forgiven I'm simply here to apologize
post Tokyo I had not forgiven myself
yeah and I was not ready to move on
there's three million tweets trash logan
paul rot in hell without ksi calling me
out I don't know what I would have done
if you hadn't given me an opportunity to
fight like go back to making cringy as
vlogs we kind of kept on thinking about
it and I came up with the idea where
Logan would fight ksi and then I would
fight Deji his younger brother cuz I
think his younger brother started
talking [ __ ] so we were like okay
this fights happening we need to learn
how to box I've never I've never boxed
before last year ever within 48 hours we
were in a boxing gym I've been hitting
the paste by Logan ball before and like
it is not a joke at all
a week later I'm sparring somebody
getting punched in the face like
bleeding but in our heads it's like we
can't lose like everybody in the world
wants Jake and Logan Paul to lose I
don't think I knew how big the ksi fight
was gonna be the first time around it
was a massive massive thing that became
the number one bought pay-per-view event
on the internet system
the kid can't box but he is a dog he is
an animal and I respect the [ __ ] out of
that big ego a lot of pride refuses to
go down
the draw the draw was a major letdown I
still think that he won the first fight
last year was the year of Elle's for me
just taking Elle's to the chin over and
over and over and over and over again in
the fight I had against JJ was my one
chance to secure some sort of win in
2018 it was a [ __ ] tie uh no I'm
gonna [ __ ] kill this dude I'll rip
his head off
[Music]
the colors of the wagon yeah
five minutes we're gonna bring those are
the differences between the Utah Salinas
and councilors this is really for your
trainers but I'm gpo's
you guys can tell my demeanors a little
more chills we've seen in the Logan Paul
vlogs I I'm uninterested in still being
a youtuber this is not a gimmick anymore
no I'm not joking around I'm a [ __ ]
professional fighter I'm gonna treat it
like that is that what made you want to
turn pro that way you can fight without
the headgear use this moment though I
mean I just um Pro sighs [ __ ]
kids got a big mouth
like me too which is why I think this is
such a big event like both our egos too
[ __ ] huge we both have a lot of the
line and none of us want to become a
mean
[Music]
[Applause]
I think caves I was scared I think he
realizes that he's gonna loser knows
that he's gonna lose deep deep deep down
who's excited to see me Logan doesn't
like us are gonna get a [ __ ] from
whatever promote haven't already come on
say it's a joke what is it Eddie Hearn
doing he's embarrassing you know etc etc
but there'll also be watching on
November 9 going fun the first time
around I got told about the first fight
and I almost wanted it to be a Paul fire
it was a really good fight when I was
asked to be involved in the rematch
I wasn't in any parts I knew it would
come with criticism they can criticize
you and the event as much as one you're
still walking out you find it 20,000
people that stay presented to fight
another men but with no protection I
said we need to lose the head cards you
got to use 10 ounce clubs the little
ones you know the ones that really crack
someone will end up face down here and
tie up and quite honestly that's what I
want now it's a proper file now someone
will get knocked out
quite honestly somebody's getting
knocked out and quite honestly that's
what I want that's right
be me and Eddie her and going at it self
aligning that's gonna be the new thing
so I'm gonna do that for you you're
gonna be the first guy to wear it silver
lining yeah
this shouldn't be allowed
I sort of God this should not be allowed
last year would fought with 12 oz gloves
and I know it doesn't seem like a lot
with two ounces is gonna make a lifetime
of a difference
Logan's punches in the first fight if
they're ten ounce gloves would have
knocked him out oh my god these are
legal - yeah yeah yeah that's the same
thing - triple G uses that's the same
one that some guys that used in I feel
like I'm holding a gun in my hands are
really quick and so if we're practicing
an 18 ounce gloves and I'm looking fast
then and then we moved to ten ounce
gloves for fight I'm not even
considering the effects of a loss I just
can't I can't fathom it I think the
loser of this fight will suffer an
immense and perpetual amount of
embarrassment
I'm an extreme person boxing is an
extreme sport every time you step in
that ring you were risking your life
part of me sort of likes that as it
makes me push myself to a level and most
humans will never dare to go busting
your nose guess what becoming nuclear I
would never and million years want to
get in the ring the current fire look
I'm scared for that side there will be a
knockout it's not going six rounds this
isn't some you to [ __ ] I'm ready for
this which is the only thing in my life
that matters I'm gonna knock out his eye
and it's gonna be sick
what kind of man likes to beat up a man
trying to beat up him who enjoys that I
[ __ ] do I like that
next question
[Music]
you