[Music]
it's early guys I came out here on my
balcony come look at home was barking at
someone this is more okay see you later
on was barking and I was like what the
he's going on and look outside some dude
is mowing my lawn like I I didn't hire
landscapers like it looks like he knows
what he's doing he makes good line but
yeah I didn't know that so this is a
nice tree also do you know I live in a
house now right so today's garbage day
why I have to take the garbage it's just
crazy
it's almost as crazy as my mustache yeah
and I guess it's the no handlebars music
video we shot yesterday is over I could
shave it guys today it might be the
mustaches last day anyways I'm gonna go
see what's up the back oh here I hear
somewhere must know the gate code how
did they get the gate code there's the
other guy calling you so oh hey oh good
morning Evan what do you do this guy's
gonna take Aria hopefully to get her
cast off today oh that's today their
cast is just horrible oh you're a broken
dog but you're not beat did you hire
landscapers oh yeah me neither yeah real
life I did not hire landscapers bro know
what they're doing later also realize I
didn't say yeah oh good morning okay and
if you're not part of the low Gammage to
subscribe we are the strongest family
I'm the Internet Oh take that subscribe
button grab it by the moustache also if
you haven't noticed our merch is the
softest and coolest in the game it's
that maverick life I have to scream over
these guys it's that maverick life
everyday we are changing the world man
we aren't afraid to be different we
aren't afraid to approach our
landscapers in boxers and Gucci slip we
aren't afraid to unleash an attack dog
on him get him Kong you savage be free
Oh auntie is up oh my god what the heck
is he doing anyway look Paul calm slash
shop or link in description come on Kong
we got people
that's my boat hey hey good morning if I
kiss is awkward dr. Chad and hold on
okay I know you've seen it but like this
is so beautiful I'm very happy with this
purchase man like I am slowly falling in
on you slowly I am quickly falling in
love with this house yeah to me mom I'm
adulting no speaking of my mom
my dad is in town I know he's here he
called me this morning but he said he
was at Jakes I know this is Lynn they do
the outside too man these guys are
savages anyways yeah my dad is that
Jake's house I was like yo you good bro
so I'm sure I'll see him later but yeah
this is just this is an interesting
experience for me I haven't taken out
trash cans in so long but it feels good
it just sucks that there's a mountain of
trash honey no no she lives far away now
she takes time to get here and is still
sleeping it hurt I realized while I was
doing that was move the trash yeah I got
a lot of the trash yes you guys I barely
moved it honestly I just did it for the
time lapse cuz you and your friend may
be like help me move it to the streets
it's just a lot you know okay Wow um a
lot of trash and I'm aware I may have
cheated the system a little bit yeah
there's just a lot like I stacked them
up on top of each other etc but also I
realized while I'm taking out the trash
what's that I don't want to do that
again bro I should make Brendan or Evan
do it not to mention landscape guy like
ditched me halfway through it's just not
the move like for all I know literally
the trash guy could have already come
today in which case honey knows okay I
showered I clean maverick just give me a
second I'm vlogging cleaned off and just
admiring my beautiful cut grass damn
well yo
Oh what the [ __ ] dude I think this is
the top of Brennan's head Brandon
Brandon this first guy he's awake bro
I've been freaking slave this morning
how long have you been awake for it you
need help honey
really because it looks like you need
help and Jesus yeah yeah great cool so
how long have you been awake but I have
your know been slaving away bro making
sure this house is top-notch
no can you help me film a vlog please
it's me Logan Paul it's actually your
big day Brendan why is that okay here's
what you know not more than 10 seconds
ago in the vlog I saw you just sitting
on the ground like a fool yeah I don't
have any furniture not for long mr.
Brendan Brendan
yeah yeah you got mattresses now oh god
oh he's just saying that verge okay
thanks Casper I remember the last time I
had I Casper box here's where to do with
that good times old Boggs enterprises
growing up what happens when you're
going after world domination who knows
maybe one day I'll be President the sake
of the United States let's hope not but
after one year of planning and figuring
stuff out yo come over here let me
introduce you let me bless you with
knowledge names Jim no they already know
who you are
this is your ass okay through this man's
expertise engine I am going to Dubai on
November left to host a polishes the
biggest meet-and-greet ever mole in the
wall average day there's anywhere
between 700 thousand to a million people
and you have a massive fan base across
the Middle East in Dubai right yes where
everywhere time I don't know only that
by the way you're speaking at one of the
biggest social media can I do this this
is the ITP conference I knew that yo yo
give him social media tips guess who
knows better than the social media god
no your trip is gonna be epic it's gonna
be historic yo I'm telling you scaring
me you guys remember VidCon
let me tell you about New York
something I've done it with Kim
Kardashian okay I've done it with Justin
Bieber that's why he's the guy on it
with Priyanka Selena's and daya okay
it's about to go down they never seen a
vlogger row nobody has ever the social
media power there you have are gonna get
all that love to the fans in the Middle
East brother it's your time literally
act like no joke every ounce of love in
my body and that's a lot of love is
going to my audience my fans my lo
gangsters in Dubai I'm coming to meet
you guys November little French no
Arabic okay no you're getting it done I
know I should've told you this my parrot
speaks Arabic maverick actually speaks
Arabic Jeff did you know I also didn't
know that she's a girl
is it gonna bite I don't know I hope not
how could you speak a little Arabic for
me I don't meet him what yes
and a maverick yeah cool so they're
gonna do their thing okay that's what I
thought I didn't know why the irony
pizza I'm so sorry no I swear to God
last at our Latin tough place before the
place before the last place people would
order of pizzas and it makes me so sad
like bro when you tell the pizza men
that you didn't order that pizza it
looks like they're kids who just lost
the Pinewood Derby sighs okay we're
pizza talk meg is leaving goodbye thanks
for teaching me Arabic Rogers leaving
goodbye
Martine we'd use your voice and do the
voice-over watch and yep that was
definitely my routine no I could do it
for your Haydn when I say that it's I
love all Emiratis how do you spell
Emiratis two E's ma Emiratis yeah okay
Marathi so yeah I guarantee your
bladders not even that big and their
cast is done
oh honey you're so good looking but your
disaster baby you need Jesus you need
Jesus and maverick merch looking but
like how /up oh speaking of that
Oh maverick merch and there's more on
the garage like that's the thing that's
taking up the most space in this house
what you know I'm not mad at spike but I
just we need a room you know for the
Maverick merch I can't make it this room
as you guys know we're turning this into
a studio yeah this all goes back to the
thing I was doing earlier this morning
which is adulting which by the way by
the way Evan - Lydia I know you're not a
camera man but can you do me the
pleasure of holding this camera
Lydia's camera now haha locating not you
okay tell me what you see yeah how do
you think it got there yeah it took me a
half hour by the way I don't know who
hired them Lydia was that you oh he's
going to the five not on purpose though
look guys the point is as roommates it's
a joint effort right it's like imagine a
scissoring all the time but with effort
yeah I knew nothing of this so maybe
it's my fault there's one thing I'm sure
of
I definitely didn't hire those like
Gauntlet is hot that should be it we
should make people do that like as a
punishment if you come over and like
peeve us you know anyway so okay as you
guys know I've been spending a lot of
money lately especially and stuff I
don't really need Gucci jacket but today
I find out if one of those investments
was worth it yo $10,000 worth of
speakers one day yes yeah cuz obviously
you guys know we like to rage a little
bit so we got some giant subs some
smaller speakers that are still big some
smaller speakers are still bigger than
just some small speakers we're gonna put
these around the house and then
hopefully we can
just freaking bang broke not like
sexually just like music
actually yes actually subwoofer here in
a centralized location
I want peepees Adams like on the atomic
level to vibrate when they're standing
here the second they walk in the house
do you know what I mean here's one you
may know 25 million views in a week
no this bangs Logan that's one speaker
and one sub Oh as dj khaled would say
another one as you would say again
another let's listen to that
[Music]
whoa mom yo I'm going deaf and I think
we bought too many speakers I think we
bought way too many speakers by like
eight too many yeah please so much more
oh these are all different speakers
where could we put them tension outside
the guys Marvin one for calm oh yeah no
oh honey honey honey honey hi honey
honey honey there you go okay time to
rage so many speakers oh we've all been
waiting for I spent $10,000 on speakers
I'm about to run through the house while
listening to my brothers song it's
everyday bro let's see if I put my money
[Music]
[Applause]
follow me bro thing that's not a city
anyways I think I think the morning was
put to good use
even my dog got turned I say hello gang
are you like huh
That's not me you good hit the subscribe
button join the strongest family I knew
to also I just want to say everyone's
getting in drama
you got freaking rice come in Jake drama
and that's pretty much it but this is
the only chance entertaining concert I'm
doing thank positive kids get your merch
American merchant Logan Paul calm slash
shop you already know but we're on a
mission to dent the universe and we are
gonna do it join the revolution Thank
You discussion low gang I love y'all and
I will see you tomorrow take it easy fam
[Music]