take pull no can pull and there's a
pause I don't count dad no I haven't my
dad well he once fight me I'm totally up
for it I'm officially done with the bull
woman's ksi versus Logan wall a boxing
match is in the word yes yes yes this is
it guys low gang this is the video
YouTube has been waiting this is
actually my second attempt at making
this video because the first one eyelid
I went too hard so I took a chill pill
gonna take it easy on this one and keep
it somewhat professional guys okay
here's a little background a British
youtuber by the name of ksi I think he's
actually the UK's biggest youtubers he
had a boxing match against his other
youtuber and he wins the match and I'm
sure you guys saw it for no reason at
all he calls out my brother and I okay
weird cuz I don't really know this kid
I've had one interaction with him about
two years ago at the Super Bowl we
wanted to meet up he texted me he said
try and find me I'm the black guy okay
and so we took this picture together I
barely talked to this guy and then he
calls me out for the whole [ __ ]
internet honey nom what's even worse he
planned this out like he almost forgot
to call me in Jake out we see him wait
he's like the guys accused of something
you want to say somebody want to call
how he's literally like is there
anything you want to say it
I said you wanted to call someone out
huh I almost forgot bro JJ I hope you're
riding the white DJ calendar thank you
later cuz you owe him one bro out of all
the YouTube drama honestly I've never
seen something sucked so dry how many
people can make a video about this topic
Jesus mother of God I'm here to cut the
[ __ ] it's over with this video drama's
done about to clear this up the question
the question am i Logan Paul going to
fight ksi the real-life scooby-doo of
YouTube he's just run away from
everything
it's just run away from everything
hearing you laugh is worse than
listening to your music is making wishes
for all these [ __ ] you know y'all
have seen the videos guys there's the
videos of me training at the Mayweather
gym see me talking about the fight on
the jack and the verdict is yes it looks
like I am fighting ksi this is going to
be the biggest event in youtube history
by far possibly the biggest event on the
internet ever
it's Mayweather versus but but even on
top of that it's the UK versus the US
aid like this Scott diplomat a couple
things I want to clear up two one I know
case I wants to fight in England his
home which is actually dope I love
England I love my English fans in fact I
may go far to say after the fight that
England is my city but honestly bro I'm
an American boy like I want to fight in
the US I'm also gonna suggest ksi listen
closely to this a new through place
maybe like Dubai absolutely my favorite
city in the entire world I don't know I
think that could be cool but honestly I
want to leave it to you guys so I'm
gonna put a pull it to one of these
corners where you think we don't want us
to fight we got the USA obviously with
the UK and
like yeah take the pole right here and
to be honest while you guys are doing
that I just want to say I'm down to take
your made-up bedazzled random YouTube
belt
any in any city to be honest I'm cool
with whatever you want I am gonna
respect that you won the last fight so
that's this is my gift to you another
thing guys we know he doesn't want to do
MMA uh yeah probably a smart thing to
avoid something like this
fine you want a box a box here's another
one DJ Khaled autumn Kisai bro
I'm not wearing headgear dawg I don't
want to do that that's the last thing I
want to do I think it's the silliest
thing in the world I know you wore
headgear in your last fight and to be
honest man if you if you insist on that
I don't really have any interest in
fighting you and also I want to know
what you guys want the audience you guys
are the most important you're the ones
we were doing this for can you shut the
scabbard I'm vlogging just the bird we
okay vote head your no headgear uh if
it's a rules and regulations thing and
like we have to do it like okay fine but
I want to do everything in my power to
avoid that I know in one video you said
you and I both know that we had to wear
head guards for Alfred safety reasons
okay one if you're worried about health
and safety I'm not really sure why
you're getting in a boxing ring too if
you're worried about health and safety I
don't know why you're getting in a
boxing ring with me another one guys
weight classes right I'm 210 pounds JJ's
like 180 - I am heavier than him so ksi
bro we got to meet somewhere in the
middle I could probably get down to like
190 while still having energy and like
being able to fight because I've already
like kind of slim I would plan I would
plan on you having to gain muscle
lastly I want my brother Jake Paul to
fight KS eyes little brother
I think that would be great I also
thought if your dad is down my dad is
down to Fox your dad
oh that would be crazy your entire
family versus mine it would be crazy so
yeah ask your dad if he's down oh so I'm
aware all right look I'm beast but this
is not gonna be easy I am very impressed
by chaos eyes body transformation a
little amount of boxing he was able to
learn for months and I'm not treating
this like I'm the king from the champ
I'm gonna train hard I'm gonna work hard
we are not under estimating this kid I
am going in there with the mindset that
someone's face is coming off and it
can't be mine it can't cuz I need my
face hey dude the goal is to make waves
to provide you guys with the most
entertaining fight you've ever seen to
make history to globalize the Maverick
revolution show the world the power of
the Maverick and show you guys that when
you've been faced with a challenge when
you've been called out you feel like
you've been wrong repair for it work
hard work hard every single day face the
challenge overcome the adversity because
that's what this is about son you called
off the raw this at maverick revolution
is part of the maverick enterprise guys
this is no joke this is gonna be the
biggest show in the world we're all in
this together it's time for the
Internet's can blow the she's top all
right I'm rambling now the point is it's
gonna be sick thank you guys for
watching if you're not a part of the low
gang make sure to subscribe copy stuff
some of the hottest march in the game
y'all know where to get it Logan Paul
calm /op leak on the dirty wheel and ksi
the ball is in your court I would say
[Music]