so I'm gonna give you two things one
here's a picture of some guy and two I'm
gonna give you this lighter anything you
want to do using those two things seems
like that's what I want to do yeah seems
about right
[Music]
hey guys today is a big day as you guys
know it is on Memorial Day weekend so
and we never do this we were having a
20% off sale through Monday on the
hottest merch in the game excited 20%
maybe it's a big deal I'm Logan Paul
comm / shot but honestly I think we need
to celebrate bigger I think we need to
celebrate big 20% off this weekend
still in the wall you start a fire
there's a possibility of that but not
because of the potato because the rise
of the Mavericks people who are doing it
different people who ride together
people who fly together examples fencers
you know the fly together booty is flyer
these are talking about it dude this new
merge deserves a sexy-ass
[Music]
guys the point is you wear sexy you feel
sexy link in description we are not
doing this 20% off sale for a while make
sure you pass on the opportunity now boy
do we have and potentially here but
today's not about that today's about a
character you guys know one love you
remember this guy his name is Clyde Oh
sir eyes now a good time abort mission
well today's the day that Clyde Daniels
makes his epic comeback so if you're not
a part of the logging I suggest you
buckle up and smash that
the low gang does to the SUBSCRIBE run
without further ado I think it's time
for the man the myth the legend
[Music]
yo Clyde seriously like we gotta go yeah
yeah we yeah speed here how bad cuz I
would love to stay and eat my Asian wok
if you don't mind yeah I'm also a little
concerned about the whole fact that
you're not wearing any pants I invented
pants applied are you familiar with que
si si you - yes I crime scene
investigations love that show no that's
what the si que si is a youtuber and he
boxed another gentleman now he wants to
box Logan Paul that Logan Paul do sure
if you ask me oh wow you got something
on your beard well you need for me we
need to gauge the public's perception on
this fight and we had to go to the best
of the best
you know if it's my perception Claude
Daniels is your man I'm getting excited
again God boy hey Daniel feels good to
be back in the saddle absolutely I see I
love interviewing college kids cuz they
are almost always permanently horny and
drunk this is a fun fact I may not know
about Clyde and it's a stormy stormy
Daniels is actually my cousin stormy
Daniels is the porn star that slept with
that Donald Trump okay you take you
without [ __ ] where's get high here it's
getting awkward at night here Hey
everything about Donald Trump
Hey shut the hell up I'm driving a
vehicle you take you happy I mean George
Oh 20% off maverick bird sale baby oh my
god I think I did link in description
oh I think we're getting close wonder
how I can tell it's because I'm feeling
orange Wow let's interview some college
kids
[Music]
[Applause]
howdy there folks fly dinner's coming
back at you live here on the beautiful
campus of UCLA otherwise known as we're
ready to go we got a two beautiful
camera man with us on camera a we got
jet howdy there I love you Chet and I
can't repeat we got my friend puzzle you
shut up when you're talking to me puzzle
[Music]
okay sitting ducks my favorite hey there
partner August 25th two of the biggest
youtubers ksi vs. logan paul are duking
it out boxing match who's gonna win and
why i have no knowledge of either of
those figures hey si versus Logan Paul
who do you think I'm staying here so
I'll get arrested I have yet to watch so
far oh my god we have struck a gold mine
ladies and gentlemen I cannot believe
what I'm seeing que si is here he is
here on UCLA campus we're gonna approach
we're gonna ask him who he thinks gonna
win the fight ksi ksi sir who do you
think it won the fight looks like he's
trash Logan Paul yeah you familiar with
ksi British youtuber know who is right
he looks like this this is this is ksi
he's fighting Logan Paul on August 25th
who do you thinks gonna win in why
as a fellow Nigerian I gotta go okay I
he's been hit in the gym he's been
working out are you drunk
I'm not I don't know you seem like
pretty pretty fit guy you know well I
said Logan Paul and I'm Claude Daniels
when I show you this picture what comes
to mind Jake Paul do you make that
mistake no I'm gonna give you two things
one here's a picture of some guy and two
I'm gonna give you this lighter anything
you want to do using those two things
seems like that's what I want to do yeah
seems about right
we're smart here I would in fact not
call that smart in fact call that the
opposite of smart I don't know buddy
yeah you
books that's that man needs to hit hell
of books sure I'm gonna ask you a
question
but I need your answer while standing on
this mat okay okay si versus Logan Paul
who's gonna win and why I mean I like
both of them I can't really so you do
like both of them yeah yeah and why are
you standing on KSS face I mean he's
looking pool training
I heard he's training yeah for sure I
agree my roommate watches Logan Paul I
don't think he has a lot of good things
to say about that's a chaos I okay would
you be mad if you saw me yeah yeah
probably just are you okay what do you
know where to find me
yeah yeah sure UCLA all right but that
but you use like a pretty big campus so
I'll probably be fine right or you could
get a load can fall to protect you
oh he would oh yeah oh and then why am i
against Logan pile of them this is Logan
I think I would like to make a new
disclaimer I love Logan Paul because
he'll protect me against this guy I've
been standing on that's right you hear
that kids
logo Paul will protect you against your
bullies yes I don't want to interrupt
the whole drum thing but ksi versus
Logan Paul who's gonna win and why is
there anything you want to do to that
face Matt of ksi all right okay
that is quite the day on the interviews
now as far as what I think I can't say
I'm unbiased pieces Clive Daniels at
your service
[Music]
Wow Oh God you are funny Brown I always
kill it out there yeah he's funny man
thanks
quick Logan Paul you think you can give
me some 20% off merch this weekend
thanks Logan Paul I love you
alright claw Daniel signing off we're
still lying right now yeah yeah we're
still we're still on so I think they
heard that thing yeah no they didn't I
sell the microphone here you still alive
alive thought to take it easy really
though guys Memorial Day weekend sale
this weekend only it's 20% off every
piece of maverick murder and we just
dropped five of the new hottest pieces
you may ever see in your life I'm not
even kidding Logan Paul that calm slash
shop or link in description we're not
doing the sale again make sure to smash
that subscribe
[Music]