I think I'll get a ticket right now yeah
what's going on here it's hot as balls
to go get some ice cream what's happened
well I think you get it ticket what
seems through the problem officer sir
what are you doing under the vehicle
yeah you're legally parked I did not
know that
nope let me show you a citation sir
you're illegally parked you're parked on
the curb Oh No you're on the loading
zone no need to knit windows you have no
front plate this is fair how much is
that for you're probably looking at to
$300 oh I don't want to even look at
that thing tickets are the bane of my
[ __ ] existence Spencer talking my
cameraman man listen is it hey whoa back
up Spencer this is official
investigation Spencer I am calm I just a
way way way way way way I'm his prank
I'm a lawyer
no I'm his friend best friend I know I
know I know
think what my friend is trying to say is
you're coming off a little racist right
no front plate you said that before but
it just it's coming off a little great
okay okay do something man I'm sorry
okay okay take it don't take the ticket
now we have to pay it tell we're not
gonna do it deal with it in court either
that or I can tow the vehicle what's
your choice you know what we're taking
the court we're taking what say the
court
look in theory this sounds great but I
don't know how this actually works that
we need a lawyer right do we know a
lawyer my family owns a landscaping
business okay noted but absolutely zero
help before I drop down at college I
took a class at business law did you
pass no why don't you represent me you
can represent me let me go win this case
I know pictures no no pictures no
pictures that's a second camera
[Music]
good afternoon your honor my name is
Officer Capelli the reason I gave mr.
Paul a citation was for several reasons
number one he was parked on this
sidewalk with his VA you're a lie and I
can prove that to you right now I am
here today your honor to prove to my
client loking Paul aka my best friend
[Music]
innocent Your Honor you might know that
my client is a well-known YouTube star
you might not know that he is also
colorblind Exhibit A Hey
very touching video I cry every time but
anyways if you take the color of the
street and the club the curb you can see
the two are very identical therefore
someone with any type of colorblindness
would not know the difference between
the two therefore my client Logan Paul
hide the pork on the curb and he is
innocent is the rest of the Internet I'm
totally sis
[Music]
I'm not gonna lie Logan it's not looking
good Oh No hey parking tickets well
Logan is your lawyer and your best
friend I got you okay thanks man
can we call the girlfriend could we take
our friends and testify mark donor used
to be roommates with Logan Paul correct
yeah I was unfortunately and when did
you stop being roommates with Logan ball
oh geez probably year year and a half
ago can you explain to the jury who
logan Paul's new roommate is you yeah
god damn I like to call one more witness
to the stand Logan Paul
and pledge allegiance to the flag of the
United States of America to the Republic
for which it stands one nation welcome
Paul do you mind telling everyone how
big your tires are yeah my tires are
about 40 inches inches let's bet big for
big time time big ascendency no that's a
fact we live in Encino big tires is it
possible that my clients tires we're too
big for that curve yeah without the oh
that's so that's why I've been saying
the curb was simply too small for my big
big truck the car is just too big for
that tiny curse all right load gang that
is today's episode with best friends I'm
not gonna lie I'm pretty salty right now
so please do me a favor cheer me up
hit that subscribe button enjoying the
view strongest family on YouTube what's
that f bro hold on honey what are you
doing have a good day gentlemen
[Music]
[Applause]
you