a long time since I've been taking
people on my ear Clara aircraft with
gloves and a bat you filming that yeah
okay good that's the pilot guys we're
about to hop on a private jet to Vegas
as you can see I got my boxing gloves
right here because guess who else is in
Vegas you guessed it my dear friend and
also my new opponent JJ / ksi a oh good
morning low gang Babu first off before I
get started if you're not a part of the
low gang make them look bad we are the
strongest family on YouTube that is a
fact my job is to distract you from your
busy lives we all got busy lives right
so I'm the sweet and detainment here
here we go by the way good morning
nothing like vegan doughnuts and a
private jet to Vegas to get your day
started but you guys know this kid
chance I you call me out in a boxing
match y'all saw ear subscribed the other
day had my friends hand-deliver some
maverick Mertz to ks eyes house I
figured he'd appreciate some of the
hottest merch in the game that you can
get now in Logan ball that got a shot
free shipping for this week only but he
wasn't home he um he's in Vegas right
now straining at the Mayweather camp
which I trained in a month ago and a lot
of people have been asking Logan is the
fight going down are you fighting ksi
I'm not gonna lie we're having issues
with the contract what's the deal
manager Jeff chaos eyes team thinks that
he's more valuable than you hahaha so
our teams are kind of classy right now
in deal points in my mind this is pretty
simple
5050 he's a huge youtuber in the UK I'm
big in the United States
seems like it should be pretty easy to
work out if they're being a little
difficult and as you can imagine he
thinks my team is being a little
difficult actually he texted me the
other day and he said your team is and
not replying properly sort this out else
this fight isn't happening and I'll
fight Adam Sala who is Adam Sala first I
actually have no idea why would you turn
down the biggest fight in youtube
history ever it's just dumb bro I think
he's scared of you right he wants an
easy fight yo JJ you scared bro no
reason to be scared JJ I've never boxed
really in my life
the point is we can do the chat in the
hubbub in the talk but I figured if I
just approach him in person and handle
it and try to close the deal write that
in there while he's in the United States
right because he's not gonna be here
forever he's like an hour flight away we
hop on the PJ find him I actually know
he's training at the mayweather gym from
1 to 3 p.m. got that inside scoop [ __ ]
I wanted to get like a real-life
contract Your Honor we decided to do
this last night so this is the best
thing we got my contract lookin ball
versus ksi day August 25th and on the
second page it's actually the same skin
thing honey the third one's the best
it's the same thing just smaller okay I
really hope he doesn't actually
[Applause]
daddy's oh go on the real though this
that maverick like like who's doing it
bro like I want to get stuff done so
imma go handle it I I'm so curious how
he's gonna react and plus he's training
right now so what if he's like pissed
and like tried to throw punches at me or
damn bro it could go down this is gonna
be crazy
[Music]
I'm also curious and ksi is YouTube
video the other day you guys saw it was
called like training with Floyd
Mayweather or something he made it seem
like Floyd Mayweather is training him
while he's in Vegas it's gonna be
interesting to see if Floyd Mayweather
senior actually stuck around to Train
ksi because I bet he did now this new
song many others kind of bang ok I'm in
the zone y'all think I came unprepared
we got the custom maverick boxing Oh
y'all know where we had is we got the
maverick bird on the leg then that's an
arm I mean thigh sometimes to get my
appendages nicked up on the back
hopefully JJ still training yeah that's
right you gotta come with back up bro
they call him the Great Wall obviously
after the Great Wall of China man is big
stuff does go down I got you back though
yeah
[Music]
so bro I came here to close a deal oh
wait what's that light you turn buddy
was a sweaty why don't you want to fight
me right now yeah you've gotta get
better you gotta give the gym who came
here to close a deal
you came here to close the deals let's
close the deal all right let's close it
over all right good you got the contract
right here for you all right it's that
ass contract
oh no it's easier I call your team each
other 5050 Hogan calls ksi our sweet
[ __ ]
in the ring start training oh because
I'm coming in hot
yeah somebody's got to do it yo yo yo
look up now you gonna be looking up
before sleeping just like your team is
right now we're hiring
some weight for your house by the way a
lot of it's my man's meal okay let's do
what though yo I think the fights off
yeah I'm good yo I'm just why is he so
why is he so chilled why he's literally
training at the mayweather gym he's
watching with that wow I thought we'd
get in there and he'd like me he made it
like a joke like laughing down like oh
my god he caught me catch sitting on my
ass I'm truly disappointed seriously I
was looking at this kid he's a youtuber
we like trying to learn how to box he's
not the challenge no don't call people
out like ah that's how you do it though
you come handle it like a man bro like
do it do it that's that's what's up baby
we do it different he didn't seem happy
about me dropping the merch off at his
house but it's okay most of it most of
it was woman stuff and I told him it was
mainly for his mom the Train like he
fights just relaxed too lazy this is
literally almost identical to when my
brother Jay confronted his brother I
don't know what it is about these kids
where they're big over the internet and
then you approach him in person and this
happens now come on dawg
you know what you wanna post me talking
to talk walk the walk I'm very
disappointed in what I saw
I'm feeling a lot of things right now
excitement tension savagery but mostly
disappointment I walked into the
Mayweather gym expecting a fighter a
champion someone ready to handle the
situation like a man but all I found was
a scared youtuber who calls himself a
boxer sitting on the couch like a sloth
during his training I smelled the fear
in him I saw it in his eyes
now as I fly back to LA I hope JJ honors
his handshake in the fight goes down in
August
I also hope he gets off the couch and
watches that bandana that he wears every
second of every day of his life because
it was smelly I would know my nose was
right next to it now it's time to end
this cheesy voiceover on one final note
JJ challenging me was the biggest
mistake of your life you big dumb dummy
haha whoa gang I love y'all
[Music]