Oh goddamn if you thought the last press
conference was a disaster this one was a
major disaster but I always start off on
a little bit on the lighter note what's
poppin low gay if you guys have not
subscribed yet make sure to hit that
button and also if you are a fan of ksi
first up skin good bro check it off by
the end of this video there's a good
chance you might not be anymore so y'all
are more than welcome to subscribe to
hey about a week ago when our friend JJ
was busy doing what he does best team
Paul was showing up and glowing up in
the beautiful country of England
[Music]
you guys don't look like it from around
here are you - the Paul brothers yeah oh
yeah how's that run gorgeous baby here's
what you do you get off the plane you
gather your stuff you clean up a little
bit and then you go for a run
kind of like breaks up all the rust that
you developed on the plane feel it like
a chance right now just curious what do
you think of que si a maverick is
someone who is like super independent
does their own thing believes in
themselves believe they can conquer the
world it's the Hat right here
[Music]
so I don't know about I don't know about
you Jake but I'm definitely I've said
this before I'm over at the talk man
like bro none of it really matters it
does anymore the vibe is different like
yeah we're gonna put on nice ass suits
and look sexiest but last time as you
guys saw flashback
[Applause]
it was hype it was so I and then we
realized the only thing literally left
to do just beat the [ __ ] out of these
brothers yeah okay I'm just over the top
man and then my whole mood about it is
just for this face right here not really
much to say wait we got ourselves a
crowd oh my god yo do they not get in Oh
[Music]
British fans are crazy these guys are
going nuts like in America when everyone
screams ksi it was still like joy in the
voice it was like ksi okay these guys
are like cool and holy ass I was right
so Jake went on stage first to talk with
a [ __ ] boy Deji and I'm watching from
the side and I'm like holy SH this could
get like really violent these fans are
crazy
it's
like they were throwing water bottles
that were completely full someone threw
a paper airplane at Jake when he was on
stage who knows how pointy the end was
catch one of those to the eye and that's
a man when we try to get out they were
kicking our cars the gold rolls and the
gold Bentley kids were like climbing on
top of buildings in
[Applause]
at one point full paint cans were being
thrown yes full paint cans
who does that so I killed someone I'm
just saying it's dangerous out there
hunched in the back of the head my dad
did he deserve it maybe you can see at
one point at one point the press
conference he took my mic and I was just
like what the Phaedo how is no one
wrangling this man back
but whatever but still I'm joking he did
not deserve don't don't Sucker Punch a
55 year old man that's horrible sad no I
think that dude did get tackled by like
five security guards after that anyway
so then I'm asking myself why what what
made these fans so aggressive and so
violent and then I remembered daddy told
them to be go out and find if in London
its to do to me okay we'll shake you
twist the light believe it that's what
we do rest in peace dokin in a pool
that's what I'm saying rest in peace do
what you will do what you want to Jake
pool pool I'm pretty sure this is
against YouTube's policy for this exact
skin reason
[Music]
anyways it's my turn I get on stage and
as you can see by my face I'm like I'm
kind of already over it ksi comes out
wearing the blonde wig I thought that
joke was used in the last press
conference but apparently we're
recycling content okay I just feel like
you should have maybe stuck with the
bandanna so he gets right into it and he
makes a joke about my scene being cut
from Baywatch oh you watch get the pole
and still not end up in the final movie
pretty good joke I'm not gonna lie he
got me good there but again I saw you
tweeted about this already like multiple
times I guess I just was confused I
didn't know we're still recycling
content but okay
but apparently JJ song made it somewhere
in the movie which is I mean that's cool
movie I feel like maybe that's why I got
an 18% rating on Rotten Tomatoes and was
Dwayne Johnson's worst performing movie
ever and in hindsight I'm kind of glad I
got cut
everyone has my back I know it has holes
besides your Ludacris mole disgusting
delusional giant it's so crazy cuz I
just thinking back I feel like he said
the same thing in the first press
conference no one has your background
besides your Ludacris bone
I won't be honest with you I thought
sitting there at that table I thought my
dad in case I were about to go at it on
stage he's standing there on stage he's
yelling you could see like the veins
popping out of his neck even more than
my Shafi neck like bro look at this
thing right now that's just crazy so at
this point I'm like holy SH dude I don't
think he's gonna shut up and then he
brings up my testicle joke which is by
the way my testicle joke no hey hey hey
it's my testicle joke so let me tell you
about my test how is he about to roast
me with my own joke that I've made very
very public I'm missing 15 percent of it
are we still recycling content Wow these
brothers sure are creative but whatever
man so I'm thinking why it is just so
one-sided why did the moderator let JJ
talk for five minutes and 20 seconds
straight yes I timed it and why are we
not talking about the fight and then I
remembered holy asshat this dude's King
hates me bullying poll this kids a big
an youtuber America just a douche bag
joke why he's not hurting anyone you
know he's a [ __ ] idiot but who cares
he's not hurting anyone while those
things may be true and you or anyone is
free to have whatever opinion they want
about I just don't think the moderator
of the press conference the person who
should be neutral the person who should
be the one driving the conversation
should be a Logan and Jake ball hater
skin pits bro whose decision was that
and he's the one who actually reminded
ksi to call Jake and I out after his
last fight because if you guys remember
ksi literally almost forgot you said
before this fight you have something
planned is there anything you want to
say to someone out
you said you wanted to call someone out
there boys
they're freaking boys bro and hehe
moderated the last press conference case
I had with Joe Weller and he knew what
he was doing then he was able to keep it
going he's even said it himself reacting
to the LA press conference
Shannon's lost it here like no one can
get in worded like as the media you have
to tell people when it's their tokoto
this is just it's gone please please
take your own advice you hypocritical
douche asaurus rex apparently not
Spencer apparently not look so there's a
reason I walked out there's a reason I
keep saying I'm done with the talk I saw
it's awful Daisy it's all Fugazi none of
it matters that literally the only date
that matters is August 25th and the more
and more I mature the more and more I
learn and I'm seeing this now this is
why I'm like kind of falling back from
the talking ksi you are the exact person
that I am working hard not to become I
made an unforgivable mistake back in
January and no one is ever gonna forget
that that is a part of my life now I am
the one who at the end of every single
day has to look in the mirror and ask
myself what the went wrong in my life
where I thought that was a good idea so
the further and further I can get away
from the Logan Paul who did that
atrocious act and thought that was a
good idea the better and you'll probably
make a response video talking about the
forest and how disgusting I am because
that's kind of the only route you can
take right now but guess what bro we've
all heard it we all know we all know I
was wrong we know I felt the difference
is every single day I am working hard to
craft a better version of myself and you
are not
for example ksi I did not want to take
the low blows I did not want to get
personal but you bring it on my
girlfriend you got a girlfriend now
Chloe Bennet
what's up babes
[Music]
where we're at so why don't you
introduce me to are apparently you only
have 85% of your testicle let me give
her the extra 50
let me show so a real man
[Music]
yeah man you ever consider that maybe
she doesn't want that
in fact after I sense this becoming an
issue after you said this about Chloe in
your last video how's he gonna go down
on you a busted lip
I'm sorry Chloe but after the 25th of
August he liked your prostitute maybe
not I mean before the London press
conference in my what was a mature
attempt to handle this professionally I
had my team send your team a message
that I know for a fact was personally
received by you a message from Logan
keeping this offline as to not cause a
huge whirlwind that destroys everything
we've been building the past four months
ksi his comments in his video today
regarding Chloe and her sexual
relationship with Logan resemble an 18
year old ksi who sexually harassed a
woman at a gaming convention and lost
his Microsoft deal a situation that
we've decided to stray away from and
contractually agreed not to mention but
quote-unquote you're gonna have to
you're like a prostitute
is a bit far considering what I've
chosen not to bring up so JJ can keep
his EA deal in YouTube red show etc
trying to keep it professional and not
make an entire YouTube video about it if
he wants to keep hitting below the belt
that's fine but I think the
repercussions will hurt all parties
involved
thanks to 15 but you didn't listen JJ
and that's why I'm not going to sit
there and talk about your disgusting
sexual harassment issues in the past
today I'm with
massive tits where have your tits gone
where'd the God because I can't see them
not big enough what are you doing Oh
fingering yourself pardon what I'm being
nice to you
your sister Casper what's her name
Teodoro my door they explore cuz I'm
gonna explore her purse she's gonna be
like you know I need that black all up
inside mouth all up inside my suit oh
wow I want him to blow his mind
I think that us girls need to kind of
stand up for ourselves
you talk about my girl like she's a
piece of meat but you know women have a
choice right you know sometimes they
don't like those comments and I feel
like you should have learned that from
what happened six years ago you know
what I'm talking about right when you
lost everything because you were
disgusting towards women it still hasn't
changed six years you're still doing the
same [ __ ] even when I warned you even
off-camera when I tried to make it clear
that this was going somewhere I did not
want it to go how do people not know
about how do you have a brand deal with
EA or any big brands for that matter and
post Malone I'm just wondering this is
the guy you want to walk out with my
girl is not an object she is a real-life
human being not a girl who gets passed
around to the dude with more ball
percentage however when it comes to the
objectification of women I'm not even
sure I have room to talk as I have been
guilty of this in the past specifically
with my music video no handlebars
[Music]
[Applause]
it's got 42 million views this type of
content no longer accurately represents
my brand and the person that I am
becoming okay so this is no handlebars
I'm going over and I am deleting it from
YouTube
BAM is gone this year I'm learning from
my mistakes
and honestly JJ I'm disappointed that
you haven't for six years so please stop
objectifying women especially my
girlfriend I actually did a face-to-face
with ksi
but this kid literally looked me in the
eye and told me he was God g.od God
that's where his head is that right now
I wouldn't get in the room I'm an animal
I'm a dog bro there were two of me on
the gold you're you're a god this is
what God looks like Jesus Christ we got
some work to go white woman what my son
toast he believes it this is crazy
although I would never ever proclaim
myself is God
I do recognize this type of behavior
before JJ you are me moments before I
flew to Japan I know this type of
pretentiousness because this was once me
you're getting too caught up in the
media the money the views the clout and
you cannot see the train that is coming
from behind you but even when I thought
I was just last year and I was sitting
on my high horse I would never tell you
that I would force myself upon your
girlfriend are you so insecure in your
boxing ability that the only insults you
have are attacking my friends and my
family but dog it's a little too late
now because there are no press
conferences and the only day that's left
is August 25th and you my friend are a
stepping stone for me to get better
[Music]
the fight is available for pre-order on
the new channel the link for that is in
the description it's discounted in July
so by that huic if you're not a part of
the low game make sure to subscribe hit
that button join the fam BAM and lo gang
I will see you next time take it easy
fam peace
[Music]
when we left they were kicking our cars
they were climbing on top of bill my