yeah hate to see it
you just hate to see it you know when
you [ __ ] up and you're like clearly
wrong and you're like back in a corner
and you're like yeah yeah we got a
classic case of ksi what's good low gay
guys if you were not subscribed make
sure to do so joined the strongest
family oh my god I am bruised and also
yokai but bruised look damn bro never
whisper look at my body okay look at my
neck that's exactly what happened you
guys saw the last video where I like I
don't even want to say rekt or like
destroyed ksi I just took his his mask
off and let people know who he was like
there was no like a gotcha
it was just like now you're you're you
were a piece of [ __ ] and you still are a
piece of [ __ ] and I will say this a
thousand times you guys are growing up
with me in the past I've done some
things where I also was a piece of [ __ ]
but every day I look in the mirror and I
say how do I not continue to be a piece
of stuff how do I grow up I want to
mature with you guys I want to become an
a doll a full-fledge a doll anyways
before we dive in I'm going to take a
second to plug the hottest softest merch
in the game unfortunately as you know
it's almost back-to-school time so a
maverick backpacks book bags these sons
of [ __ ] are 15 to 20 dollars this
week only no real talk that's this fire
so swoop it while you can also we just
dropped the fight merch yeah the
Maverick boxing team is fully lit so uh
copies of a baggie they're on sale again
this week only and grab some fight gear
while you're out enjoying the Maverick
movement Logan Paul icon slash shop or
link in description so anyways I oh boy
would I start when I posted the last
video urging our friend Jay Jay to
simply it's it's very simple I just want
him to respect women and especially my
girlfriend because I asked him politely
not to bring her in all this drama and
press I thought to myself how will he
respond will he take the L or will he
make a feeble attempt to respond well
folks he it shows the latter and it does
not give much feebler this
was a terrible attempt I tried to knock
my credibility oh this song there's so
many things I don't even know how I
don't even know how deep I want to take
this role
cuz I could I could destroy he didn't
just kind of stop here like it was the
worst response ever that I've seen in my
life I wasn't saying that Chloe's
crossed it oh my god let's start there
let's start there
no it's Adam explains my blog I'm
explaining why God try to explain what
he meant by telling me I'm gonna have to
my girlfriend like a prostitute might be
the best thing I've ever heard in my
life okay so just to clarify I am not
calling Chloe a prostitute I'm just
comparing to the fact that usually you
can't kiss prostitutes okay I'm not sure
I heard that right I mean if you listen
to that one more time that usually you
called kiss prostitutes usually forget
that you're talking about me going down
on my girlfriend but usually you know
just got a PR team in the house we got
Mike over there it was got Spencer
sitting over there howdy guys my PR
teams really helping me with this
usually you can't kiss prostitutes and
after I bust up your little ogen you
won't be able to kiss her either ah
manipulation on its finest ha ha ha I
don't think so I think you're doing that
right now
okay let's address this clearly I didn't
tell the audience to change you can
clearly see me signaling that it's not
me doing this maybe instead of that hey
guys that's Logan's girlfriend and he
told me not to disrespect her a week
prior to this press conference could we
cool it for a sec I feel like that's not
a hard thing to do or say so you can't
hold me accountable for this because the
audience did it on their own accord
interesting so so interesting because
from my angle it looked like you were
like jumping up and down and like
cheering with them just it's just a
classic method of manipulation if he
felt so strongly about it why didn't you
say or do anything there and then let me
show you what that would look like no
she's not she's not a host she's super
talented in a seat and has a bright
future has nothing to do with me if she
made that video and you knew how she
felt about the way females were treated
I feel like it almost makes it worse
that you would continue to say these
things I think that us girls need to
kind of stand up for ourselves I'm gonna
explore her purse Oh some oh oh the hole
is getting deeper when I made that video
with Cosmo he and I knew that the
comments I was making were joke okay I
don't know I just I wonder how that
conversation went
yo Casper dude I can't make a ksi voice
hey cat hey Casper in this video mate I
think I'm gonna talk about penetrating
your sister horribly okay um well why do
you think that we should do that I just
think would be so funny it's like I
can't do this thing woman the point is
this stupid I spoke with an apologize
and it was all sorted
then huh wait wait wait singing was it
or did you just like tweeted her but the
point is I just I just still don't feel
like you're right and she made a video
yesterday talking about this titled
breaking the silence in the video she
said chaos I talked about me in a
derogatory and sexist way and I tried to
be okay with it but I'm ashamed of it I
cannot believe I'm saying this but Thank
You keemstar I know what you're trying
to do and it's a shame because you're
young personable fans I'm going to fall
for it my young and impressionable fans
are also you're young and impressionable
fans YouTube in general has a younger
age audience and second off I think
anyone can watch my last video your
video in this video and deduce two
things one you are wrong which is fine
if you were to at this point be like I'm
wrong I'm gonna do better in my future
which you're not and - you're asking
idiot it's fine due to stop and make
mistakes to get better oh oh he looks
nervous in that clip he's like tapping
the desk and stuff you mad bro for
simply making a joke about your lack of
testicle oh no see this is what I mean
his spirit is simply breaking and it
sucks cuz the fights in like 25 days or
so listen to the way he laughs at the
end of his sentence testicle testicle ah
it's just such a sad laugh you hate to
see it go
by the way you can pre-order the fight
now link in description KS Ivy Logan
also maverick backpacks 50 ok fair
enough if you want to delete that video
but if that's the case then you might
want to probably delete this video as
well this is it here's the the old
classic bait-and-switch bank this is
where he's like no yo yo i'ma be honest
that girl was my friend I feel like you
didn't know this girl I see what you're
saying 100% and like I addressed in the
last video however when it comes to the
objectification of women I'm not even
sure I have room to talk as I have been
guilty of this in the past everyone
knows that you good job
digging through hours of my content to
find three clips man real round of
applause for you there ksi this is case
I try to find dirt on me come on
I think it's for five minutes
[Music]
Mike being from the UK what do you think
what you think yo dude its are you Chloe
we're making a video you're any now oh
wow okay let's wait we're almost done
we're just looking at my old YouTube
content trash yeah I was at work all day
I work on agents of shield maverick
backpacks some fifteen twenty dollars
this week only get your furniture but
before I do that the point is this I'm
gonna get deep here we have all made
mistakes in our past some more public
than others and some more severe than
others or in stupid as well is for my
case for example but what I'm urging JJ
to do and what I have been doing for the
past seven months is I've removed myself
from the tunnel vision of daily vlogging
is to realize those mistakes pinpoint
them and ask yourself what can I change
in my life to ensure that that does not
happen again or in my case make sure no
one [ __ ] up the same way I did ever
again and I'm not gonna lie it took me a
bit to realize the consequences of my
actions but unfortunately for you JJ
time is running out it's going tick tick
tick on the clock and you JJ are going
to learn the consequences of your
actions on August 25th when I am going
to
remove brain cells from your head which
isn't even possible because you don't
have any like' and subscribe' [ __ ]
this week only Logan Paul that got /op