okay long story short our limo ride here
our limo driver made it very clear he's
always wanted to do the dream racing
like that's how much it was so we're
gonna invite him he's a stranger I've
never met him his name is Goldie cool
name could you race the cars with us
would you want to race the cars with us
right now I don't think I'm allowed
well what can we call what if we call
the hotel and clear you said you wanted
to try I'm with Logan we're in the
penthouse there so we have one of your
drivers with us Goldie we are at the the
Las Vegas motorcycle and bikinis here
and we wanted him to to race with us can
we make that happen to him today
awesome car you want the dream car that
you've always wanted to drive I go for
our wheels we can do that it's not a bad
day at work for gold we're throwing a
Gallardo yeah I'm gonna need you to sign
this so maverick media doesn't get sued
for all my net worth which isn't high
this point because I got removed from
Google's preferred program typically
take me back
[Music]
let's go trap
is it like you say I Drive the limo home
[Music]
I know you told me about you I missed
this house I'm obsessed like I honestly
don't know if I'll ever sell it never
here my friends used to come to do
laundry here on Sunday expensive to keep
for that have you seen whose line is it
anyway the things you can say to your
dog but not your girlfriend I'm gonna
give you a bath and then a nice bone
dude he was the funniest one high-five
walk out
[Applause]
that's great could not do it any one
golden shovel my god sorry one more time
most users
today
[Music]
Paul makes rounds watch right here
here's the dogs dog thing in the
neighborhood he makes rounds Stream is
absolutely incredible but check this out
he's literally carved a path he's done
so many times he's into the hey how you
doing funny you guys have gifts for each
other why don't you do that to me first
and then I give you my gift so the
Internet feels bad for me and I get
sympathy subscribers I don't know what
do you mean I know it's a good no that's
fine what are you give me your gift
first are you surprised hey stop it stop
it close your eyes close your eyes close
your oh oh you rule my love
I gotta give his gift
kill him with kindness do something nice
even though he's a kid had artists to
drip paint and make a picture of my
brother cuz I love him even though you
continue to make my life a living hell
you make my life Olivia how I talk about
with nice gifts you mean ah he's the one
that gets all the controversies not me
oh that's true and it all comes back on
me mister this is my way of saying sorry
for that it's a picture of you in pain
oh man yeah oh thank you mr. drippy yeah
this is dope actually thanks bro
I appreciate that what I provide and
what he provides
[Music]
we don't have to film it oh my god
$300,000 car completely destroyed by you
I did that I could like wallow in the
sadness of my $300,000 car being
destroyed or I could make some dope-ass
content let's take him for a drive
around encino yeah what could go wrong
ah I'm sure this is safe right
all right Mike somebody's gonna get this
on tape I bet that's funny that's a good
joke all right let's do this
I'm sure it's safe I'm sure everything's
gonna be just fine
oh no we probably missed this ticket oh
no we don't find ourselves in a sticky
situation
[Music]
hey guys do you like it go right wing
that I can spit one time
[Music]
this is so stupid this is definitely not
good for the car
hey yo be a maverick JV and the truck is
still intact the Yeti baby Yeti is still
holding up we did good we did real good
except mom and we have to take this tape
off before it chips all the paint and
then really does destroy it got another
vlog give you another part of the logo
make sure to subscribe and do me a favor
stop being normal
stop being average and be a mother
posting math brick looking for that cop
/ shot or link in description I love you
and I'll see you next time
[Music]
you know that was made for this