you know it kind of sucks with all this
new like jungle stuff Kong could leave
at any second like we'd never find him
did we lose him is he gone we're all on
top of the vehicles today hey Brendan
quick toss in the camera toss it yeah
you got it right hey how you doing low
game with Papa
you got this bang all right hey bro do
it the views from up here sick
unday buddy did you sleep up there
beautiful andis sleeping in the tent on
top of his vehicle I kind of want to do
that bro like put a pen on top of the
cool bus oh no Frank oh gosh he does
this every Thursday morning we have
security cameras over there I can still
see you on the security cameras
oh here's the sign for to do with that
sign handy exact do you know well we
lost rank if you're not a part of the
low gang by the way you can see where we
make sure you subscribe with the
strongest fastest growing channel on
YouTube ever in the history of ever
mankind ever dead yeah don't get FOMO
subscribe for me rope roll that baby as
you guys know this is my new toy my
platinum presidential Rolex honey I'm in
love hey you good bro what are you good
isn't that good Oh
big day April I think I got something in
the mail for you actually
what what are you doing you merge bro
it's no joke dude our stock is rising
every single day honey the exclusive
gold backpack we go oh the favorite
hoodie you still got my favorite hoodie
and you need to give it back cuz the
Maverick revolution is growing you gotta
restock blood why I brought my boy is it
you see you youth joggers bro making
this funnier scoggs still working on how
to go down these stairs oh you love
those the guys who actually fulfill and
make the merch they called me they're
like yo Evans youth joggers and shorts
are in the mail they're gonna arrive
today they're like we don't know they're
gonna fit because the ass might be too
[Laughter]
nervous this might be an actual problem
look at that booty bro yo they made it
around the booty Bo yes it's coming we
just drop these long sleeve maverick
like sweaters so I don't know what you
call this but yo why are you so good at
everything this is so comfortable and
not even just saying that it feels like
just soft comfy duck feathers oh yo and
these look freakin good on you I'm gonna
start here start your big fat neon
hoodies are now available oh this is
ridiculous I love this one the exclusive
gold backpack honey
honey we're just killing now I have
something to show you in the back
are you getting surgery tomorrow yeah
not dirty in the morning cuz she let her
leg is like broken right yeah it's like
how growth watching Kevin think is funny
you like the growth bug Ripley go clean
yes it just never gets all this you know
Zoey's area is gonna be a door growth
blade Brooks is gonna be a dwarf again
it's warm puppy no that's not how it
works
oh my god that's gonna be so cool door
hey lot of good stuff going on right now
trolling I'm just happy in my life my
man so Lee is decking out the back I'm
literally turning it into a jungle check
this out it's the statue you guys know I
love it it's koi made out of wood it's
just a beautiful piece next to the
cement snail shell here with succulents
in it bro yo since what ever come so we
got benches we got more benches what do
you think dude is it comfy it's more
comfortable than it looks I know I
showed you guys this yesterday I just
like I love like aesthetically pleasing
things I took pictures of flowers before
I ever picked up a video camera like I
just loved the way like things look
ladies you see my fat Buddha so Lee how
many people can fat Buddha hold like
five seats sit on his lap or something
cute Andy sit on my fat Buddha lady sit
on my Buddha oh this is our Christmas
photo
oh my god now on a serious note Lydia I
think you let my dog Odie ran away
let's go watch Lou you try to catch go
there you go Lydia you know it kind of
sucks with all this new like jungle
stuff Kong could leave at any second
like we'd never find him did we lose him
is he gone
no do you see it
where is it Lydia let's get a move on it
you know like that it's all fun and
games until your sister loses pump
there's not so fun anymore
checking the cameras to see if you can
see him walk out did you see I was so
confused she saw him and then she's like
he's over there and she's just like
walking I was like oh let's go find him
he's that way he's that way let's go
yeah way to go that are you doing great
well he's so tiny he can go anywhere he
doesn't have like an off button I don't
really know what to do bro my body isn't
like wired to actually handle serious
events I just want to make jokes but
like this actually sucks how did it
happen that fast not only that fast we
were recording the whole thing he
essentially did it right in front of us
yep we will find him you think so yes he
is chipped
we haven't showed you guys yesterday
we'll find him we'll find Lydia just got
a chip installed in here the problem is
it doesn't show you where he is on our
map I think someone needs to call in and
say like yo we know the stalks chipped
and then register him some people eat
the little dogs like this it makes me
nervous can I have my dog back
how you doing hey buddy come here we
have to have a talk you can't run away
the invisible fence guys coming Friday
literally you have one day ere jail Kong
you have one more day that we need you
to behave please for the love of dog
God's behaved not off to a good start
this son of a [ __ ] she was not coming
back hundred percent bro dead sprint
that's why we didn't catch him watch
closely gone dead bro doesn't fall yo
Andy's been probably for this bro you
got bro you brought a gift he brought
[Applause]
[Music]
there's only two of these on the big
width of one you know that we are the
only one in the world I don't think
that's crazy guys this is no joke this
is your head with my hands baby I made
it for you in my woodshop because one if
you're gonna have the ham you need
something to hold them and I thought you
know I couldn't just come to your house
and be rude and not bring a housewarming
gift be a maverick Oh dance the universe
that's a fact the fat cop damn her
children both accounts lash out to my
good friend Logan from
oh this is amazing I think it matches
perfect a hand created this I had the
hand carve this no way oh you put the
leg and you're real handy yo this is so
perfect because I actually have giant
mega awesome massive news right now okay
easy people gonna eat that listen lo guy
here's the news okay a lot of you have
seen my movie that it did last year it's
called the thinny you haven't seen it
first I'll go watch it's on YouTube
Brett I played a character called Blake
reading here's a little preview the
system is down commenced continuing
moment Blake reading is a beast no I
worked out so hard for this movie i
starved myself here's a picture of me
when I was preparing to do the thinning
guys like during that scene like I could
barely breathe out just like so
exhausted a fatigue how think again as
you guys know it's about population
control in the United States movie movie
takes place like 20 years in the future
basically kids take a test and if you
fail the test you die you get killed the
government kills you got to watch the
first one to see what happens but yeah
there's a thinning - it's the sequel
it's called the thinning new world order
and I'm going to the table report right
now so look ok so we're here this B
player there's people there's people
everywhere not important people but
y'all I know for a fact mom right here
is in the low game so he's in the
thinning his name is Marcel Marcel can
you can you complete the following lyric
for me little brother
Genki charter rose
okay I'm gonna stop you right there but
yo you're the man I got a question
Marcel come here bro do you like you
like calm yeah a lot of people like huh
he almost ran away today yeah we almost
lost him would you have been sad yeah I
think the whole low game would've how
you feel about Lydia like you know bird
to hear the bird oh here we go
this thinning baby it's time to do part
two except well I'm gonna don't go ahead
take this movie is not being made by
legendary yes whatever you may have
heard of hey I do Michael
Darius that's the director no don't
worry bro I got it covered
I got a handle I'm the promotion on the
PA I'm the marketing I'm the
distribution company sorry
Marcel c'mere bro can you stand right
here yo what'd he do anyways the
thinning - table read after a good stuff
[Music]
yeah hi so good to see you again
thinning - yeah she walked in like
halfway here's what you missed that
little boy Marcel is his name he broke
he wrote yeah he broke a giant glass
poster yeah I was just telling how you
broke the poster no yeah
it was strategy care to be there anyways
I'll see you brush greasy look Oh what
time is it Eddie Eddie
[Music]
oh yeah you've done it bro
yo this is amazing no this might be the
first like adult meal I've had my look
we got some sort of salad we got steak
we got pasta whoa gagging it's a good
day I'm happy right now okay we are
gonna demolish this meal if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to
subscribe we are the strongest hottest
fastest sexiest coolers your family I
need to maverick so subscribe for me I'm
also you good me I'm a bikini shot the
gold backpack shop D the long-sleeve
maverick teach you everything shopping
for the gold backpacks drop the youth
joggers look at my body it's all fireman
Logan Paul Keim / shopper link in
description the maverick enterprises
growing the revolution of Mavericks is
growing which one of you is gonna change
the world I hope I find out one day low
gang I love you and I was due tomorrow
[Music]
if I didn't do it didn't make it
guess who the title and thumbnail is me
my roommate broke his face