Oh yo he's doing like double agent bro
this is it's rush hour you got to do it
now before you fact 9191 take two guys
I've had some good mornings but today
might be one of the best mornings never
because this is a new thing boss the
plagues what guys little disclaimer this
is not a brand deal we just like
everyone those frosted flakes yeah if
you don't like pop the flakes you're
usually a serial killer anyways dude
yeah it's good morning I haven't had a
morning feeling like this good in
probably 24 hours no coming I know I'm
swearing a lot I'm so sorry for all the
parents whose kids are watching my vlogs
I'm really a good guy yeah you want the
cinnamon frosted flakes this is the
ultimate test here come on go what do
you see life's good today Kong okay see
you later alright no I got it it's in
between my legs
what does it smell like you want to make
anything good what do you think happens
my point like a unicorn grants a wish or
like you're like that too
I don't know bro just like be careful
okay I'm not even kidding frosted flakes
and Kellogg's specifically you guys owe
me so much money for plugging this hard
it looks like gold straight-up gold bro
call me Bruno Mars I'm talking that 24
karat magic in the air shine bright like
a diamond Devon I'm referencing a lot of
pop songs today
here's one you guys may have heard here
Evan help me help you
[Laughter]
uh-oh what did you do you've got to be
smarter than the milk Evans that hard
for you but I didn't cry making me in
bed here's the fun fact guys Evan still
has his like Midwest roots so he still
drinks like regular cow milk yeah I mean
yeah everyone in LA
drinks almond milk or like soy milk
because it doesn't come from animals I'm
not a vegan or vegetarian but I I have
gotten sucked into the almond milk trey
songz a Hollywood dog I bet he doesn't
eat your cow milk yeah he's a Midway dog
got him from Ruston Louisiana he eats up
that milk
[Applause]
what a guy
I think I grew two inches dude me too
bro but in my dick it's cool cuz now my
dick is four inches
honestly that's the next level REE right
there that is some next-level responsive
place
you did get yeah you did good Kellogg's
you did good so here's something that's
been happening recently so we got Evan a
space costume anyone he puts it on his
carpet he feels like he's in space cuz
the carpet is fluffy and it gives him
like the perception of being on the moon
he's genuinely in space anyways yeah oh
you're not in space
no I mean listen while you can't go to
Spain oh oh Jesus
this is difficult while you can't go to
space Evan you can drive a car Houston
can you confirm this I'm not Houston the
other day got these pedal extensions and
we're gonna hook it up to my car and
he's gonna drive around for the first
time yeah today okay guys I don't know I
issued not actually a challenge was
issued to me by mr. Brian Leigh aka rice
gum he said he's gonna give me four
strikes cuz I've been like kind of sneak
dissing him a little bit in my vlogs
I've done it three times and he said if
it happens again he's gonna have to make
a diss track against kind of like drama
kind of like this track so I'll let you
guys make the decision I said if the
Vlaar from two days ago got a million
likes and a million comments which by
the way it's all closed the low games
goes hard bro like you guys never fail
to impress me got bad well guess what
you got it 1 million likes
1 million comments who would have
guessed oh I think you know can you hand
me a piece of this plate Oh yo
have some drama under her it looks like
I got I got one strike left and
according to the likes and comments you
all want me to take that story but I
gotta use it like smart bro I got one
strike left one little sneak dish more
rice makes his distress so keep an eye
out for the snake this cuz it's coming
doulas yesterday you guys saw I told my
brother I was not getting a Lamborghini
with them I know it's sad we had planned
on getting Lamborghinis together and
becoming the lambreaux it just wasn't
the move for me bro anyways number three
on the to-do list merch cannon heat oh
no damn it I spelled hey please don't
have that thing at the bottom
Logan you idiot Oh hate anyways let me
elaborate karna needs you to step back
[Music]
okay so inside of this box we have the
heat oh yeah yeah oh the other side
though what I'm not gonna make a big
thing out of this but this is the golden
maverick with my signature there also in
gold it's known to be the worst
signature in Hollywood not even kidding
my manager says I have the worst
signature in Hollywood look on the tag
here these are the official Canon shirts
1 out of 50 there's only 50 of these and
the only way to get them is if I fire
them out of the cannon at you so I think
later when Evan goes to drive around
will like shoot some merch but yeah I
just wanted to update you guys because
if you see me in real life with one of
these in a cannon look yeah about to
launch the first official t-shirt cannon
t-shirt t-shirt cannon yeah check - I've
got to launch the first for the first
emerge can t-shirt exclusive one of not
for sale for like probably a grand and
eBay bro
mirrors are like a weird thing I'm
looking at this mirror here I'm looking
at me in the mirror one thing I noticed
about myself is like my nose hairs dude
they're actually like quite prominent
like take it out right look I got it
like what's helping me bro I gotta do
something about that
also apparently I suck in shaving look I
got this little little patch here but I
like look at that I want to lose my deal
bro I knew I was colorblind but I didn't
know I was oh I do yep it makes me laugh
when my voice cracks but yeah I can't
talk 150 you good bro surveys given to
me by a low gangster last you
survey I've taken the liberty of already
filling one out you shave Wow and then I
circled down here I tried cuz I did yep
yep anyways yeah I'm excited for this
bro
it's your big that yeah how does this
work bro yeah show you okay so how this
works is the gas pedal goes through this
little slot yeah and then you screw it
on the gas pedal oh right and then you
push it so you can reach yes this is an
amazing bro then you can change the
length with take this screw and it can
light this change yeah put it on it now
yo 2017 is a good year for technology
and innovation indoors here let me let
me provide with light after all I am a
vlogger it's good yeah
normally when I say this I'm joking but
like it is Evans big day this is cool
get your big day yeah is it all look yes
it works no this is dawg oh now the
brake same case we don't need that one
it's all jokes we put the brakes on
although in life we're never stopping
but you look yeah you gonna put your
pedal to the metal
okay so this is it we got the camera set
up here I don't know why I'm doing this
oh wait yes you do cuz that's not this
is the first time I've given you like
anyway yeah after four years of known
each other for years of friendship we're
breaking this breaking our
are you a good driver bro you don't lie
to me not actually get a lot of
compliments how good of a driver these
people like dumb asses like this just a
nose oh stop no stop pause that's called
road rage I get I get easily get road
rage no I'm like so scared to hit the
gas pedal I'm scared that you're driving
we haven't even left the valet and
you're already cussing at people I
should probably put my seatbelt on yeah
so Brendan you being a tall guy and all
has to be great sitting behind a door
Frank so much leg room Oh amazing oh
we're very complimentary damn that's
GoPro in science they call that a
symbiotic relationship
oh yo we're going on the street heaven
we are on the street car on the street
guys this is absolutely incredible
there's cars there's buses so I'm gonna
be honest with you I'm a little scared
so I'm putting my seatbelt on block this
is this is my vlog channel like
everything we do we have to do it like
to the max can you hit like a hundred on
the highway bro easily take a right
thing right did yo easy get so like you
get you get angry quick why do you think
so they probably think a kid is driving
this angry are you okay we are
approaching the highway bro honestly I
think you just go run away you
just go around the car oh oh oh yo he's
doing like double lane [ __ ] bro this is
it's rush hour you got to do it now
before you guys like and subscribe okay
yeah bro this job got me thinking I'm
one of those guys I have to a do it but
like bro he's a coffee I've seen him
wearing the merch LC in his videos
looking good in that may every word yeah
I'm / yeah I'm like still shaking I've
never driven in LA before I know it's
it's not so I think the only thing to do
at this point is to go a launch
exclusive merge Canon t-shirt gun
maverick on the prowl for some low
gangsters bread that we're looking for
you understand
I got the merge to I watched your movie
on YouTube I'm telling you right now
like I see that okay you're so good I
really did you got the shirt yeah that's
a special one shake one of 50 brown you
got it okay little gang that is the vlog
somehow my brother showed up to my house
moving in Joey's now if you were not a
part of the family make sure to
subscribe join the low gang jungus
channel a family how you do
it's your maverick mercs link for that
is in the description or look up all
calm slash shop I love y'all and I would
you want to do my sign-off maybe you
haven't done what do you love you all
that others see you tomorrow take it
easy fab Oh
[Music]