[Music]
girls new vocals on this let me track
this command I'm a human what are you we
actually don't know what kind of dog is
he's kind of a mutt we see like a little
Siberian Husky maybe uh Australian
Shepherd we took a DNA test to find out
what type of dog he is and the results
are in Oh point five percent Samoyed
sixty two point five percent Siberian
Husky yeah twenty-five percent
Pomeranian there's no guy one more call
he's a palm ski this is amazing broadly
you're just like calm but the difference
is you're alive I miss him every day
you know let's put a ball pit in my
house not in my yeah and we never got
rid of the ball so we're gonna so today
we're gonna so today we're gonna even my
pool is missing 50% of its balls
Broly loves chasing balls when we throw
into the pool you could just bow okay
now can I do a belly father balls will
cushion the fall so it turns out that
the balls don't actually cushion your
fault I got a headache I don't how to
make it better though you've seen this
done before but not like this each
rubber band put her on the watermelon we
could put one on my head and then we're
gonna see which one pops first this is
gonna be a long enough brain trauma oh
it's actually getting tight in my head I
got a thick ask although you're my head
starting to hurt this bending turns out
this wasn't that good from a headache
you know like cuz it hurts it like a lot
you gotta be close yeah he's got that
hourglass shape we're close my head hurt
but I don't want it to pop
oh I'm sick of this self-isolation so I
stepped out for a second yeah you know I
got some fish you got a fish in a bag it
just floats around in a bag at the top
you need to acclimate and get used to
their environment so they don't think
Iggy's not into this at all dude you
haven't exactly set him up for success
there's sunken ships all around a broken
barrel you know why he's really really
upset like a penis and a vagina at the
same time girls do vocals on this let me
track this
[Music]
[Laughter]