guys we had a bit of a night last night
brendan is actually still sleeping oh
you wanna be Brendan the great angles
make sure you subscribe if you're not a
part of the low like it I just feel like
that was a little angel ah it's like I
wouldn't go wake up it makes the tallit
out of my head you can't do let's go get
Brandon Brandon oh he must be in the
shower the doors open Brandon is your
penis out his penis is now I'm sorry
about seeing your wiener okay could you
come from the vlog after you done no I
say it jokingly what his wiener was
definitely out if we're still working on
Kong learning how to do stairs buddy
just go around I'll see you later ever
you know how every time I come in USA
you always your wiener out yeah perfect
I need you Aussie Kong came down the
stairs I need you and I need you guys
all know the merch closet is slowly
coming together look at all this
beautiful emerge baby it don't stop he
walks Oh Lydia built this and I also
like how you did this like a cute little
sign like you know guys yesterday you
know be dropped backpack granted we
already had the hottest backpacks in the
game we just decided to drop more the
blue tie to the blue sherbert the gray
sherbert and then if you were youth we
have these smaller ones so that's why I
brought you guys up cuz you're tinier
hey it was a camo camo y'all know we
just dropped bottoms it will be the most
comfortable and you've ever worn in your
life no joke okay anyways Brendan I need
you to my dog it strap how do you guys
think he gets on the middle like he
either has to go up or down when he gets
to that middle like staging area what
makes him think he's trapped halfway
there you did the first alcohol you need
hell and you need Jesus and maverick
merch
now go get you are a walk you can't see
it cuz I edited it but II walk no you
can't see it's not real about it he walk
[Music]
it's that flat Oh
easy with the do one thing for me baby
bit no no no deep breath I want to see
you do it I'll let out okay send me your
location I'm gonna come and save your
ass and the rest of your body to the boy
what to drive my car car's got a flat
tire he's like should I still drive it I
was like the highway especially not the
dwarf the sirens are going on are seven
series
[Music]
do you have a tow truck
no this is crazy I'm starting to realize
why traffic jams are cause it's cuz it's
like us get like stuck on the highway
driving with flat tires and for some
reason slow down what you're the tire
though this isn't a flat tire it's just
a rim dry board that I didn't know is
that bad you didn't know that but still
thought you could just like go to the
store fill it up you could go 22 miles
on a flat ass tire going 50 on the
highway how can I help you I don't know
I have no plan we need a doe drunk I
don't have a tow truck you have like
triple-a or the battery shot assisting
battery like a triple a battery
I know batteries the tires take battery
I was like a helper boy
ska-valanche a roadside assistance
service let's ask these people
I'm a tow-truck you subscribe did you
get your merch anyway we need a signal
the distress call
[Music]
no gang coming through yeah the doors
did it what nothing here we go big [ __ ]
Duke oh I do need help
thank you amazing he tried to kiss your
nipple or something like why part oh
that's what you just said he's like damn
bro I think you're super cool like I
know you my kids know you I bought your
merch last night but you just can't park
oh what a nice guy this is why you have
flat tire
you can't just be putting two
cappuccinos on the tire bro what are you
doing okay so we're not arrested I'm
still alive I'm gonna move the Yeti and
then hopefully we get towed
oh you can't put cappuccinos on the tire
that's why your boss way to God if you
tell the cop that's what happened thank
you for watching my vlog second of all I
want to say the fact of this that I'm
coming to save you from what I'm the one
doing the saving rope I saved heaven
look at look at this great job I'm doing
that car has a flat tire obviously
Gino's on it bro we're not close I'm not
closer with Jake that I don't know this
I'm not closer with Jane I'm not closer
with Jane I'm not closer with Jane what
do you mean I mean I tried to prevent
this he was a little guys low gang I
went out last night and the paparazzi
asked me a question and III knew the
answer but I wanted to avoid the the
questions I was like yeah Jake and I are
close
I'm sorry bruh I'm close with you my
brother I love you no should we kiss no
rule number one bro never talk to the
pop around here's the issue bro Jake you
know this probably making videos since I
was 10 bro I love being on camera I love
it so when they talk to me on my game
but I'm drug crazy she's hot and he has
a Ferrari
do they like have conversations yeah
they like smash of everything that's
going on today look at standing by that
girl that's crazy bro good for him bro
it's all personality never mind
hi listen I'm close to be bro we're
super close physically you have a tow
truck
Oh buddy why did you fire no you're not
I know you know I
you have a tow truck no I had no
information what was going on you're
telling me out of all these kids on team
ten not one of them as a touch
thanks fanatic I'm just kidding guys I
love Jake I'm close with Jake I don't
know why I said that I got a little too
crazy last night but yeah I immediately
regret saying that what I like to do in
my life is like take lessons from things
that specifically I learned I am NOT
going to talk to paparazzi like I love
it I love they're human beings they ask
me questions I don't - just ignore them
like that's rude to me but obviously
opening my mouth they're just much much
worse anyways with Jack I thought you
were gonna kill me
no this is your fault how is this my
fault
do I need to bring up the cappuccinos
again that's not how it happened not to
mention I just dropped my glasses and
stepped on and I cracked them and
they're awesome to Ray Bans
save the day we know that I know I'm
stupid whatever you guys want nothing
feel like now's a good time to say no
Brendan we are going to Dubai tomorrow
guy Dubai we are coming for you don't
forget if you live in Dubai I want to
meet you on November 11th 5:00 p.m. at
the Dubai Mall we are hosting listen
when I say this the biggest
meet-and-greet ever of all time by the
way I'm sorry I'll go over here so yeah
if you're in the United Arab Emirates
you want to say what up to the Mavs or
come see me say hi and we bother yet
Crytek oh damn oh wow good work Evan
that's my boy oh thank you bro seriously
this is like classic example of the low
gang coming together to shave my ass oh
the one should I have my poison maverick
Thank You rose hi let's head over to
West Coast Customs and we made it to
West Coast Customs I forgot um these
guys are working on my cool bus it's
here somewhere
Mississippi oh we're gonna get it back
when we come back from Dubai it's a real
reason that we are here you do trucks
what do you do chair and not just any
chair bro this is like a custom-made
beast you what am I gonna do with the
chair can you like put it on a platform
with wheels and put like a joystick
right here so you can actually just
wheel like big wheels bro like if I want
to go cruising through the backyard and
it get done of course it can get done
honestly I think
one is a job for dynamite Dylan dynamite
daily dad yes I want you to stop my
chair bro is he capable of like this is
like is this is his forte
this is young right like I mean like I
get it like in the shop he knows what to
do I mean I'd vote Stephen Hawking's
wheelchair with something on a Mad Max
oh my gosh that's exactly oh right he's
perfect bro I told you you need to have
more sons okay guys we are back at the
house fun fact this is actually the
first time I've been in this hot tub and
I gotta say Brenda we got a hot tub bro
that's just hot it yeah I'm kind of just
cooling off getting ready mentally
preparing for the Dubai trip inside did
you say your cooling off in a hot tub
Bob Brendan I think about that is
actually so literally as soon as this
vlog ends we have to shoot tomorrow's
vlog like at night because the flight is
16 hours so I'm not gonna have time to a
vlog there and then upload guys do not
forget we just dropped six more maverick
backpacks I hired a professional model
to actually model them for us ah she's
right there Tom /sha portaling in
description horses game and we drop
bottles we got tops we got hoodies the
favorite hoodies sound like I got hurt
yeah and last but not least you guys
remember I did an episode of Logan Paul
versus where I hitchhiked from Vancouver
Canada to Tijuana Mexico the boy was
dropped off in a Canadian location and
given 30 hours to chop Tijuana Mexico by
any means necessary I'm talking crossing
two international borders and I'm doing
it with nothing who's trying to take a
cha South filming show
this is my show always play local
warning 400 miles nothing no wall enough
for nothing the episode is out now on my
facebook at Logan Paul or I'm gonna put
a link for that news and check it out
like it give it a share low gang I love
y'all I will see you tomorrow which for
me is actually gonna be in like 30
minutes
I met mine
I'm an my pride
[Music]