I ever take a step
[Music]
Hey oh good morning okay I'm sorry guys
I just need to wake myself up today's a
big day not cuz the coiour looking
beautiful good morning and not because
there's a creepy dragon in my pond where
did that come from but because it is my
my roommate Evans birthday yes Evan aka
dwarf Mamba it's his birthday and not
just any birthday guys it's his 21st
birthday oh my gosh on my 21st birthday
I so it's a big deal I gotta get this
kid a gift I love him oh hey Mike good
morning well it's my house so I usually
get my couple morning Johnny time to
that Mike it's time to work out anyways
guys if you're not a part of the Logan
hey what's up I'm Logan Paul sure you
know that hey Daniel
what do you think about that Logan I
think he's a great entertainer and he
deserves everyone's love Wow
thanks Mike anyways what yeah do
yourself a favor smash the subscribe
button put me in the thighs and join the
strongest family on YouTube that's a
fact
I'm out here every day except like two
days ago giving you guys content to
watch distract you from your busy life
and hopefully make a little bit
boy I got yoked in that merge yeah if
you guys haven't yet and I'm not just
saying this just to merge the Maverick
merge is the coolest softest apparel in
the game look around bro who's doing
this Hogan Paul that cop slash shop now
um okay Mike come here this is your big
moment guys do you guys know Mike what's
up G how's it going I've been a bad egg
lately you know you've seen the news
I've been making some horrible decisions
and team maverick decided to bring in
essentially a babysitter someone who's
like still a kid and I who I respect but
also that kind of has a brain and that's
Mike hey guys doing I'm here to make
sure there's no more mistakes anytime
that I go to do something I shouldn't
cuz like I can't really even be trusted
with myself anymore
no more mistakes I'm working on it right
but Mike's gonna make sure that no bad
things happen there's no more mistakes
pretty much anything like irresponsible
or that like shouldn't be on my vlog
channel mistakes
you gotta stop me I got you wrong I'm
gonna be your advisory board a seat belt
if you will perfect okay here's an
example hey guys it's me Logan Paul
about to smash this play it's gonna be
crazy
yeah
[Music]
oh no more mistakes
no more plates okay no more messing up
okay you guys I'm a loose cannon bro
what can I do
there's no more mistakes okay
first stop of Lube sorry but I just
found it's not mine we are about to go
to the party store we want to get
supplies obviously for Evans birthday
it's the big 21 he doesn't know this yet
it's a surprise we are gonna have a
giant cake yeah petting zoo a petting
zoo a baked potato station we're gonna
do an exotic dancer did you call her yet
also young doggy hi puppy I know
give me your doggy don't get your big
thing okay we look good to go and my
cars now a mess because cars don't feet
exotic dancers called me anxiety
oh yeah could we get you coming at 4:30
it's our friend Evan who's I just turned
21 it's his big day we're set to go so
see you at 4:30
[Music]
[Applause]
we're going in
we need potatoes potato station Oh heavy
loves his big potatoes what are you guys
doing later
how much $700 I'm okay I love you
haven't happy birthday everyone always
let me see we should get out of here
we should leave right now hmm well we
definitely got the cakes covered this is
what I really underestimated how many
cakes we got okay you guys can see we
set the scene here we got big old teddy
bears with alcohol we got Evan
self-portraits we got more self-portrait
straight balling and lastly we got me
and my boy that's me ask my bud just
bonding like men okay 45-degree angle
has definition are you out of your make
that make sense
[Music]
this is the worst
Oh Evan we know you're 21 bro he's just
gonna have you turn to
[Applause]
I realize we've skink suck I'm gonna go
get the birthday boy what my outfit for
tonight Mavs emerge available oh can
fall back on anyway this is our birthday
cake area good for birthday cake why did
you say to wait him there's more oh
you're gonna love this
really feisty competitive if you wanted
to zoo for that this birth is going
great so far
yo M it gets better bro I'm like a lot
better than this so we got to your own I
could really go for a baked potato right
now and we knew that I noticed that all
the tiny plates out oh no no cuz the
potatoes aren't like that big dude he
gets better
yes dude I don't know I
are you security I'm dead white guy
picks on you should do anything no this
can't be good
happy birthday
[Music]
okay weird we're gonna really celebrate
tonight you're not a part of the logo
you make sure to subscribe as you can
see we are the latest family on YouTube
that's a copy maverick March
hottest merch of the game Logan Paul
calm /aa blogging I love y'all I'll see
you tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
you fine bro you guys no one's
crammed in the back seat bro no one fan
is Ahmet ease take the Eddie