Hey ladies waffles 6:30 a.m. right and
early I got my sweet sweet mother I
looking why you wear it all white I can
explain this is day two of shooting our
music video for our song the number song
yeah it's pretty much exactly what it
sounds like it's a song about numbers
now I mean dude it's interesting because
the first shot of the day how do I say
this
your boys dangling from a ladder
dangling from a helicopter like 500 feet
in the air so I better wake up quick
look alive squad it's a big day is gonna
be a good day feel like dangling from a
helicopter might not be the smartest
decision in my life right now guys no
looking we had the incident with my
parachute my main parachute not opening
the other day
and then I had the guy break into my
house there's a kid on my couch and that
room over there who I don't think I
invited over they escort this guy out
I'm just still just as confused as
anyone else a streak of bad luck bet
this has been the worst year of my life
but I have faith that today I will not
die if I do this could be my last vlog
ever so make sure to LIKE and subscribe
join the low gang because we're lit dude
and we make dope songs about numbers oh
you wanted a sneak peek here 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8 Oh guys good news out we did not get
a car accident good job Lydia yeah so
we're here at the hangar you can
actually see the helicopters over there
my only regret is that I'm not gonna be
wearing maverick mercs we're like don't
get me wrong this outfits sick but
hanging from a helicopter is some of the
most Mavericks you can do good thing I
got the diamond pendant yo keep me safe
honey please meanwhile I also like the
gold who's doing it bro literally who's
doing it that's right guys y'all know
where to get the hottest softest merch
from the game looking for that calm
slash shop or the link in description is
just devolving to just a noise well it
hasn't been a word for a while just stop
saying link in description it's just
like yeah if people get it bro I'm
starting a new language enemy what's
happening yeah so we're gonna head to
downtown where we're not going over the
ocean no no there's there's a more epic
shot we're gonna go to downtown
wait stop
solid earth underneath me is over going
over ocean there's solid earth beneath
you like you are sick it's gonna be I'll
be fine
look at this helicopter look at the
camera we need to be vlogging with that
oh my god you want to carry that around
go for it we could do it you know how
much for this camera man oh yeah yeah
we'll stick to this one
let's stick to this one's fine but would
have thought a song about numbers being
this epic it's gonna be a good day oh
he's back she's back she's back that's
right hi how are you looking good I
don't know man I still feel like I'm set
on the idea that I'm a good-looking girl
[Music]
ring you're next to the pulleys and yeah
it looks good yeah seems legit I don't
even know you don't know how to vlog bro
to do this
no way who knows the light is good it's
not that hard ladies casinos in the Sun
I check that it's so easy to vlog you
just every time you see something funny
car zoom oh not that funny when we
compensate by a yo on this camera I'm
beautiful guys I have to sell because
they're not letting Brendan come in this
one okay Byron yo which one you said
Brandon's fat you mean that maverick
backpack available now only on Logan
Paul calm /op yes can't get over a
beautiful
[Music]
I see the blades spinning up top and
going down oh my god
[Music]
[Applause]
Pass future present
[Music]
oh you know the most epic piss ever
I kept it off the vlog but I guess this
happened yeah I did that I just didn't
have anyone to film it might be the most
epic pee ever we got it's done to do
also I just want to say this is really
hard to shoot cuz Brett is not here and
obviously we're focused on the music
video well I guess you're just gonna
have to wait and see so yeah I just mark
it down now in your calendar just be
ready to like this video give it a
thumbs up and count with me baby cuz
it's all about them numbers
[Music]
do you have any idea what it's like to
dangle from a ladder dangling from a
helicopter no no this music videos gonna
be crazy and I hope that shot looks good
because it cost $30,000 yeah but now
guys we are halfway through the day so
I'm gonna grab my redbull here cuz we
have a lot more to do which includes
stuff with my sweet sweet mother looking
beautiful as usual but only cause that
maverick merch you can buy now Logan
Paul calm slash hi guys all jokes aside
these are pink hoodies are actually back
in stock today wow thanks for the
enthusiasm mom you're welcome no thanks
as well as the favorite hoodie but I'm
not gonna lie a little game big deal
y'all know when we do merge drops it's
not just some fufu ashes to you tuber
all I make merge are the barrel it's
actually the best in the game so imma
let you in on a little sneak peak
valentine's day right we're doing
another drop this one's for the ladies
and mom i know you're a lady
[Music]
oh my bro is the favorite hoodie pink
hoodie y'all know I just said it Logan
Paul Becca let's make a music video
oh snap my voice back in character we
look so good it's new bro music hey
ladies John just feel like the song's
monumental one more thing I want to say
[Music]
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 oh no you may have heard
this song little brother jakey try to
roast me what that number song that's a
wrap wrap wrap wrap up my eye so bright
it's not here break it down all right we
did it
hello gang that's the law officially
timer how long was that day since we got
here who knows that's that's an 18-hour
day oh if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe join the
strongest family on YouTube so you can
be well aware when this video drops it's
called the number song be ready to drop
a like on I put it in your calendar and
do yourself a favor bro cop some
maverick more stuff
now wearing at it it's okay mikvah
boomers the hottest Merson game logo
pause icon slash shop or link in
description I promise you you gonna be
better with it on your body and that's a
verifiable fact low gang I love your
nose you too much
[Music]