I'll say good morning little gang what's
poppin listen I know what you're
thinking Logan why do you look so
[ __ ] cool exactly what I was thinking
I know I know why I said it the reason
is guys cuz I hate failing and guys
remember we made a vlog where we try to
jump this jet ski out of the pool we had
some problems who just ran into a walrus
- oh yeah
boy did this jet ski is a piece of [ __ ]
we bought a new or better jet ski from
the same exact guy well at least this
time we upgraded from a piece-of-shit
Kawasaki - and while I'm here I gotta
say subscribe join the strongest family
channel what we are not a family channel
we talk about Dickson's join the join a
stronger one with them strong family
enjoying this fine show let's jump the
jet ski hit that subscribe button
more good news bro after I make this
epic jump we get to do yoga with goats
did I hear yet Andre oh they will be I'm
going to show them where it is or over
there
[Music]
this can't happen oh this kid I can't
deal with this level of light down there
will not be two jet skis parked here and
then I was buying a third but what about
the goats we get to do go get that thing
started and drive it up it is they're
completely I've seen this on the
internet and the goats stand on the ball
I didn't know it was real holy Sh she
came to join us for yoga he made sure
that the goats were gonna be harmed
though cuz she's a vegan as she loves
that and figure out which one wants to
clown which one of your goats is the
most thirsty for followers horse
standing on a rock dream goat yoga goats
in the game why do you think you like
that one more than the other goats seems
sweeter it's nicer while I don't know I
just noticed like oh you say why do you
like this one more than they're like oh
hey guy while you're over here you think
you can figure out how to get the jet
skis to where these who have a major
problem that could be Amanda
she's gonna change from goat yogurt
they're just like us being toilets for
the go
[Laughter]
[Music]
are you gonna make a video on me like
the not a video it's a yes of course
it's gonna be my name if your practice
and porn things to remember
goats will jump on you on you Mike's
been pissed on we're gonna come into a
pose called Child's Pose juniors gonna
let your heart melt though
[Music]
it's therapeutic to me ah it's
therapeutic to me it's therapeutic to me
[Music]
Wow amazing immaculately blue
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay I got it apart
I am Anna you know my back
you gotta raid us at a group out of ten
how do we perform most fun ten your
focus was like - I have a brain damage
so that might do it it's gonna go Yoga
that was absolutely incredible
yeah yes you're really doing it that's
incredible you're like a frat boy Joe
Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe you might
have to get a go if you guys comment
below if we get nine hundred million
comments we'll get a go seems a bit
ambitious yeah I know you do it maybe
this has been a dope vlog except I just
feel like there's one thing we still
need to do we got another jet ski let's
go
I hate myself here we are again I don't
know what to tell you okay if you're not
subscribed normally I'd say subscribe I
don't deserve it don't subscribe why'd
you go subscribe the David Oberg before
I don't want to give up this dream I
really don't so please help me afford
and pay for my dreams and go to local
councillors shop and be a maverick so I
could jump a jet ski out of my pool just
a graveyard of jet skis that don't work
I hate this the good news is we did go
yoga that was dope and I'm going to
Vegas tomorrow with my brother Jake who
I don't know if you guys heard is single
he just dropped a new single called them
singly single okay I love you guys thank
you for watching
[Music]
said you had enough and you're leaving
way too young to be stressing out back
with the fellas now
[Music]