looking at ah guys my voice is almost
completely gone I'm always yelling my
vlogs you know that hey yo good morning
little guy goes Bob today I hate to say
this I might reel it back a bit but
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe family just released a
diss track yesterday take your gifts and
give them back purchase where it has me
check here 150,000 likes in 15 minutes
so poppin okay right now it back that
right I'm just learning how to fly drone
we've attached a piece of meat on a
string they call you got a Los Angeles
ass dog loudly wood has meat broke my
dogs are vegan happy I want to test my
drone skills while Kong chases the meat
[Music]
I can't tell these like barking at the
drone if you want some food
what is my dog suck at being a dog just
again literally the peanut butter is
[Music]
what I trained for many years baby
vegan USDA prime peanut butter for you
cuz you're a vegan Hollywood you're the
best thing about having funny friends I
feel like I heard a splash
yo someone's screaming I think it hit
somebody no bro that was just filming
laughing honey my blogs about exactly
where this when this neighbor calling is
actually ran into her yard twice so
she's cool but there is a difference
between hey my dogs in your backyard and
like I almost killed you so can I get my
jump from your pool
[Music]
Seanie job is to find my drone I told
you it was No Oh No
[Applause]
ah it's a good thing we found it because
the camera's not on today Oh
this close to being the smoothest I'm
gonna give you the favorite hoodie given
Susie the favorite hoodie reminded me
hello gang we restocked some stuff for
the longest time I say and it's not a
joke I say everybody want to be a
maverick it's true literally it's so
hard to keep stuff in supply which
actually might be a good thing make it a
little exclusive but some of the stuff
is back today so if you haven't yet
get your maverick Maher smoking ball
like I'm /sha poorly in description join
the movement baby everyone's doing it
christmas is coming up and I'm the new
Santa Cosmo look I'm the Maverick Santa
Claus now separate note guys I'm not one
to give up easy sure the drone may not
have the camera like who's this hate
still can't fly I'm wondering if drone
doesn't have a camera like is it really
useful not really it's not right are we
just
[Applause]
no way stores I look drone stuff but is
it tough enough to survive a Louisville
Slugger
[Music]
if this thing what did you do the
kitchen always know I clean after I
could Lydia I could your listen we love
and yo if you want to go to the store
and buy kitchenaid thing that's fine but
you're gonna have to grade your cheese
else what did you get me over there a
new drum your own respect respect leave
Mike alone leave before your salted be
[Music]
aggressive Lydia you got into my either
a being in a house full of idiotic mail
testosterone-driven fools is a stressful
thing or she's upset that she's not
actually having a child that said I have
the most fun vlog ever today we didn't
plan on the drum breaking so that took
up a lot of time what guys you know this
christmas is coming up
yeah stack him up lots of lights I want
to clean up if anyone else wants to
celebrate Christmas with lights sorry
I'm taking all of there we go guys
oh this is good fo real it is lit it
comes with lights on it I guess you
could say this tree is pretty I wanna
buy this wreath can you just hold this
box I told you guys in my Santa Clause
this track which you should go watch if
you have it yet it's a fact that I'm the
new Santa Claus
you ever seen someone buy as many lights
what you do is you take the diameter of
the entire scope like he knows math
divided by PI 3.14 six to eight you can
then conclude how many lights are gonna
go on the cool bus I could help you girl
what you trying to do I think he just
baited you into that selfie oh he didn't
I called you over with your song if you
ever wanna kidnap Logan just play a song
out of your van he'll run right into a
joke I'm like oh that's fire was that
next thing you know touching my body no
one watch Christmas with me $1,200 okay
we got a thousand dollars worth of
lights needless to say this bus is gonna
be lit I do have somewhat bad news guys
ah we're gonna do this tomorrow I know I
know I'm blue balling you giving you a
little tease okay anyways guys so we're
gonna work on that tomorrow one other
thing I do want to work on is Lydia's
aggression problems
be more explained that's a thing if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe don't want to miss
this little turn the notifications on to
it all have you seen these videos Santa
dis Jack I know for a fact Santa did not
see that coming what do you do also like
I said earlier copy or maverick merch we
got some stuff back in stock everybody
want to be a maverick award you're gonna
do slash shop or link in description get
yourself or a loved one something nice
for Christmas join that maverick
movement low gang I love y'all I'll see
you tomorrow
qnet take your gifts and give them back
fabric merchants where it's at got the
hoodie kappa put that sailor look in
that you should dreaming about that you
should get my new backpack throw away
that dirty sack sees you when you're
sleeping why you creeping in my room but
he knows when you're awake
who invited this buffoon why you say
black balloon