hey Jay I made one phone call I got the
same house as you same cars too it's
really not that hard
oh hey by the way welcome to the top
little brother feels good huh
but let's not forget how you got here
[Music]
I'm your new puppy call you come let's
talk about your garbage that you call a
song it should be every other day just
some strong advice I made you famous
once it's the bus that happened twice
yeah you want Disney but who helped you
read all your lines me don't forget or
you were my shadow on bus now you've got
a few subscribers and you think that
you're the [ __ ] I'll admit you got money
you got bars you got [ __ ] but you're a
dick you ain't thankful for your fans
it's kind of funny do your investors
know team 10 ain't making any money see
it starts with an Italian but it's hard
when you got none I think you kind of
salty cuz I'm the favorite son I'm a
maverick you're a sidekick yeah I
brought you to a light if there's one
thing you should know the firemen throw
is looking at your face you don't know
when the music low I'm trying to sense
an actor classes do with nothing now you
try to rap
catch the full you can't know the Kim
says gotta I mean that's how you grow
but you still can't sell out any shows
no you still can't find some matching
clothes you're just killing the vibe
you're doing it right
trying to play poet the does you don't
know what you're done you just ruin your
life here you feeling the vibe it you
ain't doing it right trying to play ball
with the does you don't know what you're
done you just ruin your life each other
after all we came from the same
biologically you know that makes us
brothers so much negativity it really
makes me want to like feel like you just
need a maverick shirt in description you
in Sami jakey
it really hurts sometimes I wish my real
brother was darkness but now I gotta go
put you in the dirt go away what hold up
hold up by the music stop those cars
eight Hertz man that [ __ ] was just
loaded gun tattooed on your leg cuz she
knew you were loaded in movies that's
your fans watch with their babysitter's
remote I thought you were my boy yes I
have a baby sister who you're trying to
be a model shoulda kept Niels another
who's the better kisser it's a koala
team ten because you take 10% of your
friends [ __ ] up Jake when the contract
I so does the career it ends that's also
a fact
are you matches cuts you couldn't sign
the toll less smarter than you so you
have to replace them with some Spanish
twins it's everyday bro do you give up a
night on the job
[Music]