[Music]
I'm just trying to wake up guys I just
chopped it I don't know I think the
survey did kick it up good you know why
bro yeah sorry a beauty look at this
merch bro I just got this like I've seen
pictures of you guys wearing this word a
brand new maverick merch and I still
didn't have yet I just got it today
Raghava take whatever I do it is a
little big on you I threw a larger you
but you're looking swaggy
also you don't have to say pick up good
god yes also I just want to say we are
legitimately the sexiest most determined
family on YouTube not I need to just end
on the inner you guys are getting your
merging you're taking the best pictures
I've ever seen for a brand and using the
hashtag be a maverick check this out how
can we all be so op it's not boy guys I
miss them I know you've missed young
Donkey Kong hi poppy how are you Tugg is
more Tuggy ER than ever you're getting
bigger Kong you get more and more savage
every day look at these teeth I must not
bother anybody okay I guess you go to
sleep now yeah yeah yeah look who's here
look who's here bro I'm just kidding I
already answered you know you like
spending booked what might be one of
those fire pieces that we had deep oh
it's been a while row do it peace what's
happening today okay number one on the
agenda now
yeah sort of there are these two pretty
girls coming over er country singers I
think too blonde twins bro who play
guitars musically talented
yeah row the dumpster it's not it I'm
Brenda come back Brenda I we lost us no
they should be here in the say Ayla I
mean oh Jesus
come on bro Evan I didn't mean it Kevin
stop Evan rowdy
okay here fine whatever I will get him
later but anyway
Wow look who's here I wasn't playing at
all anyway oh so welcome to my vlog
channel this is Diamond Dixie hey hey
guys and what did they do oh yeah
eggs Ren discussion but you guys make me
nervous yeah I'm so pretty I don't know
what you do what do you do I don't know
crazy bro thank you music yeah if you
can tell by the hat in the oh are you
from where my late daughter
oh all the way out here I was like right
in Orlando we look like Bob shirt yellow
how do you guys know each other yeah
we're similar your siblings all of us
yeah huh what ages are we talking about
here nineteen seventeen fifteen so we
stand in there over there fifteen but I
tell you six 306 yeah get the hell out
them out I don't support overgrown
[ __ ] manchild here grow old and back
home Jesus you're a [ __ ] talking so
yeah how do I walk around Vince I like
this but can you guys sing me a song
maybe oh yeah really
what instruments you guys got I click
apart I play banjo this is a box I'm
saying again get the hell out of mouth
no Evan Santa Barbara sidewalk
I forget why they're here like I live in
forget says you'll write them I know
they are called Delhi and then still was
able maybe did you have to listen watch
the vlog would be had email around 100
senator isn't awkward to read still is
no song yeah we should oh my god we got
okay how do we know that for sure
guys we could just be assuming yeah I
don't know when do I go out and a bro oh
people are discovering that you cannot
easily get on top of the hotel over
there and I should probably stop
vlogging about it but no no she wants to
buy my merch personally I got a better
idea
yeah ah here we go everyone loves a good
rubber band every and all your pieces
merge merge both know that's kind of a
toss I know for a fact someone down
there is going to record this and report
I love to locate and yo the people that
live in this building and in monitor me
like I'm sorry I love the low game I'm
giving their merch
one little mark
thanks for coming back for your man how
are you
kicked out when is everybody know
everybody picked it up how are you I
think I need one more bit about like
that bro I could easily cut that out
right and make it seem like the one just
made it but oh my god it's time one
anyways how are you good
yeah sorry I'm uh I'll be right here
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah no no what do any
[Music]
[Applause]
I love it
but I'm thinking like the box hey hey oh
you guys didn't know this because you
didn't see the edit yet but that song
reminds me of a very nice friendship a
lot so I I just put a Evan and I montage
that we have to having a shot yeah but
that's what that was I want to sing a
country so I don't you guys know this
I'm a classroom singing then back in my
good pair dream the streets really dirty
comic pickup truck in my Khmer Jean my
can of beans
this worms in the ground I got country
home as well I'm with my child
Wow okay guys back to business so as you
know Evan Brendon Ayla and I are going
to VidCon but we had this idea where I
want to strap harness strap are you good
bro any give you the survey now I think
I do there you go bro we always got one
a day look at you would you mind giving
this survey to Evan hey wait don't
forget the writing utensil second one
what you do no you actually circled one
your son but anyways as i zoom out here
I had this idea that I wanted to strap
Evan on the back of my back know how in
India they ride elephants I wanted to be
as an elephant so that explains it like
this is gonna work bro we just got to
get Evan strapped to the back somehow I
want to put a platform on you having
Evan bro are you good bro you asking
that one more time are you gonna hate me
are you good
[ __ ] is not good right back to business
chair bro let's see we can do with it we
first got to be right down market the
legs are off the chair let's see what we
can make I'm just walking I'm not an
architect or anything so I'm going to
try to figure this we're going to take a
little bit of engineering I did go to
college for being engineered oh you only
made it through one year did you
graduate or did you drop out with like
it's 4.3 what photolyze like to weather
it by weight you can still hear audio
rhododendron I left a minute ago I got a
guy oh yeah bro bro please davon that's
doing maybe try spitting on it first
Ivy League magazine oh yeah is it
working I look outside I'm literally
dying here's the thing for sure here's
the issue we're worried about evident
legitimately being trampled by fans at
VidCon like bro you my boy I can't let
that happen
oh my god
but he hit so hard you know what that
bro you're done fighting me bro I can't
beat you back up I'm gonna carry you
with someone your own size not to
mention it's the next thing to do on the
to-do list number six a line evan fight
to what Jeremy what cleanses Todd Carr
no guys I had a dinner meeting and stuff
my stomach food it was down also I just
can I say I need a haircut I'm aware I
need a haircut I got a mullet going in
the back here as you guys know I'm
shooting a movie Valley your eyes this
is where I'll topic anyways you notice
processor rings will run around in a
circle
managers yep okay but it look kids his
eraser he's going down everything was to
get it is our contender ready to fight
it Brown jr. you ready yeah she's ready
to his title ok now you're eating mac
and cheese I could finish it off for you
no are you ready by tonight male cheesy
for sure yeah why they both just ready
to fight I thought for sure I could be
harder than that
I like Robin what are they fighting with
I don't want to take a look behind me
bro oh how convenient and not set up
with that what's the name of these
things absorbed or you guys are my
contenders ready
I feel like the hearts aren't in this
brown but mine is it is by tonight Rob
Jim we got Abel over here in this corner
within super enthusiastic failure who
you got me how am I going to talk to my
partner he's is Ayla Paola yeah I'll bet
you three thousand Oh
$3,000 I never eat your ass bro I got
$3,000 on you want me to die no I really
care about you liar I just care about my
content
[Music]
evan has that low center of gravity so
what that was actually really funny but
I have a better way to make this more
entertaining I never lose that's the
only thing you go oh I don't know I did
that
okay uh-huh with that said let's go to
VidCon dhis whoa we have arrived at
VidCon image 1 a.m. so let's talk about
this $3,000 that a randomly whipped out
of nowhere earlier hey go Kong can you
watch that thanks buddy sure you guys
know I love doing money drops I love
giving back to you guys the low game
last time I did this I gave away $5,000
I placed $1,000 in random cities across
the United States we did a little
scavenger hunt and then you guys found
them by watching the vlog and so I've
decided to go even harder with $3,000
and place it at one location and vid
class so if you came to VidCon and
you're watching this lucky you dude we
were about to go places money although I
will say there are fans everywhere here
even though it's 1 a.m. so we have made
disguises in the form of paper plate
matches oh god no you guys can't tell
this is Evan right here and that's
Brendan he's right there feel like
you're gonna blow our cover Road you're
an [ __ ] I definitely feel like you
ruin everything
and they'll come back bro come on we got
to do my math use a frown face because
normally I'm pretty happy something
anyways good things me further on bro I
think we're giving up ok we got
we've got some crazy rescue jumpers
money off you got a hydro it's not gonna
be heaven
I don't know that NHP wait a second is
that dwarf mama said no one ever because
no one's going to see through this
matter in the lobby right now who
gorillas on ogre oh my god we're
venturing out into the VidCon wilderness
understand here folks just a couple of
plates walk into the street no one knows
it's a what Oh No look I think it's to
you but it's not Logan yeah I know what
you needed no I just like the matter
okay okay I am going to give you a very
specific clue on my Instagram story I'm
going to give you guys a very specific
loose it has been following that
Instagram around 3 or 4 p.m. tomorrow
I'm going to give you guys like I'm
basically and tell you where the
location is just know and be ready here
and when the story goes live be checking
checking checking Oh get that money
broke ok got three grand bro I'm very
happy that these masks works out it's
not like hey I know that cut didn't make
sense because I've forgotten I'm doing
it again but the money looks like this
it is in this white bag here but yeah
anyway so Logan you know I love you if
you guys have not subscribed make sure
you subscribe because related and I will
see y'all tomorrow when this gets
absolutely insane I take it easy fans
good
[Music]
this is going to be a big dish listen we
dealt how you got the rest