like this oh my god I never thought I
was gonna be one of those people have
you guys ever seen the videos of like
pimples being popped or like sis or just
exiting people's body through like
pressure I think I know where this is
going bro
and Chloe doesn't not look excited first
off this is my dream anytime that Logan
has anything I want to pick at it ok so
here's this because I had bad acne in
high school bad I got very good at
popping pimples very good it was good
right it was actually really good as a
comic not men oh you guys are that
couple that pumps each other's pimples
yeah only one cause listen we're getting
sidetracked anyways I'm good at it right
but there's one person who is much more
experienced and much better than myself
and that person is dr. pimple popper we
drove an hour and a half to come to the
offices of dr. pimple because I noticed
or rather I think you noticed I have I
have something on my back it's like a
little lump assist perhaps or a lipoma
some sort of extremity that I do not
like and that I did not put there it
feels am I one of those people stuff's
gonna come out of my back help
are you dr. pimple popper no you're just
can I literally we're here to get this
cyst
it's a fun life if you're not subscribed
subscribe trust but you want to see my
sis kpop and who knows maybe I'll have
cysts or lipomas in the future to get
pop I want a full human child to exit my
back today you want to give birth out of
my cyst
I never thought you'd ervice I am I
never thought I'd get to see something
in that much amount come out of my bag
I'm one of the weird people like I will
watch for hours
but now like I get to be one of those
people I'm literally gonna be so mad if
like it's like a just like a fat lump or
something like it needs to just yeah you
guys know if you're a nice well you
probably know you pop the pimple and
just Amir just removes extra ball sacks
from people I also need and love my ball
sack I think I think we're in too deep
bro I got to do it she grabs the ball
sack we get out we run with it I
actually have yes
do it who else has things we can remove
from their body just show up to dr.
pimple poppers everyone's getting their
pimple spot oh no I've never touched my
boys oh my gosh that's it oh that's
Wow should we give it away to the
Occident all right guys head over to
Logan Park on flash shop and buy
Spencer's Paolo I feel lighter dude yeah
we say aerodynamic now dude I hope I
make a compilation that's what I want to
do you know like a pimple pop
compilation 'best pimple pops 2018 oh my
gosh
are those really necessary are you I
don't know she's gonna cut into my back
in theory in my head it was it was cool
to be on the compilation no I'm fine I'm
fine what's the cause why do I have it
what that is under there is just a bunch
of wet skin cells dead skin cells Oh
imagine if that sit if you had that for
30 years and it's under your skin and
would it smell like that's like what it
would smell like oh my gosh maybe we
actually don't pop it today and wait 30
years all right I'm going into real-life
surgery right now
yeah okay oh no I'm gonna just do super
Fisher because I really think this is
very superficial it's gonna go quick
it's gonna be like your third baby kind
of thing where it goes real quick oh yes
baby okay okay what's happening
what'd she do you can see my spine show
me up we got your sack this is
everything I've ever dreamed of this is
so amazing Boosh Boosh that did not come
out of my back oh my god you know get it
away from my face I am flabbergasted
right now I'm gonna use a little curette
just scrape the inside just to make sure
we got it all out that's the area that
was in see there's like a little space
right no I don't feel anything is she
doing something to oh I felt something
about aa little pokes oh my gosh that's
amazing
wow that is that is branded there's no
greater joy than having extremities
leave your body and the only way to
describe it is absolute euphoria
euphoria I'm so happy I didn't think
anything was gonna come out it was good
possibly no no absolutely the weirdest
shortest video that's ever been on the
channel subscribe make sure you
subscribe cuz we do weird stuff we do
different stuff in fact we always do it
different that's what's that maverick
lifestyle is about y'all know where to
get the hottest softest merch in the
game it's that maverick lifestyle
looking for that calm /op or link in
description feel like you either love
this video or you hated this video we
may have crossed the threshold where
it's like oh that's that weird funny
cute couple - like yo there's
straight-up
weird like they do but stuff every night
we don't anyways we'll see you guys
next time on the video but
[Music]