hey guys future Logan bad news ksi and
his team they saw the video they must
have not liked something about it so
they blocked the video yes this is a
reupload so we've pretty much blurred
every part of this house okay si you're
killing me bro but you can't take this
one down you silly goose oh yeah
enjoy your merch guys back to the block
alright pause stop right there eh oh
good morning low gang what's poppin guys
we have a bit of a problem so this
morning guys it was like any other
morning I woke up opted out of bed I
brushed my teeth and then I pet my dog
Kong and then pet my roommate Evan then
poured myself a bowl of cereal but I eat
nails the forest razón savage I took a
moment to plug the hottest merch in the
game available now and Logan fall calm
/aa free shipping this week only link in
description let my roommate Evan pet me
then I did a cartwheel and I'm sitting
at my computer minding my own business
and what do I see
anyways guys before I dive into this if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe join the strongest
family on YouTube that's us
we are cool it as but I'm sure you know
of the chaos I drama right like the kid
called me out pull no cap on and there's
a pool I don't care I'm like I I'll
fight you it'll be the biggest event in
youtube history and I'm gonna love that
ass but I see this Floyd Mayweather
thing and I'm like wait a second and you
might have seen it too honey
no honey I just did that literally was
at the exact gym training for the exact
fight all right I'm like what what's
going on how did this boy there's must
have been some sort of mix-up so I
watched this video Logan
Jake and you do this just me and the
mayor of the gym just practicing oh can
I do that bro I gave you that idea I
already did it
I can't believe you said that it's so
dumb I've gone cross-eyed so at this
point I'm just confused right so I keep
watching - OH - quick he's too quick
he's too powerful literally just look
how much that bag is swinging truly
truly remarkable so I keep watching and
they end up talking to Floyd Mayweather
senior when you think of boxing you
think of this guy he trained Floyd
Mayweather Jr his whole life dude is an
absolute legend and he's talking about
how fast he is and someone from KS ice
team had the audacity to say this we
asked young JJ to show his speed and
throw it yeah
yeah big dumb dummy yeah so at this
point everyone's dog I'm like kind of
feeling bad for ginger like you gotta
train somewhere that was like yeah by
the way you suck
no it's sug we're not like ya know I
would not be had following their ergo
therefore what so it's like a transition
were like this like Leslie thusly
thusly he starts interviewing people
around the gym and he the first
interview does he interviews a Jeff aka
hot dog that dude is gonna win okay so I
know pause I know what you're thinking
why why did you call him hot dog guy cuz
when I went there he interviewed me and
he asked me a question that actually got
me thinking this act this blew my mind
no he asked me if a hot dog was a
sandwich help me please it's a hot dog
inside two pieces of bread like it's a
bun they're surrounding like a sandwich
bro it just doesn't know me Jeff yeah
we're boys we had hot dog discussion of
course he was on the spot so he answered
talk what did you kiss
Jeff's my boy Paul's tall he's got good
reach he forgot extremely handsome but
I'll let it slide and then he literally
in front of ksi goes what who are you
ksi what did you kiss again at this
point I'm just feeling bad for JJ I'm
just like did you go to a gym to train
everyone's like like even people in the
US like here Lydia do you know okay I
like what you do with your hair by the
way Lydia she darkened it it's called an
ombre I think I don't know I'm not a
girl anyway okay so then ksi did not
learn his lesson from Jeff and he asks
the same question to Floyd Mayweather
senior
he avoids the question completely and
he's like I know one thing I can beat
that so then they're like trying to tell
him to like say ksi is gonna win right
and for whatever reason why did they
leave this part in the Edit you could
have just like cut around it so the
prediction was right but I have no idea
honestly this is probably the same guy
that said ksi as fast with a Floyd
Mayweather senior one of the greatest
boxers of all time
JJ you got to fire this guy bro he's a
Jewish is the most uncomfortable step
seen in my life oh honey no pop asking
people this dudes clearly uncomfortably
is like yeah ksi no one at this gym even
the guy training you thinks you can win
this way yeah yeah uncle Jeff he's gonna
be working with Floyd Joyce we got to
make sure his hands are ready and then
after that you got to get some rounds in
the body hey guess what JJ I sat in that
same chair with uncle Joey and he also
wrapped my hands always that video not
enough proof literally I still have the
wrap dispenser follow me coming in my
country training with my trainers that
says LP wraps they made me the same
exact dude I can do everything you can
do can do better
anything you can do I can do better it's
true though okay let us continue okay so
at this point it's pretty clear JJ's
been taking hella elves and uh I planned
for this I knew this would happen so a
few days ago my friend Mac was here he
actually lives in London sort of near JJ
and I was like you know I'm sure there's
gonna be a day with Jay Z is like
feeling down order which was probably
when he got clown at the mayweather camp
so I'm coming in like you're walking out
well how can I help how can a chair mom
and if there's one thing I guarantee
nobody's doing one thing that just makes
people feel savage like a boss like
winner is
that maverick merch right so I figured
I'd hand-deliver through Mack JJ a
package of merch it's about to go down
ksi is about to be KS mine okay guys
come here this is my English friend his
name is Matt inside the maverick store
and Mac okay so I also know JJ lives in
London I had this idea right the kids
not quite a maverick yet he probably
never will be but there is hope so I
thought I would give JJ a gift in the
form of the hottest merch in the King
y'all know this we just dropped a bunch
of news we got the white joggers the
boyfriend sweats for the ladies black
and pink for ksi ladies we also got you
on these gray crop hoodie things I don't
really know I'm not a girl I will say
they are very comfortable I would know
I'm wearing one right now
also JJ it's your lucky day bro we just
dropped a new performance shorts I know
you like performing you know you like
short boom with the Maverick on the
snide in both blue and purple the only
way to get it logan paul dot-com slash
yeah but not for you JJ it's your lucky
day bro we'll get you some woman's March
for your mother
no I'm throwing to do a different shirt
because you're not really doing it that
different kind of like every other
youtuber but here you go
[ __ ] you to st. and he was singing that
off the vlog when I'm keeping in there
just to show the quality of our merch
speaking of soft KS I can't forget the
booty shorts oh hi Evan these booty
shorts are nice and pink I'll autograph
their all right thanks Emma we gotta go
with the classic favorite hoodie this is
a small anyway free care package
compliments of LP you can thank me in
the ring after I've knocked you out also
ksi /jg don't forget bro be a maverick
intent the universe just like I am going
to dent your face okay
iMac do it needs to be done I will see
you later no - ksi from Logan Powell
gonna go ahead and seal it here I and
you want to take this picture
[Music]
Wow hi JJ you can put that on your
fridge here we go I hope you opened this
in your channel bro I really wrote a
nice note I bye Mac good luck bro this
cars taking them all the way to London
let's make sure the driver knows all the
way to London for him all right
okay just Pacific Ocean cross it goes by
Mac we love
okay guys low gang I am getting word
that the uber did make it to London is
pretty fast
oh okay guy okay so Mac has actually
picked up another friend of mine his
name is Hayden which you guys know and
actually these are my only two British
friends besides the entire British Lowe
gang of course so we're gonna cut to the
boys right now how you doing boys
so he's just got to care sighs
neighborhood
oh wow
they are extremely British but savages
nonetheless okay let's see how they're
gonna do this
I'm waiting over there he is gonna go in
your bloody tour can't see if you
actually mean frame wall on and then
hopefully we're gonna end up in trouble
hopefully Wow
I have sent some goons man these guys
are bad to the bone - all right my
savage Brits okay guys I think it's
going down just the delivery so without
further ado my boys are about to deliver
maverick March - ksi
[Music]
oh okay there JJ yeah cuz he's a Vegas
yes isn't playing now no play in the
south and you know it makes sense I'm
making this video late but you know he
was gonna be a Vegas this is a disaster
all right let's see what happens is
there any chance you give me a bit like
in this bedroom yes okay that's good
that's good enough I can thank you okay
have a good day thank you okay guys
through my air pot right I've been told
the belly button lint has been swallowed
that's good protein very Rodinia and the
package has been delivered oh thank god
I was closed for problem he's still in
Vegas this video could come out and he
might not even be home huh when he'd go
back home he's gonna have a gift on his
bed waiting for him JJ welcome and thank
you Mac and Hayden my British friends
you guys are Doug's to say the least
- eh sure all right guys yeah that is
the vlog if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe to side the
balls in your court bro you want to read
the note front of YouTube oh no baby
could be entertaining you get views I
guarantee you that his damn youtubers
love views I would know so yeah
subscribe to me if you have not yet
copter maverick Mertz you good y'all
nobody Logan Paul calm slash yeah we're
link in description low gang I love
y'all and I will see you tomorrow take
it easy BAM
[Music]
or your skin like with some angles it
just like has a glow your videographer
Spencer is telling me about my glowing
skin I like that
God you bro