oh man this is dumb fool a nude beach
[Music]
oh good morning okay what's funky oh man
hi how are you guys yes oh we're out
here in the beautiful Hawaii I'm not
gonna lie to you my savage level is
approaching maximum it is absolutely
gorgeous in the morning across the way
we got Chloe Bennet hi Chloe she's doing
yoga cuz she's like an old lady
your mom okay okay I could do this stuff
for the rest of my life man so for those
of you who are just hopping on the low
gang train my name is Logan Paul this is
the vlog Channel we are currently the
fastest growing channel on YouTube so if
you are not subscribed abun we're what
the [ __ ] doing that we are in Hawaii
right now because we just wrapped our
movie valley girl sad we need a little
celebration let's see what's happening
hello who is that oh don't why are you
doing bro dia I mean that's my boys I
gotta say about that I don't weird
waking up here because they're roosters
over here that cuz I'm gonna kill every
rooster you ever see
he's over there bro okay what are you
doing
kawaii air guitar right here that's my
boy yeah oh I had so much runway how did
you not hear me coming to like the vlog
oh you guys don't know Chloe Bennet is a
she called a focus focus way traditional
actress it just sucks that she's like a
grandma like what is it with me grandma
[Music]
you good bro look at this Rama Chloe
we are here about to go hiking I think
stop number uno today is the fall
are they over here bro all pro you think
bro there
[Music]
oh cool
if you
go down there I don't think we have a
choice
you're what this guy got rough what are
you making a hat job I with muddy
is it personal toy bro this is the
dopest King Africa yo I see you bro cold
hard cash
five dollars attendance Riu ROA blaster
Mahalo man
Oh
[Music]
you guys we reach the bottom and oh my
gosh this is gorgeous
you guys I've been to a lot of beautiful
places in my life you got to come there
with me but y'all it's like I'm in like
this weird state of emotion right now
[Music]
I know life is beautiful
I told you guys this before swimming is
my weakness ruffle like I was so bad at
swimming Evan hey Dumbo hey [ __ ]
camera we're going into the heart of the
waterfall it's good because we're
maverick and even though we could die
hey cuz we're maverick 89 could I ever
die too fast if I'm gonna die and that's
be doing - baby oh wow I should feel
good nice comic got a kick-ass fix you
good I'm fixing the wall
[Music]
Oh
you
Wow
haha I'm literally the loudest person on
this island I was bad I'm gonna get me
beat up no bro wait what broke I'm a
savage
Bookman uncle G next item on the agenda
we got to get some food hi how are you
just vlog and that's all well here they
go nope
yo they're fads bro I don't make
decisions often but I've decided that
we're going to make our food use a
little adulting session huh
[Music]
and if you look over yonder to see a
wire Chloe Bennet being a grandma hi you
tell me okay are you gonna do Cheeta are
you gonna croak
leave me now reckon why you need Panzers
aw well that's Chloe what are we in for
dinner
you totally say my boxes off yeah well
what do ya know there's no odds I'm
doing it Sonja did you grab these
fireworks oh oh yes here's why that's
dope we're in Y for the 4th of July bro
it's going down well see me with the
ribs
Oh heart dudes really guys never gonna
beat them with that don't use the club
you too rich
what are you getting close
marry me
khloe's permanently my blog hey guys
what's up its ended I need to take a
little pause ball now uh just don't go
over dose or joke so thank you Wow for
you what do you need psyche round here
no what do you like yeah yeah yeah you
just threw its bone a marsh beat that
hey ok we're back at the crib yo my boy
Sam here is a cook I acted like I was
going to do the adulting nah bro look
with Sam a fish avocado I don't really
know bro what is it what did you make
this this is fresh ahi avocado ginger
cilantro right straight Hawaiian 7 I got
a beautiful out of real life is good god
I think we should go to the beach dude
you should that one yeah
the secret beach it's literally guys
this is like a secrets called it called
the business secret Beach I'm not even
kidding
go to the beach we're getting naked it
is a nude beach we'll see what happened
to let me naked I said Nick haha oh man
this is don't hey dude Beach oh can you
bro we actually got our dicks out yeah
got you bro yeah no that's not going to
happen unless I get exposed or yeah no
it's not gonna happen to you okay
Brendan yes or no is this nothing nicest
beach you've ever been on in your life
there's nobody here Sam where are we
dude litical did you think of each I
live this couldn't get any better Sam
brought us to a natural water spring so
this is collect fresh water my boy is
drinking it that's why you can get in
some societies ok Fiji smart water bro
and this coconuts to chill in here and
and iPhone that's my iPhone look around
it
[Music]
are you and the pack
and delicious oh yeah welcome miss Bruna
doctor oh no first one this is so cool
but I realized I have no like clickbait
like let's be honest guys the majority
of YouTube it's like something about the
title is a little clique baby like it's
kind of true it's kind of not I like
today's just a dope day like this is the
coolest vlog ever but like hot like I
don't want to do click base as a
youtuber here I am thinking like do I
get naked right do I say like getting
just call this vlog [ __ ] it
this dhoni clickbait this vlog is dope
the decisions a youtuber is godlike Oh
probably think I should do I think you
should get naked naked
hmm I just started wondering your naked
views blow I think I'm gonna go naked
views bro I'm going to get naked and
take a shower in the natural spring but
then views brown a literally just as
that we're going to get naked great bro
I'm out here being a maverick literally
my underwear set fabric oh oh wait oh
that merchant available just yet
anyways underwear torn off hey guys
London
dead naked on the Internet grab my [ __ ]
oh I feel so free guys I know this is
weird but like this is what you do when
you're in Hawaii yo guy that is the vlog
if you are not subscribed join the fact
that's going and weirdest channel on
YouTube make a the lo gang subscribe
right now get your maverick marks link
in description and I will see y'all
tomorrow take it easy man I can't do the
thing my hair is wet
are you blogging about you crying right
now I'm blogging this already right now