[Music]
no that's me yeah I smudge the screen
bro hey guys it's good to see you again
how are ya ho-oh where do I even start
bro there's so many things going on okay
I guess I'll start with this so you guys
see the title of the video yeah it's
gonna get you ceiling so if you guys are
not a part of the low gang gang gang
make sure to subscribe hit the buttons
and join the strongest and then you're
speaking of strength and regarding
someone who has none
you guys know that the ksi effect coming
up August 25th slight issue though the
dude can't stop running his mouth
[Applause]
[Music]
calm down with the profanity JJ you have
a young and impressionable I'm gonna
beat Logan so easily that people are
think I should go pro haha just you wait
Devil's yeah for sure bro you definitely
go pro you're so good anyways guys back
to stuff that actually matters we just
dropped some new Mavericks guys you
already know probably saw it on my
Instagram it's our brand new blue fly
hoodie we got dent the universe on the
sleeve here and then do it different and
then they do it different a little bit
fine it's gonna it's a big deal
oh my god I just farted but anyways guys
to do it different Road the dude
fine is that funny bro I didn't even
fart it smells like you did his okay
sighs liming cousin enough talk about
this con bro talk about there's new
t-shirts right here guys it's a big deal
what some people have been calling the
Revolution of the millennium I don't
know bro I'm just a part of the system
Logan Paul concise shop or link in
description push H Kong's hunting for
something in the water
Oh No what do you see young double it's
the Loch Ness monster
oh my getting my pull anyways bro I'm
just pumped for the yoga later you know
it's couples yoga maybe I got a
girlfriend over okay what else yeah yeah
guys since the daily vlogs ended
obviously I'm not like you're not as up
to date in my life we've been doing a
lot of stuff oh my gosh the music studio
bro we've been making music I'm gonna
give you a sneak peek of the studio
front this is like a severed whoa whoa
you're showing them now just the tip
brush little snake oh no it smells like
oh okay I get disgusting bad they're out
of here dude Oh
the only sneak peak I can give you for
now that's a vlog for another day oh
also getting other week we did a nice
little charity event let me just show
you don't call it a comeback today we
are out here about to go on like a car
drive
a car run I've never done this before
app actually the only truck here a real
maverick move but we were here to
support the mothers for a safer LA
County gonna drive some cool cars my
brother Jake is behind me hi Jay I love
you he didn't say it back but he loves
me too I think well what are you waiting
for Spence hop on in frost on a nice
Island
[Music]
I thought one car was super cool that
was cool that show was cool yeah it was
nice another thing I want to address
guys you may have noticed Lydia has not
been around some people have been saying
she's missing but what happened was she
she got up she got caught up it hid
trade embargo in South Korea
so she's just in South Korea so many
guys here's we're actually having
similar she she she moved on guys we was
a mutual decision that her time here on
Team Maverick has come to an end
Lydia you know we love you we miss you
so here's a quick tribute to Lydia yep
guys I'm pregnant
no worries guys we actually we found a
new assistant one you may recognize guys
know her you guys love her
[Music]
it's a lie
you're quitting again sergeant Ayla you
were great assistant it's no it's
different things are different no we
have a new we have a nice yard and a
nice dog and a nice path pass Kayla to
understand why you don't like being my
assistant you didn't love these moments
[Music]
well what if I told you as my new
assistant you never have to worry about
anything like that again
besides this moment right here
after that we're not doing that ever
again welcome back we love you eh oh we
said that a little bit of committing to
Michaela my assistant but speaking of
this I think it's almost AcroYoga time
guys so if you don't know what this is I
don't either
here's a picture thank God we got
instructor what happened yeah apparently
this guy can do like handstands but with
like one hand I don't even know oh oh
he's running put upside down
[Music]
all you need is yourself
straight up all you can do is trust the
other person that's going to be flying
on you and you're just gonna support
them up with but it's not any more than
myself
I need another human being yeah I see ya
Ella hey hey you know wanted two birds
is that too actually completely yeah I
think after yoga okay yeah I got my
partner Andrew
[Laughter]
no this is Human Centipede wine in the
what in the world she's spinning up
well I love we can eat well so let's do
it you're gonna take a buddy grip like
this with your buddy
then you're gonna bend your knees as a
base flyers Hanna step one foot now for
the next one your hands are gonna
connect you guys looked really bad doing
it but I could tell that you guys
yeah I know for a fact I could do that
but the question is can you either why
can't you be more like him oh my gosh
[Music]
magic words that fly he's first time
well no I do parachute flashback
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's not your time it's gonna be me and
you one day oh my god there we go
bring your feet to her hip points
[Applause]
alright that's about enough half crow
yoga for me thank you bro
that's uh that's definitely a workout
Jesus Ayla thanks for being such a
wonderful partner it's glad to have you
as my new assistant again that is the
BLA thank you guys for watching make
sure to subscribe brand new
[Music]