well we got boss Oh boss we got I'm ever
going to do he said yeah I know I can
hear him I can read the subtitle I'm
positive I'm sick maverick do you have
we make it out with Ayla bro and I'm
dying away what's your deal no animals I
love my animals oh yeah good morning bro
wait that's I know that's a human being
oh my god
if you're new to the channel welcome to
the low gang normally I don't sound like
a horse with another horse in his throat
but today I do and I'm sick and this is
bad because tomorrow I'm going on set
they're on my side yeah it's gone I feel
here you do pioneer that'd be funny for
my blog here we go it's the moment of
truth oh no I almost did but you made it
out alive this is the low gang if you're
not subscribed you're doing no subscribe
hit the button we are one of the fastest
growing channels of YouTube this is
mainly due to our litanies level the
fact that we're all Mavericks the word
maverick meaning one who does not follow
the path of others all I gotta say that
is yayi and as you guys know it's an
interesting time in my life right now
yesterday my brother put up a very
embarrassing billboard of me I was
offended
so I threatened to release the second
verse if he doesn't take it down in two
days until Saturday at midnight remove
the Billboard I'm releasing the second
verse
you guys remember the second verse never
before seen ever unreleased you know
what no it wasn't released it was leaked
because someone spied on us in the
helipad sound terrible I know but I'm
talking the full music video which is
why it's so savage it's such a big deal
and it's interesting because by the time
this vlog is now he'll have like nine
hours to take the Billboard down if he
doesn't I'm releasing it at midnight
tonight good luck Jake better get on
that twelve seconds too late there guys
I actually feel much worse Rome supposed
to be better as the day goes on it
whatever you don't I realized you I
actually don't have a copy of the second
verse I threw one out in the ocean gave
one to Jake this is gonna be a problem
figuring out how to get that but don't
worry Logan you know we always come
through good to get some clothes that
gonna make me look sexy but I suck at
shopping and I also hate it so I bought
some Fred button item five frenzy I
brought some friends
it's Sonia and that girl that kissed me
on the beach what I don't I don't need
it you will get rid of it right now I
don't know we don't need it get rid of
it clearly don't know fashion I just
know my merchants fire that's all I mean
this is okay but you know then we'll get
rid of it it's so weird that you have a
sore throat for a fusion you think
that's really okay guys they're talking
about chopping and girls stuff and I
just I think they think they're always
trying to make you be very toned down
and we're noise she's trying to suppress
them man you can't it's oppressive
dynamite it's gonna blow you can refine
it you can do that always trying to
suppress the dynamite
hey buddy I know you're having fun but
we have to go so if you could just watch
out okay all right you good bro okay
guys we're gonna go to the store
shopping I said it's my life I hate
shopping hey we're going shopping look I
go looking like a big happy
dysfunctional family so yeah are you
doing very good while we're at the Grove
right now you know chances of us getting
paparazzi oh no I think that's more like
the l'eau de l'eau de l'eau gang
definitely hangs at the grill oh my gosh
celebrity TMZ towards more celebrity
teams oh this is dope that's gonna be
famous people this is my dream come true
okay guys store number one and my slow
death begins we got some little
gangsters on uh hello gangs everywhere I
could never be honest though I never
want to run you guys it's dull these
guys are persistent that's what it's all
about
I'm just gonna do it Chloe I'm going
let's take a quick picture guys
oh no this vlog on your phone I was
thinking maybe what weekend of the 14th
pop-up shop be ready details coming soon
lo game for leper
I've been here for two minutes yo the
low game is too strong whose truck is
that the paparazzi are you the paparazzi
Chloe come here kiss me is the paparazzi
oh you're right there
you look like Jack from my don't we look
you guys got the same hair no you can't
see now but there's a picture of him on
the screen what'd you say why don't you
cry when you come on to me - hi Dan look
at all these backpacks you know be dope
if there are actually cool backpacks
like this yeah what's up da where the
dressing room we're safe are they're
coming up this is crazy bro what that I
respect you guys you want something
you'll go get it like I like problem is
I'm in a change room with Chloe Bennet
[Music]
y'all enjoy says well someone's coming
alright we got boss ah boss we got 3,800
77028 I'm not coming the only stop one
okay Logan here's the thing here's my
here's my reason I'll spend money on a
car fine
I don't love spending money on clothes
like I don't need new clothes I got the
hottest march in the game bro for those
of you who have ordered the Maverick /lo
gamer you know what I'm talking about
soft stylish joining a movement be
honest low game Chloe is paying for my
clothes because my car didn't go through
because I don't often spend this much
money you guys spend $10,000 at a time
man I don't I'm not used to this dude
I'm definitely not gonna pay you back oh
that's called YouTube star vs. actor
right there for one fan
right there Chloe Chloe let's address
something okay Chloe that's how we met
okay lo que we are going to the most la
place in LA that's right you want to say
it pretty woman see if anyone's gonna
give a shirt that's Tess yeah what up G
oh damn you were ready my people oh yeah
we're definitely in Beverly Hills it's a
dope Lambo guys I'm not gonna lie Sep
yall already know mine is gonna be
cooler ya like it subscribe know the
first door the very first one yeah
coochie Oh everything's so gold hey guys
this isn't the men's section no okay
so weird I thought you're shopping for
me but whatever what it's not
professional bro I got tape in my camera
lookit
I can't do it guys we're gonna spend a
lot of money in the Gucci store yeah
[Laughter]
Yahweh you know who else did oh my god
Chloe what have we done okay if we were
to get paparazzi now would be the time
Cheers
you know what is happening with my life
why did I just buy these oh wait yeah
cuz they're awesome now what else does
one do when they're in rows what else
does one do when they're in Beverly
Hills on Rodeo Drive Oh I was gonna say
they get ice cream from an ice cream
truck you know I don't know why this is
here but we're definitely taking
advantage of it there's so many options
like what hey man what's your name bro
you look like a shopper can I do the
strawberry burst Big Dipper oh my gosh
strawberry burst aw thank you for ya
basic basic out of all the things that
we've spent money on today this is my
farther than I'm still listening to my
joke I'm just telling she's real getting
out of all the things that has my money
and today this is by far the best
purchase now we're shopping again okay I
mean look this stuff is definitely cool
I need to be doing this it's just like I
feel like I'm having my teeth pool tell
me be sexy that's how much are you good
that way you're embarrassing in a corner
yeah
oh you guys the reason many different
outfits
um so the reason I'm in a different
outfit is I'm actually doing a fitting
right now for the show I'm shooting
tomorrow those are the scripts you saw
earlier you guys know the show it's
called for so yeah anyways look how much
money you boys spent today I look at the
shoes bro
yeah bro open a bag bro I will be honest
I don't remember what I bought oh that's
amazing
you hold up bro I see you dawg what you
got bro that's Gucci tissue paper back
up calm got some better for you take
that bro coochie shoes G the world's
your oyster
that was your Gucci shoe bro how'd you
get here so fast D come on I'm being
seven so guys as far as this billboard
goes I'm figuring it out with my brother
hopefully he pulls it down and I don't
have to release the second first I
really don't want to who knows man I'm
gonna be real with you guys right now
this whole thing is so stressful for me
like I don't know why it's just cuz he
stirred the pot and the pot didn't need
me start guard this man you guys know
that we are the strongest family on
YouTube we are the most savage we are
maverick so we have a lot to look
forward to and this is just a minor bump
in the road unfortunately we are dealing
with it now anyways I love you guys if
you're not subscribed make sure to
subscribe New York City pop-up shop
details coming shoot you're Mavericks
logo balls I got slash shop and I will
see y'all tomorrow take it easy fam come
you got this one
peace
Oh face great clip for the end of the
vlog like it subscribe