[Music]
okay so we are as you guys know in Italy
right now check this out
cool right now look these guys even sing
it to us thanks guy
we love you or since Italy should I say
diamo Jesus [ __ ] you guys it's early if
you can't tell but I don't care bro look
around they put us in a break your pal
you did go out last night that's where I
bought this the best purchase of my life
back to have a little bit of Italian fun
flashback last night Brendan hop inside
real quick I got many grapes I want to
show you yeah yeah bro mini grapes here
no like what no slip how is it like Oh
what oh oh also guys I had a friend come
and join me my UK boy some of you og low
gangsters might recognize them it's my
boy
[Applause]
Hayden woke me up this morning in a
really aggressive way flashback thanks
yeah yo look 6:59 a.m. wake up the
vlogger Jake Paul where are you so
Jake's a little late as usual but yeah
I'm gonna take this time to plug yo
Italy if you're not subscribed make sure
to subscribe join the long game honestly
I'm just talking probably to you but yo
you better subscribe to and honestly bro
I saw some awesome Mavericks last night
bro repping the merch if you have not
cocked yet you only way to get it Logan
Paul that car / shopper link in
description okay so as you guys know my
brother is here to pick up his new
Lamborghini and I came here and
surprised him for moral support to you
buy a Lamborghini that's a big deal no
cuz I was supposed to get one who knows
maybe if I am at the factory tomorrow
and I see it like I might on almost an
average I'll make the decision like that
because that's what I do baby thinking
on the spot instincts gut feeling but
the plan today is that we're going to
Venice Venice Italy bro I've never been
I heard this place is like we're gonna
miss our train little brother or leaving
Jake come on bro no no the taxis behind
you bro we this is pool let's go gonna
miss a chain
[Music]
there is it's about to get wonky
tallien for dummies okay let's see what
we got okay right here let me tell you
something it is a miracle that we are
able to navigate anywhere
exactly Oh sister we get so lucky I
don't know how we're doing this I don't
know how we're vlogging it just a couple
of young dumb kids but as long as you
put your mind to it
you two can buy a train ticket oh oh oh
we live in March it's double decker oh
hold it open arm is not good row you
could bro train is moving I just want to
give a round of applause to myself that
was quite the Power Move
[Music]
yo we took in L bro why is this so rainy
in Venice Brendon not the move
Brendon not the boom they really need
water do not go in the water it's the
most disgusting like you'll actually you
know we have to go in the water yeah you
know half the water
I've been to the hospital
so Andy is Cades girlfriend's brother
this dude knows fluent Italian he's
gonna be like our key our guy even
though it's raining hopefully hopefully
it's gonna be fun do you think Andy can
make it stop raining Andy can you make
it stop raining like this yo - the rain
this is the Venice you see in postcards
yo check this out we're right on the
river The Sitter like the streets are
literally just rivers what the [ __ ] yo
that is a boat Italy they have uber
boats
it's called Buber oh look at the
woodwork on this Buber like I said
before bro
I know boats and this is definitely a
boat so many bags and charges and more
charges that's this guy how much for the
boat
so mother's plea to 350 100,000 euro go
Ambo I find this boat no legit I could
buy this freaking boat that every stupid
Lambo now that I'm close to the water I
see what he means by its disgusting
green the water's green water I don't
think water should be green oh I've seen
that I've seen that I've seen movies
with that right here 100% channel I've
seen that yeah I'm a Mumma much Joe this
point I'm just being grace this 100%
percent oh that's a wrap on Logan PAH
yeah that's a verifiable back I'm gonna
come over there put you in the boat we
going
[Applause]
what that you know the architecture here
is incredible one freaking Italy dog
moments like this where I'm just like yo
boy from Ohio came out here in Italy
probably about to get kicked out but I'm
enjoying this bro what life is crazy I'm
not crying
if my head doesn't come off right now
I'm gonna be pissed
oh oh yeah yeah yeah oh honey no way
this is your Andy Andy is this our hotel
this is not a joke yeah
yo Sistine Chapel or hotel I don't know
I'm just starting to realize now these
aren't Kong I don't think they are thank
you for letting me know you know casual
conversation girl video and you ain't
got a word by defeating the Marx baby I
gotta
seagull and then we got pitch how do
they delegate the territory oh hi yes
are talking about territory and if you
look behind me you'll find the bond
theory out it's used for people walking
over it and boats going under it Logan
you're a tourist you're a tourist you're
a tourist you're a tourist Horace Horace
you're a tourist you I want to thank you
for inventing the theory of relativity
it's done great things
oh go might take this group I gotta say
Venice is a really a hands-on place
leave Steam account delete that guy so
signing off looking Volvox forever see
you later never know your voice is
incredible you have the most amazing
voice whoa can you say logan paul calm
/op
thanks for plugging for me GSG nice it's
not the same without it what's the move
right now pasta pizza a matzo okay a
couple of hungry boys I just can't wait
to get my pasta
[Music]
[Applause]
hey pasta isn't my future hi Jake what
did you say these ones we talking about
what are you talking about
oh you're colorblind let's see that yeah
pink pink pink pink good job I'm just
gonna sing a song as we walk this is for
everyone over there hey this is the
restaurant with the delicious Italian
food but you're looking rain the rain
started to come down hard keep your
umbrella ella ella Sklar ladies and
gentlemen don't mind if I do
you're my hero sir yeah you're my hero
I thought Durkin was your hero dear
fresh Italian pasta I promise to love
you cherish you and make sweet love to
you for the rest of this dinner two
things that got me like whoa one that
pasta at least you choose this crooked
ass towel bro that's I won't even say
like crooked or leaning the tower is
falling Italy you're not good bro one
day I wish to have something like that
and take pictures with there in front of
colored walls baby
very unlikely thing happened we use our
brains we got some umbrellas and in to
myhumber I joke sold anyway so I'm Andy
here Andy what do you have the goal is
to get these birds to attack us with
their beaks and take a picture
no let's find out what happened get on
me you know no look this isn't working
it's a bunch of Mavericks I'm just like
you Birds except better what we got if
you buy a piece of my merch I'll be glad
to pay any money you want Logan Paul Hey
Jesus mother of God I hope that shot
let's cut to it now
yo this one right here the white one
that's the maverick that's what I'm
saying but he gets what he wants he
stands out from the group he's the only
one that's different that's what it's
all about baby this crazy kid off camera
I was like yo I'll bet you $5,000 you
wanna jump in the poop water because
what about the water
they've been pooping in there for
thousands of years no bueno I've already
pooped in there today okay so yes I'm
saying everyone does it jump into the
water because he's gay boy oh look hey
little brother jakey try to roast me I'm
gonna go downstairs for a van at this
point I love you Morgan wait if you die
and your skin starts falling off because
the water is disgusting in chemicals you
may I need to learn how to say here we
go no I do ha you big dummy
we got Andy
Wow I'm Katie [ __ ] if you go in I'll
give you your money back
actually if you go in on giving you your
money
we lost zero money today yo if you call
the police ask them if they could join
the locate no good telling me it's
illegal yeah I know bro but that's all
about Yolo gang you got one life on this
earth and when your brother wants to do
some crazy [ __ ] you best do it with
that's the maverick spirit I say
everyday but yourself to do things that
no one else is doing and great things
will happen
Wow and after that Italy was never the
same I am so surprised we don't get
banned for more countries like actually
anyways guys that is the vlog one went
today bro look at the city Dahlia you're
beautiful tomorrow is Lamborghini day
Jake is going to pick up his Lamborghini
reading your comments I'm seeing some of
the rumors some of you think I'm getting
a Lamborghini as of now I don't plan on
getting my Lamborghini I don't even know
if they finished building it cuz I did
put the deposit down I have no idea so I
guess you're just gonna have to
subscribe to see if I get a Lamborghini
or no cop your maverick merch the
hottest merch in the game we are
changing the world every single day
being different being passionate being
unique ie jumping off a bridge in Italy
Mamma Mia little guy I love y'all don't
see you tomorrow
[Music]
smells like [ __ ]
he's always smelled like [ __ ] Wow