what's up guys fight week I'm getting
this question a lot Logan how do I watch
the fight where do i watch the fight so
this will be a quick tutorial video
first I want to do a want to say
something so I'm gonna say it's fight
week which also means it's media week
we're doing a lot of media a lot of
press to promote the fight you may have
seen on my Instagram I've been having
some fun with it this was cool also
Justin Bieber hosted me on his Instagram
his main feed I'm not gonna lie this is
probably one of the coolest things to
happen in my life ever justin is coming
to the fight he's predicting an early
knockout as you said in his Instagram
caption and he's not wrong but back to
the focus of this video how to watch the
fight very simple you buy your tickets
AXS calm link in description you show up
at the Staples Center of this Saturday
okay let's say you can't make it to the
Staples Center no problem probably
already know where to watch it if not
I'm not gonna lie that does surprise me
I've said it a lot it's gonna be on the
disown after zone out zone that's right
dasn't otherwise known as the zone
pronounced the zone Daz end there's an
app you could download this app it's
like the Netflix for live sports I was
actually a subscriber on to zone before
I became a fighter on to zone and they
bought my fights and for some reason I'm
still paying the monthly subscription I
can't believe I don't have a discount
there's no in tagline big fights any
device one price yeah that's right a
super user friendly app very easy to
sign up I'm gonna walk you through it
although again like it's really [ __ ]
easy you can go to the zone calm or go
to the App Store and type into zone
Daz and I'm not gonna lie it's pretty
self-explanatory you sign up it's very
easy you can get the monthly
subscription or the annual subscription
if you like to watch flights a lot which
I do the monthly subscription is $19.99
now that's too much money for you go mow
lawn or something but look you got 20
bucks like ask a friend ask parents like
collect change from under the laundromat
behind $20 you can buy this fight last
year it was $10 this year I feel the
value of the fights a little more it's
gonna be a lot more entertaining and I
want to say the last fight was heavily
heavily pirated so this is gonna be the
only place to watch the fight in the
United States Brazil Canada Germany
Switzerland Austria Italy and Spain now
if you live elsewhere
pay close attention as I read off this
list where you can watch the fight for
the UK and Ireland Sky Sports box office
or wwe.com slash box office and then
Poland TVP Taiwan 11 Sport malaise
/ Brunei Astro China CCTV were available
in China down New Zealand sky network
Indonesia red dentist Philippines tap
DMV Latin America space and then the
rest of the world fight TV but is a
twist fight spelled like this fi te so
look it's available in most places if
you live in Antarctica you but even then
you could still get your tickets and
come to the Staples Center this Saturday
look that's it dude I'm getting excited
I've said everything I needed to say
about this fight I am the most mentally
healthy and physically healthy I've ever
been in my life I feel great I look
great I got a beard now again no more
creepy mustache just overall all good
things also quickly if you haven't seen
our documentary the Maverick that we put
out I think it's the greatest most
important piece that we've ever made
also you know why actually thank you
guys for everything this is incredible
this is the happiest most greatest time
of my life I'm so stoked right now we're
about to hit 20 million subscribers on
the channel I think that'll be a nice
little reward in addition to beating ksi
this Saturday is gonna be the greatest
night of my life and yeah just super
blessed super thankful for you guys it's
been a crazy journey and it's not gonna
stop now and yeah I hope you guys watch
this fight not actually nah I don't hope
you watch this fight watch the fight
this is gonna be biblical it will be the
most memorable thing that's ever
happened in the history of the Internet
and it's the beginning of my burgeoning
fight career because after this yeah I'm
gonna be honest with you I want to fight
in the UFC Oh we'll talk more about that
later
watch me knock this new ksi out this
Saturday November 9th on the disown app
I freaking love you guys hit that
subscribe button I will see you when I'm
a champion
take it easy
you tuber anymore bro I mean I'm a boxer
guy this is a contractual obligation I
got to make a how-to video I don't know
how to make a home video bro this is
expert village
that's a throwback