[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
they said I couldn't be the dog so I
hang on adults to do adult things for me
around this is my old place and it's
cool granted I'm still gonna have to pay
anywhere from like four to forty
thousand dollars worth of cab never
people will worry about that tomorrow
I love ya guys we were actually in
Hollywood right now we came here to
shoot us skate which is weird because I
had to shot a skit in like forever yo
when I did your boy was the king you
guys remember these neighbors hey guys
did you miss me no just log in my life
away but the skit is not - aw my Latino
friend had at one place our itza mere
mono and Lele pons Oh since we're going
multicultural in this [ __ ] your boy is
going to Dubai bro I'm talking to united
arab emirate i'm flying there on
wednesday with my member and hey look
can you do that again come here marry me
tomorrow dinner going to Dubai and then
with the always this a new iPhone X no
it's not I don't know
look it's a new iPhone X what did you do
oh I didn't do anything well it was a
bodybuilder don't forget guys I'm giving
this away if you buy merch in the next
24 hours that know you are you doing
Lily yeah guys get your merch local boy
lock up /tao as you know we just dropped
maverick bottle oh wow ready
these Latinas Batson and you could win a
knife or axe actually speaking on how
about you this for me and let it bother
you
are you a small if you were those your
boobs won't bounce anywhere anyways yeah
guys we're going to Dubai host
literally the biggest meet-and-greet
that the world has ever seen at the
Dubai Mall through this a lot cuz I'm a
magician bro look at my hands they're
waving really November 11 at 5 p.m. guys
so if you're in the low gang and you
live in Dubai or even if you don't fly
to Dubai go to the Dubai Mall and come
see the Maverick baby I want to meet you
guys I want to see all of your faces I
want I want to kiss all your faces right
in the face just kidding I'm not gonna
do that I'm also speaking at the ITP
live conference there which is like a
very adult mature thing which is gonna
be lit the whole trip is gonna be lit
now as if there couldn't be any more
Latinos the same language you talks
about me I'd have no idea that's true do
it yeah I know what stupido means I
think you see that you see that can
mamba get up in this yeah brokers look
bank
Oh hold up Oh I just started just
looking we got 3 fiery Latinas do you
know I don't know I don't know I don't
know latina are you yeah peanut I'm
saying this is gonna be hilarious bro
welcome to a new segment I like to call
driving with latina
[Music]
here's something Lily was in a Camila
Cabello music video hey yo caballo my
here's the song Havana something else
you may not know and Lele might not know
either is that she's gonna give me a day
with her so yeah maybe one day I'll take
cloud a day I mean hard cuts and the
other day was coming
[Music]
so you guys eat the tacos lately Jesus
me yeah I've jail
no girlfriends give me a day with Camila
so she's never been treated the right
way the right way if I come I pick her
up in the Yeti I open the door for no no
no I put a red carpet out to a nice
Italian restaurant cuz we're throwing
all kind of cultures in the mix I'm not
racist
we have spaghetti pasta linguini
whatever she wants no sushi it's at an
Italian restaurant
I can do a good day if I tried use the
right lane to take exit 18 on just
supposing with Latinos natural habitat
oh you love my dog though clearly what's
the time do you know you speak Spanish
speak to him in Spanish what why did I
why did I Drive to Hollywood who were
shooting in my house and I'm just a bro
okay but that's simple math it's okay
now you get to see the crew oh okay he's
calling me when I was about to talk
about how beautiful my yard oh my god
just glowing it's that time of day
oh no yeah well they put a palm tree
I've been planting the place hello
I see you I see him looking wampum
behind you behind you behind you behind
you no behind you turn around completely
he's just Mexican and like
okay I'm still our back but okay anyways
yeah we got palm trees look at that palm
tree Brendan what well I think they put
like fruit oh we're gonna have food what
kind of fruits are these bro we got
berries the berries do you think they
are no no eat one maybe and not edible
where's Mary oh really though guys this
is super cool we're putting so many cool
plants here you know what I'm qicang bro
when I was in Ohio I had a garden like I
would play it like tomatoes no I wa
agua we got everything man so just as
much as my Yeti bleats the atmosphere
with its diesel gas my yard with trees
replenishes the oxygen off about to get
stupid what's happening basically I'm
gonna spin her like a baby is not a baby
that's why it's a [ __ ] I'm from Ohio
dipping breathe I got
[Music]
oh hi oh boy that was afraid to come
from the Senate yeah did you give your
phone to a bodybuilder as well like you
got all these cracks faces like it's
good clickbait I get it
one-point nose yes so I came to the
Apple Store right now I'm just curious
like obviously like my iPhone broke like
I wonder if they do repairs for this
type of stuff worth a shot
yeah let's try hi you guys do repairs
did you repair my phone yes what
happened yeah you could be on my youtube
you can find it on over Perry turning it
off and on ma'am I don't want it off
what's going on but it didn't work
let me just make one thing clear I did
not break it okay well gang you saw a
bodybuilder broke it Bradley Martin was
his name I'm in the clear but I will say
Apple I'm disappointed in you your on
and off advice did not work we walk in
and it's just a busted ass drugs row
ready this is a holdup I log I'm sorry I
broke you Joan I flew back to Mexico and
I'm never coming back
you're mono trombone yo Brendan bro this
is your drone how did they even this is
bad I flew it into a tweety and and it
was fine oh that's and this is the
cameras is posted yeah what happened
he used more Spanish - can you do you
know what that mean you know what you
did all the Spanish yesterday at your
brother
what does it mean we're gonna get to the
bottom of this lo game
what's the match the kid huh
q this is a mess oh damn the palm trees
look nice did you see where one plane
went we need to call this guy yeah I
also saw a broken as drone yeah please
cuz how do how does it happen
[Music]
no it just dropped from the sky it's
raining drones Logan no more this is
gonna be the last face you ever see
wampa yo yo yo waffle yeah where's the
footage yeah I know sleepy right the
memory cards here Oh what
so there's whomp eh
[Music]
what oh are you good
that's why did you crush and as if it
couldn't get any worse
I think my dog is dying Oh calm What's
Wrong buddy are you bleeding
Oh calm bleeding on his foot what
happened get the first-aid kit
we need perform CPR one two three four
five six seven eight good okay he's good
kill your bleeding arm all over the
glove sack what happened close this is a
get-well-soon flower here take it Carla
maverick here you go buddy oh no it's
just foot Oh
although it does the cod listen it's
okay call let's get a look at this I'm a
doctor
bro what's the cause of death he's still
alive no call we're saving you buddy
you said what you got oh no he's using
his massive long tongue to look into the
blood uh he broke this dog knows he's
like I got this bro I don't need your
boost first aid kit I'm the doctor get
that eat that foot and go Kong we're
gonna fix you right up
hey go buddy yeah there you go Kong it's
like you got a brand new pause if you
have not yet copter maverick bottom so
what are you doing bro make sure to get
the hottest merch in the game it's soft
it's comfortable it's versatile
versatile Mike versatile my boys
wrapping it you all what hold up we met
bro oh hey I'm out here Logan Paul
account slash shop or lean description
and if you buy merch in the next 24
hours I'm gonna pick one of you to give
apples brand-new iPhone to subscribe
you're not a part of the locating during
the strongest family on the internet and
ads usual okay I will see you tomorrow
cuz it's every day that Logan why did I
say am I good Who am I my jig Paul
yeah
I met mine
what do you want me to do out here I'm
gonna come in