I'm done being mr. nice guy hey oh good
morning little gang what's poppin oh
okay
how do we start this vlog okay the
articles you may or may not have seen
R&D true hi we did a citizen's arrest
last night in my house cuz we got broken
into and actually I realized we're
defenseless bro so I got machetes and
knives just a shaking beautiful I'm
gonna get into the story today I will
save you're not a part of the logging
make sure to subscribe here's why not
only are we the most lit family on
YouTube but the like I'm not just saying
this the crazy happens in my life
yesterday's vlog I talked about how my
main parachute did not open and I almost
died cuz that my reserve had to deploy
and last night someone thought it was a
good idea to walk into my house and take
a nap on the couch that home it just
sounds so stupid saying it aloud
who does that bro you go get slice
subscribe and also a copy or map of
merch it's the hottest nurse in the game
just you say are there example that's
y'all know where to get a marshalling
and description or as I like to say
marshalling and shop logan paul comm
slash shop now I will say guys it's dark
we have actually spent the whole day
talking about the incident last night
without sounding like a [ __ ] it it did
shake me up a little bit it's very weird
having someone invade your privacy and
their motive being unclear about it
right so that's why that's why we got
the weapons I don't even know these this
whole day has been crazy but hey how are
you I hope you guys are having a good
day I hope my vlogs can distract you
from your busy life or with 10 15 20
minutes whatever it is today's might be
short though but anyways let's stop must
be nice
you're still shook about the robbery
thing it's not like a robbery you didn't
robbing things that I know you did the
shaking this is yo I felt bad that this
kid came across he came here when Greg
was here and honestly I think we just
dive into this here follow me
so last night I'm standing right here
around this area and this happened
there's a kid on my couch and that room
over there who I don't think I invited
over you know I have no idea what it is
yo yo y'all so it turns out there's a
guy sleeping on my couch this guy's you
walk over here I'll just show you
we made a tape figure so you could
really understand what's going on here
there's a dude just laying here on the
couch homie made himself at home I don't
know if he has knives or a weapon like
under him and even scarier than that we
came in and we are just from dinner we
were here for about 10 minutes and we
didn't hear anything like we Evan was
supposed to be here but there was no
noise so at this point guys we are
assuming like the absolute worst I
didn't know what to do again this is a
scenario I've never been in in my life
what would you do I don't know but
here's what we did yo who are you who
the are you my boy we are about to mark
you I should have said we're about to
merge you and sell them some merch at
Logan Paul calm slash shuffling a
description when I didn't I told him we
were gonna mark him I don't know what
happened guys I I got dead you remember
when we were robbed when I was a young
dog I do
scarred me for life I actually cried it
was one of the few times I've cried in
my life the feeling of being like
there's someone invading your house when
you're out of there is like it's
disgusting to me so I hit a point I was
I lost it I freaked out a little bit
there's so many thoughts running through
my brain mind you at this point guys I'm
still screaming and Evan has still not
come out of his room yet so wheat like
the worst is going to remind why is he
sleeping so many questions and just when
I think this couldn't get any better
damn my boy made himself at home my boy
plugged it in yo you got that full
charge dark compliments of the Maverick
a soul my boy he's charging his phone
Oh God there was a point where I looked
around and I was like what is this you
in my house do I even live here because
it might as well have been his
if you're not part of the low gang make
sure to subscribe also it don't break in
my and sure another the cops are here
stop officer he's in this room I'll need
you guys to okay so the cops come in
they escort this guy out I'm just still
just as confused as anyone else and
looks like I'm gonna be going for
aggravated trespass and what does that
mean he wasn't we all do fairness it
wasn't like really aggravated here's a
conflict chill and just charging his
phone well just the fact that he came in
the house
then we get outside obviously to like
file paperwork and stuff and they're
like oh you want to press charges
against this kid I feel like the kid
made a mistake
God knows for what reason how that
happened but seriously if there's one
thing I've learned in the past month its
forgiveness okay so like I don't feel
like pressing charges because I don't
feel like he came in here with malicious
intent a mistake I make hella mistakes
it's part of life I'm human I'm just
trying to do the right thing I feel so
yeah it turns out I'm a little bit of a
hypocrite I am gonna press charges just
because I thought about it a little more
that's what I was thinking about like
pretty much all today and the thought of
someone coming in and harming one of us
or because this conversation would be
completely different if we are gonna
press charges
we're gonna beef up our security we're
getting armed security now and we're
increasing the cameras around our house
we're doubling it basically so we have
like 40 cameras or other property
because this ain't cool tape man or real
man not the move it's weird to get
serious man I'm really looking forward
to the day hopefully in the near future
where I can just stop all this just
bullsh and get back into the front vlog
for you guys I don't even know I don't
even want to cause the vlogs in the bar
on toast the more you know video the
more you know video I couldn't make this
up I can't make this up guys it's
absolutely insane it's an interesting
life I live if you want to see more of
it make sure to subscribe join the low
gang the strongest family on YouTube and
that is a fact and if you haven't yet
just take just bit brennick you've a
quick pan for my
[Music]
that's the hottest merch in the game the
beverage I really though it's sexy it's
soft it when you put the stuff on you
feel okay you feel powerful being you
because I think individuality is what
makes us all special and unique logan
paul daikon / shop with that said
looking that is the vlog i will see you
guys tomorrow do not break into my house
because next time you sell the knives i
will stab you i love you at take it easy
[Applause]
[Music]