guys I just got a text cut can you stop
cuz I'm vlogging sir no that's know that
you're keeping going just stop good guys
I just got a text from the concierge at
my complex stay there I've got something
I got hold on well that was check I'm
mopping I'm nothing you know ma ma it's
nice what a cloud met precipitation
[Music]
remember the one that came to like this
today
flashback um please in it and it's the
cutest thing ever
flashback events is the cutest thing of
2017 or you could bro call but I do have
good news what we're on a plate no let's
go see this thing dude
wait actually holy that'd be horrible
news we got plenty of play
can I show you something can I show you
something just take a quick peek down
there this is the new member of the
family before buy 4 squared G Wagen
raised this car is so big compared to
I'd take it over oh whoa whoa couple of
things we have to do one we have to come
up with a name for it I have some ideas
we will figure it figure figure it out
by the end of this vlog number two I
want to do a contest with you guys that
I'll explain shortly number three we
need a spot to park it it's huge I'm
hoping that thing says clear it's seven
foot one I don't know how high this is
but I think we give it a shot
I don't know gonna work nope oh yeah we
got it
Calais told me that it didn't fit we go
this [ __ ] dude so far we're good
all
it's so tight
oh my god no I'm so happy right now I
thought I was gonna have to like pay for
parking like a mile away it only gets
better no no no no this is the one you
know can you hold it okay so that's the
issue so next we're gonna test this pipe
here
yeah it's not gonna fit
you know how second ago I said I was
happy now I'm kind of sad oh oh oh go
over there
this area is a bat so there's like one
spot that I'm able to park
yeah hey the one spot in the garage I'm
able to park my piece I'd say it looks
sexy yeah well you know we can't even
get past these I wonder if we could ask
the complex to like to take these down
or like raise them or something I don't
know bro I'm colorblind
okay here's the thing as you guys know
we just had our first ever pop-up shop
in New York City
[Music]
okay baby
topless anyways for those of you who
could not make the pop-up shop I'm aware
that not everyone lives in New York we
are doing a giant maverick Merc shop
merge drop shop giant giant maverick
merge drop of some of the exclusive
stuff that was in New York and some new
stuff like the following
all right thanks pass Logan okay let's
start with the classic v-neck we got the
black can't forget about the white like
the dragon super sex gray because uh
Grey's Anatomy over Logan I don't like
v-necks oh good thing we got the clue
next for you too white gray the brand
new vertical lo game for live logo cuz
uh lo game for line a survey thank you
good bro survey yo yo yo you're good
papa maverick socks look at these whoo
fire black maverick backpack me maverick
backpack for all you fancy folk out
there we do have a duffel bag magic
black phone cases and a few posters man
join the movement and be a maverick this
is like you don't even need to say
things you know that is today right now
hottest merch in the game but wait
there's more I am picking ten people's
names whose names I will embroider on
the interior of the wagon wagon like to
you agony but I just took the space out
so it's just quick yes I will put your
names on the interior of my new baby on
though I'm not good at owning things and
I'm gonna fly two of you out here to
come take a ride with me in the wagon
and spend the whole day with me it'll be
fun will do savage things and probably
prank Jake Paul or something
what yeah that's the contest so yo get
your merch link in description looking
all that cop slash job be a maverick
enjoying the squad
I miss
well Tony all for starters we need more
plates and then Ayla we need stuff to
eat up so you get paper boy I'm never
gonna do paper plates mmm
I got the coolest vehicle in the game
let's just take a cruise around town
yeah
Jeff never leave the house unequipped we
got the goods here where's Evan yo Evan
you got the goods here there's nothing
in it but all right
never ever leave the house unequipped we
got the goods here and you know guess
what I got this sudden urge to buy a
pogo stick so I'm gonna go do that okay
first official driving the new whip oh
my god this thing with so hard guys it
is so smooth legit feel like I'm driving
a giant stick of butter
are you having I think you have
something to do
oh Jesus right Evan I think while I'm
driving just give it like a solid little
honk here Oh a little one no big one
[Music]
quickly realizing parking is gonna be a
problem in this thing
honestly though like I don't even care
about like that's the price you pay for
something this good kind of part like an
[ __ ]
what you say about your [ __ ] that's
just like a fun store Instant Karma
20 minutes later I'm done pogo sticks
come on oh yeah we just need to I could
get it no sorry man
I know you saw it fell on me yeah yeah
we'll take them my shoes on fire bro yo
wait what guys I think we buck Sparky
the only thing I can think of is it
we're just two fires
too much fun for one day let's go back
in the car I want to talk about the
color of the beach I got white cuz
that's what they had guys they only made
300 of these vehicles in the United
States but as you know I was thinking
like a matte black or a matte silver
I just wanted to rock the white for like
two days or so but yeah keep commenting
what color you guys think I should get
but speaking of white we do need some
more plates so we're gonna go to the
store and grab some what hey I told you
we're on a place go into the store here
we go no it's the summer blowout we can
really save on play yo Leila can you
point us in the direction of the plates
it's the summer blowout read the Sun
summer blow up come on come on leave me
sassy pants on aisle three needs to go
sassy pants on our three needs to go
it's not being a sassy pants the place
where the place where the plates at
trying to find a place I don't know
where they go oh this looks like an
appliance slash adults yeah we are you
good I'm not gonna do in the store I
would not do that oh those are poles we
don't do that
put it back quickly plates put it back
good riddance
y'all since she loses her personality
when we get in the plate section come on
ela where's she going I drove her here
so many good options but we got what
please let me see those plates make your
car let me see what your white sticker
court plastic no plastic plates nothing
happened nope yep
you trying to disrespect me I'm a vlog
Channel talk to you for a second yeah
give me a segments we have a good thing
going with this place it's really good
things you think this purpose she's
trying to show you how she does it yo yo
Elon Musk gonna give you a call
Oh Tesla [ __ ] damn that's a lot of
plates if they're not in the same one
piece are they still returnable no
they're shattered ah
no you got this oh no the baby bro don't
made it dude it's not yet bro I'm just a
divine star but maybe on my way okay I
always come prepared
congratulations tree you're not part of
the low game who's the fastest hey do
you have the stuff Ayla I called it okay
I kind of kind of answer it dollars
frustration anyone here have a broom
[Music]
[Applause]
plates ran over the plates okay I'm
gonna go get a broom clean up my plate
whoa our Zig I don't I don't know I just
didn't related to doesn't mean I know
you're not related to him come on I mean
I mean I'm related to yeah well we both
I mean both of us can be man not true I
got a broom in that team 10th house and
you're not sure man there's a lot of
stuff you should go look 12 seconds
later look I found a broom right here
but let's talk about what this you guys
could have your very own slip inside no
it's true
this is why we need a house Ayla Hey
look yeah you want to slip it slide you
can create more place having could do
more things what thanks for things
the important thing to learn from this
kids standing outside of my brother's
house is that you gotta take
responsibility for your actions
Haley you see how I'm doing this with a
smile on my face all clean hey brother
your thing whips
yeah it's dope right what did you do
with it no we just drove around the
block and I was like flooring it a
little bit am I gonna get in like ink is
gonna hit my face or something why would
I do that because you frightened me
multiple times you put my face on a
billboard embarrass me for all of the
way I had to release the second verse it
was a big thing that's why you would do
it and I'm a good brother dude I got
this for you
my brother appreciates the play yeah I
appreciate the plate what is that a
plate it used to be oh my god I'm gonna
take off I just want to you I am leaving
Jay Jay before I go is weird dude we
didn't fight or like pranky time or
anything before I go I just wanna I love
shooting merch out of the merch cannon
that girl or the tree you can get your
merch on Logan Paul comes by I'll get
your name embroidered on the dragon why
do people of always plug yes it's my
boys y'all robbed so excite know I've
had come for a while now this is a tank
yeah this this looks so good even if you
run over somebody you gonna run over to
Georgia you can legit you this yeah I'm
over me right now if I die George look
at me look at me well I gotta you got
this okay
yo if you if you you could kill me the
hell are we doing Rosa I'm not being a
man but gonna be
no no this is exactly your family the
wrong week followed up no Mavericks love
to live okay this is what a pigeon does
don't do what a pigeon
[Music]
my boy chose me I told you with the new
Dragon Oh yo yo they got I lost weight
if I pick all George that your real a
real legitimate question for you yeah do
you respond I could park this car oh
that's why you won't that's why you
asked me about your horns friends oh
yeah I got you right where I want you
the own life force yes I know this must
define the park the car here's the thing
where am I gonna Park you could be
[ __ ] part of my spot I don't know oh
okay honestly I don't even know if this
garage is gonna work no this is tight
George why is your bro oh stop stop off
your jobs man I used to be a miner oh
yes I think we're doing you just
this is good I don't get the corner
[Music]
oh yeah bro we've made it okay the moral
of this story is never give up
never goddamn it was cheesy I let's go
oh oh you're cruising bro yeah I bought
that don't forget guys I'm say again I
probably like a minute or two but I'm
flying two people out here and
embroidering ten of your names you buy
the merch I do I'm just you're gonna
hear that again in like a minute anyways
guys um that is it no wait no my bad
there is one thing left to do I'm not
gonna break it I'm not gonna break it
I'm gonna set it down and then I'm gonna
drop another plate on it and break it
[Music]
thanks for watching guys if you're not a
part of the low gang make sure to LIKE
and subscribe don't forget ten names
embroidered in my car and flying two of
you out here if you buy maverick merch
for the next 48 hours feel like today
was a pretty maverick day man we swam
the opposite way of others we pushed
back on society it was solid so remember
guys be a maverick low gang for life and
I will see y'all tomorrow
take it easy fan
[Music]
okay