you got a cop what's going on nothing
who you saw I'm gonna butcher complaints
about together oh my gosh no my voice is
completely I wonder why I probably cuz I
do like this yeah that literally just
happened anyways guys today is the day
so if you're not a part of the low game
for whatever reason first off you got
hit the subscribe button for me smack it
in the face when the strongest family on
YouTube and just living overall happier
better life now it's Christmas Day Merry
Christmas Logan pretty much every
Christmas so I spending in this house
this is the house I grew up and by the
way full of men you'll see today's gonna
be a lot of Manchester Christmas into a
man I was telling them bro today's the
big day so Jake knows I got ok now we're
safe I got my dad a Ford Raptor a 20-18
Ford Raptor this is the best man truck
in the world ok so I said this in
yesterday's vlog we've lived this crazy
life Jake and I and Jake bought dad a
Harley I'm serious
like so emotional he was like no one's
ever given me anything like life his
whole life he's worked for literally
everything he's ever got he's a man
that's how we do it and the fact that
it's 20 year old son was able to buy him
a Harley and now I'm gonna buy him a
2018 Ford Raptor I was like I have to do
this I have to share the well he's
family I love them and they're matching
their matching so this journey begins
when I picked them to chuck about three
days ago huh you might be the best black
rims black wheels
I made sure that not just sexy vehicle
guys this is the Ford Raptor this is not
a Brandi afford you owe me money it's
just such a cool truck it says Raptor
honey it's a man Chuck this is like the
Beast it's a man trope on top because
you know what I chose this truck because
when we were in Dubai this is the
vehicle they drove us around in we had
just a squad of Raptors and there's so
spacious and roomy my dad's gonna lose
his my grateful I love you dude anyone
know why I chose the blue I do I use my
brain what because Oh matching Harley
and a brand-new pickup truck they're
gonna be so sick forgive me I'm color
blind but I can match
I'm giving this to my dad I pay for I
don't even know all right
no this is good dad you birthed me and
I'm thankful for you and I had a
revelation
oh yeah oh yeah I said that wrong yeah
I'm his seed though anyways here's the
revelation I was like yo this life I'm
living is absolutely crazy and I owe
pretty much everything I've done in my
life to my parents after all I would not
be here without them and if something
happened where he god forbid passed away
all right cuz he had a heart attack
before drove himself to the hospital by
the way savage but like I don't know
like you never know what's gonna happen
in life guys and if I hadn't done
something nice for him I would hate
myself so yeah this is it man like I
hope I don't like this too much cuz then
I might just end up keeping it sorry dad
oh this is crazy cuz like y'all know I
Drive the Yeti it's a huge truck but
this is like you can put things in the
in the pickup ooh you know what speaking
of pickup oh I cannot break this car
before I get it to my dad or can I
content clickbait I gotta tell you what
man if you guys have not bought a new
car there is no feeling like driving it
off the lot and also it's kind of hurt
because literally the moment I leave
this lost car loses about 30 percent of
its value okay about to lose like 20k
here we go and I am officially off the
law dad I don't think you're gonna want
to return this but now you did can't for
as much so yes the truck is acquired
it's at my friend Max house right now
the plan is every year we go tobogganing
my dad pulls this on the four-wheeler
I'm gonna take him to like the
neighborhood down the street and I want
the truck to be just sitting there and
I'm gonna be like yo this truck is dope
like you should be pulling us in this
thing and hopefully he's like oh yeah
this is cool I could be like in fact why
don't you do that just hand him the keys
Maximus slap the bow on the truck and
hopefully it goes great like knocking
like that like that's an amazing moment
oh we need to talk about something
because I don't think that's the truck
that my dad likes there's a slight issue
with this plan okay so I bought dad a
Harley
yeah for his birthday yeah I talked to
him afterwards I was like did you want a
Harley or truck he said oh I mean you
made the right decision by getting me a
Harley what if I were to get like a
Tacoma that would have been like
absolutely insane as well so he likes
the Tacoma when it comes to pickup
trucks yeah to the Toyota Tacoma yeah he
has all who wants an orange Tacoma my
dad doesn't know what he wants right he
like he has his desires but sometimes
this 22 year old chach son knows better
this is one of those cases I will just
say it's gonna be so awkward if I'm like
you should pull us around in that he
goes no way a Tacoma would have been
better than that here's the thing though
it's still a sick ass yeah no you know
what if you make some smartass comment I
swear to god I'm not gonna say anything
I'm just gonna keep it he's not in the
low game here here dog hits your big day
now you're a maverick now you're in the
low gang you'll find a way low gang it
looks like Santa came through you guys
are all tweeting me pictures of the
maverick merch you how was insure if you
do it but yo shots of Santa man for
everybody who got marches Christmas
y'all welcome to the maverick revolution
it's very real guys how to softest
marcelin game I don't just say that
gonna change the world but being
different as y'all know 20 teams could
be a big year for the mammogram possibly
the biggest ever where we transition
from merge to a pair it's already
happened but we're gonna get like you
know real life stories and continue the
road to the top however if you didn't
get any merch or you still
more merch table V ously you know would
go look or the link is in the
description now here's an issue Oh sick
Christmas tree really the low gang we
don't have a Christmas tree you come
here where is the Christmas tree I ate
it yep fun what happened to the days
when we used to celebrate Christmas like
family when we when we were coming up on
vine and we made this Logan it's
Christmas
[Music]
are these the gifts cuz it just looks
like a bunch of bags no should we open
these gifts all the way this again
they're already oh yeah then why did you
get us tampons what the oh I was just
talking about how we testosterone-driven
that's right these these are in case of
a wound in my vagina you have a lot of
that huh I'll show this guy how to do
some man I don't if I hurt babies
because you I'm gonna know everyone calm
down
nothing that's a way to do a mensch
okay okay I'll man jokes aside I did get
you a gift that here it is it's right
here I wrapped it - I know I think it's
a mug you don't know that wouldn't is it
what oh yeah it's like the bird caws
like the Maverick lifetime warranty yeah
so what we can do the handle wait what
leaking through the handle no in there
let them warranty I got a better idea
lifetime warranty
okay okay no more destruction nor pain
we about to do some more magic take the
street and go sledding who's with me
[Applause]
What's Wrong dad mmm
it's okay yes the smaller version of the
Yeti I will say obviously guys this was
not a part of the plan I don't know why
I'm nervous and just I don't know I'm
also excited and now my guys gonna be
crazy we're gonna try to get my dad to
ride on the sled with me while Jake is
driving I do we're just gonna do this
got some gear we're going sledding only
went to Logan Park on /op cops Oh
maverick Maher dude be fine this warmoth
walk dead beside Sportback not dead
yeah I know you're getting all the
getting fragile right now all right
[Music]
we talk
[Applause]
in fact can you drive us around
yeah
[Music]
yo this is nuts
explanation what I know you like the
Tacoma or whatever but I drove this
around and Dubai it's the man truck it's
what you want no no this is not my new
favorite truck and you know it's really
cool this color matches hard you look
good next to a dad that's that ohio's
it's crazy
yeah dude Wow
[Music]
pay before we drive this and look at the
passenger seat there you go
[Music]
just some cigars just in classical
I'm surprised no totally work no 100% no
clue you know it's cool like this it's
like it doesn't feel as big as it what
that's what I'm saying it doesn't make
any sense right
it's a limo what and check it for
literally does not feel as big as it
looks it's crazy dude beautiful on this
thing all right yeah oh yeah I love the
collar I love the look
you know man
okay here we go any
[Applause]
headset Ohio you got a cop what's going
on nothing who you saw get a bunch of
complaints about you gotta drive
we took pictures for Shelburne with the
new toy yeah okay how about that brother
bye guys they don't like how you drop it
you gotta take it easy just kidding
never what yo oh my god this kid is so
dumb about you but I can teach other I
didn't know that is the vlog dad it
looks good in front of your new house
I'll end the single let's go damn talk
about Manchester the Cuban cigar just
the icing on the cake Wow if you were
not a part of the low gay make sure to
subscribe guys thank you by the way you
guys are the ones who have allowed me to
do stuff like this and I love making fat
man happy I owe everything to him and my
mom so cherish your family guys give
them hugs tell them you love them I hope
you had an amazing Christmas again
congrats everyone who got mavs emerged
today and if you didn't there's still
time you can still be a maverick oh it
looks weird like this literally the best
apparel in the game logan paul that calm
slash shop or let's go I love you dad
and I hope this was a good Christmas
yeah I'm freaking out that's what it's
all about baby I'll see you tomorrow I'm
actually headed back to LA and then to
Tokyo surprised how Kyo New Year's gonna
be crazy
maker
funny we're getting it to you tomorrow
who's there gonna be in this company
that's not Christmas mrs. in your heart
in your spirit and we always know it's
on December 25th yes actually date wise