so like I said guys there's a lot going
on in fact we're leaving right now
because we have something to go get ah
yes I'm mr. it's just I'm leaving Dubai
guys it's like 5:30 in the morning right
now I haven't slept I don't like to
sleep when I have flights early in the
morning so um I went out last night and
here's the funny story as you guys know
we made history the Logan made history
in Dubai this past week we had the
biggest meeting greet the city has ever
seen 11,000 yo we packed them all we
literally shut down the mall incredible
and we did this stuff I could go on for
days I bought this watch I spent $40,000
in a row it's the Presidential watch
it's made of titanium I actually love it
but here's the funny story so I went out
last night well not like I was this was
like two hours ago
yeah I lost oh good morning Britain
morning how you doing I know
Dubai people go hard look what these
kids did to the Rolex
know why talk about being a maverick
Jesus broach your champagne over the
Rolly are you put Bo Yeow crash anyways
guys we're leaving right now I don't
want to leave like you look if you're
not a part of the low game make sure to
subscribe all we do is epic stuff where
the best strongest family on YouTube so
hit the button whoa this is just getting
sadder and sadder how fan gave that to
me
subscribe please I love the tallest
building in the world guys it's not all
bad our last night was pretty good last
night it started with my boy money kicks
giving me a gift
guys I'm with Ross a taking money kicks
dude he calls me up he's like yo I'm
gonna bring you a gift I'm like I bro
and if you look down so that was cool
money kicks my man thank you your your
Boy Scout Louis Vuitton you boys got
desire only the best brands in the world
broke Gucci Louis Vuitton Rolex maverick
by the way if you have not gotten your
maverick merch at you know where to get
it look of all I got I don't even use it
when the movement be a maverick also yo
you guys know salt Bay the guy like
trickles of salt over his forearm we
went to his restaurant last night and
you boys went there in style
well the interior is red this is amazing
oh my gosh so we don't know if soulmate
is actually here the first thing I
noticed about this restaurant all the
servers have mustaches
[Music]
[Applause]
great now back to the sad stuff but
first one quick happy thing you look at
the side first class and plant because
they know the rollies okay sad stuff
guys it's the security team these guys
have been protecting me for the past
week incredible you see Nayeem is going
jet skiing with me in case the shark
comes up and bites me bro my boy Prince
running out in the sand dunes with me
yeah a room protecting me at the club yo
he has this slept all night just like me
neither has Prince focus guys are so
savage honestly can I bring it in guys
I'm gonna miss all of you these guys are
incredible it's very important to have
guys who are bigger than me protecting
me you guys know it the low gangster
[ __ ] it's not much I can do bro okay
back to the sense that I might see the
flight attendants who kicked me out of
the bathroom you guys saw what I did the
other day welcome to the first ever
maverick pop-up shop come on in yeah
yeah I opened up the first ever maverick
pop-up shop in the air on the flight
first-class bathrooms baby they're huge
we do anything in there anyways yeah
they ended up kicking me out and like
it's the same company so technically I
still could see them it's just kind of
awkward because I told him I wouldn't
post a video and I did it
I'm not blacklisted bro my eyes appeal
bro I don't
I don't recognize the name so far I
think we're good hey how are you oh that
look like No
hey do I look familiar I do not cuz the
last leg right oh that's cool
yo hip points back in the saddle oh my
god space is so big my boy even has room
let's go you good bro oh my god this is
amazing oh wow okay we were just weird
joking he's not gonna sit there by me
you know it's crazy I was busy having so
much fun in Dubai I didn't think of
anything crazy to do on the flight like
I have no idea what's gonna happen or
I'm probably gonna sleep who knows bro
but what I do know there's so much room
for activity yo Brendan what's up you
see that on your face it's really bright
you guess what it's wrong probably honey
honey it's so sexy
hey coming for a ball where I've ever
been blinded by a Rolex street-cred goes
up just like when I got shanked by a
bugatti key yo I'm telling you he's
shaved my Bugatti keep streak red yeah
this kind of sucks guys I'm gonna miss
you bye just really quick thank you guys
for allowing me in your country thank
you to everyone I met who came from
being for you guys it's so nice seeing
the low gang just
the united states but everywhere guys
it's a global operation the maverick
enterprise is growing and with the dream
and a little hard work and the Maverick
logo we taken over the world one day at
a time now on that note I gotta pee
follow the Maverick is back you look at
the bathroom it's empty right see
personally I think it looked better with
the merchant it may be I do something
else in here I don't know maybe I do
something in the shower like that's cool
that could totally work I just got to
figure out what exactly
ooh decisions decisions looks like
decision collision oh man I'm gonna I'm
gonna go sit down somebody sit down I
mean lay down don't forget I have not
slept yet and I'm just really thankful
he's bad this is again like a 16-hour
flight and I'm hoping that when I wake
up it's dark because my sleepy goes oh
right now is full let's see how long we
can sleep
[Music]
yeah oh my god ah what year is it
it was my roller oh you know okay
I slept forever oh my gosh the boy was
tired let's see what we're dealing with
oh oh let's look for 14 hours I'm Tula
hamdullah do it okay
ah bad news guys oh good news we're
almost in LA so I didn't get to do
anything in the shower but the good news
is I think we have a couple surprises
for us waiting back home no I want to
see Kong I want to see maverick I want
to see Evan Lydia's like she's like she
looks she's cool okay let's go home back
in Los Angeles josh is my home guys
while we were away they put plants
everywhere plants more plants and more
this is crazy this place is turning into
like a jungle obviously they still have
a lot of work to do here all the Yeti
you got a baby brother
oh my gosh I miss so much
oh wow
yo real-life moment right now I actually
missed this dog a lot like I really
loved calm yes he's so precious hi buddy
what you think the new toy oh he loves
it he loves a new Roley yeah we did no
no no - good to see you Lydia is Evan
here is your wiener up how you doing bro
don't pick it up okay okay oh yeah this
reminds me we gotta have an intervention
with Evan soon because they call he does
play video games and obviously we can't
forget about my boy what are you doing I
was in Dubai yeah I know you've got a
front center view of all the jungle
you're a spoiled little pear just see
Wednesday ritual yo good to see you
turned it into a jungle look at those
things
hey George thanks dude free Kong this is
you what are we gonna do with this they
put the mirrors up - Zoli I'm sorry I'm
coming home and is everything's new bro
it's like a new house
you about to get swole in this room bro
right look you can see yourself oh my
god it's me hey what's poppin okay and
like the that the universal oh that's so
sick as remember guys on this side it's
in Reverse oh hi Super Saiyan Logan how
are you hi six-pack Kong how are you
looking good over there speaking of Kong
is he he's pooping he's pooping pooping
he's not gonna know until he watches my
vlog tomorrow cuz you know he's
subscribed by the way if you're not
subscribed what are you doing
subscribe for me second piece of good
news this is all good stuff the pink
hoodies are back in stock yo these are
like these sold faster than the favorite
hoodie both are fully restocked still
the softest hottest merch in the game
Logan Paul calm /op orally in
description now if you'll excuse me I'm
gonna get booed at five we actually have
another guest coming over soon I think
you guys know
I crashed the mountain I cross the sea
[Music]
Italy Italian fell apart at the apone
we're going more like we're going from
Dubai to Italy to Andy and Bank
peppering in the eggs all the way baby
you got here cinquecento guys we cross
the mountain no you were driving for how
many days five days Oh Mike you're
Andy's baby
Oh yo we got Andy we got a new car we
got bro what are you doing oh my boys
hungry
my food he's fine he Brendon eats a lot
actually that's he never stops eating
I ordered a leg they sent the wrong leg
so then I was on a search to find the
leg bone in bone a leg
yo we're multicultural ass so like I
said guys there's a lot going on in fact
we're leaving right now cuz we have
something to go
[Applause]
brings on it oh yes yes Kenny this on a
remote now very nice - oh snap
they mounted the merge gun and back my
boys made in a bar bro it's a fart then
yo this is crazy
oh my gosh so drinking and driving of
course not definitely not but for the
guests go for it oh yes yes okay come
here do you guys remember when I got the
cool bus we had a contest if you bought
merch within the 48 hours of me getting
the cool bus I'll just pick 10 of you to
put your names inside here and fly two
of you out you guys are still gonna come
but the names are here bro my people
Alex kadar Chloe Mason Ben Hoffman Shane
Bowles and Samantha do Garth wedding
McCoy Marlene Lopez Austin Wright Hanna
Jean Alexandre Tober thank you guys for
joining the maverick revolution you're
now an external part of the cool bus so
when everyone walks in they see your
name plastered on the front Thank You
Kenny
no problem anytime anything so say bro
watch the windows for me real quick mmm
yeah what you know about that automatic
tent they also put a waterproof outlet
on the top and Wi-Fi whenever we need it
the bus does not have to be on so the
security cameras are gonna work it's all
good stuff it's all great stuff bro I'm
not gonna hit any more cars when I'm
backing up we got a bad joke caps trying
to go do something funny look it's
Brandon let's pin him against the wall
alright Brandon you know and with the
bus Wi-Fi we got permanent security
cameras look at this you can see
everybody and everything Ryan you boys
have done it again
why we try these requests and just I
mean it's pretty soon this thing you're
gonna ask me to fly it
I mean your house the chair color oh no
I can't wait everybody get the chair
broke whip - yeah right now I'm getting
culture I'm eating ramen Japanese and my
boy Andy what did you bring for us bro
oh you'll even be known as akuto yeah
yeah and he was watching the vlogs and
he saw that our wine cellar is empty so
he brought like the most of 50 classic
Italian wine I might be in a bit of but
remembered I mean we may get the wine oh
oh my god yeah Logan BuzzFeed definitely
worth a lot definitely this one goes go
put these in the cellar let's go damn Oh
Mamma Mia
Oh actually cool cellar you know why
it's so cool dude because this is like
real so this is a real like real because
like back in the days this is history
people writing back in the days to make
the wine sir you want the same
temperature as the earth ah
so bored by this history lesson Andy oh
look at Brenda put these for not a part
of the logo subscribe actually you know
what if you're not a part of the okay
don't even worry about we beat you also
copy amount of merch know how to stop
this dopest biggest coolest ever
maverick merging the game of revolution
of people changing the world the
maverick enterprises growing into the
top back in a way back to the grind low
gang I love yarn I'll see you tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]