[Applause]
nothing like a little fresh cocoa yeah
oh Jesus temper engine with your mother
was in this camera huh okay well that's
a good start to the day
okay as you know we are in the beautiful
state of Hawaii and it's the fourth of
July you would usually have another epic
day playing in Hawaii if you've been
watching the vlogs you have been
watching the vlogs and if you haven't
been what's lets subscribe if you're not
subscribed but we haven't had like a
water day yet so we're to cruise the
coast snorkel maybe smash little bit
it's gonna be a good happy fourth of
July everybody
Evan you ready always trying to foster
and you going out on a trip you gotta
have supply let me run you through what
we got okay so we got a bag we got some
potato chips and alcohol that should be
good numero uno importantto we need a
boat
[Music]
what are you you're allocating Paulo
yeah yeah yeah for sure that's what that
is
what's your name Oh
my name's Sofia - yeah we're just
looking for a boat have you seen it yeah
like a boat it floats
what she's been oh I love a boat that
floats I really do you know my boys got
a speaker bigger than Jake blows future
hahaha oh you know we're gonna be jammin
out boy Charlie Sonya super prone to
getting seasick I don't want it to
happen but if it does happen you want it
to happen
I got a volume yo we have like seven
hours on this boat together it's a lot
out yeah I feel like she's gonna hate me
by the end of it cool so that's a good
start for the day feel like you're gonna
hate me by the end of it so do you all
hate me
I see no no I want to see sharks they'll
be great for the vlog like ideal vlog
Sonya throws up on a shark like that's
what I'm saying
throws up on shark ain't alive we never
brought any fish guts you good bo shark
bait
you mean clickbait shark no clickbait
it's what we do on YouTube learning is
learning he don't know much
[Music]
this is so dope dude if I was alive like
way back in the day I would definitely
be a pirate
[Music]
all right Hawaii I really do
this isn't where they hide the treasure
this is the treasure
I'm feeling real it's magic crazy oh yo
can we go swimming in this water yeah
Papa has never been snorkeling before
everything
are you ready bro
[Applause]
it's so cool man
life is very good hey big bro I love
Clearwater probably one of the coolest
spots I've ever swam but now then what
is this what we're going through now
this is the most beautiful beach you
have ever seen in your entire life Wow
let's go swimming again nuts got the
camera to the island is he is he good
Rob you think are you good brother you
can't use your deathless clickbait huh
he's still alive okay a lot of people
have been commenting on my white thighs
look guys I was born that way
right I'm just a person what can I do
that be able to have a job my gosh I've
had that same reaction 12 times I need
to smash your one day any takers
ya know it's like natural shower spring
water the best height that's a lot of
water falling it really the her
specially cuz I'm sunburned yo I'm like
a lot
[Music]
Oh in the crash oh my god I would be
such a bet and homey salty and that cuz
this salt water them he's just angry oh
it's mr. Krabs I feel about crabs dude
like I look he's bubbling from his mouth
see that kind of thing worries me like I
don't know I don't know okay guys it's
the fourth of July what part of the
video oh it's okay I'll blow your face
no problem definitely not gonna blow
their face I'm just gonna go twice up in
the grocery store go what are you doing
no shoes no shirt in the Soviet service
we got to my right bro are you guys in
the low game get your ass home and get a
big Z play so they got a lot of options
here we got these good hot dogs but I
think I gotta go with this hot dog goes
down stop stop stop you're making me
upset I've been you've been making me
upset yeah anyone want to buy an oven
half off today it's 4th of July special
oh she's frozen frozen is it cold
oh it's got cold freezer for three oh we
get back to the house and yet another
surprise pink my manager is in the pool
[Music]
that's my small world you can't run a
good day my man yeah there was a kid
that pulled up what yeah how do you get
the gate code we can get the gate code
he walked right in what is what does it
cost
honestly it's intrusive as but I respect
it because it's what Mavericks do guys
it's the fact of life I just realized
I'm really sunburned almost the same
color as this shirt like look at my
thighs dude go is that like a my screw
I'm she did tell me like the whole day
I'm just stubborn guys and trust me like
three days I'm really like kinda a
little bit sexy probably not okay
wear your dress is the same color as my
skin I like that also your shirt is the
same color as my skin
oh nice murse doodoo easy with that
machete Geoffrey uh he's been here for
ten minutes or like beach party or so I
don't know I'm not for me
[ __ ] my name dear out of seconds right
there we have arrived at the room y'all
I mean this place is poppin look at
dudes standing on my shoulder and stuff
life is good by the way guys my sunburn
is slowly starting to sink in the still
going though I was back we're going
chess I'm gonna give them the server
where's he going with the giant Punk so
many people here in Jeffster just
walking around with the giant pump what
are you doing guys I literally cannot
imagine what is going through Jeff's
mind right now is why I love the guy
though Avery and Jeff is walking towards
the fire no no no no drop your whole
daily vlogs footage in there hold up
this is my clickbait this is phenomenal
but it sucks
give it CPR bro I got it on video vlog
Logan just got his thumbnail and title
for today my brother lost all this vlog
no my brother lost his entire blog he's
done it's not every day bro today from a
viewer look yeah it cuz I see my fall
you know yeah we gotta go faster we got
ever get the footage rose okay we are in
the Edit Bay let's see if the foot is
just future let's see if the footage is
still there okay first of all does the
computer recognize the car
yes yeah yeah
[Applause]
okay I love you okay here's what's going
down if you're not a part of the family
hit the subscribe button
join the lo game get your maverick merch
link in description happy out 4th of
July everybody and now we'll see you
tomorrow because it's every day
[Applause]
[Music]
do you think Jake actually got married