[Music]
that's fine that's cool
don't worry about it if Mike wanted to
play games then I was down to play games
it was time to do some research after
sitting down and reviewing the vlog
footage I was still unable to tell who
this mysterious blue hooded woman was so
I had to take it one step further okay
I'm gonna check the security footage no
too pixelated no way to confirm an
identity and then suddenly it hit me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [ __ ] oh my god did you have sex with
your birthday president did you know
where that was over this morning yeah
but I didn't we had a great night we
went got from Froyo and I know everybody
wants to hear this story of sexual
exploitation and just insane hot stuff
but that's not the news report happen
today you are know otherwise some cheek
kisses some hugs a lot of cuddling and
also dude this chick is [ __ ] awesome
bro and like oh my god well I'm gonna to
go ahead and take credit for the best
birthday gift of all times I get I've
gifted you love you guys make out tongue
anything are you guys chopping it up
laying it down like a tomahawk so this
is bear's burger play I'm like the last
person that come in here like how fun do
your burgers don't come cut in half you
pages who rabbit I mean you could just
use got it I was just had Bob mentoring
on our podcast how are you guys seeing
of commentary check out his voice Oh
hiya Bob battery with Logan Paul Mike
what a time it was here we talked about
thinking it was unbelievable Baban
wanted to have you commentate just like
random things in my life do you think
we're gonna make to have it alright so
here we are the turtle is about to eat
the strawberry first of all this is what
my dicks gonna look like after going to
the Vixen party with big mouth Larry
synapses is Maria what Maria is doing
right now is the hardest job on planet
Earth because the amount of [ __ ] stains
on this bed I mean if I had that little
flashlight it would be a nightmare so
what's going on over there in the corner
is I basically no [ __ ] idea Logan
Paul is dumping hot sauce on an onion
you think he could afford more than this
but times are tough I guess after that
big loss to Kay asylum he is doing
something know where he is putting the
onion in the socket he's looking at Mike
giving each other sub we are look Logan
spinning the onion flips up on the
ground and now all [ __ ] is broken loose
he is spanking in the ass with it on
you're beating the [ __ ] out of Mike's
being a [ __ ] this is just disturbing we
got a new tank for our turtle pancake
he's been cooped up for some time now so
this is actually pretty exciting it's
not pancake I got good news and bad news
the good news is we got you a new tank
to swim in it's a much bigger and you
can have much more room the bad news is
unfortunately your head still looks like
a penis there we go it's time for a new
life pancake it's a big day pancake this
is actually pancakes new tank it's not a
pool
[Applause]
oh it's not bad he said this was
designed to go through humans this
rubber man replicates a human and this
is actually supposed to be like bone can
I use yeah no please give me your weed
oh well I just want to give her some
character if the head comes off in one
swipe I'll hurl my lifeless body into
the swimming pool with all my clothes
head off before don't let go of the
blade when you swing right
[Music]
[ __ ] look
I have Mike's location in my phone and
he's in West Hollywood he never leaves
the house so there's only one reason
that he would be in West Hollywood why
are you down here right now
[Music]