I want to make a song with you about how
everyone has their hero and then make
the dopest music video of 2017 is gone
this is no good for multiple reasons I'm
supposed to be recording a song tonight
I'll get into that in a little bit - I'm
in the middle of shooting a movie Oh
morning Carly oh you puppy I'm in the
middle of shooting a movie and if I show
up sounding like hey guys maybe shoot
your movie it's just not good it's not
the meeting that we had beautiful that's
not the video good morning
oh good morning to you too I already
said it there hi puppy okay guys today
is actually a big day like a really big
day if you guys remember there's this
kid named zircon and he made this song
about me a few days ago okay you are my
year any minute another video like
although he's my hero like he reacted to
my song so happy and then I decided I
was like yo you know I'm gonna fly this
get out here to hang out for a day
anyways he's coming now so I yeah I'm
his hero no but do I look like a hero to
you right now bro I'm a hot mess
definitely don't sound like I'm sick and
I went out last night with my cast mates
[Laughter]
okay guys I'm gonna shower off because I
don't look like here alright now and
then we'll get into the day 12 seconds
later I'm ready now bro feeling like a
hero xx dude I never thought I'd be a
hero growing up I thought it'd just be
some rollercoaster tycoon
you're not playing roller coaster tycoon
no you're not no oh my gosh you're
actually playing roller coaster tight
dude this is why I love you
oh do we have guests yes we've got we
have guests
[Applause]
hey loser Kahn what the kid that's
coming here oh you know him by his real
name which is what by the way no like
another hour
oh thanks this burrito by the way yo
today is also Father's didn't wait yeah
a puppy I don't know what you're doing
but I'm gonna need this back okay
dog boy today is Father's Day I do have
a dad so I'm gonna give him a clap call
you gotta chill give my dad a call being
good son
happy Father's Day dad okay bye so that
was cool Brendan did you FaceTime your
dad broke no I should do that you know
it's Father's Day it's time dad where's
dad oh oh
foster bro are you good oh I don't know
what's going on with your dad I know I
got that you good bro survey right here
and take that survey guys we'll come
back to Brendan in a second okay guys
we're back what are you good bro oh this
is good though guys my voice is slowly
coming back waking up I'm starting to
kind of feel like a hero I put this cool
thing on I've had no Congo no and I
think the only thing left to do as a
hero is to dance
I was really good so while we wait for
the boys to get here I did move math
into my room wanna try something though
I had this ladder here if we put this
like this bro we could make the bridge
to terabithia look at look at how much
fun yeah I know I know if I was saying
to come here
Dorfman once you stand under it I can
almost guarantee over your left shoulder
there are some low gangster somehow that
got up on the roof that's a new spot I
don't know they got some see like there
must be serious vloggers bro do they
even know we're vlogging them right now
absolutely not I think these windows are
tinted bro which means he was just
dabbing nothing I respect the man who
could dab below that back that back it's
a universal low gang sign Oh guys I'm
going out there here's the catch I'm
only gonna talk in sign language do you
know sign language absolutely not
okay they're kind of dope i'ma cut this
could you understand you want you want
to buy merch personally it's Sunday
there's never time to not do business
I'm here to sell and commercialize our
we got the classic we got the that's got
that new fourth of July maverick tank
top bro this is like a commercial right
Elvis yeah you know classic put it in
the package thanks bro they're all
classes they're all collect you know why
I can't let me give you guys the low
gang discount what's that I just like
just having 20 bucks
wait how did you yeah we just find
stairs oh that's that maverick life now
here's the transaction I had to charge
him something okay
Sunday Funday made a quick buck I gave
him a $30 discount you know anything for
the low gang I'm an [ __ ] brush
should've given to a for free bro okay
now back to zircon I just got some super
secret Intel that he's like five minutes
away got it
so yeah bro is go time zircon let's do
this
it's up guys it's time for the big dogs
to get in the ring this is young doggie
King Kong to savage bomb both human love
him young noise come in zircon what did
you expect
did you ever think this would happen
from me either
I just yesterday I was like get this kid
here god damn it get him in my house
this is mad with the pay yeah yeah
there's Noah not zircon thank you very
much no no no what's America it's Noah
okay guys here we are all crammed in a
minivan thanks to Ayla way to get a
minivan to get us to the next location
it's true guys I'm thankful for you in
my life oh wait what looking for vlogs
is playing oh that's crazy Wow no
Photoshop at all okay guys first item in
the agenda throat we are going to what I
think is like a cool mansion house and
we're gonna do a photo shoot with the
Maverick March okay not crazy exciting
but I thought you should know cuz you're
now in my life but bro I have questions
for you dude
this music video that you made how did
you do it from like there was high
production bro
there were subtitles you are my eros a
professionally recorded song keep on
making me laugh there's photos bro your
hot tub had like a little lightsaber
boner and there's a picture of me if I
ever met you how did you do that you
wrote the song you wrote the lyrics
can you sing one line when I was 10 I
started first uploading videos to
YouTube so when I saw that video I'm not
even kidding I saw myself in you with
this like actually good video and how
many subscribers do you have no bro it
took me eight years to get 4,000
subscribers congratulations that's
amazing
come on boys okay we're at the first
location talk to me everyone we got go
around you help inspire me somewhere in
my life I see myself living in a house
like this are you down to still be my
roommate
this is the shot a beautiful staircase
Noah hop in there yo that's what the
future looks like that's what the future
looks like
[Music]
I'm chasing you got it
come get it all of my love all my love
[Music]
what you actually cannot be filming I
talked to someone upstairs when like a
little while ago some guy keep someone
from the building yeah poor guy
and what did they some important first
off and what do they say hey look they
said that every time you film in your
house you are not allowed to post it
because it violates a contract oh so
maybe I should stop so I stopped
blogging nor would you go to three what
do you think Brendan should I stop bro
yeah I don't I don't think I'm gonna I
think that for sure
in fact look outside right now there's a
full-fledged party going on across the
way this is every Saturday I'm inside
China what what Ayla I'm trying to get
work done in this parties across the way
we have the thing bro this is okay great
so what are you gonna do it I'm gonna
handle this party the way should be
handled I need everyone we need the
music
to be long I'm just saying it goes both
ways
I've notified the authorities of this
part wrap it up okay
Barney's or what last thing before the
cops come follow me on instagram at
Logan Paul
I wish I could argue sorry about that
guys back to the real ah my man you made
a song called Logan you are my hero
am I really a hero yeah why bro even I
like my favorite youtubers heck yeah
knuckle-touch me dude
bangers so dude I wanted to fly you out
to LA and I was like yo it's cool if we
hang out and do like la stuff but I
thought there's something cooler that we
could do I want to make a song with you
about how everyone has their hero and
then make the dopest music video of 2017
well I got the best producer in the game
the best house in the game the best cars
in the game we're gonna break the
Internet bro you're you're in like and
subscribe and peace what did you try to
end my vlog no and in fact okay bro I've
invested some time into this already do
you want to hear the beat okay hacky
idea - love you excited
[Music]
everybody has a hero like it well can
you imagine like okay I'm not gonna show
you guys everything it's gonna get epic
my man we have writing to do you wrote
your song yet yeah so you're a lyrical
Pro pretty much yeah we're gonna go over
some lyrics that we're gonna sing bro 12
seconds later hi how are you Logan here
okay guys some time has passed it's dark
outside in we are currently recording yo
how do you feel really awesome awesome
right bro are you ready to spit fire on
this track yeah are we gonna break the
internet yeah okay guys we were gonna
record for a little bit this music video
is coming out Wednesday cuz we're
actually shooting it tomorrow if you're
not subscribed make sure to subscribe we
are the fastest growing channel on
YouTube get your maverick merch link in
description and we will see y'all
tomorrow
take it easy Pam
Oh
[Music]