[Music]
[Applause]
as you guys know yesterday I forgot my
last name bro do you can you tell me
what it is dude I think it's Paul Hoch
up this morning with a little bit of a
deep voice a little bit of a baby Lock
them doors and turn the lights down low
for I think what the grills in and a
deep voice bro it's time for a freestyle
hey it's maybe some mappers getting a
house boy not good at this I'll throw as
you guys know I got Evan grills I bought
grills for my roommate ever except
yesterday this is list of harm I take
about haha except yesterday he wasn't
here he wasn't here to get the grill I
have his grills now I'm gonna give him
today I'm gonna show you guys what they
look like I'm not gonna give them to him
yet oh yeah here come on literally hid
them in the same exact spot that right
is yeah thank you ever that I hate his
Rolex when I got him the Rolex it's over
here look it makes sense because like he
can't he can't reach this high and yeah
Cybele get that nice jacket bro do that
bro in rubies across the top it says
Mamba cuz you know dwarf mom clever
I know yo these people won't why is the
22 year old telling adults not to party
I don't know weird world we live in some
line cost me $10,000 Evans that I got
him cost $10,000 but I'm gonna tease him
a little bit because I don't even think
you've seen mine yet rally the troops
I've never seen someone play this many
video games and not get bored not even
good bro look brah
no you put problem no you just gotta
kill you [ __ ] good now stop
oh now I'm Logan Paul calm /op no for
real those fire bro you could put your
friend in it though right so the girls
are pretty cool okay 200 you wanted your
grill oh don't push me bro
I will merge candy yeah yeah I'll get
you your girls and start snooping around
bro and he goes right for the spot he
knows
yeah yeah and turn the shower on so
Brendan have anything I'm shower but I
know for a fact there's scuse me right
now I'm gonna catch there what are you
doing Brendan maybe weird oh yeah you
can't get any more dull my man you're
dumped Brendan Brendan you betrayed me
bro did you get them or no they're still
up there you can see it can you Wow oh
you can see them up there bro you can
see him bro that's all you see you you
won't pants me right now no they all
well
Lydia close your eyes
I don't think he did it I'm no more no
more this you I got to move these girls
[Music]
speaking of cool breath as if you need
to get doper bro hey buddy with Jamie
you're already sound very convincing
dwarf he's that's that's a fact
yeah boy you're focused you're hilarious
you're a dwarf and you're my boy put you
on your knees you don't mess with that's
pretty funny bro should we work man and
reward him with his dress I think he
deserves a bone right that was funny
yeah that was pretty funny bro we're
gonna give you your girls but you got to
put on some merch now my boys
no it's you size to give you okay
anyways do we both have freaking
matching grills bro yeah you already
wore but now I'm Logan Paul outdoor
smuggler and this is that's what I'm
saying well when it can Negin canditate
my jewelry is literally worth more than
me it's kind of stuff I should start
spending my money and smarter things
this is getting stupid bro this is
getting ridiculous look well look if you
make money and you havin fun buy jewelry
good when you die you can't take money
with you that's all right you know what
we need to do but what we need to just
walk around Hollywood and just like
[Music]
damn sexy I swear swear swear I swear I
got a leash my gosh why I swear I've
never felt this qualified in sexy eating
burgers kids I also I just want to say
life is not about material objects and I
I am aware that in my vlogs especially
recently I may be like making it look
like that no that's that's not what it's
about
I find my happiness my joy comes from
the high of doing stuff that I shouldn't
be doing I II spending way too much
money on grilled it's just a bonus that
they look cool but be safe no I mean yes
be safe but be responsible with your
money that's what I'm trying to say cuz
if now you become poor and die
everyone's gonna do it and according to
the stats on Google you might die ten
years earlier than me I'm gonna kill you
before me so I don't care oh hey hi no
we outside George's house right now I
can't barking it outside that we're
[Music]
gonna take my own questions or hurting
my head Brooke sure sure I take em up
now show me you thrown in the garbage
higher yeah favors not wasting your
money on jewelry that you makes you look
like a rapper from the West oh I had
this conversation with the low gang
already dude y'all listen I come if they
did with the light here I said it's not
about material object just make me throw
my 10 does not run in the trash it's
$10,000 whoa
I'm sorry I'm gonna throw this out there
why does your boy look like post Malone
Hughes been waiting to hear that
sentence his whole life you know my
brother that was a weird thing having a
housewarming party bro woman party Paul
okay
Ferran has one bite but we want you to
come bring all your friends who are we
we can't afford $10,000 grills new Gucci
brother my turning in listen little no
quick little message of inspiration
growing up I worked as hard as I
possibly could whenever I was put to the
test I would challenge myself my I would
challenge myself and I would make sure
that I am giving everything that I put
my heart into 100% effort I'm fortunate
enough to say that obviously it has paid
dividends in my life and all has allowed
me to do the through crazy shoes that I
do now including buy some dumbass grills
and and jewelry and stuff that I really
don't need that's a fact but the point
is fricking grinded bro still now
everyday grind grind grind working
extremely hard and I'm able to now
afford these luxuries so don't think it
comes easy one day it's gonna happen for
you just put your head down humble
yourself and work as hard as you can I'm
a believer in the idea that if you do
good things good things will happen to
you so I am down to spend $30,000 now at
this point
my roommate Evan he's not a boy he's my
best friend and I know one day he's
gonna return the favor or maybe it comes
back around full circle and someone else
does something nice for me the point is
when you're doing well
treat yourself treat others because when
one squad member feasts the whole crew
foods that hive mentality we're all on
the same team we're all on the same
families what we do baby it's the low
gang if you're not a part of the family
make sure to subscribe being maverick
because every day we're changing the
world
Logan Paul's icon / shopper link in
description I don't love y'all that was
due tomorrow
[Music]
hey what do you want from the oven