what's up jay the the fly of a drone
yeah in this
area is illegal i must arrest you for
this
don't jump bro no i'm gonna jump the
train tracks that's a terrible idea
maybe next year
current time is 6 57 a.m we are on our
way to rome
italy we've actually renamed the country
legally we've named it uh literally
as my brother's friend nick crompton
would say literally
is my city oh
oh it's a tight squeeze it's good it's
all about efficiency
one leg room you're welcome
[Applause]
off one train and on to another one
a lot of trains in liberty
look at my neck fish dab damn dude it's
gotten worse it's bad yeah why do you
rip my clothes i had to grab
something that was 2017 bro what what
would you have done huh i don't know
bought some archer
yeah if you didn't see that yesterday
got rowdy flashback
fake you're out with your ex-girlfriend
again
you know what jake it's okay i respect
you i respect you
i respect your boobs oh my god
roma roma tiana we all crashed so hard
on that plane
it's a it's a train a good one logan
definitely traveling with vloggers
especially because i didn't say this
guys but this is how andy was actually
sleeping on the train better than the
neck pillow because you could vlog hey
look at this guys
you're at the hotel right now i just
like slid down one of these railings a
little too heavy for the railings and it
uh broke we're talking about the railing
oh see
look down the rain and it broke and look
at the railing and now ruin at least we
have a coliseum
i'm not convinced that that's me bro
like this railing clearly structurally
not sound it needs an extra post here if
you're five
you are you stay with your parents don't
do this he's not
he's not five this is my dad this is my
dad hello he can be a bit of a
troublemaker
he means well so don't do this anymore
how can we go places and not get yelled
at
we just don't belong in this country
like
you know what i changed that he doesn't
belong here felicia
police no no if they aren't tell them
they're in the low gang
thumbs up he's gonna be driving us
around today i feel bad for him already
please don't kick us out of your vehicle
we need to travel never mind forget the
car i got
full holy meat holy bread
honey waiter yeah like little italian
testicles
yummy brendon is at the hotel he had to
get his bag from the airport which by
the way he's been missing the whole week
but what all right what what did you say
so i walked into the
show they wanted me to wait for the
manager to come down the manager
i'm assuming it was jake uh yeah yeah
accurate assumption can we still stay at
the hotel are we good
he told me that we can't stay here
anymore we can't say it's uh remember me
i have news we cannot stay at the hotel
actually because of this guy no you
wrote the [ __ ] around
dude you slid down railings like like
everyone does it yeah i didn't say
no it wasn't structurally sound what i'm
yo wait what yo
italians hate vloggers bro kendamvl i
want to explore rome i want to see the
colosseum i just wanted laughs
what we got how'd you get us kicked out
already no bro it was jake because
this is the last time i traveled with
jake bro like as if i'm not bad enough
freaking two vloggers no
no wait what's the problem why is italy
no problem
they hate cameras in italy bro he needs
a little problem
all right yo we got places to go bro no
no no we can't do this i'll get a
copyright complaint
put out music
just to get my actual real-life reaction
the coliseum is to my right i have not
looked at it okay i'm looking
yo you see this in postcards you see
this in movies andy what's the history
the colosseum
it was built in two years by slaves i'm
bored uh enough of that two years is
freaking huge bro
oh my gosh bro so for those of you who
don't know
inside of this coliseum gladiators would
fight to the death i'm not gonna lie my
vlogs are pretty
lit but yo it doesn't get more lit than
that that's
that's entertainment they would
apparently fill this thing with water
and pirate ships would like just
kill each other jesus christ dude the
amount of subscribers that would have
had i can't even imagine
look bro we're at the coliseum it's
beautiful i get it but i also noticed
you're not wearing any merch
you buy it on loganpaul.com good good
i'm not gonna lie i travel
to so i can experience stuff like this
there's so many people here
and like literally my whole life like is
to be different that's what being a
maverick is uh
i feel like we need to spice it up a
little bit i understand uh drone shots
here
are illegal so let's definitely do that
[Music]
[Applause]
anybody got eyes on it i do not see the
drone yo we gotta go freaking man hunt
this drone
there it is oh snap it's right there i'm
wondering if that was not ours
if that was jakes or cage drones meaning
we lost ours
that's no good what we got i don't know
where it went
oh great we're drawing this i'm trying
to say so brendan just went down there
to try to find the drone aka rest in
peace brandon
he's dead brandon brennan's definitely
dead
update what we got so we just gotta talk
some brendan saying i found it
ellipsis military has it oh oh that's
just [ __ ] great oh you gotta be
[ __ ] kidding me bro
okay so he's over there i'm assuming the
drone is to the right by the military
guys
waving me the figure what what's up like
i just i literally like barely pointed
at them and they're freaking out
when they this is a disaster like it was
a [ __ ] alien
bro that's because they don't know what
cameras are here bro all right yo i'm
gonna go in i'll have to like iphone
footage this stuff
oh gang wish me luck
this is a disaster oh my god voice mojo
you guys speak english uh we we have a
drone you know
yes that's the drone i i mean we call
the police
because
he knew you he knows me yeah do you
think
do you think about it youtube man yeah
famous youtuber i'm a vlog my brother is
jake paul you know
every day bro
i'll come with you if you want i will
get in your car with you i'll go
wherever you need
am i getting arrested no where am i
going hi ow
jesus what's up g
the fly of a drone yeah in this area is
illegal
i must arrest you for this okay okay so
logan you guys just saw them open the
door
and basically i swung the camera down
because they were they all walked over
to me immediately after but they took
logan logan got into the car
we don't know where he is jake is
talking to the police right now they
don't look like they're very happy with
him
we don't know where they took him we
don't know how to find him they have our
drone but this is
real life right now logan literally got
into a police car
and left with the police
all right guys so a little update right
here logan just texted us he
is at the police headquarters he told us
not to come get him
uh until he says so i think they want
all of our footage
okay guys logan just texted us he said
he wants
uh somebody to come get him so andy
i think you're the guy good luck andy
get him back
they took my brother what the [ __ ] i
love my brother
they touched
i got to rome i want to go have fun i
get it i don't want any problems
i'll pay whatever you guys need i don't
want to cause problems but i don't know
where the controller is
so however i can help you so
you are not the controller no no no it
doesn't belong to him
i'm sorry let's just we didn't want to
do this i'm sorry
sit in disaster italy
but stay tuned
also probably shouldn't be screaming
like this right as soon as i got out of
here we got our boy back yo but you
didn't get the drone back i think i can
get some drone footage maybe just like a
little
oh i already told uh i already told them
that you can have all the drone footage
i killed it okay kill the drone
rolling now this is what i got arrested
[Music]
for
i hope you enjoyed that i hope it was
worth it yo italy
hates vloggers okay so it must just be
like
anyone above the age of like 35 man
nah 2017 bro like vloggers are a thing
yo did you get wait did you get the um
army guy taking a picture with me
uh no okay okay well that's what
happened the guy the military guy that
took the drone he's in the low gang so
he's like yo come to the back of the car
take a picture i'm like give me my drone
take a [ __ ] picture with this guy the
cops show up he's like he did it
i was yo straight up that's stabbed me
in the back
i watched happen stabbed me so we get to
the station and
they're like whose drone is this i like
i didn't fly it and i blamed it on kade
oh okay his way out exactly i didn't
want to draw my boy brendan it was it
was my fault they sell the drone joan's
gone yeah joe's gone
if cade wants it if kid wants it back he
can go get it i don't recommend it
you can't stop vlogging
oh i gotta be gone i'm gonna [ __ ] with
you because i did 18 years
for killing i understand oh that's that
is racism
that's right i kill people google my
name i bet if he googles my name he'll
get more results
i'm a googler what's your name della
medallion charge is laid
attempted robbery of downtown
convenience store bro you're not
no i went to jail bro i went i've been
in jail bro
that's all the competition man pewdiepie
is next and i'm bouncing all these
checks then i got the rolex and the
batch of rumble two and i'm filming
but as a free man the first thing i want
to do is get some coffee which is rare
because i don't actually drink coffee
but under
this is the best espresso in all of the
town in my city
say no more andy let's get got it i'll
take one coffee
okay so apparently the coffee is like
super secret they make it behind the
secret wall so you can't see what the
formula is no brenda it's a
brandon my curiosity has been peaked i
think we see what's really going on back
there just ignore the vlog
[Music]
what did you guys see was it crazy was
it illegal were they killing people were
they were they drowning are they as
stuck as me
nope okay enough funny business my
expectations are high
[Music]
oh my gosh what is this bro this is so
good
i'm quitting youtube because of coffee
yeah because of this coffee yeah what am
i supposed to do
oh i don't know figure out i'm gonna
make coffee for the rest of my life
italians may hate vloggers and may hate
the internet
god damn they can do coffee look brandon
it's a me mario
[Music]
damn bro i've seen some fountains in my
life but this is a [ __ ]
guys fighting horses water flowing into
more water
[Music]
[Laughter]
like a wish it's my big day it's my big
day
i'm not gonna tell you my wish i can't
right i can't okay i'll tell you
i wish for health and wellness and lots
of smashing in my future
and to find a nice midwestern wife who's
not a hoe
that's a big wish big wish yeah big
[Music]
dreams
[Applause]
okay okay you're the best lawyer i've
ever had bro i know thank you for
thank you for saving my life bro don't
call sal call andy yeah for real the
italians were touching my butthole and
stuff and you
know you saved the day andy is leaving
us in rome we're
certifiably is that a fact that's so
funny
i don't even know how to say hi yet xiao
i thought they were talking about dog
food
you guys will be fine just a like a
following subscribe if you guys
subscribe we'll be a-okay
jesus christ hi
yo we are all exhausted italy you've
done it again
you son of a [ __ ] um good news though
as you can tell we got a hotel room so
we're not that bad after all but as you
probably guessed that is the vlog okay
today is actually this is our last night
in italy
sad i don't want to leave cause tiamo
again even though you arrested me not so
cool oh speaking of that bro the last
piece of drone
just the bag drone you've served me well
but
we'll see you next year probably not
okay if you're not a part of the logang
make sure to subscribe
hit the button for me we are the
strongest family on youtube i'll erupt
the merch i wear this shirt every day
logang
for life logan paul.com shop or link in
description hottest merch in the game
baby i love you all and i will see you
tomorrow about to fester tonight that
means party in the
italian yeah forgot the language for a
second i'm tired all right hello okay i
love you i'll see you tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
that's pretty thug