Lydia has come to the conclusion that
she thinks Kong pooped in this cage if
this is true I'm not gonna be happy
I was bald guys we're in Nashville
Tennessee right now as you know
yesterday we captured the total solar
eclipse
ah
[Applause]
deikun bro I'm sorry yes science thought
we do have to catch a flight back to Los
Angeles first I'm gonna put down this
camera good morning
what do you do with that useless stop
stop stop
hey Zeus Cristo welcome to little
Kampala guys this is Colby Colby thanks
for letting us stay your app man as a
gift I want to give you this dog no no
honey no I'm giving you this comic dog
pay attention to the comments Colby okay
thank you the comments room yeah I'm
just saying Colby like that's the
difference between like let's eat
grandma and let's eat grandma come and
save lives
yeah Kobe come and save lives Oh guys
since like the hotels flights everything
in this area had been booked forever
everybody be trying to see that Eclipse
that we had to drive two hours outside
of Nashville what's over there Brenda
the car that we used to get here oh yeah
you could drive two hours outside of
Nashville to get to this Airport where
are we dude Livia what city hunt let's
bail bro and then we got a connecting
flight into Lana to get back to Los
Angeles gonna be it's gonna be a travel
day for reals so we're standing here and
I'm looking at this door and I see this
cool blue sticker take a closer look
okay look do you guys see it it's big
guy holding a little guy hand come in
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah so I'm standing here and I see this
water foam right it says out of service
but what happens if you put a service
door under water fire here we go
wait a minute put him in our Jail put
him in I don't know why that works
here's why I like that dog he's white he
matches my shirt brother that maverick
we're job to you today car service dog
not an [ __ ]
I do have bad news as usual when we
travel I don't know why this happens to
us we got delayed we got too late and
it's a connecting flight land in Atlanta
at 3:20 we board to go to Los Angeles at
322 we're so clear they're all in the
situation what do we do for every bite
of airplane food that I eat I feel like
I died a little bit more and more on the
inside which isn't saying much because I
feel like a lot of me is probably
already dead I'm just sad we're not
gonna make it back to Los Angeles dude
this is this is your fault how is it you
booked the flight no I don't know my
travel with you it's never good I know
but but you know what is good no Rolex
on your followers in Huntsville
Huntsville what's that where we are
right now I don't know what you're
talking about yo what is this this an
astronaut jumpsuit you got to get it we
have to this is amazing bro I love once
ville thank yo this costume is out of
this world this is your big day all
right I think we just go right into like
an Evan astronaut space montage
[Music]
Bates Whitley no Evan no we're not going
to space we're going to Atlanta and the
flights 30 minutes so don't get
comfortable no space so we landed that
was a quick flight problem though it is
a 323 our connecting flight to Los
Angeles Awards one minute ago is this a
disaster
oh no it's not gonna be okay Lydia go as
we're not okay gotta yeah you know we
have no time where's our gate
again I need something to be turnover
transfers a mix is bad you've got very
difficult are making progress let's go
space do that we lost a yeah
time for day we're looking nice
I'm just screaming and everybody's
bloggers doing on our plane oh look it's
Lydia hello we're at a nineteen we're
going to Los Angeles you coming you
can't find us cuz you were slow dude
you know get that maverick pace angry
you're on you're on team maverick that's
what we do Lydia she's so angry some
guys should come what have we learned
no no no now when we learned what have
we learned Lydia you gotta get what you
want to get against all odds Logan we've
done it become a space cadet next to me
it's a good day yeah also you I forgot
to mention my song and music video help
me help you I woke up yo it passed the
hundred million views lo que we're
frickin flying bro and that cause I'm on
a plane is because we got a hundred
million views you know you guys know
this I'm starting to do like actual
music I'm coming out with an EP my goal
is for all those videos wait for it to
get a hundred million views nothing we
can't do shoot for the moon even if you
miss you'll land among the stars less oh
man dude I just I can't be trapped in
please bro you guys know the dead let's
go back home
oh via has come to the conclusion that
she thinks Kong proved in this cage if
this is true I'm not gonna be happy
it's true guys if I'm suffering you have
to suffer look at it's right there it's
right next to the boarding pass look at
it okay
absorb it holidays suck bro I got dumped
this poop yeah
use the boarding pass is a soft poop oh
man life is never boring here so yeah we
get back home the little gang as usuals
waiting for us my guy I can't tell if
he's good bro I can't tie his energy I'm
just gonna go ahead and say you know you
know it's great about the video you're
recording this video bro is gonna just
show all my acne so just make sure to
tag me at loca pull I used to be Logan
Paul yeah how long have you been waiting
here you're on a flight for like twice
as long as that travel days yeah oh one
small step for man and even a smaller
step for Dorf yeah there goes Kong
running back and forth didn't miss a
beat I know a lot of stupid dogs but car
may take the cake do we need to give him
the survey not going me yes there you go
bro can you do me a favor fill this out
you let me know what spilled out and
I'll get back to you I'll okay
yeah hit house no no it didn't happen
here that's why we had to go to
Nashville no that's actually factually
incorrect anyways anyways anyways ready
you're gonna calm down
ah oh look you finished her low back
home yeah I see you filled it out Oh
you good bro dog makes sense an
interesting day for sure Kong has been a
bit noisy so we had to put him in their
jail no my boy but yo if you're not a
part of the logcat
make sure to subscribe guys you you know
this you watch the vlogs we are the most
live family on YouTube but I will say
that every day until I die what's given
my daily activities might be somewhat
soon hopefully not but yo if you have
not kept your maverick merci I'd do it
man join the movement I'm serious guys I
see wearing the merch posting pictures
with it using the hashtag be a maverick
our merch page maverick by Logan Paul is
over a million followers yo we are so
out here it's unreal there's the
incredible link for that in the
description or logo ball COMSEC Chuck
hey it was good to be off a plane low
gang I love y'all I'll see you tomorrow
take it easy fam hello can paul man it's
no surprise that when i see your face i
want to swim in your eyes are so dreamy
and no dude i don't like guys but your
godly features got me hypnotized yo