just grab it yank it out bro three two
[Laughter]
this entire pulls a green screen with a
guest it's our favorite friend and I am
is penis hell yeah suddenly my pool is
clean except that's not the reality and
this is gonna cost me thousands of
dollars some kid hit me up he's like yo
you wanted to join my zoom collection
and so I was like okay why could you get
in trouble for this
you think they'll recognize me like will
my cover be blown like I'm clearly not a
student it's a film class I'm some funds
Oh Karin this that Karin what did you do
did you tell me we'll go upside down
until let dad's ejaculate marinate like
my brother probably why everything in
your life on your birthday is upside
down
oh no I've been doing improv classes you
didn't think I was weird
this was the birthday gift that I got
that Mike told me would change my life
and technically it's a mantis shrimp
which you guys watched my podcast it
positive it is my favorite animal and of
like a knockoff mantis shrimp like a
real mantis shrimp is super colorful and
I think that's why I like him so much I
just found out some very disappointing
news from Danny oh god he doesn't know
doesn't know I hate my kid my mom said
even when I was 2 years old I would give
the gifts back to Santa if I didn't like
I gave the gift back to Santa so this is
just a thing I do since I was two years
old
oh if everyone knew why did you still
give me the gift I was kind of thinking
it was funny how Logan got Mike a hot
girl with the Lambo and in return Logan
got a shrimp why did you just say what
did you just say no no no I got him the
Michael Jordan of porn and he got me a
$6 marine animal feel bad for the shrimp
dude like he doesn't know me that he's
whackers you know what I'm saying like
he doesn't has no idea it's kind of like
most of these like guy tick tock stars
like they don't even know how bad they
are a proposition for you on the ping
pong table you see that a can of spray
paint if I can hit it from here you have
to pee your pants
on your stream but if I miss I'll be my
pants on your stream no if you miss you
have to pee your pants on every stream
with me if I edit what I'll pay $500
I got a huge bladder here I'm going it's
too late Oh suddenly you become the
little brother I hate again to close my
brain I feel like you hit my brain oh
she's crying that's not true these are
tears of happiness you're crying
it's too bad taking it out right this
hurts so [ __ ] bad son it said that
Sunday Oh
we're an emergency right now because we
can't get it out that sounds like
torture Jesus mother of God how do they
go now that we know that just grab it
yank it out bro no no you think so
3 2 1
got yo ass that is so dumb do we got
bolt cutters I didn't think I'd be at
this point in my life ever this what
happens we turn 25 it look like you
after your party gets dougie
alright don't hey look at me guys I need
my dime I'm not gonna actually eat it
[Music]