so how you been it's been a great day
today it's my best friend's birthday
dude is happy the great state of mind
yeah about that hey what's up today's my
25th birthday I'm 25 oh [ __ ] this is
crazy I'm actually not a fan of
birthdays on if you guys want to give me
a gift just hit that subscribe nobody I
was born on April Fool's very fitting
cuz I'm a [ __ ] fool however full
transparency I hate my birthday I hate
birthdays ever since my brother pranked
me on my 22nd birthday with the fake
Lamborghini prank and I cried and I told
it was the best day of my life and then
on my 23rd birthday when I got kicked
out of he was somebody National Park and
then on my 24th birthday when my mom
shot me in the back with paintballs dude
it's just real and so I really have like
severe PTSD and trust issues with this
particular day it's a disaster so I'm
not doing on stairs I'm gonna be very
cautious and hopefully no one
[Music]
Oh my birthday's are oh that's a [ __ ]
nightmare what have I done these are my
feet
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is what happened before the fake
fight scene a real fight I get severe
Savannah even getting an Alec anxiety
and PTSD just cuz like I birthdays have
been don't like the pressure put on hey
guys my heart is beating faster than it
was before my fight so for the past
month I've been trying to figure out
what to get you that could repay you for
the gift that you got me for my birthday
I thought about it all porn stars houses
cars the problem is you already have
everything as a group we sat down we
thought to ourselves what is the one
thing the one thing that he never
thought humanly possible for him to
possibly possess as a human in this
world
the remainder of my testicle there's no
way you told them what is this bro it's
gonna be a dick in front of me now
that's what I got one two three
no [ __ ] way bro no Qingwei oh no no
no is the stag beetle your favorite
animal
no the mantis shrimp everyone knows the
coolest animal on earth is called the
mantis shrimp the mantis shrimp not
[ __ ] is a badass it's your very
own mantis shrimp you're [ __ ] lying
how did you do this I thought they're
like illegal here what's the special
power let's do this let's go again
I'll act surprised and then we're going
to one two three
oh oh oh it's a mantis shrimp boy like a
dick gonna be high for this bro it's use
literally it's like been the only thing
that you couldn't get I thought you were
gonna be excited for two months you
having me up to get a shrimp like this
is the thing for real brothers like for
two months I've been told like yeah
there's some crazy give coming and you
give me a yes of you guys the Polish you
don't like you know I like things what
he's barricaded himself guys he's more
disappointed in fact he all forgot him
for the original crank of the fact that
he became the butt of the joke welcome
to LA home of the fake tits and real
[ __ ]
this is yeah it's bad is this your oh
this is like why I don't like birthdays
because like I took the first thing I
said today expectation management and
the pressure of like gift giving and
receiving it just gives me so much
anxiety like for two months for all mike
is like you're gonna look at me as a
different person because of the gifts I
asked you for your birthday you might
cry like these are like to kind of guess
they're gonna make you like well I'm a
little bit beyond us with you bro I
don't really care about that shrimp is
dealing why it's not a really a mantis
shrimp dude like it's it's a part of the
reason I I think I'm obsessed with the
mantis shrimp is because I'm colorblind
and the real mantis shrimp is so vibrant
it's kind of just like a monochrome like
shrimp on over
like when i walked in i was like that's
i don't think that is what it looks like
[Music]
[Applause]
it's been a great day today it's my best
friend's birthday dude is happy the
great state of mind
yeah about that horrible sigh did you
think my acting was good when I was like
pretending to heaven that I didn't like
this room what if I told you that I
wasn't acting have you sad and now I
feel bad I feel I feel bad because I
know how you how excited you were to
give me the gift and then now I'm
wondering why I feel bad on a day where
I ideally shouldn't have anything to
worry about and this is why I don't like
birthdays
oh snap free crying I appreciate the
gift simply the gift of love and
camaraderie that's exactly right Jake
otherwise your presents I'm sorry mr.
[ __ ] I really am you know it's not a
you thing it's a
[Music]