let me do this right now I'm with the
man Congress average con could you look
at the camera for me just look right
here come here okay I'm also with the
man wait hold on hold on I'm gonna get
that we'll get there so what we're doing
right now is actually huge game changing
denting the universe every single day I
have a dream every single day maverick
every single day I'm gonna get there in
a second okay so um you guys saw
yesterday's vlog it's not up yet so Jeff
actually doesn't know this I think this
is good that he hears this I spent
$12,000 yesterday and Gucci clothes
receipts don't ya it's not my brand to
return stuff Logan we only wear the
Maverick brand I know I know I know I
know I know I know but there's no
handlebars music video we're shooting on
the 24th you know about it you're
producing you said it I'm just trying to
win a Gucci breath I'm growing up the
stache it's all about having a look
hence the mustache family so that's a
thing also I love one of the Rings I
bought yesterday I lost as you guys know
lost at the premiere for my movie King
bachelors movie uh where's the money
what I was combing through the footage
cuz you know her log last I blog
everything and I noticed at one point I
was on the bus and if you zoom in here
you can see I'm still wearing the ring
on my pink and then we shot outside the
bus and if you look here you zoom into
my piggy you'll see the ring is no
longer on my feet which is good news for
me cuz that means context clues right
it's on the bus somewhere it has to be
or right when you got off its self
just say after this we're gonna go check
on the bus for the ring it's like a five
hundred dollar ring I really want to
find this ring that's right now today's
the day guys I've been talking about it
for weeks you already know what it is
from the title of this video monkey can
you get up here and give me views but
your boy has found and today is
purchasing a house just a boy from Ohio
who moved to Los Angeles to pursue his
dream didn't listen to the haters who
didn't listen to the people who said you
couldn't make money and actually make a
career out of making videos on the
Internet those people have Simple Minds
they can't help but think inside of a
pub they're not Mavericks and everything
we do is a maverick moon it's what I
live by it's okay to be different in
fact I encourage you to be different you
follow the same path as everyone else
you become a drone you get sucked into
today's society I made it a point in my
life at a young age I was going to
remove myself from that and make
something of myself my parents did not
come from money no none of my relatives
came from money welcome to the of love
left home anyways it's a very expensive
house it's a very very cool house I know
right now we are going to sign the
papers so we can move in this weekend
yes move in this weekend so if you're
watching this vlog you don't know who I
am I am logo blown welcome to the
channel join the low gang subscribe hit
the button for me bye we have the
strongest family on the internet and
that is a fact and it's not because of
my Mustang believe it or not no it's cuz
we religious so yeah subscribe because
with this new house guy new stories are
gonna be told new adventures new
projects new endeavors who knows might
get a new roommate new pets new freaking
Jim [ __ ] every loking a personal private
gym inside your own house no not inside
my own house in the guest house which we
have to it's so lit I want to drive by
today to show you guys also I feel like
I should point out after the premiere
yesterday we we pardoned Jeff called me
this morning and told me this
recurrently is happening now thanks for
the heads up Jeff appreciate you
that's what you call hash tag manager
talk anyways look at me bro besides the
merch like look at my hair I'm a
freaking madman disaster like I put on
gucchi slip looking sexy I grab my dog
car and I came to sign papers as the 22
year old to buy a multi-million dollar
house I'm living a very very interesting
life I gotta say that so you guys know I
normally have Brendan with me my
videographer he went out with us last
night and he's probably still sleeping
right now so I just I'm selfie blogs
very very interesting I think I'm gonna
let Kong take over for now Kong if you
just want to yes go ahead and look at
the camera it's just crazy how his
tongue never actually makes it in his
mouth how does that happen like is it
too long or is his snout too small but
regardless y'all already know it's my
big day it's a big day yeah if you have
water
I would appreciate get a replay right
there I tried to fist bump a water
bottle how are you good bro I apparently
not you deserve a yes but on that no
Jeff if you know anyone like me who
potentially isn't good bro just send
them over to you good bro calm haven't
fill out the survey and we will know if
they are indeed good bro it's my first
home dude where do I sign here who came
in at Josh Berg Josh proof right yeah
cuz without this I'd have no idea where
to sign thank you thank you man never
owned a home before I can barely tie my
shoes this is a life moment I need call
come up you decided no I actually think
I'm gonna have Kong sign everybody grab
this [ __ ] no no Kong don't just what
what what what what you mean assistant
manager I feel like it's do like here go
pong this is a special moment buying a
house with my dog signing the papers
just bought a house Logan oh my god we
should make a song about this oh wait a
second I already did is it made me
called
I just bought me how yeah it is and
honestly one of the best songs we've
made this one's a banger this one's
gonna get a quarter million views that
so much music so much heat I'm not a
singer but I make them bang it's
official call me and you who I just
bought
okay I said I'm done being a hobo and I
took a shower feels good to be hygienic
okay we're at the buffer now y'all I'm
gonna look for the ring like I said I
think it's on the bus just going back to
the house think for a second guys cuz
like I said like it's a big day for me
hope when you watch this and when you
watch my vlogs in general you guys get
inspired and motivated and work hard so
that one day you can buy a house for
your wife your problem how do you feel
you didn't shower and you remind me of
the homeless people oh my god no I'm not
pooping outside your bus and it's a damn
good thing
hey what's up man all right it looks
that we get my favorite thing okay
Brendan the Gucci ring yeah 500 other
Gucci pinkie ring in the bus bro it's
gotta be bro it was on and then it was
off before I got off the bus bro it's
gotta be somewhere here yeah if I were a
Gucci ring where would I be not a nickel
no that's nothing to do to you know pay
for a new one though yeah if I had 20
thousand nickels uh but I don't cuz I
just spent all my money on a hot no
that's a Polaroid oh wait a second cute
see look by the way guys we're making
this cute little like photo wall I'm not
some tumblr just baby I ring okay just
how the security cameras on this episode
of how to catch a blooper is it in the
microwave it's my big day
hahaha magic of vlogging bro if there's
one thing I love about vlogging it's the
fact that I record everything so I know
like when I loose things that ie this
ring GoPro like I really like this and
lion cuz I got that light mentality time
to go to West Coast Customs here's why
we discovered a little something on the
bus not so good
if you go over like 45 50 miles an hour
the steering detaches like literally you
lose control of the bus this is bad
because of death
ha ha ha so I hit up West Coast Customs
guys can you try to fix this they're
like not try blogging and also I asked
them um if you look at the the windows
here remember they tint and unn tint huh
Thank You Brendon however they're yellow
and I wasn't sure if that's how the
windows came or if they put a yellow
tint on turns out the yellow tint was
put on which I don't love because it
makes us look yellow when we're inside
the bus I'm already a disgusting color
like pale creamy white I don't want to
be another disgusting color like a
mustard yellow oh they have some work to
do we're gonna drop the bus off there
for a few days and my man Kenny's gonna
take care of you know so here's the
thing when the bus is over like 50 miles
an hour the steering wheel like this
connects and you can't control it I mean
I hit a car but I think that's it out
from that wasn't because of the steering
no that was just I just backed right up
into that page come to West Coast
Customs the bus gets so anyways we were
about to say goodbye to the cool bus for
a couple days but yo you guys know my
brother Jake sorry yeah he was in LA
it's a hefty one bro think he said he's
gonna turn this into a merge truck which
is dope but like you know where to get
the March Logan Paul coms last shot but
I was thinking I'm like yo this is here
I'm here why don't I urinate on it Jimmy
P Brendan Brendan I do this a lot the
only reason I'm doing this is cuz I
actually don't have a reason well my
logic is this if my bus I got peed on
like why should Jake's thing not get
peed on in incidence awesome security
cameras Jake install security cameras
just like we did and you can catch up
here or just watch my vlogs just take it
caddy
[Music]
just a cake happy treat her well she
likes water in the mornings and long
walks on the beach I am leaving I feel
like I'm sending my child off to school
for the first time and it's ironic cuz
it used to be a school bus as you guys
know we have another music video coming
up on the 24th for my next song it's
called no handlebars that's all why I'm
going out with the montage and we want
to tweak the song a little bit change
some lyrics and make a true absolute
bang this music video is gonna be solely
my goal is to make it the most visually
aesthetic piece of content you've ever
seen and to help me make the Banger I
got to buzz you guys these are the
McDonagh bros AKA before you exit look
before you lo gang you know I'd love to
give you them preview you heard that
correctly I can ride your girl with no
handlebars that's what the chorus is if
you're a young person mature quickly cuz
this song is out there anyways
you boys got some wraps to spit I came
in today I texted them cuz we already we
already finished a song but you guys
know I party last night when I party my
voice was nice and deep and raspy a
rapper rap rapper Ebro I'm so white it's
disgusting well ya gonna go spit some
bars in the booth which by the way yo
it's a closet but it works bro I'm not a
singer okay I don't use booth to make
him famous let's do this
[Music]
got the tesla ass this is huge we came
to the house we are right next to my new
house which like by the way I had been
searching like I know we joked about
being homeless a lot and we were but I
found this house and I couldn't vlog
about it because ago she ations all that
stuff I'm looking around I know what the
neighbors still like already hate me
this guy with the camera in the street
yeah I want to give you guys a sneak
peek tonight we'll do a full house tour
and everything I think we're moving into
a Saturday
how did I do that I said it's my big day
with like no breath I'll okay check this
out we're by gate number one okay here's
a little teaser oh yeah that's it that's
it that's it it's very surreal like
signing the papers this McCool with Kong
sign the papers this morning Kong yeah
you signed the papers
I missed that once we actually get
inside the house and just find it like a
new creative space my brain is gonna
open up the vlogs are gonna get better I
never thought in my life that I would be
able to buy a house this nice I always
believed in myself I was not afraid to
be different be unique be a maverick I
worked really hard and I had big goals I
haven't said this often but like guys we
all have struggles right when I was 15 I
had knee surgery on both knees thought
my life was over like III played sports
and I couldn't anymore it was an 8 to 12
month recovery time I couldn't do leg
lifts with the rest of the football team
that's why I have such skinny legs I
mean they're kind of freaking dope now
but they use I've heard they used to be
skinny and I'm gonna tell the story
again but I wrote down on a piece of
paper like a hundred times I will be
more successful than anyone I know I was
15 in Ohio I didn't know what I want to
do with my life I just knew I wanted to
be quote unquote more successful than
anyone I know like but what does that
even mean was it money was it a monetary
thing was it happiness was it love who
knows but I just I wanted it and I
worked hard and I believed in myself and
I kept pushing and pushing and pushing
to make that happen and now I'm frickin
ah living a different day living a life
of my dreams no gag so the point is I
don't often do these inspirational
speeches but if you believe in yourself
if you can expand your brain and think
outside of the box and get out of the
whatever bubble it is that you live
assuming you live in a bubble like I did
you
do whatever yo you want bro be a
maverick baby lo game for life cop your
maverick or low gang merchant Logan Paul
calm slash I'm out of softest merch in
the game and if you're not a part of the
low game what are you doing both
subscribe low gang I love you
[Music]
barring them down to start
West Coast Customs is everything dude