i paint you nude um
how was the date up until right now
you're never getting any [ __ ] privacy
babe my best friend baby wants to hide
under the car grab my girlfriend's torso
you can do that you guys have no idea
what i went through to make that happen
okay mike and amara have been fighting
all week he took her on a nice cute date
they're paddling a swan around the lake
except
unfortunately i'm kind of bored so i'm
gonna [ __ ] it up that's right i'm
a grown ass man climbing into a trash
can
i'm [ __ ] fit dave all right all right
we need to rethink this how clearly can
you see me dave how clearly can you see
me
we need to rethink this i don't think
it's going to work
oh i can't get out i swear to god i'm
stuck
oh [ __ ] this is the worst prank ever i
have no idea what i went through to get
him to take me on a date
sorry you are here the homeless problem
in la is pretty bad i drive by the
highway every day there's always someone
standing underneath and today we saw a
nice young lady so we're going to see if
we can help her out a little bit hi how
are you
doing i love your smile thank you would
you mind holding this for me why
it has a lot of rust on it i don't know
i'm kind of allergic to rice i'll give
you this side would you mind breaking
this open for me yeah with one hand
i want to set it on the ground
oh my god is that mine yeah yeah there
you go
okay the world's going to [ __ ] but not
everyone's just
hit thank you
i'm not gonna get like mad at you but
how many times have you seen my
girlfriend's nipples
what the [ __ ]
i'm pretty sure i've seen your
girlfriend's poops more than you ever
for sure yeah cause like i replayed them
constantly oh i should not have told you
that no do you think it's weird how her
nipples are like cross-eyed but it'd
make me go cross-eyed it really
starts to hurt my eyes hi
i think the more genuine concerning
thing is the amount of people who've
sent me on dms on instagram begging for
these boots they are good boobs i must
admit
i can't vouch for that all right i'm so
uncomfortable
you hear the rumor about butter no
what's the rumor well
i'm not gonna spread it last night i
watched a documentary
oh about beavers what happened to the it
beavers the best damn
show i ever seen hey come here
what do you call somebody with no body
and no nose nobody knows
hey can i paint you like one of my
french girls okay
can i paint you nude um
ready baby the question is are you ready
baby
oh my god damn shawty oh my god
can we [ __ ] real quick
[Music]
ready what's on my butt
your little butt hairs are you serious
what do you mean you don't like it
what the [ __ ] i spent three hours on
this it's really nice
what's that on her butt eyes are [ __ ]
hair the butt hair's a little weird
honestly it's not that bad her feet are
definitely backwards crooked
it's great dude like i would buy it for
how much i'd probably give you a couple
bucks for it i would never buy that
painting
nothing
[Music]
i was watching a beaver documentary last
night it was the best damn show i ever
saw
beavers make dance it was a damn
good show get in the car for going home