me my new mom hey yes I placed me I like
it yes Jack okay yo I don't know but it
wasn't a oh good morning low game was
poppin when you guys leave Thursday okay
that means we have two days to get it
right you guys noticed this isn't my
house check this out I'm actually at the
team ten receptacle because it's a real
life trashcan I had to come here because
my parents betrayed me they told me they
were here in the morning I have to come
out to hunt you down and find you good
thing I got little never merch even
though I'm at Jake's house know that I
know dad's empty universe Greg I think
you have dental records
why don't I go this way I'm perfect is
I'm a member okay there we go now you
guys look good at mom that's 95 bread
eat it don't you get a small what
happened there let me learn okay this is
something like okay you're all ready
Jake we dinner get over home our camera
we blog with you what do you know about
Plaza you wouldn't know this blog so
fricking warzone in here bro I'm
surprised no one's died all right guys
I'm leaving
what Jacob and my mom back it's my mom
okay
come on mom fight to the savages geez a
mother is a mother ah funny mom there we
go okay I think was kind of Rudy look
what what stealing me how did you I know
I do not steal you mine right I am makes
I'm borrowing you it's a war zone
dude YouTube's crits like it's literally
war people are dying wow I was having
fun
what did you just say what did you say I
was having fun yeah Lydia can you go
around the block okay that's our cue you
can go have fun with Jay God why would
Jake yo this is a little messed up
what does Jake have that I don't a wife
what a wife yeah I know
bro I need a wife I don't know Greg but
literally I talked to a parent cuz they
don't have female companion show just
like every relationship just scare them
away
yes josh is just not right man cause
don't touch that plate cause don't touch
that plate just stop come stop
call them move don't touch that plate
good dog now just kiss okay here we go
he's got a wife right yeah don't rub it
in my face never and now we've got a mom
and a dad but we just got to replace
them put your mom yeah Lou George has a
mama I know for a fact he does dude
let's just go get George's moment I know
if you're missing bro I still miss you
we will find him I'll never let go Jack
but yo Lydia
I need you to give me a blonde wig
because I'm getting a new mom today it's
my big date because apparently I'm not
my mom's favorite son are you good drop
how did you even get in here come here
oh we got call hi yeah look uh this was
down go keep going down bro it's going
down what we got it's immaculate surgery
it's a fighter you afraid of a little
birdie - maverick that's not you're
feeling a little ball Go Go honey watch
Lydia blonde wig blonde wig one okay
text me when you have it I'll be over
here what what what
we're the same size before there for a
second it's funny it's called walking
Lydia or as Lydia walking Kong anyways
I'm excited right now headed to George's
place to get a new mom it's a good day
for me hey George hey where's your mom
I'm up yeah she's all there can he go hi
this is my vlog plugin pause blocks
hanging so Logan Tom looks blog you got
a son do I have a happier yeah why
what's wrong
you can want another okay oh why are you
looking for mommy
yeah come on can you remember you have
to carry me but I'll do it
[Music]
how do you mommy daddy have to be wrong
cause I love you think they all want to
come to me I must take things out a
console yacht they're like 600 thank God
but I would love to give you my mouth
but here's the thing
so you guys don't look alike at all ah I
actually have that under control
ha ha ha my lord mom is that you Oh like
she's an old surfer me to give you
advice about life so she's wise man goes
the wave so with my real mom we talked
about like relationship advice and like
relationships are having girls tell you
I happy when I die for me no I don't
need advice what are we here for a smash
last night too much information is that
why you stopped talking to you real mom
yes I could see why now I think I'm
sorry I'm super open with my parents in
real life like my mom and my dad but I'm
just there that's why is it so crazy I
think that's why I'm so crazy I think I
didn't know I was gonna do that
you're a good mom this is like okay okay
enough bro this is but mom okay is it
blog or brunette blonde or brunette yeah
who do you want to be yeah maybe
fish every day bro with that Disney
Channel flow if I feel on YouTube in six
months everybody
he's a cooler for older members thank
you this new family is really treating
me well that looks dumb dude my hair
your hair what little brother jay-z try
to roast me what little brother I'm a
dog you're a puppy call you car let's
talk about your garb and you go looking
for I can finally do it what if you
finally can do it alright allocate space
for everything I'll see you guys later
dude easy shirt kitchen logs not over
that we all right it's a good time we're
in a quick sidebar you're taking this
like a look to for a little to folder I
think they actually think to burn the
ball family I know they're not brown
they're Syrians I don't think it gets
like whiter than us watch me whip though
yeah it looks pretty white that's really
why hi guys um this is this has been fun
I like this life yeah yeah cool I'm
gonna go go back to living mine yeah
we'll come with you no I'll go by myself
I'll see you guys later yeah man
Georgie's mom just don't fulfill me like
my family does those are real sneezes by
the way I don't know they're like mad
waiting bro hey bro all you want
you need a sister right doc no no if you
got Jake ball and you got what you got
no JLo ball Lydia could you get a girl
that can be like my sister for the day
let me know what she's here I'll be
right here what you got there
the vegan yeah I made it I'm going to be
honest with you Orla I need a sister
assistant a sister why do you rescue a
sister
Brendan am i speaking Spanish like a
foreign language or something no they
give you a speaking Spanish you would
understand you girl oh yeah
I need an s Lamanna M I need a diaper I
needed condoms
I need a pickle I need an air tamanho
commit oiler seriously can you be my
sister like actually I need it fixed up
come on put it on so you can be my JLo
pickles oh my god touch me Nikolas I
think you look like you look like the
girl version of Jpop my opinion no but I
noticed one thing when you walked in you
said you had a vegan shake you good bro
you can shake if you want to be like a
true ball brother you can't be vegan
like I want to tell you I want to make
it eat a steak no I had Lydia pick up a
fresh take oh you have to know if you
want to be a Paul family ever you got to
do it and I took the liberty of giving
your smoothie
Oh what does it drink that you got to
eat me if you want to be a nepal family
these vegans go hard rock crazy oh
you're my hermano that's what we do you
love each other but we fight sometimes
just like I do with Jake I got the steak
if you want to know that me away from me
now no you want to be grateful galo be
great yeah why ha I don't know what her
deal
oh very quick sidebar Tillman oh I
didn't tell you I was going to do it
like she she's kind of in real life
she's been I doing JLo looking just like
a family member died are you good
drought I'm not scared of a service
let's fill it up just I'll be over here
so let me know what it's done all right
well we got you are stupid Q damn
oh come on out you know what I actually
think someone's at the door I want you
to be hello look that no one in the body
you're fine no no look this yes yes yeah
this is JLo JEP like Jackie loggin but
female yeah Jo to my daughter
yep this is definitely working to meet
you finally yeah I'm sort of weird
what's uh yeah so this most awkward I've
ever seen in my life
shut up
just to me a chance if you want to know
if I had some ever can I made a mistake
I jumped again means I did you know my
dad funny guy our dad our dad the funny
guy look it
she really is my daughter ah no I mean
yeah we will dad
this is getting weird tell me there's
not a resemblance you looking yeah yeah
we good we look together honey no no
so as my big sister like is there any
sort of advice you can offer me on life
or anything call me Michael yeah
what go manage the duck what staying eat
vegetables really vegetables yeah minute
this is our dynamic we got picked on
each other here punch me in the face
harder all right there we go Zoila I
mean JLo if you have someone I want you
to meet you haven't met her yet it's
actually our mother yeah yeah she cooks
good late
so let's not yeah let's go do that now
go gang I think it's time I'm excited I
know my big sister is excited I know
Cong is excited so I am that's your cue
ma oh well look who it a my my
Marguerite your new daughter her name's
joy hello joy
J laughs yeah yeah yeah she's she comes
from fresh fresh off the boat fresh
shuttle screen say something in Spanish
to prison oh yeah yeah yeah no I'm sure
it's all far right it's all fun until
you find out it's gonna replace you
because it was more fun no so was her
place you was a better on a more a
Syrian mom ha ha ha you're a sidekick
yeah brought you to LA
if there's one thing you should know
okay my new mom hey
yes I placed me I like it yes Romina
Drago pulp mean listen I have to split
time between you Jacob
oh my god all I hear is blah blah blah
I'm a date part yeah this is Janko pol
is nice to me and she wanted to spend
time with me and she loves me and my
sister oh yeah and your son up big balls
yeah replace him to Potter bring water
boom
it is Jeff rose with a GC channel slope
Bosnian are you too busy bus never W
bow-wow would be slighted yet yeah
that's my fam that those these are my
family members and we love each other so
cute really and you jealous you jealous
bro you want to go back to Jacob are you
having more fun there no you stick out
like a sore thumb
hmm women they're not really your family
you're just trying to irritate me
what's wrong with us lady what are you
doing mom you made me cry you talked it
in I'm gonna accept you back coming
offing your God out of your life oh
whatever
hi mom I'm glad we're even hated son I'm
sorry my guts got a little jealous
and why I have more subscribers anyway I
love you so much
it's okay okay
uh yeah that's a block okay if you're
not a part of the local gang make sure
to subscribe hit your maverick and lo
gamers oh go out be different be
passionate be you me don't live in a
bubble man think outside the box see
life through the lens of possibility
that's the slogan we're maverick that's
what we do Logan pause icon slash shop
or link in description
[Music]
yo we just recorded a whole thing we
broke two plates on George's vlog and
his audio was off
welcome to the fly