oh my god i can't believe
that just happened and we caught it on
film hey yo good morning okay what pop
what the [ __ ] yo this is what a good way
to open a vlog after being gone bro
literally precision just wedge this in
between the two clamps
bro i am an animal yeah that is quite a
feat so guys okay we got a couple things
to address one oh
i know i haven't been vlogging for uh
two days now in a row no vlogs guys i've
been doing a lot of things so i train
boxing in the morning right get a little
swell
i come home i have business meetings
look the maverick enterprise is not
gonna grow itself right and then i come
home and i've been streaming on twitch
doing fortnite every day at six pm you
all seen it and that actually explains
this
when i lose a game i break a play that's
just kind of my thing
sasha's been crazy busy guys i'm so
sorry logan you guys know i love you i
say it it's good to be back to the vlog
i've been trying the gaming thing right
we got the little cockpit here we got
the game center
that vlog life is my bread and butter so
guys if you're not a part of the logan
make sure to subscribe smash the button
kiss it on the mouth and then punch it
in the door what
what i don't know how to say can we say
we could say
why can't we say hey mike what's up it's
a fast-moving land animal dude i have no
issue with it whatsoever
you guys have seen it before on on
discovery channel where it chases the
elk in the desert look at the fast
moving you've seen it bro you're
thinking you have a cougar not a
it's not the same thing also cougars
aren't spotted here's a picture of one
basic science
vagina so i don't know
look the point is subscribe join the
channel guys today's vlog is gonna be
crazy
so my brother you guys may have seen he
just got his merch truck built it's a
giant red truck that he sells jake paul
merchant
looks good but i yo i can't help but
think how did he get the idea to
customize
a giant vehicle i have the cool bus
right one day
oh god we gotta like race them or just
like head-to-head battle but that day is
not today the point is we both have
these giant vehicles
i will say something inside me when i
saw him get the merch truck i wanted to
steal it i want it i want
that here and i prefer right that we put
maverick merch inside the hottest
softest merch in the game dare to fly
shirts dropping today
literally go to jake's house steal the
truck come back here fill it with maver
merch including the new drops we also
dropped the hockey shirt guys logan paul
dot com slash chop that [ __ ] and sell
some freaking merch
we have anybody on the like on the
inside that can help us yeah we do
i'm not coming in unprepared i'm really
not also you guys may have noticed still
haven't unpacked from the yosemite trip
that was fun
that's a kayak flash back to when i
almost drowned
should we do a smell check on the food
to make sure it's okay to eat
i can guarantee it's not but i'm down
some bagels i'm sure those are still
pretty good it was probably fine i'm a
little worried about the cooler
oh sh oh my god it smells horrible
quick it's mad it's just remember i
gotta show you something not going
anywhere come on bro i'm not going
anywhere
we took an uber because we're driving a
military truck back right but i forgot
to order uber suv i got uberx a little
tight a little tight i feel like a
piece of string cheese in the back seat
i feel pretty comfortable
up here why are you in the front seat
she's a girl bro no she's not
dude you got to respect what she wants
zero negative i'm six foot eight i'm in
the back seat my head is
can we just go around the speed bumps
from now on please make sure when you
hit the speed bumps you're going 90
miles an hour
oh god all right so here's the plan
we're gonna go to jake's house right
we're gonna get the keys to the merch
truck his giant
20-foot tall military vehicle drive it
off his property without him noticing
first off oh
okay we get the keys let's bribe erica
with coachella tickets
erica i like erica her basic level's a
little high
bribery tickets they'll do anything
are you gonna wear that to chella we're
being a little hypocritical because
we're going we're going to sell off
but other than that i think this plan is
pretty buttoned up
bye uber thanks man all right the
mission begins good thing i know the
gate code
all right step one we need to find an
internal resource
to get us the keys to that goddang truck
we're going we're gonna go for erica
and also we gotta find the truck but i
feel like that's not gonna be hard
that's gotta be it right that's
definitely
we are not gonna be able to hide i think
we just go in and be like yo what's good
and then take erica aside and then just
play it cool
erica what's up so crazy you're here
yeah it's weird
whoa why are you here i didn't know it
was uh
you're being so sketchy right now is
jacob i think he's in the girl oh
perfect here can you go over here
yeah fancy seeing you guys crazy so
weird
nuts wow look at do plans this weekend
yeah yeah
coachella do you want to go to coachella
twice twice in one weekend
wait wait are you good bro she's already
let's just ask her no no listen keys for
the merch
truck it doesn't have keys i mean did
you press some buttons
hey good good to see you guys we'll see
you at chella catch me at chella we'll
get you real trouble shout out
let's get out of here this thing's loud
since we started we're not gonna have
[Music]
time
oh this thing is loud bro i gotta go all
right back it up back it up like maybe
you should be a little more quiet
try to whisper back it up back it up
oh [ __ ] oh wow this thing is a big
mike
looks like he's in a pretty good
position right now so we could probably
just get it yeah i think we should
probably get over here
whoa dude
yeah got him whoa
oh no
oh
oh my gosh yo this is crazy wow that was
flawless
all right all right we're stopping here
let's rearrange i was not as
covert as i would have liked but we got
the job done no he had me by the leg
like
i was that close do you even know what
you're doing dude i know i have no
besides
pushing down on the accelerator i have
no idea what i'm doing breaks are the
important part we're working on it
this looks so stupid the position of it
is oh my gosh
yo this is hilarious these shorts hold
up to just about anything
maverick performance show it's available
not only on loganfall.com
i don't know how much time we have i
feel like jake is on his way over here
now
he has much faster vehicles than this i
gotta make this thing in the maverick
merch truck real quick and get ready to
sell some merch
oh damn so many things that are so
fire we got the dare to fly shirts that
we just dropped today by the way oh i
look
up there and just kind of like grab
things and just go hey i got these
performance shorts
i got all these girls sweats and
leggings you know good old hoodies here
oh look who's wearing that the worldwide
hoodies good choice we're trying yeah
all right all right guys
i'll grab some i'll grab some too i
don't know
this is why we got the step ladder oh
yeah hand me things
pink boyfriends blue leggings foremost
shorts that new new
meat level bam kind of crowded in here
so i'm just going to start hanging these
up oh dude it's cool in here man
see this is nice because finally jake
and i can like collab on our merch right
like he sells jake palmer but also while
he's on tour he also sells
my my merch you know so thoughtful of
him to do to do that voluntarily yeah
but just
you know just probably for for now for
now he does
his needs is here right yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
that's the sticker bro
yeah it comes off real clean there we go
this is it's flawless for sure it
doesn't stick either
no come on it's got it's careful careful
ah
god almighty this material is sticker
resistant
we know we're coming i don't understand
what about our operation gave us away
oh oh it's so bad no stop stay positive
man
yeah there's bare oh hey there's barely
any wrinkles in it
that's good i think we have smaller
stickers yes
here we go that should do it
all right guys i give you the brand new
maverick definitely not jake paul
merch truck
what about that right there what about
that part what do you mean mike do you
mean the
the black bar that says loganpaul.com
because that's what i see
anyways this is so crazy how we were
able to turn jake's merch truck into a
maverick merch truck
that's what it's all about bro we do it
a little different around here right
it's the maverick movement when they go
right we digitally transform them or
instruction to hours all right guys it's
only a matter of time before jake gets
here
i think we just sit back and wait for
the axe
open the gate open the gate okay
what are we paying
look at the maverick logo right on the
side
no it's the mavic truck now he'll never
take my merch
he already did it and when you're on
tour tell your friends they can go to
loganpaul.com and cop the hottest merch
in the game hey what's on that tree
not even my tree it's the neighbors
at this point i feel like we could have
easily just walked around yeah
hey man good good good stuff man yeah
good
good pranking hey good stuff cool good
thanks for being
my friend yeah bro i'll see you later
all right man we'll see you around take
it easy jake
send her off take her to space goodbye
maverick merch you're going to go change
the world
and okay logang that is the vlog it
feels good to be back in the game oh man
if you're not a part of the logan make
sure to subscribe smash the button and
then hit the bell next to it so you get
notified when i post and also i've been
saying it the whole vlog cop yourself
the hottest softest merch in the game
logan paul.com it's that maverick
movement baby the dare to fly shirts did
just drop today because that's what we
do we dare to fly we take the risk and
we work our asses off to make our dreams
come true
that's a factual guys if you're not
watching me stream on twitch at night
which i do by the way add me uh the
username was logan paul was taken
because logan paul was taken usually 6pm
psti i'm talking a lot okay i love you
and i will see you tomorrow
i ain't trying to break you down but for
real you might as well give up now think
you got
a chance but i don't see how got a real
tight grip when i hold that crown my
life been good and bad and all around
the more things i lost the more i found
one thing
i taught myself to do no matter the
problem refuse to
you can lose if you can't take the heat
don't light the fuse see i walk in slow
and ignite the room
like fire everything i touch i consume
i'm getting up while y'all just snooze
while you make breakfast man i'm on the
move
i got i hit myself you okay yeah all
right