yo guys we just got done a 14-day bender
we were in New York courtside tickets
seats at the Knicks game also a lot of
partying and then I went to Ohio party
some more got influenza feel like I'm
gonna die you can probably still hear it
went from social-media influencer to
social media influenza nice nice joke
and then we traveled to Lake Tahoe where
we snowboarded with your music festival
and yes partied some more I'm not gonna
lie we've been drinking a lot of alcohol
but that's because 2020 is gonna be
sober 2020 is a big year for us me and
Mike are doing it sober
we just get the most done and we think
it's smart if you want to do it with us
that's dope if not no problem live your
life we figured the best way to get 2020
started was to come here Washington DC
for combat tactical intervention
training for a three-day grueling
training course to prepare for combat
anytime anywhere it's reserved for SWAT
and military which we are neither of
those we had to be honest guys we've
been training a lot at home because it
is dangerous we are gonna be running out
around with loaded firearms and I do not
want to end up shooting Mike or him
shooting me in the face U+ live weapons
just scared hit that subscribe button
and let's do it combat tax will
intervention training here we go
Oh wake up bro or on drinking coffee
like a normal human you sound like a
dying whale it's day one to be honest I
have no idea what to expect
I do [ __ ] murder we're gonna get
bullied to be honest I feel like they're
gonna take advantage of the YouTube kids
except little do they know I'm a
professional boxer a professional boxer
professional loser
[Applause]
[Music]
welcome to combat exceed man shaking my
hand goes by the name of Tim Clemente
he's an American counterterrorism expert
who's protected the u.s. from rogue
nuclear weapon attacks and taken down
members of the Cali cartel among decades
of high profile FBI military work
Wikipedia describes him as an excellent
terrorist hunter unfortunately for me
and my body he's also the guy in charge
this weekend release and waiver of
liability
I'm literally signing my life away it's
the same contract I said remember hey
you guys got any hot chocolate this
course has literally been designed to
take what is an intact human being break
them into pieces and reassemble them to
somebody who is combat ready I think
Logan Paul is physically in good shape
he has the potential to make it through
this course and do great I don't think
he's going to its physical challenge
it's mental challenges it's can you
endure beyond the point of your
endurance and I'm gonna ask you now can
you I don't know what this influenza hey
come on it's a joke for comedy yeah so
that's what you think now let's see what
you think later
it doesn't matter how great a shape
you're in we want to push you beyond
that capability that you have or that
you think you have because in the end
your physical capabilities your skills
your endurance everything can be
challenged in the real world run at the
obstacle course no problem I've never
done it before but this is sending me
through it no problem
you ready am i following you you're
you're going I'm leaning don't your
figure in the course you're not even
doing with your own good I've never done
it
wait I have you know they're just
sending me through this is bullying
up up up vertically
I think get a warm-up oh you tired
I got influence this is tired come on
okay gotta get on top of that road you
have to get on top Wow one leg down one
foot on the road one leg down Logan come
on Logan let's go now you got to get
over that long there's so far
ah it's gonna research I knew I
shouldn't wonder
[Music]
come on Logan come on
proper procedure heel-toe heel-toe climb
with your legs stabilized with your own
[Music]
stand up stand up hands off your knees
don't make it a habit of putting any
hands on your knees you're not defeated
you're not done yet
hey how does it feel to have a new
record all you had to set the record for
yeah he does have the record this is the
first time we had to go past a 24-hour
period for somebody completing the
course he told me he was gonna beat the
course record
he winded it was tough right he was
tough it was a challenge is it more of a
challenge than you expected okay well
now you're in the right mindset to begin
getting ready for this okay
[Music]
here's the barbecue flavor pork patty
rib shaped what is this so is there like
a phone number on it and that's how you
call uber eats like I understand how is
it like a post mate's thing where you
see the order like dominos or something
not gonna happen
Logan gave up lost the fight
this sure is good let's talk about
expectations versus reality we came here
with expectations we started the day
with the expectations you did your first
run with certain expectations and your
first run was horrible
nothing short of horrible it was
horrible against what logan paul was
capable of what if you just got better
at maneuvering the obstacles no i'm not
saying he did Tim I want to juggle so
shut your mouth Mike I'm not talking to
you we didn't break you yet you're not
broken but you were beat the next run
when we start mixing a gun into it it's
gonna really challenge you because I
don't want you throwing my gun around in
the mud I don't want you pointing in a
direction it shouldn't be pointed I
don't want you shooting in a direction
you shouldn't be shooting
I don't want your finger on a trigger
when it shouldn't be on the trigger just
warm you what does he even look like to
you Logan
you got a kit you got to pull in deep
down from out of you get your ass goober
eat right now give me some so that's
dirty Dom the ex-navy seal he's about to
run the course this is what it should
look like
[Music]
the man don't miss oh I see what he did
holy Sh I do look like Ed Sheeran he
just slayed that rubber man
all right way to go Doug da see what
we're talking about you guys getting
this yeah that you you can't quit I know
you're tired and you know how you were
sucking wind he's sucking wind same way
you were down on your knees and he kept
saying don't go down on your knees why
is he saying don't go down on your knees
I can't be in the fight if this is what
you're doing he was in the fight
he was as tired as you are that is as
you'll see the will to fight
what the [ __ ] is a five guys cave Tim's
gonna kill us
okay what did you do come on let's go
always say we're just wasting time let's
go he's got for you forget the beaches
right got me - yeah B - guess what we
have to do
we brought the beach here who are you
yeah we got the sand and we got the
water oh because you just took a bite of
that burger well not no way we're
supposed to have a nice David David
bendeth our respective sand water and
you're gonna do two laps Logan Paul when
he came here this morning was concerned
about Logan Paul was concerned about
himself he was talking about how he had
the flu and that's what was defeating
him on the first run it was physically
challenging but that's not what did it
do him it was all mental but when you've
been through difficult things physically
it alters what you think you're capable
of you know everything so our strategy
going forward based on what we saw in
that last run of Logan we're gonna take
it up another notch there are more
things yet that he hasn't done that will
be incorporated into what he's just done
how's it possible that I miss ya it must
be different for you nice toss top bro
ready for it yep it was tough at the
beginning for Logan it got easier
towards the middle now comes to the end
and the end there's gonna be way harder
what do you got what do you got in that
window
the Gnostic we're putting all our skills
together right we learn how to shoot we
learn how to do the obstacle course
hopefully it goes well
something tells me it's not though this
vest is like at least probably a hundred
pounds this gun is probably 300 pounds
just a lot of extra added weight to my
body that is gonna make this extremely
extremely difficult there's nothing I
don't know how to do at this point
bad they couldn't train you how to win
up boxing match should we leave those
jobs in 2019 it's 20 towards a new year
I don't know Mike do you like hurting
your friend's feelings because if so
keep going bro yeah this is the full
gambit here yeah I know right gonna
double-check your gear okay this is
bringing everything together like this
is no bull not everybody gets to go
through this I'm gonna do this this way
so I want you to question you have the
ability to do it I know you do
[Music]
all right sure - ready sir be aware
threat
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
let's see what you got you see your
target up there
Hey Hey see the difference could you do
it could you have done more after the 11
minutes yesterday oh hell yeah
did you know because you were
psychologically out of the fight today
you're in it thank you I'll go get that
tougher puppet
[Music]
so we don't want you walking around
shirtless here Logan so
[Music]
welcome to the combat experiment program
alumni yes thank you
notice the only other people wearing
these were instructors
[Music]
shirt everybody gonna do this do now
have the training the knowledge the
skills and the mindset to save lives in
any way sort of Samaritan does
[Music]