warning the following vlog features
stunts performed by experienced
professionals do not attempt to recreate
or reenact any stunt or activity
performed on this show
hahaha okay we're losing the cool bus
she's hurt and she needs to be fixed
[Music]
hey oh good morning low gang what's
poppin kind of sad man you guys know I
love the cool bus and you guys know I've
been getting into twitch and playing
games for tonight specifically and one
of the things it's called the battle bus
in for tonight here's a picture of it
right the battle bus looks exactly like
cool buzz think I'm actually gonna do
something with the cool bus about the
battle bus for my first live stream
gonna be live I got some ideas trust me
you do not want to miss it guys my
twitch handle is at Logan Paul was taken
where why is it that cuz Logan Paul was
taking so make sure to add me on there I
hope you always smiling I hope you're
having a good day if you're not hey
that's what I'm here for
and if you're not a part of the low gang
make sure to subscribe and if for
whatever reason you're looking down at
the subscribe button and it says
subscribe and not subscribed it with the
D real quick go ahead and hit that for
me and the logo the strong family of
Mavericks the family of people I think
plug commercials give me a second family
of Mavericks the family people who do
with different people who embrace their
differences right guys that's the
movement that's what it's about and
y'all know where to get the merch it's
the hottest softest merch in the game
Logan Paul calm /op now I'm looking at
this space here and it's empty it's kind
of making me depressed
he's just ago I got thanks for
populating that space for me low-key
though we probably should fill that hole
so he doesn't fall in damn cuz you guys
know how the earth is flat and for every
do you think the earth is flat skew
seriously yo why'd you go say that to me
do you think there is flat yo let me
give you a little science lesson Spencer
alright the earth is round that's all my
science that Spencer doesn't think the
earth is flat I think you're joking
right yeah totally joking what's he
doing Kong's playing with leaves it's
cute
get a calendar photo you guys need to
get in there bro September calendars
literally only the month of September on
Logan Paul that okay we're getting
sucked into the Kong trap literally I
could film his dog for hours stop stop
he's amped up you know he's crazy bro
it's so easy to film and be funny no get
away from me okay wait alright this we
gotta focus we gotta focus
I'm populating a space I'm so not used
to this a miniature crossbow I'm not
feeling it what about uh yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
you're cool and like I think you're not
this is wrong thing that you don't you
think you'd be the bigger you know
what's funny meeting you a michigan
state the exact same time and then you
know who the logan fema see me not you
you know what the cheese wheel over here
in the cross row what do you think about
him row sends bro off of your balcony i
love you whoa
I feel like a just a a Oh watch out Evan
man yeah you might be right about that
one he might provide more cushioning for
the same
[Applause]
[Music]
some sort of elevation system oh thank
god
I know these really well yeah yeah yeah
yeah gonna do with that
well at first we're gonna bounce in it
now we're gonna bounce on it from above
it on top of it yeah look at there's my
dog barking at the rain no contracts
dorks great not a good picture gotta go
inside
yes I'm looking at this from this angle
looks pretty good from down here I'm
looking up from this angle it looks
pretty good too
the difference is it's my house right I
signed the waiver bro he did sign the
waiver I saw it I don't even know how I
have insurance in the first place bro
I'm back back all jokes aside
technically I am a professional so I
have to say don't try this at home cuz
yeah I know how to do this
you're pro Hawker I've been Hawking bro
yeah yeah good stuff hockey for sure but
that's cool it's high but like that's
I know you're about to say some
important so let me get the butter zoom
okay roof it's wet it's been raining you
don't it'll rain you know yeah
professional yeah no you are perfectly
laid out I saw them teacher check Logan
Paul versus Cirque I swear that was
exactly they tell you look I just know
how to fall alright so that was cool but
what if we went high not really anything
really higher but I have an idea what
you just jump from so it's like going
backwards
don't worry Jeff I'm not jumping
oh my god okay I got the reflexes a cat
you see that case I I'm coming in guys
before I sign this vlog off and I know
it's a short one as much as I joke I
have been training and it's kind of hard
to train and then vlog and then do
business and email so I'm gonna go ice
my body and play some for tonight no
forget to follow me on Twitch at Logan
ball was taken but this box this box has
been sitting here all day we're gonna
open it up this is actually from my
uncle in Ohio if you can see the
Maverick is right there I don't know
Jeff Dean I see all these little tiny
things around oxygen ding okay oh she
did everywhere champion Mars
I love game that is whoa Jesus that is
the floor again you know the drill hit
that subscribe button for me your mom
and your yeah that's more the Maverick
movement get your merch do it different
like my shirt says right there I've had
use myself as an example in high school
I was a kid too made videos ever thought
I was weird blah blah blah that's not a
career you can't make money off of that
well for the most part that's true guys
if you genuinely believe in your dream
I'd you have just a burning desire to
accomplish them trust me you can do it
example I am now I guess a youtubing ex
vining instagramming facebooking acting
producing directing writing musician
boxer gamer they don't tell you that at
career day kids wow you're gonna be like
the coolest dad be a dad so yeah hello
gang I love you guys and you know I will
see you tomorrow
[Music]
what do you mean you might be a dad
Spring Break 2013 Panama