the tornado not again sorry guys just a
little nervous today Brendan and I hi
hello guys are going to burning man's
maniac hole mean manacle maniacal
maniacal its maniacal yeah yeah wildly
disordered well that's what Burning Man
is we're just gonna go we get concept of
people being maniac it is all how you
view life no here's why Burning Man is
cool for me but where everyone is
finally like on my level of weirdness
I'm always already all the time myself
but feel like not everyone else is and
here it's just it's so beautiful
everyone is just weird and being
themselves and I should have got merged
Brendan I just hand it out to everyone
at Burning Man bro - after Burning Man
they can just go to Logan Paul calm
slash job or click the link in
description
[Applause]
oh no we officially left the main road
by late oh my god oh my god crazy cuz
guys I don't think there's service out
here I'm gonna be shutting my phone off
literally my only source of
communication is gonna be these vlogs
and it's not even a conference is
there's no communication it's just me
posting vlogs like no one's gonna be
able to reach me running bro what's up
this is convened rocks this could mean
drugs I'm gonna be saying that's so
often because everything here could mean
drugs
the best here is like dangerously crazy
the problem is it gets literally
everywhere like it's probably gonna seep
into this camera yeah no unfortunately
your camera we take all the crevices
show like the lens the audio jack the
LCD screen on the back basically we're
professionals last year we had a little
issue with recording the entrance to
have to scout your car to see if you're
smuggling anyone in the only weapons I
got of these guns haha the only animal I
got is these guns check in the back
right now
I really hope we don't have any weapons
or anything literally like what like so
security here at Burning Man is
obviously like a little subpar we easily
could have snuck Evan here but I think
it's just cuz everyone's here to have
fun like we just chilling rock bottom
and it's a Burning Man oh this place is
crazy it takes like forever to get in
here you have to find our friends my
boyfriend you guys no friend also I
gotta pee super bad so let's go fight
100 percent this is now your RV / camp /
friend because this RV / can't slash
friends are not little [ __ ] if you're
looking for the [ __ ] camp it's not it's
not even at Burning Man it's at 1600
vines tree in Hollywood that's where the
[ __ ] first off Frank can't say that
word of my vlogs but I'm at Burning Man
so bucket Frank that's right mom why why
I'm tired I'm tired of jacking for your
Steve why are you acting no I'm being me
this is real me this is real me I don't
want to do this anymore
let's try stop a lot guys low gang
that's that's it for the book
good to see you
I've had some pretty like show peas in
my life this one this one's awesome bro
Burning Man is off to a really great
start I'd like to point out that this is
not the first time of recording you
paying you recorded me peeing often huh
mm times I like it what's your question
question are you tweaking about yeah my
phone is what I don't even have a phone
bro oh I don't have a phone no hey Alex
bro Alec Alec oh sorry bro
ah ah it's getting very real guys worst
case me I'm just gonna go in there and
like you know tweet some stuff but this
is it lo que this is it the vlogs bro
like in subscribe hahaha can feel the
adventure beginning l we brought the hot
pocket well I got the text are you
staying 24 240 bro there's eight of us
you've forgotten zero bro right and
forget a zero can I check it on my phone
no yes lo gang it is mean you can tell
because of three thing one because of
the maverick fanny pack it's not
available yet I don't know why I have
who the blue bandanna 3 the voice is
more than 3 4 the Maverick had 5 I'm a
shock but I think the burn is about to
get started here's why this whole thing
is good for me I'm not good at not
having stuff to do here like I don't
have anything to do like we're litters
gonna ride bikes and see if we find
something fun to go check it out this is
like a good little like mental reset for
me I wouldn't call it a vacation but
like it's good it's it is good for that
soul with that several let's get this
burn start can I just say last year this
was the trio we got Eugene we got Frank
we got the Maverick you make like a
bicycle and shut them up
listen make any concern god ballgame for
mocking me Frank before you shut your
mouth when you talk make like a bottle
of water and shut up Frank your
analogies don't make sense weak Japanese
like I do told you guys the rules about
Burning Man
what happens at Burning Man stays at
Burning Man and also on my youtube
channel for almost 11 million people to
see that doesn't make any sense
Brendan
you know that's bad well it's only
getting worse man oh my god bro what
have you learned from trying to be
beautiful Beauty pays no no no Beauty is
within a tall wedding dress it what show
your nipple go get me to say to me you
keep on my merchant hope all that cop /
let's go we haven't made any progress
wait what about your merch no no no no
no no no oh no no no no I'll get my
necklace I'm free fine your marriage is
falling apart already man guys this is
why like I feel like these vlogs I can
give you a little taste of what it's
like outside like whatever bubble you
live in like there's just desert desert
I'm Brendan I was gonna say Brendan and
I kind of taking it easy today following
days we're gonna get like the drone shot
we're gonna get the GoPro footage from
like dope angles like time-lapses sunset
sunrise today's the first day we thought
we ease you into it I don't want to just
give everything at once bro like play
the hand yeah you might be a god bro
I'm just looking at Frank I'm like that
meant that man could be a god I'm not
sure and the way his wedding dress has
devolved to just like a crop top like a
black tee that's some monumental wedding
dress merchandise now available in the
shop $99 per wedding track just for
maverick maverick wedding dresses we get
it now let me get the tornado holy I
don't know how to say this
Frank's bike is Kayode Rusty's bike
behind me is ko yo you idiot you can't
wear wedding dresses they get caught
I've been at Burning Man for like an
hour haven't get to have fun if you ever
come to Burning Man
snow please note this do not wear a
wedding dress not to move okay we got
nothing to do with chillin I just don't
like seeing two of my boys ko bro so a
Bernie man there's a bunch of different
art installations this particular one is
the Flamingo looks like you're able to
climb on top of no scientist but it
looks like that girl is climbing climb
there's no legs no legs I'll provide
easy wait you work out scale of one to
ten how safe is it to go through like
two seats to say it's to say physician
oh this is not safe look around my man
Brandon is to my right you can bet his
crazy Oh coming out of nowhere that
stories do really guys we can't see
anything right now this happens about
every five to thirty minutes here at
Burning Man they're five feet away and
they're they're hard to see right now
there's a reason no one has daily vlog
from burning man's hard yo like there's
so much stuff that goes into it look at
Brenda's hair right now my arms are no
joke here I don't wanna get the lens
dirty but just so you guys know the
lengths that we're going to get you guys
footing like Logan I've dedicated my
life to this because of you guys I
dedicated a few cameras today we're
gonna dedicate not even kidding
maybe it doesn't more for these like
three Brennan's camera broke just as we
had suspected this [ __ ] is dirty oh
this sick looking that was that that was
the artsy camera that got the good we've
been here for three million eyes are
numero uno camera broken I can see
through it it works thumbs up yeah yeah
like we said before guys the dust makes
it so hard to vlog here that's why no
one does it and also the whole footage
situation I mean look at her yeah you
have you have to drive to Reno tonight
you're like I like to like people gonna
think you're a hobo no one does the vlog
at Burning Man no one cuz it's
impossible to pass walk but we by the
way you're with not nobody you know with
just somebody but you're not with just
anybody
no buffer you're with new gun it's not a
verse album new gun your gun lick gun oh
that's a peach brush okay low gang I
don't know how to say this but I guess
that is the blind a weird today I know
but I told you guys like Bernie man's
gonna be weird
mainly because literally as soon as this
ends we are starting tomorrow's vlog I'm
is like not a thing here so as soon as
the stands we're going to riding to the
next what day but as usual if you're not
a part of the locating mixture to
subscribe hit them
hopefully Lydia can get this footage to
the outside world cuz like I don't have
communes of communication it's tough
Lydia hi my vlogs let me rely on you you
look you look super dusty right bad but
yell if you have not copped your
memories for that in the description low
gang I genuinely love you and I will see
you tomorrow easy easy
definitely not good bro I will see you
tomorrow
take it easy back
[Music]