changed my life that was a gunshot
oh it's fireworks no there's no problem
okay here's I need I have something to
say if you guys remember every piece of
merch that we sold during the month of
April we were gonna do a one-for-one
giveaway so you buy a maverick hoodie
and we give one to a kidney okay I'm not
gonna lie dude being around kids like
just perpetuates my want of a kid wanna
kid well you have to get on my toes job
failed are you gonna judge the kids by
what they choose the ones that you get
pork rinds I can't really like takis how
much money was on Google preferred whoo
crazy mom now I would say like enough to
buy like two bags of Funyuns
girl whose name I still don't know
that's right kid
me Minnie that's who I am
I forgot to get a snack we bully a kid
to give us a snack completely counteract
everything I love seem you get life
lessons from little girls I wish I had
the empathy you had
[Music]
Wow
yeah remember when I said I wanna kiss I
changed my mind
oh right biting extremely underestimated
exactly what it is that we're doing
today I thought we were giving away
hoodie I know you they go for my dick no
that would hurt no why can't we all be
friends the world works the world's a
cold place full of dick shots in
half-court shots figures up oh my god
it's terrifying dude they're stand
around kids I have something to tell you
I came here today expecting to make you
guys a little happier and expecting
maybe to leave a little happier doing
something good for the world but you've
ruined my life and I've had a horrible
time and I want you all to know that the
duck he's gonna chase me
don't worry Kenny goes faster than that
you guys are the watts empowerment
centers right what do you guys do yeah
so everything from after-school tutoring
music arts dance theater sports teams
everything this is one of the only
neutral zones and watch it this place is
kind of readathon you've never had we've
been here every week for 13 years
providing mentoring yeah haven't had one
person hurt in 13 years I think that's
the most important question I was gonna
ask is like who are the kids or these
magical beings running around and
beating my ass
this is watts after-school tutoring
music arts dance theater all the sports
scenes if we don't provide it it doesn't
exist but it's because the community
they really run the center they protect
it so when the average age here is 21
and the largest age group is 10 or
younger
so it's kids that are raising kids and
the dropout rate at schools little over
50% to less than 3% even make it to
college and I'm like guys I love you but
I got no money and they're like figure
something out what is the gangs that are
asking you to figure it out you guys
have incentive to try so this is
government housing so basically everyone
just lives here this is all they know
and this is all most of them have ever
gone within a two mile radius
most of them have never been to the
ocean that they've never been to a
sporting event they've never been
outside a little circumference so it's
like you guys showing up like you're
bringing a little bit of the world to
them I think a big thing for us is like
a dream right now what I want is I want
us to be able to build a recording
studio and a film studio for like I saw
a couple of kids running around like
Andre will give him the camera yeah I
was like yo what are these kids like cuz
Andre given cameras like you all want to
be ographers
hey we're just hustling for the hood out
here so like honestly if there's any way
you can help us hustle for these kids
because they deserve the best and they
aren't second-class citizens and I'm
tired of them thinking
why did you do this and they've changed
my life honestly it's just I don't know
I came just because one of my friends
was hanging out here one day and I
wanted to see him but 13 years later
every week I'm still showing up for some
reason and they understand that the
future is bright but it's not because of
some system that's in place but because
they're going to write history
I've never done anything like this in LA
or ever in my life
and I like I really do like kids and
like being here makes me like realize
that I think I definitely come by it
more often or however I could help go
sailing I want to get behind something
man and I really appreciate you guys I
really appreciate you guys allowing me
to come in and
[Music]
it means a lot because lots of people
they talk a big game and they'll apply
to Africa but they won't even come to
the other side of town thank you for
actually caring about this side thank
you I think it might be it's not a dream
confirmed wow you are quick you are a
quick young man wow I'm actually
impressed by wow I said it to you back
there
you cried why I don't know I got had a
moment bro what was it I don't know if I
haven't had to tear my eye probably like
15 years dude you're lying
ah cuz the girl said that there were
people that said I like people calm here
like for one-time visits and they sit
tell the kids that they're coming back
and no one ever comes back and it like
made me so sad we should do our best to
not be one of those no we are we got to
go back bro and like as I wasn't lying
when I talked to that guy as much as I
did get hit in the dick like I enjoyed
myself too that was a lot of fun I felt
like I was finally around people my age
yeah you looked like it dude you're in
your full element those kids have so
much energy and there's so many of them
which is actually also like kind of sad
so many kids I mean I've never done
anything like that in my life and I feel
like it really puts it in the
perspective how much different someone
else's quality of life can be I'm
incredibly fortunate and thankful for
what I've been blessed with with but if
I can help them do whatever it is they
want to do achieve the goals they want
to achieve by inspiring them motivating
them whatever it is I really I really
want to do that and I made a point to
the guy I said I don't want to be one of
those people that says he's gonna come
back to the dissenter and not come back
to just abandon the kids forever I
really did have a good time with them
today even though I can't feel my penis
but yeah that is a relationship that I
look to develop further further
with that said lo game you love y'all
thank you for watching this video if
you're not subscribed make sure to
subscribe to it the low gang gang gang
skirt the strongest family on YouTube
I'm gonna take a nap and ice my balls
get your Merlot Gopal calm / cha I love
you like I take me
[Music]