in three hours 600,000 comics three
hours and I am a man of my word
hey yo good morning okay what's up we
have a lot of new people coming to the
channel man guys welcome to the loge Amy
our average relate word of we're
maverick
no not you Ayla maverick Oh we're a
little bit different than everyone else
we do not follow the path of others we
do our own thing we are independent when
everyone else goes right we go left
yeah no I'm also they're like hot dog
boxers on Washington oh yeah welcome to
the squad if you have not already hit
the subscribe button this morning
something cool happen before I started
recording this I hit puberty why you
hear that yeah sounds different than my
normal voice no you know what it's that
way
what is this Ayla I go Ayla let me see
your phone I want to see where our song
help me help you is on the iTunes chart
I go on her phone and I just want to see
it every day way why I got my little
brothers so you have the full song
playing yourself there just pause get
him out of your life you want achieve
anything I don't like you right now and
it says boy even by you're off the hook
today
no little update you guys probably know
this help me help you with that twenty
four point seven million views twenty
four point seven million views bro the
fall of Jay Paul this track video is at
four point seven sixteen hours 16 hours
piece of cool he's a dog he's a maverick
what a G hi how are you yeah well he
just waved at me you see that I'm about
to go work out all of the new people
here that is a diamond bracelet I put on
my Birds ankle not your savage that's
what I mean when I say like we pay her
own pass like why the [ __ ] did I do that
I know cuz it's awesome I anyways this
guy come on car let's go you watch
themself guys yeah you got a good song
just come on he cooperative buddy hi hi
ah yeah you got to keep going you got it
buddy hi we'll be over here here's the
issue right now we got a dog we got calm
and can't you see the dog because as you
guys know content to freak out when he
sees as a dog yep that's like that we're
about to work on Sunday everyone says
Sunday's are for relaxed not gonna lie
sometimes they are but not today baby
not pull the bomber throw is looking at
your face you know know what a music
level trying to dampen active classes do
with nothing now you try to back come on
cash before you can't no baby jim says
guys i mean that's how you grow but you
still can't sell out any shows no still
can't find some matching clothes okay by
the end of the workout our nipples are
out we got max nipples we also got a
third set of nipples I don't know why
this is here not a girl but I think this
is like a sticky bra so real recently or
honestly though not even roasted I think
your rice is ready as is bralette juice
anyway the only one who it fits on is my
boy
put it up tighten up a little bit there
we go yo ray I know you remember of the
low gang but my boy looks much better in
it than you do this is hilarious
is it for dudes or woman you know uh
when you pause I would do this for you
please don't report me you through my
god bro this is sticky Oh for the nipple
Oh Nana's Omni silver ah back at the
crib Oh yo Ayla came over she is outside
playing with cops she's right there do
you guys hear she's playing with my dog
funny because they're like kind of the
same size but let's talk about that what
is she thinking and she what I was
saying was she comes over wearing the
tightest booty shorts I've ever seen
both and it was got them buns
what is she expecting right now mortal I
know I locked her out so we could vlog
about her but hey come on in
Oh what honestly what were you thinking
you're comfortable comfortable okay
talk to me ever seen you're playing with
it bro what'd you think of that booty
you're a lucky dog bro that booty though
really that's my boy yo guys so there's
a party going on at my old apartment
complex right over there guys you want
to go all right let's go cuz Ayla wants
to go yo a light is a pool party though
so you guys are like a bikini or
something
Oh yo is Layla can you go to engineer
bikini no a lessly you know ones booty
pants
yeah alright let's go good news I
convinced Taylor to change but yo is
that cause this is like a big uglier
version of car big party lots of dog yo
Taylor's dog is the FIFA Congress no
easy with a yo here - this is a puff of
meat in muscle right here he's a QB
weighs 50 product challenge you to a
wrestling match
[Applause]
stop dog Utica you're wearing opponent
now can't talk to you like oh they got a
DJ thing I came they got more game yo my
real home right here baby
Jim baby let's workout again oh the
Bombers role is looking nice come on
behind the pole yeah yeah waters all
leaves explainers knows like why not
okay cool
dog great but you can walk you're ugly
version rollin I said why don't you - hi
buddy I have a dog that looks like you
oh my god he acts exactly like Kong -
like a dog like you
yo star I hated I'm you honey skin
perfect beaches I'm a vegan wearing a
bra earlier so you know like expose no
you haunt us watch your right hand bro
be careful bro Eila have two things for
you I have this tanning oil I have my
back a huge gala please yeah Madeline's
yeah I'll buy you I'm definitely not
gonna buy or loan know why I can't even
please
I'm from Ohio there's no Sun there okay
bad would you smash that okay yeah I'm
working out ahead first time in the gym
in a while today guys I think after
you're done with this Ayla I'm never
letting you spread lotion on my back
again everyone wait just one second
George is almost cousin I don't know
what their relationship is but look you
got them pink toenail that is George's
foot I just want to clarify with this in
cahoots
oh my god by the way bro are you coming
over tonight I have a thing
you guys gonna love this what is it
hypnotism bro it's real bro show 14 you
might be able to fall in love with not
having pets aren't really so are you
coming bro hypnotizing right yeah
absolutely
not even ought to use my own brain I
don't know I make up words he'll make me
jump on one leg it start shouting Oh
vocabulary oh my god what did we make so
hot it's not a vegan anymore oh my god
how many times 100 percent 100 percent
oh this is why I got a list to do it
because I wanted to avoid looking like
this no he did not just spit on him
yo Georgie explain yourself
there's one thing you should know -
don't talk we feel okay I didn't squeak
that one I know it's crazy oh so I'm
watching this video and I realized I
made a mistake in yesterday's law I said
if it gets half a million coming I might
release the second verse I said that
number and I was like no way I were
gonna get half a million comment but I
forgot how strong the low gang actually
is and we might hit oh my gosh I'm like
kind of freaking out right now
oh it's at 300,000 compensated hour -
you guys oh this is my fault
you guys surprise me every time for the
[ __ ] sorry about that guys okay while
we're talking about numbers help me help
you our song that we made you forgot
sounds like this tell me how it is
number six on both the United and global
Spotify top 50 list let's go bro feels
good man I'm glad you guys are liking
the song by the way look at it has 300
others 37 1k oh my gosh grow in an hour
and a half in an hour and a half look at
y'all really want this second verse I
don't what I'm a dope you're happier but
this is this is a thing for sure to
clean up I'm ready to go what do you
want in love isn't he we got choice here
we got your highs down here but more
importantly it better than bullets
we got rich dirty incredible hypnotists
crazy but I feel like looking into the
eyes dangerous growth you don't have
this thing huh you know the pendulums
you don't need them anymore just let
your left and just focus on you like
that with my hand what in a weird
because you have an accent like I'm more
nervous now no you're not nervous or
morning okay I felt something okay you
guys know this I'm going to that map is
like motion like do new stuff
experiences in your professional
businesses and you've been everywhere
bro they know all
going to teach you how to focus relaxing
drifting to a natural state of it notice
I will teach you how to do this both now
and in the future what do you say to
people who don't believe in hypnotism
because it's like this is not a thing
like I feel mostly we're like military
no matter where I go there's always
somebody so I normally say how many guys
don't believe in hypnosis is always
won't and others say well that's alright
I've been taking it 20 years
successfully and I've been getting away
with it yeah this is the victim card as
you can see we got a are going to be
your harness store which would take you
away but what i hypnotized you it takes
about 3 to 5 minutes I need to listen to
each and every word I say if I can't
exercise you to the kind of person takes
500 pills every day just to feel normal
arrogant heroine a question how long
does this you could hypnotize anything
laughs so if I wanted you in the street
like me please fill up you definitely
tune back into my voice absolutely sure
you if you got anything in your pocket 5
money give it to me I'll keep you safe
from the enemies what I want you do is
the point of deep relaxation so I want
you to relax your arms your legs your
base your peak and just listen to each
and every word I say and just allow
yourself with for an opportunity into
the lashes that guide me Logan I'm going
to do a little voiceover right now to
speed up the process of this a little
bit but right now Richard is just
mesmerizing us helping us relax and
preparing us to fall into a deep sleep
he's telling us to look at an object
he's counting three and he's repeating
himself over and over and over then
right here he starts to yank out our
arms where [ __ ] really gets crazy
please open your arms just relaxing my
friends you'll did a wonderful job what
was your suspension like when you're
honest you'll have us your honor let's
get sweeping the fair closing lines and
relaxing and the more you relax the
better you feel what you never going to
go okay no touching my body especially
right we're going to sleeping relaxing
just for the person I'm touching now I
want you to realize from this point
forward no matter how hard you try and
remember your name it's completely
disappeared and gone from your memory
bank I want you to realize the more you
try the more you sell the more you sell
the more you try to merge the head if
you understand next a little bit Richard
was telling me that I was an
international farmer and he told me I
was gonna milk a cow or something
it started pooping or I don't know just
like that cow my friend look it works
out for you sorry around this button
click get it
Mokomoko mother watch out watch your
head watch your head bucket out look at
that
you can see it right now that diarrhea
that buttcrack diarrhea keep milking it
one more time you know push the cow away
without a labor of it but just sweet
things just relax and let lands you
realize from this point forward you're
going to realize in fact that smell
wasn't a nasty smell at all I want you
to understand and realize the smell was
the most beautiful smell you ever smell
in your life and the more you sniff that
the better it feels one two and three
eyes open breathing wow it smells pretty
good actually right there take a good
sniff
like that's welcome well that's about
the best amount of the world right there
you smell that which one is it you think
that's a beautiful smell in fact it is
coming from him take a good sniff
that smells absolutely beautiful so best
smell you ever smelt in your entire life
with mike cronin just sleep just
sleeping your neck since I'm touching
there won't remember his name at all or
to understand your name was completely
and utterly disappeared from your memory
banks welcome back everybody so I'm just
explaining to um a couple of it why did
you put yourself underneath and I just
want you to count from the last attempt
or start on one that's the last one
won't ya - yeah
sweeping just give account for one up to
ten you're going to realize and
understand the number two is completely
vanished disappeared completely nada
head if you understand one two and three
I always open just put your finger there
again my friend let's put your finger
that and the type of thing is count from
1 up to 10 number 2 is completely
vanished open your eyes get ready get
ready 1
great
we'll assume it's three three key card
he came for
let's try that one what's that trick
three plus three okay yeah I know what's
four plus four plus one plus one
think about it
how many arms dealer
but how many have I get what's the guy
without any name what's your name huh
okay George
what's his name No what is it you're on
your harness your harness
listenmi listenmi listenmi your name is
your harness Yeah right right
take it eat with it it's gone open your
eyes
try to think about it but it's
disappeared right now did we get do we
get any arms you know I just I can't say
do you want to have a guess I know how
many arms I have I just can't let your
finger man worst thing in the script
okay just put your finger and it touches
your forehead allies of the goods oh
you're fine fight it with your car when
that such as your forehead it will send
you to sleep but try and push it away
but it won't the closer it gets the more
you fall asleep try and force that'll
use your other hand you just push it out
away but it's coming closer
let it go coaster on let it go closer
little books this vlog let it go closer
let it go closer in deeper deeper and
closer the minute your finger touch
avoid allow yourself to relax closer and
deeper deeper and closer push it away
but you can't push it forward which you
can't the minute it touches your
forehead allow yourself to close and go
further and deeper deeper and further
into a sense of relaxation push it away
but you can't pitch it away closer and
allow yourself just to drift away my
friend just relax and drift away in the
DP though but then you filled up in a
second but not yet you wonder what the
heck just happened it will be crazy for
you but your name's grant still try my
vote and why the wait they made you
drive again
pretty well so what we have is two
really good candidates you would have
gone you'd have gone just a bit more
words don't be the [ __ ] no George
George you would have gone you just not
as relaxing that if you like georgia
tech's come here both howl ingrid bro
my hand if you remember the number yet
loving so gone
how many has you have to good I knew it
like I didn't want to say like I was
like no I I can't happen to me why can't
I do it because you're ten throat I
tried you to shoulder massage didn't do
[ __ ] Hannes hasn't move for the last
five minutes has not moved my love my
kitty realizes he still doesn't know his
name right no because I really I removed
it he won't know it until Charlie until
he has a choice bro what's your name
yeah I do know your name
can you tell me your name so he's just
smiling and breathing out of his nose
he's good over how's he ever gonna plug
his Instagram but it's just I hit my
little brother that's what you're under
it's just what it is look at me just
like this close your eyes and relax my
brother we should go to a t-shirt sure
she realizes nameless returned
bullying frankly there is no lock on
your name once you understand you'll
know your name to the rest of your life
and you say live in Prague on three
whatever actually they will complete you
really want to add three ounces and a
brother there you go you got it back
straight no it's a neat one no you're
not bad but I can't give him another one
I mean what you want Shaniqua no I'm
good with at your partner do you think
he was such a good subject because like
he doesn't have anything blocking his
brain like I got a full head of hair
like oh I want much hairspray that makes
so much sense
like right they blocked it out and hit
him it just like right to the core okay
what's going on give a girl a friend of
7 mm oh oh wait let me just replay the
clip I feel bad that they don't get to
experience when we just go maybe maybe
if you guys convinced me enough people
comment have many comments below it
maybe I'm not gooey like I'm coming
second but I didn't mean to say I like I
just said it I didn't think he would get
half a million comments that's crazy
internal struggle internal struggle oh
we're gonna get back to the subject but
first Richard bro thank you that was
amazing magical a gangster yeah well you
guys are all so yeah the fact you
already know so Richards dope now that's
just the real prop do I do it oh it got
half a million comments I know Brendan
says yet here's the issue yesterday's
vlog got half a million comments and I
said I might do it and like I'm a man of
my word okay you guys remember what I
painted this chalkboard of the wall it's
a kind of glue on it's pink but it's a
chalkboard I think this is a good first
time used I've never used to hear this
joke ready walk I'm gonna diagram is for
everyone to see ah hashtag the second
verse bang Morricone father like I've
been saying we have a lot of new of them
gangsters on the channel also guys I
think we are the fastest growing channel
right now I just want to take this time
and say make sure you follow me on
Instagram and Logan Paul always plug
okay I strike the second buck not going
to release it because a bro but then I
make a promise to the locating that
yesterday's vlog a half million comment
on your post they got six hundred
thousand comments in three hours six
hundred thousand comments three hours
and I am a man of my word is it a Big
Brother you do or is it a man of the
word I guess I didn't leave a diagram to
explain this I did not tell because to
be more complicated
I say yeah Big Brother a little stupid
in a minute promise of the longer every
can you always look stupid with the news
blames an L with a second breath away
when we don't show why go fifty when you
can go 100 oh my god I have a solution
sighs I just choked a little bit is it
like this I released this roast rack I'm
the whole entire internet to see the
second verse hashtag the second bird
expendable it's going to fire 50 million
views done to the lab but I don't do it
because I didn't
come I'll be back as a mouse 600,000
comment I bet this will be a million
much mark
so what if there was a way we could have
these people the 600,000 people come to
and anyone else is going to come and see
it like just that like a result
inequities really Netflix will be doping
yeah yeah I'll give you two kisses April
I'm making my own app and you got to go
down money to watch on the skin in that
decision move I like the music they
don't like it can you do that I think
then you have to pay for it also takes a
lot of this like a week feel like these
people might be willing away if I put
the music video on iTunes everybody on
YouTube doesn't get to see it exactly an
exclusive girl being thank God it's
really tight it is about good night the
second birds going live on iTunes
uploading the music video I'll let you
guys know when tomorrow's blah oh my god
I really didn't recognize I know my god
it's funny she's jumping but she's not
really getting any high what I need to
make a diagram is brother be careful you
didn't consider it that you are man the
door and yes you are the big brother
will people understand is that the
second verse is actually unreliable
connect these to being a bigger brother
no no no no no help we're going to
release it on iTunes in a date I will
let you guys know and the second verse
I just feel any growth
I'm contented with ah what a day we're
dead no gang that it did you not forget
go out today be a maverick do something
no one else is doing do not forget to be
a maverick go out and do stuff that
other people aren't doing hard work baby
success passion to the dough and if you
are new here subscribe to join the
family and until approximately tomorrow
at this same time itch I will see your
take it you guys know what I've been
wearing our new maverick merge recently
it's not out yet but it might be coming
soon we're going okay let's do it