go to giant feel sick but to okay why
the mood is kind of somber this all of
us woke up this morning and we found out
about the despicable incident that
happened in Las Vegas I did not know I'm
sure you do at this point by the number
right now is that 50 people have been
shot and gunned down with over 500
injured this happening so close to home
guys Las Vegas is an hour flight like
rattles me logs are usually
light-hearted and are usually fun but I
think when stuff is this serious and
people like me with the voice with an
audience somehow affect or change or
amend the situation I think it's our
responsibility to do so I just want to
say if you live in Las Vegas or know
anyone that lives in Vegas heart is with
you the low gangs heart is with you stay
strong the world is Rudy this happens so
often at this point they're almost
getting brushed off like oh it's just
like that that thing happened that's
horrible this shouldn't be like a daily
thing like that's disgusting human
beings need to change I'm tired of
seeing the hashtag pray for Orlando pray
for Paris pray for Vegas like thoughts
and prayers aren't working anymore we
need to induce some so what I'm gonna
ask you to do and ask you to ask other
people around you to do is emanate kinda
positivity spread light laughter humor
smiles like man everybody like people
are so negative never know when
someone's gonna need that little bit of
that little bit of light in their life
that that maybe this guy his name is
Steven paddock maybe if Steven paddock
someone said something to him that was
nice or something maybe he wouldn't have
done that's the first step I think you
can find to reach in yourself start with
kindness and posited eventually one day
we won't have to worry about this book
anymore
okay back to the regular vlog all right
it's a bit weird cuz now we're in a
little bit weird of a moment but we're
gonna start like joke Brendan is wearing
the colored socks little bro
okay thank you bro rude nun you're in
Vegas and you watch my blog thanks kid
stuff okay okay as I said I still feel
sick what exactly Beecher had a business
meeting this morning with manager Jeff
he suggested giving a an IV just shot my
sister up and taking vitamins problems
they're not doing hopefully it's just we
get a bunch of nutrients and stuff in me
that's gonna heal me because yo tomorrow
is a bridge exact the cool bus bro like
oh my god you don't know about this okay
I'll be like four months ago I woke up
one morning I was like dude I need a
school relatable I know I bought a
school bus it was in New York my dad
drove it here they dropped it off a West
Coast Customs and we talked about how we
can just make this the coolest bus
happens to be a school bus tomorrow it's
gonna be a cool bus see what I did that
yeah thanks
like I've been waiting so frickin long
to pick up this bus and tomorrow is the
day I don't really get excited about
things they were like like everything is
just awesome school buses like like bro
I feel like it's Christmas so that's
exciting and then I have an announcement
at the end of the vlog that's exciting
like tomorrow's a huge day that's why I
can't be freaking sick also you probably
yeah I know what I'm saying cast by the
shirt cuz you've never seen it before
tomorrow is yes and numerous yes it's
huge so yeah this isn't available yet it
will be tomorrow but the be a maverick
line down the shirt innovation son
changing the game hannes March let's
feel a little under the weather I'm
actually gonna hoverboard walk cause we
I can use the energy I would normally
use for walking for full recoveries
Congo so hard
eventually he starts going so fast he
doesn't even use his front legs
[Music]
okay papi your daddy's got to go get
here I'm gonna go put nutrients in my
veins let's do this demons in my system
need to get him out how does this work
and then what's gonna happen what other
nutrients pumped in good that's Brandon
I do blogs on YouTube
whoa gang like and subscribe logging
don't we don't feel we always do not
subscribe they told me I couldn't film
obviously I'm gonna film a mugger and
okay I got your back but okay I got
frickin needle in my arm this fight
against going into my pot look at how
big this bag in that whole thing right
there is going into my body feel like a
freaking robot right now I'm hooked up
to the wall this doesn't make me feel
better like I don't know what mm-hmm
no like it feels good but something
about that much liquid just going like
right into your veins you can just feel
it cause it's weird Brenda but thanks
for the smoothie Lydia it has a moon
immune oh hi baby
it's just so beautiful grow like every
time I get in and out of this car I just
have to stand here for like five seconds
at least and she's a Meyer watches Lydia
go stand next to it you calling Lydia
fat not someone called you fat this week
the savage he's lost 30 pounds there'd
be nothing left if you lost 30 pounds
you'd be gone so don't lose 30 but no
jokes about Lydia big fat let's go home
as you can see my eyes are just got done
laughs because this email I just
received notice to vacate in violation
of CC&R
I don't know what that stands for but
I'm assuming it stands for a colorblind
chach and roommate which describes me
and EDD but here we go
roll down the shades dear love her our
60 day notice to vacate you have until
today to make day you have not made any
arrangements to vacate the unit please
advise when you plan on vacation lady I
wish I could tell you in addition we
have been advised that you have two dogs
it's a violation of the Association CC&R
is article two section two point eight
point the man is hereby made that you
correct this violation okay I'm gonna
fix the dog situation right now I know
you love living here but unfortunately
with you and Aria I are yeah
unfortunately one of you has to go the
tough decision honestly bro I love Kong
you know our ear seems cool she has a
lot of potential but I think I know what
I'm gonna good bye cog I love you so
much buddy but the colorblind shots
everybody's association dictates that
you need to the person who sent me this
email we fixed the one problem I know
you guys watch my vlogs and I know
that's how you know I have to had to Dan
I'm probably gonna get an email for
vlogging this whole situation they tend
to frown upon that little bit it's just
one problem with that we did not film
I'm gonna fail got people that want
then I'm putting out I got blue
gangsters they gotta be entertaining
some scribers bravo unless you're gonna
physically remove me which I don't think
you are cuz I'm yo unless you come my
house you take of it you take me you
just yeah I'm stayin to all jokes aside
we are looking for a new place and we're
gonna find it soon do you think you
could you surprise me put them on there
for me so you don't have the key
actually I have the key yeah yeah I'm
not gonna let you drive without your
studiously ten thousand one day one day
okay but to be honest bro there's not
one day it's not your big day no I
wanted to do with driving with Logan
broke so yeah I do just got a new
vehicle so news segments driving with
Logan fuse to be yelled out on driving
judge hey shut your mouth but do you
know about this yeah I woke up in beast
mode
that's leap no no where do I go to eat
yes you got it
oh no pardon over the poopers haven't
actually have something serious to talk
about what is it got this letter today
from the HOA they said in addition we
have been advised that you have two dogs
in your unit that is violation of the
Association CC and ours that stands for
colorblind chachi and roommate Sam and
is hereby made that you correct this
violation I said something very
seriously though um cuz like we don't we
don't have anywhere to go
I was here before our yeah like is there
anyone who could watch Aria or something
but would you ever like get rid of her
considering no I'll move out within her
it's not like I want re out it's like I
need re out you know I tell you you
would really leave with your daughter
okay
yeah yeah you live in my house unbuckle
your seatbelt for you ride my car not
during my segment you see you later
trying to get in the car
why does he care he's not even care okay
first off what was the last time you
actually cared about the rules
shut the front door I've lost took
everybody all right Evan let's go get
you some food you're a growing dwarf
emelina's back here I hope you enjoy
driving with Logan you've been locked
out before I'm sure right and what's the
only thing you can do does anyone gotta
take an intake an Instagram page so what
did we do we brought me yeah second ago
the Sun was setting it was all I'm sorry
for constantly talking about my baby
here I'm also not literally and I've
said this in my snaps and Instagram
stores is the love of my life like
currently in my life
this is Milo I'm gonna be one of those
guys that marries his car 100% blog
content grave yo Jericho bro I'm
marrying the yep I guess that is the
vlog ro is a huge day here's the
announcement that I've been saving the
whole day cuz it's kinda big not only
are we getting the cool bus tomorrow
which I have been losing sleep Oh to
morrow your boy is gonna be on a TV show
you've all seen Jimmy Kimmel bro yeah
Jimmy Kimmel you know Jimmy Kimmel is it
down good guy funny you know if you like
that sort of thing yeah dude it's gonna
be dope it's gonna be on ABC at 11:35
p.m. tonight but tonight obviously I
mean by the time of the vlog by the time
this vlog is out so Logan I want you to
watch it bro go tune in and watch it boy
watch the maverick on TV with Jimmy
Kimmel bang know what we're gonna talk
about but I can assure you slash shop or
link in description the movement be a
maverick subscribe for me if you are not
yet sir
I've joined the Logan the strongest
family on the internet and Logan I love
you and I will see you tomorrow take it
easy phanpy hey Lars not over sorry I
forgot one thing
episode three of Logan Paul vs. is now
out on my Facebook page just looking
Paul vs. slackline do like ski walking
across two canyons like thousand-foot
draw hardest thing I've ever done most
scariest thing covered it was rattling
etrailer 8220 Juba cost about a hundred
forty feet they're coming down to the
wire my dad did it with me too so uh
yeah look for that in the description or
just my facebook local ball
[Music]
right though that Fred's not reach
mirrors my friends reach for their goals
what