one two three okay guys I'm looking at
my watch it is 202 p.m. that means your
boy is about to do his first ever live
stream on Twitch playing for tonight was
good I'm excited man we got over 103
thousand what people are waiting yeah
but I know what I'm waiting broke I got
a straight come man Center literally
guys there's a hundred thousand people
in the lobby the chat is going crazy
right now
needless to say this is gonna be lit so
guys if you're not a part of the low
gang a make sure to subscribe B if you
have not added me on Twitter cuz I am
gonna be streaming more than this go
ahead and ooh so at Logan fall was taken
you can see you boy rolled some heads on
f9 you okay so we're gonna be running
squads and duo's today straight up yeah
my heart is racing right now entertain a
hundred thousand people more than board
for a row and it's a fact then we go
hockey baby by the way Vince how you
doin bro
it's the fact that we just drop these
Huggies shirts you would only know that
if you watch this stream we're about to
do yesterday well there's a crazy time
vlog but yeah I know you guys have been
waiting the huggy trips now out looking
ball that calm slash shop or link in
description I okay you guys have been
waiting for like eight minutes for us to
go live I think it's time bro well I'm
nervous rope oh yeah come on at least
one W today broads oh I gotta prove to
the world yo also this is live bro they
will try to catch us slippin alright
they will try to make us make a mistake
but put your best behavior on because
anything could go down right that's what
makes this so special
oh I'm about to click this live button
oh boy Oh
oh we like you know I've no idea
Oh huh twist is that you mom
we watched my first last [ __ ] was good
150 thousand people watching right now
we put our hands over here bro because
we about love today all right ready whoa
okay guys um if you did not see that
here's the debrief and even if you did
here are the best highlights oh my gosh
this is crazy okay so I'm not gonna lie
I'm gonna be honest with you guys
ah there was there was too much going on
the room everyone's trying to like kiss
me on the face whatever they're trying
to do I was distracted the tips of my
fingers was very sweaty the dog was
barking dog was barking the spiders are
flying the point is I started off
that's okay man while you do that it's
okay
well hit me though so hard I didn't just
saying like I don't know what happened
and also guys I'm not a professional
gamer I feel like I will be though once
I put my mind to something I get really
good at it okay anyways I took me a
little bit to get my fortnight
livestream sealegs on and then you boy
started Hawking it bro nasty with the
snipe here's the update I am playing
with chance Anthony and my brother Jay
Paul guys we grew up in Ohio together we
got that chemistry because 12 people
left in the game of golf at W I feel
good about this round all I want
honestly is one dub one dub on my first
fortnight live stream and I will be
happy first game this is by the way my
first game for sure
[Music]
Wow one person left bro we bout to get
this dump get that jump that I'm going
in hot bro
I feel good about that
103 thousand people that just saw end up
how did that feel you saw the dub you
know it's tough it's tough it's up
getting these dubs before now but you
gotta do it bro I'm training for months
for this moment here you're not a part
of the low gang you saw bro I don't even
you say it
subscribe look at the wall there that's
no that was a good stream your boys
signing off thank you guys for watching
dude I did that for four hours I'm not
addicted I don't even like four at night
oh boy LP oh wow I'm not gonna I'm not
gonna lie to you streaming is exhausting
it's like I gotta I'm screaming for like
three hours straight maybe I you know
what I'm working on that I'll work on is
also you just watching you yeah here we
go and that's another issue
why are my plates indestructible bro
what's good well it doesn't break it
doesn't break yo what's good what's good
all in all a very successful first
twitch livestream I'm glad I'm able to
like actually come outside though cuz
like I got like four hours god also
thank you to everyone who donated you
know really you really don't have to but
your support means a lot I'm gonna be
doing subscriber mode only soon though I
can't do it yet cuz I'm not a twig
affiliate partner for I don't know
logging that is a vlog I know it's a
short one for obvious reasons if you're
not a part of us here make sure to
subscribe to in the Strongs family on
youtube and also the hunky shirts drop
today because that's what we do we hug
it right Kong yeah
nice a Logan Paul back on slash shop or
link in description low gang I love you
guys and I will see you tomorrow
hey guys future Logan okay real quick I
want to be streaming live at 6 p.m.
today on Twitch again I think I'm gonna
make that like my daily time that's
right daily row 6 p.m. Pacific Standard
Time yeah come hug it with your boy
today Logan Paul was taken orally in
description
feel life I feel I feel for your life
Oh screaming room as well