[Music]
it's good to just shock your system into
waking up sometime so what's up guys
first things first if you're watching
this video in the button below to
subscribe and not subscribed it with a D
do me a favor and subscribe times you
just gotta send it but yeah guys if
you're not part of the logging make sure
to subscribe relate but most importantly
we send it like we were doing today
Oh as you guys know in yesterday's vlog
we hand-delivered maverick Merc by the
way the hottest sauces motion the game
Oh compile that got a slash out to my
boxing opponent JJ
through my boxing opponent ksi start
training for your house by the way
JJ I got you during my breaks from
social media I've been working on
skydiving getting my skydiving lesson
today is a big day because I think we
are actually getting our official
license today as of now technically
we're still just students yo right I'm
actually extremely nervous
yo egg clouds get the look if we get our
license we can jump with headphones in
you can listen to music while you're
jumping maybe the number song which I
just dropped who knows a lot of stuff
and I don't know I guess that's why I'm
a student but the most important one to
me is we no longer have to wear our
jumpsuit now don't get me wrong we have
dope-ass jumpsuits obviously but I've
been meaning to jump ass I don't know if
they'll let me do it here but the point
is I want to get the license and then
send it in the nude I'm pretty sure
that's called perish longing yeah I
think so so let's go perish so friendly
they know about Paris everyone I mean eh
he didn't even react he's probably done
it before song together and nothing is
Paris long time longer I'm alive I'm
realizing these clouds are actually
gonna be a problem we live like two
hours away so coming here is a hassle
when we get here right we just want to
jump jump jump but you model cos gotta
go home the reason you can't have clouds
in the skies because of the dangerous
factors well I've been in the danger
zone I you guys saw I had that time my
parachute didn't open up
gabbro okay I had a cutaway I did the
danger and plus I got this cool suit no
this is actually fire you guys gonna
love but wait there's more as if I
wouldn't get a sick helmet actually this
is like my warmup helmet I have cooler
ones coming but check it out we got the
wings on the side we got the maverick
going down the head all together bro
this outfit is a boy I see alright guys
as we wait for the clouds to clear up
which it looks like they are we are
gonna hit the wind tunnel I don't know
rocket scientist but I think that is the
wind tunnel right over there yeah no I
know it is I can tell because it says
wind tunnel on it maybe you are a rocket
science baby bro or maybe I'm just Logan
is rocket science it is after all you go
her name is Daisy like the flower just
focus in on your pin here also guys my
at home addresses what look good I'm a G
bro yo but how's it look bro I'm kind of
nervous it's whiter than my skin
honestly it's whiter than you so it
makes you look really tan feel like I'm
about to run these guys go you look good
too though you open me on green maverick
the gray suit yo you're about to send it
9 times harder than the Superman
Oh to follow deep in my sleepy head
[Music]
oh snap you boys sent it Spence and I
actually kind of actually are still in
the learning phase of skydiving oh this
is our pilot are you the pilot you're a
pilot is that the plane will be jumping
out of No thank God yeah we're still
learning stuff that's why the wind
tunnel is good but the thing about
learning though and trying new stuff is
like Yuki I got stumped in that tunnel I
tried to do a barrel roll I like
shouldered the wall and then I got like
flipped on my back and was just
stumbling along the ground like a fish
out of water it was just extremely
embarrassing the point is we still have
a lot to learn now we are about to jump
for the first jump of the day these guys
are packing our chutes how come nice
guys you tip them and they pack your
parachute the right way if you don't tip
them you know it's iron non-licensed
jumpers are on a window I'm literally
this close I'm one jump away I know this
morning was the cloud guys and now the
winds God you said yeah here's the thing
about wind delays if the wind is over
twelve miles an hour and you do not have
a license they do not let you jump they
tell how fast the wind is going my flags
and stuff see the flag is blowing but
look I'm an ideas man right i vlog so I
have an idea right now that's some tape
here my idea is if we tape the flags so
it's like stop so it looks like there's
no way maybe they'll cancel the wind
delay it's gonna work nothing to see
here
oh no pay the wind stop
you go tell them yeah but we will let
them know that the wind stop looks like
a wind stop
there's a flag seven knots east and it's
just staying still all right hey Joe is
there anyone available for me okay
thanks I'm pretty sure that flag that we
saw was this there is Thanks how did
that not work oh this sucks like I'm
actually sad around I'm one jump away
from getting my license bro I could be
jumping in the moon right now parish
long just said nice job
they said it right we were recording
they just said man your license yeah
this is the jump bro this is the license
Joe we just need this wind to stay kind
of chilly
what Google savage in the dictionary
picture of us what would you say
slightly view Google savage in the
dictionary is a picture of us I'm
totally blanking this is good release
the parachute the red one
uh actually you know I think it might be
this guy right here how do we know for
sure what's it with you I have you have
another it's like the same thing you
have the same you have the ball yeah but
I think you're right it's either it's
one of them right okay so one of those
theories we asked know they're calling
for us right yeah no I think we gotta go
[Music]
yo how was that bro bro it's been sent
package delivered I mean look I was
hooking it right I did barrel I was
spinning threw up the Mavericks on I was
on my back all good stuff but you know
what the best part is bro what I don't
know I think I just got my license guys
no no written test and use my brain for
a seconds that's the golden egg right
there let's go get that sumbitch I'm
here to take a test yeah this is it I
have to get my school on for one second
feel confident my jumps are smooth my
landings are smooth my suit is still
white these are all good things okay I'm
wait how many was that loud to miss how
many damn is oh did you pass what did
you pass the test bro you got it
yeah passed where's the certificate
though items
no probably our two people the two
people they said Loki used to study I go
I'm smart okay I got a perfect hundred
percent on your last test and yeah I
didn't pass damn nine I'm joking right I
didn't know yeah so that means you have
to wait a week my ego who's just too big
I thought I could pass without studying
or a letdown I failed I think like I
think this is like where the screen goes
black and white and it's like this is
the moment Logan realized what why would
I why would I like jumping out of the
plane like only insane people do that
right like why would I like feeling like
a burden flying yeah I mean it's yeah I
guess you're right okay I think next
week we just got to come back you got to
grab the bull by the horns that
confidence back that's the water if
you're not a part of the Logan make sure
to subscribe
actually you know what you gotta sign
off no you it you gotta stop not even
plugging the merch that you can get now
and Logan Paul dot-com slash shop but
I'm not gonna do that cuz I mean dude
you did just plug the merch
why would I plug the Murphy and get now
looking to pull that cosplay shot Logan
I love y'all
[Music]
whoa easy tiger