[Music]
[Applause]
mr. Brahma busy guy I got things to do
bro I got merch to sell I got views
think I got the brothers to row so when
I come out here getting ready to stretch
for my morning jog and I see this King
dead bro it was the one that we were
looking for and we were looking for this
rat the other night guys know what it
has like a home in a tree over there and
it just it's apparently dead didn't come
do it I can't I can't tell cuz Kong is
over there he's just a lion in the
jungle in his natural habitat you would
think he'd be like playing with this
kill right don't touch it don't touch it
why because Oh what does he look like
he's just been frozen like mid-run bro
like he was running and he just died dah
God did you do this did you do this just
the familiar to you oh no stop it down
there's my cue [ __ ] okay anyways the
exterior designers are here they bring
in a bunch of plants and stuff but
they've been like digging holes it's
actually perfect for this his dead body
will blossom into a beautiful plant
exactly bro this is all this is
reincarnation here we go
[Music]
come don't go in there rest in peace rat
cause of death unknown
[Music]
anyways hey good morning little guy was
Bob fost I'm just washing my hands to
rid myself of all types of potential
herpes that I may have oh it's because
of the rat Naughton realized yeah that
was disgusting I'm sure has like plenty
of diseases but as usual guys today is a
big day so if you are not a part of the
low game make sure to subscribe because
we do stuff we find dead rat and bury
them yeah we don't normally do that but
today that happened but yeah subscribe
for me hit the subscribe button in the
face during the strongest family on
YouTube that low gang I don't think
you've seen this yet one thing I am in
love with they bring it in the artillery
plants Brendan oh holy wow hold you guys
we're decking out our yard or make it
look dope Oh like giant palm trees this
is awesome our yards gonna be sick y'all
and I feel bad bro I have to get
everything just through this like skinny
little alleyway in trees small alleyway
not our jobs
another project we're working on this
one has less diseases we gotta merge
closet we turned the creepy guest
bedroom into a little more fun bra we
still get a lot of work to do as you can
see there's like boxes everywhere box
box box box
brennon new joggers box box box just a
lot of stuff we got Lydia on it she's
organizing this room cuz she's the
closest thing I had to an adult in my
life
what
that's terrified it's just a little
rocking horse this is the creepy joggers
performance trick leggings for the girls
we oughta look how sexy we cannot be
stopped if you guys have not gotten your
joggers yet local all that cop / shopper
anyways we gotta clean up this hey bro
yeah it's gonna start to rot yeah that's
not good it's just we got so many better
things going on like yo you guys know
what the iPhone 10 came out today a
little secret connect I think Lydia was
able to grab me one blood had Lydia see
if she could grab two cuz I want to do a
giveaway with the numeric bottoms with
the new iPhone X with you guys know
hopefully she was able to grab two we'll
find out soon but yo I gotta go for a
run Shaunie's I'm busy bro Brendan I'll
see you later bro what what Rhonda I
messed up bro I was like halfway down
the street I got a text for my barber
he's like hey man excited for your
appointment at noon that's now hey can I
get the camera I gotta go get a haircut
earlier I guess I'm not jogging this
morning oh damn I don't know if I can do
this with my hair maybe one day if I
play like a bad guy roll like do I look
evil or just like I found also we got my
boy Mike over here okay guys I've said
it before I'll say it again I truly
believe that in order to be beautiful
you have to look ugly first which is
exactly what's happening here mom
go back to coconut heads you guys
noticed looking I like the zooms much
more than breath it does bra here good
15 my acne blemishes like this right
here yeah see we're working on that yeah
it's just tough when you have hit
puberty five times we're back at the
crippled guys it's a weird day not cuz I
look like an official coconut head well
because we get back and you're with them
just watch all around this car
oh yeah it's broken for sure hold on
don't look now Mike it's actually good
now okay yo ignoring the wasps one other
thing I noticed about this I've been
letting Evan drive this does this look
like someone hit my car like look that
was looking good and this is looking
like bus TSS what is this dwarf dude two
questions why did you put a wasp nest in
my car well you did hit somebody why is
my muffler inside my trunk I gotta watch
me ass busted ass car what does he want
[Laughter]
my god it's still alive go and finish
the job man did you do that did you kill
that white trash Spanish equipment or
not do as well let's not kill a wasp oh
you speak Spanish I speak speak as me if
you killed it was that's a good boy con
he's a cold-hearted killer bro he could
have killed the rat for all I know
maybe Kong got stung in his tongue by a
loss when he was younger and that's why
it's always hanging out and then avenge
my house to get my subscribers they call
you a minute hello gang we're gonna get
to the bottom of this and we're gonna
figure out what's been going on
[Music]
[Applause]
it's super-exclusive it really only just
does what the 8 does no it's much more
advanced brothers more screen there's
more screen dude look at all the Apple
hasn't made a significant upgrade in
years I feel like you're an apple hater
ruff know why Lydia was holding a bottle
over her face now I know acne today I
have acting looking at you I went
through puberty five times Lydia this is
Mike by the way I never met you before
Oh gang we're gonna see what that pimple
looks like and I'm gonna get in there
get my hands dirty put my work boots on
it Bob fetch so look when a new iPhone
comes out everyone makes iPhone videos
do they get a lot of use I'm gonna do
the same thing here these are both 256
gigabytes we're gonna be giving away
this one yo go get a mic just be gentle
on his tongue Oh
yadi yadi yo you're crazy
what are you park it out buddy oh I
can't believe we haven't done this yet
[Laughter]
well yeah anyways you know unboxing
videos get a lot of use a lot of
subscribers described nothing low gain
so I figured what I do it here we go
first thoughts is the plastic packaging
is very high quality and then the
material is soft look and if you look
closely it's lo tricolor
that's oh damn the camera goes
horizontal Wow that's because of the new
metaphase in drogyn ater that they for
sure
metaphase oh oh look it's turning on oh
my god this is a magical mohel oh ha ha
Oh English oh my God look how much
screen there
hold your new iPhone up to the camera
yo wait watch dude look at this circle
and then you put it like in this photo
camera oh so many things to do with the
extra space bro look at they could put
the time in the top left new times in
the top of the watch
we don't need you anymore well I needs
no time ok so just getting a little
doctoral here I'm swapping the SIM cards
out this is the closest I'll ever get to
completing college it's a tiny little
thing
no joke the amount of data on this thing
is scary not only because of like
technology technology being able to
store data in this because of how many
nudes I got on this I don't think the
sim card is the memory it's just your
cell phone can recognize the unique
three-dimensional features of your face
that's terrifying you do have a unique
face do you think it'll recognize me
even though coconut heads right now
[Music]
you catch the jawline okay good
Apple you've done it again I just hope
that when I get a girlfriend she doesn't
hold the phone
[Music]
I guess this one is just like Oh what
are you doing on my face it's right
imagine this yeah I was gonna say yeah
she's dead she oh no she's cut out oh
damn it
because you're making a big deal out of
otherwise we wouldn't care we all have
acne I said to myself you to my said to
myself you you life owns pro people like
what do they did you drop tests Yeah
right may see like you're thinking like
blending of blinders you know I have a
better idea but first what's what's over
there what do you do you look ridiculous
come on let's just see it
no there's nothing there though yeah oh
my god I wish so much time all right
here's the real reason that came in here
we're going to uh see the strongest guy
I know to see if you can actually break
the phone some joggers route let's go
test just how strong the iPhone X is
what is that oh no so guys Bradley is
legitimately the strongest guy I know
look at this guy oh he's no joke and
this is his gym bro the gym this is the
first time I've seen it
this is impressive boobs are not my bro
Bradley around fish I ripped this 50
times ready oh yeah I'm getting
distracted by the yoke miss Bradley this
is why I came here oh I saw next dude
it's new I'm trying to get views you
guys lend them in blenders legit
breaking right now honey break break
break it right now I'm gonna break it in
my head two things one I didn't know if
it actually be able to happen in two I
didn't realize okay I thought I was
gonna be giving this away maybe I still
AM maybe you won't break it but the
other one has my you know has my face
facial ID on it and everything so this
is the second one brand new iPhone X
like I want to give it to the road no
you have to use your hands so I'm not
gonna cut now because I want to I want
everyone to realize that he's actually
gonna snap this yo pressures
you know I know sorry now this is a lot
cuz it's not as long as I hold it like
this you can see the horizontal - x4
just do it oh oh my god my boys
yes yes might be able to like using as a
paperweight though but no problem
this was 256 gigabytes this was the most
expensive one yeah I can you know I can
go check see if they can get the screen
fix on it because they have screen I
just feel like that's not possible
oh you could give it away you're right
yeah I'm gonna give away a low gang one
of you is getting a fresh new op Bradley
Martin correct all you have to do is get
maverick merch in the next aisle let's
say like 48 hours the collector's item
exactly guys Logan Paul Keim slash shop
or link in description the joggers
maverick bottoms we just dropped it
we're changing the apparel game forever
oh I have a joggers bro already brought
bro in the black these are actually real
like actually actually real nice-like
not some you - bullsh
exactly because I do pair of stuff and
this is this is really nice they're cut
so like I'm not playing three cutting
and sewing this you break my iPhone X I
give you my joggers and I take your
blood that's my boy forgive you guys
want to get one of these awesome iPhone
X's copier maverick merchants it's
amazing it's functional Logan Paul Cobb
slash shop is your I think it's your mom
hey mom yeah can you come pick me up
with thanks for coming yeah good if
you're not a part of the low gig make
sure to subscribe otherwise hello you're
not a part of the Logan oh it's just
getting gross bro but you know this is
what the Mavericks do bro most people
they use their iPhone X is me I have
bodybuilders snap that matcel okay I
love y'all I will see you tomorrow take
it easy
yeah
I met mine
I met my pride
push the glass further into his hand