if this video gets 8 million likes I'll
get a diamond nipple ring I'm not even
kidding I'm sorry it's just more to brag
what you doing you know you're freaking
out my dog Bobby you're scaring him come
on Kong no more this is the real you
that's not the real you oh ok ok
anyways lokay you're in for a treat this
morning look across the way there's some
little gangsters standing on the roof of
the hotel when I first freaked them out
a little bit by sending Frank out there
a little bit I I said Frank them alright
and then we're gonna shoot merch at them
so they hopefully they don't get scared
and Sue me all right let's do this right
what up guys me Logan guys love the
Logan yeah
Logan yeah don't fall for him I'm ray
I'm Logan and you're Logan actually one
of the official Canon t-shirts yeah we
only have 50 and the only way to get one
is through the can these local gangsters
came on a good day not easy
Logan it's not that hard act hey guys I
hope this makes it I'm gonna throw the
fidgets spinner I don't think we have a
choice but you got to do it see the good
thing is if Frank throws it and like
hits them in the head he's the one with
the law so you go for it I'm staying at
your place liabilities on you watch your
head it's heavy bro here we go baseball
Oh bro you made it it made it cool
riding the bull you said we should get
out of here buddy I didn't show you this
yesterday but the diamond gold maverick
pendant kiss it it's you buddy
what no it was actually $20,000 as you
guys know I bought this yesterday well I
got it yesterday this logo this bird
means so much to me I'm like yo why not
drop some money and make a cool thing
that I can wear around and just look
like a total douche bag oh I did I'm
gonna use this for like performance oh
oh performances and like music videos
and stuff but I realized Burleson I got
this you good well since I got this like
custom-made like Brendan we don't
actually know if the diamonds are real
or the gold is real or anything you get
it appraised then appraised like we take
it to someone professional and they tell
us the actual value of it wrong you
should get Evans Rolex appraised as well
just like why not like double triple
check what are you like doing why you
know all my friends are being weird this
morning what are you putting the merch
closet what up boys plug in for me
anyways bro where's your Rolex oh come
on do the thing what'd you put it in the
laundry dawg oh yeah where's Rolex let's
check the water oh I got 11 million
people had no wear your skin Rolex is
anyways yo can we go get these appraised
today
actually working on your father you need
my permission to do you know why there's
some good news my man Frank just said
he's gonna make breakfast for us they
say you'll know if I start we do you see
also what he saying oh yo we exposed
Evan last night
roll the clip yo there's someone in
Evans room bro what don't know you're
crying Frank is like 3,000 what we have
we thought it was a joke it's just a low
weren't some ever merge she's just
chilling
I know you got scared oh my god I didn't
know there were hours bro the grind
never stops here in LP vlogs def gonna
kill you in your sleep
oh great can you let me know before you
do it anyways Frank we're ready for your
breakfast breath my breakfast burrito oh
do you have the tomatoes and stuff for
the breakfast burrito no you did not get
your little buddy
Samantha Mayhew cover me you vegetable
me onion me something made with rose
cucumbers raised you mom Frank you know
apparently you can come in the house you
don't have to do this here
I hope you got the tortillas more
tortillas Oh leave my kitchen I was born
under the Sun so one must so fatally may
be peaceful I've done but I just wasn't
enough
oh she's an actual sometime let's keep
it making in here bro Frank this is
unreal are you dude be honest with me
Frank never made these in my life before
but we're gonna try them out I like but
stuff it's all about presentation oh now
that I'm grateful bro I'm grateful for
Frank I really am but Dawg you stop my
kitchen how does that even happen is
that growing there or did that land this
[Music]
oh my gosh Frank this is amazing I go
with that said I don't even know what
this is that's how much of an odd is it
a quesadilla breakfast quesadilla I
don't know but it's got cucumbers on Oh
oh yeah no stress oh no Frank
bro oh my gosh yo Brenda quick sidewalk
go it's not that good at brick yeah you
can be honest with me it's not business
but like I don't want to hurt Frank
really why did you say this is a
quesadilla let me show you got turned
into a cardboard cutout no Brendan watch
yeah yeah so Lydia if I were you I'd
tread lightly punch me in the face
oh my gosh the diamonds sparkling bro
it's too icy bro okay we're gonna see if
this is actually real diamonds real goal
what I'm not yeah let's see if our
friendship lasts oh if it's not real
you're not gonna be my friend no out
here down here so I could buy you a
Rolex
and I felt bad cuz your blog needs
someone to come out cool so uh stuff and
welcome to driving with them never mind
Frank's whining what's wrong this is not
how you treat your friends Oh Mike this
seat is broken I got my yetis in the
phone oh wait I can't you're just what
look it's not moving Frank can we just
please get into our segment please
welcome to drive levity just help me get
my ankle back what do I do about this
bro
I don't know rob about the turnover you
don't call me Sammy Adams ever again in
your life would you rather be a dwarf so
now that things have calmed down a
little bit what I said about calming
down I think he's angry I think we
should you know maybe get him some anger
I know he's taking improv classes doing
a really great job of that top of the
class but anger classes you know what I
mean it's like a different type of
warning hello my friend won't shut up
stop can you help me yo do anything this
Rolex is fake no I don't think it's fake
just my people suggested that I just get
a double check because I realize like I
haven't you keep saying again I don't
know what that means Frank I'm just a
vlogger my foot is not a watch Oh
I'm a potato haha it's a freaking
miracle we made it thank you for
watching driving with I'm always so
nervous filming in jewelry stores
because they always think we're gonna
like rob them they don't want to taste
it dude I'm sure we documented actually
robbing a jewelry store it get like at
least 5 million views no should we do it
I know diamonds bro
I know done very well to make breakfast
my man knows diamonds bro they're real
diamond do you think I take it anyone
you're giving his back robbed us $20,000
there's nothing left to spend your money
on here we are with all the ball hi how
are you I have nothing left to spend my
money on look at brother see there
beeping there's good diamonds in there
just some of them might not be the best
ever but this looks legit to me bro I
guess I'll let this one slide Thank You
Evan but the next time you give me a
diamond Rolex I could have diamond
nipple ring this video gets eight
million likes I'll get a diamond nipple
ring I'm not even kidding this is pretty
legit yeah it's my big thing so that's
good news our stuff is not fake now I
can continue being friends sounds good
let's go that way
hey we went that way you look at Evans
mouth right now bro why are you such a
messy eater I use such a doll I don't
know good question anyways this is so
much better than Frank's quesadilla this
morning we're eating
I didn't see you there oh no it was good
it was good it was just like it could be
better so we ate my man walks up to me
has me this what did you say bro I'll
carry my merchant all day around my
backpack just in case one day I meet her
you're just walking on the boulevard
here we come across dude Papa's side
smells like Jake Paul in here bro doggy
way that this Dalmatian pitbull came
over to Evan right as he said he wants
up dude I don't know this is like a dog
version of you ever just like yo I think
the thing is Evan sees how good of a dog
Kong is and wants one of his own he just
you know he runs back and forth all day
it's a funny thing
yeah it never gets old bro it's getting
worse is he losing brain cells dude are
you stupid
come here buddy are you stupid hi okay
just I'm just gonna stay here till you
decide to come on god I'm trying to get
you a brother bro who can fit tongue has
the longest tongue I've ever seen Kong
we're trying to find you a brother oh we
tried oh my god claw was raw Brendan a
hundred percent losing brain cells like
we would have be your dog yeah shut up I
found a perfect one no you actually did
yeah
oh it's now oh this is a commitment bro
I think I'm gonna go tomorrow no way oh
no gang what do you guys think should
Evan get a brother or sister for a car
the car what do you think that's a
commitment bro I just like put you in
the face he's like I keep missing today
like woosh woosh Oh Britney you have to
do it that could be a sound effect no no
no see Brendon like that it's crazy
anyways comment below if you think we
should
another dog that would be Evans dog and
ever couldn't ride in or something fun
okay low gang it's the moment you've all
been waiting for Brennan over here yeah
yeah it's the moment you've all been
waiting for okay it's the title it's the
hook it's the thumbnail let's talk Logan
Paul versus season two yeah so yo for
those of you who have been with me for I
don't know maybe like five months now
you were with us when we shot up he
versus season two yo it's skiing insane
bro just look at this thumbnail bro I
got a freakin alligator on my back baby
let's go that episode was Logan Paul
versus alligator wrestling yes I did
that bro documented on camera today I
get to release the trailer for Logan
Paul vs. season two it's a big deal bro
I'm just I'm done talking check it out
one man stands in the way Logan Paul the
viral sensation you're maybe gonna beat
he tore the sleeves off and he came to
play get out of my office
[Music]
I need help
Russia I'm gonna call you back
Russia i'ma call you back that was when
I was a mayor of a town in actual city
for two days so many good episodes bro
I'm so excited for this to come okay
that is gonna be on Facebook you guys
can see on my page actually which is
dope but you know what's funny is the
Facebook is actually my biggest platform
Facebook yeah my biggest platform I
think you have like fifteen point eight
million likes on my page first episode
is Logan Paul versus American Ninja
Warrior yes the show yes I went on it
and competed that is coming out Monday
so you all have that to look forward to
but I suggest getting caught up on
season one if you haven't seen it yet
that'll be on the Facebook page as well
link for all that stuff is in the
description or just literally type in
Logan Paul on Facebook if I can find it
bro I'm out here with that set low gang
that is the vlog it was a fun day good
vibes today I really like this thing
right here Naoko no no he likes it too
much oh he likes it cuz it's that
maverick spirit bro that's what it's all
about not being afraid to be yourself
and break out whatever bubble you live
in I've read this quote the other day
I'm quoting lately you remember who you
were before the world told you who you
should be think about that that's deep
also we are approaching one year of
vlogging 365 days on September 12 we
have an exclusive peach peach piece of
merch we're dropping for that so be
ready cop you're mad at me right now
little Bubba come /op link in
description maybe not subscribe make
sure you subscribe below gang I love
y'all I'll see you tomorrow take it easy
man
[Music]
good