oh my god I can't believe it I love you
lady I love you guys are going to Texas
why no we got a reply into Texas all
right make two taxi I know they have
horses in Texas I just don't know where
they are
Oh Oh my ex is live in Texas like in
George Strait I don't have one extra
Texas but I'm looking forward to making
that happen
why were you Texas okay I could tell you
I'm gonna do it
I got pee first don't get my wiener I've
been waiting for this day for the last
four or five or five months look dude
team average is growing okay and guess
what I'm forming a new team to a team of
talent a team of two to talent and so we
don't have means of transportation for
both my team of people or the new team
on perform until today folks they say
everything's bigger in Texas when I was
peeing I was looking at my wiener and I
realized that's still not true I'm a
crawfish Texas and I'm already we're in
the hottest merchants in the game I am
scheme flirting uh it's gonna have the
hottest merch in the game make sure you
head over to love you brother like I'm
and get your red hoodie it's extra
important that you do that today cuz we
just spent a hundred and fifty thousand
dollars on a vehicle ever about to get
and we're no longer on Google preferred
so please I need yo this is actually
awesome I've waited for forever every
night we're like yo can you imagine if
we had the we got a Sprinter van I'm
just gonna say it we got a [ __ ]
Sprinter van it's been being customized
for the past like four months I was
gonna get either a Rolls Royce Wraith
which I believe actually Austin McBroom
just got gifted by his wife Catherine
paya's and I chose the Sprinter so we
could mob around La in style looking
sleek looking fresh looking at how a
little woodsy Kiki
we just have so much fun with you
controversial dude bro he gets to say
anything he wants because he think cuz
it's all like a joke like he laughs at
like watch you just laugh after whatever
I said hey Andre Mike doesn't have an
STD I feel like it's more just like a
long line it's like crazy that a girl
could vote now Shh since I tell you what
we can do go get this goddamn Sprinter
van put our whole team you know I'm
excited we've been doing real good
lately bro ain't not a controversy
content is super quality I'd like to be
a little more consistent but let's be
honest bro like we've been putting out
some of the best vlog in a while it just
don't stop son I'm really excited for
this dude oh well I've waited so long no
this thing's a unit oh my god
[Music]
ah the day has finally come boys let's
go I'm smashing so much smashing oh damn
oh it's like this in case I want to eat
or read a book a great great place you
could set things watch this great
exhibit eights plus it's perfect Oh
where's Jackson oh it's not an emergency
I'm just testing the emergency Oh God my
favorite part about the whole thing
maverick logo on the headboards oh damn
it'll bother me for the next four hours
the horse is there by chance not seeing
them right now man this is the stuff
that really gets my gears grind and this
is good stuff we've got the g6 a control
system solenoids and everything seems to
be in completely disconnected what do we
need to know about this all this stuff
don't catch it on fire okay great let's
go subtle yet distinctive I could have
said that better myself actually I feel
like I could have let me have a shot
beautiful yes grandiose but well refined
descriptive and perplexed
remarkable yet tasteful valid and chic
okay
hi baby let's see you back in LA are you
dying okay please don't she's gonna be
shipped back to LA on a truck hey guys I
got a confession to make this video was
shot like two weeks ago we've been
hiding the Sprinter from social media
we've been using it in LA like we went
out last night we partied a little bit
here's what that looked like it's just a
great thing you know but ideally we
finish this vlog with some sort of epic
race between the cool bus in the the
Sprinter van we just didn't have time
but here's a really of what that might
have looked like
[Music]
[Applause]
but anyways I wanted to take this time
to just like just talk for a second and
update you guys on my life because I'm
gonna be a little vulnerable here and
open up my emotions I'm not gonna lie I
am so [ __ ] happy right now I finally
feel like we are on the cusp of
greatness again like that 2017 Logan
Paul that's about to happen again the
momentum is with us you guys are really
enjoying the content whether it's
impulsive whether it's the vlogs whether
it's the challenger games which are
coming up and I just announced and
actually the tickets are available for
that so if you're in LA or actually if
you're anywhere in the world I want to
see you there
July 27 the biggest entertainers in the
world are gathering and we're gonna see
who's the fastest I'm betting $100,000
that I'm the fastest youtuber it's gonna
be live streamed with a donation link a
bunch of money is gonna be raised for
charity but yeah just a bunch of
celebrities racing and then figuring out
who indeed is the fastest entertainer on
the planet link in description for
tickets like I said July 27 also
impulsive our podcast look it's the
number one podcast in the world I have
no reason to lie I could not make that
up trend lately men don't piss off the
sponsors tread lightly man okay we don't
have spawns [ __ ] you I won't argue that
right I screwed this whole operation it
has been so much fun we are almost on
episode 100 so we're actually going to
do the hundredth episode live could
potentially ruin my career once again I
hope not but it's gonna be a three-hour
livestream on July 17th at 5 p.m.
Pacific time and 8 p.m. Eastern so be on
the lookout for that we're gonna do two
awesome guests and a musical performance
I'm not sure by who just yeah hoping why
don't we I don't even know if I'm
allowed to say that but I just did but
as far as right now goes I'm on my way
to Sweden I'm going to Sweden to record
music for two and a half weeks while
we're there we're gonna be training
boxing etc so yeah I'll be in Europe
just grinding my ass off and yeah just a
lot of good things man thank you guys
for your support seriously means the
first world to me
we've been through a lot of [ __ ] and
like I said the tables are finally
turning and I'm at a very good place
mentally physically emotionally probably
the best place I've ever been in my life
so I love you guys thank you for that if
you're not part of the low gang hit that
subscribe button tune in for the
challenger games link in description
July 27th and July 17th first-ever
impulsive livestream for episode 100 I
think that's it thank you guys i frickin
love you and i'll see you next time
[Music]
I don't know what I'm doing either