[Music]
this hurts my hands you guys caught us
in the middle of sound so as you guys
know we put up this pulley system
yesterday from my dog Kong so I don't
have to go down there in the morning
it's all about efficiency 17 the
merchants I got Church status site yeah
but we got the freshest joggers in the
game the Maverick joggers sister V next
we got the pink hoodies and stuck the
favorite hoodies aren't stuck y'all they
can't stop us baby it's a movement it's
a revolution two maverick people who are
thinking differently doing things
differently to accomplish their goals
maybe that's what it's all about looking
for that kind of slash shopping link in
description now prime example of a
maverick is my dog don't move don't you
move no don't throw your money I told
you not
[Music]
you're crazy little puppy but you're a
maverick and I respect it right guys we
got stuff to do so we're gonna go do
that stuff but if you're not a part of
the low game make sure to subscribe
it's days like these that I realized
truly how weird my life is we got the
Cinquecento next to the Yeti next to the
cool bus yo like four years ago I was a
kid in college in Ohio studying
engineering okay the three tokens
vehicles on the black but every about to
take the cinquecento to get some
breakfast and we need the squad hey do I
get breakfast with us we got the perfect
car for you Evan back here is like we
actually have a lot of room like we're
kind of scissoring but it's cool let's
go get some breakfast
[Music]
like a good old Sunday morning
Cinquecento dry guys also we have a big
week coming up so guys this week as you
know I'm starting shooting off for my
movie the thinning - it's the sequel to
the first thinning as you guys know your
boy is an actor and it's so good my
character play grunting is coming back
dropping the no handlebars music video I
read your comments I know a lot of you
are waiting for it so that's pretty cool
I think my man Evan is it is Grossberg
wait for the past 10 years
[Music]
hey everybody want to be a maverick yo
we have a giant massive mega biggest
ever merge drop we've ever had on
Wednesday you guys know like Black
Friday's coming up Cyber Monday is
coming out so we're just discounts new
stuff love up why can't I talk discounts
new stuff it's gonna be epic um I hear
something funny to happen though my man
Evan ordered two chocolate chip pancakes
but they mistook that for two orders of
chocolate chip pancakes it's actually
six pancake collectively this food like
it weighs more than you also weigh
before you drink that I think maybe it's
a little kiddie there you go again Logan
you okay so I don't know how to describe
this we came back home and I looked over
there and there's a girl
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my my Sophie Dawson what are you
doing up there
do you guys set this up in my yard
cool how is this stable Sophie is this
stable I think Evan could fit in the
bucket and we could like do the same
thing we did with calm with how did that
remind you of that so let's try it
you're a bro I want to try something bro
he's not complaining look at it you got
it sorry I got sidetracked Sofia no it's
now actually like a zipline okay here's
we're gonna use it for obviously we have
to test this out so we're gonna put
ourselves in a hypothetical situation
and I'm talking like extremely
hypothetical let's say your friend is
down by the pool he's not wearing
maverick marks again hypothetical
obviously he would be but let's say he's
not he's talking to a girl right picking
roses whatever he's doing so we take the
marled short throw a little pink hoodie
actually wrap it up with a dad hat Danna
okay skip the dad hat for now let me
just take it don't forget something
[Music]
don't worry about it why do you always
make me do this yo that's crazy how
would just pop down you broke
anyways selfie why don't see my trick
okay right I'm not really sure how this
is gonna work I forget my name is Jay
Paul Jay coming at you it's everyday bro
I felt like my face was wanted to just
leave my my bones just like everything
just wanna fly off but I'm pretty sure I
drooled bro fish are truly a lot replay
was happy you didn't puke on us why not
we go content yo real life that was
actually crazy Sophie I don't I don't
think I've ever been that dizzy ever
[Music]
yeah again just not sure how that's good
hey yo I wish my little sister was this
cool didn't have a little sister now
there's only one way this can give
better I'm just kidding I don't know if
he get any better than that bull it
can't get better okay so look down look
at Sophie's got her famous bow and arrow
if you guys remember this girl shot a
pineapple off of my head
with your feet though right it's all
cool fun except I'm over it bro I'm done
with the fruit no more fruits so today
I'm gonna catch it with my god
darn pan sorry for swearing I know
you're young wish me luck I'm suited up
ready to go Sophie's gonna hang by her
neck yeah you go ahead and do that yo so
Sophie's gonna hang by your neck and be
casual no I'm not nervous I'm just like
I've never caught an arrow that's been
shot at me by feet before and like I saw
the tip and it's actually sharp honestly
worst comes to worst bro but deflecting
with the Rolex you know it is platinum
so I think okay so it's gonna be a thing
bro
[Music]
first time first time do it okay so that
was awesome I caught it with my maverick
merch Sophie Darcy you're a true
maverick here maverick women's leggings
take them put stuff as usual that was
amazing Oh interesting
okay before we sign off you guys know I
always have people coming in in and out
of my house so I put on my boy Mac you
look what are you look it's a maverick
jumpsuit it's just maverick down the
sleeves with the logo and he's got a
matte black maverick on the back okay
low gang that is the vlog we're ending
in a bit early today cuz I'm going
somewhere - no Thank You Mac I'm going
somewhere tonight to do like a sort of a
bigger vlog it's gonna be fun so if
you're not a part of the low gang trust
me you want to subscribe you do not want
to miss it I've said it a thousand times
today I don't even need to say it but
I'm going to you on the way to get the
marshal involved I got slash shop join
the maverick revolution I'm excited to
see that it may be like 10 to 20 years
which one are you gonna be inspired by
my vlog and who of you in the low gang
is gonna change the world low gang I
love y'all
No give me a minute man I might need a
bit more peace of mind all right on the
rickshaw
oh don't endure a pigs flying my mind
and I live for
the prophecy is true