yo so how does it feel bro I feel like
Mike like my crotch is tingling but I'm
not sure
[Music]
oh my god you okay guys so by the time
you're watching this video tomorrow it
will be my birthday thanks Andy
it does fall on April Fool's Day pretty
much you got sums up my entire existence
so you guys know this yesterday in
celebration of a birthday we dropped
these brand new Maverick worldwide
hoodies and the t-shirt here and some
women's leggings but guys in celebration
of everything that's happening today
only t-shirts are gonna be five dollars
today five dollars you heard that
correctly y'all know where to get some
our slogan fall icon / shopper link in
description join the maverick movement
excited you're actually yeah it gets
worse you don't stand back there always
and step forward you are leaving me I'm
like no I'm not but yeah but you're
invited to go on the trip have fun at
your sanity okay
you and use me as clickbait bro no but I
bought the grapefruit
super juicy like that actually neighbor
Suzie brought me those some on do you
get your screw you Roger yeah whoa screw
you face
alright let me tell you what's going on
here from now on by the way I will be
addressed as Scout leader Logan's yeah
yeah we went to the store yesterday we
walked a couple of go cards I'm pretty
sure that's the ATV that's what I said
Spencer sorry Scout leader Logan that's
why Matt okay yes we need this to say
we're definitely to be Hawking it this
weekend I also feel like now's a good
time to say guys if you're not a part of
the Logan make sure to subscribe because
this this literally might be the most
interesting trip of my life colleagues
actually coming to hey he's never been
camping before look at him yeah yeah
brother think we're all excited but
according to my watching we are about
three hours late so we should probably
get going oh wow hey it's gonna be
crowded in here if you're a girl raise
your hand okay I think you two switch
that up mom you're not coming so go
ahead and put your hand down one two
good graduated math class okay and then
if you look out here $1,000 worth of
groceries looks like I'm not sure if
that's gonna hold this in the trip I'm
still working on the whole adult thing
and then Mack up front has been working
on a nice hood ornament for us brother
Jake Paul's face wearing the hottest
murse in the game was a good road for
sure he's gonna lead the way there with
his face I love you I'm gonna miss you
with your last chance you're not coming
all right well as of now the bus is full
so we will see you later all right guys
before we take off efficiently here are
the ground rules
I didn't say anything yet rule number
one again use the bathroom please do not
use the bus bathroom because it will
smell and you will regret it yeah - no
BUTT STUFF yes get later
and lastly rule number three first stop
and I realize this thing is a [ __ ] -
pork I'm not even kidding guys I've
never pulled a trailer in my life this
this trip is kind of a fingers crossed
operation my bag is sitting in the
middle of parking lot I'm moving that
literally all this stuff is just easy
accident this is actually there's a
method to my madness I have something I
want new there's water in Yosemite so we
knew we needed a kayak now the only
issue is getting it on top of the cool
bus alright one more step alright just
throw it to me okay Andy maybe help him
out
what perfect are you sure this is gonna
work no I'm not sure of anything on this
trip guys by the way you don't have any
plans literally I've never been to
Yosemite none of us have you'll have a
campground so we're just gonna kind of
wing it no service there so we're not
gonna have GPS or able to text people
and honestly I don't even know if these
vlogs are gonna be able to be uploaded
so I guess if you're watching this
that's a good sign we're still a lot hey
this looks pretty stable I'm thinking
because we're like five hours later so
we're gonna miss out of the daylight in
Yosemite you think we should definitely
hug it right here I didn't play this
dirt bike to not ride I don't care if
we're not Yosemite oh we can't hug it oh
we need to hit the road jack this is the
worst thing you could have done a to
pickle situation pickle in the front
yeah and a pickle and another ground a
pickle here in the back we just take the
wheel
there's no chance I can make this turn
over oh you gave me this time one more
time Oh move it that way
what
making progress hi
okay this was the last stop guys we just
needed some propane and they'll be off
to the races I like it we're gonna leave
at 11 o'clock and now it's 6:30 7:00
yeah yeah that's my plan for tonight
all right we got propane we got gas and
we are no longer stuck now who's ready
that's ours yeah we're working on it
what's the key here we go know the name
turn me up a little mo set traps I'm
alone you know you wank I'm a Manny yes
well you know I'm black to the pawn pick
a place to pick a date I'll go Goku
piccolo thought you was cool huh take
you out back
oh hey do me a favor you know it's good
I know is my birthday don't won't it she
don't won't it you know okay great only
four hours ago so Logan what's going on
here
shut up are you playing for tonight
right now what but you know you can play
by go literally we have a TV and if
there's cellphone service we have I find
you better give me those songs right
move get that loose yeah
why get that one I am having the shock
of a lifetime because five minutes ago
we can charge our phones and now we're
playing a game live on a bus on a
highway Hawking
players left
[Music]
yo yo ant ant and one second I'll pull
over right quick
yeah yo this is crazy oh stop what I'll
get a motion I'll get all emotional and
stuff what time what time is it right
look at the time bro oh no I almost made
it to 23 oh this is crazy Sister Sister
oh this is crazy so many years so many
years of fun life oh you you've hugged
it for 23 years right 23 years of
hucking yeah so how does it feel bro I
feel like my like my crotch is tingling
but I'm not sure
[Music]
[Applause]
23 it's America Oh
[Music]
feel so good no you're looking and
you're looking like quite the prince I
feel good bro yo yo this year be 22 it's
been the greatest year of my life like I
without getting like incredibly deep
blow gang man I love you guys so much
thank you for supporting me you guys
motivate me you fueled me every day to
create content for you guys a real talk
it means the world to me the fact that
you guys support not only myself but the
Maverick and the brand and this motion
that we started to not be afraid to be
yourselves to do it different my sleep
stand right here literally wearing my
heart on my sleeve Oh life is good but
we have a road trip to go on so
[Applause]
[Music]
hey how are you okay well we made it
kind of my lack of planning really
really this up although all the
campgrounds are full so we're kind of
Lehrer there's like a waterfall on
mountains right there but you can't see
him because it's too dark wait yes I can
oh my gosh come out here can you see it
I can see bro this is hella okay then
look at the bus right there it's not a
campground we're just like kind of gonna
[ __ ] camp parking lot go look at that
you know the best view in the game
that's Yosemite Falls okay so there's a
good chance the park rangers come and
kick us out of like you know 6:00 a.m.
it's 4:00 a.m. right now but hello gang
that is a vlog okay guys as usual thank
you guys for watching if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to
subscribe next couple days are gonna be
interesting so subscribe for me and ring
the bell next to the subscribe button so
a you can be notified when I post and be
joining the strongest family in YouTube
bro to make you stronger better faster
smarter sexy these are verifiable facts
also you guys know today is not only my
birthday but the one-year anniversary of
the Maverick brand we just dropped these
brand new hoodies these brand new
t-shirts oh and these brand new
performance from its but you know before
I get into that can we just look at the
inside of this puzzle
Jesus let me go home oh this is a
disaster
Evan Street kept passed out it was a
road trip for tonight for one night um
you guys comfortable okay yeah also guys
t-shirts today only I swear it's today
only you gotta pass on this fast you
know I love you it's Fan Appreciation
Day five dollars Jess maverick t-shirts
five dollars soap ounce while you can
yeah during the maverick movie Logan
Paul that console a shop or link in
description guys I am skiing exhausted
so I will see you a most likely bright
and early tomorrow morning low gang I
love you I'll see you tomorrow
[Applause]