do you know how to vlog how to vlog do
you know oh my god I have never felt as
sick as I do in my life I joked about it
yesterday but I feel like I'm dying my
voice is also gone it hurts to talk I
begged the question what am i a [ __ ] No
so I'm gonna deliver this daily vlog to
you just happy hey if I died doing so so
be so if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe guys all
jokes aside with a little strong family
on you - no one doesn't like us baby
despite my illness there are some good
things going on my man Bret Holliday it
was nice how was yours it was good
before I came in contact with tablets
okay here's another good thing that's
happening uh guys we're going to Tokyo
right now it's like Rolex o'clock 6:30
in the morning and we gotta go catch a
flight to Tokyo now let's check in the
cave hi buddy how you doing that's my
[Music]
little puppy smash kid yesterday no big
deal with popping how do you say goodbye
in Japanese I honestly don't know how I
got though uh I got those nice thank you
ah okay I'm just gonna say hello then
even though I'm saying goodbye gonna
need you up okay guys Brendan and I are
on our second Oh LAX Airport because
we've only been traveling lately I will
say oh my god this is bad we might need
somebody to talk for yo let's do that
well before we do that we did have an
incident on the way here to fight it we
go
each call dude care prevention right I
give it a car I'm like cuz we chased it
towards her house good job Logan swear
to God I pull this up real time I see
them sprint across the frame I'm a Kaku
stay away from konglish maybe he's
Japanese
oh hey you just caught me being cultural
as [ __ ] no coyotes gonna take over my
neighborhood on my watch more
importantly though we do have to find
someone to vlog from me since it's clear
that I'm gonna die oh my god no guy is
it calm it's that car but that's a good
idea
yo Armani it's an emergency I need you
to bring my passports in the airport the
good news is we can bond quality time I
think we should really use this time to
go find something to my channel though
if anybody's gonna if anybody's gonna
get my passport here in time it's gonna
be Armony are you running a red light I
need you to break the law to gate bro my
voice is so it
Oh gang it's a Christmas miracle
it looks like we're gonna make our
flight Tokyo that was a close one
what are you doing we're going to Jimmy
out yeah of course the same flight but
we wait oh my gosh wait I this is where
my blog well she might be the one
yup gosh we're here right now in love
you merch well hi I'm Barry and I'm
speechless I couldn't talk if you guys
follow me at Logan Paul
[Music]
what is this class 14 maverick don't
mind if I do I think you're right there
alright we're on the plane got all the
trucks we need figure I take all of that
by the time we land I should be okay
it's quit your science basic science
this is actually really miserable
besides a business class flight to Tokyo
but my voice is sad thank you thank you
what they couldn't eat you are is it
really interesting you can get the
hottest merch in the game at what Logan
Paul that comma slash shop go Japan is
crazy one two three okay it's cute and
she is let's find her I've always said I
want like a foreign wife Logan maybe I
found my future wife in Tokyo you'll be
sick though
what if I found my voice and talk it out
I locate we're about to take off I took
enough medicine to kill a horse but
luckily I'm not a horse but I'm hoping
it's gonna act as time travel you
literally want to close my eyes and just
wake up and tell me oh oh oh my god do I
feel better
absolutely not
I forgot another thing what I was saying
was if I'm gonna be sick Tokyo is a good
place to be sick second international
trip with you no clothes
that's my clothes this time I still
sound like I ate a meal of STD
tarantulas delicious yeah like spiders
covered in sexually transmitted diseases
but we're here in Tokyo we got a mob out
but we still to find someone to run my
vlog channel what you're a fan how much
of a fan enough to take over my channel
yeah you got to talk about your day we
just flew into Tokyo I barely slept I'm
tired it's my big day I found my section
look guys the quarantine
that's exactly where you belong right
now
you have any extra anymore thank you sir
it's my big day yeah Brendon I don't
have to go to quarantine no I don't have
to get sick from you it's good stuff all
right
look if you think I'm worried that the
airline forgot my bag you're wrong not
sick not sick so yeah hey I forgot my
bag it's just it's just not my day
hello gay Oh well I'm gonna be wearing
this outfit for the next like three days
oh we could get you swag down absolutely
oh wait what oh no vlogging not a lot of
filming they lost our bags I'm sick as a
dog but you know what hey life ain't
like yeah I'm talking to you you can hit
me in the face as many times as you want
but I'm was come back and hit hard plus
when I'm reppin maverick merch for the
next three days bro that's fine I'm cool
with that I look like a list box now I
still do want my bag cuz I would like to
change my underwear we should play a
game which country do you think my bag
is so it looks like the Sun is finally
coming through it was just a simple
mix-up someone took my bag somebody
thought they were loaded ball look it
happens I look like a lot of people
sometimes I think I'm looking Paul it
happens but um redeem up some backpack
it's a Christmas miracle
[Music]
the low gay yeah yeah respect I'll of my
low gang man you know we ride in style
yo that's a bus I know I was picking the
cars out and I was like huh I could be
softest Buster I could be a savage
[Music]
okay so let's talk travel
Logan why Tokyo so Logan when I did the
splits around the world like two years
ago who wanted to get Tokyo so I came
here literally just to do this place I
was here for like ten hours and like I
had to leave but it was the most amazing
city ever and I was so pissed that I had
to leave and I don't love spending New
Year's tea in Los Angeles I like to
travel cause it's the end of the year
and I actually have free time to go do
stuff so I figured why not come back to
Tokyo I do it the right way I just need
my voice to come back so I can scream
get the energy back in these vlogs
[Music]
beautiful good huh no but real talk we
still have to focus on the mission at
hand got to find someone to vlog for us
got it what's up G I brought me do you
know how to vlog yeah he knows how to
work you got it I plug your much you
know I'll do it for you Logan Paul
thought concise bear all right tell us
dope they gave me a bottle of vodka with
my name in the maverick I will say kids
don't drink if you drink you'll die
these are facts we're just gonna look at
the box we're just exactly one other
thing I want to point out there's just
like Tomatoes chillin yeah it's gonna
why did you know that was real that
easily could have been wax also you just
have to have faith how hard can this be
how to vlog do you know sweep do you
know how to dammit we're talking
everybody that you wanna YouTube channel
15 million subscribers 15 million
subscribers big deal low gang if you
want it you're pretty good-looking guy
no plug your March good good no that's
good and then tell me like and subscribe
know goes good that's good that's good
I'll okay this is harder than I thought
well what I forgot we have people coming
okay we didn't come to Tokyo alone oh my
god this is perfect there's someone else
coming that you guys know that you guys
love that can take over my youtube
channel my god I just remembered
[Music]
this whole day we've been looking for
someone to take over my vlog channel cuz
I can't talk do you sound miserable no
it's bad I need you to be the new Logan
ball came to Tokyo I knew the
possibilities here we thought you would
perfect to take over my blog guys you
know I do just want to do like to
finally tell them to subscribe the
fastest-growing families on the chin on
the YouTube and I got what Andy said
subscribe if you're not a part of the
low getting very important also top
yourself from the hottest party maverick
movement is real it's now in Tokyo
people shop I think in description ok I
love you I would see you tomorrow
hopefully my voice
[Music]
I like your scarf I just like the sky