[Music]
good morning
today is the day you guys i am starting
my movie
valley girl today this is the movie that
will transition me from internet star to
traditional hollywood actor it's a big
day dude i'm excited oh hi mom
oh hi
guys unfortunately we did have to put
him behind a gate as you guys know he's
a little tough to potty train
look yo puppy i don't want to do it
either this is the saddest thing of my
life it's just you're pooping on my
thousand dollar rugs that's all your
little sh
i know puppy it's like he's in prison
crime being the cutest little thing in
the world bad joke
that's my boy hi buddy hey
what what what
good morning baby how you doing
gotcha mom catch it i love this car guys
i really do but don't forget the lambo
and by soon i mean like four and a half
months hey mom
do you like my hair
yeah right okay listen valley girl told
me not to cut it because the first thing
i'm doing today is actually a hair test
thank goodness they're going to give me
like 80s here it's going to be shagged
welcome to my trailer
walk into my trailer i got my own
trailer and i'm just attract from ohio
her name is mickey yeah my character's
name is mickey my grandma go go
oh my god our grandma's name is mickey
welcome to my trailer ma
super spacious for ultimate smashing hey
oh
i got gifts i got hella good i got yes
yo these are from my agents at caa jack
paul and avi i love you guys thank you
they're the ones who got me the audition
for this movie i will let you down guys
i'm just i'm freaking excited
oh oh did you want something from my
mini fridge or perhaps we can cook
something in my
microwave or how about some music want
some music on my radio how about a tv
because we got that ma
we got that too early in the morning
and we got him oh
man i'm gonna cry back for my scene this
is awesome it's the script
in a hardcover book valley girl like
totally a musical
lp that's my initials ah i freaking love
you guys
all right what is in this yo i think
it's a car no i think it is a car
i don't think they would have got you a
car so quick oh
it's nick cage and a girl that looks
like you mom
this movie is actually a remake of the
1980s movie valley girl
and pretty soon i'll have my own valley
girl poster anyways here's a more logan
like question uh
oh my god what do you think ma i think
i'm hungry
you guys this whole thing is actually
food like from my sweet mother to that
trash can over there also i'm pretty
confident that like none of the crew or
like even the actors maybe
have seen like a crazy vlogger like me
running around like
aka vlogging aka that vlog so it's gonna
be an interesting adjustment getting all
these people used to
this and you guys the logan so guys this
is kim obviously
she's a beast are you happy now
kim it's your job to make me look sexy
and to make my hair look sexy yeah
yeah your hair not you yeah i gotta do
that myself
i trust you kim oh mickey you're so fat
you're so funny
i think you look so 80s really i i think
i'm worried about my giant forehead and
receding hairline that you gave me
because you gave me shitty jeans
i don't have a receding hairline that's
your dad i feel like i'm doing that a
lot this morning i'm just like i'm doing
with them
do they dab in the 80s no i'm gonna do
it anyway
all right guys i don't know what
happened but they decided to change my
hair you know how it is hollywood's
never got makeup on yo what do you think
now i love your hair yo i'm mickey bro
bro oh your mom stop mother i'm gonna
get naked and my penis is gonna be out
mom we can't be in here
yo this is i got like a head of hair bro
and i had a head of hair before this
this is something else bro
anyways today the first scene is prom
day and by prom day i mean prom night
this is my office sexy shoes they're
going to change into that start looking
like that oh what the how'd you get
in here mom what
wait wait before you answer that don't
move oh my god inception
boom here we go number one i gotta take
out the maverick socks bro the maverick
socks bro
my feet smell bad no
oh what logan what happened to your foot
oh that's it yeah i had a peeing in the
middle of night and i
kicked the door and the worst part was
that i did it on purpose because the
door was talking
nobody goes okay i don't know why you're
still in here mom it's getting weird but
here we go
i'm missed all right now here we go oh
that's still miss god bless it hey yo yo
guys this up is pimp son
i'm definitely starting to feel like
mickey uh at first with just the hair i
was like i don't know bro but now with
this whole outfit out i'm like
hell yeah headed to set in the passenger
van do i look like a kid you had a crush
on
in the 80s totally do i really because i
feel like mickey's a stud bro
you do i'm definitely out here i would
have i would have been on it
you would have been what on it i think
that's what i said
i think that is what you said with the
one okay guys this is the set for today
it's in a house mom this doesn't look
like a movie set doesn't
yeah welcome to hollywood bro so we have
to be quiet because they're shooting
right now it's a big movie a lot of
people as you can see a lot of moving
pieces
you don't have to kiss a girl do you
currently getting miked up guys they
changed my hair again look at look at
bro you know how it is hollywood and
stuff mom what's that
i think you look really good it looks
good yeah okay guys i am in the bathroom
i'm really nervous guys like it's my
first a big scene in my first big
hollywood movie
i just wanna i'm just yo i'm just
kidding y'all freaking out this is what
i was born to do bro i'm just i've never
been more prepared than right now
can i show you something before i do
this scene real quick it's kind of kind
of big news guys kind of big news what
is this uh
we're on the trending page on youtube
here what's on the top oh no
oh wait logan paul helped me help you
featuring why don't we yeah check it out
guys youtube trending page right on the
top there's your boys song pretty little
live star shane mitchell logan paul's
new music video is getting 2.2 million
views in 24 hours you know why
we are such a powerful family all jokes
aside not me and you because we're blood
related i'm talking about the low gang
like guys we
freaking rock looking for life fact mom
she knows
right where you wanted to be on top i
like that ma
always even when i'm smashing oh no i'm
just kidding never just
smash two hours later i'm still doing my
own voiceovers
so i shot my scenes it was dope you know
how we do bro and now it's lunch time
bro and yup big movies
big lunches check this out we got the
veggies we got the cutting board we got
the ribs sea bass fries
fist meat pasta foil mac and cheese
sausage beans corn rice
more rice corn bread passion fruit
smoothies do i even need to say how real
the smash is yeah i do and i will
i definitely should not be eating this
also i don't think i'm used to this hair
yet dude if you lived in the 80s and you
had this haircut um
why oh father forgive me for i have
sinned you guys
i ate so much
okay guys i am changing into my next
outfit this one's actually pretty cool
this one's actually
i'm just gonna show you hello
that's right baby your boy is a tennis
player let's go i'm also just realizing
mickey really likes white dude wait a
second wait one second here is mickey
racist no no no mickey is played by me
right
logan paul and i deem mickey not racist
so ergo mickey is not racist literally
just had an entire conversation about
racism by myself there was no one here
yeah my mom left and as you can see guys
it's a slow day on set
yo this is real life bro what do you
have dude
oh i got some delicious chocolate cake
here oh i can't do it but i love you how
about look at it this way bro
fruit with a little cake some fruit with
a little well when you say it like that
no locate don't
two of them guys they're devious bro oh
got one
must be nice bro must be nice hey oh yet
another outfit chain
i'm bringing polka dots back baby oh my
god i love this movie
trust me guys in the 80s mickey would
have been the kid that everyone was like
oh my god what is that they got them
everywhere what are these bro
i think this is a camera is this how
they vlogged back then
oh wow yo you wouldn't know this vlog
live bro
can't imagine i can do pearls with this
[ __ ] all right i'm gonna stop touching
the props cause they're not mine hey all
right guys your boy rap set good first
day kind of slow but solid and uh i just
i realized this this thing i got no no
vlog content today
so like so like this is where as as a
youtuber and actor i struggle because i
want to entertain you got the login
hey who are you just screaming at my
camera vlog life you wouldn't know that
vlogging so yeah guys i'm just i'm not
sure how to finish this vlog
but savages always have a solution which
is why i am outside of my brother's
house yeah when in doubt up jake
paul looks like i'm going through the
back like we did the other day
that's what she said yo i feel like such
a creeper but yo this is content bro
i see my dad i see my mama see girls but
no jake paul where is jake paul
surprise
how about you me mickey dude i like
myself in the back door did you see in
my vlog
so fun you
okay i stopped but they're still going
it's a song of their generation they
love it
where is jake paul he is shooting a
prank
blog right now on what i need i need
some content i need something okay
is jake not here is he not here but he's
coming back
go you have an idea i want to take you
on playing basketball
[Music]
guys i think we have a plan for some
content okay this was erica's idea and i
really like this idea
you work for jake yes but lately what's
the situation
lately you know i've just been stressed
out why tell me why because he's in
charge
well no not just living with all the
boys like doing too much
not being very appreciative not not
being appreciated like the young
intelligent respectful woman that you
are you're the mom
yeah and your daughter being
unappreciated okay exactly
i know that yo and over here at maverick
media we respect women we appreciate
them so here's the plan when jake comes
home you guys tell him that i left okay
but you erica you tell jake that you've
changed your mind and you're coming to
work for me okay and i'll just be like
i'll be hiding in like a cupboard or
something is this going to be believable
like i think so because you've been like
kind of sour lately not sorry i just
like normally me and jake talk about
everything everything yo did you notice
your mom always talks when i'm clearly
pointing the camera g like you it's okay
you guys know why you know
these two right here man you're all
when jake gets here take him into like
his office or something yeah and i'll
just be in there like post it up hiding
in the box or something
here we go
he's here he's here
this isn't working at all just do it
anyways just do it on my
guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
yo yo back up back up back up look what
he did to my yeezy
that's the break back to break
yo it was gonna be so easy bro it was
gonna be such a chill
chill prank but then now i got you on
camera saying this is the second pair of
shoes you bring
bro but it's the first pair of brother
that i've won
doesn't make any sense mom can you clean
my shoes yeah my mama
i messed up jake shoes i feel bad i will
i'll clean them all right that was
we're reckless i'm pretty sure you
knocked that camera over and i got it on
camera bro i have expensive cameras
you have 4 million cameras 4.5 million
because
and guess what they're savages they
ain't jake paulers
can i be honest with you yeah be honest
i came over here because i got no
content bro
yeah you're on set all day how do you do
it bro
he's got a team he rolls squad what's
the name of the team
team 10 sucks no it's hard 12-hour day
on set
and it's dark outside and i don't have
people bro all i have is
a pomeranian at congress savage on
instagram
god is that what we should talk about
guys i have a confession to make
guys anthony did come up
with the name yes
he did he did guys yo but i have an
explanation i told him i got a dog they
made fun of him said he was a little
[ __ ] dog
kind of true i want to name him like
zilla or like spartacus and
anthony suggested like kong i was going
through instagram names i kept changing
him and changing him and it
stuck on calling the savage wouldn't let
me change it anymore so i was like i
gotta name it congratulations now it's
great so it's like it's kind of you know
that's dope
it is fake that's how life works but
that's why i got kong in the first place
what am i still doing in this
corner
yo yo you know what's dope they don't
know what we're about to do
oh they have no idea bro you guys got to
keep on watching
it's about to happen we cut and then we
talked about some next level redo next
yo i need a thumbnail caught my brother
picking his nose
no that won't get that many views oh yo
easy is that a giant rat trap no way
he's gonna do it nobody's gonna do a rat
trap
oh what though yo is he insane no he's
dope
i'll do it hold it hold it hold it hold
it
okay why didn't it hit that hard on you
i'm a beast bro
yo i'm leaving i'm leaving here's here's
the thing bro here's the thing i think
i'm gonna change it and just be like i'm
gonna change my channel like jay paul is
still
exposed like anger problems and you'll
get like
good views right yeah yeah i like this
joke right
all right heck yeah yeah wait but we're
still gonna do something dope no we are
still gonna do some dope it's just not
gonna
happen yet all right guys after a long
day i am home i took my mom from jake's
house because that place is crazy right
right crazy i missed my boy kong though
where's my boy melody but more
importantly no offense god
hi dog hi puppy did you miss me did you
make me
oh i love you the joys of being a dad
when you don't have to take care of him
he doesn't poop on anything
hello god bless america that is the vlog
i don't know what that was today guys
fun day cute day thankful for my real
life teddy bear and the big thing that
jake and i were talking about
uh wait i'm actually gonna save for
tomorrow's vlog
which by the way i'm flying on a private
jet to go to the billboard awards to
present an award on sunday that's right
your boys going on tv presenting awards
and oh
yeah and i'm on the private jet with the
white dopey boys yeah
anyways guys if you were not a part of
the logang do not forget to subscribe
and i will see y'all tomorrow
take it easy
[Music]
stupid
spend