warning the following vlog features
stunts performed by experienced
professionals do not attempt to recreate
or reenact any stunt or activity
performed on this show because the level
was here and I'm taking it like here I
think the problem is because like I
don't know how to remove the nail polish
guys like I've been taking showers
colored toenails stop touching something
you put on right there to remove the
nail polish you got to be some form of
like a mechanism there's gotta be some
move there's literally such a thing it's
called a nail polish and over nail
polish remover
everything about that that me - hey yo
good morning locaters day if you're not
a part of the logo make sure to
subscribe we're live yes sometimes paint
our toenails yeah life's good so smash
the subscribe button for me to win the
strongest family and most family on
YouTube
these are verifiable facts oh my god
today's vlog is gonna be so late bro you
guys know yesterday I dropped the cool
bus off to Jake's today we were making
history by jumping over it on a BMX bike
but first guys I figured we'd send a
quick Huck at the house here first
Andy wisely spent his money on this
giant gumdrop inflatable towel here
purchase I make oh my god Andy Romy such
a good time really truly exhilarating
come help come help Andy Romy oh this is
actually amazing I have an idea
here we go one two three
all right yo we're gonna go jump the
cool bus now huh I love how you just say
that casually this is the sketchiest
thing I've ever seen in my life oh my
god bro yeah as you guys know this is
Ryan the English BMX bike rider who
apparently doesn't sign waivers how you
doing bro good good today I am gonna
need you to sign that waiver I'm gonna
be going in today I did I brought it
he's actually got one we're official
today this is in case you break your
neck or if anything else happens to this
is saying that Jake Paul and Logan poles
are not liable for Ryan Tanner's life
mom Oh
[Music]
honestly this is the dumbest thing I've
ever seen in my life yeah it's not even
a ramp it just go straight up oh did he
sign the waivers that was in the process
right how are we doing on that right we
don't have a pen either out of this
house no hot seventeen hours no pen I'm
just gonna make sure this is certified
yeah that's good
oh good all right yes oh speaking of
chapstick do you have the nail polish
remover it doesn't even make sense my
vlogs tend to not do that advanced nail
polish remover the exact mechanism
mechanism check it out ma painted my
toes I put a bunny on him
who did that she was an interesting
woman no way this works bro oh my god oh
this is amazing no believe me not so
why did you guys pick green and orange
my game room theme is orange color no
I'm a gamer now I'm not what are you
talking about you know for tonight is
I'm a gamer ma I'm gonna streaming on
Twitch at Logan Paul was taken oh you're
gonna get addicted like you did with
World War that's right already addicted
I tried to pull them off the other day
we're playing last night together
they're taking everyone to duo's 0 0
that means Miriam no ID because you're
not a foreigner loser
that's that Roman engineering structure
on the bottom there yeah you know
actually though I'm seeing something I
have a vision involving the raspberry I
know you're busy can I get that yeah
[Music]
oh yeah why'd you do that I trained them
to just advertise deposit box we're
gonna get to the bottom of this these
guys have been building this all day
safety-wise what are we talk about here
is it good is it ready to go oh yeah
totally
I sent my mother over this he'd send his
mother over it so I was wondering maybe
you do the jump later maybe I'll hook it
I feel like normally I'm the one doing
dumb things but you definitely trump me
today but I still want to do something
dumb I mean the jump over yeah yeah yeah
I got you bro let's do this a 60 percent
chance that it 100% works
all right tonight too easy I think
there's only one thing left to do the
official hug we got to get the dead bug
started
I'll start the dirt bike rack me if I'm
wrong he's gonna pull you from over
there
so Ryan's gonna get launched up and over
and hopefully land in this area
wait are you gonna gonna flip we just
jump it depends if the low gangs
subscribe to my channel as well mommy
boy she will push you to stay in the
house don't open your mouth we live in
the swamps like be in a sub Township
[Music]
don't try
Oh oh my god I wasn't even looking bro I
was purely focused on the thumbnail like
and subscribe Dogen Paul blog yeah go
ahead and plug it you earned it link in
description below and okay low gang that
is the vlog thank you guys for watching
yet another epic day guys if you're not
a part of the low gang make sure to
subscribe smack the button in the phrase
backflip over pocket and ruin the family
on sir do not get do yourself a favor
cop yourself some of that hot is merch
in the game that maverick lurks but
every single day we're out here being
ourselves every single day where I were
doing a different I encourage you to be
yourself I encourage you to feel
comfortable in your own skin that's what
makes you special that's what makes you
you it's dope all cop / shop or a link
in description low gay I love you I'll
see you tomorrow
don't try