oh yeah boy just jump the Lamborghini it
is gonna get much more epic later guys
we got the neon Lamborghini we got the
neon maverick woody what's up good
morning okay was laughing look I don't
know how else to say this if you're not
a part of the low gang you suck but the
good news is you can unstuck bye
subscribe subscribe button in the face
and join the Strongs family on YouTube
guys we're Mavericks we change the world
every day we do it different no one does
it like us that's the revolution if you
haven't kept your money looking back on
fleshed out so how to stop this merch in
the game now I know what you're thinking
doggie dogs why do you have a
Lamborghini what's going on cuz I'm a
[ __ ] boss just getting it this is my
Lamborghini how you doing bro man so I
just have a question hi you got a
Lamborghini my name is Parker I run a
YouTube channel called vehicle vergence
all about cars and I bought myself a
Lamborghini by doing YouTube by doing
YouTube man sorry guys I'm just getting
worked up it's just a crazy world we
live in you got young dumb blind choices
by spending money on stupid [ __ ] like
busses painting it blue it's an
interesting life I feel like next life
I'm gonna come back as like a squirrel
just as like payback like alright look
so anyways one Lambo it's cool what am i
poor to Lambos is better this one's mine
just kidding it is maybe I am poor in my
soul this is the most pretentious vlog
I've ever made I'm so sorry if you're
new to this I'm not normally like but I
don't think they're as cool as the mini
Yeti oh my god
Park next to the big Yeti oh my God look
a lot of vehicles today when we drive
around we're definitely gonna be the
biggest douche bags on the road it's
gonna be sick but as you guys know a lot
happens in this house it's like a
machine like everything's always moving
yesterday I surprised my roommate Evan
this was not in the vlog but I think he
liked to gif I got
you look good six right I think it's
life-sized bro yeah always knew my major
salaries look these are dope but I still
think it's not better than this just me
and my boy doing God touching barriers
and stuff I even have to blur my penis
in this painting this is amazing hey
shut the front door
all jokes aside guys oh this was from a
company called no Billa Fida so you can
thank them I will say when I met the
make-a-wish kids they told me they
missed the playwriting so we got
someplace yes they did
give me that plate earring girl good
stuff good stuff and now good stuff my
dad is quite the handyman guys he's from
Ohio so he's building me some stuff so
as of now you can see through the holes
in the fence but not anymore thanks to
Greg Paul cut the size custom you got a
peephole right here I'm gonna put a
little slide over it you can stick your
penis third if I get hit that we're
literally putting this through here so
when people drive by they have nothing
to see so we're filling all these holes
I don't like being like watched like
people just stand here or watch even
wears running around naked which I've
done both or even worse me run around
naked like it happens these things
happen I've seen it I've seen it I can't
trust me so this is necessary on this
fence - no one's seeing through on this
fence - no would see you 3:8 yeah check
it I'm proud of you dad and also I
what's what's on your forehead oh well
you get hit by a nail nice oh Jesus
I just I don't know game coming comment
comment orange if you think I should get
a lamp comment green if you think he
should get me one comment and they
anyways guys I'm doing a lot of work to
this house I've already done it but we
put the pot in the koi pond cuz I want
to make like literally I'm crafting this
to be just like my perfect paradise
quick side note it's incredible that I'm
able to do this I owe this to you guys
so absolute thank you but I'm putting a
path in the backyard cuz there was a
rock path I didn't really I can't put in
a new whoo it looks good this is like
Japanese wood style oh my gosh Robert do
you burner the koi or something else
that makes me happy that happened
earlier guys my neighbor Susie's
neighbor Suzie Susie's not the best in
Instagram but we're gonna make her the
best at Instagram we got this so general
I like your head is literally just like
so much information to process and then
you can tag me at Logan Paul only an
Instagram there's me I'm the one with
the blue check next to me I'm verified
cuz I heard that some people are faking
my name already oh for sure you're
famous
you're the hot commodity let's do a
caption like by your mercy we're gonna
get neighbor Susie by your merch check
guys it's that time we are gonna drive
the vehicles on the road but it's okay
because the one person saving us is
gonna be driving the cinquecento so like
yeah we got Lambos but like this is like
a passenger car it's like the Godfather
of the Lamborghini don't think so
all right yeah see
Oh yo I act like this is the coolest
situation I've ever been in when it
comes to vehicles who Lambos the matte
black you look so good on me I'd to
match the birdie okay I'm done being a
car geek it's now time for me to jump to
Lambos why look when I was younger I saw
Kobe jump a vehicle and even me I jumped
over cars before four fine but I've
never chucked a Lambo and I've also
never jumped to Lambo I think I have to
do it guys I think I'm the Maverick I do
things no one else is doing so here is
Logan Paul's attempt to jump do lever
against the Lamborghinis are getting in
position Yash I tie my shoes yeah
probably
if I die or sustain any bodily injuries
and I have your youtube you can have my
youtube right Brenda North you got it
alright look a lot of energy right now
but I think there's only one way to make
this a proper vlog you gotta jump the
Yeti bro it's 8 feet tall huh
it's 8 feet tall nice observation
Sherlock I'm a maverick that 8 feet tall
yeah all right how about to do something
really stupid thank you this is great if
I die in front of some little gangsters
Joe goodbye Eddie no I met that kid
today I literally met him today the kid
driving yeah
do you trust him I don't know
No what are you doing jumping so I went
under it hey thanks guys
I'm still alive wow that was stupid I
was like 20 feet away from it I was like
oh I can't I'll just throw away my crazy
in a weird way you've earned my trust
yo you know what I just realized
if this is what I think it is we
definitely should have used this Oh oh
my god yeah yeah yeah oh it's so many
many Yeti oh my gosh identical broom
broom mother it would have been so much
easier to jump this you do it now
where's your beard in the toilet in the
drain no he actually gave me the
physical description where it is okay
can you do me a favor and push this I
got to do epic you didn't even jump in
okay that is the vlog I feel like
eventually I could work up to jumping
this so actually I
if you know the part of the little gang
make sure to subscribe for the story
family and you do we jump over Lambos we
duck under Yeti what don't we do bro
that matters in front the maverick
spirit the hottest soft is immersed in
the game if you have not yet cop
yourself some while you still can't look
up all calm slash up some like hotcakes
another fun day low gang genuinely I
love you I'll see you guys
yeah if we come
Hey
I dunno what