okay 16 hours later in the maverick has
landed it Dubai oh you guys anyways yeah
I turn to thee so this is the $21,000
seats first class on Emery and that
turned the shower yeah you can shower on
the plane that's the best thing they
turned it into a merge class mile-high
club
[Music]
like that very much to be honest I'm
surprised I'm still on the plane like I
said yesterday guys if you were not able
to make it to the world's first first
class you can get to merch on local ball
Nikon slash any love Logan any Logan
governor the meet-and-greet I think she
would I think I can't read Arabic but I
know that says welcome to Dubai let's go
okay so guys literally I have no idea
what to expect I've never been to Dubai
it's gonna be interesting with vlogging
because the times are off this is 12
hours ahead of Los Angeles so like I
don't know if the vlog starts at night
and then goes throughout the day or like
what's gonna happen but your boy hasn't
missed an upload in 400 days honey no
[Music]
honey honey honey yes honey
what oh this is not for this is all the
prisons the wrong car so we have to get
out we have to get back out to the
Sharks let's go
[Music]
I'm alive
[Applause]
oh my god yo one way to start bro that's
it one way to enter Dubai you can tell
just how tall this building is guys this
is the Burj Khalifa this is a guy this
is a guy the one who set this up in the
past year yo so he's saying is when they
asked me what I bring to the table
I bring the damn table and I was wrong I
was just I was just testing to see who's
gonna bring the table my mans bringing
the table in the most luxurious
luxurious hotel planet if you look
really good put this in the next Star
Wars literally just make this the
spaceship that's your boy on the cover
of Arabian business the Maverick let me
read this Eliezer you can hear mm-hmm
why logan paul is set to become the
world's first social media billionaire
enough said
oh so far in the ten minutes we've been
here we've done Dubai right this is what
I mean guys cuz it's nighttime so we're
gonna go to dinner and then like this
isn't a complete loss then I'm gonna
wake up tomorrow and what am I gonna
vlog what are we gonna upload questions
I don't know the answer to but I think
it's time to rock this is my guy sagen
I'm doing well welcome to Dubai that's
how we do all our we do in the bathroom
can I just can we just dab okay this is
his rolls I you know we do in Dubai this
is always say welcome to the below it's
been a good first what like two hours
yeah yeah I like this let's stop it look
at the ceiling there's stars on the
ceiling first thoughts of Dubai okay the
city is very extravagant but luxurious
everything is grand big you sort of like
me I like to consider myself very extra
like guac like guac bro it's just so
extra so staying in the tallest tower in
the world driving in a Rolls Royce these
are all things I like I'm very fortunate
man but we have a while here the night
is just beginning I thought we going to
a club right now huh you know what
happened last night we went to the club
bro heavily what happened you fell
asleep
I was tired bro
16 hours late what am i doing bro would
do plies through by stuff look at the
view outside backflip oh honey we're
staying in the tallest building in the
city like world in the world yeah sorry
let's go get the day started do it and
it's weird that we're like halfway
through a vlog and I'm like saying ayo
good morning a gang was robbed and a
twice so let's go let's go pretty good
smallish [ __ ] bro
oh I gotta say guys this is the first
time I've worked out 76 stories in the
air you can't get here resident true so
he lives in this building
look at you yo what
[Music]
can we come the hatch oh no this is a
cool experience
bro look around us oh and look up like
this is crazy can't even see the top how
do you see the top the old I realize
where these the Maverick bottoms kind of
function as swim shorts - what don't we
do Sagat what don't I do bro I'm still
sleeping man we have a lot of fun stuff
agenda as you can tell by the title of
this video what why don't you fight a
lion you can do that here I can fight a
lion you with the right people
okay go tell me this road cuz I'll fight
oh I will wrestle a liger i wrestled a
bear it's clear i wrestle the crocodile
anything happens to him it's not awful
it's like or smoke give me a lie saw
last night if i'm gonna wrestle a liger
your boys gonna arrive in style its
totals again is it rolls the next
purchase like I'm considering it I want
another vehicle I just don't know what
to get you know if you buy a rolls
yeah you need a driver you don't know
your own roll you want to be my driver
or do you want to have a videographer
I'm gonna stick with this thing this is
my okay yeah you're right so we'll need
the rolls and a driver
yeah here we come
we come
we come oh snap the squad is lip broke
and we roll in hard okay so if anyone
could just point me in the direction of
the animal that's gonna kill me just
that'd be great okay so I don't think
the zebra is gonna kill me but I
appreciate the zebra biting the medal
instead of my arm
thanks mr. zebra oh dude he's more
trained than Kong whoever trained the
zebra could you train my dog yo how much
this is the giraffe room it's like a
bedroom but with your ass also I know
giraffes have like really long tongues
I'm trying to see if I get like yo you
see the giraffe it's a big thing with
the long neck you guys see it yo y'all
see the ostrich bro
no no joke I know for a fact ostriches
are they're legal in California can we
get ostrich come on brother
this guy I'm just saying these could be
the move I want you bro oh yeah look at
it look at it I want a head like that
this is it bro
this is it bro I'm going for the tongue
[Music]
I just kisses the giraffe bro to all my
side chicks and my main chicks
he's the better kisser than all of you
let's talk like this is dangerous
anything okay oh I make eye contact with
Lydia oh these ones I'm pretty tough oh
wow eat this jump stick but now my
fingers make your fingers high five does
he just inhale the bones as well how
many humans right here I'm sorry I'm
sorry my brother after I released the
follow Jake Paul that's the noise you
make I don't think this guy will kill me
I could be wrong I've seen him bro no I
know this guy he's famous on YouTube
yeah um what did he do oh he screamed
Alan love your work bro real big fan I
think I think this is it
this is a reinforcement we're going to
give to them so the reinforcement is
milk good look yeah I wrestled in high
school I placed fifth in the state of
Ohio oh yeah and so we got ourselves a
match oh wow a little bigger than I
expected
you know you know this is legit cuz the
Gucci rings coming off the bracelets are
coming off my whole mentality here if
you die you die I'm gonna change it so
in rocky for Yvonne Drago said if he
dies he dies I'm gonna change too
if you die Dubai good dog Logan I didn't
sign up for this you grabbed my leg life
insurance for Brendan hey good job good
job being a lion hey buddy it's your big
day
hey buddy hey take it easy oh come on
there's only one hero
[Applause]
no I was just getting started
take him down get two points I don't
know how this is possible this is we
haven't been to the main zoo yet
apparently this is the main put
underground you already died oh snap
this is actually a zoo oh there's more
white tigers more oh you're supposed to
be out there running amok white tiger yo
I'm putting a koi pond in my house I
feel like we need a zoo is there monkey
there how much for the monkey he's not
saying if you like the monkey kiss me
[Music]
yo no joke like super single but I think
I love your monkey bro well no wonder
you know I could sell me this monkey
she's amazing so we have the doorman 4
million seriously yeah I'm not joking yo
that's actually the coolest thing ever
bingo I know that's crazy no the baby
tiger she's so cute
yo they named this tiger Logan you're
gonna do great things one day Logan
you're gonna dent the universe you're
gonna take over the internet and you're
gonna conquer the world maybe one day
you'll be President probably not but
it's a good day Tigers named after me
monkeys kissing me my man money kisses
thank you for having me at the farm
anytime I've gotten a lot of material
gifts and and things that you buy with
money but the tiger being named after me
is something you cannot buy this next
scene when you come back yo this Tigers
gonna be huge
and maybe I'll wrestle her and she'll
kill me Logan versus local okay that is
the vlog divides just getting started
guys we've been here less than 12 hours
if you're not a part of the Logan make
sure to subscribe if you have not kept
your members make sure to do so Logan
Paul calm /sha Patrick's changing your
world getting Tigers name that has me
never money can't do buy speakers long
long we are here Logan I love you I'll
see you tomorrow
I'm that much
oh man my pride
yo what up G you ever arrested one of
the loggers he don't talk much