I'd already won I like my women
[Music]
[Applause]
hey guys doing I hope you're drinking
water we are as you can see here I took
three gallons a day stay hydrated it's a
weird one today but that's not important
guys hi my name is Logan yes for
whatever reason you're not a part of the
locate punch the subscribe button effect
enjoy the Strongs family on YouTube my
job is to entertain you distract you
from your busy day I know how it is we
all got just going on but maybe I can
make you laugh make it smile if you saw
yesterday's vlog guys it was Valentine's
Day right and I had a date it went
pretty well we shared lots of laughs and
smiles until her ex-boyfriend showed up
which was interesting but then I found
out he follow me on Instagram so it
should at Logan Paul if you want to do
that mom you got it thanks it's from dad
he says can you shut Kong up what's that
spot is that my mom is getting blind
brushes agents my mom's old I think so
her vision is increasing yeah 40 it's
hitting you soon your eyesight gets
worse guys Kong as you know is not much
going on in here what are you doing gone
what he's like a wild lion you think
it's a bird I think she did wait why I
got lemon I mean if you're butchering
the English language mom look it's a
lemons lemons make lemonade no we should
definitely eat one of these lemons we
should make lemonade we should what we
doing my mom just said oh we are getting
distracted you crazy dog what are you
chasing what do you
I swear to god this dog has a mind of
its own today the happier he is the
longer his tongue hangs out it's how you
tell how happy is bro there's nothing
going on in his brain
absolutely zero it's transferring to me
now I'm saying issue so we can shut Kong
up but more importantly do using this
lemonade when life gives lemons you make
lemonade wow this is gonna be yummy
skiing it all be a maverick it's so tart
it's too tart for me Logan I'm gonna eat
my acai bowls I think it's time I tell
you some pertinent information as well I
have news guys
I'm going vegan what did you just say
what turn the camera this is the camera
on this good good not ugly
editor don't put this part in I been
think about it alright know a lot of
people that are vegan say they're
feeling better you know what that's cuz
you're not from Ojai I mean I wait too
long oh but no matter what I love you
really even Kong maybe the issue with
young dougie if she doesn't have a
girlfriend right he had one for a minute
it is crazy cuz we you guys know we made
him a smash pad don't try to change the
subject
what's this be it done okay no it's done
no I mean my soluble I'm blogging on
there's the middle oh yeah but don't be
a big thanks could make you [ __ ] Jesus
car it has his own little pad we even
got a picture of him and his girlfriend
back then but I don't know where she
went
so we got to get him a new girl
right young Gogi okay and I think I have
a little something in mind so guys today
we are doing a photo shoot actually for
our new maverick merch we got the blue
joggers to do a different shirts all the
good stuff the hottest merch in the game
for the ladies you guys know yesterday
we dropped the boyfriend pants and the
staple hoodie in both pink and black
Logan Paul cops last job no one's doing
it but the point is one of the girls one
of the models coming over her name is
Olga Olga send me a picture she has a
dog a white version of Kong looks like
this right she's a little cutie just
sitting in the cage and I'm like yo
clearly my boys why not get him another
new and improved girlfriend so while we
wait for her something fun I want to do
you guys know when I say we're the
strongest family on YouTube that's not a
joke we have the absolute best support
system in the world and I'm holding in
my hand some fan mail so open the letter
right and oh what the heck money $20 in
fans okay so I gotta read the letter
right dear Logan Paul my name is Haley
and I'm 14 years old I live in
California
and I love you so much like actually so
I've heard that YouTube and Google is
cutting you from all this so I have a
close $20.00 I know it's not much but
I'm 14 and don't have a job so my cash
flow isn't the best okay first off Halle
thank you but uh guys can't send me
money stop sending me money but I
appreciate it get out of that mud get
out of that mud Kong Dougie have a date
tonight oh god there's money bigger
problem those are Toyota Tacoma tacos
[ __ ] he's gonna have to call you back
we're gonna give you one opportunity to
come clean yeah no matter how many $20
bills the logging sends me it's not
gonna fix what you've done to my grass
you know who did this I know well I
think we start off by giving me an
apology I'm sorry dad I'm paying you
this $20 that is definitely mine thank
you accept it in with this money I'm
gonna donate it to a good cause
Wow so regal everyone just calm down for
one second there's more fan-out I want
to show you before Olga gets you with
your sexy pom pom pictures based off a
real picture that we took in real life
really tough now leave it leave it
I'm not ashamed that I can't speak leave
it so here's the picture as you can see
it just costs the squad and our mavar
March looking sexy and this photo got
recreated digitally and it looks like
this and I know what you're thinking our
first glance it's like okay whatever
no now whatever let's zoom in let's top
it Mike first up doing them Wow well
they do your face and let's move over to
me Ozzy
I feel like this no I feel like this
one's accurate it's no wise weight cogs
actually good clogs good car looks regal
here and then my favorite the Lydia and
like that thank you for drawing that for
us we appreciate that effort well next
time try to make you some potato booth
come on Olga there's a path on my lawn
if you want to just run it over Oh God
oh you know using what that lawn is
ruined
Coco oh my guinea pig do you think it's
a problem that Coco is three times as
small as young doggies yeah she might
not be smarter than cuz I'm not smarter
than cob okay we're gonna introduce Coco
to the bachelor graphic content we've
blurred our dog's this type of thing
this just in from the legal team due to
the graphic nature of this dog friendly
event the following scenes 40-tooth and
47 have been blurred from today's vlog
in an ongoing effort to ensure that
content is suitable for people of all
ages and species and species I feel I
feel like the size thing is really gonna
mess things up size doesn't matter
oh okay yeah okay yo I think the other
models are here problem look up in the
sky tell me if you see the Sun no Sun
day the sun's gone glow in the dark I
probably not look the point I don't know
how much we're gonna be able to shoot
[Music]
his name is king if his name is king
boom oh my god oh my this is a boy or a
girl
that's a boy oh my gosh we have two
white Pomeranians here Oh
[Applause]
this is crazy
so many legs in so many dogs
this is a disaster
oh Jesus Christ what's going on dogs
what's happening no this is a disaster
Oh what's better than one barking
Pomeranian blue barking Pomeranian
no you guys need to shut up yo this
looks so just God Hey all right guys
we're gonna cut to a montage enjoy all
the new products by the one and only
maverick apologize it's a car for her
sweet 16 no spends a second dollar bills
on a limousine that one the girl who
takes a bus in you is Becky T's rocking
Nike is what the hell no but II don't
want no fake tits Oscar that's funny
don't work up until you drop on the town
stronger than a father someone new I
left for trying to fit in the crowd
right before you change to the Pink's
you have a boyfriend then how are you
wearing the boyfriend I'm just kidding
though the best part guys is you don't
even need to have a boyfriend
to wear the boyfriend pants no the idea
is that like you like I've stolen from
my boyfriend and like now you have it's
a dumb joke anyways guys during the
little montage there there's a part
where I step behind Olga you could see
me there looking flawless and whatnot
also looking creepy as well I'll do
anything
[Music]
take the money don't spend it and I said
and we
[Music]
selfies wanna make up free don't wanna
mean go lady in pink prom queen I wanna
go to clubs trees always said on a Jean
Haddadi toda how to fix cars maybe she
could fix me buying and wearing maverick
by Logan Paul will in no way guarantee
or assure that you will get to hang out
with models oh oh we definitely did say
that probably will happen not gonna let
a lot of pretty girls here right oh we
can't guarantee it's gonna happen
yo when I say who's doing it who is
doing it
[Music]
it's the hottest in the game guys we've
had so much fun all day you guys know
where to get it Logan Paul that concise
shop join the movement propia maverick
that's what it's about it's about being
different it's about doing it different
and just straight up all around kicking
life's ass now if you look behind mr.
Brendan here there's a weird little love
triangle going on here
and my humble opinion there's only
really one way to figure this out I
think we just have to shove them all in
Kong smash pad and see what happens oh
if you're ever trying
[Music]
Coco escaped this is crazy yo so this
only means one thing
it's the boys okay hello gang that is
the vlog if you another part of the
Logan make sure to subscribe smash the
button hit it in the faith kick it in
the mouth enjoying the Strongs family Oh
factual cop Dodd is working the game
Logan Paul guys last shop y'all know
where to get it looking I love you and I
would
[Music]
don't worry
no I don't want
yeah yeah oh the numbers dog see it's
gonna be important so calico girl