oh I already know what you're looking at
bro you look at the bad should I give
her that no yeah for sure no free call
Evan
[Applause]
[Music]
good morning that's an Ohio wake up bro
problems when it starts melting yeah
didn't think that far ahead boy oh it's
okay
the snow is cold but it's hitting the
hardest shot this merch in the game yeah
guys I'm in Ohio I flew to Ohio for the
holidays man slit as usual again
California Ohio Guatemala doesn't matter
where we all suck you're not a part of
the low gang you could hit the subscribe
button for me smack it and join the
strongest family on YouTube it's tough
because my brother's like the second big
as you do right now and it's like if I
say it too loud he'll get angry oh hi oh
you eat chips for breakfast can you
prove us you love us by making us walk
Oh
respect young doggy you've never seen
real snow
oh no sure we showed us know one time
when we made snow in California but he's
a Hollywood a spoiled dog like look at
how delicately he eats this burrito are
you good there's supposed to be a dog
that's supposed to be gone by now so I
think we go show young dog eat some snow
oh this is not gonna lie guys this is
exciting for me too like I actually love
snow look oh he's like what that like I
woke up groggy I haven't been sleeping
much and then I look out the window and
it's snowing but without further ado be
free young what do you think huh no what
are you doing don't run away god damn it
be snow doggy
that's a good boy yeah okay look at him
go yo this is the happiest Oh what did
you just do
hold on sorted me what do you do this is
my sword I I grew up with this Oh
looking just you guys know there is a
difference between a prank and murder so
just be careful like how you're pranking
people look Kong a weapon of death so
young dogie growing up in Ohio a general
rule we follow don't eat the yellow snow
you can do it because you're a dog but
in general just not the moves little
booties so wack also my mom is filming
Brendon I miss you bro if you notice I'm
selfie vlogging again look it's dope it
takes me back to the days of vlogging
selfie style something else I thought of
that's kind of crazy this is the first
time I've worn the Maverick merch like
out in actual cold snow yo and I say
it's warm and I say it's off but
actually seeing how
it isn't real life yo man the Maverick
movement is real Santa by the way you
better come through for a lot of people
out there wanting maverick merch man I
hope the diss track work but if he
doesn't I got you anyways I'm falling in
love more with my dog Kong independent
dog he walks himself he don't need no
man to get him along it's good to see
you little bro you come here often my
dreams are coming true you're the last
person that made me one day
rest in peace nd also here's something
some of the neighborhood kids stopped by
hey guys okay I see a young savage I see
a maverick what the are you doing Pauli
was your much Oh Jake what do you call
Paulie why you've done my carpet what
that one right there
while we were watching ooh he's like me
he likes Nadia's Kong's poop shot out
like a rocket you know I know why he's
got stuff to do my dog's efficient so
it's like get it out quick and back to
the day I'm just curious look isn't it
just weird cuz I'm still in my boxers
that's what I'm saying ain't nobody got
top of Pam you have the fluffiest hair
ever oh my god you know this is not
about there's things in there I'm afraid
what what are you doing yo this is crazy
respect thanks for your hair awfully
mm-hmm
so the craziest part about being here is
the lack of plans I'm so used to just
doing stuff in here it's like we can do
whatever we want
oh I think I'm gonna go make fun of my
dad for being bald shine bright like a
diamond you got you in your bald head
see kids you guys should be doing that
for your daddy
- why can't I walk with this dog any arm
swing motions that you do let's say
about this aggressive on the way here Oh
God this lighting makes me look pale
actually on the way here something
interesting happened people say each
other but we copy each other everything
everything we do yesterday if you
remember we both said the same exact
thing in the mornings the same thing
knowing we're parked across from the
biggest house in my hometown city it was
like one of the biggest houses in the
city looks right here that is the
biggest house in every day I would drive
by this house we would always drive by
this house and I said to myself I'm
gonna own a house bigger than that one
day and I good but my house in Los
Angeles cost twice as much as that house
guys and I'm 22 years old
[Music]
you also Jake like rented a g-wagen bro
what are you doing it's like bigger no
bro it's like a smurfier version of the
Yeti I said that in my blog there is I'm
so proud of him and all the
accomplishments he's done yeah there is
that was a little too close look it'd be
cool if it wasn't just a smaller bluer
version of the Yeti look growing up I
never thought like something like this
would happen things go wrong I know
you're used to this but I'm not I just
grew up here oh no they're singing the
diss track stop no every other day just
I'm strong as I know I kid I made yo
this is bad guys Jase here's some where
you got wait what Oh anyway there please
look low gang you guys know I love you
like actually and I will take pictures
with you guys anywhere I'll say what's
up but my house guys don't come to my
it's the one spot where I do want
privacy like who knows you can bring a
girl home and there's like kids in my
backyard Mac has been my best friend
since first grade he is he's the day one
day one now on that note he had an idea
we have dumb ideas we're gonna go to the
mall
I'm gonna take this opportunity to buy
gifts for my family that's my boy that's
my boy no no you're not only gonna be on
the vlog I want you to help me pick what
gif I'm gonna get from my mom what
should I get from my mom it's on you
that way if it's bad it's the Asian kids
fault man you're so much taller that's
what everyone says I'm also much more of
a cha-ching real-life mom at the asian
kid he's gonna get you gift but what's
your name so I can stop call you by your
grace Evan oh I already know what you're
looking at bro should I give her that no
yeah for sure no good call Evan much
appreciated you're the man I think my
dad would like this he's a handyman it's
just a wooden mug I don't know guys I'm
bad at this yeah look at I'm such a good
side thing okay I wasn't going to he
said it was a lifetime warranty guys I'm
just joking I bought two literally just
so I can make that joke I kind of messed
up by telling me not to break it
cuz now I gotta break you know what else
I just remembered my parents are
divorced so we're celebrating Christmas
at my mom's house tomorrow
so her bad [ __ ] gift will be a surprise
however if my dad watches this vlog dad
if you're watching too late he's gonna
know I got him a man just wood mugged
but you know what I got some other stuff
too
Matt wait no I'm not here to wrap my
gifts look there's gifts look this wrap
no what are you dying one of you is
actually done car oh god no I swear to
god I'm just minding my own business I
was gonna wrap all these then start the
vlog and like sign up me I gotta get
little please deal with this what is
that
shirt by the way I picked it right up
off of him yeah no no no weird I did not
plant it there I swear to God I don't he
just walked up and it's stuck to him why
was this stuff this is bad okay if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe why
stop stop us to come to my house that's
it stop if you haven't yet make sure you
get the Maverick merch I don't want to
rely on Santa to bring it to you just a
little mad at me with the diss track and
also yeah looking for that cough slash
shop or they just it's the hottest
softest merch and the gang verifiable
thing with us hello gang I love you and
I'll see you tomorrow and hopefully I
have my voice back take your gifts and
give them back merch is where it's at
got the hoodie what's up Taylor look in
there you should dream about that you
should get my new backpack
throw away that 30 sec how much are
these 90 each okay