[Music]
thank you thank you thank you I'm gonna
be better all around I'm gonna be
quicker I'm gonna be faster I function
well under pressure pressure creates
diamonds and I'm a [ __ ] diamond so if
I don't have a have you're on I can't
get hit and I'm not gonna get
the first TV standing front of you right
now you will not see this person in two
months completely transformed into some
utterly world creature you got two guys
two villains with the biggest egos in
the world the biggest pride in the world
we're subscribers money clout Fame and
they actually know how to fight this is
not a gimmick anymore I'm no longer a
youtuber right now I'm a professional
fighter I'm gonna treat it like that
people die in this sport this is a
dangerous sport I'm not gonna go to war
without my weapons and to get those
weapons takes years of training
dedication passion so I don't think the
average creator can do that this is this
is a second chance
[Applause]
[Music]
can I be honest with you guys yes please
I'm not in the mood jokes today I'm not
I'm not in a good mood I'm not at all
last year the press conference like
before you know we had the big party bus
we had the whole squad of people
everyone was getting so high last year I
was a youtuber first and a showman first
I wanted to put on a good show I wanted
to look good this year I'm a boxer first
so I'm treating it like that and I'm so
mentally just as zoned in right now the
fight is won today if I can get in his
head which I know I can and just seep
beneath that small that it thinks all
that is ksi I think this is the
beginning of the end of our friend JJ
Evan what do you think about all this I
feel good
Oh Shh the secret weapon
haha hey how much is this watch probably
300 K yo yo put a richer million I've
not had no idea how I got I could figure
it out
[Music]
let's get ready to rumble
[Applause]
good opponent the nightmare kazar
[Music]
that bro I said it this morning she it's
like a job to me I'm trying to be I'm
trying to be as locked in as possible
and he comes out with some that was the
weakest of her do nothing bro I told him
I told her to his face I'm like bro
nothing what happened you were so good
last year everything you said was funny
in a hit oh he's making like Drake jokes
well I'm so disappointed I'm so mad
right now watch the kids demeanor the
whole fight watch the way he sits in his
chair he slouches I'm up talking [ __ ] to
his face talking about his family trying
to trigger him a little bit and he gives
me nothing he talked more about me than
you nothin ever in sporting history have
I seen someone that is so bad and
trashed
he was good last year he was do trust go
do it good like still at the bottom but
this year dude he little son you know
why you know why you know why you know
why you know why he's gonna lose cuz I'm
next controversial you got nothing
bro oh man watching knock this man out I
already won I already won I'm gonna kill
him okay that was yesterday I've had 24
plus hours to sort of decompress a lot
of [ __ ] was said in the press conference
my opinion I got a little out of hand I
went somewhere that unfortunately I
didn't want to be mentally and I'll
explain that I'm gonna sort of give you
guys a play-by-play of what was going
through my mind I will say everything
that I said was true starting off with
even just seeing JJ because mind you I
haven't seen the kid physically in
person for a year the last time we were
locked in a 20 by 20 foot square
literally just beating the [ __ ] out of
each other I was excited to see what I
would feel like when I was when I was
face-to-face with him again I wish I
could say I felt something when I saw
him there was no apprehension there was
no it was just a pure sense of
domination
and when I looked in his eyes not only
could I see the fear on him his eye was
still bleeding from the last fight if
you all remember post August 25th the
kid had a blood vessel popped on his eye
I think from a couple of my jab and when
I was looking at him he had a brown spot
where the blood vessels were pop and as
soon as I saw that I got crazy confident
cuz I was like yo this was from a year
and a half ago and I've scarred this kid
I've left him something that's gonna be
with him for the rest of his life the
kid is gonna look in the mirror and to
be reminded of me that was with head
guards and 12 ounce gloves with no head
guards yo oh so then the press
conference started and I hate to say
this but before it started I tweeted
time to do what I do best and that is
quite honestly when I want to flip the
switch be an [ __ ] like I can be an
[ __ ]
[Applause]
and this press conference is that it
kind of sucks because this press
conference is like the epitome of the
worst version of myself the one that
just prods and pokes and is a little
cringe and it's just yelling and
screaming and saying mean stuff but then
again that's my job I feel like as an
entertainer as a boxer and my job to
sell tickets and move product I'm here
to put on a show you don't have to like
me you can hate me I'd rather you hate
me than feeling different about me but
at least you feel something and you're
out there gonna come and watch me beat
the [ __ ] out of the kid or you're gonna
come watch me to go watch you mean to
watch me to watch me get beat up I don't
know what happened there know we're
sitting here and Eddie Hearn is talking
and I'm like yo this like my opponent is
sitting four feet from me why would I
not turn to my right and just start
saying some [ __ ] so some dude handed me
a cup of of ice water
I took the ice and he got mad the team's
kind of gotten a little bit of a scuffle
but you know I'm such a [ __ ] punk
dude and I know it I've been away from
this kid for a year and a half and he's
right there and I'm fighting him like
why not just prod him a little bit so
then Shannon Briggs
by the way who's my coach two-time
heavyweight champ of the world goes
right for the biggest guy he can find he
goes yo dude big guy yo and Shannon
Briggs is in your corner one as a coach
is incredible two as a bodyguard I don't
care how big you are
Shannon will disrespect Shannon will
hurt you bro he will say let's go champ
to your face let's go over and over
again and over again and do it then some
more let's go champ
so then they let our coaches speak
Shannon went up there he said some stuff
let's go chat and then Vidale who's que
sighs coach he went up there and he
started talking he goes up there and
Shannon goes I don't know if y'all y'all
got this he's like he let wrote a speech
he had notes in the same if it all comes
up there with notes in his hand and I
looked I was like he's just dude about
to like give a speech like it's not your
day so I start talking to food all he's
up there and I'm like go like what do
you do to make youtube videos are you a
boxing coach and he actually ended up
getting booed off like no one wanted him
there anymore
[Music]
then I go up there it's my turn to talk
I don't feel like staying in one
position it's not my thing I like to
walk around I like to be mobile and so I
go to remove this mic and a few people
might have noticed this if you hit me in
the head
all right listen soon as they hit me in
that I was like no this is not to do a
good start but you could see I pull it
yank it up and it just comes right down
and like hits me I was like in case I am
good all notice and they started
laughing starte and minds you guys I
have no monologue prepared when they
told me it was open format I'm like yo
okay I don't know what this like do I
just stand out there and talk and be a
bully first like the goal is obviously
to piss the kid off but there's no
question there's just like I go speak
about what dude the first thing I go for
obviously is Deji the brother who
disowned him where's that yet where the
[ __ ] is that yet where's your family at
I like responding to ksi better like
last year he said so many things and I
wasn't quite as quick and witty as I am
now I think actually partially because
of the podcast talking on impulsive at
length has made me much better at being
able to respond real-time and so I don't
really know what I'm doing here I
thanked his parents for birthing him so
I could be dishing out of him
mr. and mrs. ksi thank you for giving me
the opportunity to beat the [ __ ] out of
your [ __ ] son and by the way I stand
by that like thank you guys I would love
to give you a gift card of some sort
take you out to dinner sometime I told
the kid he smelled like herpes so what
do you hope you smell like if JJ had any
brain even the smallest amount he would
have said yo how do you know what herpes
smell like and then it would be like no
mr. shott there and you go miss your
shot in the ring boy that was the
cheesiest thing I've ever said if I'm
being honest with you he didn't he
didn't smell like herpes he smelled
bonala herpes baby take it off take it
off
cuz your super glue TT uh-huh that was
your wig bro so I started getting
confused here cuz he was saying that was
that was my weight he was telling me to
take off his bandana and then I was
saying last year if you guys remember at
that press conference last year I tried
the bandana I ripped off the wig and
then I tried to take off the bandana it
was super glued to his head so yeah I
got super confused I started to question
everything around me I was like yo this
is a space crime time continuum broken
cuz I could have swore could've sworn I
ripped the wig off real easily and then
the bandana was the thing I couldn't get
Wow by the way your own your brother
said I'm gonna win this fight hey that
is true that is true Deji his own
brother said I had the edge in this
fight no good has an edge I don't know
what isn't connecting with people when
they say that they think ksi is gonna
win this fight cuz I see a lot of the
Twitter pulls and stuff and ksi is
actually he's the favorite right now
technically I'm the underdog which I'm
totally cool with I love being the
underdog but I don't get it
it's cool though it's a cool opportunity
your suit is nice your suit is Usami on
every doll at this point cuz every time
this do poster youtube videos are you
doing maybe this is why your pupil looks
like a fine meatball I don't know
wherever dolls been if he's out making
YouTube videos but how many times can
you put me in a video before you realize
like yo you should probably focus on
making your kid the best athlete you can
your suit is loops get a better tailor
you gotta pay more oh my god I just
realized maybe that's why I don't show
up maybe that's why you got this brick
[ __ ] of a man holding pads for JJ
and not Vidale so that this was funny
but Vidale had to encourage JJ to go he
said go get him JJ go go do your best
job so this was cool with JJ walked up
finally I'm like yo I don't have to just
start holding [ __ ] from my ass I can
respond which is what I do best
that's it before I talk about you Logan
I want to talk about J let's talk about
a chain rule quick that's your opening
your opening is yo let's talk about Jake
where's the JJ from last year where's
the JD who brought the props he had the
wig and everything I wanted that JJ and
the first thing he says was let's talk
about Jake and I can see why I think
Jake made him upset when in our first
face to face Jake came up to JJ and blew
smoke in his face
nice yo this dudes talking about
spelling I like it for those you don't
know what semantics mean it's the branch
of linguistics concerning with meaning
so I'm like what the [ __ ] is this kid
saying he's talking about like a
spelling of the word [ __ ] my brother's
YouTube video
yo lock-in dude like get your head in
the game right now mentally I'm telling
you he's not there he hasn't been there
for the past year and a half look at the
pictures of us from the last fight the
one we're both holding in the belt I'm
there I'm smiling what a great first
boxing event huh we did good
jayjay not even present you're a plan is
and are off the 405 I'll wait you after
in there I'll wait till you after it
I'll wait
I'm really trying to understand I'll
wait till you I'll wait to you after
this okay literally like I just told him
his breasts Samin like herpes then he
told me my breath smell 4500 miles
that's how far you flew from London to
America to steal my jokes and talk to my
brother no I don't know about all this
they say looking good for you dog I'm so
sorry I didn't know you were there oh we
knew the Kong jokes were coming there's
no rebuttal there's no response
it just said like you ruin my day you
ruin my day did you good job dude good
job I hope you're happy
I missed that little dog they started
making noises you're up you go so
confident doctor beat your ass and I was
with take a picture with Drake post it
on social media
I'd still win it bro what are you yeah
not funny that's the joke you flew 4500
miles to make that joke I'm like yo
Drake's not gonna take a picture with
you
ever nood my musical you don't know you
couldn't sell on a 50-person venue in
your own country so that that was me
just getting under his skin because he
went on this music tour while I was
training this past year at half a if you
guys didn't know this he was on tour and
some of the venues were so small and not
sold out and as an artist that is one of
the most embarrassing things ever his
music videos cost Hawley between fifty
and two hundred thousand dollars each
and they get like what two two two to
eight million views let's just say JJ's
music career is not probably going the
way he wants it to I put my hands okay
so first of all you look like you're
running with a dildo up your ass what's
wrong with having a dildo up your ass
shout out to Jordy where'd your
personality go like a easy
hey JJ has no dick I reached a point
where I realized like after he sat down
even just the way he's seated he's kind
of slouched over like this body language
experts will tell you it's a defeated
demeanor everything about him had just
sort of given up and and by the way I
actually kind of get this if you all
remember in the press conference last
year when I went to England I sat down
you could see my face I was kind of sad
I didn't really want to be there I
wasn't having the best day ever I was
kind of tired and that's what happened
if you remember I literally just left
because I was like this I don't want to
be here and I I sensed that a little bit
with him here so then this is where the
infamous JJ has no dick part came in JJ
has no dick change it has no dick at
this moment that I knew this [ __ ] is
this press conference as God to shout
out my mom for really making this
segment come around momma Paul hands for
the way good morning pastor good morning
pastor
he missed another shot there he could
have been like yo how do you know I have
no dick you've seen my crotch what
missed again and then my favorite part
about this you got no dick what I go you
got no dick and he's like what like he
just found
Hey what news flash dude you just lost
your dick listen can you imagine he goes
home later I mean he finds out that he
has no dick and this is the noise he
makes so my eyes now at this point he's
defeated he's not giving me much to work
with so we put the nail in the coffin
with him do me a favor
these next 55 days are gonna be the best
days of your life Oh Tecna Brite stop
training seriously Oh get up your life
yeah after November nah gonna be
miserable okay no JJ go go go skydiving
broke hey go make a cake go fall in love
my god do something fun cuz your life is
gonna shock after November 9 okay this
is where this is where the
disappointment really came in I just
expected more and he wasn't he wasn't
giving it to me is it over already
I want to sit what are you doing but
give me something dude just weak dude so
finally they put us together at the end
and I had one more opportunity to make
it make something happen here so I get
up I get in his face a little bit and
easy man easy man to move I tweeted this
easy man to move I pushed him I barely
put any effort into him he goes back
like two feet and I didn't want it to
end there brother like I'm a little bit
of a sick father like I wanted to get in
his mind a little bit so I took off his
glasses and now we're face to face I can
see that that mark on his eye again and
I'm Raquel I got a little heated here
your eyes
I thought at one point I was like yo
this dude's about to kiss me right now I
was cool with it
no I'm just kidding no I'm not and that
he looked a little hot right so like I
was just looking out for him I I blew on
his face I hooked him up so he hooked me
up back he blew on my face we're calling
each other off no problem I guess you
could say we just started blowing each
other and then at one point I started
crying
what are sweating out of my eyes or
something I don't know why do you
remember that happening look it was a
hot day okay and sometimes yeah I sweat
on my eyes [ __ ] you so do witches we're
just talking for like hours it seemed
like and Allison I'm like stroking my
invisible penis and then like humping
the air and it's over and I'm like yo
what's good just confused confusion what
what just happened why was it like that
and then I see this video of ksi talking
after the press conference and the dude
is just not in good shape
he's got bigger boobs than most of the
girls I hook up with and I'm not body
shaming him but actually I absolutely am
you're like 55 days get it together
I really hope you do I'm being
absolutely honest with all my content
the past six to eight months I've been
shot I've tried to be extremely real
with you guys after that day my
confidence even more so than it already
has
as skyrocket I don't know if he's
satisfied with the amount of money that
he's made from this fight or what but
that fire that JJ had last year that ksi
that I thought last year was gone that
kid was gone
dead and gone the kid I'm fighting now
feels like he thinks he should be
working hard and he should say certain
things to offend me there's no substance
there the wall was was broke down way
way way too easily so yeah I hope he
loses sleep every day knowing that I'm
working harder than him knowing that I
have more valuable assets on my team to
him knowing that I'm also working
smarter than him everything about our
training camp is so much better than his
and if you're a ksi fan it's not too
late to come over to the light side oh
gosh that's that naughty not a skin
thing like like it's like a Star Wars
reference hit that subscribe button we
love you we accept you November 9th I
want to see you guys there if you live
in LA actually even if you don't live in
LA I want to see you there at the
Staples Center tickets are on sale now
link in description
shirts are also on sale if you want to
wrap these Maverick boxing club it's
official logo Paul that calm slash shop
I haven't plugged in awhile I felt weird
and it's gonna be available to watch on
the disown app if you can't make it so
download that be ready I'm excited this
is gonna be good now if y'all excuse me
I gotta go train oh I'll see you I love
you hit that subscribe button
[Music]
that's ironic that's ironic how I just
farted when I just caught him discussing
just now
[Music]