previously on lost
and now these took a conclusion from
yesterday's ball hey maybe it was a
little while in English good morning
little gang what's poppin look guys I'm
gonna get right down to business
I got a twitch account now homie gaming
live streaming it all on a platform
called twitch if my Twitter account is
at Logan fall was taken why cuz Logan
pull was to make sure to follow me there
guys give a quick side shoutout to
anyone into the low game who comes up
these videos like guys I know this I
read your comments
I see the thumbs up thank you guys man
seriously it means a lot guys and if
you're not a part of the low game you
guys we invite you to join us and
subscribe join the family unless you
suck so yeah guys yesterday we left you
on some cliffhangers which we will get
to shortly but first a while back you
guys might remember I sent some of the
hottest nurse in the game that maverick
merch to my new boxing opponent KS I
know his crime scene investigation
that's a TV show yeah PMS so PMS is like
but yeah he wasn't there as you guys
know he was in Vegas training no wait
sweaty well you wanted to find me right
now you gotta get ready we gotta give
the gym it's funny cuz when I'm training
I don't sit on the couch look ok what
I'm getting at is he got the merge
yesterday it's pretty nice to you
because normally someone not you mr.
kiss I hope you liked the match thanks
for being a part of the Logan I can't
wait to beat your ass [ __ ] no really
though thanks for being in the low gang
and also just like the note said I
cannot wait to obliterate you in a
boxing ring on August 25th that's gonna
be good I'm gonna be very satisfied
after that alright enough [ __ ] let's
get into the vlog today yesterday guys
you know all that stuff went down and
I'm sure you're wondering what happened
ok so first what happened with the
attempted ball pit with glass in it in
I think it'll just be a special surprise
sign the waiver and it's not my problem
I can visibly see the glass Oh No - the
shards of glass in my ass this is
actually like this was the move not to
kick the glass up guys we left the
creepy elephant in here forever rodeo
elephants
oh that's such good fun guys make sure
to subscribe make sure to get your my
slogan fine hey it's kind of nice nice
nice so yeah this is gonna be cool if we
have a guest in this room like I said
watch out for the shards of glass in the
bottle and then regarding the BMX spider
rider biker you guys remember we weren't
sure if he signed the waiver or if you
could Huck it off the house but ladies
and gentlemen the suspense is over
[Laughter]
oh just watching over there like a hog
you're good you stop otherwise you can't
do a montage give me a minute man I
might need a bit more
[Music]
so man's can definitely send then the
last thing obviously guys did I find
true love in the form of my roommate
Evan did I kiss him in public
it was the thumbnail of yesterday's
video after all well ladies and
gentlemen this is Spence is over know
you Evan not in public anyway so there's
there a chance I may be home when I'm
streaming on Twitch at Logan Paul would
say can follow me there Wow oh yeah so I
definitely love Evan I just don't know
if it's true love you know and the way I
would love a female with my but enough
to have adult stuff guys look ank that
is though vlog if you're not a part of
us make sure to subscribe do yourself
and your family's lineage a favor and
copy yourself some of the hottest
softest merch in the game no joke guys
you put this on your definition of soft
completely changes and it's that
maverick movement side we are here okay
being ourselves and loving me that's
what it's about Logan Poldark on slash
habló gang I love y'all and I will see
you tomorrow take these bamboo Peaks lag
in my mind and nothing
get picked and I will pick yours
Prince's paupers timing servants excuse
me while I make a slide from inside the
circus bare-knuckle fight club like
tyler durden like all invite through
what i am
[Applause]