[Music]
I'm always pushing the boundaries that's
just how I am okay I never thought I'd
be even a pro box at all
I've never boxed before last year there
we go
the first fight I ever did there's
15,000 people watching and a million
plus at home I went in there essentially
beat him up there wasn't a time to fight
where I felt threatened I'm ten times
better of a boxer an athlete than him
I hate harder than unfossilized
everything better than him in the first
fight I should have won it I want to
fight most people thought I want to
fight if there was another round I would
have finished him for sure I'm going to
knock this kid the [ __ ] out on November
9 the kid is gonna be damaged I called
our local pool and I for looking for now
we have very much there won't be a third
I'm ending this November night when this
bell rang two of the biggest internet
stars ever beating the [ __ ] out of each
other
incredible
this is the moment we've all been
waiting he watch this before my time boy
Logan what somebody come on ticket is
discharged yeah
Matt's got this boat right now any
youtuber wants it you can come get it no
can pull and there's a pool I don't know
how you're gonna react to 15,000 fans
booing you at your first boxing event by
the way you're not like not really a
boxer the first fight it's sold out the
Manchester Arena and it was 1.2 million
pay-per-view buys any loss will be big
two very big names and I knew the whole
America versus the UK thing was gonna be
huge as well
it was like a movies swear to God like
you are walking out people in this part
I look I look to him
I remember thinking what the [ __ ] is he
wearing watch right here this is the
cheesiest thing I've ever seen in my
life
[Music]
he's suggesting
both these guys clearly have a personal
disdain for each other they got very
heated
Loden as the maturity of a 12 year old
the kid wanted to eat my face
and I felt that that cycle still the
look yeah right now they don't know what
to do
I noticed off the top that you know my
guy he knows how to throw punches he had
a good job and he was quick no he's not
logan paul what you saw was him starting
really really fast this is where I
started to get cocky because I knew I
was faster than him right and I was
landing punches that he he wasn't robbed
one I felt like the greatest boxer in
the world I literally couldn't believe
how much better I was in this man
so I started taunting him cuz I'm an
[ __ ] she's hoping to
this is this is where it gets good
[Applause]
best combo in internet history
bro this is one China muscles don't
equal power it's out there look just out
there look what you're gonna do what was
that slightly win the respect buck
because feels like he's lost that first
rung swings are getting wild what the
hell is he doing
you see that I have seen that toy in
school I have a signature then without
each a Mack what look what that what my
hands oh my gosh
mother cat seems to enjoy this they even
said it right they're like Logan seems
to be enjoying this cuz I was and I
wasn't focused on like hey I should
probably end this fight as quickly as I
can
I was just having fun being his first
right we never did it before you know he
didn't understand about stepping up to
the plate after you know in combination
he kinda I was looking at his work and
I'm saying admire his work reach above
it just just so important on the boys
[Applause]
that he's such a dirty scumbag who was
in a hometown that's okay
that was that was cheap for me man I
should have done that okay Jake like
he's gonna do something Jay damn near
got me disqualified sure though I hate
ksi with all my heart I was on edge like
like if my brothers fighting then I'm
fighting we know Jake is yeah next
question I coached Milton after the
round he said hey you won that round by
the way stop showboating showboating I'm
winning this fight I'm fine
turns out I wasn't fine
in this box
round three started zero all of a sudden
I had nothing left I had no energy I can
barely pick up my arms and I couldn't
wrap my head around what just happened
and why a little bit tight now I'm JJ he
loves his job
[Applause]
in 6 min chicken hips now the question
is how do you get tired from only
Flickinger I felt like it turned round 3
and that's when I was like I need to get
in his face and beat him up London
imagine those are straight oh my god I
was too stationaries a smart guy I let
him I let it set up for everything thank
you yeah that's good cuz that's intense
yeah yeah this is my body though dad
what happened
JJ can finish strong here then you'll
definitely take this wounds
I was like go out yeah get inside
I'm fighting around free becomes a 10-9
ksi around because the pace changed
[Applause]
there's so many times I could they just
all finish their mind
it's suck to like just see him getting
punched in the face but I know him
Logan's not going down like that we're
tenants guys I promise you those new
damage this is a ton this is here I'm
unloading you know this right here when
we know it means and we know what to do
he gonna be tired from swinging like
that yeah but Logan this is a one two
around fight yeah I'm gonna keep it real
if you just hit him with the jab the
first ride he's gonna be so busy looking
for that he gonna be frustrated you're
gonna be doing like this you already
doing like this it's like a small cloud
over his head you just calm down with
thunder
[Applause]
2:42 you stay on him you gotta stay here
you go stay inside he don't like it no
one can question your conditionals or
your chin yeah yeah he's conscious
I'm telling you now if he hit hard you'd
be able to tell me I said come on come
on stop there was a point in the fight
where case I got hit by like four
punches and I'm like okay he's gonna
he's gonna beat this kids ass I don't
know what I thought I just knew he was
showing signs of weakness so I went for
it as you sure champ in the fifth round
I thought you know Logan kind of got
control of himself and he was back to
straight punch and the Atlanta some
great shots I thought was great for
frankly gt6 it up as if it's nothing
shockingly good with puppets I'm
changing this
I literally do not remember my corner
telling me anything I went I blacked out
I'd have no idea what they said I think
at this time I said boy we need this
round we need to win this round this is
when JJ goes to tongue round six I'm
like this is gonna be the longest three
minutes of my life this is uh he's gonna
be tricky
[Applause]
good shot good shot
keeping top of him whether his fitness
wasn't quite the same level over the
rounds he started to actually empties
ten in case I came back into the fight
times I thought case I might look to
stop him in the contest this was such a
crazy experience fighting with no energy
for like two by two rounds now believing
I'm winning the fight by the way and
just knowing that I got one more round
to go just hold up and follow today
the only rounds I give him was three and
six if that I can't really do a six shot
it's really swinging the swinging
tell me he won the fight he finished
that fight so strong Logan had
absolutely nothing left 25 seconds she
was talking if there was another round I
would have finished him for sure not
this year I couldn't believe what just
happened
he's actually gasps these they're like
yes so many different thoughts are going
through my mind
milton whispered to me he goes it's good
you didn't lose I'm like but I didn't
[ __ ] win okay so what's the point the
point is dissolved it's gonna be big
it's gonna be very different and let's
hope he's prepared for it looking back
in the fight you learn last year I kind
of knew what I was doing this year
there's an animal inside me there's a
killer that I I suppress because he's
[ __ ] evil but on November 9th he's
gonna come out and it's not gonna be
pretty
last year I was just a white next five
I'm ending his career you're gonna see
much better technique I'm gonna see look
like a professional fire it's a
different ballgame now you know I'm
seeing ksi doesn't respect a little bit
I think I'm gonna come out you're gonna
stop on punished on November this is a
big moment I believe for professional
boxing we've seen the biggest stars in
the world in a rematch said we need to
lose the head cuts and you got to use
tennis clubs the ones that really crack
it might be a little bit surprised at
just how big some of those punches feel
when you're not wearing headgear and
you're wearing those 10 times closer
fight night they're like weapons dude it
feels like I'm holding lethal firearms
in my hand one right hand and I'm
putting Logan to sleep
if someone is gonna step in the ring
with me I'm gonna do everything in my
power to take over this person mentally
and physically this is like a death
match he can punch me in the face and
I'm still going to be that and then he
can punch me your face again I'm still
gonna be there and when he realizes I'm
still that it's gonna scare him the
first fight is any indication these guys
are coming for each other and coming to
finish each other off
someone will get knocked down it won't
go six rounds lists Amish rule and it's
a real fire people curiosity want to see
who the hell is gonna win JJ's
leadership is not just his physical
shrine
it's the things you can't see and
measure great hunger the will to win yes
he's a strong competitive man I'll guess
what Logan Paul is going not clear sigh
Oh cold
I can't wait let's go champ you had
people there's fans of both Scott's at
fighting they're gonna watch a roofer
there gosh
that brings attention I know absolutely
I'm winning November night is gonna be a
spectacle I'm gonna beat the [ __ ] out of
the guy he's putting on an act to try
and hide his eyes she very nervous why
should we watch why should you watch
because you're gonna see one of the
Great's is knockouts of all time
[Music]