realize what you've locked into
I finish you off an angel career well
here we go
things just got real they've turned pro
they've ditched the head gear but one
thing remains the same for two of the
Internet's biggest superstars in chaos 9
Logan Paul but they still hate each
other and here we are downtown LA behind
me the Staples Center which will be sold
out on November 9th November 8th rather
for the big fight the rematch between
these two superstars for the press
conference now sponsored by mash from
boxing and Eddie Hearn I'm Lauren
Gardner here on the zone what's up
everyone let's take a look at the
Twitter pull who you got who you got in
this fight is it can sighs the Logan
Paul they both been training really hard
for this one we will talk to a
professional about this here in a second
and Tevin farmer who is the IBF super
featherweight champion of the world
Tevin what's going on my friend how are
you feeling right now
I don't know energy is a big big fight
maybe not to some boxing fans but sort
of people in the world this is a big
fight two very very popular guys and I'm
looking forward to I seen the first one
and I can't wait to see the second one
yeah here's the deal there's been some
criticism in the world of boxing people
who subscribe here to the zone some of
the boxing purists have you that say
this is kind of a joke whoa yeah it's
pretty interesting so let's take a look
at the tale of the tape here and we will
get to that here in just a second so
tale the tape here this is six rounds
these two are close to the edge close in
height close and weight in your opinion
who's going to have the edge yeah
they weigh the same amount so the better
fighter that night
it's will win the fight and I'm looking
forward to it like I said before they
broke the Reach's 71 175 you know I feel
like looking Paul the uzj I'll play he
can take over the fight yeah so last
year that first fight in front of a
sold-out crowd 21,000 people the
pay-per-view subscribers 1.3 million
people that's not to mention all the
people who are watching on YouTube and
twitch let's take a look at how this
thing unfolded
this redisplay isn't it JJ Malcolm even
telemedicine or whatever I thought would
change is gonna cause that distance and
it's a left or a while loop in Paul
shook psi the jobs rider repeatedly
[Applause]
I will never forget the look of shock
and disappointment on both fighters
faces now Tevin here's a look at the
rules for the upcoming fight this is a
real fight you know no stay in the 8
count no three knockdown rule fighter
cannot be Saved by the Bell in any round
doctors and referees can stop the fight
and the extra hay but after Round four
okay here we go six rounds three minutes
apiece
both fighters guaranteed a knockout what
do you think we will say you know me
being up me being a professional fighter
and myself we promise a lot of things
sometime we don't deliver yeah we had to
see who deliver yes you know who's going
to deliver for us that's our own Katie
Austin she's in the crowd it's absolute
mayhem down there by the stage what do
you got Katie hey what's up everybody my
name is Katie Austin I'm here in
downtown LA the press conference is
about to happen right behind me and this
crowd we're bringing the heat guys we're
bringing the heat we got Logan Paul kids
dive is right behind me oh yeah and this
isn't the normal audience of a boxing
match we have two huge social media
stars going at it so really anything can
happen let's take a look at what
happened at last year's press conference
I can't wait to punch you right in your
stupid smug face when you feel by power
repeatedly punching you in the face it
sound like a super villain
then you will realize when you feel the
rattle you will realize that you've made
a mistake to try to fight me
I've made this appeal a continuous lack
of my judgment
[Applause]
yeah you [ __ ] [ __ ]
all right so that was pretty nuts let's
see what happens this year but I'm here
with Natalie she is Logan's biggest fan
you even made a sign for him why are you
excited to be here today I'm so excited
because I know he's gonna win he's gonna
whip ksi JSS and he's better lucky
number one podcast no more on youtuber
and already you know he's been training
for a year and a half he's been working
his ass off so we'll see what goes on
just a bunch of crap talking but I know
Logan's gonna win are you worried that
Kent side's gonna knock him out in the
face too worried when his beautiful look
no I will not worry cuz I know he's too
quick to be dodging all those all right
well back to you Lauren Thank You
Natalie
thanks a lot Katie well Natalie had a
beautiful pink Stein and there's a look
at him the man the myth the legend the
YouTube star this sensation Logan Paul
making his way to the stage here in
downtown LA just outside the Staples
Arena for the beginning of this press
conference that will be starting in just
a few moments but first we want to
remind you that this is the beginning of
fight season right here on the zone not
only can you get this big rematch only
on two zone ksi Logan Paul - right here
in downtown LA behind me munguia in
Carson California later this evening we
have triple G we have bucyk we also have
Canelo Alvarez arguably the biggest name
in all of boxing and of course on
December 7th Andy Ruiz against Anthony
Joshua in Saudi Arabia one device one
price all the biggest fights right here
on to zone now let's take a look at a
preview for that triple G fight
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm going with triple G I'm definitely
going to be G I just like need a bigger
puncher and he uses Jack very well he
also know how to cut off the distance of
a fight his ending fight any fight fan
no a dad and cut you this is very
important in the sport of boxing okay we
just talked about the biggest fighter in
all of boxing Canelo Alvarez who will be
back in Las Vegas it seems like that's
really his home arena arena there at
t-mobile yes he will be fighting on
November 2nd just before this big fight
between ksi and Logan Paul let's take a
look at that preview
[Applause]
how can you not like love Canelo how can
you not let's not let's not put another
crime kopelow of he's a he's a bigger
fighter than Canelo um he have a big
punch he have a lot of knockout bout for
lucky none of the runt of the storm he's
very fast he's very strong and his
footwork is amazed and his defense get
better every time I'm picking Canelo for
the win yeah he continues to involve and
he continues to improve so of that slate
of fights isn't enough for you we got
one more for you that is between the two
heavyweight champions following the big
upset at Madison Square Garden this past
summer I'm talking about Andy Ruiz jr.
I'm talking about Anthony Joshua in
Saudi Arabia
Italy's as an underdog that's a physique
it's just nothing like Anthony Josh
Vance and social media look at and Ruiz
who say all that chunky kid what's he
gonna do
[Applause]
Andy's a type of bot ser Hugh - his face
he's turning a devil
[Applause]
you have an immediate rematch clause do
you expect to exercise that 100% now he
knows he has to be that's the challenge
hey hey hey dr. C I had Peaks for other
fights for this fight is gonna be hard
for me to pick and the reason why is it
Natasha was a friend of mine and rohui's
came from the bottom just like myself I
thought the boxing League so it's really
hard for me to pick I think what the
best man to win this fight
now walk out of there safe we still
think that you think Joshua is going to
be the favorite in this fight but you
can never count out any ruins Joshua
will be the favorite fight you can knock
it out the underdog never yeah this is a
fascinating matchup and we are here for
the press conference between ksi and
Logan Paul the rematch that will be
taking place right here on to zone it
will be exclusively on to zone your home
for all the best fights in the world on
November 8th at Staples Center right
behind me the stage is there for the
official press conference about twenty
or thirty seconds ago we heard all the
fans are up that's because ksi is making
his way to the stage we have Logan Paul
up there we have Jake Paul on the stage
and we have our own Katie Austin in the
crowd with some of these rabid fans all
right you guys the crowd is going nuts
behind me here but I grab Salvador from
the crowd a huge ksi fan why are you
excited for this fight
because I mean KS eyes are really like
trained so much and I don't Logan's
trained so much that's why they got a
drawn-out this fight there's obviously
gonna have to be a winner and maybe even
a knockout how long have you been
falling category since I was 12 years
old I'm six no 17 years right now and
yeah five years that's awesome well
thank you so much back to you guys
okay so everyone's saying there's going
to be a knockout in this fight obviously
the two fighters are saying there's
going to be a knockout it might be a
little bit easier said than done
as we take a look at the updated Twitter
poll here so it looks like a case is
favored 72% to 28% for Logan Paul it's
crazier yeah 75,000 votes are you
surprised by these results yes a lot
you know as you can see he's down the
dog look upon the dog rohui's with the
underdog as well I don't like the polls
give me anything okay I feel like it
just give it a better look or how many
people you turn into the fight yeah
that's a good point and how many ksi
fans are out there following us andhe's
own that's what we want to know that's
what we want to talk about cuz I won't
give it everyone a big platform yes they
do and once again this fight will be
streamed exclusively right here on to
zone for more on this let's send it on
over to Michael buffer rematch that the
world has been waiting for 13 months ago
in Manchester England in front of over
20,000 fans in the Manchester Arena
10,000 fans outside trying to get in
these two fighters fought each other to
a draw this time in the rematch it's
going to be different they're gonna be
licensed professionals fighting as
cruiserweights in a six round contest
scheduled for six three-minute rounds
now millions and millions watched on the
internet on YouTube and now they're
gonna get a chance to see this as a
professional contest this will be an
event like no other at Staples Center
and an anticipated twenty plus thousand
fans are going to attend so let me ask
you this for those who have come to the
first press conference are you ready
white fans are you ready for all the
fans in attendance and the millions
around the world watching right now on
the Internet
ladies and gentlemen let's get ready to
rumble here they are first ladies and
gentlemen Logan maverick Pau
[Applause]
next to the stage his opponent the
nightmare chaos ah
[Applause]
damn
- Sophie look at
you almost got knocked out the first
time check
time logan paul ksi ladies and gentlemen
here to tell you more about the
particulars of this great night Saturday
November 9th here at Staples Center for
matram boxing USA mr. Eddie Hearn
[Applause]
[Music]
I love Los Angeles how we doing okay
this is this is one press conference you
might not need me for which is good news
for you I just want to say thank you all
for showing up tonight this is a big big
moment I believe for professional boxing
we're two of the biggest stars in the
world battling it out just there at a
Staples Center November the 9th live on
the zone all across the US this is going
to be an amazing event and I've got to
say I haven't seen two guys today these
boys are ready first time around I tried
not to like this I tried not to be
involved I saw a sold-out arena
I saw 1.3 million pay-per-view buyers
and I saw a great fire but this time I
said a few changes no head guards 10
ounce gloves a real fire and I promise
you this time someone is getting knocked
out
on November denial unquestionably
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna pass you
over right now
I just want to know I want to get his
feeling we got this time last time we're
in Britain we have America versus
Britain this time is Britain versus USA
but how does the crowd feel who's with
ksi
[Applause]
[Music]
that's decent
who's we Logan Paul
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay before we go to the teams I
was just gonna get the corporate stuff
out the window the reason we're here is
because this amazing new streaming app
the zone of support this event
ladies and gentlemen MVP at the sound
Joe Markowski thanks Eddie
I think like most people on stage we've
all been a bit surprised by the some of
the negative feedback to this fight I've
disowned us say we are focused on
building one of the strongest schedules
in the history of boxing this event fits
right in the middle of that alongside
the big names triple G Canelo we
announced yesterday Anthony Joshua Ruiz
in Saudi Arabia on the set of the
December this fight as is cleared today
by the turnout the media interest is
right up there as one of the biggest
fights and the back end of this year on
the zone we look forward to welcome you
to the zone looking forward to
introducing you all to the broader
schedule we've got and we look forward
to a fantastic night in LA on the night
to November thanks very much guys look
forward to it right finally before we go
to the fighters we want to hear from the
training teams ok first of all we know
this guy
everybody knows let's go champ two-time
heavyweight champion of the world a
Logan Post trainer Shannon the cannon
Briggs let's go check yeah we hear now
yeah November night the first press
conference I told Logan real simple I
said champ don't really start until you
see him at the first press conference he
just seen him it's on disenchant we're
gonna be in phenomenal shape it was
Logan's first fight and guess what he's
pulling in front of thousands of people
the anxiety was overwhelming he went
into another man's backyard but that's
what now we home champ he's gonna be in
the best shape of his life he's gonna
tear my poor child
I guarantee y'all USA England is a great
country I love my people they are great
people around the world
I'm gonna tell you something my boy
gonna be more more prepared than any man
ever I'm giving you out my guarantee
Logan Paul is gonna knock that man out
cold
let's go champ a great fire himself
coming through the ranks and of course a
I saw his head trainer beat out Riley
[Applause]
that's cool that's cool no one's heard
of you for that last five years but it's
okay it's okay okay
all right anyway back to business back
to business back to business
listen I just want to say I just want to
say this is a big event as we we'll know
and being here from the beginning of
YouTube boxing I'm telling you this has
grown so quick yeah I do sometimes but
you know this has been a big big thing
yeah
2017 February 2017 ksi had his first
fight eight and a half thousand people
sold-out in London and now you'll go
bigger and bigger to the point where
we're gonna sell out the Staples Center
can size the champion will come in with
a strong team our team in the UK is
strong our team in the u.s. is strong
we'll have jeff mayweather helping us
out Larry way these are world
championship coaches we got leo new
helping as well you've got a strong team
so I want to say everyone keep sharing
keep supporting the event and uh
knockout coming for ksi on November 9
[Applause]
okay now to the most important people
the fighters the ones that make this all
possible when we sat down with the teams
I remember the look in the eyes of the
agents and the managers when I said no
head guards ten ounce gloves both these
guys said let's go I'm not sure whether
they know what they let themselves into
but this is a different different sport
now on November the 9th firstly we want
to head up to the stage one of the
biggest stars right now in the world
ladies and gentlemen Logan Paul
[Applause]
how you're gonna make me stand here this
year
I can't move around goddamnit
alright listen listen listen listen
who's excited to see me knock this [ __ ]
out on November 19 yeah I think so
hey even your fans want me to knock you
out cuz I don't think anyone likes you
your brother doesn't like you where's
that yet where the [ __ ] is dead yet
where's your family at last night I
remember you were hitting your mom on
Christmas and you got kicked out of the
house for that hitting your mom on
Christmas it's [ __ ] Christmas dude
where's your family JJ mine's right here
where's your brother JJ your parents are
at home watching this right now on the
screen and I got a message I got a
message for them zoom into my face right
now
mr. and mrs. ksi thank you I [ __ ]
love you for giving me the opportunity
to beat the [ __ ] out of your [ __ ] son
thank you thank you no head gear no head
gear ten ounce gloves you made me wear
headgear last year not anymore
amateur boxing dawg what bout do you
have this is a professional fight and by
the way JJ you're looking a little thick
and you smell like herpes I could smell
your mouth and you smell like herpes you
are disgusting you are disgusting take
the bandana off bro how many years have
you worn that bandana I can't take it
off because last year you glued it on
your [ __ ] head cuz you're a sicko
you're a sicko hey take it off bro maybe
maybe take it off take it off cuz your
superglue tto hey that was your wig bro
I had your wig nyah
your I've made a severe yes thank you
Wow I love how you cool it away from me
where's Greg
where's Greg Greg pool gp's in ohio
shoutout GP we love you dad
hey what he's Ohio Oh
who is your family dog there are you on
your parents house there you like do a
good lot back did they take you back yes
yeah and what about Deji good cuz by the
way your own [ __ ] brother said I'm
gonna win this fight and by the way you
know who else ever win this fight the
best boxer from your country Tyson Fury
said I'm gonna win this fight the champ
Andy Ruiz jr. said imma win this fight
ok nothing leaves in you make several
youtubers slash boxing coach
badal what the [ __ ] do you do make that
happen do you make videos you click man
in my face five times profession when
was your last fight in May you've had
one fight sit the fight your choice is
Loomis your two is loose your soup is
loose get a better tailor get a better
YouTube channel are you done are you
done I'm gonna respond to you cuz I'm
making a widow he's done all right me
too
I first of all before I talk about you
Logan I wanna talk about Jay let's talk
about a real quick
you you do want to talk about my brother
the guy you're not fighting I mean what
about you talk about the beauty of my
video saying [ __ ] ksi ok so but it's of
an F pH real nice real nice girl make
sure it's don't expire make sure you
don't make the kids you know upset okay
talk about semantics from somebody I can
feel like a [ __ ] cry-baby
take your [ __ ] cry-baby
yo talk to me this you're not fighting
Jake [ __ ] these a week these are weak
give me the [ __ ] give me something else
okay so I won't let me fight this JJ you
flew to America to do this hey yo no no
J I want you to fight Jake no no no
listen I want you to fight but I want
you to fight someone that actually makes
[ __ ] sense no one wants to see you
fight soldier boy we don't want to hear
I know what you see you fight
soldier boy no one's to see you fight
food seat you okay hey big whoop he
knocked down the clown that was half his
weight
hey Hank we boot this guy quick we lose
this guy that was the main talk to me
talk to me
fantastic say something important wants
to see you fight fouseytube
JJ be fine oh you take a year a half of
you two but you learn you pretty how to
talk after in it okay say something you
want to fight fouseytube
don't wants to see that so there's one
guy that you keep talking and diving
alright you keep making sure you don't
fight him and you know who I'm talking
about
I need some kid I need some kid we want
you to hold me
we don't want you find people that don't
know how to fight we want you to fight
someone that everyone wants you to be oh
I'm sorry
talk to me it's my to me okay Wow
Lu to America to steal good cool cool
Sjogren's we know it's coming where's
Chloe let me talk to you then all right
let me talk to Logan hey Logan how you
doing okay in this fight you're gonna
become and I'm gonna be the [ __ ]
coyote that now is [ __ ] all that give
it now you that was [ __ ] you just ruin
my day
you just ride good [ __ ] glide good
back my dog so confident that I could
beat your ass and I was like take a
picture with Drake post it on social
media I still win bro what do you yeah
not funny
yeah did you write that down did you
practice that drink we take a picture of
you food like hey yo you don't know how
to sell our events when I do my music oh
you don't know how to say you couldn't
sell out a 50-person venue in your own
country you ain't [ __ ] and you saw the
video safety person values what do you
do so how how about your challenger
games
I mean you promote this oh wow then one
challenge again on the charity event for
the Special Olympics well I've done two
charity events as well on time battled
out so what's your Excuse so talk about
the Challenger groans I've done it three
times and I've sold out
yes knowing your [ __ ] cool site man
you [ __ ] you had so many youtubers
featuring you promote the [ __ ] of it and
how many people came to the event the
charity they came like a tenner whole of
the whole track and field shares pretty
poor man brother you're a music guy you
can't sell out 50 per German you don't
know how in your own country events and
you don't know how to compete in event
with the challenge hey yo I'm gonna be
everyone yo ok ok so first of all whoa
easy it's what happens in this fight
that's a great question Eddie I don't
think anyone that watched that fight can
tell me KS is a better boxer you know
you're not you know you're not I got
tired my first fight adrenaline dump you
know you know you don't stand a chance
and that was when I didn't know [ __ ] for
months of boxing this year I got Shannon
Briggs on my corner
the two-time heavyweight champ of the
world what are you laughing about you're
youtubing boxing coach Vidal what the
[ __ ] do you do shut the [ __ ] up we are
working hard as [ __ ] to end this man on
November 9th cool most knockouts in
heavyweight history who do you have the
YouTuber as a coach the Mayweather's
newsflash you got the B squad you got
the B team of the Mayweather's
okay sigh okay I saw you you've had two
fights now this to us everything changes
I know you said you wanted no head
guards like i'm he just said that you
want it no why is he shouting [ __ ] and
it's Logan I mean this guy is the king
of child [ __ ] bro you like more than
powwow [ __ ] heroin like your baby's
pop culture revolution good job they're
not funny
just wait when I get my ring bro you're
gonna pound my face in repeatedly over a
we [ __ ] shits all you say please
stand up bro where'd your personality go
like is it easy
hey JJ has no dick change it has no dick
JJ has no dick change it has no dick
take your hands no tick dorsal bow
bro people are saying you don't have a
dick out there shabam hey your mom's
right there hey how's my day hey mom no
you got no dick hey I got one more
question before we have a final
head-to-head up here Logan Paul boxing
only twenty thousand people in the
Staples Center
we've got world championship boxing on
the undercard we've got Devon Haney we
got Billy Joe Saunders you get to
headline just there in this iconic arena
with millions of people around the world
you walk out into a prize fight what
happens and do you win this fight by
knockout on November 2 9 first-round
knockout first-round knockout you don't
you don't stand a chance
you know what's rigged you know I want
the boy you know the last fight you know
to the judges do me a favor
these next 55 days are gonna be the best
days of your life Oh take a break stop
training seriously Oh get up cuz of your
life
yeah after November now I'll be
miserable okay no JJ go go go skydiving
rope hey go bake a cake go fall in love
Mike I do something fun cuz your life is
gonna suck November 9
stand up bro is it over already
I want to sit what are you doing baby
have you given up
give me something dude finally I know
you believe you win this fight do you
believe two nd inside a distance ah
ultimately I'm gonna go in and knock him
out that's just a mother gas original
that's why I mean that's what I'm gonna
do I'm gonna go in and knock him out
[Music]
the objective of boxing you don't say I
won this one stand up like a man it's a
some [ __ ] that offends me what it's
boxing one about it's boxing the whole
Kong thing oh you're never my day with
that one yeah we're gonna have a final
head-to-head say huge thank you to you
for coming out here tonight November
tonight it happens in a staple center
last week and we're gonna come bring
these guys head-to-head right now hey
this was weak Gigi USA USA USA USA
hey yo real quick shout Simon cloven yo
the boys lookin real good man
the boys lookin real [ __ ] good jeez
jeez goddamn Oh your shirts dirty your
shirts dirty what are you doing
[Music]
que si a [ __ ] I got the mic
[Applause]
USA USA USA Wow this is this is very
excited it this is very exciting
um I don't see who want to watch this
fight I know I want to see it I feel
like I did a little bit too much but
that's what made me want to see the
fight even more I really see yeah you've
been doing this professionally for
nearly a decade when you see this unfold
on that stage here today leading up to
the big rematch normally happens leading
up to a traditional boxing match no no
it really don't but I feel like they
selling the fight and I've played a
series I feel like somebody's getting
knocked out first round
they're both claiming a first round
knockout now that's really difficult to
say I'm not sure whether they go first
or the six but someone getting knocked
off the stone they're still done as we
speak they're still on the stage they
cannot be separated I can't tell if this
is an actor or not now so now they're
smiling at each other but it looks like
they're still insulting one another this
is this gonna stop
oh well that's that's nice for the
children oh he had great reach yeah
75 it's reach that's Barry he's putting
on their each other's way right now I'm
sure all the fans there at home watching
on YouTube and right here on just hope
you're home for all the biggest fights
in the world Lauren Gardner Tubman
farmer here with you for immediate
reaction following what just unfolded
there on that stage let's take a look at
the tale of the tape here for a second
between these two guys we have both of
them similar ages similar Heights
similar weights but you just mention it
seven the reach
that advantage goes to Logan Paul yes
the Venus definitely goes to Logan Paul
up like you did great fighter who say
that youtubers can be fighters okay all
right well let's send it on over to
Katie who has one of our fighters all
right guys I'm here with a fighter
himself Logan Paul how do you feel after
press conference I'm disappointed what
the [ __ ] was that he gave me nothing lot
of trash that's the best he got I saw
the fear in his eyes he had nothing to
say he sat down what who knows who knows
body language watch his demeanor
the man's defeated already I I knew the
fight was gonna happen today and the
outcome will be determined today but Dan
he gave me nothing do you think you have
the home-field advantage here at Staples
Center yeah for sure my fans are amazing
my fans are absolutely incredible I love
them we're gonna be in LA more important
we're gonna be in the United States I'm
repping the US this fight we ain't doing
the the UK stuff right here Manchester
was tough for me a lot of people are
gonna question how serious were taking
this how serious are you about this
fight serious as a heart attack we
trained for four hours a day six days a
week that's crazy
yeah that's nice alright well thank you
so much luck and good luck November
night back to you Lauren thanks a lot
Katie yeah looks like he just almost
flipped a switch it was all fun and
games yeah when he was going
head-to-head there with ksi but then in
that interview with Katie Austin he was
serious I will quote him he said I'm
taking this fight seriously serious as a
heart attack does that make you feel a
little bit better about the upcoming
fight yes
he's he's taking it very serious
they six days a week that's a lot of
training how does that compare to your
training regimen Oh a tree about five
six times a day okay no Joe you tubers
can be fighters I'll play fighters give
you two but I feel like you do whatever
you want in the world I actually have
YouTube now seven for me yes you do did
you just plug it real plug it in a
second for first Katie see anybody with
can decide confident hey what was that
Nico annoyed well this is gonna be a
walk in the park man
are you nervous that you don't have the
home turf advantage this time no no I
don't care about that I mean it's a ring
at the end of the day and I know I need
to do so it's it's old if anything it's
more work for him because I know how he
fights now a lot of people are
questioning how serious this fight is
two youtubers are extremely serious and
that was a lot of trash talk you just
say one more thing to Logan Paul before
this November night fight what it mean
have fun bro fun you're gonna have mine
trust me thank you so much ki good luck
November 9th back to you Lauren thanks a
lot Katie well really similar reactions
from both of our fighters as we get
ready for this rematch following the big
press conference here in downtown LA
Lauren Gardner ton partner here with you
it dude I don't know I've never seen
anything like this this was like reality
television and I was here just to watch
it all unfold
maybe maybe Logan Paul learned a little
bit from standing standing because this
stuff that scene it Briggs do I haven't
seen it in a very long time I don't know
what to do with my president imagine
what's going on I think he was saying
it's all part of a slate of fights right
here on his own starting tonight with
Jaime Mangia we have Triple D triple G
rather we also have Canelo Alvarez
arguably the biggest name in boxing was
just announced yesterday that he'll be
worth fighting Sergey Kovalev
and of course all leading up to the
chaos night Logan Paul fight right here
at Staples Center and the biggest one
yet another rematch between the two
heavyweights it's andy ruiz jr. and
Anthony Joshua I was there ring sighs
ring side for that huge upset
msg it was absolutely incredible so
maybe we'll see an upset here we saw the
Twitter poll it was heavily in favor of
ksi so in your opinion Tevin if you had
to pick a guy right here right now based
on and everything you've seen here today
who would you pick this fight I would
pick Logan Paul really he's taller okay
I had the advantage and I feel his
energy is crazy
yeah pretty Energy's yes and that's what
fighters need okay so it was more like
his demeanor on stage he took over that
stage he grabbed the microphone there's
no doubt that that guy who's been
entertainer he's ready he's entertaining
okay I feel like they're gonna sell this
place out he's ready he's a fighter he's
not going to shy away from the big
lights here at Staples Center in front
of a sold-out crowd here in his own town
of Los Angeles California well that'll
do it for us here from Los Angeles
California be sure to tune in tonight
for the Jaime munguia fight live from
Carson California I'm Lauren Gardner
this is tavern farmer we'll see you next
time three million months ago in
Manchester England in front of over
[Applause]
I listen listen listen listen who's
excited to see me knock this [ __ ] out
[Applause]
[Music]
hey JJ has no dick change it has no dick
JJ has no dick mom's like then hey how's
my dick hey mom does Jenna know can't
tell if this is an actor or not now now
they're smiling at each other but it
looks like they're still insulting one
another this is this gonna stop right
now I'm sure all the fans they're at
home watching on YouTube and right here
on just hope your home for all the
biggest fights in the world Lauren
Gardner Tevin farmer here with
[Music]