what happened what happened become get
out yeah Kong it out but then he just
like walked back in and I saw Lydia's
reaction I'm finding out that Kong ran
away and then decided to pay us a visit
back so I feel like we're about to
experience that it's a new head of
security
good morning low gang was now that you
rescued calling any safe and healthy hey
buddy hey how you doing who knows what
kind of bad things are going out down
out there Lydia can you please keep us
safe we like to see your psycho no think
your psycho I'm fine you know the giant
night that's bigger than you but I think
like the neighbors also understand like
the need for security okay we know this
we're the strongest family on YouTube
bro if you're not a part of the low game
by the way make sure to subscribe to pop
we did the universe look at the shirt
get your March look and pull that cup /
up baby we just drop Baba it's not a
joke it's know just like did the
universe broke that the universe bro
yeah join the movement but yeah Lydia
get get the Stabbin hi cop god bless it
I got this is what I'm saying drugs
become exercise it's a good thing bro we
cannot really routine I don't even have
to have a gym membership anybody all
right you know the deal is done
[Music]
hey Mike are we doing you crazy savage
Oh buddy we're doing some really
exciting with you today I need you to
it's gone you need to calm down calm I'm
gonna paint a picture of himself but
we'll get to that later to the test bro
feel like she's not taking her jobs here
so we're on the balcony to Evans room
and now you can actually see Lydia she's
over the ledge here
so we're gonna put on this mask and be a
trespass so we're gonna see if Lydia is
up for her new job you know she wasn't
assistant now this is no joke like she's
protecting people's lives what if she
thinks he's here for like a meeting or
some not a meeting today that's guy
right there okay so we got the
bird's-eye view right now I see Evan
he's up top he's coming around let's see
if Lydia stops you're protective okay
we're gonna work on that Lydia will get
better but my man Jay bro also I stepped
in dog poop soaks two other yo this is
so funny so we saw calling actually
leave like it's a good thing we have him
back actually because my dog is about to
become an artist oh okay guys so this is
Sarah aka simply Sarah art she does are
we painted with her before she's like
really good at stencil stuff do you guys
remember this
[Music]
yeah like okay I'm still not quite sure
how this is gonna work brain can only
process so many things like one big day
Kong you're gonna be easy being artists
you can be Vincent van Kong non-toxic
not my brand is organic does not start
with an abstract piece no these are
simply Sara art this isn't you made
these look you can kind of see it looks
like calm kind kind of looks like in hey
I know that I don't like it we get his
feet is beat painty yeah no don't eat it
oh my god this is crazy
here you go calm no no okay oh this is
so silly Kong years from now you'll be
renowned for this [ __ ] all over that car
there we go car you're a good boy i boys
me doing work call you're a savvy feel
like this didn't work
feisty little artists come on car we're
gonna sell this painting for million oh
this is really funny I love doing oh
snap it's the moment of truth the
painting we just need our artist he's a
little distracted right now he's walking
himself ok Kong it's time we Vincent van
Kong is no joke Bruce Van Gogh did some
dumb cut off his ear and he's a legend
now telling me calling to savage paints
a self-portrait and there's sking Lee I
don't believe it hand me this oh no this
is horrible like I don't even know what
to do I don't know what a look this
isn't I mean it's a new neighborhood oh
god yeah we lost Kong he's gone I mean
have you seen Carl also why is your dog
wearing a jacket Arya have you seen
brother Kong where is brother Kong
where's your brother Arya communicate
with him via dog Kelly didn't eat this
he painted his final message what I'd
said was gone bro he's a legend he's
going down in the book he finished it up
cut off his own ear only thing he has
been thinking about or doing over the
past week has been going so my guess is
he's probably going to where he can
finally go the promise he'll like it
whoa
[Music]
definitely take 10% security
what's with the fruit with the root word
secure not secure insecure where'd you
go
did you get any good offers on the faint
thing you worry me Kong you think he was
coming back or was he just like no he
wasn't coming back he'll happen to be
going this direction
I think that that was like a holding
spot like he was gonna wait for all of
us to go that way to look and he was
gonna stab ya all jokes and lost puppies
aside this is actually a doe piece of
simply Sarah not so simple quite complex
animal also this is what the original
look like see it's on the right side of
the frame have young dog you sign it
it's your big day it's horrible
you're so bad at being a dog car and
that's why I don't know hi guys I am
gonna give this away so what do you guys
the loge a go to my twitter at logan
paul retweet the tweet with this image
you could win a Vincent van Kong
masterpiece
thanks again Sarah
[Music]
oh my god all this steak looks so good
oh oh I know I know that if you get food
from a restaurant you like have a girl
over your house you have to make her
think that you cooked it you got to put
out a place yeah there's no girls going
over but still look at this presentation
[Music]
me just makes me happy as do like boobs
or something but like y'all I'm glad
you're here kong-kong
you make me happy too bro and guys all
this happiness reminds me I forgot to
mention today maverick dropped another
piece of Merc
oh my god Pete says of merch not just
one we didn't emerge closet look around
Lydia you did an excellent job of design
we got merch we got murder bang bang
bang bang bang bang
I do actually leads me to my next point
guys we just dropped like six more back
back starting with this like blue
sherbert backpack yo this is say my case
Oh Oh Mike's wearing the gray version
ever guys we're so out here these are so
led to the highest quality backpacks in
the game and this blue Tiger one it
doesn't come with Cong but it is still a
dope backpack and havoc on the front and
the strap and yeah if you're a youth and
your in the low gang these are a little
bit smaller here Evan try this red we're
not looking good I did the other iPhone
giveaway we got this new iPhone se Oh
our lucky winner is Samantha Taylor from
Texas man thank you for buying the merch
in the 48 hour window I'm gonna sign
this for you what so you wanna give away
a new iPhone bro so Bernie laughs well I
didn't I didn't do it Logan you see you
so anyway Samantha we're signature in
Hollywood got a brand new iPhone X
coming your way like why is this an
issue now like you didn't know this
happen I had no idea do you even want in
the lab oh my god
what
what do you what keeps you so busy I'm
sure this guy Logan Paul yeah still just
like yeah I think we put it back on
security huh yeah well that's the worst
time to be out there you're vulnerable
if we're vulnerable if what if we're
vault loves my kids beginners so we're
we that's why we hired yeah he's right I
have promoted you security detail men
keep us secure Lydia you know my brother
had someone breaking her sauce the other
day this is no joke you're not gonna die
you have a big knife
just use the knife dohsa Lydia's been
slacking bro so we're gonna put it to
the test again I'm starting to think
like Lydia's not quite made out to be a
security guard so we're gonna put it to
a test again but this time at night and
this time with some real danger like
someone's gonna try to break in they
could just grab so here we're gonna do
that we gotta make you look at the back
I like these black gloves will people
never see me let's get Evan let's put
this plan into action
okay the robber cam has been started you
guys just go we are gonna man the fort
over here yeah this is it
don't let me down don't let us down Mike
looks like she's texting what's new
ideally she should be looking around us
because something anything can anything
good happen like this no oh this is bad
this is bad he's right he's right
[Music]
they never saw me coming just what
robbers wear no no it's like it was
written was going yet cuz I wasn't
expecting your milk quickly there's no
test in this world don't think it's not
happening it's happening the job no
they're dead I hate to do this I really
do you're just not fit out to be head of
security
you can be my assistant again yeah
you're just not like to be honest like
this this can't be happen again like
Lydia we both I like all jokes aside I'm
gonna have to bring our old security
guards back and your fight you're fired
yeah okay okay low guy that is Oh cop
your new back we got plenty of them
Logan public ops last shop or link in
description the hottest highest-quality
march in the game every single day we
are out here dancing the you it is no
joke
and if you're not a part of the Logan
make sure to subscribe to us family on
YouTube and guys I'm going to do buy it
soon I'm having a meet-up November 11th
to Dubai Mall and it's gonna be the
biggest meet-and-greet Dubai has ever
seen I want to see all of you there I
wanna meet all of you I want to get the
crowd just chanting okay it's gonna be
says gonna be awesome so I cannot wait
to see you guys there with that said
okay I love you yeah yeah
I met my I met my brother said I met my
prime we get up
Hey