today I'm going to movie movie movie
about to go to set for my movie the
thinning yes it's the sequel we got to
finish yeah your boys an actor guys I
get to punch people in the face just
like I want you to subscribe if you're
not a part of the low gang punch it in
the face literally punch the subscribe
button and if I joined the low gang the
strongest family on YouTube now as you
guys know yesterday we brought $11,000
worth of snow to California who's doing
it bro I'm sorry I'm getting amped up
because literally guys today's a very
physical day on set for me a lot of you
you know winter's coming in and probably
don't be afraid to step in the snow why
do you probably get to see and witnessed
and experienced over here in California
it's not a thing yeah it's fun dude this
was for my music video my Christmas dis
track coming soon literally being edited
right now the Mavericks waste no time
baby
which reminds me right here you see this
here dead the universe right on the
shirt that's what we do and today I'm
denting the universe by not wearing
pants who's doing well Lydia as usual hi
I've made a mess I could be I don't know
death in the universe how we do now if
you'll excuse me I gotta go become the
world's biggest entertainer
yeah I don't know how to feel about this
on movie sets
Hollywood professional movies got a
little sweet you're welcome and you fill
my boxers before I gotta do it but I can
get more makeup you're still not wearing
pants what give me pants I'm pretty sure
they give what are those those it's now
my merch this is like a super like
secure safe like cleanliness ility sighs
what'd you give me been just an acting
technique like a no pants rehearsal they
gave me I'm really good
apparently some of my fellow actors
aren't as fond of my thighs as I am but
okay right now it's time for me to get
fakers and put makeup on Hollywood baby
guys I'm just kidding everyone knows
beauty comes from the inside that's not
a joke but I will say I'm still not used
to this whole makeup thing when we do
the under eye under eye makeup right
here I have to oh my eyes like this
would look like a deer in headlight this
is also the face I make when my side
chicks called me out for having a main
chick see it's like kind of like a panic
but like still like let's hook up time
to face tends to work tends to work
serious scene you guys know this but
don't love being serious but I have to
do that's what acting is my character a
Blake writing is coming back
[Music]
Seaver I couldn't do it for too long
I can be serious for like maybe two
minutes at a time but one thing I forgot
about the actor life when I'm acting
it's hard to vlog music videos I can do
photos I can do interviews I can do it
but acting it's like you know I mean
there's only like literally I mean
they're beating people's asses right now
Sun is setting look at it's beautiful
and your boy is probably three minutes
into a vlog so I brought the a-team
[Music]
funny story about Lydia we made a joke
about her being pregnant as you guys
know she's pregnant I'm not and she said
she wants to name her baby
Logan jr. because why Lydia why did you
say that while you were nervous about
I'm not saying it's why you said it just
came out your mouth and now it's a thing
Logan her Logan
his roommate tweeted at me I know no I'm
just ruining people's right oh god I'm
sorry
calm down yo there's no better way to
pass the time
[Music]
Lydia ties we made it on the roof that's
cool but your boy is more seen so weird
going from traditional acting to a
vlogging cuz I'm vlogging I can control
stuff well I don't actually don't
control their zooms Brennan controls it
go ahead and zoom nice hi you'll
definitely get there one day
sorry about my squirrel
anyways pay attention kids open your
ears I think this is actually a valuable
lesson so nice and special about being
able to literally just make your own
stuff like the magic the beauty the gold
comes from within so like the vlogs for
example like yeah the movies cool it's
great I love acting what it ain't of
love bro it ain't the low gang low gang
when I mean this I say it I love you
you're damn anything Spanish como estas
that was how are you you be quiet while
your daddy shooting a movie bored be
quiet he's such a savage
I told you your boy was a chef beating
ass today Kong calm down
good boy guys we wrapped up set but we
aren't done with the vlog just yet what
we're calm calm down Jesus man anyway
it's time for you boy to go home let's
get get you got your shoes yeah the boys
back home guys it's midnight right now
would you best believe I'm gonna deliver
that content now what the my mom could
be in there stop how would your mom be
in there who knows
Mavericks man a custom mattress Geoffrey
Logan Paul Logan time to get your ass
off that my current mattress brand and
smashing 2018 with your own brand that's
marketing these people are maverick
oh wow it's pretty comfortable smashable
I think so yeah I can't lay here for too
long they're about to fall asleep Rossum
is such a long day whoo okay so let me
tell you what I'm thinking this pretty
cool I can't believe the snow is still
here guys it's the end of the day we
live in California why did not know this
could become an actual issue like I
thought it was cool at first but the
neighbors are apparently getting pissed
at us cuz we have snow in our driveway
for the microclimate oh what a
microclimate please educate me Brendan
what the [ __ ] is a microclimate it's the
fact that the snow is having guys this
is a microclimate and the snow is
affecting stuff the point is now if you
got it right if you can't erase it
embrace it
Oh a head I do
it's just like it's humping the garage
door so what if we blew through the
ground on the other side of the garage
let's go but there's still hope you can
unsubscribe any bigger shovels gonna
help you thank you we got a harder with
the shovel snow this is how I made my
money in high school I would literally
shovel driveways like that's how I was
able to afford my first laptop to edit
on Hammer equipment everything and now
look you may have know your partner you
don't start like a local pool on the
victory tuber of the world
I guess so much money that microscope of
my house I'm doing eclipse Oh for
content Oh
[Music]
oh this is coming together bro heaven
you could sleep in here yo
despite my messy-ass garage this is
actually working wanted to happen
yo it's Ashley say cheese in here Oh God
alright okay that is the end of a very
weird I'm signing off of the day
oh also guys we just need 14 releases we
are the fastest growing channel to ever
live on the YouTube platform guys making
history every day if you're not a part
of the logo make sure to subscribe help
your math merch the hottest stuff is
merch and again it's getting cold on my
phalanges soak up all that cosplay
shopping link in description low gang I
love y'all
oh so roomy but I'm cuddly with my boy