good morning Mavericks morning buddy
hi young doggy how you feeling puppy
what is a good boy
[Music]
Kong don't try this at home buddy
you okay no okay good morning okay
what's poppin oh man
the twenty seventeen year review video
where do I begin I guess I could start
with this twenty two years old I bought
my first house for six point five
million dollars and moved my two boys in
with me so II but I wasn't quite
satisfied so I had a koi pond foot in
painted the walls of the guest house
what a giant shock known as the Yeti
bought a school bus and then turned it
into a cool bus install the home theater
system more material objects guys the
point is I bought a lot of things
including this Rolex hey guys anyways
2017 was the year of Logan Paul this was
my rocket fuel year hi how you doing
this will see here that the two first
names Logan and Paul became a household
name before you make your judgments let
me stop you guys the legend Muhammad Ali
once said it's not bragging but if you
can back it up Wow
your boy put a dent in the universe this
year let's start with number one
internet domination low gang we became
the fastest channel to hit 10 million
subscribers in the history of YouTube
ever
[Music]
it took us 333 days and I got my diamond
plaque this is pretty cool but the
plaque was only a small representation
of how strong the low gang truly is
realize our true power after we made
history by shutting down the Dubai Mall
with the biggest meet-and-greet in the
world yeah
[Music]
next level guys 2.8 billion views on
YouTube this year even old people know
who I am
I also continue to break down the
barriers of traditional Hollywood as
Internet star turned actor political
even chattier than me named Mickey Bowen
in a movie called valley girl this will
be my first movie going into theaters
it's coming out next year June 29th by
the way so say the day react was
produced by MGM it's that that lion that
roars yeah that's the one I also did a
movie called the thinning - it'll come
out next year around the same time on
YouTube red so save that day - then also
did a second season of my show Logan
Paul versus I went on an episode of Top
Chef I did a demolition derby I've
wrestled an alligator I dressed up as an
old person for the day and went to a
retirement home oh yeah I hitchhiked
from Canada to Mexico and I was the
mayor of a small town in Louisiana for a
weekend and lastly let's not forget
about my movie airplane mode starring
your favorite social media stars coming
to YouTube Reds in January I don't know
if I'm alive
yeah so that's cute that's fufu
but the biggest game-changer for me the
thing that helped me build all of this
was when I started the hottest clothing
line on the market maverick by Logan
Paul we had our first maverick pop-up
shop in New York and we shut down Soho
for three days straight
he's insane seeing everyone joining the
revolution and following the brand
literally we possibly work City Kings
about 40 million dollars because the
planning wasn't the best that's my bed
New York I also took my shirt off hit
head what's new
but it's funny because the second pop-up
store was actually on a first class
flight to Dubai and just a little
forewarning I don't think I'm allowed to
fly on it again throw me off the balloon
but it's all good cuz that was fire baby
Wow
life is amazing guys I've learned a lot
this year too and I think even though
I'm a young charge everyone can take a
piece of wisdom with them from my
experiences cuz I've done a lot of guys
I believe that life is all about a
mindset it's about perspective or how
you look at things for example check
this out hey so for me guys the grind is
real like I'm barely sleeping but I
found what it is that I love so I
started saying I don't work but I work
hard maybe start thinking like this I
don't have to go to work
I get to go to work right I don't have
to go to school I get to go to school I
get to learn think grow better because
not everyone has that luxury
needless to say 2017 was absolutely
crazy but let's go rapid-fire for a
second cuz here are some things I left
out I shipped my roommate Evan to Paris
in a bag I crashed france's first ever
Saturday Night Live I don't know with
the rock again I faked my death and then
got kicked out of my apartment for that
but then I moved and then also got
kicked out of that apartment too I
officiated a wedding I filled my
brother's pool with slime presented a
Billboard Music Award filled my bust
with balls caught a homeless guy trying
to steal my bus and touched reptiles
with my mom
yeah yeah so I also have the Secret
Service arrest my brother Jake
I also made a diss track against my
brother that got 200 million total views
after I released the second verse in
movies that's your fans watch with their
baby CD but that's only because he made
a discharge against me getting ish he
didn't mean that we both ended up
apologizing but we did perform the
second verse live
like I said though guys we made up with
each other like actually love the kid
Jake I love you sidenote
don't use us as examples when it comes
to how to handle at your family that's
beef that should have stayed offline but
we're both stubborn and our egos are too
big okay I met a boy band named why
don't we I adopted them as my little
brothers and directed a music video of
theirs they got 30 million views then
made a song with them they got one
hundred and sixty nine million views
that you what you trying to do
guys I also made a song with designer I
flew a fan to Los Angeles to make a
music video with him I won two Teen
Choice Awards and then for the Tennessee
to watch the solar eclipse then I made
it on Jimmy Kimmel and then I broke a
Malibu Gotti yes I broke that and then I
went to the tallest building in the
world the Burj Khalifa made Oman okay I
got a dog named Kong I got tackled at
VidCon vacation in Hawaii got paparazzi
down the beach in Hawaii that wasn't
cool by the way I gave a little gangster
tattoo bought my roommate evident Rolex
then bought him diamond grills bought
myself diamond grills got crazy at
Burning Man flew to Italy to surprise my
brother got arrested by Italian police
about the biggest pumpkin in California
dropped it use the crane to take a ride
down my new Street drop 3000 pounds of
dry ice into my pool I made 40,000 tons
of snow in my front yard surfed down the
street on the Christmas tree put a
million Christmas lights on my global
bus ha and if there's one thing I've
learned
they say life is short right but this
year I realized life's not short
you just got to do more
[Music]
here's some other stuff I learned from
this year number one exceed expectations
it's not overachieving but it's always
doing that little extra step to impress
people to the theory of yes but know
where everything is possible until it's
not and even then it's still possible
number three your team your squad the
people who you surround yourself with
make sure other people who are willing
to put their heart and soul into every
project you undertake and people who are
just as crazy as you
[Music]
[Applause]
and lastly be different be a maverick
don't be afraid to go right when they go
left that's how you dent the universe
what is no-one else doing
it's called market-making personally my
goal isn't to be the biggest actor in
the world or even the biggest
businessman I'm gonna be the biggest
entertainer on the planet so I gotta do
both and it's so crazy because the scary
part is the part that most people don't
understand
[Music]
I'm just getting warmed up and at the
end of every year I hope I can stand in
this planning today of my life
[Music]
thank you guys for watching do yourself
a favor and join the low gang the
strongest family on the Internet
hit the subscribe button get your lab
emergent oh the [ __ ] on flash shop I
love you I love you I love you and I
will see you
[Music]