[Music]
with medicine dripping into my arm right
here
my mom chopped up some ginger for me
thank you mom
oh oh honey I'm vegan rose honey vegan
is honey vegan a lot of very good does
it come from a beat but of bees and
animal great
my brain is hurting a yoga morning okay
so what's happening here guys but ain't
nobody got time for that okay I got a
really horrible so I'm hoping this giant
liquid bag of vitamins amino fuel me
through this vlog that's what I'm here
to do my job is to distract you from
your busy life we all got busy lies we
all got different stressful things going
on but I'm here to hopefully make you
laugh and smile a little bit so if
you're not part of the low game make
sure to subscribe join the strongest
family on the internet and my hoodie
says it that's always plug cop yourself
some map emerge the highest quality
March in the game Spencer matching yeah
oh my god my mom got the legging things
Logan Paul background slash shop or at
link in description join the maverick
movement now guys you guys know I've
been gaming right I've been playing
fortnight every night because my game
room is not complete yeah I've just been
sitting here playing fortnight it's
getting pretty bad
last night I do yeah yeah that was
because I'm gonna be streaming on Twitch
at Logan Paul was taken if you want to
add me one why'd you call it that
because Logan Paul was taken no really
though I'm just trying to get good at
the game so I can I kind of have a
backbone to my to my streams you're
honestly sick right now
some games you think that's why I'm
saying it a little concerned
dude I caught you it's like I think 12
to 14 hours
and I think there's a future here
Spencer you look let me show you guys
the game room real quick I don't show
you guys a little sneak peek just a
little bit I the Maverick game room oh
no more yeah that's gonna be lit you
have a real issue with me playing this
game I'm a 4 neighbor play this game I
don't what what if what about this mr.
real-life bro 49 real life huh I'm
saying I knew you'd be like this bro
and so I prepared for this oh my god it
applies I guess you could call it a
supplies
surprise surprise did what I went out
and I bought real I fortnight supplies
and a lot of people although you've
probably heard about foreign I may not
know like what it is even me like I'm
kind of a new I mean of course I still
Huck it but the typical fortnight
character looks like this right yeah it
kind of looks like me right noticed the
chiseled jaw how you doing ladies so we
went to the army surplus store we got
some more stuff there and you got some
more stuff and some characters in the
game and have like angel wings so we
bought a $300 pair of angel wings so
yeah man I think we just get dressed up
and we started cause yeah
[Music]
look like a fortnight we talking about
my swag and my street cred anyway so
we're so ready right now and literally
feel like a foreigner kid do I look like
this guy like that was the goal he was
the inspiration for this I feel like I
do so now that I'm looking and feeling
better than I ever have in my life
like they look watch his jump dude okay
that's pretty a lot bro watch calm
coming in hot hey hey there jack wait
you're Jack I'm the for tonight
okay so yo when your first play for a
night when you first off the game
there's a okay can I get a second here
guys how do we there's something so cute
following us around all the time tragic
I swear to god it's so hard to vlog he's
just always right here just barking
looking at nothing oh yeah when you
first start the game this is bus it's
called the battle bus here's a picture
of it right here and you so you jump off
that the characters jump off that and
they fly into the map and I was thinking
I was like you know do you know anyone
with a giant blue bus Spencer uh you I
do have one right and it's right there
right yeah yeah bro the cool bus is
gonna become the battle bus I'm not even
kidding guys for my first stream I want
to be in this thing
screaming why while its raised like a
hundred feet in the air but we'll get to
that later it takes a little preparation
anyways right now the characters like I
said they jump off the battle bus into
the map that's what you know anyone who
likes like jumping off stuff or Hawking
it
the inside the horn that bus looks like
how can they fit a hundred people in
here man it's a good thing I am not
claustrophobic do you think they get
nervous before they jump out that's why
they got up Ella's in Paraguay yeah yeah
a good thing I brought mine okay yeah
definitely gonna hug you with this thing
I'm feeling nice and good feeling safe
yep I think this is my stop
all right guys
[Music]
[Applause]
quick we got a collective life no wonder
this game is so difficult to master
[Music]
[Applause]
some news my character stops alright
love going that is the vlog but wait
first lend me your ears for a second
guys I have some important things to say
I don't know what yeah they're called
air pots you're doing some business
calls they're like you're pretty pretty
cool I don't know how I don't know I got
stuff staged just let me say thanks I
mean go ahead what guys YouTube
apparently I just this is a thing going
on you may have heard about Heron if you
are subscribed to a channel sometimes
you don't get notified that the new
video has been posted look guys I don't
want this problem happening to me so
really next to the subscribe button this
little bell I need you to hit it so it
looks like it's ringing right then you
will be notified that I posted a new
video on because yet you know so yeah
not only am I gonna stay subscribe to
the channel also ring the little bell
next to the button hey thanks welcome to
the family number 2 guys this is a big
deal the original maverick t-shirts like
some of the first ones we made March
Madness is happening right it's March
maverick Madness is now happening to $10
original t-shirts limited time only guys
so make sure you get it we've never done
a sale like this before we probably
never will again so yeah $10 maverick
madness t-shirt right now Logan Paul
calm slash shop or link in description
join the maverick movement and lastly I
just want to say guys my birthday's
coming on my birthday's on Sunday April
Fool's Day and well it's even better
guys it is going to be the one year
anniversary of maverick by Logan Paul on
my birthday we're gonna have an amazing
cool special drop for that so be ready
for that literally a movement it's a
revolution we are at this point
worldwide and we're pretty much
unstoppable at this point anyways go
gang I'm rambling now I love you I will
see you tomorrow
[Music]
safe to say didn't thing about the
cleanup on that one oh boy I feel like
these are gonna be here for a while