[Music]
hiding our garment it's a good day yet
another guy I'm not gonna go to the
Opera it's going to be yet another good
day heroes Olga Pablo guys we are in
Santa Monica look I got Lydia she's a
tiny little girl I got Brendon as well
what up it's a fun day like we haven't
had a day where there's like stuff
planned for us that's why the vlog to be
almost like a long sketch but today bro
okay you have no art later today I am
performing with the why don't we boys at
the Roxy theater my first live
performance here in Los Angeles and be
singing help me help you and then maybe
the second verse we're not going to plan
on doing it but like in New York when we
got off the stage this happened this
Danny second Hurstville obviously I had
to give you guys what you wanted we sang
the second verse probably going to
happen again today but knowing I had
that just like it's gonna be a lot of
fun a lot of energy wanted to bring the
squad down I think we're just gonna
chill in Santa Monica go rollerblading
just hang out there guys you know this I
don't come to the beach often what I do
I want to be festive oh this reminds me
when Jeff was drunk in Hawaii running
around with okay yeah it was on fire
giant cannon so this is like a thing
here in Santa Monica and when I look at
it I can't help but just want to sell
Lydia in time it was a bit so perfect
fine I'll do a hello lemon shape pepper
this is more like circle oh oh I think
I'm gonna suck yeah well I'm sweating
it's my nose dude oh oh oh this is
something my nose a little mark yeah I
know I can't believe your head fit in
there how about that good start to the
Dyke you're Logan you got somethin on
the back your neck here bro what is it
is a cannon its cannon it's definitely
cannons out of a [ __ ] oh it's a giant
white version of cause uh awkward okay
this all you just need call me dick [ __ ]
come on don't come to the beach off so
when I do I want to loosely good bro
what's up G
I'll take one more extra moles on my
mouth please the sky blue there's a bear
poop in the woods a lot more subscribers
and my brother up coming in fits up a my
group cross are you kids right now is
your growth oh no that's a giant version
of calling yo I like your dog got a dog
like this but he's smaller in bed thanks
for my mall with extra mall and whipped
cream on as I sip on this Moulton thing
life is full of hard decisions such act
got cruisers pass our smoothie timers
mountain bikes for everybody kids like
full compression small tennis canons
baby debrief it or lecture Boise
trailers cave which pump utilize so many
options guys but I think we're gonna go
with the Cuba because Q stands for okay
I'm gonna go ahead and rescind that and
say no now if you ran my credit card
boat straight up a decline in my portal
and my good bro okay thank you video do
good bro how about this poor cube or did
you go through it would be okay oh I
thought it was rice go oh thank you Mike
you brat oh my gosh look at him go
could it be me one day Hey
there bro when you get all the girls on
this cute boy haha my big day oh no this
is dull door oh no you get one of these
is a new house dude absolutely by the
way guys we are making updates on that
new house we're looking we're out here
we're grinding I promise you you guys
know it's going to be savage it's going
to be maverick gonna be rude so again
you know my favorite thing about
vlogging in public - everyone - and how
here so guys we got Brendon rollerskates
we can film we're going to keep up them
out yeah you're looking good on the cue
bike Lydia why do you think it's called
a cue bike yeah it was a little more
enthusiasm more like yeah okay we'll
take it all right let's get riding good
[Music]
I was cool under the gun so I am I still
craving it paid off more than I appoint
I think I'm definitely gonna catch it
wanna go home one of those
[Music]
oh man ma does what I would say yo I
also thought like this is a good like
solid time to practice for tonight in
front of some low gangsters maybe little
brother Dickie gotta roast me what
little brother standing on his own way
ha ha ha ha gonna be too late tonight
turning the good old [ __ ] you have likes
and Brendon stress on me what did you
say we're over the black you're standing
on 20 bucks
oh it's a fact of life growth I've got
like this is this is awesome this is a
good luck sign I go buy more more some
extra more whipped cream on them I don't
need this someone gives us to someone
who needs it
there you go dude I appreciate have a
good day bright side to forward yeah
back from the Beach Boys as good as much
as we go somewhere I've been missing all
day oh I didn't know it should be that
I'm always doing it what was that well
yeah well I don't understand us be
telling no what do you want you saying
sweet speaking on things like English I
might at least unless come to a stop
problems I got so far deputies nah I bet
it'll speak dog I do mom I was good day
but we found a thumbs okay right yeah
guys I did notice that this is a
bracelet I bought for your mom for
Christmas
yeah what's the occasion mom what's
happening tonight us we're going to a
concert
Oh performing so why don't we boys
featuring oh he has noticed when I shot
the merch cannon I shot a wig out of it
and it looks just like a rat's nest oh
wait it just how much like my hair
this is why it came out so powerful
these things like leaked into it is
going to be sold out hmm
sorry bro happening tomorrow you know I
miss you guys we still haven't found
Evan yeah as you can see I got him a
virgin see I know I know you know where
he is
yes you do yeah oh he's lost he's a door
no yes it is
a door I'm everyone keep being a dick
and poop on my floor yet oh I see you
well I do hope you know you can't go in
that little Hall I don't know what's in
there
could mean drop I want to be the best
dad for you that I can they've just got
a new dog you have to still be better
than it's just what we do call you're
part of the low caste Jake's dogs new
name Apollo
like the God exactly children named
demoting obviously guys since I'm
performing tonight there's no better
meal to prepare the ribs or that lady
blond man I'm blushing different no oh
why would you pick up a plate in my
throat you know whose house you're in
I've never made it anyway Deborah paper
Pizza time it's a new age guys it really
is the Mavericks are taking over guys I
mean you've seen it my blogs and the
internet other internet creators wearing
them are you guys wearing the March mom
dad daughter son aunt uncle kings queens
where are the merchants to fire that's
not just because it's cool and soft and
comfortable it's like this symbol
obviously as you guys I mean some which
is why I had to do some special for the
performance to know you got the gold
silver Mavericks cover never efficient
yeah ye man that's all I have to say put
this on look nice and spicy bi yo as you
guys know if you have not gotten the
merch yet okay Paul calm /off for
linking the scripture in the revolution
man this is no joke hop on the train or
get off go to work hello excited
[Music]
Logan why are you such a charge why do
you have sunglasses on it's nighttime oh
that's my brand deal with it you like
that joke MA she subscribes for sure
she's no Logan I have a question for you
if the low gang starts chanting you know
second verse second verse the diss track
against your other son was a reaction
like I know you hate the diss track you
would call me guys crying don't release
the second verse of why I do it yeah so
performing live accordion thoughts I am
NOT allowed to say what I think it might
hurt other people Wow
so that's that's bad I know my mom she's
she's simmering right now on the swimmer
of boil yeah good that what mom would
like two sons fighting against each
other no one so I don't love it being
performed but the views MA but the view
come I get it I get it
got manager Jessica let me go what did
you just say so the rock there's no way
to get you inside the rock sea without
anybody seeing okay gonna be cute from
outside the Roxy and we have a path for
you to go directly to the stage from
outside one song plays so literally like
like the songs are like running in from
an outside the rocker okay okay enter
the Roxy from outside never done before
[Music]
you're gonna hand me to my senility go
straight this I mean look I'm down bro
and then if they chant we do it it's not
chant and you're going back go back
[Music]
I'm hungrier than do I just wanna get
into about the traveling oh and here's
the random strike you still got my
favorite movie and you need to give it
me
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
this is back then about you I love my
WVW hm
so I could be here the whole thing
managed to just apologize I'm sweating
my ass off and I brought water brother
[ __ ] your mouth the fro dog is just
touched I got pump up Abba song makes it
tough dude I should have worked out
before at least like ran a mile or
something got a little warmer so again
you guys go too hard too I was trying to
match your energy who stuff me even for
the Mavericks Bush goddamn I'm on him
you understand the views now or any like
are you kind of angry a little bit
here's what I am mom don't like you
singing against your brother in any way
shape or form don't get me wrong okay
okay but it's energetic and the views
and the music and I get that if there's
one thing you should know you know okay
okay guys I'm at home with my sweet
sweet mother
I love the why don't we boys I was gonna
say it like performing with them is it
your absolute dream come true and just
like you know coming from Ohio and I see
huh like hi everybody
I also love my brother Jake like I know
I know you I don't know if you believe
that I love Jake it's just like the
Logan loves it's a high songs about the
energy not necessarily like what the
words means all you had to be there but
at the same time like this is what you
signed up for a while you're like you go
back to Ohio it's like doing that row it
gets me so high for when I drop my EP
and then I can go on my tour but yeah
I'm just uh fur okay I'll get your much
of what public onslaught shop doing the
low gang be am average subscribers
you're not a part of this family it's a
rocket ship headed to the top I love
y'all and I will see you tomorrow
take it easy son
[Music]
well this will be my thumbnail clickbait
wait back up