okay you are my ear oh you mean the
world to me come one Michael Paul put me
in one of your videos really happy well
I like you a lot I'm gonna fly you out
Delhi I want to make a song with you to
make the dopest music video from 2017
it's the fact that everyone has a hero
yeah and sometimes when you're tickled
just the right way you've got to make a
dumbass song about it fact so this is
that dumbass song double effect and
guess what I'm feeling tickled wait what
hahaha yeah he I saw this video saying
Logan you're my hero say and I'm the man
like I'm since ever Robert DeNiro I
don't know why though this kid looks
like a shadow but he talked that track
like a gosh-darn tornado the boy from
Ohio following his dream I'm somebody's
hero wow that's amazing and if you
really believe it you can do anything
you can go and start a movement look at
Martin Luther King no I'm not saying
that this little dude is Martin Luther
King but I'm not saying that he's not
it's not a sure thing you don't know it
I don't know now who are you to say that
that kid am okay
or even Kanye the point is he's a
maverick he pays his own tab
he don't listen to the haters who makes
laughs he took his neck out for me like
a full-grown giraffe now no wait return
cuz I did the first AB everyone has a
hero true hero people shouldn't have in
your noggin is my hero he is really nice
back so I went minutes all about his
life
what song about me is like no and that's
really nice yep hit me up if you ever
need advice job and here do you take the
math of merchandising a file everybody
needs to wonder idol I true yes my hero
we share some time for example this
Messiah
let's do something cool like a star some
crime hang with all the curls in
paradise but we have no ended life
decide my man is the savage I can see it
in his eyes it's true love it you're
really wise also really true but almond
eyes
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay enough of that time to start making
them sent back to the hero stuff let's
talk future 10 in 13 to 20 years we'll
both be President Stiller do talks back
we'll call that Secretary of Defense
not to mention will balance the federal
deficit and yes I'm aware that my Rob's
are super intelligent it's because I'm
in the zone I'm an avatar in my element
I'm a rug vendor it's a resident
everyone has a hero you know people
shouldn't happen here Logan is my hero
he is really nice so a minute song about
his life
what song about me is like Noah that's
really nice yeah hit me up if you ever
need advice job and here you take the
map of merchandise Lincoln file
everybody needs to one to idolize true
he is my hero we share sometimes for
example this piece aside let's do
something cool like go south to crime
hang with all the girls in paradise but
we have no women life disguise my man is
a savage I can see it in his eyes it's
true love it you're really wise also
really true that's why you're my guy
hahaha make sure you like it subscribe
mr. maverick Marge link is in the
description making music videos is dull
bro especially when you got a savage by
your side like and subscribe already
said that I peace
[Music]