hold up bro he said he wanted to it what
do you mean he wouldn't do it
Stannis said he won't deliver the
Maverick March this Christmas bro why
would he not deliver Maverick marches
here it's the hardest merch in the game
no no kitty stand up yeah Santa for sure
I got a message for Santa ready relay
this oh hi mr. Claus speaking down my
chimney homie that's a crime I'm
breaking in and met to read you just
past the line got no milk and cookies
here boy you ain't ready got a 2-ton
play yeah we called it the Yeti and I
heard you from the north but I'm from
Ohio
Christmas run the corner get your merch
Lincoln buyer love your Paul you use
your stock to put your marriage yeah boy
I'm the battery why you feel it hurt
yeah yeah oh yes I do in church oh yes I
put in work hey who's that tender look
in that take your gifts and give them
back fabric merch is where it's at got
the hey
what's up Taylor looking at you should
remove the belt back
you should get my new backpack throw
away that dirty sack did you come to
Minko
or did you come to chinko you know I got
that blingo year jingle dreams are your
reindeer on my roof man you're messing
up my shingles they call me LP this my
holiday single did I mention I was
single I'm addictive like a Pringle yeah
I'm extra like some sprinkles educated
then bilingual a we should boil em merge
oh yeah I rap that much oh yes I do in
church oh yes I put in work hey who's
that sound of looking at take your gifts
and give them back fabric merchants
we're exact got the hoodie kappa put
that sailor look in that you should
dream about that you should get my new
backpack throw away that dirty sack sees
you when you're sleeping why you
creeping in my room he knows when you're
awake who invited mr. food why you sleep
like a balloon why your life be pays
your food why you can't be super food by
your email still yahoo add your help to
make us to do let him live why you
play with little kids why you come
around my trip why your beard look like
a squid why you leave already lit why
yeah I read that Murch oh yeah I read
that Murch boom yes I do in church oh
yes I put in work hey who's that sound
of look in that take your gifts and give
them back fabric merchants where it's at
got the hoodie
what's up dinner look in there you
should dream about that you should get
my new backpack throw away that 30 sec
yeah I'm the new Santa Claus
in fact I'm daddy call me daddy daddy
Paul yeah Merry Christmas
[Music]