do you love Lana Rhodes that's how I
feel right now but I think it was
because of the wheel I smoked a little
bit last night I was stressed out hurt
my ankle it's a bum ankle now so it
sounds like you got two problems that I
can relate to you're a drug addict
you've also damaged your eye tank like
has a full-on machine in his ankle I
think it's part of a track there's rod
and screws and all that it looks by the
time this vlog is out that's my birthday
but I do want one thing for my birthday
someone please buy my Mercedes couches
[Music]
[Applause]
hormone monster brush hey it's me I know
what you're thinking about what genitals
so if you follow me on instagram at
Logan Paul you know I've made an effort
to sell my mercedes-benz couches I
bought them three years ago for forty
five thousand dollars each and I pretty
much hate myself for that because
spending $90,000 on the couch is [ __ ]
stupid but now they're ready to
disappoint their next owner so we put
them on Craigslist for 20k and waited
for the right buyer these were some of
your responses Wynn says ain't nobody
gonna pay 20k for that ugly pieces
Etha hedges says i am located in
Calabasas and we'd love to buy the
couches provided you could prove you'd
and I have Kofi 19 and you ease my
[ __ ] Thanks every couch so well like
nobody's gonna want to buy these as soon
as you sit on him you want to
automatically drop yourself into a pit
of acid Kong doesn't want to sit on
these dead every night every morning I
come down it's like god you're so
uncomfortable
michael says interested in not buying
the couch because I know Mike's ass was
[ __ ] on there with Lana or more
whether her name is Maria though I was
sort of interested in ice tarted to
actually think for once ah Logan's life
is happy like where's the axe is he
Logan bro no one's gonna buy the couch
so go suck a dick lol
I put this giant jawbreaker in the
microwave but not because I think
something's gonna happen I just like my
job breakers warm sure again I don't
think anything's gonna happen but just
in case you should know I don't know
anything look cool they cut the
jawbreaker perfectly enough looking at
this it kind of reminds me of my right
testicle cuz you're putting in your
mouth right now it'd be a privilege I
could do this to my own testicles just
like you guys I've been trapped inside
uh with my squad for some time now and
I'm really starting to wonder like are
they really my friends do my employees
like me there's Mike love his girlfriend
love and most importantly did Mac
vandalize my fine art well there's only
one way to find out the truth this is a
professional lie-detector test now I'm
gonna ask my friends some questions and
I want you to respond with yes or no yes
do you like me yes I'm scared
do you like living with me yes true
never had a sex dream about me yes you
have a crush on Omar from yes theory yes
true did you vandalize my painting no
why
just admit it I don't have anything not
did you write Banksy wasn't here on my
artwork no why were you jealous that I
replaced your art with my art no I was
disappointed did you pee on the wall at
my ranch lyin ass dog how do you like
being my assistant yes giant mountain Oh
No you ever had sexual fantasies about
Mike's girlfriend
Lana Rhodes
No why are you worried that Dave is
gonna fall wanna know you love Lana
ROK's yes did you actually think you're
going to be ksi ya crew does it still
haunt you that you lost no crew are you
a sociopath
no he believes bang bang give it about
skinny Babu I'll ever see what happens
before I do the scene that's it