Oh God it sounds like an old man with
letters how you guys doing most
importantly you yeah you young noogie
today's vlog is all about Kong to savage
guys if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe put your
face bro enjoy the strong family on
YouTube yo I got to stop exerting myself
you guys saw a second ago well I'm still
recovering from the sickness my voice is
disappearing and we're working on it so
I'm gonna try not to yell but I trying
to yell a lot so I don't know that's
gonna happen so now that you're
subscribed write in yesterday's vlog you
guys saw we went to Jake's house we
dumped some rotten fruit on his fall
well it was it was gross actually yeah
then when we left we were running out of
the house um something happened that big
giant and beer dogs the demon dog bro
this dog tried to bite avid and then he
had the audacity to come and bite me in
the ass
I thought it was just a saying brother
oh don't Frank your brother Logan it's
gonna come back and bite you in the ass
so I'm sitting here thinking right now
when I play with my dog look he kind of
looks at me he looks at the camera he
looks at and he's really confused but
not a Paulo man that dog was a frickin
canine he was a bully who barely knows
where he is
look at the confusion on his face watch
why is he you see why is he backing away
my dog needs work he needs to learn how
to be a dog otherwise he wouldn't do
that
I do nothing bro what's going on come
here come go fetch I just want an attack
dog man is it possible to train him to
just become what we need let's well
that's what's happening today
who knows when you're gonna need a
little Pomeranian who often skips leg
day and is 85% for to neutralize your
enemy so today there's no more games we
are going to extreme attack dog Kong the
savage doggie boot camp okay
drill number one young doggy you must
learn speed icon gonna start you off
slow one two
Wow Wow I think that is enough agility
training for one day check him out bro
he's already gained so much speed okay
the next lesson in the jungle a young
Kong doggy that was impressive but
everyone knows stealth is nothing
without a koala good job young dokie
Jesus Mother of God creating a monster
he's like the next Michael Phelps again
though back to the leg day thing we're
working on it yeah buddy you got chicken
legs he's practicing his stealth the dog
has lodged himself in the tree feasting
on the I'ma be honest with you I think
if he gets the attack portion down of
his training man we will be good to sex
figures are gonna come off I think it's
safe to say he's almost ready
most importantly can't have my guard dog
looking like a wet rag this is a
disaster right now so we have to give
Kong a badass that's honestly what your
haircut may call more attack dog ish
yeah we just wanna look like king of the
jungle
nah booty pebbles are gone and we finish
those this morning so that can't be it
this is a bonding moment you know I know
that tastes yeah tastes like my dad's
ex-girlfriend and clonking sloppy
seconds they're taking my joke way too
far okay ping chill I can't watch this
from ah
just show me what he's done
[Music]
[Laughter]
in the face area on the end of his stay
in the cut before you look at the rug
rat to your right
I've know I've been itching I've been
live streaming Paul was saying guys a
stream for net every single day bro
people saying where's Jorge bro guys I
followed
torch up his uncle's yeah you took the
words out of my mouth
this is actually good right I wanted an
attack dog he looks vicious I think
everyone here including me
I think we're judging a little too much
for howl we know his attack dog skills
which by the way we've got a full day of
training okay so you're right you're
right you're right so we gotta put him
to the test with I've thought of this
all day a simulated robbery
oh yeah no he can't understand it let's
just head ruff ruff ruff
you just said ruff ruff in rougher and
the subheaders in the video you both
sniff that Bell he can't read didn't you
guys decided to speak dog over my dog
huh blow your cover put a helmet on or
something so he doesn't recognize you
were robber close bro
gosh already stop it George good this
good while he's in the zone bro no I
mean you put that back bro
while he's in there so let's go
downstairs get ready for college let's
just place him and then tell George to
come in and see what happened karma has
to bite his head off
okay so George
he's about to break in the house for our
simulated robbery simulations are you
ready for this
[Music]
oh hello gang that is the floor it's
good to have my boy back in the vlog
thank you bro free [ __ ] I like you a lot
Georgia my friends like your company if
you're not a part of that low game make
sure to subscribe some active one in the
face kiss it on the mouth Jabba on
Android the strongest family on YouTube
now with the strongest attack dog on the
internet make sure to do so Logan Paul
calm slash shop or link in description
it's the maverick movement millions of
people around the world who joined it's
about being different it's about
changing the world
one day at a time by working hard and
doing you that's what's up baby low gang
I love y'all I will see you tomorrow
take it easy BAM
I don't know what kind of character that
it's