oh I feel good I felt good and then I
had four bowls of pasta not feel like
I'm gonna yeah yeah oh good morning
little gag was popping okay his update
time you look you look who's filming
it's uh Spencer it's there's a reason
it's it's literally just me and Andy in
the house evany I don't even know where
Evan is where's your location again see
you later I was in Colorado Springs her
and then Spencer and my new assistant
Danny are both actually at wedding
weddings they freak me out it's a sign
of responsibility mature aren't you
you're gonna be my position at your
wedding it's like a big thing right
you're the best groom it means you get
to stand next to me thank God Andy so
yeah it's just
Andy and I today it's gonna get a little
walking you guys see the title we got
new neighbors yeah this is a big deal
guys they are dull so anyways guys if
you're not a part of the Logan hey how
you doing my name's Logan Paul this is
Logan Paul vlogs if you couldn't guess
and if you look down below the screen or
on the that's my dick down the channel
and you see that the subscribe button
does not have a D at the end it just
says subscribe not subscribe I make sure
to a smash the subscribe button for
that's my dick again back up here yeah
yes make sure to subscribe guys and join
The Strongest Man
it was a pasta overall just phenomenal
the vibes let me tell you and we started
the day off right with a little a little
cryotherapy session
by Logan some of the hottest McGee right
now guys I've been training really hard
every day for the ksi by August 25th it
is going to be the biggest event in
internet history this is a nice little
recovery session and guys I found
interest in the press conferences this
much so if you guys live in LA I want
you to show up I wanna be a spectacle my
nipples are hard
update my penis did shrivel off and I am
now exactly genderless but it's 2018 so
it's cool excited about the new
neighbors maverick I know kind of a big
deal so yeah guys this morning we had a
little incident
what can I just talk for a second you
miss me we had a look we had a little
heads we had a little bit we had a
little bit we had a little is there with
the humming I walk out of my room and I
hear like fluttering I'm like maybe it's
a mom you know sometimes the Mafia in
the house and then I look and there's a
little hummingbird he got trapped in the
house were you doing no hummingbirds no
that's not the way out any girl from the
door hey he's so close to the door oh no
wait what
first it was Huck I'm guys number Huck
the ducklings you have a duck we found
Huck in our backyard and now we have a
little hummingbird in our house how do
you get in here oh oh
should we open the door you know I'm
just worried about calm I'm just worried
about calm I think you're fine mmm look
be free bird
he doesn't want to be so weird cool
what's he doing oh this is so sad so
guys I actually have like a secret
obsession with hummingbirds
we put a couple hummingbird feeders out
back because I love looking at them I
love when they come by the windows Oh
is it oh no this is one of those
situations we're like what we do bro
then also we looked up he was gone the
hummingbird was gone oh wait what I
don't know I looked away for one second
he's gone what I don't know
so we try to chase it like any normal
human being and and he fell off the roof
oh no no no Andy what why'd you do that
[Music]
once he was going he was just going
quote of the year but he's fine right
no he's funny he's turned away ever so
and he's fine anyways guys he did he
signed it everyone signs the waiver when
they walked through those doors everyone
sign the waiver he did sign the waiver
yeah look guys we're getting sidetracked
we got to focus on the neighbors the new
neighbors it's a big deal bro this is a
big deal like neighbor Suzie dad yeah
guys my neighbor who lives out right
over there he made her an Instagram
she's got like a hundred thousand
followers now she's kind of popping
which makes me think makes me think
under we should ask neighbor Susie what
gift well housewarming gift we should
get for our new neighbors you know cuz
she's been around the block you know
neighbor Susie used to be a hit man what
yeah I believe it actually I have a
question we have new neighbors and I'm
friending them and I want to get him a
gift and I was wondering if you have any
house gift ideas a cappuccino
that's a good idea what about some sort
of pet using a fish what about a bird
exactly and we found a hummingbird this
morning it could be a sign I think I'm
gonna stick with the bird that's the boy
their names are actually this is a great
this is a great reveal guys I'm gonna
tell you right now are you ready Susie
are you ready donor five minutes away
down the street yeah
Susie it's a big deal yep that's the one
I'll talk to you later Susie yeah well I
think that went well
I like the neighbor Susie's idea getting
them a bird was that actually right yeah
get a cappuccino maker yeah well I'm
gonna get him a bird instead they just
here's the thing birds take flight right
they're growing up they're maturing into
adults is becoming real Mavericks some
may say bro they want to join the
movement might as well get them a bird
but that's not all folks there's more we
came to may be the best party store in
the world you guessed it front door you
don't like she hates party I'm here to
party let's go I know oh my god wait
Andy this all right you're gonna get us
kicked out if I was a grown man just
moved into my like first house what
would I want as a housewarming gift
didn't you already do that yeah what did
you want when you moved in honestly just
a large pack of condoms really though we
should get that for them Oh number one
cuz they're number one this is a good
two caution
slow Senor because I'm sure it's gonna
get pretty rowdy over there I think we
need advice from experts what's a good
housewarming gift for a friend champagne
okay champagne a bingo just like the
nice lady said campaign is like a common
celebratory item you know what we're
doing here you're Italian
well the champagne would be French but
you know I see I'm just not good at this
with the Prosecco pretty sure that's
good one more thing we'll get four packs
really George especially George I didn't
know he's that type of man oh he's that
type of man
George of the jungle condoms are the
whole lot of sex oh my god they're
joining the bird gang Oh pigeon Birds
some sort of penguin but the doves are
nice they have orange eyeshadow on yeah
so that one's sitting in the food is the
boy just when is the girl do the deficit
by him in a pair you should I'll take
them I will take five yeah there's only
two let's take two we're actually gonna
go pretty much right over to their house
right after this so I'm just gonna
assemble this cage in the parking lot I
know how it is this is what being a good
neighbor looks like yeah we just run a
dumb farm a tobacco farm out the back of
the Yeti oh yeah oh that was a bird oh
we got like a little compartment no like
the birds are here okay he's a free bird
there's one the eagle has landed
oh they're so ready oh they're so
beautiful don't worry Birds you're going
to a good home
it's the moment of truth my new neighbor
daddy's home
[Music]
reunited and it feels okay I don't know
the lyrics but I wish I was a part of
those yo if you guys remember we all
used to live together in Hollywood and
we would hang out every single day mark
and I were roommates for about 300 years
it was a fun time I was that was the
unlisted roommate it's actually crazy
and this house is beautiful oh thanks
yeah we had a white picket fence we made
it I know oh my god the American dream
literally when you grow up as a female
you're like no I know it's a female
he's got George you're actually like
guys they're five minutes down the
street they're actually kind of like my
new neighbors
I dig it you break anything really guys
these are all positive things can't
destroy my house I'll come you guys stay
right here I'm gonna get the gift
if he breaks anything I will personally
delete his YouTube channel goddamn
incredible who gives a unicorn no one
around here sometimes it wouldn't be
very logan paul of me if those are the
only gifts ahead they got one more i got
a one-way merch no no good guess but
super gonorrhea is what i'm not to give
you so stay right here and I'll go get
I'll save this for you
you're going a little too fast for me
slow senior no one's getting hurt
you know what you see you from this life
[Applause]
Lexi what a surprise
there's a reflection
domestic Hey yeah the two does a pear
tree
okay so dead eyes they don't make any
noise nothing right I guess nope not
even like that it's actually kind of
think about this this is like if people
come over oh yeah this is for showing
the house check it out it's a mouse
exactly bro and you guys are new to
Birds so I got you this dove packet oh
wow
teaches you how to raise them we lost
hell okay low gang that is the vlog I
saw they're vegan
thank you guys for watching if you guys
are part of the low game make sure to
subscribe I got some neighbors
did you take the birds with you guys
have a cop the hottest office merchant
game you know where to do so Logan ball
calm slash shop or link in description I
would have brought you guys some when I
figured the birds would do it for today
yeah yeah judging by the look on your
face I can tell you really appreciate my
gift oh my god the condom
[Music]