Oh see look it's to Lydia and I started
name with T's because your little never
not wear maverick a pair but if there's
one time that I won't be wearing
maverick apparel it'll be for some
charitable event something nice so
that's what I'm wearing today we went to
an epilepsy walk today for my lawyer's
daughter Audrey team calorie item Batman
that was my lawyer
Adam Cal look good dude super good dude
Mike put the merch back yeah bro and we
just dropped bottoms well beverage
matter buddy look I'm wearing the
performance shorts look I'm wearing the
performance shirt and we just dropped
them so that's a big deal I'm kind of a
big deal hahaha and a shot yeah guys you
guys know we just drop bottoms you can
get your bottoms at Logan Paul calm /op
in fire bro we got performance short we
got joggers leggings for the female but
I digress
yeah we went through this epilepsy walk
this morning was cool we took some
pictures for some little gangster
[Music]
sweet place will we
but you feel
oh just some plastic okay well yeah guys
it like I'm I should do more charitable
stuff like I definitely like it haven't
found something I want it's like a sink
my teeth into a hundred percent if I
participate that means I'm gonna have
you guys probably participating as well
and one day sometime very soon we will
change the world in some sort of
humanitarian philanthropic away but now
right now hold up hold up pause skirt
breaks they don't have the tram please
out here there's you have pictures I
mean we got options like what you think
know the chaplains was one great take
the 14 14 foot so while we wait for that
real good vibes today we had a cool
thing happen outside no it's just so
many things are going on at one Heaven's
back and he's doing audio for us thanks
there Evan know you haven't been in my
vlogs for 80 years bro it's good to see
you
good to see you Evan also oh here Mike
is making what you know what you're
doing these are cinnamon toast crunch ah
peanut butter with honey bites doesn't
make any it's made for you remember my
Mexican friend me Romano wampa yesterday
he said he broke the drone and we showed
the footage that the drone captured of a
crash it turns out we through shows the
wrong footage we have cameras so we got
the real footage here on the camera like
it hit the house dude I haven't looked
yet but I wouldn't be surprised if I
have to buy you house to this Evan I
need you how do you see anything all
right it wasn't here
I hurried away carried away that's good
there's no damage but yo it's not all
butterflies and buttercups here because
you knew she peed on the wall
she doesn't like me she just leaks ro
she just leave I'm just super stressed
right now
the good news is Lydia we bought yeah
you did we got you a gift I think you
should come see it it's your big day
it's your birthday calm down you need to
calm your ass down
okay all right here we go it's not a
joke wait seriously it's not 15 foot
tree actually no that's not your gift
this is a gift
Oh see look it's to Lydia and it stars
your name with t's because you're lit I
wrapped it I was here yeah I can tell
you dropped it
my heart's like racing I told you that
gifts not over I'm giving you a
promotion I'm giving a promotion I don't
want to get your ration so I want to
vlog it
wait promotion yeah we like my heart's
like racing Oh No here and then if
anyone comes you know what Gigi we're
gonna test it out here big day good you
failed
look pected than them who are those
people they're driving suck get a mic my
cab look see you can barely see it you
look strapped already go like she's
great this is good you just like stay
here kind of and just like make sure
like hold down the fort
we're gonna go vlog she's killing it she
can't be texting right let's talk to him
yo are you texting job your phone yo
it's a dangerous world Lydia we need
your help you need behind the security
nobody's here because you're out there
scaring the ball good job oh she's good
she's a good security guard
[Applause]
you may be small cool no that's actually
yours yeah we gotta build a trap Oh yo
Lydia's security knife is sharp oh yeah
yeah okay so we got these nice gentleman
to help us build this trampoline yeah we
are gonna put it inside I know my
brother did this it's just getting a
little dark out we figured it'd be fun
to jump from the balcony up there and
honestly you're probably gonna end up
getting like five more which we will put
outside and do epics with but this is
the least of our problems I think my dog
has rabies come on what's wrong oh oh
he's speaking language what language is
that
I don't know if he's been good lately
low gang okay we're gonna worry about
that a bit let's go jump on the
trampoline it's 15 feet oh there's a
much bigger than I also can't help but
think this was an extremely bad idea
tell her my name is Logan my name's
Paulie can subscribe and load up all
blood
okay okay that is the vlog we are gonna
do some epic stuff on this trampoline
the next like few days so make sure
you're subscribed only gonna give you
like a little teaser today that's what
this was my boys doing flips and cap
your Mavs immersed the hottest Mirchi
nah nah it's done worked hero bro the
hottest apparel in the game bugga ball
that cops last shoppers link in
description voce I love y'all I will see
you tomorrow
[Applause]
oh hey are you doing