oh oh it's so bad that's my boy it's
ruining my vlogs yeah you're my boy just
like ya Mary I know I know it's not me I
just have a bird named maverick and he's
dope okay
maverick he didn't mean that bro he's
your my boy he's my I got two boys I
know he's just a boy with you got a
March cannon you got oh my god haven't
you put the merch cannon down with the
merch cannon down Evan down boy down boy
did you change your mind alow going be a
maverick with the rest of us yeah every
day guys we are doing something that
makes us different unique or special
some maverick spirit we live it we love
it we learn it George
oh sorry did I scare you my boy how'd
you get my husband I climbed through the
window like Brendan's doing now come on
in Brendan yeah anyways how are you dude
how did you guys hear maverick forget it
are you hungry dude cuz I have this idea
I've been wanting to make this like a
certain breakfast food for a while do
you want to make out what anyway three
things I love for breakfast one banana I
love bananas - I love almond milk ahold
of you look at the merch bro Mama's
wrapping he's a maverick it's got three
Cheerios like you know those golden
honey o's I wasn't engineered before I
graduated college I didn't graduate cuz
I was studying engineering in college oh
for Logan's crazy right never let's go
and I came up with this really good idea
to like combine everything into one
efficient me but first we need the
material teach you a thing or two about
the dog team okay guys so usually we
would take up one man and that's one
nice banana if I've ever seen we got a
full-fledged uh banana here I'm gonna
carve out the middle okay so if you look
with your eyes you'll see the banana no
longer has a middle go ahead and save
this stuff for later oh you're just
kidding next up we're gonna take our
honey ode and we're gonna stuff this
banana like a teddy bear oh oh oh wow
that looks good I'm gonna take our milk
pour it in the groove here this little
canal that's pretty much it we got
ourselves in one of these oh well if
buyer likes right about damn damn like I
would definitely do this in real life
not as for the long seen the stripper
the gingivitis that looks better than
that oh my god wow that was the least
mess you've ever made in my house
coming from the guy who fills a giant
bathtub up with cereal bro well Jorge
cleans up this house that I kind of mix
up a little bit let's let's go driving
dude that's what I want to do good by
the way I did take one of Jorge's place
here we go good stuff I literally can't
hear right now that was loud I was
rolling huh
is that you it's okay locating we've
prepared for this by using a broom ha a
donkey tell me
[Music]
you know you know I'm not even kidding
I'm not even kidding
I just got in a car accident what I mean
I'm a little shocked I'm not gonna lie
you know you had me pretty hard right
there
we're in the middle lane I was turning
left yeah I'm aware yeah you didn't see
me
it says no left turn man yeah yo my my
forehead smack the window is it ready at
all yo I can't go out we need to get out
no stuck auto police are here the police
hold on one sec I think you're caught my
wheel I think you may be you got it back
stop stop stop stop I'm maintaining my
calm because like life is life is too
short to get angry over material objects
it's just a little disappointing but you
know blog life spice it up a little bit
I'm gonna feel this is horrible
[Music]
I'm shook like I've never been in any
car accidents
she literally just back no ways is
happening right now
she just ban I hate I might be king cost
I hit my head on the window like I I
don't want to say I am because I feel
like that would make it worse but like
I'm a little shook right now all right
team would you be able to move the car
yeah what do you want me to move it
[Music]
no left turn right turn only very
obvious one of the craziest parts about
this is how public this is like
phone number so we could Netflix and
chill Netflix and chill yet watch
Netflix hangout and also I can fix my
$300,000 oh it's so bad Oh while they're
figuring things out let's let's play
some life a little bit like a
description look about like a flesh up I
got a surprise for the low game you'll
have a submerge belongs to only one
person only one person and I want you to
have this because you're a savage you're
a savage didn't care if I was in the way
she said I'm going through them that's
[Applause]
why did you know but I died I need to
serve it cuz I'm not good bro who are
you give me a second of your time sure
I'll be the boy back one second bro Oh
sir
he said boy man from the UK I was like
bro they're not there why don't we boys
they're not the way no he's like I get
it mad respect but you either why don't
we were a big shout out to the low kick
for supporting me in this town
it's an interesting day interesting day
for LP this is Chris I love you too
literally hoppin right outside where I
live I'm like that's my parking cut guys
lo gang I'm just I'm sure bad things
happen in life and once she hit me at
the car shook like me first her Orleans
area but when she hit me my head slammed
into the window and and now I'm I've
never been in an accident before I'm a
very good driver honestly though what
I'm most upset about is that she didn't
take the savage shirt that I gave her
that's lit you know I didn't think I
would be this I'm pretty tough dude but
my head he's really hurting you hit it
pretty hard bro mmm hey guys I feel like
80% of my life I know one time you know
what make me feel better yeah oh he's a
look at what happened I don't know bro I
was driving and then I just some lady
keep on me like a steak medium-well
but thank goodness you don't have a
concussion am i right you're right
no I do have a concussion though I'm
believe you meant to say concussion no I
have a concussion
wow that is one severe concussion if he
thinks it's pronounced conclusion I
literally have a concussion
it's a cushion with ton but I also think
I have a concussion
how many fingers around me Jake Paul
that seems about right you're good well
I sit here in recover from my concussion
I'll show you guys something enjoy this
behind-the-scenes footage of yesterday's
vlog which uh how do I describe Oh yep
last night
[Music]
[Applause]
bit of a weird one today man daily
vloggers so interesting like a frickin
life dude for the concussion and have to
get your car fixed that you just come by
anyways guys do not forget get your
maverick mercy she's little Odin Poldark
on slash shop or link in description go
I'll be a maverick do something
different guys we're here to change the
world death the universe that's what we
do it is a movement guys this family the
low gang people who subscribe to me
every day thank you guys for joining the
movement and being unique and special it
different cuz that's what it's all about
man like who wants to be the same as
everyone else right we doing to do this
also um Teen Choice Awards for male web
star are for some reason the voting is
still open maxed out your votes you can
vote 10 times per day the link for that
is in the description hopefully your boy
you got some keep voting I think for
like another like can we I want to win I
want the world to see us on my
television and just be like yo what's up
flex love okay I love you guys and I
will see you tomorrow
take it easy fam don't forget to
subscribe
[Music]