before this video starts we are choosing
the winner of this month's $10,000
giveaway and beginning the Dodge
Challenger giveaway so go join the
Maverick club this week and get
automatically entered maverick clothing
calm okay enjoy the vlog [ __ ] alright
listen here it is currently 7 a.m. I'm
at my ranch and it is bro Lee's favorite
spot on the planet every morning he goes
outside on these adventures and we never
know where he goes or what he does until
today so we're gonna put this GoPro on
and see where this crazy little husky
goes come on these three buddy have fun
be safe
[Music]
huh okay I have a pie yeah and some
cream
okay green buy Wow all right take me
actually don't take me with you
did you see this horn yeah yeah okay get
off tick-tock No please give me a hand
okay
nice job thank you no make it stop and
those might be a little awkward you guys
are divorcing together dad was one thing
you regret about getting married to Pam
okay
regret about getting married to Greg
getting married you [ __ ] hear me
stutter I know I'm emotionally I'm
hurting how does that feel [ __ ] wow it
looks great though I'm sorry I ever
doubted you dad will you be my dad again
what do you think of our horse I'll get
you ass if you want I could use a little
ass okay I'm about to go for a horseback
ride after this morning I saw what
brother can do and I have the worst news
what is it you're fired
no I mean bro you got no horse cigarette
save some money just have my dog film
[Music]
I'm giving you a raise all right so if
you saw Ivan's last vlog you know we
found a leak in our 70,000 gallon water
tank on the property now although this
doesn't look like a big deal here's Greg
Paul to explain why this could be a
massive problem listen Greg you're the
groundskeeper how you gonna fix it I'm
not gonna fix it dad come on that's
terrifying yeah how am I gonna get out
don't worry about that you're thinking
these guys operate best by not thinking
and just doing he's not wrong all jokes
aside YouTube this is gonna be the same
mental challenge to overcome but it's a
good thing I'm only kind of a [ __ ]
let's do this last kiss
[Music]
Hey
you know it's just creepy
step one we gotta clean this
disgusting oh my god Oh dad dad this is
a big leak and placing the putty right
now
[Music]
before taking our water supply oh my god
oh hey love it I think the latter is a
little steep Wow cool you got old man
hands you're literally shivering for
real I think I have hypothermia watching
this YouTube video like it subscribe get
your very cozy
[Music]