hi my name is Logan Paul and welcome to
a new animated cartoon series of mine
called chach tails that's right I'm the
choch these are the tails these are all
100% true stories that have happened in
my life that I can only tell via cartoon
it is a new format no gang so I do want
to know what you guys think of it
comment below hit that subscribe button
and I yes enjoy it this one is my first
time making out sick believe it or not I
was quite shy as a kid I didn't hang
with the boys in my grade because I just
didn't get along with them as well as I
got along with the girls and this was
about 8th grade so the time that
everyone was going through that awkward
puberty staged the girls were like
taller than the boys every kid named
Adam had a mustache like oh god what a
time to be alive now this was also the
time with boys and girls and sometimes
boys and boys and sometimes and girls
and girls would start touching tongues I
thought making out was the weirdest
thing ever I didn't really see what the
point was but the peer pressure to start
lip-locking with someone was too much
for young Logan everyone else was making
out why hadn't I done it yet and then I
realized maybe it's because the girls
had all friends on me and they were
taller than me and preferred Adam with
the mustache and then who talked to me
about how their makeout session was and
I'm listening like what the [ __ ] how did
I put myself in this position well lucky
for me about halfway through the year a
new girl got transferred to our school
let's call her Kelly she was really
pretty and super cool and we ended up
bonding in study hall because she liked
drawing pictures of kitchens and I
happened to like looking at pictures of
kitchen to is a match made in heaven
soon enough we were dating which in
eighth grade doesn't mean anything but
we thought we were in love because we
both liked kitchens and I don't know I
guess it's weird saying it out loud now
but it made sense back then so one day
I'm talking all my girlfriend's who had
all made friends with Kelly and they
popped the question hello you know what
are you gonna make hell with her and in
my head I'm like oh [ __ ]
about that man this is stupid I'm
nervous I don't even know how to make
out she's taller than me and why does
that relationship have to be validated
by our dogs of course I played it cool I
told the girls uh tonight at the party
obviously and they're all like oh my
gosh we're gonna tell Kelly I'm a girl
but it was too late
Kelly and I had a make-out date at the
party that night
[ __ ] so I can home and immediately hop
on YouTube how to make out and for three
hours watch weird adults teach me how to
touch tongues with another human being
one of which is actually this video Oh
[ __ ] weird anyways I get to the party
and I'm locked and loaded basically a
makeout master and Kelly is standing
there fresh chapstick on Oh
so I give my battle call I marched right
up to Kelly and I say can I talk to you
upstairs sure you march upstairs my
heart is pounding out of my chest so I
give a second battle call but quietly
into myself and I say Kelly hey do we
really have to do this right now and
she's like wait you don't want to make
out with me no no I do I just I don't
want to be pressured to do it you know
like we should do it one more ready yeah
but we love Logan but Kelly the only
real thing we have in common is that we
like kitchen Oh Kelly I kind of feel
weird and we start sucking face I'm
using all the skills I learned from the
YouTube videos and I'm not sure like
whether I'm supposed to keep my eyes
open or closed and at one point Kelly
and I made direct eye contact and we're
just staring at each other she's like
licking my gums I'm trying not to choke
on my own tongue and after the most
Awkward 30 seconds of my life it was
over thank God
wow that was amazing yeah
truly remarkable Kelly goes skipping
downstairs happy as a clam and I'm left
in the garage alone and confused next
day the girls rush me like a herd of
cattle good and I had to be honest right
so I just said ah I don't know it to be
honest it seemed kind of forced and I'm
not sure I really get the point of
making out so she wasn't good no no she
was good I guess like I don't know what
does that even mean just leave me alone
please and all the girls left that was
once again left alone and confused
one hour later Kelly finds me in study
hall holds up a picture of a kitchen
rips it in half so making out with me
with pointless what no I just was I I
don't know Kelly I just wasn't ready
even though I thought it was due to my
hours of YouTube preparation I breaking
up with you I don't love you anymore
[Music]
that was once again left alone and
confused my heart was broken not really
but it still sucked and for that reason
I did not kiss another girl for two
years listen do not rush into
relationships you will end up staring at
your crush in the eyes when you're
playing tonsil hockey and you'll be
emotionally scarred for the rest of your
life facts
[Music]