mama mama mama don't fall I know you
look beautiful on the camera but do not
fall no what's up dude what are you
doing I'm back I know you see that
you're on top of me you literally
standing over me I couldn't wait to
start filming today oh wow yo Matt
respect the pro go downstairs I'll see
you down there in a bit start the vlog
good morning okay what do have some bad
news though how do I say this
okay cyber monday Black Friday guys the
20% discount absolutely slay so many
people join the Maverick movement too
many people too many there's no such
thing as too many this is actually a
good problem guys a lot of this stuff on
the website sold out I'm sorry I know
I've been saying it everybody want to be
a maverick guys there's no joke so if
you want to go buy something and it
wasn't there guys for me to you I'm
sorry but those of you who were able to
get the stuff before sold out
congratulations welcome to the movement
we are here being different being
Mavericks changing the world you guys
will see when you get the clothes and I
say it's the hottest office merch in the
game I'm not kidding literally soft as a
feather watch oh did that hurt oh no the
evil eye super so yeah guys if you want
to join the Maverick movement you still
can obviously we still have a bunch of
dope stuff in the side you got these
hoodies we got the black and white
hoodies it's still there it's all still
there and winter's coming up so grab a
hoodie you guys want to stay warm get
some socks we just drop the Red Sox low
deep all calm /op oiling in description
now Brendan I actually have big news bro
what's up we got a new roommate no we
didn't we did let me show you what are
you doing guys we got Postma little here
and we got Logan Paul hey yeah you look
no fun yeah okay guys if you saw
yesterday's vlog I was
I look like a thumb having a thumb with
like greasy ass disgusting practice I
came here to show Brendan a new roommate
you remember the new roommate yeah you
don't know I'm convinced we don't have a
we do it we do this is outside this is
not a room no bro mama mama mama this is
the new roommate
that's a praying mantis that's not a
roommate it is we can still be a
roommate yeah Brenda don't be racist so
Brendan this is our new roommate mama
he's a pregnant praying mantis that's
why we call her mama look at the ass bro
she got that fat ass she got that thick
thorax bro she's bursting at the seams
been living with us for the past like
week dude you guys replaced me that
quick it's not replace you we just it's
addition you know say hello to roommate
Brendan hi mama
yeah she's a beauty mama Red Sox
here's the thing so you guys saw I'm
releasing a diss track soon a Christmas
diss track in the music video for that I
wore an all red outfit using the the red
merch we just dropped and it's sick so I
sort of feel bad that the stuff sold out
so quickly but we actually aren't done
with the music video just yet he's the
guy who shot the video yo it's gonna be
sharp top like has dude like half
million dollars with a camera so this
thing can make anyone look sexy bro like
how do you guys think I do it this yo we
should we do that
no this cameras don't it's cool they
need a $100,000 camera base logging with
this for an hour
oh no I'm vlogging from $100,000 camera
right now Brendan Brendan how stupid do
I look bro it looks ridiculous Thank You
Ravi yo yeah it's heavy dawg but good
thing I'm yo look at these guns I mean
yo it's a fact that I'm out here yo
everything is so crisp look at these
leaves yo my succulents looks so good oh
the Statue probably looks lit oh my gosh
homie that's the moon
Oh guys if you're not a part of the low
gang subscribe right now
subscribe to be vlog on $100,000 cameras
Brendan you look so good right now this
is the move you always look good but
right now more than ever Buddha Oh
Buddha bootiful he's good yo Brendan
what I think you take the reigns bro it
looks good right okay what is it gonna
say I wonder how mama praying mantis
yeah yeah yo vlogging on a new camera
bro go for it stay really heavy dog I
told you this is no joke we're gonna
check out mama you look good though bro
thank you yeah bro this is the future of
vlogging like if anyone's gonna do it
it's gonna be the map this is how you
raise the bar and take it to the next
level yo you please don't fall mama mama
mama mama don't fall I know you look
beautiful on the camera but do not fall
no dude she's crazy she just jumps okay
so obviously this camera is beautiful
however it takes up so much memory we
can't record forever we are gonna record
the music video on this tomorrow yeah
here's what I want to do I want to take
snow fake snow because in California
obviously doesn't snow and just fill up
the entire driveway tonight and then
just have like a winter festival bro I
want to get like a sled off the balcony
this could be the greatest day of my
life no because you're pregnant you know
yeah having your baby students y'all saw
the vlog what are you gonna name him
you had a boyfriend at high school named
Loki that's why I say we're gonna put it
in their day if you watch my vlogs
alright time to do fun stuff
okay guys very near to where we live we
parked down the street there's like a
reservoir or something now we've seen
this on the map we've seen it we've
driven up to it there's cameras
everywhere we're technically not allowed
to go in but I don't really like to
follow the rules so I'm gonna have some
stuff do some spins do some jib moves
hopefully don't get arrested and just
check out this spot cuz we think it
might be cool so look at this guy here
it's locked as you can see okay so what
yeah if you think you can climb over
this Evan be my guest
yep that's yeah just watch out for that
camera that's pointing right at you ever
do that honestly think I could do that
here's that here's what we say officer I
had no idea
I saw a gap and I thought it was okay I
didn't see the fences saying no la WPD I
didn't see your giant camera and that
grappling hook that I brought is not
mine if you guys excuse me I'm gonna do
some illegal I thought it would grapple
[Music]
spider-man is that you it's just me
Logan Paul vlog boy hey Brendan toss the
camera no just do it over there oh you
got it baby care fingers yeah really
shady look 100% that building could hold
murderers who knows these are gonna put
their fingers up our butt it's a giant
frickin hill right the reservoir is over
now correct me if I'm wrong mr. Evan
it's legal
like how illegal like pretty illegal
like you could technically took the
water supply if you wanted to is there
anyone in this city that we don't like
we should just like poison this does
Jake live in the city no no no guys low
gang I like to push the boundaries I
know when to when to stop I mean the
penalty for this is like like like this
is actual jail time is like not-not-not
youtuber get out of jail time it's just
real life jail lawyers in the game below
this isn't like all my kids are fans you
can leave no this is like you poison the
city's water supply because your drone
fell okay so here's we're gonna do we're
gonna droney get the footage show you
guys where all the hubbub is about and
then just for street cred we're gonna
grapple something
[Music]
all right reservoir let's see what makes
you so important okay so I understand
now this is like an actual this is legit
we were down here at the bottom this is
crazy though this is this is crazy this
is beautiful you wanna go I know I could
go to prison for two years but imagine
the Instagram picture
oh man Eli here Evan clack your Rolex -
mine why does this always happen doggy
we hear the occasional bark other than
that you can imagine guys he's so hard
to see we're this close to him never
running away again apparently the guy
putting in the electric fence got
halfway done with it and wasn't able to
finish that was while I was in Seattle
and because of the holidays and
everything he's coming back tomorrow
who's so close and I can't even use this
his clickbait I've already had Kong run
away twice what are you doing bro are
you even good what do you have to say
for yourself Kong my life is like a king
snakes yeah yeah
now you don't move now you sit down like
you're a tame dog okay here comes the
adulting part of my life we haven't like
quite moved in you guys just oh hi Mike
I do there's so much was gonna clean
that up was gonna be responsible and
actually do something useful with my
life but I decided the truly responsible
thing to do would be to hire someone to
do it for me so yeah okay here's me
redeeming myself I doing some
responsible cooking you know how to make
steak
[Music]
slava stay a weird one today i think
it's cuz we know tomorrow is gonna be
like insanely epic like i said we're
gonna bring snow to California cuz it
doesn't snow here and I want to do like
a winter wonderland theme park thing I
mean the finished shooting my Christmas
distract music video that's gonna be
cool so if you're not a part of the low
gang you remind me of this piece of meat
you just you just are edible and you
suck so subscribe for me join the loge
ids strongest family on youtube also
copy or maverick merch the hottest sup
is merch in their gang bad news you
missed the sale or our black friday
cyber monday sale but you know it's not
too late you could still be a map a
movement of people working hard to
change the world by being different
passionate unique and not being afraid
to work hard to achieve their goals okay
I love you
[Music]
[Applause]
what do you have to say for yourself
calm