[Music]
man did you Jeff came by this morning
doing some business I gotta say because
I'm not doing this we're taking over
dead the universe always bro every
single day speaking of that y'all know I
preach being a maverick being different
right here maybe that's the Ambo yo okay
better than me anyways a lot of jokes oh
okay so this is why I bring this up to
em that's our symbol that's the maverick
symbol yo what is this bro Westside
hold uh is that what that is yeah
everybody knows what that is I'm just
looking at it it's upside down
if you do it like this you get that
umbrella can you see that it was a joke
what is actually kissing yummy I'll take
care of that oh that's not all right
baby how are you calm how are you oh did
you notice the other package we got the
mail over here check it out okay good
stuff next back use bro I'm gonna save
this for later in the vlog but judging
by the title you probably already know
what it is
[Music]
he's yelling about stuff as usual what
do you think rocking it do sky ride use
went down doesn't even like you
spin this fidget until it stops in them
a [ __ ]
having people love my jokes can we just
agree that people love us together
if you agree I'm the best-looking one
here I don't know granny what do you
think we got Kong Kong's hot for looking
at me is he dead car car hi
you're the best-looking one here whoa
you admitted it replay
you're the best-looking one no no no no
no replay already happy what stop the
mop is just too long right now like Evan
was kind of right this morning when he
said he had better hair than me dude's
got flow and I got no oh man my puns are
awesome anyways I need to find my dad
later and ask him like what's up with
the mop dude like why he got to give me
these mop genetics like what do you
think bro hey no more mullet Neko yeah
like I did with my finger guys have you
seen my Instagram story I've been
flipping machetes recently and I've been
cut like this whole side of my finger I
should chill but then again I'm just
kidding guys
yo the mop is gone coconut head his bag
cut off the list yeah I know looks like
I have a bowl on my head right now but
trust me once I shower do my thing it's
gonna be great good luck to four more
girls
have any playing game oh yeah no I'm
from Ohio
no but once I do my thing it's gonna be
gravy I just said it over there he must
I would watch the vlog here yeah what do
you think of my hair after I do my thing
is gonna be gravy though I gotta say
like that hoodie Lydia yo Brandon bro I
don't know what have you guys like what
what I didn't say anything is no no you
didn't cuz I'm trippin bro I'm freaking
tired low gang you guys know how I said
I think I might be sick I think I am
might take a little snooze bro really
yeah
I mean look this is a great way to wake
up he's such a savage man why so horny
all the time Carl oh my god he's just
like his father
my dad brought you sushi shot that is
that's right I'm not gonna lie low gang
up until this moment I had no idea you
love me ma now I know oh no I do I just
say you love me more than that
what's his name Jake I love you guys
equally let's say are you leaving
tonight yeah you go back to Ohio
oh the package [ __ ] what's in the bar
Ivan told me all day I know guys Brennan
asked me off-camera he was like yo
what's in that package for sure oh you
know I know so I see he's scared mom's
gonna love that don't not for her Lydia
look it's my big day feel like I look so
stupid right now so let me elaborate a
little bit in the light custom-made
diamond maverick gold pendant with the
Cuban link diamond Joe I don't even I
don't even know bro here's what I do
know how much do you think this cause I
might say it was every bit of 198 bucks
more than 198 bucks
I'm an expert in this stuff let me hold
my uh hundred twenty nine thousand
dollars oh Jesus Christ that's a big I
don't know how you went from 128 dollars
two hundred twenty nine thousand oh you
know what you said it is euro I'm smart
no yeah because that's
kevro Oh as if the Maverick isn't
already enough of like a power boost
dude performances in this thing music
videos in this thing oh my god yo this
thing brings good luck I'm starving
right now I did not order this did you
order this Lydia this food chicken matzo
ball soup
wow you didn't order that no it's like
if car were to have grown up and were to
have kept his balls maybe one day they
would have turned into those with my
natural honey cocoa butter brilliant you
know what's up with this guy bro okay
why are you distracting me with this
with the cafeteria hey hold up it's
gravy it's gonna be gravy where I
already said it had Paul Rudd or Frank
I'm love you pow saying dude why are you
not talking you're real boys dad Paul
how do you watch a dog dude there's I
fall or disagree you always have been
always will be where's the cocoa butter
stop with the cocoa butter Frank don't
you give me my own let me know if Mike
did create that you good for a survey so
go ahead oh you got bro what prove it
you said you got surveys you got I'm
pretty is this solid gold solid gold I'm
break guess how much it cost
that's my doing that I could get kicked
out of this place for like urine through
the halls and filming oh it's already
kicked up press release won't get pulled
out of things to spends money on there's
nothing left
oh you steal my building slowly you want
to try the other pendant you try to flex
that buddy yo calm your flex no spicy
ice god am i feeling good in this I see
Madrid kinda feelin like a king feeling
like a congress sad oh man we have too
much fun here I still want to show
heaven ah I didn't want this moment to
happen but my dad does have to go back
to Ohio you love me more than that other
kid yeah shut the front door crap it's
my big day car don't stop okay close I'm
just bored
everybody just spend money I was talking
to Jake about this too
cuz Jake likes buying cars and like
we're just bored and we need clickbait
and titles in thumbnail and also the
diamond maverick is just such a good way
to represent that beautiful bird yeah
maybe girls are finally like you and
like want to talk to you probably not
hey Avenue arse okay if you're not a
part of the family make sure to
subscribe hit that subscribe button
debby scuba scuba diving okay anyway if
you want to get the maverick merch Logan
Paul icons last shot at the logo baby
joined the movement joined the
revolution we are changing the world
every single day it's okay to be
different in fact I encourage it there's
this quote that has been said it's
really famous you may have heard it
before yeah
being inspirational anyway the people
who are crazy enough to think they can
change the world are the ones who
actually do okay low gang I love y'all I
will see you tomorrow
[Music]
oh god I'm the microphone that was