okay we're ready yeah it's just nice you
know being able itself so much much hey
oh good morning okay what's muffin sorry
I'm going right in my blog if that's
okay just wrapping up an interview with
Pakistan's biggest TV network it's
called ary digital also I don't point
out by the way I just wanna point out
dude do you hear that noise right now
just listen what is that
so that's been going on during this
interview they like nice soothing music
to test the fire well yeah as you guys
can see using no business money moves
bro everything's good the merchants
selling camel riding how does the
Campbells think about it alright guys I
stepped outside it is our last day in
Dubai that makes me sad if you're not a
part of the low gang first off subscribe
cuz I don't know why it wouldn't be how
can I say goodbye to things like the
tallest tower in the world the Burj
Khalifa this is nobody to keep this
angle I'm vlogging from this so they can
understand the extent of this building
it's incredible low game this building
is so tall it casts its own shadow in
the sky you don't know what I'm talking
about walk I just watch and look it's a
beam of shadow it doesn't make any sense
I don't want to go I got stuff to do all
right guys we're doing another interview
let's go back in the saddle my boy Chris
okay guys he played an instrumental part
in me coming to Dubai so he has his own
radio show on virgin radio here's the
day you for all your game please oh
that's what friendship continues living
in Dubai we have brought out some really
big artists we brought out like you know
the Kim Kardashian's the J Lo's that you
know Will Smith's and this isn't no lie
I've never had more people send me
messages on whatsapp say can we meet
Logan do you know where Logan's gonna be
Chris can we meet Logan boy I'll do
anything you can do to meet Logan boy
and I mean like nearly a thousand
messages in about three days I wanted to
change my whatsapp status to I cannot
get you to meet Logan ball crazy bro
you're the maverick Enterprise anyways
we're gonna do another interview and
then we're gonna go right Kim oh my god
we all we're in the gold district is
literally everything is gold oh just got
the back oh we got money so much jewelry
dude Jewelry George jewelry
[Music]
I don't want to waste your time I don't
want you away from my son point me in
the direction of the most expensive
watch you have three million dollars
what three million dollars
this watch is so expensive he doesn't
want to be seen with chopping wood in
Ohio put it on these films do much the
watch there's a three million dollar
watch sitting on my wrist
there's the watch time travel this is
three Bugattis oh this is very cool I
must say I'm confused why would anyone
do that
[Music]
oh yeah right now about four or five of
these pinkies you could buy my house
when I get a wife one day I'm coming
back for this mother this is I just
wanna say a message for my future wife
oh don't don't don't cheat I mean we
came in here I'm in Dubai I'm having the
time of my life I want to spend a lot of
money on something the presidential
Rolex is the highest they make president
of the company Wow how did you do that
you're maverick Oh like you you know
what I like about it the most
it fits perfectly on the pinky bro Oh
bro is my responsibility we might be
talking to a young legend and it's
turning 24 today happy birthday at
Brendan North on Instagram wish him
happy birthday
Oh
and diamonds for the birthday boy hey
squad feed you boy just chop 40k out of
presidents you're rolling home ha ha ha
I finally have a Rolex and not just any
Rolex yo come here let me spit some
facts Oh first off it's made of platinum
it's the most precious metal there is
the presidential Rolex too because one
day like who knows it might be President
the second hand does not tick it glides
it's called the sweeping take my watch
and there's no battery moves with like
kinetic energy so when you move like
this that's what power is it no
technology and yo as if it couldn't get
better we're back up on the highest
floor that humans can be in a building
in the world at the top of the Burj
Khalifa for 152 during the daytime all
my Gil this is incredible
you're doing some real mavar stuff bro
this this ring is actually amazing yes
if you guys haven't joined the maverick
movement yet first off are you good
don't be afraid to be different don't be
afraid to be unique that's what it's all
about
encourage you to do that every day guys
work hard accomplish your goals I
believe you can do it I believe anyone
can do it if they actually want it move
it's right here baby be a maverick logan
paul comm / shop or link in description
you already know it yeah your boy just
plug from the i's building in the world
over mom I'm out here are you proud of
me
[Music]
oh my gosh bye I love you you know I'm
gonna miss the content overload bro
let's go ride camels at the Safari
hello it's me or Habibi Logan oh look
we're driving out in the desert did you
like the classic Range Rover yo Habibi
manager Jeff and be a mentor to Jeff hey
hey no they said Safari I thought like
jungle but this is like the desert
version of a jungle safari I like this
already
[Music]
okay so next up they're doing a falcon
show yes like the bird fits yo cuz you
know like my average and everything but
if they never told you that the world
wasn't round once you flip it over you
playing poker with the Joker but let's
keep it coach
mama your son Finn and go supernova keep
your focus really I just might spaz out
in the place but that wall painting my
face
just run around in the face was like
I've been running in place and I got
hella clean of hilary's I'm ready
Madison do you know maverick the parrot
you're standing on a new Rolex how do
you feel did you vote for Donald Trump
be a falcon no this makes me miss Kong
dude just how does that remind you cuz
like
[Music]
take
she won't give it to me imma take you
know what there's Jeff that was
everything I've ever dreamed of we're
going a super cultural right now looking
good looking good looking good
I shouldn't be flogging someone put the
camera down because there's one more
thing we need to do today we have a plan
for him okay so when he gets a little
older he's gonna come out work for
maverick enterprises we're gonna demote
Lydia he's gonna be the intern and Lydia
is gonna be his assistant what you got
I've got the Beast
yo Suraj Viraj rise she's like a little
Shiraz manager Jeff we got matching
rings brother you know every time these
touch of Africa's born we are we talking
black diamonds bro thank you okay guys
this is sad it's our last night you buy
Christy the first serious for a second
my man we made history oh my god first
of all let's be very to speak from the
heart
okay I love you because you're a man
with vision you have guts
you you go beyond and when I asked you
let's go to the bye let's conquer it
let's make it happen you didn't ask me
one question you had ultimate belief and
you said we're gonna do it we're gonna
go personally want to thank you all your
low gang fans and I've never seen a
raving fan culture that you've built
because it really is a movement you've
touched people's hearts you've touched
people's families we keep creating
history and inshallah we'll hit the next
solo I've got to ruin the moment but
when you say you love me like you still
got a mouth every way like buddies no
real love it's heart broke it's just got
D by logo that is the flaw
thank you all for watching if you're not
a part of the little game make sure to
subscribe it's the strongest family on
YouTube and that's no joke merch always
plug maverick oh no with the two Rolexes
in all the Mavericks both kiss oh wow
Logan balls I can't / shopper a link in
description blow gang I love yarn I will
see you tomorrow
take it easy [ __ ]
[Music]
thank you
but you won't give it to me
[Music]
taking
she won't keep it to me how much shaking
yo she voted for Trump dude