I just need to find out at this place
like some kind of alien plate or like
say it's not good here we go you've been
doing this recently and I'm gonna have
to ask you to stop but still a judge oh
why I have makeup on I did a photo shoot
this morning it was kind of a big deal
but I can't tell you exactly what it is
yet my boy kong is back in my possession
I took him back from a car
oh is it car huh baby the little gang
has missed you using fake arm just
wasn't the same
oh my god stop Abby we hear you you just
want attention maverick you don't want
my heart
that's the Charlie puth reference it's a
good song see you later maverick boy
roommate Evan cameras which cameras
which cameras which yeah wait a thing it
oh no no I forgot guys David's gone
that's right he okay so Evan went to the
dwarf World Olympics he's super athletic
and he left us okay so I guess I'm gonna
hang out with fake fake Evan for a
little bit what do you want to do buddy
good idea your buddy
[Music]
it is not the same anyways what's
happening today oh my brother just
called me and he said someone had to
make a wish foundation is at his house
right now I'm assuming he didn't give me
many details but I'm assuming they
probably wanted to meet Jake and I maybe
I'm just a cocky piece is just I'm like
I said I'm assuming so we're gonna stop
by cuz he asks me to do that and then
yeah just say what's up
currently pulling up to Jake's house oh
hey what do I see right dang this is
nice dude Jake's got security now I have
a parking spot there is always always
the Americas brother J brother Logan
Paul yo okay so basically Haley from
Wisconsin named okay Gretchen she's the
best she's the best girl ever so
inspirational amazing she basically got
cancer in her leg okay and
they had to amputate her leg and she's
going through like a ton of like
hospital stuff okay but she's still
smiling amazing still grind as you
wanted Mimi or you know but her wish was
to meet me no no I'm just like a bonus
like a minor credit you're the extra
credit okay cool and our sister really
likes you okay okay come on all right so
I'm gonna be in in a sec I'm gonna grab
something from the come in
[Music]
dude I was like my Adrenaline's pumping
that you got the same horn as me what do
you do I got just a merch
yeah maverick market a little big
oh okay for lighter it goes she's a low
game caller yeah and she's like a Jake
low game ballin oh okay I see how it is
so like what do you guys think about the
fact that I'm gonna beat Jake to 10
million subscribers like spend more time
with you anyways cannot we just get like
a little group hug here your plug bring
it in that's amazing bring it like why
are you being so awkward
yo that was dope dude good energy though
like - I'm smiling anyways guys I am as
you know getting more into music lately
I don't want to train my vocal muscle
and get better at singing Stevie's gonna
teach me how to sing
yo this is happening stop here's the
issue that dog looks like the bigger
version of Kong I don't think he likes
it he just got his balls removed he's a
little aggressive sad day yeah yeah no
the system that I fired she did it oh
this is hilarious they're like the same
dog just different size this is like me
and Evan this is amazing oh speaking of
Evan Evan I never forget you buddy go
can't forget the boy can't forget him I
bro oh this is Evan yeah yeah he's all
quiet everyone yo I know fives but like
mom you got the stuff over there you got
Evan we got a piano
oh my Stevie now go touch you're doing
it right yeah okay guys here goes
nothing I got moral support Evans here
here we go that's good
[Applause]
[Music]
don't say my little heart out thanks for
the support Evan okay anyway go it's
time to go buddy
come on stop playing with that dog come
on wait what the [ __ ] hold on yeah hey
which one is co-op which one he's one of
you two for sure what stop stop everyone
stop feel like this one is calm yeah
yeah yeah you guys see you you can't run
cargo then who is that what is it what
are you bro are you good you want to be
gone this one's just posted up right now
it's a good day for Pomeranians
apparently come on Kong here right there
we go I'm not falling for it it's time
to go buddy we got to go home and grind
and grind is what we do okay no
something amazing is happening right now
no way get it come get it no keep
humping no I know you are no cause there
we go that's my boy I knew he had it in
him Eila can take your balls but she
can't take your heart in it oh do you
think YouTube is gonna flag my content
or you think I'll give just more
subscribers it's time talk about a
pressing pressing issue at hand the
to-do list we've been doing that a lot
of stuff but number six assistant it's
tough man I gotta find a maverick
somebody was like willing to do stuff
outside the box
anyways yeah let's move through the door
I heard you need a new roommate a
maverick I know that's false Evan is my
roommate he's right there I haven't I do
buddy assistant it's true number six in
the to do this I know someone who's a
maverick you know dense the universe
when they go left you go right I like
this yeah yeah yeah keep talking yeah
come with me what does have to do with
finding an assistant okay I qualified
for this job you're gonna be my
assistant mark there's gonna be my new
assistant no not me
I brought someone who is
whoa whoa weather would you describe me
and marques el stupido
what oh okay stop stop mark quick
sidebar I'm special hi this is very
awkward for me why I actually found a
new assistant like I already have one
like I was saying for the vlog cuz like
I was gonna make a thing about it but I
might as well just introduced her
because ninety minute really offers
miele the oily didn't work out there
will be the situation and also the fact
that haynes not spoil oh no yeah I'd
love to meet your newest is yeah here
it's kind of like hello mama's got you
watching my blog it was cool when we
lived together because we were both
six-foot right but now it's like I
everybody has to be able to five what's
going on it's it's dude it's true guys
Lydia's I think she told me for nine
that's the shortest one yet do I do I
make this better as if Ayla came over
and they stood by side by side I don't
uh about that I'm glad you could make it
I have not done anything stupid oh I
think you meant to say callbacks Kovaks
callback isn't that right how stupid Oh
me me yeah oh yeah like idiot all right
now you're just being racist surviving
say yo this is not right this and the
point of this vlog a little sidebar
Sebastian can you please my man you're
stepping on my roommate if you could
just say thank you I found a new
assistant and guess what
she's butter than you Wow
she bother than you Ayla this time not
yogurt and guess what she's shorter than
you know she is this swear to God
Lydia please right there she's been
saying what I don't know what it is mean
finding shore assistance I guess y'all I
just realized good things come in small
packages and I just know it I real you
try to turn my assistance against me I
can't I cannot well you can stay I like
you also quick little sidebar jack found
a way to stop Kong from humping earth
you just hold him he's so calm up here
he's still calling up there because he's
always calm pretty much anyway he looks
like the line calm
so Euler as my axe assistant who I fired
do you have any advice for my new
assistant Lydia yeah yeah like what
plates should I buy
I never was your assistant you never had
me I've never had a sister you're right
I see oh no actually know what before
you say anything else
this reminds me of some look near Linea
I got you some merch it's the Maverick
OD oil ah I got you submerge - I
actually made it a point to get extra
large so it'd be funny when they wear it
there you go
look it to be honest guys I don't even
know if oil is wearing pants anymore
yeah dude let it do like no she's a
person anyways guys Logan Paula calm
slash out for this but I actually have a
delivery over here that's a fine wine
China fine wine China a box inside a box
oh just don't say any words just watch
are you good I'm gonna find your family
and I must smash to recall the keys are
you okay no here's the bank resume find
out of this place there's some kind of
alien plate or like some [ __ ]
I'll be saying it's not good Pope here
we go wizard plates I don't know how
they don't break
that's the blog guys it's weird it's
weird vibes here you know if you are not
a part of the low gang make sure you
subscribe hit the button join the family
the fastest growing channel on YouTube
also yeah we are gonna beat my brother
at 210 million I think so that's like
kind of cool back yeah that's a fact
jack
also I'm avid merch link for that is in
the description join the movement and be
a maverick okay I freaking love you I
will see you tomorrow
take it easy fam
[Music]
this is this is my roommate Oh what is
that what is that oh [ __ ] how does a big
bug floor it out here