jeez stir hard we making movies well
well well it's 6:30 in the morning right
now little guy let me tell you a story
and today we're shooting a music video
for my Christmas song like two days ago
we released my other song no handlebars
thanks you guys are loving by the way
you know the music videos fire oh that's
like straight dabbing you guys love it
it's beautiful man I love hearing your
feedback also we just did the Maverick
red drop warning Crescenta Black Friday
discount on the entire site how does
Marin the game looking fall that cops
last shot but okay here's the thing last
night um you guys know I have a little
brother named Jake he came to Seattle
last night at 1:00 a.m. I was sitting in
bed waiting to go to sleep and little
brother jakey burst through the door we
started that Andy and I started that
that's our thing what are you doing here
Thanksgiving what the brah brah homey
it's 11:59 and November 27 put it down
in the books I'm sitting here I'm laying
in bed and I hear the pitter-patter of
Jake pop footsteps they were like super
unathletic like just pounding like
didn't hear the raspy voice of everyday
bro literally just flew in so he can
spend thanks I don't get you bro every
day I love you oh but like having you
around it's just like I'm so nervous bro
like when you kick through my door every
day bro you're gonna get lit up with
confetti or something no it's just like
at this point low gang I realize I'm
never safe he could be anywhere at any
time
like right now where's Jake where did he
go oh shooting a music video tomorrow
you you plan staying for that I could
just like do my thing sure I'll figured
since I'm getting up early anyways and
Jake's here why don't we give him a
little taste of his own medicine
you know the Italian
to put the chicken in the bed of the
gauge so chickens at my brother Jake
pause so let's go get some chickens hey
[Music]
good morning guys
I got one I got one
honey hi guys we got two chickens we
have to go quick cuz we got a music
video to shoot I feel like now's a good
time to say two things one a oh good
morning okay what's Bob and two if
you're not a part of the low gang and
joined the low game we have the
strongest family on YouTube we'll lay it
throw chickens it's all good stuff
oh snap we look good right theme cuz
it's Christmas on Melissa honey oh my
god yo so cute
you guys make me want to get a wife and
vlogger every day just ignore them
please Lamar Lamar come on come on
please all right guys we're gonna do
this music video and I should probably
spill the beans on exactly what it is
it's a Christmas song right but it's
also it's a diss track your boy is doing
it this track bro first shot of the day
guys you know how we do it we gotta go
epic with it so we got a giant horse a
big black hole his name is Diablo look
at her moment
guys they used to use these horses in
battle yeah they used them in war so El
Diablo himself has been in four Wars
actually survived both world wars and
the Civil War I've heard like 300 years
that's a fact the horse is much bigger
when you're close to it el Diablo I
can't believe I'm meeting a legend
fought in both Roman holy wars even the
way this horse is standing is sex it
like puts one leg back and just kind of
like post out its ass he's crossing his
legs this horse got a dog boys back in
the set oh whoa whoa easy boy
easy boy you name my vlog so people can
subscribe he wants you to subscribe he
said it not me
this just still grow it just makes me
want a horse now granted only I'm gonna
get a horse this big definitely guys the
mini horse I will start commenting what
do you think we should name the mini oh
yo he's eating my shoe ah yo easy you
know that's not for eating
that's not for consumption stop it ah so
I didn't tell the guy this who owns the
horse I actually don't know how to ride
a horse clearly I have no idea what I'm
doing
hey-yah blow blowing off to war nope are
you ready to shoot a diss track my boys
ready
[Music]
oh mylanta diablo you're a star you're a
big day you're gonna be famous on
YouTube buddy you guys you can all
follow Diablo on Instagram at Logan Paul
he's got great pictures
good good saturation contrast it's all
great artsy anyways thanks again Diablo
I love you yeah no big deal just calling
in my Tesla I know my brother has one of
these these are sick brought technology
Elon Musk good job dude anyways yo
Seattle ooh there's a seaplane which is
actually where we're shooting the next
scene yeah my planes in the sky
we got Tesla's kind of in-between cuz
they got wings what do we do chances of
dying higher not so much look I've lived
a good life if it happens it happens
just kidding I do have to finish this
music video first y'all that was sick
bro guys we were banging out these shots
quick I could compare it to the first
time I I could compare - yeah the jokes
ruined but I could compared to the time
I lost my virginity kazoo banging out we
got anyway anyway sister rap I'm a shot
on to the neck from the entire City of
Seattle this is my first time in Seattle
I gotta say I am pleasantly surprised
hey Seattle you look beautiful from up
here yeah yeah boy Brendan went home to
Boston he's having a meet-up he's
facetiming me right now and then Brendan
yeah he told me he was having a meet-up
and I told him who's gonna be little I
will see you back in a music video wow
we're not annoying yet but yeah it's so
sexy looking contrast with the red night
oh oh guys we're running out of daylight
but what's new is getting dark so early
I hate it no joke one day I might start
a petition I want you guys to sign it
low gang for life I want to abolish
daylight savings time bro Wow
anyway it should have museum
hi guys so this is a little hard to fill
because amar is driving the Tesla hey my
mic is gonna be shooting from outside of
it with the wing open by the way this is
Mike the savage he's the one making this
look amazing the Mavericks are gonna be
in the yellow mustard car yo how do you
feel about am are driving your mom
should be like real talk though guys I
cannot wait for you to see this dude I
love the music videos where you just
like throw everything together and go we
recorded this song from inside of my bus
from the idea to the writing to the
execution less than 15 hour and I think
it's gonna be late like all these shots
look amazing and I don't think the
internet is ready once again welcome
what's the issue Ahmad it says what we
have one Maya left well hold up the
Tesla's electric protons in the battery
charged no it's not because I need
forgot because you brother showed up
last night no no Jake apparently last
night distracted Andy and he forgot to
plug the Tesla in look at that yo so
what happens if a Tesla dies like you
can't have someone bring you gas because
it's electric and there's no like
chargers on the road we'd have to get it
towed we would have to AC and heating
and every oh this is terrifying
I know for a fact Elon did not design
his battery to actually run out of
battery he knows humans are dumbass and
I feel like he accounted for this we
gotta tell Andy
I think so here's some bad news and 8000
we got no models and a no and a we got
this I have no idea if we got this I
feel like we definitely don't got this
battery power very low oh boy
brother that's what we said it's Jake's
fault Jake
oh my god literally guys I had one
request when I saw him I go please stay
up I'm actually impressed that it's been
on zero for like the past five miles
Tesla bro you guys know what they say
man if you're Tesla's not dying you're
not living who says all right people say
I've seen it on the Internet Oh
looks like a house it looks like we made
it bro I have no idea huh okay so here's
what I think is gonna happen we're
racing daylight we now we need a tow
truck Andy we actually do need a tow
truck bro how we can drive 20 miles back
your house and
the horse house most things in my life
we're gonna worry about that later but
right now last location it's a tree
house it apparently that's just any tree
house it's like the tree house as you
guys know I'm getting a tree house built
in my backyard hopefully I can get some
ideas from this I heard it's epic oh my
god tree house just build a house
so Mike built this by himself I told you
he was a savage crazy you ever see
something like this tomorrow so this is
the last shot of the day I'm watching
some of the stuff we shot this looks so
good guys we've spent zero money on this
production and it's so crazy he's like
no handle bars cost me I think it was
like 80 K out of my hair was like 150
help me help you was another 70 and guys
this is all coming out of my pocket like
that's the kind of money I put into my
work but it tends to be that the stuff I
spend zero money on is the best
I want a billion views on this video
okay I won't breathe like look check
this out oh geez stir yeah we make a
movie who's doing it who's doing it okay
hello gang that is the vlog I cannot
wait for you to watch this and I know
what you're thinking Logan is that a
read Brandi oh why are you showing the
logo no it's nice I'm promoting my
maverick read drop now look of all time
slash updates red jaw drop top no
composer comes a shot no I'm so white
it's unbelievable as you guys know 20%
off through Cyber Monday yourself
submerged by your friends so much
everyone wants to be a maverick guys
it's a movement it's a revolution if
you're not a part of the low gang make
sure to subscribe we let Mike seriously
thank you bro straight-up you'll see
guys he killed it today Andy also thank
you baby
this is producer-director friend right
he helped me write the song and a
thank you for just being a sec okay so
they're gonna they're doing it again
yeah back over here alright little gang
I love you all I will see you tomorrow
take it easy
[Music]
goodbye Tesla yeah we're leaving it