Wow you can't be throwing paddles now no
[Applause]
[Music]
no I'm not constipated I just worked out
hey uh good morning low guy was Bob it
was a good day for exercise if you look
to my right you'll see my friend working
out with my mom and my dog being an
idiot it's another day in the life
what's up guys my name is Logan Paul if
you're not a part of the low gang good
make sure to subscribe smack the button
in the face master kiss it on the mouth
mwah
and joined the strongest family on you
through my man Ari is filming today
sorry for hitting you
oh the merch is looking good speaking of
mom y'all know where to get a Logan Paul
back on slash shop that's what this
channel is about it's about being
different it's called the Maverick
lifestyle it's about being new and not
being afraid to be you because that's
what makes all of us special except you
Mike I'm just kidding this channel is
about fun positivity I hope I can
distract you from your busy life of
10-15 minutes whatever it is so let's
get the day started
oh hi how are ya it's me Logan I know
what you're thinking looks how did you
grow your hair that fast guys I've been
working on it for the past couple hours
it's not looking good but you think I
can pull this off a real life-like
ponytail oh we were good okay I can
explain
kinda hello gangsters who have been here
for a minute you guys remember me a
while ago I told you we were making a
song but this is not just any song he's
not just any song this is the number
song today and tomorrow we're about
counting here's a sneak peek 1 2 3 feels
pretty good right had to put on the
Maverick gold pendant and tomorrow how
do I say this
helicopter ladder floating through the
air change like an angel that's that's
the best way to say that's why the hair
is blond and long you know how it is but
that's tomorrow today we got a scene in
the famous genders the number song I'm
telling you guys it's gonna make history
look at Frank's beer 2 ponytails on a
beard who's doing it so Frank does not
address stick now's not the time
what are you doing thanks for letting us
drive your car Andy if we break it Jake
will pay for it oh this is the dumbest
thing I've ever seen in my life this is
the worst day of my life actually is the
worst day of my life singing the song I
sing the whole song say God you need me
okay so a little background Frank
approached me one day he said y'all had
the song I said all right cool Franklin
what's it about he said it's about
numbers and Counting that's a great go
home and then he's like go just trust me
it's a good song I was like whatever I
was bored so I trusted my boy and we
went to the studio and ended up making a
song that people some people are saying
it's gonna be the number-one song in the
world oh I'm not sure if it's gonna be
the number-one song in the world but I
can promise you it's gonna be the number
song in the world I can guarantee it I
did some Instagram stories on the way
over here at Logan Paul if you want to
follow me there and I realize y'all I'm
a good-looking chick admit brother me 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17
18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
if you blog
you guys know we're shooting right now
this is weird of all the lyrics Oh
hugging himself god bless wow that was a
good day and I know that because my
pants are ripped you can see my really
though you guys saw that was straight
fire so this is only the first day
Mauro's gonna be exhausting like a
14-hour day Oh mom mom I want to show
you what it would look like if you had a
dog don't think so I think you look a
little like aunt Shannon more games guys
it's Monday we want to get the week
started off right so we are doing the
first-ever maverick annual ping-pong
tournament this is a big deal I'll tell
you why okay first off these are the
contenders we got missing play think I
my my father was Andre Agassi my mom
okay
Oh Lydia okay the Maverick okay listen
y'all don't know this yet all right it's
kind of a big deal play it for money
yeah the stakes at home speaking of
stakes we also do a stakes yeah that's a
big dinner
the other way for $102 tournaments on
the budget got this $2 bill I thought
it'd be cool to add Brett no noon okay
well I play for money more guys may have
noticed I didn't say I'm these names we
got a beautiful tournament board here
right all these matchups aren't credible
to come over to the champ section you'll
see that the champ plays Andy is
something you might not know low gang
when it comes to pink bombs and
to mention he puts his glove on his left
hand it's a big deal guys tensions are
high
who doesn't want a hundred and two
dollars okay first match of the night
guys looks like we got Logan Paul calm
slash now it was up maverick Bobby
versus uh Danny oh I'm moving on to next
[Music]
he threw the paddle at Frankie who's mad
that I want what did you do that for I
bet you got that broke mr. wide angle
lens bo can we get a replay you can't be
throwing paddles how I mean oh honey you
were never here what's the deal bro why
what what no top actually it looks kind
of good match man none of these
interruptions is just negative
interruption nobody really wants your
hundred and two dollars you could you
tuck it bro it's not even in play
anymore
[Applause]
oh no more flying rackets and when you
hear the sound of the Trump will be
saying yes
Hey
we come
[Music]
it's really stinks it really seemed like
that was really most competitive matches
every baby but you played me baby we're
gonna end the vlog there huh
Andy doesn't lose that's what I swear
I'm putting in that work you know I'm
saying you're not a brother looking guys
make sure to subscribe tomorrow still
shooting a music video are the numbers
song dangling from a ladder dangling
from a helicopter it's masters subscribe
button in the face of the game map of
merch baby logo paul dot-com slash shop
congratulations Frank you're the winner
and you're about to lose to me baby
wiener don't be afraid to be yourself
man that's what I'm always trying to
preach out here in these blog channels
type step low gang I love you
[Music]
this is what I mean Andie's glove isn't
even on the right
[Applause]