[Music]
my parents used to do this right for the
divorce they would eat together but not
say it you know it's no bro watching
without the vlog camera
give me cleaning my dogs do anything for
concept I did and you told me to get it
was my last dog without this time Gotti
my coyote you were supposed to accompany
I'm supposed to be an attache you let
him outside alone and just wrap around
like smell so Baro guys everything's
going great over there dude just keep
enjoying yourself my bad person maybe
just in general person for sure that's
specifically a mind bleep rack so wait
for a hack to wait for the next song
shut them up with water am i bad dad I'm
just worried cuz bro Lee hasn't lost yet
and I feel like it's my duty to be [ __ ]
scab I lost my virginity when I was 7 to
a russian my dad facilitated it I've
brought actually you bright Bren as a
dog that is beautiful if you're gonna
lose your pup your pup benedi oh hold
for the first you please do something
buddy him with the RP puppy anyway so we
set up a nice day we did this with Kong
as you guys remember
little flashback they're back from the
flashback
now it's brawly's turn she's here she's
here she's here
okay broilers dates here she's hot wait
most not weird way possible bro your
dogs hot like you're not like that but
also like she's pretty you know this
dog's name is actually blue this dog's
name is blue that's crazy bro Leigh's
Instagram is burly blue they get married
she be blue blue do you know she's a
virgin still
I just wanted not for me I'm gonna be
the next Jane Austen well I should no I
swear to god bro it's not like that I
was just oh thanks for watching I'm done
with YouTube forever bye
here we go bro Lee a possible love
interest
whoa narrow escape that cop Oh once I
mean this chick we're going back and
forth just tackling each other hitting
each other in the face was sick though
we ended up making out like it's here
all day I watch these dogs play but we
got a date to go on for real he's just
getting started so come on guys stop
mounting each other's faces keep this
party going
alright ladies and gentlemen my name is
Logan Paul I will be a chaperone for
this evening please keep your seatbelts
on your hands and the vehicles and your
private parts and are you topping her
stop it no easy tiger you've just met if
we're getting personal I'm gonna be
honest I used to be in love once but
turns out I'm an emotionally unavailable
[ __ ] working on it I got to become
the best version of myself you guys know
what I'm saying what's going on back
there are y'all kissing what whoa it
down easy there buddy at first base
[Music]
[Applause]
all right here we go oh man you guys are
excited I hope you're not gonna fight
and kill each other stop it stop it stop
it
here you go guys yeah watch out for the
candles all right it looks like they're
really enjoying it so far I see you guys
just plus up here and I'll be right back
with the menus good job good job
all right how you guys doing my name is
Logan Paul controversial youtuber
overall douche-lord got the menus right
here if I'm if I'm being honest there so
there's only one option and it's a yeah
at stake I hope you like steak
I'll go get God's to be a team player I
really am
alright so I'll get the steak like you
guys asked for
[Music]
there you go oh I got dinner for you
guys whoa I know you like that what do
you want oh wow this is having the
opposite effect
I'm really falling in love guys it must
be nice you guys enjoy yourselves let me
know if you need anything I'll be over
there good dog good dog
[Applause]
[Music]
parents used to do this right for the
divorce they would eat together but not
say oh no you're right yeah my dad would
say listen [ __ ] I'll take the rest of
your food - I oh no bro Lee's JumpShip
he's taking over the steak he's eating
blue steak now I've seen this before
he's right before the kids start getting
beat at this point in the relationship
this is usually when my dad would throw
me down the stairs and my mom would try
to hit me with the wooden spoon it's not
joke that's like ting with comedy but
really some part of me is missing
[Music]
Rollie has completely iced her out I've
never seen a date go so badly before I
think it's time for dessert I think
there no no okay
hey guys notice everything is going not
so smoothly figure a little dessert
could help little sweets
hi guys just just stay put please hey go
for good dogs good dogs I'm just trying
to get out of here as soon as possible
Rosa disaster all right guys just take
it easy
got a little dessert for you both here
you go
[Music]
awesome completely ignoring it just like
the first thing this Sox row spends
maybe that age thing we were talking
about is actually right it's technically
they're like not even seven years old I
think you're right man I've severely
underestimated the the maturity and sex
drive of these dogs
I really just gotta get my mind out of
the gutter dude but y'all wanna go put
him in a room and see if they smash
little by little by Allah's sniffing
that's a good start it's a little for
blanks out bad looks like things are
getting kind of rough
[Music]
Wow that's great thank you guys for
watching this vlog if you're not
subscribed anyway happy to March
look up all that consular shop be a
maverick my maverick gang is growing
everyday that I said I love y'all hear
how glowy blue Instagram a parolee blue
I will see y'all tomorrow TV offenders
[Applause]
[Music]
bro
[Applause]
[Music]