guys so uh something I've been wanting
to talk about for a while now the KS I
think good morning to you at yo good
morning little gang what's poppin hey
guys it's me No at this point it's just
a sculpture cuz spoons are literally
embedded in the cake
Leonardo da Vinci couldn't create a
master he's like this but yeah guys if
you're not a part of the low game make
citizens be the star don't eat that bro
all jokes aside guys it is Evans 21st
birthday today
roommate Evan he's not impressed with
his family my house is a mess but I'll
do anything my boy like yesterday I'm
sorry we threw a party for him
we had an exotic dancer but now we had a
real party last night my house oh hello
gang I'm calling on you I need you to do
a favor for me open a new tab go to your
url type in logan paul comm slash shop
and cop yourself some of the hottest
softest merch in the game that maverick
merchant what is the body's about being
a maverick doing it different trash in
your house for your friends oh good
stuff this is gonna cost me some money
to clean up plus you put on the merch
you just feel like a boss now party
glasses on let's get the day started
okay I'm dope that happy birthday bro
you're 21 now about that whole party
last night though you explain that do
you want to go to flea market bro for
your birthday would get a gift for you
and it'd be nice and we could bond I was
also thinking bro we haven't done
driving with Evan in a while hi guys
welcome to no sacred driving with Evan I
will say it's your 21st birthday we
gotta squeeze this gap you gotta squeeze
in there bro how do you feel being 21
well that was pretty good ah it's hot in
this car holy water supply the only
thing I can think of is who's gonna
clean up that ice cream cake hey guys
all jokes aside it's too hot in here
this segments over thanks for watching
tune in next time for oh snap okay we
are at the flea market
what's the flea market I actually know
the idea there you go why why'd you take
my first bro it's just birthday wait
ma'am can you say happy birthday to my
friend on that machine we nice you wee
nice you what does that mean I think I'm
gonna take this opportunity to get these
are great Evan do you like any of these
yeah
he doesn't like tribal masks okay maybe
it's not the move what if I just get you
a pile of clothes who knows they all fit
it'll be pointless yeah you're right all
right that's not the move this could be
good they got these little plants little
cactus yeah and these little logs bro I
don't know okay maybe that's not the
move you love those boards oh go away
bro you can't be here about the ball you
give also you guys know I'm the Maverick
right I'd do things a little different
but we're gonna get him aboard mm-hmm
dude you gotta go away rogue ah go away
stop it's not the board isn't gonna have
a wheels boy I got you a gift
[Applause]
[Music]
are you okay you look like all the frat
boys I hated in college at what did you
do Wow I'll take five
well that board has wheels my work is
ever offended okay so a pretty
productive day at the flea market I'm a
boy some gifts got in escaper I got the
robot I also did end up buying the
little cactus in the little law I've
made a mistake
there's dirt everywhere so yeah guys a
lot of good stuff today absorbacron
the space going on what are y'all doing
what are you doing what am i the Haunted
robot this thing I guess this is a good
time to say my mom is in town hi we're
matching that's cool be a maverick Logan
Paul calm /op do it different maybe we
should have left that there he's got a
name now okay actually no I let him go
let him go I just feel like that's not
how it was meant to be used yeah you got
it another day in the life subscribe but
there is bad news
little Jake brother Paul he broke the
robot the haunted robots broken so it's
possible out Donna said also yesterday's
vlog was reading some of the comments
and you may have noticed guys there was
a speck on the middle of the screen
oh sorry guys I don't know what we're
doing we get this speck off here but
yeah we're gonna make sure that doesn't
happen again looking I'm sorry let's
rock okay guys so uh something I've been
wanting to talk about for a while now
the KS I think I know bro I don't know
my team literally won't let me I go too
hard I got I'll give you that sneak peek
bro whoa gang you guys know I love you
no one has ever seen
[Music]
nice watch we need to change the lens
bro this is bad
yeah my change lines hey bad news we
shot an entire scene last night
involving that haunted robot well this
is one of those instances where I need a
babysitter we sent the vlog to the legal
team for review and this is what they
said
due to and in light of recent events the
team has decided it best to isolate and
omit scenes 42 through 46 from today's
vlog as part of a continued effort to
ensure that content is suitable to be
consumed by viewers of all Oh No the
cotton me bro creativity be it stifled
it's okay you know what I need this I
need this guys no glugging this is how I
stay on YouTube but that said low gang
that is the vlog thank you guys for
watching you do not a part of the low
gang make sure to subscribe
punch it in the face punch bind in the
face turn your notifications on for the
channel comment below I read them all so
you want to be smart or cool or sexier
faster stronger bla bla bla do yourself
a favor cop some maverick merch the
hottest merch in the game do it
different every day keep it clean leave
it yeah keep it clean don't be afraid to
be yourself be unique be passionate and
be a maverick look upon that kind of
slash shop or linking to sweet hell ok I
love you I will see you tomorrow
[Music]