right now you see a natural Logan Paul
in a state of happiness and in about two
minutes he'll be a mad no Logan Paul
frozen to the bone good morning Logan
what really though guys there's a
thousand things going on right now you
guys know my roommate haven't build me a
PC
well what happened ever what's going on
I broke the motherboy was defect the
motherboard got lost everything that I
put together and money $6,000 to be
exact
I'm gonna fire on four night when I'm
streaming twitch at Logan Paul was
taking always bloke oh god I hope my
jokes get funnier in this vlog so there
is sort of a method to my madness why
all this stuff that happening before I
get into that high call good morning
y'all know Kong to savage us out here
living his life not much going on in
that brain is really nice yesterday I my
toes I got orange in a bunny rabbit and
on this toe I got the maverick now
Spencer over here he got green then we
look good what do you think young dog
I'll get off okay okay you keeping up
with me now you guys know I'm building a
game room right I'm definitely gonna be
taking this gaming and streaming thing
pretty seriously guys because I think
these next five or six months or so
while I'm training for the KS I fight
going hard practicing for like six hours
a day I'm gonna be sore I retired I
don't know if I'm gonna be able to vlog
every single day so the streaming and
the gaming is gonna be nice for me to
just like relax and heal my muscles
while I'm still like entertaining
technical but with that said let me show
you the first step to the game room yeah
no it's cool though it's orange right I
mastered my tone yo this is gonna be I
know where did my toes go all you can
see is a little bunny when I was a kid
yo orange you
be my favorite color I don't know why
though I don't think we have any orange
merch what thought about that shirt is
this don't don't just yeah you know I'm
colorblind Spencer stop you know but
speaking of colors and merch you know
how does Mertz in the game we're looking
Paul that calms last job who's doing it
today but who's gonna dent the universe
that's what we do that's about pushing
ourselves right working hard to achieve
our goals
all right looking description it's time
to get my baby guys remember the other
day they took the cool bus it's been
having issues and all I want to do is
make content in her around her and on
top of it so we're here today to pick up
the cool bus from West Coast Customs oh
I hear I uh
how's she doing she's doing great
homemade Randy oh no new lights all
these are the new light these are the
hall lights that was definitely the move
[Applause]
okay so we're gonna put this thing to
use right away but first we do have to
get it to my brother Jake's house
good it feels good to drive my baby
again off she's so beautiful it's good
to have you back cool bus now guys there
is a reason we brought it here you guys
remember the other day the English BMX
rider Ryan yeah well he's actually right
there I got the waiver actually yes
that's not a joke this time got waivers
as well you saying waiver yeah okay
nothing eats away photo on the wafer yes
on the waiver the thing that actually
matters this man rocks it to the high
Jesus okay wait did you sign the waiver
oh Jesus I think I'm like kind of
actually clear cuz this is not my
property right Jake would be the one
getting sued there we go he swoops done
oh my god okay we still need the wave so
yeah there's a reason the bus is here it
involves him let's just say he might be
going over the cool bus what he doesn't
know about it yet though all right we'll
see you tomorrow so Jack follow me I
have somewhere to take you okay
now I'm with my brother Jake he's right
there you guys might know him from this
song from Disney Channel you've seen the
videos before where the people go and
stand in these ice chambers called
cryogenic healing tank in fact I've even
done this before flashback now anyways
as you guys know I'm training for the
fight against ksi coming up August 25th
and Jake actually is gonna be fighting
KS eyes little brother what
house-training been going for you do
trainings great man like I actually
started going to Pizza Hut like every
day okay just like meatlovers pizza high
in protein right put on the muscle and
wait that's my main event sit on them
mainly you're going down [ __ ] it okay
our people just killed the club wrapping
a wrap you know our up Pete she's got no
autopilot you want to check this is a
test coke Turner I stopping I'm telling
no you don't need to stop dad just let
go
oh let's go what have you hit something
stops in traffic Elon Musk is not a dumb
dumb dumb evening distracted by the
stuff the point is guys we're not boxers
right we've been training it hurts our
muscles are sore it's a man hard we are
going to a cryogenic healing chamber
this is not like the ones you've done in
the past definitely not training this
one is no joke guys you standing there
for three minutes I just called it Shh
yeah you gotta hold this what wait what
every one minute you have to hold the
steering wheel oh there is some sort of
Savior do you see that the fans and hey
but if he's gonna win we're gonna go
your dad you got now I here we go
it's like a shower but for coldness oh
you have no idea bro your skin starts
frosting up are you gonna be mad at me
if I give up now you got there I just
want to make sure you know I'm not I am
so yeah I think it's best if you stay
out there
[Music]
what's the problem what did you do hold
on now no need to customize their nice
this one's a bunny rabbit yeah alright
so I'm gonna take things too far bro yep
that's definitely my brand we should do
kicks
[Music]
you tell that ice baby today
I'm not gonna freeze today it's oh you
listen to songs no more like this is so
much more official than everything
pretty good so far
[Music]
you do a good J look at his hair you
look good his hair is starting to get
white okay it's starting to get really
attached
only a minute 40 like this thing I'm
telling you it's so long it hurts so bad
there's definitely a point where it's
like not even funny
always like I'm done performing for the
camera like this sighs oh my god this is
what happens when you come to LA you do
dumb so there's a song that's popping on
the charts right now it's called the
number song right now you see a natural
Logan Paul in the state of happiness and
in about two minutes he'll be a mad Noah
Logan Paul frozen to the bone
[Music]
I feel bro I don't know yet that is the
law
nothing like a good cryotherapy session
to end the day if you're not a part of
the low game make sure to subscribe join
the strongest family on YouTube oh
you're a Jay Paul are you in the lo game
yeah the second strongest family on
YouTube if you're not a part of the lo
game make sure to subscribe smash the
button kiss it on the mouth punch it in
the face oh and also you know the drill
guys Katherine maverick merch we out
here doing it different every single day
this is a maverick movement baby logo
bald icon flash shop or link in
description low gang I love y'all and I
will see you tomorrow
[Music]