[Music]
hey man you know we got showers in here
right it never rains in Los Angeles why
not use the gifts that Mother Nature
gave up listen guys welcome back to the
vlog 40% of you are actually not
subscribed so exchange that subscribe
for me and I'm gonna go inside my
girlfriend when - like three stores and
they had no toilet paper
you have to wipe your butt a lot yes so
this is our last roll of toilet paper I
don't know how long it'll last so we
need to share and we need to ration
sorry take my dog for walks finally come
pancake you got it buddy oh you got it
dude this gives me immense joy he's
gonna probably eat those fish well what
wow he looks like an absolute predator
right now imagine if you were a little
guy looking at a big guy let's go ask
how do you feel when you look at Mike I
can't handle another pet death I saw a
picture of maverick this morning he
looks like a Cheeto
now I know why ginger 800 was so fickle
wait what all have I not know this
wait wait what like I'm like why I'm
gonna jar your green tails now that's a
pickle pickle changing frequently
especially as regards to one's loyalties
interests or affection Facebook YouTube
do you think that's why I don't have a
girlfriend
if you describe someone else pickle you
disapprove of them because they keep
changing their mind about what they like
or want my mom said a cool such a cute
word like you're so fickle no okay I
think you're thinking of pickle
serious and that how your toe is CRO
what is that I don't know Oh
fickle what is cuddling itself - your
toe giving me a thumbs up have you ever
[ __ ] a girl huh
why are you getting this again come
closer yeah I it's really just a chest
cold
are you sure upper respiratory blockage
than a fever what would I be so worried
about it's not like there's a global
virus going around and those are the two
core symptoms so this morning I tried to
prank Mike with plastic wrap when he
walked outside of his room but
unfortunately it did not work given the
fact that he's also sick I thought it
would be a good idea to place him in
quarantine and redeem I should pray so
we picked up some wood hammer nails and
went to work
[Music]
[Applause]
standing down there little short [ __ ]
are you drunk mom yes you are