it's never gonna work that's not true we
just need a smaller kayak wherever you
plan on taking it like the ocean or my
stairs over my head if you're gonna be a
bully be a bully ah now it's hurting on
you too now I know why you gave me a
wedgie it's for artistic Lana you lost a
fan me I can't my friend's girlfriend
anymore
I just can't it's weird what about me
and my ex porn is that happening we have
a sex tape now well you want to know the
worst part about all this I'm lying I do
last night
I'm sorry beau I even lied to Josie
about it he asked me if I watched you
and I was like no yes yeah Josie you
know Josie just the way that she where's
that kid okay I asked you something dude
does it look like I have a deviated
septum what do you think of me like
personally like aesthetically
anyways what are you doing later uh I
I'm gonna go I've been to this doctor's
office at least 100 times in the past
two days little partition of your nose
piece of bone sticks out like a thumb
but I can't breathe through the left
side of your nose we're not gonna be
able to fix it until you stop doing
stupid things like getting hit in the
face that's gonna be tricky Doug this
nose is gonna collapse in with a few
good punches because it's been so
destabilized on the inside please don't
do anything stupid
got it doc you can trust me hi next in
the agenda we're at our friend Ryan
Garcia's fight if you remember Ryan came
on episode of impulsive it was a great
episode he ended up last hurting my
liver Oh bro know what's good I almost
died it is a wreck show up late dressed
like a tampon throw up in the trash
here's your here's your whole thing on
your YouTube channel is to undermine
your brother
guess who won [ __ ]
[Applause]
Oh
when you calm on abortion your wins you
win
[Music]
[Applause]
second I was like I want to do something
nasty but please wait lucky guy bro you
okay the last person you try to hit the
camera out of your hands got choke choke
myself I can't sized