logan paul take one feel like you've
done this before first why i moved like
an athlete this year i moved like a
boxer i know how to strike like a boxer
defend like a boxer it would be nice to
secure a fabulous fantastic knockout
that makes ksi a meme for the rest of
his life excited for my preparation to
be put to work what's up folks at you
boy LP this is the last video you'll see
of me before I'm crowned YouTube gym
YouTube channel is anything it's
Saturday it's fight day I said this in
yesterday's video if you didn't catch
you the flight will be on an app called
the zone and it's available pretty much
everywhere check my last video on how to
watch the fight if you don't know how
yet definitely download the zone sign up
for it's gonna be a spectacle so today
we had our weigh-ins we did a face to
face and yesterday we had a press
conference which press conference was a
press conference which you may have seen
extremely memorable moments ksi
apparently doesn't like math 10 times 10
you know that one he shoved me when I
asked him what 10 times 10 was very
clear to me that I'm deep inside this
kid's head this is the beginning of the
gradual breakdown and even you guys
probably already saw the face-to-face
know anything about boxing bro don't
know you're making this a [ __ ]
mockery give me boxing fanatic so like
this is [ __ ] huh because these guys
they just want to easy paycheck it's the
same I am just nestled in the middle of
his medulla oblongata and I think it's
gonna hurt him in the fight but here are
some other of my favorite moments from
the press conference that's why I've put
blood sweat and tears into this making
sure I push myself to the limit and I've
come back a beast I've caught you said
you didn't believe what I thought you
said you didn't believe you said that
yeah I don't believe so when you say you
put blood sweat tears what do you mean
when he said the blood part yeah
internally
[Music]
[Applause]
eleven times 11 it's 121 i'm quoting
jeff mayweather okay sighs coach it was
basically a good thing that I was part
of the camp because I did have to
harness everybody and to make everyone
realize that no matter what he's not a
real fighter okay
all right well you know your coach said
that about you we'll see on Saturday yes
we will let farther than is he your
coach I mean yes then why is he saying
you're not a real fighter am I missing
something or are you not a real fighter
I'm a real father
I'm not according to your own comes yeah
yes it was just hard for me to follow
this kids logic he says he's a fighter
but his own coach says he's not a
fighter he doesn't bleed well he bleeds
internally like internal bleeding cuz if
so that sounds like you need to seek
medical attention being totally honest
with you guys I actually don't like
trash-talking and smack talking I'm just
like good at it because I can think fast
on my feet and I'm kind of [ __ ]
annoying but it really makes him mad I'm
much better at performing and just being
an athlete that said we are about to do
the official way and even though I
already weighed in this morning I'm a
weight this one's for the fans this
one's for y'all Lauren one ninety nine
point four pounds for
Paul
what 93.2 pounds will night bank a side
over the Maverick Paul the nightmare ksi
six rounds in the cruiserweight division
but more
of the world-class professional boxing
for your
[Applause]