[Music]
see hey I told y'all this was coming you
don't like what you see which I'm 100%
positive that you don't might be on the
wrong YouTube channel you should go
check out my brothers at Jay Paul
Hollywood hasn't changed my son not at
all you don't think I'd be doing this if
I was back in high it can I ask you a
question and don't take this personally
wrong dog foods would that make
something wrong no it's dog food to try
it yo you got him major huge thick old
leg you'll ever see a Victoria's Secret
model Rhonda razor you swear
I love you I love YouTube I love YouTube
it's a great place to make videos oh
it's a [ __ ] dragon in the house oh do
something oh just be careful cuz some of
these things come back from the dead
oh he's right there Evan Evan Mach
please
[Music]
yeah I'm sorry George got me up last
night drunk Q&A for the maverick Club I
can say this hangover kid sucking fat
fat girthy penis why don't you go by
yourself what oh [ __ ] you guys are both
so beautiful and and girthy alright guys
be safe wear condoms extra extra extra
large up for riding the razor and we got
actually do feel really bad about taking
Evan off the jump earlier without
telling him so I'm gonna let him give me
a wedgie using the Bobcat
[Music]
you know I love you too
we'll put this at the end so they know
it's real all right well I still love
you too
[Music]