thirty thousand maverick pandemic masks
gone in three hours first off thank you
guys it seems like you guys are really
digging the new design the second off
it's cool that we actually provided
something good like these will help you
and give you that extra layer of
protection that you might need there's a
lot of people working really hard to
restock these so we do have more and
we're saving some for the first
responders here in LA nurses doctors
police officers firefighters etc who
keep checking the site it's mad for
clothing I'll also update you guys when
we do restocks all good stuff and it's
about to get even better it's not cook
Bay I'm getting a new bird you guys know
about the tragedy that was maverick the
parrot on my [ __ ] evil evil Tibetan
Mastiff ginger the giant ate him now his
legacy is preserved in cloth it's
actually kind of sad I am a bird guy
like I'm AG admit it I'm a dork bird guy
is equivalent to cat lady like it's
[ __ ] weird I'm not proud of it I
don't know why I just like bird so for
the past two months I've been looking
for this breed of bird I think is this
coolest [ __ ] bird ever it's called the
African Grey they're so smart they have
the intellect of like a five-year-old
and they could say up to a thousand
words I couldn't find one so finally I
took the social media you guys may have
seen in my Instagram I was asking like
does anyone know someone with an African
Grey one of my friends reached out
pointed me in the direction of this
family who had an African Grey and it
needed a home so I figured who better to
adopt him than the Owen one youtubing
boxer he's about to be here I'm really
nervous but also excited so let's do
this he's so beautiful
[Music]
hi buddy
what's up Logan nice to meet you yeah I
feel that oh my god I'm already doing
the thing oh my god bro there's gonna be
a moment where he says his first word I
love it I love him so much
oh this is so weird and oddly kind of
uncomfortable but I guess if this is how
you do it that's how you doing he's like
deep throating this syringe is actually
kind of horrifying Lana wrote scene am i
right I'm just kidding come on guys it's
a job so that's it the new member of the
family Holies
[Music]
my heart is melting right now good boy
yes of general rule of thumb if you see
this dog who is also that dog just stay
away from her got this weird thing which
she like eats parrots no no stay away
from her to think that if things go
right and he stays away from that dog
will be boys for fifty years 50 years
that's half of Mike's age I'ma be honest
with you bro you better start getting
used to me in my pale thighs Tommy it
was like everything else in my life my
bird is [ __ ] on me welcome to the
family
sweet so sweet crazy right well this
birds doe probably it has a bright
feathers I'm like actually gusto it's
like when your dad approves your
girlfriend so we put his cage in this
corner and we actually kind of like the
location of it so I think we're gonna
try to find a custom cage build or to do
like a curved one right here that way
he'll be around people he'll be social
and everyone could see him from the
kitchen someone's jealous he's never
given me this much attention oh why are
you so jealous bro this bird can eat his
own ass I've been trying to do it for
years that's cool as you can see this
bird is extremely uncoordinated he looks
like me attempting to run in the
Challenger games I have never seen an
animal this uncoordinated but it's cause
he's still a baby we're gonna work on it
we have a lot of life training to do
[Music]
it's our first morning together are you
kidding me is he perfect or my tripping
we're having pillow talk and everything
well be honest he's a better color than
most of the girls I thought homie for
life he's been kind of jumping around on
the bed testing his wings a little bit
think if he keeps on doing this
eventually he'll be able to learn how to
fly look somehow this bird has become
what I like to call the instant homey
it's funny cuz with maverick you know
when I talked when we put subtitles but
since this bird will legitimately be
able to speak English I don't think
we'll need subtitles here's what I'm
teaching him to say [ __ ] I love
you was Bob yeah does it look like a
flying am I about to take off
hahaha they told me his wings were
clipped I think it's like half true he's
been flying around the house he's ran to
the fridge a couple times I think cuz
he's a baby he's been sleeping a lot
it's kind of funny I don't know if you
noticed about birds or not but when they
sleep they tuck one leg up and somehow
balance on the other but they also put
their head like on their back so if you
look from the front they can look like
they've been decapitated but don't worry
he still has a head I think oh my god he
almost went in the fish tank holy Sh
look at the fish broke they're animals
they're like a lion pack just waiting to
eat the near spirit period with the word
dysfunctional he's stuck dude if it's
good look at him this is the dumbest
never
[Music]
now after spending a few days with my
new son it was time to give him a name a
name that would make a statement a name
worthy of carrying on the legacy of
maverick the parent a name so epic that
it causes tremors in the earth every
time it's uttered and I finally got it
ladies and gentlemen introducing Sir
that's right his name is sir the African
Grey hooking it above on Instagram at
sir the grey or don't I don't really
care this loves oversubscribed by where
he says his first word