[Music]
Rockabye Kong dougie on the big charge
it's time for nap time and someone's at
the door so now I got to move you sorry
buddy what's up man
i'm chris evans best friend from back
home
evans what you said evans best friend
from back home best friend yeah Oh back
in the day status mocha what's your name
Logan Logan hello Logan well yeah yeah I
don't know ah here come on in bro that
was weird
cool man check it out man this is my
crib I like the crib thanks man
reminds me of mine I don't yeah except
it's a lot smaller with less girls
running around huh
that's a cool dog you got Oh Rexy yeah
yeah get the leather jacket - it's real
Leatherman yeah that's cool it looks
like it looks a lot like my dog I feel
like uh-huh
a little except there's no leather
jacket oh yeah
no leather jacket hey I saw the edge you
wagging outside oh yeah yeah it's called
it we called it the Yeti yeah yeah I
know yeah I had some before but you know
I had to sell them and get the g6 like
the private jet yeah they're loaded
yetis I'd upgrade the life you know
gotta grow up sometime
honey's me no nothing just all these
guys around here always guys guys
Oh Logan oh yeah yeah man
Chris and I met it seems pretty cool
cool cool awesome
what is house shit's on this house yeah
well I thought okay anyways yo do the
intro for the episode so Steve Ott show
we're doing for Logan's YouTube channel
Oh YouTube sq the door I think I just
heard the doorbell ring I mean you want
to go get that yeah I guess I'll get the
doorbell geez okay great great anyways
ah Chris it's pretty fun picking Evan up
huh oh yeah yeah brings back old times
which all I'm do that sometimes
[Music]
hola hey can I help you Oh looking for
Paul Lauren for me go yeah what's your
name
Pepe Pepe Pepe and what you found today
Oh so Mexico yeah no oh hi oh Ohio Ohio
Ohio amigo hi um so just to clarify
you're friends with logan paul for Ohio
si amigo okay
y'all Logan I think there's someone here
hey hey hey but no guys no brother
hey okay Evan this is my friend Pepe the
best best friend from back home in Ohio
yeah Ohio you from Ohio huh
Ohio that's I choose it Ohio
Massachusetts he gets confused sometimes
we've been friends for how long has my
friends yeah 16 years 16 years 16 years
huh
yeah Wow that Bay you look uh well there
no really no I don't think so no no how
are you how would we over 23 and a half
and a half so yo enough in this small
chat we are gonna go do some best friend
stuff I think me and Chris are gonna do
best best friend stuff real best best
stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
come on step back come on brother
Oh No come on Pepe breathe breathe burly
brother
[Music]
[Applause]
yes they breathe breathe amigo breathe
breathe Pepe when your sigh come on Pepe
I'm glad I could save your life
it's my brother I'm fine so I have a
confession to make
Pepe is actually not my best friend from
Ohio yeah no [ __ ] yeah we got him from
Craigslist I kind of figured that when
he called you Paul Logan in the
beginning yeah two first names
it happens yes I have a confession to
make too Chris believe it or not it's
actually more of a douche in New York so
it's kind of stuff that I actually don't
believe that yeah that's amazing
that is crazy do you want like no I'm
gonna do a real best friend [ __ ] yeah
all right my best friend
hop on let's go your best friend [ __ ]
[Music]