hey little gang what's poppin okay I'm
just gonna give you a little rundown on
this situation I'm on my way back from
Burning Man which is where Logan is
creating you know epic logs for you guys
my job is to take the footage go to Reno
upload the footage and everything the
vlog can be made for you guys the issue
is that about 20 minutes out from
burning me on one road to get to Reno
and that road is closed because there's
a huge fire if you are attending Burning
Man it may want to actually postpone
your trip because the main highway that
leads to the event is currently closed
Here I am stuck in this little town girl
trying to do freakin Wi-Fi you guys
don't understand like it's not even us
there's Wi-Fi like there's no Wi-Fi like
these bars are getting run by generators
so here I am carrying a freaking laptop
nothing's working so I just talked to a
cop he said that the roads should be
open by 8:00 a.m. it's um it's 11 p.m.
I'm just gonna chill here for eight
hours because literally guys like
there's no other way to get to
civilization where I can like get decent
Wi-Fi to upload this footage I don't
have anything but we do have some cashew
granola bars yeah yeah I'm actually
having a good time just chilling here I
got some cashew corn oh boy I don't
blame you Joe I got the comfy merch hey
Lincoln bio besmirch in the game JA heat
I mean this wouldn't be my first choice
on how to spend my Wednesday night but
like it may be my second choice I don't
have a pillow but at least I have the
steering wheel yeah
Oh welcome to another segment of drive
me okay so we're gonna go we can't go
anywhere I just realize if we don't got
the low game we could have the Lydia
gang whoa Lydia Kenny and go follow me
on twitter to live my D Kenny always
plug guys get me out of here this is
like very ironic they're like we're
going to Burning Man and there's like a
huge fire if I Drive through the fire
I'm gonna be the burnt man okay update
it's 8:15 I have been here since 7 p.m.
yesterday and they just now opened up
the roads