[Music]
you tell me what's going on better look
at the sky what is this substance
falling from the air it looks like some
sort of liquid look at the ground here
guys it never rains in LA and it's
raining today
hey yo good morning LoJack what's poppin
we woke up today and it was pouring rain
people are freaking out but I figured
for this vlog we should use it so if
you're not a part of the logo make sure
to subscribe during this strong and
family on YouTube for the family of
Mavericks the people out here doing it
different and instead of staying inside
when it rain with you [ __ ] you do I need
to say it we're gonna like water wet
stuff do they not have to got your merch
hot Smurfs in the game you can get a
Logan Paul cops last shot but I just
gave it to you
what y'all son cuz I'm coming in hot I
know there's liquid falling from exactly
and you know people in Los Angeles they
told me go get some boots put on your
chef at put on your apron you'll be good
they said that to you yeah
silly but you have your GPA yeah alright
good we're gonna attach this to the back
of it and kind of hug it through the
streets in my mind your heart is gonna
work will have andis Jeep will attach a
rope to it and then obviously at the end
of the rope will be the tube andis gonna
drive on the street pulling the tube but
hopefully the tube kind of catches like
a puddle on the side of the road let me
just slide on through there I did I
invented it the waiver actually you can
show you when we get home Andy cuz you
have to sign it because you're gonna be
driving the car if I sign your waiver
you sign my waiver
here's what I'm visualizing okay hey not
getting hurt beat not getting arrested
and see
[Applause]
[Music]
oh you look good over here
chin up put your chin up we got
sidetracked
this looks good Andy says it's supposed
to be like kind of deflated sometimes
kind of okay oh now you wanna uh yeah
ever exceed 20 miles an hour
never toe in shallow water or near the
shore we're just gonna have to find a
deep hole deep puddles only this is good
too while you're reading the warnings
I'm actually gonna have you sign the
waiver that we have printed up it's just
reliability purposes is waiver just one
turn sign the waiver we're just gonna
need to sign it yeah feel like I'm
signing my life away
you got this keep on going so look I'm
not a tubing expert I don't know if this
thing's gonna be able to handle it on
the road so I figured I'd give it a
quick test drive you guys saw yesterday
still gonna send it with the tube this
time
it looks like she honks yeah bro this
thing's good definitely hungry I think
we take her to the road well that's
because you brought camels Andi that
seems good that one line 47% chance of
working honestly I'll take those odds
let's hit the road jack how long before
you think saying Huck it is just really
annoying it's been a pretty good two or
three days that we've been saying it
right and I'm already really annoyed of
it but until today is over I'm still
gonna hack it
listen you signed the waiver so this is
kind of unnecessary conversation but
what are you driving don't slam on your
brakes cuz I will literally just slam
right into the back of the Jeep okay
we're driving in the street and all the
water dried ups we were like and then we
pull into this park and it's the most
beautiful
just acres of muhahaha look at that
model that's a deep one remember no
shallow water you think you can drop
through this mud there Andy no I really
am salty we weren't able to do this on
the road everything was soaked this
morning you know it's all dry it's gonna
be a disaster
this is the best day of my life oh by
the way Jack yes straight eating mud for
dinner is mud vegan I don't know how to
tie knots bro well we were skydiving you
told everybody that you were an expert
not tire it was like I call this one the
Greg Pole you call this a Greg pole all
you did was just tied knot after not
simple but gets the job done
[Music]
oh yeah my twitches that Logan Paul was
taken why'd you name it Logan Paul was
taken yeah that's a dope seafoam though
yeah yeah it's legit certified from the
seat belt do you feel safe we need to
get going before it becomes safer yeah
all right any last words any safety tips
before we do this yep kids just make to
wear your protective eyewear huh
[Music]
right now but you see what we learn in
Ohio is where you get dirty in like I'm
filthy right now I'm screwed the only
way to clean up is to use the I'm gonna
take a bath I am dirty I need to get
clean I get a towel from anybody thank
you I just dry off your excuse me for a
sec okay much better wow this merch
cleans up nice Logan Paul icon slash
anyways guys that is the vlog if you're
not a part of the logo make sure to
subscribe join the strongest family on
YouTube also join the Maverick movement
copy yourself some of the hottest
softest Merson the game the link for
that is in the description low gang I
love you tomorrow a pic slag in my mind
another for
get picked and I will paint yours
Prince's paupers time and servants
excuse me while I make a slight
disturbance from inside the circus
bare-knuckle fight club like Tyler
Durden like all invite for what I am