[ __ ] this and get a ferrari [ __ ] this
and get a porsche hey bugatti mr bugatti
i want a bugatti chiron right now what
do i do
logan hey oh good morning little guy
what's
poppin yay current location guys is
venice
italy current time is 6 40 a.m today
today is a big day
it's my big day it's actually not it's
my brother jake's big day
if you don't know what i mean allow me
to bless y'all with some information
most of you are in the low gang so
you've heard this before but if you're
not a part of the low gang make sure to
subscribe yo oh what the [ __ ]
we just hit 12 million i i had no idea
you guys are growing too fast looking
[ __ ] slow down i'm just kidding bro
mavericks never stopped so yeah
subscribe if you're not subscribed but
okay story time good morning
paul brothers in italy i don't know how
we didn't get kicked out yet
okay we're still here dog oh okay here's
the background i'm gonna make this short
jake [ __ ] lamborghini prank on my
birthday no
you did not jake give me a lamborghini
and mr princess
yeah and that was not cool yeah i'm not
even kidding literally went from the
best day of my life to the absolute
worst
[ __ ] and then being the freaking loco
young man i am i said this there's only
one way that i can come back from this
if i say
you jake paul yeah and go out today
and buy an actual lambo boom so i was
like yo
[ __ ] it dude i'm buying a lambo today
found out you couldn't do that because
they're very expensive cars it's kind of
a big deal jake was like yo
if if you're doing it i'm doing it too
and then it was his idea to customize
2018 lamborghini huracan performance i
went to the lamborghini dealership i had
you guys
actually choose the color and help me
customize it logan y'all got my back
and they told us what about coming to
italy they were like yo you're going to
come to italy
you're going to wait like six months
it's going to be amazing you're going to
get a tour of the factory
basically come and pick up your own
lamborghini that you customized i was
like yo that [ __ ] dog
i've seen some dope and that's dull then
i
yo the time frame and i got using my
brain which i'm not good at and i was
like hold up pause i'm about to drop 350
on a car i just bought the yeti
[Music]
and like i'm not a huge car guy right i
like cars i don't love cars like he does
i love it it's a genuine concern like
it's a very dangerous car and
me behind the wheel so i was like dog i
don't know
i don't know i decided not to get it and
then i had to tell brother jake
and then i cried like a [ __ ] i
am not getting a lamborghini with you
and then we get here the other day and
jake starts broke and starts
murmuring in persuasion because
originally i just flew here to surprise
him and
support him while he gets his lambo so
now that y'all have been blessed with
some information i think you should know
uh we're running late again
yeah my mama mia london get in the boat
i'm getting it i'm gonna get in the boat
come on guys my brother needs a
lamborghini
[Music]
i just want to say according to my phone
our train left one minute ago
nice rapido
italia i gotta be honest i wasn't even
sure if i'm still able to get the lambo
because i canceled like i put my twenty
five thousand dollar deposit down i told
them like i wasn't getting it so they
don't know i'm even here
no the park's gone
i gotta be honest i've never like
actually missed a flight or a train i've
always like made them by the hair of my
skin this is kind of
sad anyway called my business manager
andrew
i asked him last night in the middle of
the streets of italy if it was even
possible for me to get the car this was
last night
last night this is hypothetical if i go
to the factory tomorrow
and i see this and i and i want to buy
it
because i put down the 25 000 do they
still have it could i still do that is
it that is that even an option like my
exact
lambor the one that i customized is at
the factory like
i'm gonna see it
we could tomorrow switch things around
as you can still get it
it's hypothetical it's all hypothetical
bro this could go down future logan take
it away though
i feel like while we wait for our next
train and hopefully don't miss that one
it's a good time to say
uh it's gonna be one of the most real
vlogs
probably ever like bro brendan admit
this from real life
this is really like only once in my
lifetime am i gonna be presented with
this opportunity
to buy a supercar with my brother all
gonna be a split decision like
if i get there and i see it now knowing
that my business manager oh
shut the [ __ ] up i'm vlogging shut up
shut up anyways andrew said
my car is still there built and ready to
go so if i see this thing and i'm like
like who knows bro i don't even know the
actions i'm gonna take until i take them
look at this bro look at the bird bro
i'm the maverick and
hey i don't want to miss another train
ending how did this keep happening
oh it's a miracle it's with me popping
logan with their food
[Applause]
bro i was not gonna get this car i like
[ __ ] it is so persuasive so please bless
the logang
with some facts as you blessed me about
this this vehicle the lamborghini oticon
por fermante
fastest lamborghini ever made fact
fastest car to lap
the nurburgring fact nurburgring is like
the most respected track in the world
fact this is also one of the first like
mass-produced lamborghinis with like uh
the exhaust coming straight out the back
like absolutely they don't know them
oh god no honey now i hate butt stuff i
can't say the same
0 to 60 in less than 2.5 seconds you
know what fast 2.5 is
go oh i don't think it's that fast paul
look the point is the litmus level is
freaking maximum and i love doing stuff
with my little bro even if it is buying
a super car
that way you're not in our lives not
doing it yet or are you no i'm not
i mean as of now literally bro i have no
idea
with that said let's head to the
lamborghini factory in modena
and he's at bravo bravo madame
going to modena lamborghini factory
lamborghini
[Laughter]
look whoa whoa andy's car is sexy bro
but not sexier than lambos fast
the lamborghini museum see modena
i think that means yes no what are you
doing
no we're being kicked out right now
we got no ride yo this is an angry man
angry
hey you need to watch his vlogs they're
good you'll be happy thanks jake hey
paul.com back to the shop get that merch
bro be a maverick yeah yo all right car
number two
here we're going to this place
lamborghini museum
[Music]
lamborghini factory literally like the
middle of nowhere in italy it's going
down you're
[ __ ] crazy you see your lamborghini
is italian that's multicultural
i don't know why i'm excited i don't
even know what i'm getting right now we
missed our training
oh yeah are we late
[Music]
you already spoken with my colleagues
because you should leave
all your cameras here oh they are not
allowed
oh yeah so slight issue right now and i
think this is part of the reason i was
like
on the fence about getting a lambo
hearing those words like no filming bro
just might as well just
stab me in the chest yeah is my like is
my car
in there so i can't film it
no i'm gonna go all the way to italy
listen buy a 400 000 car and they won't
let him film it
so we're having a little powwow over
there i'm hoping they let us film bro
cause
that would destroy the point of
literally like the reason we're getting
lamborghinis is because of you guys the
viewers the logang the jake paulers and
if we can't film
what like what it doesn't make it making
no sense in the brand of the logan paul
talking to the boss lady the boss man we
were told hey come to italy
order performante pick it up we'll do a
hole on field tensions
tensions are high like that was your guy
that was from you guys you guys said
that
no no yeah you did no i didn't the
vehicle is buying
the 400 000 vehicle don't you think you
should be able to take a picture with
that
it is
so jake is talking to like the boss
people
this is hilarious i'm having so much fun
now because like i'm just i'm here for
the ride today but apparently not in
the actual lamborghini weird
what just went down bro uh i don't even
know like
i can't summarize it like it's it's
it's laughable it's disrespectful
childish
it's basically the end the end of the
conversation was
uh i have a card if you want me to give
you my card he was like
he hit me
oh my god he's not possible it is
possible look he's doing it we got some
sketchy rules bro
where can we film when can we not either
we can film outside or no but we can
film inside possible
can we film inside not inside okay no
film
okay for sure obviously i'm gonna film
everything we're vloggers why would we
not film everything jake is deciding if
we want to do the factory visit
that's the security guard's hand as if
that's gonna stop us
yo andy andy can you tell them we're
very sorry we're going to put the
cameras down
and we'll do the factory visit here
comes the hand
the hand
that describes how i'm feeling right now
i'm feeling such
oh sorry did you hit me you did you see
that
this guy's just hit me i'm feeling such
a weird rush of emotions i just got hit
by a car they just gave us a tour of the
factory and i saw the car that i was
gonna get
literally it was right next to jake's
lambo he's over there doing his vlog of
disappointment
yo jake the scream i'm disappointed
damn it was just like the worst torture
like for me
okay yes the car was cool but like i
said i'm in different i'm on the fence i
will say they gave me a nice gift bag
kind of like a lamborghini i'm sorry i'm
being a shot
here is who i feel the worst for not not
not the driver not the vehicle
just there we go jake paul he wants
nothing more in the world than to get
this vehicle he's been waiting six
months and like i said i had not planned
on getting a car
i planned a different vlog so maybe i
can make his day i did bring a little
joke by the way this is what the vlog
was going to be i was going to say like
like i bought a lamborghini or just to
be this while jake gets his actual
lamborghini but looks like i'm just
giving this to jake
how you feeling honestly
i feel like [ __ ] i got something that'll
make you feel a little better
is it the [ __ ] dumbass notebook that
they gave us
you mean the gift bag it's not the
dumbass notebook
it is a brand new lamborghini
oh he's he's straight up silenced
all right i'ma let you i'ma let you do
your thing
told you today was gonna be a very real
vlog
and that it was that it was
what the [ __ ] what the what are you
doing that's my gift
what do i do what do i do what the [ __ ]
do i do
can you tell me it's tough it's tough it
really is
it's a mix of of his his pride his ego
is so big
and he feels like he's been it's minus
two but he feels like he's been insulted
personally
like i actually need you bro like i act
i actually need you
do i go do
this and it a ferrari do i say this
and get a porsche hey bugatti mr bugatti
i want a bugatti chiron right now what
do i do logan
hey i got you andy watson
i need
yo we drove five minutes down the road
this is one of the huracans like
straight up
the exact same car that we ordered
we're in the middle of nowhere the kit
the kit this kid's dying right now i'll
be out here this is horrible i feel
so bad for him bro oh he's
dying devastating like super
oh
can i just can i say something it's the
same [ __ ] color car that i ordered
it was the most expensive color it's
like [ __ ] now i'm hurting a little
bit bro
oh
[Music]
all right so okay we've had like two
hours or so to just cool down relax
we're at this super cool villa right now
look around bro italy you've done it
again
i'm gonna show you guys more of this
tomorrow with the house tour go down
there and the vineyard drone shots sexy
stuff but for now i just okay here are
my closing thoughts on the situation
for me the whole possibility of getting
the lamborghini like if i was gonna do
it it was all about the experience
unfortunately today as you guys know our
experience was not so bueno so
long story short i i'm just i was very
turned off by it like you guys don't
understand when we went in the factory
we did the tour like i'm not even
kidding out of all the cars they're
making
my my [ __ ] lamborghini my customized
lamborghini matte orange
beautiful is sitting right next to
jake's finished car
like how were the two paul brothers
vehicles just sitting next to like
how like dude they knew we were coming
from and they put like stickers over our
iphones and it just
[ __ ]
and like i'm gonna be honest with you
logang i had a plan i always have a plan
i was
not not a joke not lying i was going to
flip a coin i have it here here we go
uh a euro a european coin i was gonna
literally
flip a coin if it landed on tails i was
going
to spend 400 000 to buy this lamborghini
in the moment
one shot 50 50 chance that was the plan
because yo i'm a maverick like i wrap
the logo every day it's what i do
and that's where i get like my like ugh
that's where i get my excitement from
that's
like why i live life what can i do right
now in the moment how can i be present
so i can i can milk life
and live life to its fullest potential
but i didn't even get an opportunity to
flip the coin
so like ah for that reason
i'm out it's a real one bro
it's a real one with that said hello gay
that is the vlog
if you are not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe hit the button we
got a couple more fun days here in
italian so join the strongest family on
youtube i
i feel bad for my brother jake hang in
there hey jake hang in there buddy cop
your maverick merch it's the hottest
softest merch in the game the low gang
reps it changing the world every single
day it's a movement logan paul dot com
shopper link in description i love y'all
and i will see you tomorrow take it easy
[Music]
they hit people here they hit me a
little bit ago