oh snap Logan you guys got me at a weird
time still shitty money - it is this
kids all over the floor my spot is right
yeah but just like yesterday amazing
crazy day today boom like an entire vlog
before I even came to say so once again
let's rewind back to if you don't know
what this is let me give you a little
briefing yesterday 7:30 a.m. 50 pond
experts invaded my house saying maverick
stay in the low gang so it was cool they
then started digging a giant hole cuz
I'm putting a beautiful koi pond in my
backyard and by the way if not a part of
the Logan yet make sure to subscribe
knock the butt in the face guys you know
this was the strongest family on YouTube
who else is doing it bro who who
completes the answer isn't nobody I
subscribe for me okay I am just very
impressed you guys are up this early
oh you don't we woke up like this
[Music]
that happened we got a new member of the
family it's a Chinese softshell albino
turtle yeah yesterday while they were
here making the koi fine your boy was on
set kicking ass from my movie the
thinning - coming this summer - you to
Bret and California decided to be a real
thought yesterday breaking news now a
wildfire in Los Angeles has grown to
2,000 acres this forest fires like down
the road and the ash is discussed yeah
yeah a lot of good things not that many
bad things life is good we're Mavericks
so it's all good so Greg what's
happening around can I see the pond
please cannot see the pockets we have to
go get your fish oh
I'm also down for that that's cool well
I got a question though can we give him
a ride back in the cool bus bro I would
be pissed if we decide that's right so
we're good to fish that Pacific outdoor
let it cool
[Music]
cool okay pull us back to the present
sets hey it's me look at yo first up
look at this set bro this movie's got a
race Oh God anyway so I'm standing there
I'm holding my key in the door right and
then disaster struck you guys got car
we're trying to jump the cool bus right
now start another forest fire bro see
why is that big cool can I just say
thank God for adults cuz I have no idea
what I'm doing but thanks to this man
his shiny head and his friends I think
we might be okay okay so I was wrong
let's do this Sunday Oh
oh snap yo yo I think we're good he's
going in 1 2 3
I think the more fires we can like get
the better so like yo see this tree here
see if you can just catch it all on fire
oh that's just [ __ ] awesome my cool
bus is broken sick but the good news is
I found this kid on set because for sure
what you can do with your elbows oh man
so as cool as that is that doesn't make
up for the following phone call I had
with manager Jeff yeah what's up manager
Jeff what's up yeah yeah there's ash all
over my yard Oh
Bad News Bears my managers house burned
down maybe we can build him a pond after
this morning
it's so weird let me tell you what it
means to be a maverick okay a maverick
is someone who exhibits great
independence in thought or action that's
what I am that's what have been my whole
life and I encourage you to be differ
one's got flaws everyone's got things
they're good at so find what it is that
you're good at and long for it work hard
to pursue your goals and that's that
maverick revolution baby I did it and
look at me now grow I'm a YouTube star
with a broken ass but yeah
[Applause]
let's go get some corn
[Music]
it's time to pick out some fish that are
going in the world about the fires on
the news don't worry of your house yeah
the that's the one with the white that's
like one of the most valuable ones it's
like a Japanese black oh it's right cuz
the Japanese flag it has that circle in
the middle fits right here
educational who says they don't learn
anything from Logan Paul bro that's what
I'm saying I'm educating the youth dude
[Music]
ginrin is the reflective shiny scale
she wrote series a white face black man
so much knowledge in koi bro who
would've thought
oh look at how beautiful these fishes
we're gonna be friends one day so this
is awesome I will say Annie and I both
agree we do feel a bit weird that the
grills are next to the koi I mean I we
don't want to miss beautiful guys it's
gonna be our big day guys I'm also gonna
be late to set so we got the koi we're
at home guys it's been a weird day my
managers house is on fire kinda sucks
but here's a special message for my
friend Frank it's Wednesday it's the
morning we're gonna have a great day we
have a pond now we have fish it was a
bleak day now it's a sunny day it was a
miserable day now it's a fun day let's
put the fun in funeral together Frank's
right guys we're about to put the fun in
funeral I finally get to see the pot
okay I just want to say these guys all
of these guys you guys are amazing I
can't see most of you cuz they got here
yesterday they did this in one day talk
about hard work all the time but
actually seeing in real life seeing
people work hard thank you guys thank
you guys and thank you Greg bro love it
this is a big moment in my life mom I'm
gonna have to call you back it's the
biggest moment of my life since I feel
like this is like our home he would say
move that fast now it's not a bust
anyways my child
[Applause]
[Music]
doesn't even look like a part of my
house how did you do this
it looks like it was just taken from a
jungle and just placed in my yard
and I feel like that's what happened
with me - oh my god you guys got the
Folies thing in the water did it this is
crazy man check it out calm oh this
never gets it's crazy because the pond
is right next to the gym so you could be
like chill and just sitting outside
minding your business
and then you close the gym yeah or the
koi we're gonna feed them with protein
powder oh here we go bro you guys can't
forget about another pet pancake look at
guys it's pancake can you guess why was
why we named him that Venus looking head
go from now on I'm sorry guys pancake is
gonna be blurred what is that what am i
holding guess you'll never know I'm just
kidding guys it's just pancake we're
about to throw him in the pot for the
first time this is pancake careful noisy
pancake wants to bite you at all times
he's a maverick like you dude that's
right Oh first let's give him some merch
- here you go pancake
here's your merch you can buy on local
Paul yeah
[Music]
see how he named a pancake brother
identical
[Music]
Lydia fell apart my hands can you clean
them up okay guys so this is amazing
there are some complications with the
fish just like chlorine in the pond we
don't want them to die that would not be
good and we're gonna wait for the water
to clear out tomorrow so we're gonna cut
to tomorrow actually putting the koi in
the pond oh thanks max Logan appreciate
you up in Cody check it out looking for
like a flower shop anyway guys the fish
are ready to be put in the pot is the
next day look it is clear it's ready to
go
hey Kong how are you buddy hot to draw
fish in the pot it's my big day miss you
are now a part of team maverick Rolex is
coming huh you know it's about to get
serious
Tonto poncho the Japanese flag fish you
are now part of team maverick lane how
beautiful this is
such a pretty picture so we are gonna
come up with names for these fish it's
gonna be on my Instagram at Logan pop I
may be sure to follow me there beautiful
fish
[Music]
there's no room to like actually swim I
can't make laughs alright guys so this
is the guy
this is Greg Witt started his YouTube
channel link is in the description check
it out if you like YouTube anyway time
this is the guy also he's doing
something like educational like pond
thing Adams the other times for Kids
program you want to be able to build
ponds in classrooms all over the country
and put it on a pond in the ecosystem
pot in your backyard or your school with
certified aqua ski country they're
certified guys let's get kids back
outside in nature or watching my vlogs
inside on computers whatever works guys
the links are in the description thank
you I think you're in there
Wow yo from Logan Paul from T maverick
thank you everybody this gives my yards
a nice like final cherry on top that it
needed I know it was hard work and I
appreciate it I always tell the low gang
it's so important to work hard if you
work hard you can achieve your goals
that's what the Maverick movement is all
about you're all Mavericks and I'm happy
to have you on my yard my property and
in my content thank you all so much for
the best one in the world
[Applause]
[Music]
it's a big day man such good vibes man
that pond is so cool so at this point
right the vibes are good the day is
looking up but I know what you're
thinking Logan is your manager dead
well oh my god I feel like I'm seeing a
ghost house your house burned down dude
where do you think this ash is coming
from your house opposite of a fire yeah
Moe bridge the bridge the bridge okay
so sick yeah the boot of the dope baboo
a new home if my house burns down can
you do that for me no I this is why I
love you jump even when his life is gone
completely to shoot got me wrong your
body your soul your health your wellness
your children coming to YouTube red 2018
I will say that kid is a maverick
assuming you still alive yo your mouth
appreciate you okay okay that is the law
if you're not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe here subscribe yo
English is sometimes hard when the
strongest family on YouTube she smacked
the subscribe right in the face and grab
your maverick merch you know the
holidays are coming up Christmas is
coming up by somebody you know some
maverick murder how does much in the
game bro I would be wearing it right now
but they're making me look like a stupid
nurse you know sexy nurse really Brendon
yeah just an actor live local Poldark on
/off oiling a description low gay I love
y'all I'll see you tomorrow
[Music]
resting position is like a constant look
of like I didn't do it anything I don't
even know what you're talking about but
just take it easy brah