logan paul yeah once meter wrote ten yes
okay
PewDiePie gave it to me hey yo good
morning okay what's up okay guys it is a
626 a.m. right now I am currently headed
to Anaheim California which is an hour
away don't shoot my MA
shoot my movie valley girl it's supposed
to be the last night ended up shooting
the music video which you should have
watched by now just fire bra the link
for that is in the description I want
two billion views I'm running on like
three hours of sleep right now but a few
good promise
oh good morning young bogey apparently
won back I'm sorry I gotta be a dad to
guys you know how to go potty go potty
no don't go fight over there don't go
back I think we know ya parenting is
rough man
I gotta get over now if you look closely
my dog had escaped the hunt cuz I'm the
last America okay I'm leaving hundred
kid guys I put him away good morning
Hollywood we did it yeah here so guys
that was actually an hour drive and
we're staying in Anaheim tonight your
boy brought a suitcase and now it's time
to eat because I lost my Apple yah yah
yah yah yah yah yah yah oh my god bro we
got so many a good morning Danny how are
you doing great yo yo yo hold on hold on
pause real quick
is there a wolf on your shirt hahaha
wait how many hours of sleep did you get
three or six three
okay yo say hi so we're in this together
both possibilities that's our nickname
yeah cool rollerskating today so let's
not fall asleep far worth doing that
you know dick Oh God God I'm just
tricking myself into thinking I'm awake
somewhere though I never rarely come
down to Anaheim and I'm actually headed
back here in like three days for VidCon
weird it's so crazy right anyways you
guys remember I broke the door when I
was throwing the chair when I was
vlogging yeah man blogger actor youtuber
entertainer singer writer producer
director got the Grand Ole stop playing
Mickey back bringing Mickey back bring
me back oh those are socks immediate use
dirty smelly socks
oh you're shooting it's a rule oh my
gosh so what what you're good bro you
got bro good regular chick-fil-a you to
see you can get famous what's he doing
yo oh yo you're doing more than one
chick I only asked for one trick Wow
high five mama said well guys it's lunch
time Brody see you across the way I'll
see if you recognize that guy wait how
did you know I was here sign us it logan
into you and you new valley girl coming
2018 and over here we have all the
actors getting ready to look sexy for
the scene how are you bro how are you
bro well I'm good it's good to keep good
dental hygiene he's right dude I'm doing
this your dress is doing it to looking
fabulous she's looking pearly how you
doing where's your dental floss think
you can use in mind oh whoa whoa if it
isn't Chloe Bennet before I make fun of
Chloe what's going on with you just you
good I need to perfect
yeah W Chloe why can't you be as fun as
Jesse you're so basic I've been doing
this for five minutes you think I'm good
I think he's like 25 oh yeah I'll be
there
oh okay but I leave my keepers weird you
let's talk about this interesting
bathroom setup I don't know how this is
worth any privacy but okay that it wants
to say it again life is amazing yeah oh
whoa John Boyd ah would you say he'll
help you girl what you're trying to do
because I don't got a clue des we have a
somewhat serious problem yeah if you
guys know I do this thing right they
quake me close to glory played the
character called quake on this show
called spies of swords on TV so I came
to set I was like I was like don't quite
be closer than we play this music now
you guys are all commenting it on
Instagram like other fathers they pump
like thousands of times because my guys
you need to stop fine
Kelvin all you feel don't you feel no I
love you guys I'm glad you guys know she
asked me to ask you guys to stop it you
guys are sending me like song remakes
about Rome
Chloe quit quote once I made a shirt
let's try to made a shirt
well you got to be loud employ take it
down like I do like Chloe and I care for
her low gang we're strong we've seen it
we know what I do think we should share
with the quake nice anyway this is how
we are shooting a movie on a roller rink
looking look Chloe skating look the
stage always shooting around I was doing
everyone just ignore the vlogger yes I'm
just kidding guys we do have a movie to
shoot oh wait this is my stunt double
because I'm not domesticated in the
world he's better looking I like that
you're taking you stuff out oh you're
here bro
yo honestly like this on the scene I lay
with Hawk collars we're gonna do savages
bro I do like your hair better I think I
argue with you alright like what I'm
just gonna go here myself I got a stunt
double
I got a stunt double hey yeah cuz I can
skate like kind of well look good but I
can't do the tricks can you do a trick
good trick you know everyone here is so
good like all the experts are so gonna
do a trick Chloe - Treecko oh cool he's
a fun girl in real life guys don't worry
good this is how we shoot oh because I
need to show you this guy she has not
seen this yet go quickman Chloe official
music video as you drop great quake big
play Chloe you good bro shooting right
now but this is much more Larry
Chloe's doctor skate is literally
staggering it's going on social media
you're gonna be so embarrassed your
heart is happy this is so embarrassing
holidays damn bro I can tell you for a
fact if I gave Chloe's a service you
wouldn't be good no way this is what you
do when you're bored when you're not
shooting hello gang doing mean it's
chill chill doing the mclogan gave me
this camera to do some video you know
let's go hang out with Logan dude
where's Logan at man I was something we
got Logan right here with us how I know
this was a colleague's one but I would
not look it okay we got we don't know
where Logan sighs if I'm going to find
Logan dude dope oh here's Logan what's
up look oh man I saw wrong Logan seems
like I don't know Logan that well this
is this what is this Logan come is this
Logan coming up what's up Logan
that's not look it has a 100% out Logan
okay I don't know Logan at all I've
worked with him for two days I just want
to get him his camera back at this point
I got to get out of it oh my god that's
Logan dude I'm sick I'm a blogger no I
think you are yeah do you feel you got
it dude I'm ready oh wow yo got hold the
camera just a little hi everyone I hope
I was holding it the right well I don't
know bro look I chose I think
I don't know how to say this so I'm
gonna sing it we are Paul feels good to
you huh Chloe doesn't like me young I've
seen you looking real basic but this
might stop the cake right typical super
base for that I understand it was a long
day yeah yeah yeah I know I'm feeling
good all right this hotel room that the
gaming is actually kind of cool temple
gets the job done but you guys know I
love you whoo and this is sick you know
we got the 480° unsetting over here I
love coming home like after a super long
day and you're just exhausted but you
get so much energy
okay okay yo so here's the thing well
gang I've been saying it for the past
like week to week we are currently the
number two fastest growing channel on
YouTube indicated by this graph here and
my graph I mean chart right under
YouTube movies I don't even know what
that is but it's not a person so
technically we're number one yeah baby
yeah also guys I was listed in the
forum's top 10 influencers list as
number three wise up from the number
three best influencer biggest if I don't
know what it means but I'm number three
Pro Thank You farms but let's be honest
guys we're number one but I'm definitely
appreciative of the honor it gives me
something to look forward to and
something to chase for next year's
really what's all about chasing your
goals and achieving them yeah also guys
I think I saw so know that Chloe Bennet
no what are you reaching for no Chloe
don't chuck Chloe I like you this is
trouble oh she's leaving damn bro I'm
definitely out here I'm in here I guess
who I was later yeah it's been like two
hours as you can see since the title
card just said I went out just for a
little bit with the cast tomorrow is
actually my last day of valley girl kind
of sad dude it's my first big studio
feature film and it all ends tomorrow
dudes anyway you guys may or may not
know I've been like poking the biggest
youtuber on YouTube his name is
PewDiePie otherwise known as beauty
pageant or roast me he's gross - my
brother twice now all I want to do is
get roasted by this guy and finally
finally bro he put something out now I
watch this let's see what we got come on
PewDiePie roast me bro give me a good
welcome Paul yeah wants to meet her rows
10 yes ok beauty pie give it to me bra I
don't really see the point because
heroes themselves practically with every
single up no you're a hatter I'm gonna
kill you
no no brothers did not I must have
missed something I don't really see the
point because he wrote himself
practically burn every single op close
my cool there for a second ok so beauty
pie responded to me I'm not roasting me
God bless Amer you guys this look
internal struggle right now it's true I
do roasts myself it's like part of my
strategy roasts me I'm aware of
everything that I'm roasted will for its
logic role and then an eight-mile have
you seen the movie anyway guys that is
the vlog it's an interesting day I said
it before being an actor and also
vlogging is tough but I'm doing my best
for you guys what happens off I make
epilogue I shoot music videos with fans
as you guys hopefully have seen by now
if you have not go watch the music video
it's called hero the link is in the
description so give it a thumbs out know
why I make my thumbs up like that
maverick merch also get yours link in
the description selling like hotcakes
bro yeah I will see you guys tomorrow as
usual guys thanks for supporting me the
Logan is literally the strongest family
on YouTube you know I love you guys all
right take it easy away Chloe Chloe
Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe Chloe
Chloe quake is Lucas no I'm doing the
cool trick