is to show that I am Logan
dude what are you doing man yo are you
okay I might as well be homeless Ari I'm
embodying the role of a homeless man
he's a situation here I was renting
furniture hey Lydia my assistant she
made a mistake
and the other day the parental people
took my virginity
[Music]
okay let's flashback to the other day
when they shipped me of everything I
[Music]
just can't be dealing with this guys
it's a big weekend the numbers song
drops tomorrow the music video which is
absolutely insane drops tomorrow 11:00
a.m. by the way be ready to like it it's
actually crazy I'm really excited for
you guys are gonna love it so yeah man I
can't be being distracted got a lot
going on Hey look
let's just notice my quick dodge on the
fingers there replay reflexes chaos I
watch out Evan Oh slow parkour bleep oh
yeah we got a big issue on our hands
buddy first off we don't have a roommate
right so we got to find a video not only
a roommate a videographer roommate also
I don't know if you've noticed my room
okay I'm about to show you but also if
you're not a part of the low gang make
sure to subscribe we're still it always
will be the most Lapham Leone YouTube
and also the strongest family on youtube
so smash the button copy or maverick
merch normally it's a nicer shape than
this Logan Paul Keim slash yeah a
movement of people doing it different a
movement of people sleeping on the
street is anything like me now let me
show you my room look I know this sounds
bad um thank you maverick I was thinking
the same thing I'm incredibly fortunate
to have a house in a nice house at that
I just would prefer furniture in my room
I don't love to be sleeping on the
ground
[Music]
how you doing with what you okay Oh
weird actually no no I don't want he's
not complaining
cuz he gets the poop on the floor and
possibly hit calm you're ruining my
floors maverick and you're gonna hit
comm one day it's just no bueno look we
gotta do something about this we need
stuff here here maybe even here but I
can't say I'm a fan of like decorating
and interior design so I have enlisted
the help of a professional
kind of hey what up Greg ball what up
log in my house what do you call it took
everything from me any furniture I can
help you good because any bro I'm a
furniture expert it makes me certified
you're he's what he's lying about pretty
much everything sadness before we do
that there's one thing I want to show
you guys how you doing calm good boy I
told you we're doing a podcast well as
you guys know it's called impulsive and
the set is gonna be here in the garage
yeah it's gonna be lit I need all the
thoughts over the age of 50 to stop
using that word
it's so little mister hey we gotta
figure out this roommate situation
somebody bro I know it's like they gotta
be special too it's just gonna be hard
to find someone as dope as us what do we
put it Adson we're late going like
Craigslist or something I'm saying like
yeah oh yeah that works yeah why I don't
boom a wall they gotta be a videographer
I have hands to hold the camera God will
send it the guy outta here man but yeah
so definitely send it for sure I'm gonna
maybe to ask you about that evidence
Moke detectors are covered with the back
like that makes them pretty useless in
malls in the sky a jacket
no need to so much or bring shock into
this game like the city this can't be
safe it's like the new roommate should
be able to fix smoke detectors we have
to do it what about that carbon monoxide
hi this is good hey Lydia I need you to
make a resume we're gonna find a
roommate new roommates going on
Craigslist here's what we need guys send
it you gotta be able to send it send it
ability you're gonna have to be a
videographer I have hands to be a
videographer yeah and gotta be able to
fix smoke detectors yeah Oh maverick
House roommate application videographer
sending ability smoke detectors
application back to the other issue I
need furniture yo are you joking up for
real this takes me to Home Depot I'll
tell you what this isn't a complete
waste of time because I did bring some
extra roommate applications I feel like
we just hand them out to people oh wow
they do have like nice things this right
here it's comfortable this one spins
that's great that's great yeah are you
looking for a roommate roommate
application mm-hmm okay I'm looking for
a new roommate are you interested here's
the application Oh No thank you we're
okay okay thank you so much okay okay
can you send it because if so does this
chance you could be my new roommate and
what
I guess I've never thought about it can
you read a shirt oh I'm good okay so we
got a pillow and this plant
the good news is that while we're at the
store we did get a lot of roommate
submissions via twitter at logan paul if
you want to follow me there so yeah i'm
gonna go grab evan and potentially find
a new roommate Skippy it I will watch
the first guy this guy looks interesting
let's say handy I could fix all your
problems your smoke detectors aren't
even on my radar that's so easy I don't
need to say much as you can tell I'm
black okay I'm six-three got dreads I'm
very savage yo yo these are all good
things to show that I am with Cyn deer
but he can't fix the smoke detectors
yeah but he's black that's though we
need some diversity bro I'm so pale
can you fix smoke alarms smoke alarm on
the ceiling do I need a ladder no cuz
I'm seven feet right Wow yo yo yeah
7-foot guy boy I think he's too tall
descending
I think so too it would take a while
right right not too high drop you have
it sorry both I was told welcome Cole I
see you have an open house yeah he's a
little to you he's young right I just
feel like he should be in school
learning yeah you wouldn't have time to
film for us or yeah we'll fix smoke
before fix there's time for that break
your algebra this search is going
horrible well well can't send a kid most
some people can but it's just now those
are three rare qualities to have new
people can get fixer some of detector
send it and also be a videographer look
guys I'm calling it quits all right
that's the vlog the roomie search will
continue if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe so you can
see who exactly makes it into the
Maverick house needless to say I can
promise you they will be savage so smash
the subscribe button also tomorrow guys
the number song is coming out the music
video here is a little preview
I hope you enjoy that gonna be a good
one and if you haven't yet copied
yourself the hottest murse in the game
that maverick merch Logan Paul calm /op
link in description or link I wall got
the newest drops the crop top booties
for the ladies the performance for the
males blue and purple it's doing it bro
no one little gang I love you and I will
see you tomorrow 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24