we got some updates it's a it's a big
day it's an interesting day we got
Congress average coming down the stairs
how are you young billion we got Spencer
on the grill my boys are always jumping
up here will you make him grow a little
salt BAM Wow that looks delicious and I
say I can't believe I'm saying that
because when I can live before I went
vegan something about like a pile of
vegetables was not appealing your kids
I know bigger okay huh you gotta eat
this you Keaney they do the emoji you
know anyways guys who may have noticed
I'm wearing one of the new Maverick
t-shirts we just dropped this week here
are the other ones super fire the
hottest softest Mercer in the game back
Logan Paul calm /op I preach it every
day you know how it is it's about being
you it's about being a mapper and they
go right you go left not being afraid to
do it different in oh my god he's
actually eating it okay I feel like I've
made mistakes I don't think you grow
your penis in the first place I meant to
say eggplant I think that's a zucchini
Rose is a disaster guys we are now at
the LAPD Newton station yesterday they
have boxing practice for inner-city kids
come on cam you section they box after
school so you know they learn
sportsmanship how to work hard etc it
was pretty cool here's a flashback Nick
hi guys we are currently hiding we're
doing like a LAPD inner-city kids boxing
training sessions all these kids after
school and they come here and they train
boxing which is obviously a much better
and smarter alternative or I see him
brother over there
how does this work am I gonna box the
kids how's this work what am I just
going swing its knock them out apart I
feel like it might not be a good idea
this cops are will takes the knockout
yeah yeah
[Music]
we got the same hair color dude I like
that going on right here yeah you know
we got that boxing ring and everything
but goosing is that daily TV boxing team
this year
do a little something with the kids I
they're very excited to meet by having
you guys stick a lot
[Music]
you guys working hard who's gonna win
Jake you're dead G you like you zip up
my pocket yes
I can't move myself I gotta go time yeah
hold the camera just like that thanks
man thanks you know the Maverick yeah
pockets they got zipper
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my I almost hate I'm excited over
veggies but I said later guys you guys
know all Gus she's that she's the he's
right here that's a picture of her it's
her birthday and I told her we were
gonna go laser tagging the issue is I've
changed my mind I don't want to do that
anymore I'm just tired man I'm not
trying to sweat running around shooting
lasers and mice like I already had
boxing class this morning do because it
come up with me an excuse to tell Olga
why we can't go laser tagging you could
tell her you're allergic to latex
hey so you know how he's supposed to go
laser tagging yeah no I'm not flaking
I'm not flaking
I actually actually have a real thing I
just found out that I'm actually
allergic to lasers I went to the same
area for I know this and I found out
that I'm allergic to tagging it's a
doctoral thing otherwise it'd be so much
fun no I'll just stop don't be like that
we could do other fun things I'm
actually like not allergic to bowling
balls yeah yeah Rommel is two balls but
I guess yeah we could go oh that's the
reason you clicked on this vlog there's
some more drama brewing on you know what
you know why people like drama I think
everyone especially like in LA people on
YouTube everyone Instagram whatever is
so fake and social media definitely
doesn't help with that because it can
just heighten people's perceptions of
who they think you are quick example
when I walk around in public I'm not
like screaming at people but in the
vlogs I but the thing about drama is it
makes people real it's it's a raw form
of entertainment that people just love
watch another quick example on August
25th I'm fighting that I'm beating up
that British kid I am gosh darn positive
that it's going to be the biggest
internet event in history just cuz
people like seeing people fight and have
drama into it with the Klout gang who
which by the way like it's you add three
letters to low gang and it's clogging
I've always had like something so minor
be for that boy specifically this
dude Wolfie well I'm actually cool with
um this is the video I saw he did then
think Jake posted the full confrontation
on his YouTube channel I haven't seen it
yet so we're gonna react to that yes
yeah so excited for this was about to
happen
[Music]
walk the walk yeah I remember this I
remember this Wolfie was posted up in
the background just watched like no one
had daddy's back it's a whole nother
issue but yeah I remember what it was
thought that was weird I'm not the type
of person that like strays away from
this stuff in person like on the
internet like yo that's cool whatever
but like if you're gonna talk person
then like I'm from Ohio dog like true
this is how we do it like Saints there
gonna happen with chance and Anthony and
rice come like they saw him in person
rice I'm trying to shake their hand it's
like not it's not like that it's not
like that isn't it that's not that's not
how we grew up in Ohio it's like you
could talk all you want over the
internet but in real life if you're
gonna act like a school it's not like
let's settle the beef and then we can be
cool but not like that this like whole
thing happened for like four minutes I I
got I didn't think like I didn't say it
like no one was there I didn't think
like a six foot four [ __ ] here's the
issue like I said like I saw Wolfie a
Coachella bro I went up to him and his
boy I was like it was a club Jake is my
blood that's my brother right there so I
have a little bit of an issue but you
want to watch the vlog here's the vlog
[Music]
no that can't be it I came for drama bro
come on where's the fire whatever know
what's good Jackie you click mated your
own brother oh come on you know what I
think you won't be fuzzy some very new
memories just drop for new t-shirts this
is one of them really oh here the other
three oh I see anyways I guess what what
what I'm just kidding violence guys is
not the answer unless it's logan paul vs
k aside then it's the only answer
alright guys yeah cop the new march
Logan ball that kind of /aa draw in the
Maverick movement we're getting more and
more every day they're selling like
hotcakes I'm not gonna lie I had if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe as it says on that
wall which is depending on how many more
plates we throw through it we might
break entirely through the wall yeah but
yeah guys I love you and I'll see you
tomorrow not tomorrow I will see you
next time
[Music]