[Music]
okay what if I told you I woke up at
3:00 a.m. this morning and we are no
longer in Los Angeles what if I told you
we flew to Seattle to spend Thanksgiving
with unlace family hey you guys are
glass today oh good morning okay you
guys know we just had the red drop you
no matter Marissa how to stop the flirt
in the game oh the railings are even red
bro he's is blood and moves oh I'm so
white yo and we got the red map back
guys you know this we're doing an entire
site wide 20% discount through Cyber
Monday we've never done a discount this
big and we're probably never gonna do it
again
you know christmas is coming up so go go
spend a million dollars worth of
maverick merch for you your family
member what led everybody want to be a
maverick everybody want to be different
passionate we work hard to achieve our
goals also I'm flying two of you guys
out here to sitcom two of you I here to
container riding the red Challenger with
me
so yeah time is it God Church o'clock
look like I'm slash shop now let's go we
got Thanksgiving things to do
oh no okay I'm just remembering it's
something you guys may not know about
Seattle oh it rains here and a and they
and they gonna give me rain stats I got
50% to 60% every single day yo it's
depressing
I don't like right I like being from
Ohio but living in LA
like literally I've forgotten what it's
like to see you and smell rain you know
we are 70% water so humans
I still hate
in the rain what a glorious
okay guys I'm not gonna lie I'm a little
nervous as if I'm already not obnoxious
nothing at my own Thanksgiving penting
it with another family bro like they're
gonna hate me bro there's a good chance
to get kicked out of your things you
know you're part of that let me thank
you
they're warming me up baby you think
you're gonna come here and not even your
feet this is amazing this place is
beautiful like you're in the nicest way
possible
what's my family your family so much
better bro mama look you got like a
little Hobbit Dorothy this is one of the
most my favorite parts of the whole
house this is oh so beautiful oh wait
I've seen this I've seen this in a movie
what is the movie um Harry Potter
I've seen his Harry Potter ha ha I've
seen this I could do this bro
dance studio no this is crazy
this also reminds me guys no handlebars
came out yesterday is funny because I
actually haven't released it yet by the
time you're watching this vlog you will
have hopefully seen it giving it a life
yeah officially later I'm so excited to
hear how your families react to me
singing I can ride your girl with no
handlebars let me know how that goes in
the comments below anyways you know what
I'm realizing the more we walk around
I'm like yo Andy is like the perfect guy
like this is the guy you want your
sister today I know you're engaged or
like whatever can you please marry my
sister bro Oh what I do isn't jakey no
Jake I love you baby but the oboe nose
look at this is the woodworking station
my guy's the handyman Oh animals is the
turkey it's Thanksgiving this the actual
turkey my turkeys just like the koi they
call on the men birthdays why are we
eating that turkey Andi that's kind of
stuff bro okay I'll go get it
oh I didn't realize that action be able
get this close Wow
come here turkey come on now Oh God oh
my gosh you're so ugly you're such a
friendly go I see a donkey just because
you're his donkey this burrito
oh hi go did you know that it's 20% off
through cyber monday on the maverick
website what about your burrito you get
your read drop march here I'll hook it
up for you oh no hottest version that
yeah okay anyone could be a maverick
even if you're a goat you can tell he's
the coolest animal in the shed
oh that's my boy looking like a maverick
what a start with the chain there's only
one way this go can get cooler and
that's what the $40,000 Rolex huh can
you calm down I'm vlogging yo let's go
cut a rolly on this goes a mess any
unique clothes go to your family's
Thanksgiving or what we should honor I'm
blinded by the Italian Chester honey Oh
what those nipples away sir I'm so sure
your family's gonna hate me by the time
I leave I'm also sure they're all gonna
be long gangsters all jokes aside guys I
got clean the goats pooped on me
chickens pooped on me there's the
frickin turkey scratch me bro like dude
I know I'm out here no mom the turkey
scratches street-cred instant the
ultimate Thanksgiving street cred
anyways I'm gonna get dressed I don't
want to but I have to you know got to be
respectful
yeah hey you want some cheese yes great
handmade and milked from the goats down
at the front Oh sick
hey go woohoo I'm not ready for this
lots of people lots of responsible
adults and these families better than
mine I came here oh that's right cuz
Andy's just your girl right you have to
behave because you're like you're like
the kid like looking for approval you
know parents and family have a collared
shirt on I don't let's go and you're the
one who jumped in the water why'd you I
know was you I have no idea what you
don't even everybody I just want to
thank everyone we're letting me blog you
and also apologize simultaneously for
ruining your Thanksgiving please
subscribe to my channel it's good daily
content
standing with your girls looking good I
just gotta have you started compensating
then you asked me all about my shampoo
thinking what's that about but it kind
of made me that so I told you come
through you know what we gonna do
candles and live light sit down playing
Cody since running your fingers through
all of this Blonde Ambition to the fudge
you in the shower but the water ain't
run and you still got all your clothes
on got my products on the counter and I
put it all together I just can't get you
out of my game hey hey be thankful food
the social media guy huh cypher family
get off your cell phone this food is so
good I can put you in a mansion
perfectly steal all of Andy's day as
responsible people and then become
responsible myself
hahaha adulting yo I'm imagining this is
how all of you are watching no
handlebars I literally just uploaded it
I feel like uploading on Thanksgiving
was a bad idea that's a dirty song
literally the course is I can ride your
girl with no handlebars I don't even
know what that means I literally have no
idea there's like huddled around is
dirty
like yes you can yes you can Andy has a
really cool family as you saw in the
montage just for those of you who are
getting dirty looks from your aunts and
uncles toe your aunts and uncles are
soft bro maverick life I can ride them
girls with no boss and speaking of
remixes yo my brother just released his
his viral hit every day bro he did a
remix anyway the song features Gucci
Mane which is awesome and I'm about to
watch it for the first time and react to
it man uh it might be Shh it might be
good I don't know I remember the last
time I reacted to everyday bro um he
made a song called the low gang sucks
and then I made a song called the fall
of Jake Paul and the Paul Brothers
exploded the internet with be super
volatile super unhealthy but got a
little reacting station here and I don't
care about the consequences that
happened last time I'm gonna do it again
exactly Oh actually no that's your chair
yo come over here you ask Andy you got a
nice okay reacting to my brother's
everyday bro remix for the first time
here right away he says that disney
channel flow palsy bro oh my gosh your
burrito do you ship Lambo baby could you
put a Lambo on your back no okay
[Music]
I will say I am I am actually impressed
at the flow I'm gonna be honest one
second can yo can you guys shut the [ __ ]
up I'm vlogging damn got roads because
they didn't get eaten on Thanksgiving
they're so happy when Jake told me he
wanted to be a rapper I remember we were
sitting at the team's henhouse the first
one in his garage he's a gamete I'm
gonna start rapping I literally I
laughed and I was like what are you
talking about bro and like I am
pleasantly surprised at the flow I will
say though back to check Jake I love you
I don't think you've ever taken a
private jet to Ohio I could be wrong but
I chopped up look about a console job
it's true though 20% off discount flying
to you I hit around the red challenge
with me Oh yo I gotta say for one second
here stand up this is good energy it's
so cool dude my brother and I are from
Ohio I remember he faced I mean when he
was filming this he goes bro I just want
to say I love you I'm filming a video
with Gucci man our lives are crazy bro
and I love you I was it was out of the
blue I love you too and it's just crazy
dude I expect you'll respect Jake
respect I think I saw a familiar face
three-wide Oh
oh damn Jake damn Wow killing I hate
that I I hate that I like that song I
really wanted the roast you good stuff
bro I'm proud of you man we are we're
making waves doing who's doing it bro
Rito
who's is out here is me maybe Andi with
the spinning hat potentially the music
industry you you might be [ __ ] it's
crazy to cuz I know for a fact like
right now Jake and I are just we're
literally just having fun and playing
around with music and we both start
taking it seriously and get like actual
people who know how to do music bro
that's so rap quotes hallo gang it's the
next day are currently on a horse yeah
you'll see why it's tomorrow's vlog guys
we're shooting a music video right now
but new camera guy Omar as you guys know
something was wrong with the footage so
I'm doing the outro now simple stuff man
you guys know red drop today's Black
Friday so get your merch looking public
on slash shop 20% say wide discount also
gonna fly out to lo gangsters to take a
ride in the red Challenger with me if
you're not a part of the lo gang you
suck you can unstuck if you to smash the
subscribe button hit it in the face for
me guys we have the strongest family on
YouTube in real it we ride horses and
make music videos that said lo gay I
love y'all I will see you tomorrow which
is actually just my today
[Music]