new home goodbye pancake I love you bro
you're free turtle everyone just shut
the hell up for one second
I'm lay we're gonna be late what's new
hey oh good morning little guy
we're back with yet another vlog today
on today's a special one as usual great
job chop now we're on our way to a make
away so make a wish guys if you do not
know make a wish is a foundation that
grants the life-changing wishes for
children with critical illnesses today
for kids have chosen me they wanted to
meet me that's their wish why I don't
know but I'll do it eating these kids is
always so inspiring we have done this
before Jake and I did this at Dave and
Buster's once this we're we aren't we
actually already did I already flashback
to it and today we were making pizzas
together
although guys you know I'm vegan I've
been vegan for like three months now
they had to make special some special
ingredient accommodations from wha-what
is it made of like soy it's just so I
don't know Spencer's the vegan master
Spencer what's vegan is there
grasshoppers in it vegans aren't real oh
yeah we are no touch me I can't because
it's not there hey look we have to get
off at yanny Canyon bull with our boys
I'm a bad driver what else frightening
not to be a total douche ah but I look
it's like you got that new man for
murder I put on a fresh pair of shoes
today I'm feeling good oh my boys up
there it's hard to speak today brother
my boy Mike's got us do a different
teacher except it's funny because the
only thing he doesn't do different is
wear t-shirt other than that one in the
game yeah guys you know we just drop
these new t-shirts and a brand new blue
hoodie I don't actually don't know if
this restaurant Logan Paul calm slash
shop is gonna make a wish of it oh I'm
just not good at getting to places oh oh
you know how I know what this is it's my
new assistant Ayla she's on the phone
she's handling calls for a team maverick
hey Ayla cancel my 2:00 o'clock hey
sorry I'm late guys I uh
my brother is uh hi how are you I don't
want you I do a robe stop oh yeah all of
it I like that
here's the issue if this involves any
sort of like intelligence or like adult
responsibility I'm not capable of doing
that
Ayla Ayla Ayla Ayla could you help me
measure things very difficult part of
opening the east and putting it in I'm
just gonna do that for you and a look at
a flower recognize Ayla
so she's my new assistant again
playing jokes to the camera what's his
deal no she's pretending she's not the
new assistant somebody should tell her
it's make-a-wish not Rico
[Music]
do any of you guys need help from Ayla
much Jake as well the flower resistant
you like that alright hey look I made a
heart taking all my friends she's
supposed to be assisting me
are you a professional chef yes I am are
you my mom no I'm not all right
sure yeah I'm sure okay okay pretty
shirt would you want to view her huh
Andy you're the master chef ro oh my
yeah Andy hey
it's so good I knew Andy it's unex
oh my gosh my looks so boring nice puffs
to it everyone it looks so sad bro
[Music]
okay yellow clothes
take a cute picture I got you guys
that's good good the hottest watching
the game you could sell this on the
black market for three times as much a
big happy family it's really good to
have us have everyone back yeah it makes
me feel like stop working you just put
the dough right on that bag I know yeah
the make-a-wish event was absolutely
amazing I love meeting those kids at
what I'm sorry I couldn't bring you know
I didn't take Kong either that's why I
know I just know I didn't know I didn't
know I didn't know I didn't it's just a
little awkward cuz Kong's down here
looking at maverick like he's a little
high so actually speaking of paths today
is the big day most of you guys know
also by the title of the video we we
have it like a ten thousand dollar super
rare Chinese albino softshell turtle
I don't understand why he cost $10,000
he's super rare and his head is shaped
like a penis it's very special he's
extremely exotic Real Talk though he was
about to be eaten bro
they were about to eat him I think they
caught him at JFK Airport I think I
don't know Chinese folks the turtle
eaters yeah he was about to be a snack
he's looking like a whole snack so for
the longest time guy Han cake has just
been chilling in this little aquarium
and we have an entire koi pond out back
there oh we could never put him in it
because it wasn't the right temperature
it wasn't summertime wasn't hot enough
we thought you might eat the koi he's
pretty aggressive he bit me once
all right guys end up talking about him
let's put him in the pond I'm not
looking forward to this bro oh it's for
the better pancake oh this is actually
smooth oh oh no no bro you can't because
his claws are so sharp
hey why is it being such a dick what if
we put him in some sort of container
[ __ ] it okay actually right here you can
see why we call him pancake cuz he look
like a little pancake toad
put a little syrup on that boy no no
we're not gonna eat him it's his big day
let him have the glory bro leave us
alone dude oh my god I'm so excited guys
so the guy who built this pond he put a
little sandbar a little beach for
pancake and then one under water as well
and a gay underneath so he can't eat the
koi how does it look like pretty good so
instead of the little aquarium right
pancake gets this half of the pond and
this is for the fish and then young
dougie gets the whole entire yard that's
a real non alkaline water disgusting
it's time for the real pancake new home
goodbye pancake
I love you bro you're free turtle Oh
looking goo he's a turtle oh he's
navigating the waters using his head as
a penis guy oh it's a turtle yeah I
think he's getting a
for the punks way right now I've never
seen an animal so happy here as his head
gotten bigger
[Applause]
[Music]
from this angle bro you can't tell if
it's a turtle or a straight-up pancake
oh no that's gonna be a problem
what are you doing Kong this isn't your
territory bro they saved Turtles why
does this a head look like a penis oh
the question we all want to know the
answer to
[Music]
not a shower
well boys our work here is done
you know it's always a little emotional
sending your kids off to be an adult are
we ever gonna see him again
I think so because you know we live here
and stuff anyways guys that is a block
thank you for watching if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to make a
sign in the face and also copy yourself
some average merch it's the hottest
softest merch in the game we out here
doing it different every single day
example we raise penis turtles and
release them into the water doing it
different or the same
I can't do it every day I wear the same
shirt it's too hot bro Logan Paul a cop
/ description
[Music]
tomorrow oh you should say see you next
time
Hey
[Music]
you