[Music]
[Applause]
I spent the whole morning shooting look
at me I'm a mess it's slime on my body I
can't tell you what it's for it sucks
it's even in my hair though it's it's
like a big secret
you'll find out soon but the point is
I'm a mess what am I wearing okay
yesterday we dropped maverick bottoms
why would I not be wearing them no joke
they're too late I know for a fact I
know for a fact Lydia's wearing this
[Music]
joggers marled shorts athletic shorts
leggings for the females to thank you
maverick yeah and you guys know if you
buy merch on this site within the next
like 48 hours joggers pants maverick
hoodies whatever you want oh by the way
the favorite hoodies bad still got my
favorite lady gonna choose five of you
guys to come in and just talk to me chat
about whatever while I'm on Instagram
lives yeah that's a new feature I
figured why not talk to the low gang
so yes he said it for him you guys get
your merge to Logan Paul Keim slash shop
or link in description it is not a joke
guys the Maverick movement is officially
the Maverick revolution this this logo
means so much it's about people and not
being afraid to pursue their passions
and follow their dreams regardless of
what the naysayers do or think we are
drones like 99% of society we act
independently we do our own thing and so
that's what it is and now we have
bottoms to accompany that yo its Saran
son Jeffrey stop yo we should get rid of
this rental furniture before I destroy
it we should definitely have to buy it
all
what are you doing I'm trying to pick
you up
be my friend maybe he doesn't like the
color your hand is Oh this was from this
lime bro he's definitely afraid of it
damn he doesn't like those I think the
clothing brand after you show your hand
oh yeah what mattress even more colors
than I do bro so guys if you remember
yesterday we put 3,000 pounds of dry ice
in that pool
yeah that was dope so if you're not a
part of the low gang yeah ah ha ha ha
you good make sure to subscribe we are
the fastest growing channel on YouTube
we have the strongest family on you two
guys were just the best on YouTube and
that is the facts so hit the subscribe
button for me I'm but it was fun right
but there was one person here who wasn't
here who I love and I wish was here my
second roommate mom but now he's back
and he's in his room right now and he's
been missing from my vlog for like four
days
aka no point are you boys not happy this
is gross Evans play a game called how
many STDs is Arya's cast have good to
see ya Evans via maverick bottoms drop
kind of a big deal what do you have a
you say as a matter of fact we do
haven't you missed literally so much
while you were gone bro
look at all that stuff you missed davon
I didn't see me there well there's been
the adit you missed it you can catch it
tomorrow on youtube.com slash Logan Paul
vlogs art in the gym the gyms done and I
think they're waiting on us to show us I
think they're ready yeah Logan Paul gym
is ready here's the deal it's a big deal
it is a big deal and that is a fact okay
so this is the team guys they have been
slaving for what what three four days
now King love you guys gonna be so dope
here's why it's special because when
they got here we all had like a
brainstorming session and they came to
me and they pitched me ideas and you'll
see everything in there has something to
do with our lives like it's not just
like a random art like thought went into
it any to you talk to your dad what we
talked to your mom I didn't know that
you know at the end of the day it is a
gym my man and I are gonna I have a
feeling when you get excited when I see
this cuz I really love art you're gonna
get emotional I won't get emotional I
just get excited that's why I had Lydia
bring a plate I was gonna say diaper
diaper I don't meet people who grind as
hard as me and they got to work right
away the 18 it's noted there they are
the 80 okay y'all this is it for the
vlog he has not seen this since the
first samples I'll bring Kong out here
don't look and I've avoided like looking
up here cuz I don't oh yeah I'm nervous
bro he's gonna be okay I might not be
okay are you ready to go super Logan six
all right three two
on a real bro oh my gosh oh my gosh
that's what that is so then the universe
is literally it's bent on the wall it's
dented and it's backwards because we're
putting a mirror all along this wall
look at the mirror the reflection will
say so you guys remember when I did the
house tour had that like really long
emotional motivational speech at the end
where I talked about the paper I wrote
when I was 15 about all the positive
affirmations that I wrote down and you
can see this oh I love you to the moon
and back yo got it and if you notice
this constellations right this is the
galaxies the gases the universe that
were dead - no I'm so glad you guys put
that here bro like the astronaut it's
the same astronaut love the painting
inside the house do you see so it's door
of mama right after the mama's name you
see this name
I love salad I won't be the best I will
be show the better looking pulled on
comport / I know he knows anything at
the dad let's go everybody hears them
working around the clock since the
moment we showed up who big props yo
please please joy please go seriously
thank you so much doing seriously I had
this idea since I know that this wall is
gonna be filled with mirrors I want
everyone here goal that you want to
achieve in the next let's say five years
and then it'll be like a little time
capsule thing because it's gonna because
mirrors
[Music]
Oh
no we're not taking a photo I just have
some things to say this is an amazing
group of people a hard-working talented
group of people I am blessed that you
guys blessed my gym with excellence
don't forget locate these guys are
looking amazing they painted a match and
now they painted the most savage gym in
America's walls hey why don't you guys I
made two videos the link for that is in
the description I'm also gonna put his
Instagram in the description if you want
to make your gym savage or a mansion or
whatever we got our goals and everything
[Music]
yeah it's a magical time to be alive
guys my mom is here hi my sweetie who
are you amazing especially because we
got Chinese I had this idea my mom had
this idea okay can you give me one
second I'm so Jake obviously brother
Jake you you birth him on your vagina
he had issues with his neighbor's in
fact his neighbors hated him so I'm
gonna be proactive right so my mom today
what did you do okay so I made a few
phone calls to try to find I'm gonna
speed this up she got gift baskets we're
gonna give to all the neighbors look how
amazing they came out no they're really
good like it's like if I was a neighbor
and I got right I'd be like damn that's
nice so after we uh inhale this Chinese
food me Brendan Evan and my mom are
gonna go around and just deliver these
to the neighbors the conversation is
gonna look something like this hi I'm
your neighbor Logan here's a gift basket
please don't sue me we got a trunk full
of gift boxes yo neighbors I'm a bless
you with this gift box goodness wish me
luck
neighbors are so sweet and cute guy this
is amazing man shout-out to the a-team
for doing this again
seriously guys like I love art and when
it actually means something to me
oh come on guys locating I want to know
what your favorite piece of art is in
here is it the comic ABS is it the Super
Saiyan bogey is it
all throughout the gym so comment below
what you guys like the most and if you
have ideas maybe just put him down we
might add some stuff this will slowly be
turning into a gym do not forget located
bottoms have just dropped the hottest
softest highest-quality merch in the
game I say merch but it's an apparel
company maverick by Logan Paul is
changing the world guys we are
revolutionising we are innovators you
join the movement during the revolution
get your merch looking for the cops
slash shop rolling in description and if
you buy merch jogger sweatpants leg
whatever the want in the next 48 hours
don't forget I'm gonna FaceTime five of
you on Instagram live we're gonna dress
just like it's tough and everything you
do is so yeah and the favorite hoodies
back to men everything you just sound
like a god shirt son every day we are
denting the universe you can't see it
now but every day that is what we do
little gang I love you and I will see
you tomorrow
[Music]