it's not right to do murder okay so this
morning I get a text with my brother
little brother Jake Paul everyday bro
I'm sure you know him anyways he says yo
I say yo classic brother convo and then
from left-field he comes at me with some
series he said I'm making you the
beneficiary of my life insurance policy
so here's the thing I didn't graduate
college guys so I say what's that he
said it's like if I die who gets my
money to split it up and I will say the
it though was with the capital i dot
capital T Apple you're on some weird
autocorrect right now I'm an ideas man
guys sprockets in my brain start firing
this could be a good cash play for me so
just to clarify I said so dot if you die
die die I get to decide how your money
is split up he says I guess it's kind of
confusing but I think okay so then I go
I put meanwhile in the back of my brain
I'm like yo christmas is coming up I
want to buy my dad a mom a nice gift
that could use a little extra cash right
Jake me said a lot of money he's like a
multi-millionaire so I thought about
what any logical rational human being
with a brain would think I I do have to
kill my brother
so that's what this vlog is about hey
good morning if for some reason you're
not a part of the low game make sure to
subscribe I know it's a bit weird
talking about murder and then asking you
to subscribe but guys trust me like it's
not like that the strongest family on
YouTube will it so hit the subscribe
button for the copy Maverick merch where
you can look before that cops that shop
ah he's doing it literally our stuff is
the next level ok back to the topic I
will say Jake is smart he would do the
same thing because literally the next
text he sent me he said please don't
murder me I noted I hear you but I'm
sure I'm positive he would do the same
thing and Jake this isn't personal bro
like you know I love you
this is strictly business - bro that's a
thing it's been an interesting morning
maybe 30 minutes ago I saw my manager
Jeff randomly driving on the freeway
next to us no no way is that Jeff yeah
he's driving the Yeti sister look at
this thing
when did you jump waiting for nobody I
will say I can't say I'm a fan of this
traffic yeah it's always good to make a
scene on the highway but then even
before that we had a little incident at
breakfast I was sitting here just
sipping on my cappuccino and she just
shoves the camera in my face we make the
juda snapchat half-hour
I love meeting you guys in real life
especially when you have energy like
that yo like actually that girl's
amazing but not as amazing as the fact
that you look like this in your republic
with the merchants with the bare feet on
I don't even know if kill she's wearing
underwear I don't even know either way
yo all jokes aside she might not have an
underwear Chelsea knows how to party bro
really though guys we shouldn't get
distracted anymore I'm kind of here to
find something to help me kill my
brother I feel weird saying that but
it's like it's not that bad like it's
not personal like I said I'm getting
distracted by these awesome clothes I
forgot Andy likes Jake oh and he's not
gonna help if he thinks we're actually
gonna kill James we could give any part
of money
yeah and Andy will help us yep this vlog
like my title and stuff we're gonna kill
Jake he said he'd put me as his
beneficiary on his life-insurance policy
I get the side we get some money he
makes a lot of money bro so like I cut
you in like 10% profit and you helped me
dollars and Jake Lamborghini and you
helped me we have to decide I think how
we're gonna kill him like there's gotta
be something here how much is this snake
cage this cane is a snake I see it
that's a real snake speaking of killing
things do you think we could use this to
kill somebody okay
I don't know those teeth look pretty bad
leaves a little that this snake is now
Akane you can have this back you got a
ring it's all I know
how could I bring me a watch somebody
ring yeah you may need to keep looking
oh we got oh my god some kind of bull it
looks dead it is dead
how much okay moving on hear me out we
had this piranhas right these things are
gross and deadly we do some Frankenstein
somehow we revive it bring it back to
life and put it down Jake's pants I'm a
genius
you know what I'm realizing this is like
a pretty peaceful place there's not a
lot of violent things here for murder
like what am I gonna do with this
figurine of a pig nothing however I will
say I have an idea
guys I want this to be done quick
painless easy so I think we should light
him on fire what light him on fire
that's the Lamborghini we got to go big
we got to make a spectacle out of it I'm
in the intelligent business you spot a
new house and we like the house on fire
- we let everything on fire bro team
dimension down to the ground arson but
team 10 do they'll become team zero bro
I don't know bro there's not gonna be
any members left after dude I think this
vlog seriously the next day we have to
do is go to this door and get gas cans
and you guys remember that awesome shark
helmet they took away from me yesterday
at Disneyland
I want another so I'm gonna go back to
Wells Mart and buy another okay please
be here please be here okay kind of it
bro this is dope I just want to have my
nose will look to that soon some meowy
christmas because there's a cat on a
shirt meow yeah so this moment right now
these are solid disguises I definitely
think we're ready to kill someone the
only thing we're missing is the method
of execution all these are perfect five
gallons of gasoline yeah I store at the
gas station doing up these cans here all
Jesus
are you for real like yeah this could be
a big I can make a lot of money so I got
you gotta do what you gotta do problem I
said I know you
it looks pretty serious to me hi we're
good to go gotta fill up the other one
and then go cuz we are losing daylight
let's do it I'll okay we're rolling into
Jake's right now personally I've never
killed someone and I don't plan on doing
it again I'm a little nervous I know
he's got security but they're cool with
me so they let me through how are you
we're here to bring the heat I can see
that yeah but you had no idea for sure I
don't know where Jake is so we have to
be incognito these gas cans are full of
fire I'm full of bad ideas take this
lighter don't forget I'm Ragini you help
me beneficiary I'll give it to you
Lamborghini bro there is gas in there
and you're sparking those I'm holiness
Oh whoa whoa whoa all right here's what
I told Andi you can drive a Lamborghini
you cannot drive Jake so I'm thankful
for your help now let's let Bob
you don't need it you don't need it
Oxana just kidding I'm not
you're this young you get Sam he's still
a little bitter
stop stop stop
whoops - all right is that gas yeah it's
a cash it's a cash bloody I make money
more you son of a [ __ ] is this about
the oh just let me kill you I'm making
so much money murder me I know I know
you said that let me catch you don't
murder me I know I know I know
go respect relation that novel bro if I
was your beneficiary I don't want to
kill you - hi I'll get to maverick house
Oh
understand you are my beneficiary
I was gonna tell you because I feel like
you
when gasoline is ignited brothers come
United what I'll okay that's the vlog an
interesting one today I couldn't get
them this time but something I have
learned guys it's not right to do murder
so do good things and good things will
happen to you guys this always like fun
and jokes and stuff but when things come
actually serious guys like I'm not
actually gonna kill my Hey
not this time Jake I'm home I'm alive
I'm saving with my low game that's the
vlog do yourself a favor cups on the
hottest Mercer the game that maverick
Merc link in description look a ball
that got slashed up or your Lincoln
store we got it all if you're not a part
of the low game make sure to subscribe
nobody doesn't like us bro no one likes
their brother on fire who's doing I was
Jesus sounds bad don't do that nobody
doesn't like us guys we're different and
that's what makes us us that's what
makes us special with that said looking
I love y'all I will see you tomorrow Oh
make-a-wish foundation think tomorrow's
gonna be amazing anyways take it easy
Babu
you