kids in the candy shop yo guys we are in
a gym equipment weight room boss
multiplied facility guys we're getting
weights for my personal at home gym it's
too late we took everybody's live
Brendon babe if you're not a part of the
low game you subscribe the strongest
family undo to that we only getting
stronger not cuz we're lifting weights I
don't work out facility but because we
grow when we work and we getting better
every day that's what it's all about
progression working hard to achieve your
goals that's what these vlogs are about
feliu I can inspire you guys to achieve
whatever you want achieve that's the
maverick movement it's what we've read
bit off this is doing it no one's making
much like this but it's still important
to stay healthy and exercise oh dude
this is a partner workout I really like
this one
friends Oh change Roga one thing about
me I never change but I always change
one thing the low gang doesn't know
about the Maverick
what are you doing just like you don't
sleep on hospital I will say she's got
dope shoes
alright respect joggers - yeah feel it
fashion we definitely need one of these
cages bro this reminds me of the cage
fight I had in my movies are thinning -
coming next year and it's red oh
speaking of that not at all do you wanna
hear what Gucci sounds like an stainless
steel blue is the color to discuss on
the original over here yeah just because
I'm the original maverick logo the the
ends of the wings aren't Brennan back
here the tips of the wings are blue
well these arms already off I got them
right here
wellness anyways guys all jokes aside we
did pick up a bunch of good stuff good
stuff those are all words you should
know now on my friend Andy he has a
fiancee police commitment anyway they
are being cute they went to Disneyland
today and we're kind of close to them so
I think we're gonna go to Disneyland to
ruin their day we're going to Disneyland
also Mike what the you wearing bro what
is that shirt bro bro I ran through take
that stuff my snot merch take off it so
while Mike goes into Wells Mart and goes
to buy a new shirt
cuz I forgot ahead so don't have any
merch with me it's in high demand
everybody wanted to be a mother this is
a good time to say if you follow me on
instagram at Logan Paul you'll see we
went out last night we got pretty crazy
last night a plane wait what wait a
plain black shirt no I worrying since
one of my boy loses personality
we're gonna try go Disney way that's
what I'm talking about
much better it's really because you're
out of this world are you in the low
gang whose phone is this who's gonna
steal hi what's up I'm gonna give the
phone back because I could go to jail
for robbery feel like a kid again
now from a developmental standpoint guys
I am worried there's probably a lot of
low gangsters here no promise it would
stop I just want to keep moving and not
trying to get like mob and killed by you
guys are very strong in numbers
so uh Kelsey Wyss Kelsey look like a
cone wait wait we should say who Kelsey
is uh I was gonna say that out of
everything at Wells Mart oh this is
amazing
I feel Sharkboy and Lavagirl
cuz she's a red let's go to this new
hand profile oh oh I don't know if this
disguise is gonna work but bro you have
your face on your shirt what I'm cocky
burning I'm a good-looking guy that's
correct but it's disguise it's not for
safety reasons this cannot be used a
weapon unless immediately if he walks in
there without that helmet on you will
have a mass of children congregating
from every angle into one place it'll
cause an issue of epic proportions
ah
I wish you were allowed to keep that
helmet bro I wish you warned you we
won't you
Disneyland just making me sad I have an
idea yeah they might actually not as we
try to go again and well I'm breaking it
cannot be pretty man you're a man so no
you can't be pregnant beautiful to know
me and then you don't know me I'm
pregnant
your baby has a fin 2017 the speed of
pregnancy and every dips peanut bro just
like kinda changed I got one item on the
agenda and that's fine
we're out here at this new head Oh who's
a busy you a surprise you'll ruin your
date with Melissa I come to ruin your
day look at this
are you done told you it wasn't gonna
work boom man they're nothing pictures
of me no you can leave your candy palace
bro can I pet you guys all take a piece
of candy bars right call back you're
looking a candy palace yes you know true
and love candy powder
you know them you're a real man
my nose is bleeding
Wow Disneyland's great I'm happy quick
give me the highlighter yeah all right
all jokes aside I really do gonna get
the busting here however it this place
is really cute me I'm probably gonna be
single and lonely for the rest of my
life but Andy a Melissa are getting
married here kind of like opened up
doors camera there you go and then turn
your heads and kiss a little bit great
and then just kind of stop trying
health relieving having dinner or
leaving no as if people were already
staring at her cuz she looks like a
highlighter
what are you doing she's running away
come back how's the Chelsea hello I'm
fine
Kelsey used hair relief
okay low gang guys we're home we're safe
Kelsey still at Disneyland you ditched
her I got to do block I'm gonna do
something I should have done a long time
ago bro but don't worry Mike I got you
there you go did you have that in your
pants the whole time yeah I always have
emerged in my pants Logan baldock comes
last job orally in the shop yeah yeah
we're out here if you're not part of the
low Gaming salute
that's that's Cantonese for subscribe or
you look weird
this is gonna be a new designer hit okay
that's it okay that is the boy I love
y'all I would see you tomorrow
hahaha