I'll say this this is comedy writer this
is good stuff the only thing that would
make this better is manager Jeff what's
poppin oh come on my man shooting the
merch Kevin like a savage Jill where are
you going uh are they gonna be with you
today
no it really the whole day well the
loganing needs you do look at bro they
need you I need you too nice backpack
you ever way before you go bro I got
something for you take it there you go
and then I got one two will count to
three just kidding let's got the one one
are you okay you need to call Jake Paul
I'll be even more scared oh yeah don't
call it Jake by heaven
probably not smart to be here in my bare
feet this is pure entertainment value
I'm a savage I'm fine I'm just havin to
get a job get that yep yep we're out
here mom's I'm sitting here now and I
realize that something cut me a little
bit I'm not sure if it was the plate or
Jeb's broom but you boy got blood on his
foot right here who's gonna take some of
this make a little war cry this is my
blood it's your blood where is it
I'm the face oh my god your real blood
yeah you know I don't know why I did
that
oh yeah savage get your bone flesh oh I
gotta fight back it's Amalia but first
and is here good morning Brandon how are
they all looking for love
so before I open this doll package you
you guys have probably noticed there's
somebody we've been missing
yes oh my god
are you oh wait just a second I'm sorry
[ __ ] again are you good
this is not calm this is the stuff here
that's touchdown okay yeah let's open
this thing because this is actually sick
here we'll open it using fake Gong oh it
worked
yeah we get we get breakfast burrito
shipped to us every day bro sorry Jeff
had your fun Jeff I'm just kidding guys
we thought it was gonna be something
else the new Maverick backpack oh wait
what oh we new maverick backpaki yeah
yeah Jeff can't put this on oh but there
is one thing I dig in the mail that I
know is do boy boy Jeffrey put that down
burrito
come help me life-size cardboard cutout
of your boy
always reppin row I feel like I'm being
rebirth like this is I'm being born
again and this time I'm not even coming
out of he mom's vagina okay what Betty
30 you're watching are you feeling
recording yes how is it wrong is it like
is it doe or I think it's perfect Paul I
think anybody's gonna make out would you
like it real life or make out with this
not it's not before me mmm I feel like
that's a pretty good like I would I
would kiss me I think Jeff would you
kiss me bro oh wait a second there's
more
Hey looking scared she always is because
now we should march on her all the time
by the way like here's how I tricked
Ella into posing for this hey guys so
Allah is doing a photo shoot with
Brendan right now we told her it's for
the merch but I thought Brendan to have
her take it like a couple scared ones
and like happy ones and sad ones like
just for fun but we're only gonna use
the scared one I did have an idea I want
to take this down to the street cuz uh
you know we just hit 9 million followers
subscribers guys can we get 10 million
I'm coming for you you son of a [ __ ]
but what I was saying one recently like
I've just been you guys have seen it
just getting bombarded like noticed on
the streets and I love it I love meeting
you guys some why sometimes when I'm
walking to the store since you guys are
like right outside of my house I'm like
okay I like I just want to get milk or
like almond milk or like condoms
whatever it is if I put this out there I
think it could be a good distraction
maybe you guys I think it's me and then
I go get ready Logan no yes see Brendan
you fell for it love me okay
we're gonna be sleek about this I hope
this works just walking myself oh snap
bro the lo games are there well they
know it's going I'm so calm right now
that's actually pretty cool I like it
wait that's it a bird just I'm a bird
wait is that your bird yeah you guys
have this bird this is that we have oh
my god no should we bring them upstairs
and have them eat maverick you know you
introduced your birth to my vertebra on
a hundred simply let's go upstairs and
make this happen
welcome to the crib of your hammer cows
now dude so what kind of bird is is
France each green cheek conure maverick
is a Sun Conure is it a boy or girl it's
a girl oh my god maverick has never been
with a female bird that is also a conure
ever in his life always never smashed
little mama bird baby little maverick
babies row so they took une out guys
this is a beautiful bird like I'm not a
huge bird person but I know a pretty
bird when I see one hi how are you can
you give me a kiss
[Music]
just like every other girl in my life yo
my boy yo you have no idea no I know I'm
telling you you have absolutely zero
idea what's going down watch this by the
way give me kiss mm yo look you guys
could be in love this is the first
interaction Mavericks ever had with the
female bird yo he's flirting with you
say something back Danny
oh he's not headed for any quick little
sidebar first impressions maverick you
don't need to be nervous
does maverick need the service you need
are you good yeah you got it right here
for you do you go bus or head yeah I
know just like deep breath and it's time
to smash buddy
I know maverick G come on you're
embarrassing yourself
no you're embarrassing me too okay you
got to start talking to Scott I stopped
running from your problems you're home
now okay now I'm gonna put yes good idea
actually I'm gonna put you guys in your
cage and we'll see what happens
maverick you yeah this is cool this is
gone Bonnie with yeni maverick does not
like hands he doesn't like hands going
behind him but yeah he does yeah fights
me sometimes yeah he bites everyone
I don't know like I got stuff to do
obviously like you you guys are
lovebirds
literally okay guys I think we're gonna
put up a maverick cam leave them landing
and we'll see what happens good idea
[Music]
okay I'm not sure exactly what happened
we go there's the time-lapse I couldn't
see it okay do I feel like this was a
pretty good first day oh where you going
okay like I don't know did they make it
to first base possibly but yeah that was
fun
where you go I want to thank you guys
for coming to my house oh yeah that's my
baby yeah you're good I got you guys
some March there in the lawyer unit for
you you look like you're working out
yeah and you're a maverick this does you
know what I write you guys know why you
saw every time I look at it it just
breaks my heart a little more and more
guys so if you didn't see yesterday's
vlog some lady ran into my brand-new
Yeti lo gank don't worry though my
insurance company is handling it I think
I don't know guys but the important
thing to remember is hey guys look
there's the sign that says right turn
only the lady must not have seen that
yesterday when she turned laughs like
like duh this will be the show oh my god
like she just ran into me right here
with an 8 foot tall gleaming white car I
don't know how you I don't know live
questions pay attention and go infinite
life questions kids stay in school
otherwise you'll hit $300,000 gee let's
see what the local gangsters think of
this whole situation
Eddie being damaged absolutely jinx that
if we came out from that building you
were gonna come out I'm leaving so I
don't get arrested but I'm banned oh
good cook me
calling Ella right now because I want my
dog back don't go she's a claim like
puppy sitter hi hello Ella it's me Logan
Paul on Instagram yeah yeah for sure
anyways oh you still calm hopefully yeah
you didn't lose him or anything you've
done it twice before did you bring him
over you can come as well but I'm tired
of carrying around fake Kong like he's
just not as satisfying to me emotionally
oh great okay thank thank you for
bringing my dog back to me see obviously
I'm thankful for her she's been watching
calling and stuff for me I've been busy
enough where it furs and hoping fake
hogs and she's my joke today
[Applause]
I got waiting for this thing on his face
oh because he just had surgery
he just got neutered so he'll lick
himself if you take that off neutered
like like you guys balding this is a
joke I know yo if she's serious I'm
about to cry stop feel my heart don't
even act like that feel our did you fix
my dog in the past like three days
without asking me hey look my dog has
enough coals right now you are gobbling
your monster you can't reproduce you
literally stripped him of his man
this is I'm losing my mind I was gonna
have you look at I got you this cool
thing I was going to surprise you with
you it's the lie the Queen let me show
you
oh he's barely a man oh my god he
doesn't have fall he's just cold
he's not like dead how would you like it
you wouldn't you know what then maybe
you shouldn't have told me to make this
appointment all right this is why I
can't be your assistant this is what
honey said why I fired her cuz she did
this looking sexy I gotta say this this
is a comedy writer this is good stuff
the only thing that would make this
better is
[Applause]
calm down I know I know it's bad okay oh
look now my head is in this big ego goes
back I'm angry and you don't know about
it just call Ayla
well you good bro only I'm only doing
this because you're my boy bro that's it
for the vlog honey your head if you're
not a part of the family make sure you
subscribe oh Jesus okay and also get
your maverick merch the link for that oh
also keep active and also keep maxing
out your vote for me and the Teen Choice
Awards the link for that is also in the
description lots of links in the
description okay guys I love you guys
and I will see you tomorrow take it easy