hey oh good morning low gang what's
poppin our guys I'm gonna get right into
it because it is hot as balls outside
and not because of the Sun because of
them every March what's up baby hottest
merch in the game look Paul that kind of
/aa so before we dive in here guys good
news there is a second press conference
yes that's right a second press
conference for my beat down against ksi
this one is in the UK it's on July 18th
so Wednesday should be a big deal I'm
sure you all remember the first one
let's hope he doesn't run at me again
this time move mark your calendars guys
okay without further ado let me tell you
a little bit about Chicago
[Music]
oh my god we have made it to Chicago a
lot of travel lately this is the last
little bit of like vacation I guess
before the fight well I mean you know
odd is but we still have taking days off
I'm still yoked this hey there
cam here's the fourth of July know that
holiday where America declared its
freedom is simply against the UK we
whupped their ass to talk in UK aside
but I'm not here to get diplomatic I'm
just here to have some fun if you are
not a part of the low game make sure to
subscribe guys we are the most lit
channel on YouTube we've been through so
much but that's what makes it a strong
that's what makes us a family that is
what makes us Mavericks you guys can see
I got the new merch right here we just
dropped five new pieces local balls icon
flash hey what's up dude all right for
sure local ball that cop slash shop or
link in description you guys know how it
is I gotta say don't bug travel and
excitement rolling so far Chicago is
looking way
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I wish I could tell you how this
happened somehow Chloe got asked to
throw the first pitch at the baseball
game she's from Chicago so it's a big
honor and stuff the only issue is
Chloe's really really unathletic like
like I don't think she's ever you know
bro I've known her for a year and I
haven't seen her run once she refuses to
run in front of me I can't imagine what
it's like throwing a projectile needless
to say this should be interesting
I've been to a baseball game India all
I'd sing another brothers all play
baseball I
they never let me play Chloe play
baseball she played left out
it's like a joke cause it sounds like
left-field but she just sits to bet
those are acting shoulders those are
baseball phone shoulders
[Music]
we thought there was gonna be no one
here to see her throw the fits but yeah
there's a lot of people here so how do
you feel about this is gonna be pretty
impressed with myself that's gonna make
you look like you can actually pitch a
ball no I'm just like I'm so excited for
you to like throw something
oh you got us
I'm a sweet she's fainted she's doing
the antic
[Applause]
[Music]
to the game
pretty cool montage right now cut that
show real quick Benson I was right there
by the way say hi Spencer
we almost hate each other and ruined
both jet skis literally missed each
other by inches and then still just
didn't didn't learn the lesson Spencer
who's right there still by the way say
what's up he got thrown off the jet
violently thrown off the jet ski it
looked painful can we get a replay okay
well it's a good thing we have that
homemade cast for you otherwise you'd be
in trouble saving a lot of money great
time but [ __ ] we maverick we can't let a
little broken arm stop our fun after all
it was the fourth of July let me tell
you these fireworks were amazing
[Music]
there's a play
yeah not really literally as soon as the
fireworks ended our whole group fell
into the bosom of Satan's
you know I don't know everything was so
beautiful and on the race back to the
harbor just a fan oh no the beach is not
okay I don't know how these stayed up
that's amazing it must be the chosen
glasses those are the chosen lasses yo
there has to be a boat that that's hid
out there that was sketchy I feel like a
real pirate right now well like I said
earlier low gang were Mavericks and
ain't no storm I'm gonna smile
alright guys that is the vlog thank you
guys for watching if you're not a part
of the low game make sure to subscribe
also copy stuff some of the hottest
softest merch in the game during the
Maverick movement it's a movement of
people doing it different a movement of
people who are not afraid to be
themselves a unique group of people who
are gonna take the world and I'm working
on my motivational speaking logo
Polikoff slash shot alright say that
link in description i low gang I love
you guys I will see you tomorrow ksi
imma beat your ass yeah we stand
oh we do it start oh we do it start yeah
we start all we do is done all we do is
done
oh we do it's done all we do is done
doing stunts are we doing stunts are we
doing
those are acting shoulders those are
baseball consoles we all we do