oh wow hey yo good morning Logan what
okay guys we are gonna get right into
the day no stalling no waiting we who I
and all I gotta say is oh oh yeah well
gum a voice is god oh yeah I'm supposed
to go down so hard as if our place is
already not cool enough we're putting a
giant bounce out to you good boy atta
boy
how have you existing nice yeah so if
you just look over this area over here
over there cut like over the spot oh you
look like a bounce house type of guy
tell me this isn't a spot broke she love
you Ringo killer I've killed people
while looking at this view that's a joke
guys I haven't killed anyone
it's not a joke so this is the mover
here god you had to come to the front
because apparently that thing is too
heavy to get to the back man whatever
dude is this the big blue one that we
got oh let's talk about that guy so no
yesterday I told you was gonna be a big
blue one Hurley was too big and too blue
rest in peace so we got a different one
it's a double yellow slide still cool
though so we can play yeah we're gonna
Marissa and dicks off Brendan you know
what needs to be done while they're
doing this follow me with a mortise Coco
session watch your thumb I've never done
this
do you help me bro you guys didn't see
literate Bennett in the dick mr. famous
if he goes off oh you're my boy set it
up for me bro you know we need straw if
your life is good in Hawaii right now we
got straws we got knives we got coconuts
I realized those completely unnecessary
it's cut it open like that guy I killed
I mean um like a oh so delicious you see
the fresh coconut water in there now if
you don't mind me mmm good Monday deuce
morning hello warning entity Evan say
something back so I know your life comes
the slide doorknob right now row that is
yeah get aside from working I got some
coffee okay I cool
so beautiful
Mahalo Mahalo yeah thank you in Hawaiian
yeah yeah okay time for the kids to go
up put on this dog USA Mavericks sure
because by the time you're watching this
vlog it's the fourth of July but also
because it's the fourth of July and
we're savages ten percent off the USA
line for the next two days get it while
the iron's hot yogi hello good go raise
some clothes I'll be there personally I
have my money on Evan just because uh
three two one we're going to eat level
is high ah I'm gonna miss roe is tight
up here
holy Sh I clearly underestimated how
fast you go and I'm heavier than Evan
dude I'm gonna die I'm cool with that
dumb 22 I've lived a good life okay here
we go bro that's dog dude I'm a happy
camper but I used to care about your
body is home hahahaha bro sale today 10%
off you would say merger what okay a lot
of people aren't secure about the body
[Music]
okay we just showed up through the beach
we got some inside information that'll
help other turtles in the town called
turtle turtle cove knowing a turtle I
like turtles
the water is so clear top our life
[Music]
low gang I you know this love beautiful
places but why you're taking the cake
for me yo know how cool is that it's
like a comb or the turtle oh yeah
probably Turtle Cove good old Logan
using his brain
I guess doing yeah the turtles who
people have confirmed that there are
turtles inside of this Cove I'm no
mathematician but we got to go find me
[Music]
I'll never let this maverick I think we
made it
what got it Chloe if you find yourself
lucky enough to run into these beautiful
creatures be quiet and disrespectful to
state they have a hard life and this is
the resting time I'm going to be
whispering when we get closer to them
but thanks
[Music]
[Applause]
I didn't think that actually be turtled
internal cold like what happens when the
turtles leave new this called Co
[Music]
oh no down girl down onion card free
anytime you recording right yo more lo
games you tell me a story lady friend
pretty much we're Regis on sleepover
when we were like let's just kill
North's maybe go to Turtles Co and we've
been kind of looking for you just a
friendly what did you find Logan Paul
and turtle cove and I will drive buying
this van and the dad's like Jojo here
anyway they're going everywhere bro I
request now the question when the
turtles leaves is it just called Cove oh
they're all by just awesome okay here's
the dose of thing about a turtle cove
besides the coat it's actually though
the water is beautiful super clear so
we're going to go mess around a little
bit isn't that right
[Music]
like I said I'm not a mathematician but
it looks like this some sort of like
crevice under there and if I die here to
rather looks like an Egyptian
[Music]
[Applause]
haha did you have mercy
yo I don't know it's fun to top it all I
mean that was fun attack we just got
back home I'm not even kidding there are
girls in our pool like a lot of girls
this is not a bad thing to come hope is
what's uh just do this and you know just
a lot of like really pretty Hawaiian
girl time to work some magic
what's up ladies you guys enjoy the the
palace yeah it's pretty pretty W yeah oh
man how the bigot is happening you ever
got to Philly we've got it started out
and it's the whole thing is literally
collapsing Logan to the rescue boat I
don't know how to do here this one says
on
okay now that we got that unlock we just
got to get the girls out here and do a
montage and make it look like we're
having fun go cue the montage
[Music]
it's a honeymoon over here honeymoon oh
this is amazing
no don't right look at look at right
here yeah right okay use that in YouTube
maybe I'll get married one day but you
know quick menu quick sidebar they
invaded our home like shared up the
invaded around our house I have an idea
though we have fireworks legit I didn't
use him yet today and I said I was going
to let you use them let's shoot him at
Jake and his wife I'm there honey let's
ruin their honey remember what do you
guys want to do I don't know we just got
here and I think honestly I think you
should check on the anchor Beach bro
it's a secret intelligence
I see me tons of okay but they're my
boys so I'm got your back Brooke wait
are you gonna check out with us or no
I'm gonna tell me I gotta use on the
montage girls and suffering
I don't see in montage this is the
posted yet oh yeah you doing watchable
what happened for sure okay guys we're
at the beach
Brendan prove that we're at the beaches
definitely at the beach for something
Jake is over there I don't know how real
this honeymoon is but regardless like
don't don't spoil my vacation little
brother he's posted up over there
okay I love you guys can see but Kate is
like shut up third wheel in it so uh so
I think the plan is to take a while to
get going the ocean is loud we're going
to light them here when they actually
start popping we're just going to run in
left do them oh sure he's gonna [ __ ] hi
my brother's over there what you get for
ruining my vacation
[Music]
that works Oh laughs brother got my eyes
yeah I know my son is birkoff I think we
[ __ ] them up a little bit more though
you're right I think we won that yeah
are you good oh we had a thing all of us
need to work out a part why are you
climbing spoil my vacation I'm just
gonna go I did I did for the vlog it's
kind of funny bro look at my feet yeah
but actually kind of hurt y'all y'all
almost you on camera last one is the
last one you if you step on camera
[Music]
you're in the honey man it's not I'm
glad you're Hawaiian I'm glad you guys
are her life I'm celebrating your
honeymoon okay okay that's the washcloth
side hard be inside be a maverick
kitchen maverick merch 10% off the USA
line today and tomorrow only a part of
the low game we got some dope gear link
in description like and subscribe baby
we're the fastest growing channel on
YouTube for the month hahahahaha I think
you got more daily but like for the
month we still we still enjoy people
that were underneath the airs I know
crazy one two and three hold up wait hop
three I know I guys you know I love you
I was you tomorrow
[Music]
can you tell me help it's great it's
good