I was gonna open up apologizing you're
not having said what's up to my boy man
so he decided to take over the vlog oh I
know we haven't talked or even seen
maverick in so long buddy I know you
know I love you oh okay yeah give me
kiss that's a good idea
mm-hmm hey it's my fault how could I
forget about the most famous parrot on
the internet bird who started it on we
started an entire brand after him I'm
the Maverick he's like the og man for
that buddy I'm sorry Internet I'm sorry
hey good morning okay with Bob okay I
look can you just give me one okay I
love you if you're not a part of the
logging make sure to subscribe just
about dumb stuff it's what we do it's
entertain so dab on the subscribe button
ok this trauma I watched a vlog my
brother he sent it true yesterday you
know it's got the hottest mercs on the
game on at the pink hoodies and the neon
hoodie y'all know where to get it
christmas is coming up you know what I
just haven't aged
this is a terrible idea I'd like that to
be on record
Oh Leon let's go okay so here's
something that happened when the tree
was still up Susie she's a star our
family kids loved your merged shop you
know this is amazing
we don't need they can be your Suites
enough already
Susie those were already broken you may
remember from yesterday's vlog a nice
box right here leather it's fancy it's
not leather no now he looks like he's in
a cast
rest in peace dog a piece con you lived
a good he's not dead it was a practical
joke he's a savage true my boys in the
fact business what something else is
happening right now as usual cookie my
boy
look I got this strawberries and he's
making Penghu head ain't talking pancake
Detroit don't worry buddy I'm not gonna
eat you oh whoa whoa his head is more
penises than ever today but you guys see
he looks like a pancake so it's gonna be
weird eating actual pancakes around
pancakes
Oh oh my god guys Andy's the guy not
every God wears this hat backwards got
your strawberries your whipping cream is
pending oh my god butter boy a butter
that's a fact fact business oh oh whoa
I'm gonna go a different route and eat
actual foods wait till you put that in
your mouth
I've said that before uh-oh I ate that
one I'm showering on my pan kidding him
by himself boy loves his leather throne
boy God buddy we'll see you later
thank you Rick a pancake for Brendon no
no no let's pancake the turtle take the
pink I just said I wasn't gonna eat him
now we try yeah I know he looks exactly
like a real pancake love you big mmm
well look the merge trees down now we
gotta tell Frank the guy who bought the
tree for us Frank I got bad news I don't
know what happened but the tree like it
fell over dude why the tree why would
you assume it's me the issue was the
merch was too heavy in it topple because
good advice kid you gotta be willing to
pay for the consequences of your action
today it looks like I lost some grass
it's gone just give it up
I have an idea it's not my brand just
send it once not even sent it twice it's
like I send it three times kind of guy
full of dumb ideas by my British friend
Hayden yayi goodbye Malloy I don't know
what I'm doing what are you just
constantly I think I'm not in the
morning I'm a savage listen hey what
yeah Los Angeles is not your city bro
England is your city so go back and be
British god save the queen
it's like sending your kids off to
school but stupid
okay you boys up
Oh Mike actually Park this in the
perfect we gotta cut this here or not
I've gotta be willing to pay for the
consequences of your actions or in my
case pay people to pay for the
consequences of your action which is
what I do tomorrow
Lydia so we took our tree come here you
guys if you're not a part of the looking
make sure to subscribe strongest family
on you do and we rep the strong as hot
as merch in the game the Maverick Moritz
so tough you can ride Christmas trees to
the ground it's so amazing you'll become
invincible just like me I love you Paul
that cop slash shop or link industry
possess that low gang I love y'all I
will see you tomorrow take it easy
why'd you stop