in the center of this problem so I'm
about to get tested for kovat 19 has
I've been joking about it but I really
do have a dry cough and I've had it for
a little too long we're at the testing
site right now it's crazy and those
tents oh it's like a drive-through for
diseases oh this is [ __ ] terrifying
you just have coughing on it I will be
horrible sucking dick here's to being
Corona free thank you ma'am again
appreciate your help those are the real
heroes bro what the hey just
deep-throated a cue to find out if I
have a disease well hopefully I don't
[Music]
what the hardships of being a parent at
first it was so cute now it's just
annoying it'll stop eventually squeaking
[Laughter]
I'm not really sure what's happening I'm
definitely too heavy for him to take off
with me attached to him but he's still
giving it a shot persistence it's all
about persistence being me with this way
hi how are you also how high are you Wow
hi how are you hi how I've never seen
you this high only you guys could see a
picture of me right now I'm a vlogger
Bru I have a completely lost my mind but
I'm close I've always wanted the alum
Bojack after all I am from Ohio let's
see if we can do that
holy Sh it's login pool okay pool after
all these years it's finally happy
login pool login poo mother oh look ant
hey guys how's your quarantine going
[Music]
that's the first thing I warned in like
two years yes good now we just gonna
master the log roll
[Music]
would you mind
yes exactly oh no he just means a brand
new shirt
who doesn't [ __ ] on you in your life oh
what the [ __ ] you [ __ ] dumbass Oh
know what I do upside down I don't think
you realize how bad it really yeah what
the [ __ ] dude perfect
yes that's efficient ah alright I don't
wanna make this all sappy and [ __ ] but
the clip you saw at the beginning of the
vlog of me yelling at Mike and Mike
yelling back at me was real gotta fight
after he gave me this shrimp on my
birthday and it wasn't because of the
shrimp although that's what we've been
saying and joking about it led to a
larger problem that I mean as you guys
can see like things got serious I asked
Mike to leave the house for an
indefinite amount of time and it's been
a week and I just can't imagine like a
50-year old version of myself telling my
kids that I severed the relationship
with my best friend because of a mantis
shrimp so he's been staying with his
girlfriend Lana and she actually kicked
him out of the house too because of a
shrimp but not the animal because of his
penis that's that was the shrimp anyway
I told him that he could come back to
the house today and yeah he's about to
be here so let's see how this goes
it's not like I don't know my youtube
views same bro channel scaling it like
an subscribe [ __ ] what are we doing
here I'm standing here what are you
doing there well I mean for one I'm
trying to figure out why the back of
your head looks like it got run over by
[ __ ] lawn mower business in the front
party in the back he looked like Charlie
from Charlie and the Chocolate Factory
right what about your what about your
face what about it it's [ __ ] stupid
so you got that new bird yeah I did so
you got that same girlfriend so you
still don't have a girlfriend it's cuz I
chosen to not do that it's a lifestyle
of mine listen man I got to come back to
the house dude I can't stay at Lana's
anymore my dick is like a limp noodle
I'm [ __ ] useless you can say that
again but your limp noodle is always
welcome here Mike cuz you're my friend
I'm not gonna let some dumb ass shrimp
ruin our relationship
[ __ ] it sorry I'm sorry too you want to
give me a hug hey her hair is really
stupid but why just give me a [ __ ]
hug
[Music]
welcome back Mike Lake for real yeah
there's some serious logs in there damn
it