for 40 minutes crying like a baby
bikers joggers tourists runners they
went by me police officers searching for
suicidal people want Bobby twice I'm
standing at the ledge leaning over the
rail with tears flowing down to the
waters and I thought to myself
absolutely nobody cares and then the
voice in my head said jump now and I did
and the millisecond that my hands
cleared the rail my legs flew over it
was an instant regret the depression was
wiped from my mind and all I wanted to
do was live and I thought it's too late
Kevin Hines was 19 when he jumped off
the Golden Gate Bridge he is one of the
many incredible people that I've been
grateful to meet over the past three
weeks as I aim to further understand the
complexities surrounding suicide I know
I've made mistakes I know I've let
people down but what happens when you're
given an opportunity to help make a
difference in the world the backlash
against the social media star very
popular guy called Logan Paul is in some
honkies are complete and utter
insensitive idiot I'm gonna break from
daily vlogging he says his latest
content was his biggest mistake
apologize to the victim and his family
it's time to learn from the past as they
get better and grow as a human being I'm
here to have a hard conversation so that
those who are suffering can have easier
ones so I've never been so humbled in my
life by a single event were you kind of
shocked but I was shocked to discover
just how big this is you've never known
anybody that killed themselves no one no
one that was know as that was part of
the problems just my ignorance on the
subject I didn't Ohio where you come
from it's the second leading cause of
death
and I know while I'm not able to solve
the problem by myself I want to be a
part of the solution and that solution
began across the country in New York
City
we sat down with dr. Chandra the
director of the National Suicide
Prevention lifeline we have to change
the conversation publicly from just
focusing on suicide and how something
bad is happening and say well what do we
do about help people understand that the
first thing they need to do is reach out
and talk to somebody when they're
feeling in despair because you're not
alone with anymore they've done studies
with people who are who are experiencing
any kind of pain including hanging off a
cliff you can hold on a lot longer if
somebody is right there with you I think
as a society as human beings we just
have to be more compassionate and that
includes me too that's something I'm
learning along this journey and
something else that dr. Draper told me
where the five steps that anyone can
take to help prevent suicide
step one is simply just ask and ask
yourself ask others are you thinking
about suicide and I know that sounds
like a daunting question but literally
that question can save lives
step two accordingly would be to listen
be present don't make any judgments and
then step three would be be there for
them even after you've already asked
because dependability is key step four
is then help them connect whether it's
with a friend a family member or local
suicide hotline therapist but help them
reach out to someone so they don't have
to deal with this alone lastly Step five
is just checking on them show them that
you care call them up say hey I want to
make sure you're okay can I check in
with you over the next few days so one
of the things that is so important about
reducing stigma is getting stories out
there about people positively coping
with suicide do you guys know anyone I
could talk to
with the lived experiences absolutely we
have quite a number of people that we
could deliver over to you yeah
that'd be great yeah and that's how we
got introduced to Kevin Hines seventeen
years ago Kevin jumped off of the Golden
Gate Bridge and survived
these are individuals whose stories when
people hear them they say you know maybe
I can get through as opposed to hearing
the stories when people happen and those
unfortunately those are stories that
we've heard before now we're hearing
more and more stories of people being
more open about it as I was saying
before Logan for every one person that
dies by suicide there's 287 other people
that think seriously about it but don't
those are stories again that have not
been told if we told those stories of
people who got through it as opposed to
one who didn't imagine what kind of
influence that would have on people's
behavior when I found out that one in
six high school kids seriously think
about suicide that's that's stunning
yeah this is such a common problem Logan
all I wanted was for one person to look
me in my eyes say hey kid are you okay I
am so grateful to be alive and I'm
grateful today for every millisecond I
get to breathe cuz it was almost all
ripped from me by me what's one thing
you would have said to your younger self
to the Kevin who was 19 sitting on the
bus if you were next to you and instead
of the guy who pointed and laughed what
would you say I would just put my hand
on this
I'll just put my hand on my shoulder and
I would just say I'm here for you
I got you we need to be a society that
comes together for every person in the
community that's going to hell and in
order to do that every person that's
going through hell whatever hell has to
be honest about their pain and if
they're gonna be honest about their pain
we are going to collectively answer the
call and be there for that individual
because if you don't see beauty and the
next person you meet you're not looking
hard enough you're incredible dude this
is not it's an honor for me to brother
[Music]
from this point on I want to make an
effort to contribute and immerse myself
in the conversation so I'm pledging to
donate 1 million dollars to various
suicide prevention organizations with
the first $250,000 going immediately to
the National Suicide Prevention lifeline
so they can increase their capacity to
help those in need for anyone watching I
want you to know you are not alone and
most of the time crisis passes so if you
or anyone you know feels alone we're
trapped I encourage anyone to call or
even text a suicide or crisis hotline
both of those numbers over lo and
although this is a tough conversation
it's important because things can and
will get better it's time to start a new
chapter in my life as I continue to
educate both myself and others on
suicide I'm humbled and thankful to say
this is just the beginning
[Music]