[Applause]
kids what starts out right ends up right
you need to start your morning yeah guys
as usual unblessed this morning with
andis cooking again big moves yeah
literally big moves we have my vehicle
the g-wagen a Yeti or what makes it
better
hey yo good morning lo que what Bob this
is hilarious bro Evan we've done it
again $300,000 dollars that we buddy
featuring the low game guys we were
average aging the world everyday we are
different we're passionate were unique
we're up the hottest merch in the game
that man doing it the answer's no buddy
okay trust me you want to hop on this
train
guys we got a new merch from yesterday
life is good I'm going to set later from
a movie to standing you know acting vlog
like you know how it is baby week now
with that said I'm its mom Deb uncle
aunt maverick
[Music]
you guys saw this yesterday I can't get
over how good the new we got pink
mannequins repping the merch was doing
it I'm not you look so sexy
just cuz the Maverick movement alright
its savage its rugged like we're not
afraid to work hard so we got that sort
of cab and feel that that died jungle
that brawn
Oh woke up please man we done it we just
we did it was the best ever oh my god
who's doing it starving on set like
you're right oh speaking of I gotta go
to see a ride sure it's just like yeah I
guess I could go to set like actually
like driving a car or I could ride on
top of a car in my friends tent so I'm
gonna go
yeah
oh boy to put on makeup or your the
makeup room is in a gym ain't know me
too well I'm trying to get some reps
it's me vlog boy so what do you want to
do first make me look good or should I
pump up a little bit
yo you guys may have seen Devin on my
Instagram story yesterday she made a
noise like a cat don't look at her
beauty is on the inside right look god
damn I look good
apparently the location today we're
shooting at is very cool obviously it
right I'm not a scrub someone I gotta
show up looking fricking yeah
[Music]
no thinning tooth thinning New World
Order we're currently shooting at a beer
factory so who thinks this place has
beer and giant elevators ha ha oh that
whole thing filled with alcohol I don't
know bro you could do the most epic keg
stand ever and I said this before kids
don't drink you will die fact crazy cuz
it's kind of cold in here reminds me
this snow in my front yard hasn't melted
yet we're working on at California if
you could get like a little warmer for
like two days for me that'd be great
what happens if I turn this knob don't
do that no no Ben gets louder the more
you turn it one more time drops to the
producers for not kicking me off your
movie thanks
[Music]
so yeah guys if you didn't know yet
Lydia is pregnant so Lydia is very
pregnant she said it in this vlog yup
guys I'm pregnant I'll play it again I'm
pregnant she's pregnant and you know we
have to prepare her for mother yeah you
gotta be fit to be a mom I won't let you
be a crappy mom I won't do it I'll go
longer won't do it know what's happening
you have no idea what anybody said
that's right so we have a real live
mother coming to Sam right now we're
gonna teach you how to be a mom oh yes
[Applause]
already off to a horrible start the
baby's crying practice makes perfect so
the babies come by two actually way more
than Lydia so I understand who struggle
right now
[Music]
ladies no cannot job baby I would know I
always dropped as you can imagine
multiple times this is so cool all right
this is all fun and games right this is
the easy part when the baby is actually
alive right what is the most important
part about being a mother giving birth
so today we're gonna teach Lydia how to
[Applause]
pretty much identical right it even
talks I need you to focus cuz I feel
like you're not this is how it's done
I've had a mother I came out of her
vagine and I know what this is like
watch carefully
[Applause]
[Music]
it was good huh my clothes on well I'm a
maverick so things are a little
different around here get this baby
submerged vengeance got that what have
you learned what do you mean Oh like
everything I've done the deed time to
lay on your back Lydia you've got to
give birth to your baby you know they're
taking YouTube channels down for this
kind of stuff please don't take my
channel County Police for mine thanks
you two love you hi Lydia I'm not alive
I'm disappointed I think that dad needs
to be here to experience this who's the
dad yeah stupid name but want to explain
this yep guys I'm pregnant tell them the
truth I'm pregnant I could play this so
many times I'm pregnant funny every time
yeah guys I'm pregnant
people think I'm actually pregnant oh
you are yep guys I'm pregnant everyone
my assistant Lydia is newly pregnant if
we could all just go
you're all invited to the baby sign look
low gang if Lydia refuses to be mom and
wants to be a bad parent I will take the
reins I'm response so much so that I'm
going to take the baby in the sea with
me I'm doing the scene with the baby can
I do this scene with the baby
okay little gang I'm back home and I
know what you're thinking Logan what
happened to your face and neck why are
you so sexy well it's a very simple
explanation actually I got attacked by
some thoughts tragic now guys that is
the vlog I know it's a little short
trust me I'm grinding I'm trying guys
when I say doing movies and doing vlog
is tough it's top but you boys a savage
and I'm gonna do it I'm gonna deliver to
the Logan because that's the promise I
made to you daily content hopefully I
can distract you guys from your busy
lives whatever stresses you have I'm
here to relieve you of that so if you're
not in the low game make sure to
subscribe we're liberal with the
strongest family on YouTube it's pop and
so smack to subscribe but I didn't
advise me I also figured I'd end it and
the new merch room cuz it's so late guys
I cannot get over how good this look if
you've not yet gotten your merch what
are you doing bro Logan bother cause I
show everything we make everything we do
the Maverick bread is the highest
quality it is the absolute best the
softest clothing you'll ever wear and
it's a movement of people who are
different passionate unique Oh Oh before
I sent off broad forgot the bird is back
the beautiful pink cords bird that I
broke the other day last back
yup yeah that was a $10,000 mistake but
someone fixed it for me
yeah if we're at all I am an idiot
that's a fact but look it's fixed don't
pick it up again it's good it's sexy
it's beautiful I just wanted to show you
guys I love gang I love you Marge
[Music]