guys look around it's like 1:30 p.m.
right now yes this is y'all the rings
about to happen a thing I've been doing
that's it goes the Sun is a sliver which
we clearly go hey yo
good morning little gang what topic
today is August 21st 2017 the skies are
clear the air is hot and I'm still a
challenge my team and I have flown 2,000
miles in an attempt to capture and
document the great American solar
eclipse
[Music]
my name is Logan Paul and welcome good
morning
Oh yo yo bro what's up hold up hold up I
can't hold up I can explain no it's just
a thing we do in our vlogs it's not
they're not real punch this is fake yo
you could throw guys that's Kobe we're
staying out at his house in Nashville
Tennessee oh oh oh maybe actually hit
him on that last one I'm not sure I
think you made contact yeah anyways guys
Kobe dude thank you for letting him stay
here as you guys can see he's in the
Logan shop are you guys good that's my
boy
oh wow dude I like it when you do this
I'm so excited for today like I'm making
this for me like finally I feel like I
can make a piece of content for myself
to enjoy I'm a space geek bro and when I
found out there was a solar eclipse
happening this year I was like oh you
know what I mean I haven't brought it's
a bit hot outside if it gets too hot can
I use that Rolex to say I is mom boy the
boys are getting scientific Yul Brynner
what are you doing bro building our
filter cuz guys the Sun is so strong
that you need something to protect the
lens it would melt the inside of the
camera
that's scientifical actual factual guys
this is Josh by the way he's gonna be
helping us hold up bro
is that Jake Palmer shine you know okay
the water broke localized oh yeah yeah
yeah okay we're gonna test this
concoction so it's crazy because in real
life this looks like a solid piece of
foil when you pointed at the Sun it
doesn't look like a solid piece of foil
this is funny because we're gonna be
doing a bunch of scientific stuff today
we don't know what the hell we're
talking about yeah science [ __ ]
resonant
what do you see I think I see the Sun
where's this damn it cliff it's coming
bro we have like an hour of speaking of
that Colby bro we got to get going soon
we're gonna miss ya as usual guys we're
running late yes I refuse to mr. solar
eclipse I would rather my brother lose
all his subscribers actually kind of
happen the other day I'm just gonna
here's the deal low gang I must be some
facts it's actually factually the last
time a solar eclipse like this occurred
was in 1979 it was pretty cool to see
here check
while the footage isn't that amazing the
last total eclipse of the Sun for North
America for the year 2017 well guess
what mr. newsman its 2017 also I'm not
sure if this is true but this is what
I've been saying solar eclipses like
this is only gonna happen once in our
lifetime what that means I don't know
maybe just like across America again I'm
not sure I think that is what it means
it is America so a solar eclipse like
this probably will happen elsewhere in
the world this one is the Great American
solar eclipse and it's only gonna happen
once in our lifetime u.s. totally we are
headed to a private Airport apparently
when the eclipse happens there's like a
360 degree sunset so this particular
Airport has like a lot of space we're
going to see all of it hopefully not
sure whose idea it was to run up in an
airport senator hasn't so much as we
love you Heather and you know you but
you sound
[Music]
all probably Hebrew set up dogs that are
$14,000 lamb shot whatever
Brendan made this morning don't I think
I'm gonna chase you solar eclipse and
I'm gonna get you engaged or slip and we
can show these doors I too easy to be
blasted amazing as Cochran oh my god yes
this is a little sketchy I love it
okay guys does the reason we chose the
rooftop obviously like I said so take a
look around guys
everywhere that we can you the Sun will
be setting it is curly up there I decide
I'm Margot Paul okay we can see anything
that's my boy
I got you of it yeah we are going to go
back up there later that's the viewing
flooded part I will say yo it's really
hot and I heard when the moon covers the
Sun the temperatures drop a little bit
some wait for that because you are
freaking burning that bro I'll be a
Jonas brother did it that's if you get
that reference
- thanks also most people don't know
that I majored in engineering in college
what does that have to do with space
nothing nothing but here's our solar
eclipse or Logan I'm a teacher of
science in a fun way
Evan call me come here okay so this is
what we do so let's pretend Evan is the
moon and Colby is the Sun normally if
the moon ever crosses the Sun it doesn't
matter because it doesn't completely
cover it so that rarely happens but
today given our current location on
planet Earth the moon is going to cover
the Sun in such a way that it completely
and fully blocks out the Sun so normally
maybe the moon possibly sound like this
you think nothing of sometimes the moon
crosses the Sun like this again still
nothing where you saw we're like partial
solar eclipse
but today the moon is going to did I get
ya Edgar do that where it completely
covers the Sun for a duration of two and
a half minutes during that time the
earth will get pitch black like it's
nighttime
apparently you'll be able to see stars
and the planet Venus animals will start
acting differently that's why I brought
Kong I want to see what he does
apparently able to hear like crickets
chirping because you know they all think
it's night time to quit idiots it's just
a neglect sigh to all the animals who
wants to have logs just to remember just
gives you merch link in description logo
balkon / shot one thing i forgot to
mention is during the Eclipse we yeah we
get to wear these really cool-looking
Eclipse glasses mmm these are these are
super cool look at eyes this feel like
I'm at the premiere for Spy Kids 3d it's
crazy guys because I can't see anything
it's absolutely pitch black the only
thing I could see is the Sun Oh Evan oh
that is oh I know what Evan we're not
yet
sure look Brendon can you see through
them nope I told you pitchblack that way
we don't burn our eyes when we look at
the Sun that would be bad
hey guys so life wouldn't be life
without problems one we are experiencing
right now this lens is like breaking of
the Brendon what's happening bro it just
says it won't communicate with this
camera no oh
$14,000 lady we tried that camera we
tried Brendan's camera that lens was
going to capture like an extreme closeup
of the moon covering the Sun the worst
part about this is that it's 1151 or an
hour's point of contact with the moon
touches the Sun is in eight minutes so
we should just speed this is the third
camera body and still in air this is no
bueno
stop dog do you know how to fix it I
don't know what happened so I can use on
how did you find this game ran out on
time accident lenzburg Brendan oh yes
so what's the delay $14,000 then it
works anything nah don't want to rush
anyone but we got about four minutes
look I literally just got the
notification or its contact in two
minutes you guys Thank You rose we have
one minute climbing up this ladder I do
not want to miss first contact I'm
reckless and I'm crazy but I'm also a
geek my awesome solar glasses are going
on I don't know where my people are
maybe I'm the only one that wants to
appear playful a journey for we make of
it Brendan
it'll roll on it anyway okay doctor felt
their first contact about the habit you
know I think I see it almost exactly I'm
Q 11:59 a.m. is it if you come over the
top right
oh snap yo so we're all just sitting
here waiting for totality to happen we
have about one hour
yo this lens think itís not good try to
figure out what we can do so we can see
the moon covering the Sun like way close
up that footage you saw earlier was from
this camera and it just doesn't do it
justice kind of Santa bro
pitch fortune does no such look at this
one I wish I could just grab the lens
like oh you good boy
yo did anyone give it any wonder if you
go further up
Thank You Cole can you fill this out you
know when you filled it up here brother
any is there any dude I swear I had an
idea
Brendan I did alright so I had a second
camera right yeah that's it two times
zoom why hold up yo yeah and if we shoot
in 4k we could put your side well we can
punch it we can be done
you like brother support life is the
power power we have problem with I love
okay on another no my boy finish you
good roll your pizza at $14,000 bro I do
hello gang we are very very close come
to excited your chickens up we got GoPro
set up here we're gonna do some time
lapses we have a camera here to get our
reaction
this one over here not as big as the big
lion slide is going to have to work in
fact right now you can see that the moon
is covering maybe more than like
three-quarters of the Sun when the moon
completely covers the Sun a couple
things are going to have one there's
going to be like I heard anyways look
I'm not a scientist Brahma blocker but I
heard there's going to be a ringer on
the Sun and if you have a lens that can
get close enough to see the moon you can
see the sun shining through the ridges
of the moon there's going to be like a
big flash when it like finally happened
at which point it will get dark will see
the stars the blah blah blah blah yeah I
think it's good time guys I'm aware this
might not make sense but this its
physical weird energy right now it's
like you put an Instagram filter on life
like everything is just like tinted but
not completely dark yet Wow
this is rough here's like we're just the
horizon is getting darker but the Sun is
still shining directly on us guys look
around it's like 1:30 p.m. right now
yeah this is oh look at the shadows bro
guys the shadows are so sharp right now
y'all the rings about to happen I think
I pinned it it goes the Sun is a sliver
way
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
so this is so cool oh I can't believe
I'm seeing this right now there's the
360 degree sunset going on right now
this is absolutely insane this has got
to be one of the coolest things I've
ever experienced I'm not even kidding
[Music]
it's like popping out a big giant
rewrite you got to see it's almost
immediately lights again
[Music]
yo seeing that in real life but I'm
speechless I don't even know what to say
I'm just I'm lucky and I'm glad I have
an audience and a family to share this
with you guys the Lowe gang seriously
that was so cool I'm so happy I came
here
I guess this is a good time to plug them
our show
get your mouse Logan Poldark y'all did
you see that a cliff yeah bro
argentinian clip right in the guy's dick
never seen that cool sing your lighter
you know what not the coolest thing in
my life is my $14,000 lens didn't work
on it
cool not not so cool that's also the
eclipse is cool you see could we what do
you think
get off him amazing right yes you did
okay pretty awesome pretty cool right
now it's time to deal with the problem
at hand
I got songs to make I got an e p.m.
doing Bo can we Chester fly back to LA
with you guys yeah here can we really go
that way I spent all my hearty sausage I
was like oh yeah we missed our flight
with those dudes from Vermont looks like
I'm staying too natural no thanks to you
$14,000 left oh just kidding us my boy I
gotcha anyways guys go that is the vlog
if you were not part of the low gang I
say this every day why dude what are you
doing just hit the button subscribe cop
you're mad former still links with that
in the description or logo Paul back on
slasher with that said low gang as usual
I love y'all I will see you tomorrow
take it easy felt bad
[Music]
this is just in case I break this this
is a practice hopefully I didn't drop it
yeah we're chilling