this is the one where it jumps on me
dude I seen it op drop dry okay listen
guys Sunday my birthday's coming up Duke
boys turning 23 oddly enough my birthday
falls on April Fool's Day pretty much
describes my entire life full full we
came to the store cuz I figured oh I
want to buy myself a gift not only is it
my birthday but it's the one-year
anniversary of the Maverick brand and by
the way Saturday we're doing a big drop
including y'all saw Spencer was wearing
it yesterday yo yo we look good who knew
and never seen before maverick hoodie
this is straight Street where bro you
have to do it different going down both
arms we got the Maverick world wide in
the chest this is actually the year I
was born 1995 and then the little
Mavericks all across the globe because
we went global
now Oh still got it anyways I'm getting
distracted with how fire our merch is
it's my birthday I'm getting a gift for
myself what about this guy oh he reminds
me of my dad just a really pale there's
no Craig Paul like a crotch thing on
there you guys also know the original
t-shirts I'm actually wearing one right
now thanks little t-shirts for $10 this
week only through Monday so poke the
gummy bears while you can Logan Paul
back on slash shop or Lincoln you say
Pope yeah what does that mean exactly
just get it while you can because it's
not gonna be your friend Josh you your
swag will increase you will be cooler
stronger faster sexier but it's not
toddler yeah yeah yeah yeah Oh make you
taller too for sure oh I'm growing on
poor dude that 23 is a big year so I
came to the adult section to do like
tours and stuff we could get a dryer or
a while people can't all right I
couldn't do that do you want help no I
just shut the door
okay well let's keep looking huge fan of
the game in a four day Logan Paul was
taken on Twitter start streaming soon by
the way guys oh you don't even want to
be in it
I was smiling a bit weird it's fine it's
fine okay all right cool
do you want this back thank you have a
nice I like you too what seem to do with
that you could have found that image on
Google why why are you not just be in
the picture with me what do I smell bad
no I don't think you smell you have an
ice axe
I had an ice axe I got a knife back oh
yeah feel like this is more my speed
just drones right huh I was a fortnight
two days ago when this happened
I'm the king of the flashbacks bro hey
bro there's one more thing I want for my
birthday
yeah hi guys the segment I know you love
[Music]
y'all having quick question do you not
believe in air conditioning because I'm
sweating it is very hot here and not
because of the merge we should go
somewhere be birthday we want to go like
Alaska or like oh you were good one up
like ever the basic a silent person on
their birthday 23 dude this is
officially the year I kind of have to be
responsible
how about instead of OneNote we go to a
place where there's thousands of Oaks
Alaska no camping oh you know guys can
you comment below what I should do for
my birthday cuz it's stressing me out we
should fly this drone in this vehicle
no no quick no no drilling takeoff no
drone takeoff I don't think it's voice
commands drone takeoff I'm taking the
boys command whoa take off take off the
segment's sucked bro just a crappy
droning what why didn't sell what is
drive you with Evan saw it no no no no
no you should be thankful we have a
friend like me to drive your blazes yeah
Lidia I come to you with the task flies
this is a disaster it's my birthday
shouldn't be like this tie your birthday
oh never dreamed of it's a mini drone
Hunter is so beautiful haircutting
[Music]
[Applause]
like I've had enough but you'll have
you're good at that boat yeah wait hold
up what if we put weapons on it bro come
on help me make this the best birthday
ever
okay it's not your birthday yeah but
it's close look at all our toys so I got
these plastic utensils here because
they're light right but they still be
dangerous watch this
I'll see dangerous yeah okay woohoo why
is this not being used in the military
oh no they come near us looks good any
knives left for four month oh yeah
no but we do have this spoon right see
bro I told you looking pretty lethal
imagine you're like flying over somebody
maybe Avenue just like tea bagging with
your spoon what are you doing
be smooth Hey wow I feel like we don't
stand a chance
[Music]
[Applause]
right no more games guys look you boys
you're training right I'm a little sore
and it's important to take care of your
body remember we did a cryotherapy and
the other day flashback to when that
happened how was that and right now guys
this is dr. Jason you guys may have seen
him in some of Jake's videos you're a
chiropractor come on you're the
best-looking doctor but we did have a
really good-looking doctor the other day
this man's gonna take care he's gonna
jump on me and break my back big breath
in my man you know what's so good about
it arrives Woody's reminded spines the
minds connected with divine no one told
me you were a rapper have you on your
right side now facing this way this is
the one where he jumps on me dude I seen
a top top dryer
I feel fine these little tents man going
on guys I'm sick you noticed the
capacity days the vlogs have been a
little slow I don't know I feel like if
I completely just like let my body go I
feel like I'll actually my spinal snap
luckily it won't are you sure sure man
you certified wrong certified licensed
14 years down man almost as old as I am
measures we got the man's films on the
phone we know exactly what's happening
man oh yeah damn I look good even in
x-ray form so I wait before you do this
bro yeah maverick t-shirts $10 the
original t-shirts get it this week only
local baller counselor shop go for it
hey we're making waves brother we're
getting you aligned so the branded body
can communicate oh my god makes it sound
so magical oh that was spectacular
yeah aligned and dial go oh wow that was
amazing
yeah you look better now bro really yeah
man thanks dr. Jason appreciate that
[Music]
I'm a sharpshooter that is the blog guy
so much stuff going on why do you guys
know $10 maverick t-shirts until Monday
guys we're not doing the sale again so
get the merch while you can looking for
that calm slash shop or link in
description you may have a hunch my
birthday is coming up Sunday if you want
to get me anything there's gonna be a
major drop in volume like this involving
the dope ass shorts mentors wearing
right there not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe not only do I
want you to subscribe though hit a
little bell next to the subscribe button
that way you can be notified when I post
cuz you don't want to miss this witness
bro
I though gang I love y'all I will see
you tomorrow
[Music]