oh yeah good morning look guy what's mop
I'm gonna be honest guys christmas came
early and Santa's new name is Logan Paul
that new maverick red drop that 20% off
site-wide discount and wanna fly two of
you out here to come ride the red
challenging with me huh man baby I'm
hungry
oh yeah I'm hungry too actually so this
is so sick oh my god not only does it
look good but this wrap is practical but
good for spin y'all know where to go
look up all that concise shop or Lang a
description be a maverick join the
revolution guys it's a movement of
people who are different unique
passionate people who do what they need
to do to achieve their goals now oh hey
I know Andy's hungry we're both hungry
so this is funny okay we're gonna race
Andy's got his cinquecento Ferrari yeah
[Music]
big paycheck those fast she got me on
that turn that red Challenger broke
coming okay some interesting stuff just
happened so first let's start off with
Annie literally just spilled his coffee
this whole day has gone like kaput in
two seconds I wouldn't recommend that
he's doing it that well actually he
actually did it and II broke to be stag
oh oh snap it's Thanksgiving John
forgotten happy Thanksgiving everybody
I'm thankful for you guys I'm thankful
for Andy I'm thankful for BC and his
ability to Christ you know it's not
completely his fault actually so that
leads into the next story
Logan why aren't you wearing your hoodie
no way did I just nailed the drop yeah
that's Andy's drone and Joanie's VC was
flying it yo this is what happens when
you replace Brendan when they come back
[Music]
it's dude it's not your fault here's the
problem the drone was idling at like
eight feet and the cargo van had a
ladder on the top and he's got you
looking up oh no oh my god it's so
broken all right here you go drone rest
the piece new red drop at least she's
being buried I map
[Music]
we gotta get so then yeah I brought
breakfast for us and like as if enough
stuff isn't already going down with the
red drop wait fish again true and easy
oh you're a little like commentary on
the side is so accurate and true which
by the way guys we have never seen this
many people on the site at once everyone
wants to be a maverick everyone wants to
read gear literally have never seen this
type of conversion like it's just it's
amazing so again thank you guys for that
but then another interesting happened
with Andy's Cinquecento oh no you got
another problem not even in the vehicle
the cheese white cheddar has no front
seat right they go good news is you can
kind of just like so then we came back
to the crib and I found out my boy Frank
is leaving just like Brendan no what you
got a family for Thanksgiving Frank oh
I'm sorry I thought be selfish you being
selfish and being yelled at and this is
you're being selfish why do you tell me
to hold this pumpkin holyoke muscle do
my bicep feel my bicep
oh yeah I'll work that once best
decision of my life so yeah guys
everyone's leaving I don't plan on going
home to Ohio for Thanksgiving sorry
family I do love you but I was wondering
nd I know you're going home bro can I
come with here to spend Thanksgiving
you don't have to ask you don't even
have that I kind of had to I know you'll
be weird no I'm not gonna impose bro
like I'm a vlog or I get it but like I
could be chill that's good that makes me
happy I like Hyundai but I forgot to say
this happened as well this morning I was
backing out this morning in the
Challenger and I was backing out I just
ran into the bus oh no dad bro what's
wrong with Mary horrible bro
probably not guys it's just a weird more
no no where you going
why's everyone have friends and families
be selfish Evan it's Thanksgiving but do
you think I'm thankful for his height
you think I'm thankful please baby care
fingers you think I'm thankful for the
word bro cuz I know you're thankful for
the word bro oh that's not even true and
while you're there why don't you make
sure they got their red drop merch on
Logan Paul at customs
yeah yeah I think I think this bumper is
fine literally so much stuff is going on
today guys I forgot to mention no
handlebars is coming out today I know
you guys been waiting for it's coming
out probably a couple hours after this
vlog is up so cool like your fro go
watch it give it a like yo I can ride
your girl with no handlebars also if
you're watching it in front of your
family because it just Thanksgiving I'm
sorry it's it's uh it's out there not as
out here as me but it's out there and
later today I'm shooting my movie the
thinning the thinning sequel called the
thinning new world order so much stuff
but all good it's all good stuff it's
good to be busy
hi I know buddy it's been a while I
haven't seen you in a while I you you
know I love you know I do look bro I
want to spend Thanksgiving with people
no you're not a human you're a bird no
okay
oh yeah you guys know my character Blake
riding he is quite the savage we just
pulled up the set guys I'm excited the
last movie I shot as you know his valley
girl which by the way is coming out next
year June 28th is gonna be my first like
theatrical movie you boys in acting
today or my scene anyway but I know they
shot some stuff in a cemetery and like
I'm surrounded by dead people right now
I'm not even kidding these are a whole
deadbeat even have a garden of dead
people plants that people fountain gives
me the heebie jeebies Grove it's a weird
start to the first day of beautiful for
me yeah you've been to a funeral for me
when I die just kidding I don't I'm
invisible
it's a trippy like I'm supposed to be
dead actually no wait if / when I die I
want to do a low gang meet everyone come
to my funeral and just throw up the
maverick sign and dab double dab ha it's
gonna be hysterical
yo it's classic thinning guys we were
about to shoot my scene I'm gonna give
you a little sneak peek here we go okay
that's it I'm gonna focus on acting
right now but do not forget guys no
handle bars are gonna be out it's coming
out today
[Music]
bro the music videos he and we get the
Maverick merge red drop guys it's the
hottest softest merch in the game y'all
like everyone wants to be a maverick so
join the revolution guys looking ball
like I'm slash shop oiling a description
20% off the entire site till Cyber
Monday I think it's like four more days
yeah I was never good at math actually
wait yeah was in engineering but I'm a
beast 20% off the entire site per also
I'm gonna fly two of you out here to
come take a ride in the red Challenger
with me big moves lots of moves guys
loping I love you and I will see you
tomorrow take it easy been doing this a
lot today hello gang I love y'all I was
few tomorrow take it easy
[Music]