[Music]
we're doing it I literally go to pick up
my blog camera this morning I'm blowing
dust off it actual dust but what's
poppin LoJack how you doing Matt what's
good buddy I know I look I know I get it
I get it
okay Leo this is things that I want in
my life I want to be back on YouTube
preferred partnership program I just I
do I want thank you and two I want a jet
ski they're two very common things every
American one every American wants those
things here's the issue I'll go to the
beach I have any lakes I goes to piranha
jet ski but goddamn right I'm sure has
been done before but god damn my return
on investment with this pool has been
subpar
I just never ate it you know hey
helicopter can you shut the [ __ ] up is
one of my first vlog back I see one step
back I think you got it I should do the
trick come in Jake when you look at this
pool what's missing a jet ski with it
you won't you don't have the capability
the time or the energy it's already been
done it's been tired it's already
happening you are a maverick how rocky
has arrived how fast is it go 40 miles
an hour in about 20 feet how much speed
can I guess you can get pretty quick in
20 feet
all right how do you turn it on like
this oh that's different
this
today Logan of water not a little
here's what I see how they build a ramp
and I need to learn how to balance this
thing is the most in sorrow footage then
again I'm not hey you ever see anything
like this yeah you look really cold I'm
not cold hello why is the concrete is
magically white oh we got some - we got
some hall damage I say you don't rap we
visit this is I am this close to getting
hypothermia what we're gonna do is we're
gonna have Logan pilot this jet ski
roughly 80 to 90 knots off a large
floating brand that is held down by two
miniature potato men will be very
careful to avoid the porpoise purpose
for this that's swimming around your
pool this is the edge of the pool this
is the bottom so what we need is we need
a crossbar here a 2x4 that supports the
rent this is the ramp coming up got a
real shallow grade to it okay 26 degrees
rock oh my god I just wanna know what
you do with the money
what I know what you do with the money
[Laughter]
got a cross joint that goes across the
bottom of it so you've got the two cross
joints the [ __ ] the 2x4 that support the
top of the red these two guys have no
end up with a piece of lumber in my
heart you want in the water guys are in
the wall
that's what I said do I come on whoa
y'all killed this good from this angle
I'm starting to look at all any parent
feel like it's not that great just grab
a piece of map emerge because it's the
hots off the Smurfs in the game I'll
just land on it in
[Music]
no bro no did this can't have like dip
dip below the water no there's water in
the gas it's just not running anyways
you ruined my life because I broke the
front we got some hall damage this whole
thing is a disaster that is thank you
yes probably why does it start
[ __ ]
[Music]
I am not done here I'm gonna buy a jet
ski that is not broken and I'm going to
skin Pluto that was my excuse I said
this sucks but I do have some good news
Evan and I released a trailer for our
new show coming Tuesday called best
friends yesterday except I think it got
buried because it was so short so I'm
gonna play it again right now this show
is amazing if you already saw the
trailer then I guess you could just
fast-forward but yeah enjoy the trailer
for our new show best friends now
surprise big things come in small
packages yeah this is for our webseries
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't know what it's like to wear girl
clothes
[Applause]
ah she goes
this sucks what a shitty way to return
to vlogging Logan I am so sorry I don't
know what happened anyways for all my
Mavericks out there guys life does not
always go as planned exhibit a what as
long as you stick in there do your thing
buy a new jet ski I promise you will
launch it off a ramp and make it to Mars
alright guys I'm gonna go cry myself to
sleep I love y'all Oh
[Music]
I knew it I knew it that's the hole that
I made earlier I suck
[Music]