I got 10 K here for the person who has
the highest IQ test now the loser has to
get their score tattooed somewhere on
their bodies let's hope no one scores 69
assigned someone at the meeting to take
notes recapping decisions and why do you
try to make this a corporate thing bro
or a dinner table talking about YouTube
because our productivity rate in this
meeting has been absolute just because
you be mindful of time designate someone
to keep the meeting on schedule this is
it corporate money I'll be here in a
creative environment is what I'm saying
and you're trying to apply like real
life straight up is the environment when
I'm not a roommate I simply have a
non-exclusive revocable license to use a
month a month portion of the problem
please put your phones down and let's
try to figure out the blog what come on
back into Google boy for a night
corporate world I don't I will
don't talk to me touching you when I
taught you
I see so good so good understand it bro
it's not corporate it's just at the end
of the day dude and this is gonna help
me prove my point you don't get it
because not to put this yeah you can box
bro yeah you know academic ride to
college and a 4 7 7 GPA in high school
when you say full academic Raju
beautiful
I would prove it to you that I'm smarter
than you and you and you I could be the
smartest I need you just sit your ass
back down on that elevator do it sit
your ass back down
maverick house I demand to take an IQ
test right now and we will see who the
smartest one is mr. Bailey we have got
quite the setup here for the Maverick
House official IQ test as you can see on
the screen it's the BMI certified IQ
test I'm holding 10,000 dollars in my
hand obviously we've gotta have some
mistakes to this no stakes like
consequences stakes okay this is the
word 10k here for the person who has the
highest IQ test now the loser has to get
their score tattooed somewhere on their
bodies let's hope no one scores 69
to be alive certified IQ test one you
have 20 minutes to answer the following
20 questions if you want to lose you
cash for Sherman to choose the
appropriate shape ABCDE or F to replace
the shape that is missing the one with
the question mark on it every question
is replacing a shape we chose this
because Joe Rogan did so what it's just
an expanded version I'll put the round
peg in the round all but done Mike good
luck team maverick we're about to find
out who is the smartest new guy John boy
boy boy Spencer and assistant Danny all
right guys I'm a kadhai for three at
which point we will begin one three two
one begin
[Music]
this is
we'll see where we get these results
back the results are in I am nervous
wait before we reveal this I want to
give some stats about IQ 0 to 70 that's
lower extreme idiots more like a banana
banana 72 84 is below average like you
got the job at Walmart maybe a piece a
bridge 85 to 114 is average it was
height or a tall one it 115 to 129 you
are above average Joe Rogan score 127
132 144 that's where the gifted people
come in above 144 it's probably like 1%
I feel like PewDiePie would fall yeah ok
so let's get this going so sixth place
with the score of 105
well 100 is perfectly average or
slightly above perfectly average yeah
they're good coming in next step 110
[Applause]
coming in fourth place with a score of
122 third place with score 125 Oh Andre
let me take over the camera
Andre took the test dude Holly wait how
do we know it's not Ellen how do we know
give the tie first coming in at a time
with a score of 127 where's Andre and my
[Music]
um no I hate that Mike is higher than me
oh the mindful meetings where I like
bring an agenda to the beach oh yeah
that's fine it's fine
nobody knows before you go inside before
you go outside waiting stop quick
question come back oh you're so close
one more second to think about one
question Danny Danny hadn't gotten the
food Oh at least we got an episode of
best friends coming out this week that's
good huh it's good to make sure like I'd
like the video when you see that yo real
talk Congrats Congrats Andre very
impressive boys I'm gonna give you guys
this 5k each I hate that you beat me but
I love that I've surrounded myself with
some smart folk 5k for you my friend
5k for you yeah yeah but the poor just
yeah yeah sorry about that guy oh oh wow
that's amazing oh you know we can buy
with that $200 when we're gonna do is
you gonna wake up tomorrow who knows but
all right thank you guys for watching
yeah another vlog if you're not part of
the logo make sure to subscribe to cop
the hottest office merch in the game
maverick by Logan Paul you know how we
do we do it different sometimes we get
tattoos on our legs sometimes a 69 not
often though also congratulations to you
boys that's impressive I'm jealous
both smarter than me so good work thank
you guys for watching we'll see you next
time
[Music]
kinda reminds me of your mama show the
gas money
[Music]