there was really nothing to do in Ohio
we were always like bored and kind of
like trying to find like fun little
things to do we kind of just made do
with with like whatever we could
I remember them just fooling around with
the camera I didn't really think a whole
lot about it so let me start I just want
to ask what is this documentary the
backlash against the social media star
who posted video of an apparent suicide
victim is intensifying viewed over 6
million times in just 24 hours people
and creators of all sizes denouncing
Logan Paul and this video but he insists
that he only did it to raise awareness
about suicide prevention he starts
laughing and his friend starts me
you said before this fight you have
something planned lads got this bout
right now come get it
no get born
so I'm ready
[ __ ] wanted into second
is is you know just like ask directly
is this a fluff piece to make people
feel better about Logan fall
[Music]