ladies and gentlemen boys and girls the
moment you've all been waiting for
I give you the long-awaited y'all have
seen it the low gangsters that have been
here for a minute the Maverick Jim give
it a moment of relax give it a moment a
real em cogs been a dirty dog lately and
I'm a little too lazy to actually give
him a bath so no he's just gonna get
dirty again
hey good morning long has been going
crazy lately and the pool heat when you
put him in you saw he just does a little
paddle kind of takes care of himself car
you are disgusting
what is wrong
maybe we just I think he's a lost cause
you can tell like really look into his
eyes there's nothing there man anyways
guys hi there my name is Logan Paul may
have seen me in the news hey what's up
if you're not a part of the low gang
that is you make sure to subscribe
during the strongest family on YouTube
that is not as a joke we out here
straight murky in it guys speaking of
Kong and when you look into his eyes
there's nothing there this morning I
lost my mind in a pod here hey there
okay long story short this is Spencer as
you guys know he invited me to a float
oh my god being deprived with my senses
as if I need that right now I'm gonna
get in this tank I just sit here there's
gonna be no sound no air no nothing it's
gonna be okay very good naked
this is weird I'm alone now and I was
joking but I guess you do have to get
naked so crazy bro you see this in space
movies here we go uh it's kind of
awkward cuz you're here with me and
[Music]
the sensory deprivation tank that's I'm
actually like floating honest hello gang
like and subscribe I'll see you a little
bit alright what are you doing that's
why you're getting dirty why he's just
eating dirt no he's a lost cause just
like me today's vlog guys you see the
title I have this gym I have been
waiting to show you guys this forever we
got the walls painted we got equipment
in it oh I'm not gonna show you just yet
stuff there's a lot of people in this
house we're gonna check it this is the
bunk room it's been made an absolute
mess by a bunch of young dudes reason we
come in here guys I've been stressed
lately I've been breaking out acne and
stuff puberty you got a lotion have a
special especially and he's got this
Italian lotion I don't know I'm only
vlogging this cuz what are you doing bro
are you wearing ksi work hey yo
seriously hold on but were you doing go
bring sideburn that stuff like actual
real life cool maverick
I came in here to get lotion on my face
cuz I have puberty issues do you want
let me fix it I'll be four seconds
continue doing you do it I'll fix my
mistake okay if this stuff makes me
break out more well I'm gonna be pissed
when I was a high school look here's a
picture tells me at high school I had
acne bad tormented me I'm lame oh I feel
like I'm already breaking out yeah
either burnt you're gonna break out
really bad for a couple of days and then
it'll go back to normal
since you two is clearly not working out
for me I think I'm just gonna become a
beauty vlogger and this is how you
spread the hood get 1 to 10 how's your
facial
oh no acne what do you
with the human still wearing maverick
Joker keep the brand say
all my receipts geez thanks my good his
budge no wasn't me it was he's sprinting
towards the pool could be the phone case
and my passport that's good looks like
I'm staying here for an extra couple of
months new iPhone ex destroyed
waterproof rope it's waterproof but you
just cracked your screen everybody ha
hey this Rolex what a groove Jen I was
left alone in a floating pot oh thanks
Andy that's my boy that's my boy okay go
oh my god my senses who are deprived a
tank is crazy dude how they're so silent
it was so quiet I was just alone with
myself and that's pretty scary anyways I
digress yo that was crazy
sensory deprivation tank I hope to meet
you again one day oh snap so yeah the
pod was cool that's probably why I have
to put so much lotion dry my face out
get back home your bookcases like I
definitely don't read but we getting
furniture today yeah Larry Oh boxes oh
my god oh my god it's giving me a little
anxiety all these boxes hey man what are
you doing in a box well as you can see
I'm using this boxes like a metaphor
what's the metaphor box and there's a
boxing match as you should do against a
sari
yo you may be wondering lo gank for
those of you who are subscribed watching
videos every day first off thank you you
guys know I love you but the reason I
didn't have a video yesterday you know
this I made I made a response video to
ksi like like nachos I went in do what
after I showed it to my team they're
like yo you can't release that cuz I
went I went really hard the idea is I
already have so much stuff going on we
don't want to just bring in purposely
more drama that we're gonna put that on
pause for a second sorry Evan you're
going back in the bar
apologies buddy what guys listen that
doesn't mean I'm not getting exercised
working out and stuff it's speaking of
that I think I think it's time to show
you the gym Oh ladies and gentlemen boys
and girls the moment you've all been
waiting for
I give you the long awaited y'all have
seen it the low gangsters that have been
here for a minute the Maverick gym they
give it a moment of relax give it a
moment I relapse ain't got a problem
3:10 hi so guys I am absolutely obsessed
with this everyone in the house is we
have been working out here every single
day it is good because if you guys know
I haven't been working out really this
just gets me motivated ready to go let
me give you that tour everyone watch
them blues now we got that big old LCD
screen Netflix all because we got
YouTube even hell yeah you can watch me
like it subscribe holy jesus this is
getting hard
we got a treadmill for typically running
but boys been sleeping today got the
elliptical elliptical keep your joints
safe we got the leg extension normally
there's more way down there in the
mirror the famous Santa universe with
the Maverick and when you go over here
real life it's backwards take outside
the box kids it's that maverick life so
what is the back of this for these days
then the universe you know that's for
Sam bro these are by far the most
comfortable hoodies to work on it that
is an actual verifiable fact logan paul
back on slash shop also young dougie
y'all seen it there kong with ab we're
working on this corner we're gonna put a
door there because in the back here
we're gonna get a mini horse in a barn
it's gonna be amazing but below the
window the beautiful mini horse we're
gonna have a nice Dumbo rack right here
we got mats we got square bars we got
the types of workouts you can do are
limitless
[Music]
stand out to get a hand up making a
brenda this kilt each measure gotta get
a car
I need all the candelabra now look back
at that board show no great fast-paced
win a cruise back to forward but my
absolute favorite the rap yo this just
screams a man we got chains on the
weights cuz weights aren't enough the
finest rubber in the game the sexy blue
metal right next to Super Saiyan Logan
that's definitely how I look we got the
rubber bands 400 K for a swing I guess
again guys the point is we got options
it's limitless in here but wait there's
more make it to the NFL folks because of
his bum knee I'm gonna clean this little
guy up thank you guys for watching if
you were not a part of the low gang
you're good make sure to subscribe join
the strongest family on YouTube actual
again verifiable fact and cop yourself
to the hottest nurse in the game cuz we
out here dent in the universe
Logan piss old Paul pop fly slap pop pop
shot sorta low gang I love y'all now see
you tomorrow take it easy look back at
that board show no green fast paced win
a crook Mac - for dos
and a half a stroke after they
in that last play see mr. death like
Jojo but [ __ ] still sitting in the glass
case no I ain't no B's nearly all I got
in hand
nice key bhai trying to sell the man cuz
his shots ain't enough [ __ ]
what does that what's happening I kept
it in there