I'm done if you're actually down have
you ever seen someone work out to a song
about numbers answer's no that's simply
because there is no song about numbers
until today hey yo good morning okay
that changes today guys the numbers song
my music video my song the dumbest
you've ever made is that today if you
have not watched it yet go watch you
give it a like it'll make you smarter
better sexy faster stronger these are
facts I have no motivation to lie to you
not convinced okay here's a preview oh
you wanted more guess you're just gonna
have to watch it we about to get this
day poppin but if you're not part of the
low game make sure to subscribe smack
the button in the face is doing the
strongest family on YouTube actually
today's interesting I am about to put a
brick by Logan Paul my clothing line we
just dropped these blue prism
performance short for the brows who like
to perform drop them in blue and also
purple oh all right these are the
woman's performance reports and purple
as well the merch is so soft and so fire
sometimes I literally forget my gender I
don't no way to get in Logan Volcom
slash shop now it's free shipping on
domestic orders over $50 get it while
the pancakes are cooking the iron's hot
the griddle is running also guys as you
know yesterday's blog we're looking for
a new roommate videographer we got some
pretty interesting submissions I could
fix all your problems
Wow he should be in school still looking
for that person but okay guys I'm done
talking it's time to work out to a song
about numbers 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
[Music]
Oh two things I learned for that workout
one our performance shorts definitely
perform very impressed with them they
got the interlining right here the
ultimate thigh grip into working out two
numbers brother that gets you hype it's
great everyone knows the lyrics
hopefully okay never a dull moment here
guys this morning something interesting
happened have you ever woken up to a
bunch of balls you know when it comes to
that vlog light it can get really stupid
and you never know when you're gonna
need a pile of balls to fulfill your
vlog needs I actually do have an idea
for these balls but you gotta subscribe
we're not doing it today however I do
have an idea something we could do right
now okay alright stay there all right
guys I'm not gonna lie some time has
passed it's dark outside if it's too
busy sending it hey by the way yeah hi
good to see you bro what you wanna be a
videographer go for it oh snap this is
totally gonna work
so I have something super crazy to tell
you hi I have some super crazy to tell
you guys and yeah it's not gonna well is
that gonna make a vlog funnier swear
work out blow your problem for me bro
look in the mirror here you got two bros
who were just savages you can't just
walk into this tree oh right you gotta
earn that I think I'm gonna make Greg
Paul the roommate in being our new
roommate yeah yeah when's the last time
you actually like you know like sent it
we're just a little concerned haven't
sent it in a while in two seconds wait
wait wait 90 seconds well I was not
expecting that uh here here you try it
what do we do yeah
Papa Papa Jim what's it gonna be not
first off you point up a little bit more
I think to get both wasn't the first now
send it with a pop zoo these pops ain't
going this way
I like the angles I just feel like you
are a little too you know how to feel me
different doing me and their peoples I
film the important things
oh I hope it's security you guys know
Spencer Taylor okay what are the most
savage savages in the world easy with
the possums no no I don't think so I
think he was just on his way back to
Ohio oh no Taylor Ramada application no
we know your videographer yeah no we've
shot a lot together we've raced cars
yeah oh we've web people husband and
wife you may kiss the bride so you are a
videographer and a damn good one but we
noticed you also checked off the Senate
ability everyone me the camera to shoot
this because it's the best angle for it
your shorts no that's a great idea
holy no one's calling you sure like
don't wake you pop zoom zoom to
overcompensate for this non funny joke
ready guys
put your asses your son Greg our woman
boy shorts are still really nice you can
get him downloadable we know you're good
yeah I can tell you how to zooming I can
see it is good yeah what's up with you
missing the check here whoa you know can
you not smoke - have you seen of it I
just got to see the situation the
problem yeah you prepared your smoke
alarms got bags on Umbro again this is
not safe
this is why we go with Spence this
carbon monoxide bro get it away
it's fires hard no he's a genius
to extend his reach and using the stick
of the lint roller he's gonna get the
bag used the stick of the lint roller
I'm done if you're actually down
and he's environmentally conscious whoa
I'm actually losing my mind
actually yeah I think absolutely got
Evan yeah one thing we have to do is
true this is true
[Music]
alright alright lo gang that is do well
we got a new roommate dog actually
welcome you gotta get your stuff move in
and we'll make it official out of bed
you're that so I guess officially
welcome to the Mavericks Wamba squad if
we're gonna do it different y'all know
we do this every single day and if
you're having a captain merged how to
softest Merson game go ahead and do that
Logan Paul Keim slash free shipping on
domestic orders over $50 get it while
the iron's hot
lastly go ahead and make out with the
subscribe button for meelo gang I love
y'all that we'll see you tomorrow
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16
17 18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25
[Music]