Kong is about to meet his new sister
aria who is right there I know what you
guys are thinking Logan why do you look
so good maybe you're not thinking that
but you know maybe Brendan why do you
look so good there is a reason it's
because we haven't slept that is a fact
we went out to the club time chief an
hour ago I think an hour ago yeah double
fact and if you look indoors and burn
them lies down low we got the morning
voices but now we have to head to the
airport Rome I just want to say te amo
Italia a2a
bellissimo I just combined languages but
hot damn I really am gonna miss this
place it's beautiful I'm also gonna miss
you Hayden sorry for waking you up sorry
there is no time to waste we figure it
would be better you just stay up through
the night enjoy Rome have fun with the
nightlife and then go right to the
airport I have actually done this before
which the OG lo gangsters might remember
but yeah we're gonna miss a plane what
what we have to go now
bro we gotta go now Italy how you bought
the show three savages in a small you
mean like today no oh you bro anyway
good good good morning so yeah this is
one of those very real vlog like I make
this so when I'm like 50 years old I
could come back and watch him be like oh
yeah that's what happened yeah it's the
magic of the vlog life that's why I do
it yeah if you were not a part of the
loading make sure to subscribe we are a
family we're changing the world every
single day so hit the button for me imma
wait I'm away
you hit the button you hit the button
alright dub-dub-dub let's go to the
airport
yeah oh you know what I just remembered
roommate evan has got a new dog
literally there is an American I think
it's a pitbull terrier brand new puppy
what uh Brendon name name name Aria Aria
Aria there's a baby puppy in my house
you can bet your ass I'm gonna use that
for click buy that dumb nail also one
question someone please tell me who
decided to put a snail outside of the
airport next to what is this Oliva the
meerkat a meerkat what next what is the
[ __ ] I just don't get it but Italian I
still love you ciao I do it oh my gosh
are you in the lo game no forever bro
you can't stop I respect the low game is
too strong
no I'm wondering if the Italian police
like stamped my past or like put it in
the system that like I'm not allowed to
come back and I like am i deported it's
like this is taking a bit longer than I
had expected Milan straight through like
no issues dude they like I'm I'm
blacklisted Italy like I'm a Tiamo I
said it before am i banned from my legal
you're not you're not really they said
no really so there's like I can assure
you I'm a good Ohio boy have great
credit I got a good family the low gang
I got the hottest merch in the game you
don't be a maverick local pawn
you know oh we got a locator go with the
line for like customs to get into the
United States looks like that no this is
not cool they let me up front because
they recognize me but I gotta split I'll
do as many splitters I need come not
waned in that we haven't blogged this
but no joke we've been walking for like
two miles we two miles I'm gonna check
my step counter on my life is engine bro
this is like this whole airport
everything is just maximize kind of like
my Vince
alright let's one point
[Music]
okay it is official oh this is fun
that's a good time in case you want to
get to know the person next to you oh
maybe she's the babe who wants to make
some cookies oh I have officially been
awake for 24 hours that's right Logan I
pulled an all-nighter
we are in the spaceship section of the
plane mama mia by the way Brendan no
good oh this is my first time flying
first wait wait wait actually oh my god
call the first class this is business
you a friend
normally Logan puts me in the back of
the plane yo listen budgets are tight
I'm just kidding bro y'all smooth emerge
man my boy can do business
I don't know where to get it Logan Paul
Cosmo okay so I called this time trap
clearly I'm I'm exhausted there's a lot
of things in my system that shouldn't be
in my system and I'm literally going to
close my eyes in time travel to Los
Angeles where by the way it's gonna be
like the same time as it is here now we
let go back in time with time travel
oh yeah she'll be fun all right back in
Los Angeles baby that's time cameraman
Brendan I gotta ask how was your first
class experience we are both extremely
tired anyways yeah straight-up time
travel we slept the entire time but
we're still both exhausted we feel sick
definitely sick definitely sit right
look at my shoes bro I'm the most
wretched mother at this airport well
ratchet in you okay also yo Brendan I
remembered during the play cuz I was
laying on my back I got cut last night
dude and do you remember I fell guys on
the metal railings if he's that bad
that's pretty bad yeah okay you should
get that cleaned up okay literally fell
on the metal railing I probably need a
tetanus shot who knows what kind of
diseases I have but I want to say G
means get out of look
and I was weird we okay look immediately
we are getting back to the grind or
through emails and stuff right now we
have a big week coming up like like a
big week yo we get the yeti back
tomorrow thank God
yeah it's been hot right it's like you
mystified it but I can't sit in the
backseat of your charge right now it's a
challenger it's a Dodge Challenger
challenge I know a plus bro imagine the
driving with Evan segments in the rap
that thing is fixed because as you guys
know the lady hit it and I decked it out
like they're like it's not gonna be the
same car but it's a straight-up monster
now then I'm gonna late night talk show
later this week oh we do we get the cool
bass back this thing is insane might
have to live in this soon no no oh yeah
that too we are gonna be homeless this
week because as y'all know where you
getting kicked out and we have not yet
found a house sick so that's gonna be
interesting also we're shooting a music
video for a song you guys may remember
it's called out of my hair's a lot of
stuff okay let's focus on right now I
miss my boy maverick I miss song the
savage I miss my roommate Evan I sort of
Miss Lydia because she's taking care of
Kong I purposely had lady I take Kong
away from my house oh my god
oh this is a good sign bro I had Kong
separate Kong from Evans new puppy aria
what who did I say come what you hadn't
come separate comb I said I had Kong
separate Kong yep
it's been a rough night it's to Peter
it's been a rough day I had Lydia
separate cars from Aria we could get the
meeting for the first time ever on
camera no cos call cogs getting a new
sister straight up except to be honest
they're probably getting probably not
gonna be brother and sister feel that
Kong's good definitely try to like hump
her a lot so
that would make them like husband and
wife eventually I don't know we'll see
what happens let's go see this puppy bro
quit paws I told you guys we were
getting right back to work it's my
business I know the Maverick Enterprise
is no joke you know something you don't
know though I don't know a lot of things
I've got a new dog in there right now
yes that's what we're going to I'm so
happy
come out if you're in the low gang don't
come out you're not coming in he's an
adult now
[Music]
you know you've matured with them no no
he gets a dog okay let's go see this
probably shouldn't be yeah I know for
germs and bird flu and [ __ ]
I'll be back no I will be back wait
where's your dog Lydia has him that's
some samurai separated they're gonna
meet later it's gonna be epic
click subscribe look at the shop
every bro it's good to see you dude I
wish I could say the same
oh okay it's 4:15 right now what's doing
that I'm doing now Kevin you really
outdone yourself bro we have another
girl in the house officials you know a
girl in the house we get the legs bro
she's posted up just like a frog the
question is are you gonna train her at
the same time of training calm I think
called wall overdue for training yeah
I'm saying but you look like you've been
training and like you're follow the
rules he's not doing that I don't know I
don't follow you can't meet or hang out
with calls like another month or a shot
yet - she does meet poems she'd get a
heart worm and killers yo this just got
so depressing so quick yo I hate you
don't Levin you can't what oh sweet oh
don't Levin sucks we want Evan back
where's that who you want we want Evan
yep you'll see Brendan it'll be worth it
neighbors like Logan bag
it's a little too big rewind how do you
say that he started the a before he
finished the domain music let's go
protests we want we want we want Evan we
want
Evan we want evidence we keep you though
we'll keep our yeah yeah are you do you
know where evidence why do you sound
like ass what do I sound like ass yeah
let me tell you about the night we've
had we didn't sleep we got all right on
the plane time traveled wrote like
Brendan and I are both a ratchet as you
tell you're gross both you guys thanks
Wow thanks Jeff yo this puppies so cute
I do think Brendan yeah we should get
cleaned off bro okay so you don't live
here I don't wait I don't know I know we
have probably don't live here either in
the very near future I think you go home
okay yeah bro like you should just go
home reset I'm gonna do that too then
we'll rendezvous after our Jeff and I do
some business there's not really into
the dab transitions today a look at me
dude I'll clean this feels good yo man
my man Brendan is clean it was good damn
bro you're a new man yeah so we're both
like we're both super silly took a toll
that is a fact Italians are no Joseph
we're waiting for Lydia right now I told
her to come over she has calling who
even though Evan said we probably
shouldn't introduce to sister aria is
gonna smell that another dog has been
living in his house for the past week
and bro his name is calling The Saboteur
he don't take that slightly he's gonna
be pissed at me so Evan actually left
he's not there we just do it like we're
not gonna put him like next to each
other or like on top of each other
there's another dog in the house so even
like OPA aria indicate
I know I'm much better than your dad I
know I know it is freaking little me q
brother you're so cute well yeah I think
we keep aria in the cage and then like
just like show Kong are you see how they
interact and then we'll do like a
full-on like meetup for another vlog I
don't think I've ever seen a dog with
eyes no eyes right okay you're gonna
meet your brother slash husband slash
boyfriend sue hey no don't hate me
because you ain't me washing my hands
because I don't want Kong to think I
cheated on him by the way uh him in
Lydia are outside
I miss my boy hi wow I'm gonna set Kong
down let's see if there's any like
suspicious activity see if he knows is
another dog here oh you hear that gong
what's that noise
oh no oh I'll call you here okay yo I
think I think that's our cue I think we
just do it Kong meets his new sister REO
for the first time let's do this oh my
god Kahn's not barking or anything this
is like this is kind of magical you guys
can't interact it but you can look at
each other okay no I think that's good I
think we did Olli that was anticlimactic
yeah pretty calm he's always calm what
did you tell me cuz apparently you
changed yeah because he's not that
everything I know
twice not the Kong I know I think he was
really happy at my place honestly come
on yeah no way no one's happy at your
house I'm happy he's happy thank you
guys for watching we are on to you Lydia
we're know you doing some fishing
activities if you're not a part of the
low gang make sure to subscribe row we
live we pop be a frickin maverick every
day do something different change the
world we can't do that one day but you
can sure as hell try and that's what we
do every single day by being different
by not being afraid to follow our
passion forgetting about what all the
haters and naysayers think we are
Mavericks baby that's what the logo is
that's what it means copy yourself some
maverick merch how does merch in the
game looking ball that cop slash shop or
link in description okay I love y'all
I'll see you tomorrow oh oh oh the Eddie
tomorrow we're kin big vlog bro I'm
excited you hear that
[Music]