it's no longer fight week it is time to
fight guys we're at the Kansai versus
Logan Paul Jake Paul versus veggie
official weigh-in I'm in the best shape
of my life I feel good I look the
greatest I've ever looked give me a
little uptown boy I am looking freshest
Foster Mavericks showed up today baby
it's the hottest softest nurse in the
game I'm just I'm ready Jake and I have
worked for five months five months to
achieve this one goal and that is to
beat the shifts please brothers and we
finally get to do it we finally get to
shut them up tomorrow I'm just excited
bro I'm ready so let's do this
let's bring up first he's 23 years old
he stands six feet to originally from
Ohio but now living training and
fighting out of Hollywood USA America's
number one youtube acting music and
video sensation making his youtube
boxing debut tomorrow night is the
official Challenger and he is low
Oh
there he is Logan Paul and his opponent
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
86 even 86 even 86 kill
oh look at this dude tomorrow night
YouTube friends it all goes down at
Manchester Arena
holy communion
it's time to fight ah I was like oh
you're gonna sexually harass her - yeah
I was like you're kind of a pervert you
know that and he's like oh yeah and okay
sighs huge on the mental game he was
wearing a picture of my girlfriend's
face Chloe bent
okay it's funny I gotta respect it but
I've been through too much mentally this
whole entire year to let that affect me
so I don't know bro eyes I saw it his
physique honestly was impressed should
be a good fight
unfortunately for him I'm gonna have to
knock him out though damn him Hey
delicious he did he did he took the
piece of chewing gum he took the bait
it's gonna be the same in the fight say
no more words it's time to fight okay
guys tomorrow girl you know I'm gonna
make you my [ __ ] and you know you're
gonna crumble and from the whole entire
world brother you've had a good run but
it's about to end
low gang I love you guys make sure to
subscribe if you have not yet cop your
maverick most hottest off this merch in
the game it's going team maverick I will
see you guys tomorrow on finite link in
description to buy the fight a kiss bro
[Music]