having me to make this vlog for a while
I wasn't sure when the right time to do
it was but okay listen let's talk about
guys in fact I'm still in a weird mood
from Burning Man feel slow just like
worn out what we do today huh the boys
are back in town how do you make plans
to go to the beach and like I don't want
to invite you because you already been
like around a lot of sand already yeah
actually I have you're more than welcome
to come then might bring back a lot of
bad memories Wow seriously look at our
suitcase no this is ridiculous
watch our cameras - I just straight up
covered in sand and dust look at the
GoPro as well the point is it's a
disaster but yo don't even want to come
don't even want to come Jake are you
doing I didn't mean that I just panicked
so I said it oh yeah the guy he doesn't
have a dick huh yes I do I could show
you
I will see you Evan bye yo Bernie wanna
go to the beach yeah here at Venice
Beach I got one question where the
honey's at lo oh damn see bro it ain't
no Yeti but it's sexy Brown did he call
me sick I'm not really sure talking
about his own car I think he called you
sexy I'll shake it Randy this sand is
bringing back bad memories brother over
okay hey what the [ __ ] yo why is that it
well no way what
yo it's so crazy you decided to come to
the beach great what you tell me more
coming Road no way I didn't know you
were gonna be here at the beach wait
what no way that's crazy coincidence
anyways good to see you bro damn damn
bro I've got the setup [ __ ] your
umbrella skateboard will give walk we're
ready to go to the beach baby go home I
got ya we gotta come out would you say
I'm too out here
look out
bodysurfing
demands in her body serving come by
[Music]
you just kick
I was on my knees in that way I'm not
gonna lie this is exactly what I needed
to just like cool off chill out right
now not to mention I think this is the
first time I've been in the ocean since
I've lived in LA
you see I think so we're right like four
years whatever man is the first time for
anything like but stuff anyways cause
here let's do a little carmine no Jill
right now today he doesn't like kids he
doesn't like birds and he doesn't like
water
the beach is not good to calm calm down
I'm aware his ass out there bro
[Music]
work at the crib oh okay as you guys
know this vlog isn't insanely long as of
now shut the [ __ ] up Evan I like to give
the low gang at least at least 10
minutes of content but today like I said
guys I'm just feeling sluggish like I've
been meeting to make this vlog for now
I've been meaning to make this vlog for
a while I wasn't sure when the right
time to do it was but okay listen let's
talk about no it is a big deal it is a
big deal when I first started doing
YouTube I was at about a half million
subscribers which actually by the way
Evan is that right now and he's he has
like two videos out screw you wait and I
made this video called these glasses
cured my colorblindness currently I'm
looking at it it has 19 million views
I'm talking anyways I'm sure you've seen
the video but if you haven't the gist of
it is I got these glasses and they cure
to my colorblindness well that was the
title and that's what I made it look
like I had this big reaction I put the
sunglasses on I went throughout the day
like explaining what color blindness was
blah blah here watch I'm color blind and
inside this box are glasses that will
fix my colorblindness I'm a certain type
of colorblind as for example I can see
this too
top as you can imagine I got a lot of
hate a lot of people made fun of me a
lot of people said it was fake said I
wasn't colorblind yeah yeah I got made
fun of them don't like you make fun up
there you know I know so can you stop
Elise sorry I just I get made fun of too
so yeah anyways a lot of people made fun
of me a lot of big youtubers watch this
[Music]
[Applause]
and I'm just sitting here like damn I
just started YouTube why am i the center
of attack right now because the worst
part about it I'm just gonna say right
now I am color blind however there were
some things I did in the video where I
made a mistake and opened the doors for
getting made fun of so like your birds
just one color to you what your bird is
just one color yeah to you what what
you're saying but he's like four
different colors he's all of those
colors he's orange red yellow maverick
yeah my bird your bird man whose burden
we'll be talking about maverick is
yellow I know for a fact maverick is not
all yellow for a fact I put that in the
video thinking people would a hundred
percent take that as a joke because in
the vlog I made it very clear that I'm
red green colorblind which by the way if
you don't know what that means I'll
explain it in a second here this is you
time that was one second so a red-green
colorblind bait it's not like I can't
see red or green colorblindness in
general means when a bunch of colors
that are like sort of the similar shade
are like next to each other and mesh
together to me it looks like a giant
blob anyways I said I said I thought
maverick was all yellow and people
believed me and that was that was a huge
point of attack for people I shouldn't
have said that
I thought it was obvious that that was a
joke I guess I'm just like okay yeah
first let me start by saying that whole
vlog I wanted to create an amazing story
an amazing piece of content that first
started by showing like what it means to
be colorblind
testing the glasses seeing if they kind
of work and then ending on a beautiful
sunset and looking at it with the
glasses on just like any storyteller I
made it a I exaggerated my reactions and
the colorblindness that's why people
thought that I was lying however I will
say this I did not lie I did not like
what I did do is embellish there's a big
difference embellish is like and what I
was doing in that vlog is you heighten
the circumstances or make something yeah
yeah exactly hi in the circus to see if
I would war still
you make something a little bit more fun
a little bit more exciting but there is
a core any root of truth to it
did it work be crying it's beautiful
like like life life happen and then as
far as my reaction goes where I actually
saw the sunset
what those glasses did for me is they
accentuated the blues I've never I
legitimately had never seen the sunset
that intense and that beautiful so it
was it was very easy for me to to get
that reaction out of me like it my hands
down was the most beautiful sense that
I've ever seen so that part wasn't fake
did I exaggerate a little bit yeah but
like dude no one wants to see a boring
story I'm a storyteller I'm Annabelle
sure I'm a boost you might say there
embellished tips and polished it yes
brendi that's what I'm saying guys when
I hit Evan they're not real they're a
ballast sometimes I'm real no they're
not you're the one who hits me for real
you kicked me that one time and I one
time bro just like that I think it's all
I want to hit with that set low gang
that is a block if you are not a part of
the family make sure you subscribe we
have the strongest family on YouTube
we're the fastest growing the fastest
it's actually anyway cop your maverick
March go out be passionate be different
be unique don't be afraid to expand
outside of whatever bubble you live in I
did it when I was a boy in Ohio look at
me now I'm a youtuber living in Los
Angeles link for that is in the
description
Logan Paul con /op I love y'all I will
see you tomorrow take it easy man this
bro so close
[Music]