hello gang let's dive in for a second I
do owe you guys an explanation you guys
are my family you inspire me the reason
I make content is literally for you guys
so I felt like this needed to be like
one into the water
you bite it's not ruined your big dumb
dummy you didn't think I thought this
through never think they use your brain
oven of course I did I'll be right back
with the plan by the way
don't worry bowl of rice works when your
iphone files in the water nope I should
do it how long do we wait now anywhere
from four to six minutes
but anyways hey what's up little game
guys I know I missed the last two days
oh sorry about that I'm gonna get into
that later it's a whole little thing I
actually wanna like take a second to
talk about blood if you're not part of
the Logan make sure to subscribe smash
the button in the face to me cuz as you
can see we are the strongest most lit
and probably weirdest family on YouTube
we do have a flaws though we have some
flaws such as whatever happened here I
don't understand what happened bro when
I was building the ramp it all made so
much sense in my mind it's all science
you guys know I just got back from
Coachella yeah boy yeah boy definitely
chill at his ass off but basic level was
very high I fun fact I haven't showered
or even shaved since then once again
I'll say yeah we're working on it and
you guys can probably hear my nasal
passages are a little congested I've
been sick
which reminds me by the way quick put
all the energy on a real note we gotta
figure out what we're gonna do about
this soil in the pool because because
soil doesn't necessarily mix with water
I don't think this is gonna just
disappear
Adam I'm a real adult level it's
actually sucks
any ideas Spencer my granddaddy used to
say first shirt Coachella's for go I saw
this hand side a little rugrat he's back
at it again coach Mellor is feeling kind
of vibe us dancing doing what we did
after my fight in August I want to
travel the world for like six months and
go to the most exotic places and blog
everything just like super positive let
me tell you I decided to respond I'm
done with you evil super okay surprise
yeah in the soil yeah yeah the hottest
merch in the game that you can get now
only on Logan
oh my god
this is horrifying
[Music]
any to up
quarter million stub your car cause it's
just the blood you can hook in my hot
something very drastic went down have
you ever smelled like food that has been
rotting look for weeks
well that's what we're dealing with oh
my god are you kidding me open up all of
your windows that you come into park
basically that's what we are hot dog bus
actual hot dog bun so here's what
happened Jake came over he was like
y'all wanna be part of team maverick I
would love to get some of your merch
because I know it's hot in the game I
was like no bro
he got pissed and he slimed my car and
that happened let it soak for another
day and then deliver it to Jay's house
absolutely what's happening so guys
tomorrow's vlog we're gonna deliver this
no we don't get this off soon it's never
coming off about this liquid perfect
perfect in my mind it works perfectly
it's just science oh damn it well I
guess somebody miscalculated the
algorithm this bad boy overseas to case
always house mmm you'll be in no
condition to fight but the tournament
box gets to your house Spencer you were
in the midst of that whole slap fight no
your maverick joggers literally spotless
absolutely no idea shirt
ruin not like that's amazing row
we're witnessing miracles folks a son to
give it proper cookies right okay man
I've been waiting all day let's go see
the freaking dirt
here we go Evan I understand it works
with iPhone maybe it's because we only
got the back tire yeah yeah yeah it
started with oh wow
that's just phenomenal oh wait what rice
bro I knew it would work
this is crazy bro so God I told you guys
oh man oh God
every part of the play kids get a tire
did you ever pay phasic have you ever
had an iphone wait wow I'm just thankful
all my friends are much smarter than me
we're working on the Cygnus I look like
a freaking mess right now hello gang
let's dive in for a second I do owe you
guys an explanation you guys are my
family you inspire me the reason I make
content is literally for you guys so I
felt like this needed to be said ha
vlogging a daily vlogging I did not vlog
for the past two days because that was
at Coachella and in combination with me
being sick and having low energy like I
made a conscious decision to put every
ounce of energy I had into like dancing
and just having fun in like my real life
and you guys don't know this at
Coachella you're not a lot of film
professionally and even though it is
just a couple of us running around like
idiots with the camera technically it is
like professional and again you guys
don't know this but we had this issue
with Burning Man after the festival was
over we ran into some difficulties with
filming inside and whatnot even at your
70 National Park and we were there the
forest rangers they're like yo you you
cannot monetize any of these videos I
don't know if you guys noticed none of
them are monetized there were no ads in
the u.s. 70 videos over my birthday
weekend which was fine but when it
basically when it comes to filming in a
large environment like Coachella there
are so many things that I just didn't
feel like worrying about in combination
with being sick in combination with the
fact that it's a music festival so every
time there's music playing in the
background which was all the time
there's gonna be a copyright complaint
and then the video would just be either
taken down or not monetized just the
storm of us and I did not really feel
like dealing with but the reason I bring
this up is because I want to dive a
little deeper into the conversation
because it is it goes beyond just
Coachella you guys know this I read your
comments whether it's me on a live
stream whether it's on Twitter at logo
ball Instagram Alec and Paul or just I'm
the YouTube channel and a lot of you
guys are commenting logan or uploading
today where's the daily vlog are you
even daily vlog anymore you've done in
the past why how come you're making
excuses now I'm at the point where I've
vlog I've done I've done the daily
vlogging thing for literally 460 days in
a row and it is fabulous but my goal and
you guys know this I've said it before I
say it all the time with the vlogs is to
give you guys an escape from your daily
life just come to this channel and have
fun you get entertained you get ideas
you get inspired whatever it is that's
my job and me
personally I am uninspired when I feel
like I cannot do that
to my full potential whether it's me
being sick whether it's me wanting to
allocate my time to branch out and do
other things guys I I know you don't
like to hear the sentence but I'm not
gonna be vlogging for the rest of the
mile I have so many other projects I'm
working on you guys know about him like
we just built a $90,000 podcast set in
my garage because we're gonna be doing
podcasts live podcast it's called
impulsive for you guys just as another
source of entertainment even this room
this gaming room is something I just
wanted to branch out and try it just cuz
like I my goal is to be the biggest
entertainer in the world I don't want to
be locked down to one little thing
whether it's YouTube daily vlogging
sketches on Instagram making music we're
putting a studio I think the studio is
like two weeks out from being done in my
front guest house gaming building
businesses the Maverick Enterprise the
merge the oddest merged in the game
maverick my Logan Paul all of these
things combined I'm testing sort of I'm
dipping my toes in the water to find out
not only what I like as a 23 year old
human being what makes me happy on
planet earth but what you guys like
because as you know I didn't I didn't
get on YouTube until like a year and a
half two years ago before that I did
vine they have to Instagram than have to
Facebook and then got on YouTube I like
trying different things I want to do
everything like a full 360 degree circle
basically I'm rambling right now but
your guys's patience will unlock the
universe for us when it comes to content
by Logan Paul most importantly guys
something I've realized even this past
week in the Coachella this vlog as silly
as it is is so much bigger than me and
my team I had a fan come up to me at
Coachella you know who you are you dog I
told you inspire me a person and I'm
saying it now I hope you're ok with it
the low gang is gonna know so he had
lost someone very close to him they were
like this and he told me he was broke
the only reason I got out of bed the
next morning was because I was looking
forward to watching your vlog and I
literally got goosebumps the person he
had lost was his father and mmin I'm
like probably even you you this is why I
made content you are the reason I'm
inspired to make vlogs so I take that
and it just re-energizes me and is a
positive confirmation for me that I need
keep working on how I can use my
platform and our strength as a family on
YouTube to make a positive impact on the
world very soon I have been itching to
go like just just help people and maybe
you guys can help me figure out what
that cause is whatever attendant it
turns out to go to them whatever it
turns out to be look I don't know what
it is okay and I know it's not cheesy
but someone's got to do it the point is
low gang I freaking love you guys and
your patience with me is going to unlock
I promise
with that said locating that is the plug
if you're not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe
I enjoyed the Sharks pamela and youtube
also do yourself a freaking favor dude
cop the hottest merch in the game logo
paul calm / shut up orally in
description we do it every day we do it
different every day
it's that maverick movement low gay I
love y'all I will see you tomorrow take
it easy
[Music]
with the concept for that one you really
hit it out of the park
I miss fun night