three years later and he's gonna cure my
color-wise goodness again oh that's me
and Julius tandem bike have you ever
taken off a jump or something I'm down
one of those red jumps that's a giant
I'm telling you bro if we hit 50 miles
an hour we can't really afford to get
hurt it's 5:00 in case I still coming up
I have like a saying that I wrote down
in my notes it's don't be a crash stuff
we used to be crash dummies bro we were
just do stupid vines yeah yeah we
definitely don't do that anymore Logan
I'm not feeling safe back here this is a
mistake I'm gonna play the agent role
here and say no after that's crazy
we're on a second coming from someone
who's made no mistakes in the past rust
me when I stay like this
faceplant hey hey yo y'all want to know
something about Jake hello in the first
videos we've ever made it still on
YouTube it's Jake riding a mountain bike
up a picnic table called me a [ __ ] for
saying no you'll do it with you I'm done
Oh Oh
are you good I think so are you are you
good I think so I'm chilly
uh yes should be re-roll where's jack
he's going at any point what jeff has
been telling you for two weeks went into
your mind when you got out it's like so
hard as hard as I could probably do you
know how I am I get an idea you might
even feel a condom with water then drop
it on your head stupid challenge I'm
doing every challenge that's ever
existed because this quarantine do look
everybody has magnet loving posit giant
[ __ ] is lying it's not true
my names are so functional kill your
sperms keep you from having babies and
can be used as a water balloon
Oh [ __ ] hell man hurt me emotionally
mostly I [ __ ] up now what does I mean
I swear to God that was not intentional
you gotta put your hand under it at
first you see a published author but
he's still dropping water filled condom
on his friends head oh this time guys
who feel confident about this one
[Music]
hey guys I think we did it wrong I let
her have a testicle hang out with my
face
[Music]
[Applause]
three seven one I can't see anything you
can see that my eyes are ridiculous I
guess I'm trying to do here is like
three years have gone by since the color
blind bTW I'm wondering if I'm still
colorblind it turns out I am some of
these things I just cannot see wait what
are you guys so you guys just see
nothing I cannot see Bri you have really
real trouble with teals and greens
oh-oh-oh
Roatan colorblind I'm pretty sure when I
made the video back in the day was mild
and now it's strong now they're trying
to sell you a glasses well that's the
thing maybe now that it's more severe
than it was in the past somebody call a
tree a tree up we got to gotta go to the
new your sunset which I believe is
happening inconveniently one hour so
beautiful
you know last time I did this guys I got
pretty emotional you remember but that
was before I grew a dick
so hopefully this time I'll be able to
collect myself but it's just hard
because you know when I look out I see a
black and white landscape nothingness
and ideally these glasses will make me
see a little bit more vivid crisper
definition of this landscape
three years later he's gonna cure my
color wine again
Wow Wow this was a joke at first but it
actually is Wow
oh man it's kind of sad I'm not even
kidding no it's really pretty this is
what I'm missing out on I was gonna be
all dramatic and like fake cry but
actually cried I'm gonna be honest even
I remember in the video I made last time
I wasn't like faking it I was just
exaggerating it like yeah I didn't need
the waterworks I didn't do the crying
she but it really is pretty like the
blues are much more vivid the oranges
are much more vivid anyways guys yeah
maverick clothing drop Friday it's a big
launch really freaking excited we're
doing a VIP club as well gonna be
limited edition consider it my version
of it only fans and if you're lucky you
might even get some tasteful nudes
that's a joke play it's gonna be good
matter clothing calm this Friday hit
that subscribe button also fits around
this beautiful mountain landscape I want
to say for everyone with the
notifications on and for the people who
comment first and watch a video I really
do like you guys like a lot I appreciate
your enthusiasm for consuming this [ __ ]
to make because I put effort into it
it's nice to know that it's being
received the way I want it normally we
end on a funny note but you know doing
throw backs today so I'll see you guys
on Friday
what happens
[Laughter]
[Music]