at this moment you may be asking
yourself what is Logan doing hold
transparency I did not have a good
answer you guys watch the vlogs I'm
losing my mind officially my garage is
turn too so I've decided to turn it into
a giant green screen looks like Shrek
sneezed on your floor what do you want
lazy river no problem actual like sedge
picker right here you could see Kong's
paw prints and he used to run around the
garage when there wasn't carpet in here
when we pulled the carpet up the other
day and put the sign in on top of her
house I said send nudes cease were
revealed and it's actually uh it's kind
of sad I don't know
I bought this vlog dude yo you think I
could dunk myself Evans to this house Oh
Mel I'm gonna be the bigger person I've
tried the good news with like all this
quarantine is like we can save like this
and we control the footage and like we
know that this will never end up on the
inner mic help me come on Evan aids me
too or monster so I forgot what I was
doing in this room oh yeah
[Music]
nice come on come this way follow me you
see that those are bird eggs I know but
you gotta look out for the mom and you
know and your thumbs going right on my
my question is should we have scrambled
their sunny-side up oh my god scramble
how you doing
isolation vacation am i right just
trying to find some companionship that's
why you got to send the news I don't
want to see you nude just send them know
anyone's fine I'm not ages the tops and
nudes you think we should take that down
[Laughter]
this is what the virus wants biological
warfare turns us against each other
exactly it's a green screen oh look a
lion someone very important behind you
oh you know these guys Disney they
rehired you hi I'm Jake Bolin you're
watching
[Music]
yeah duh are you kidding college where
do you do it you're doing oh my god your
diet we were talking about your stomach
bro
how big is your dick social visits holy
[ __ ] I just ran from a stranger don't
take this personally everyone is the
enemy where'd you say you do this you
love her back I'm so glad I'm single
don't comment below drop a comment below
they actually already have they had some
things to say about you I'd like to read
them now yo Michael is John shaped by
that distribution so disproportionate
out does the per capita income disparity
in third-world countries that I like it
was a well-thought-out it had actual
terminology and also design is delicious
that's what I'm saying by surprise while
acting like I'm the one that's not
involved in everything you're the only
one that's oh my god we did she know I
don't know guys I've no idea you turn my
life around does he know [ __ ] of course
I know you don't know
whoa
[Music]