Oh your holy autumn ah Brendon North
said you suck at driving please let me
out of the car not to reply no wait hold
up this thing is dangerous this just
reads your text okay interesting way to
start the morning yeah yeah
good morning okay what's bobbin no as
you can see the mustache is on fleek
right now which is important because we
are headed to a Ryan Seacrest radio show
actually
good thing it's the radio yeah wait no I
think it's taped bro I think they can
see this beautiful stache am i right hey
Brendon am i right yeah as you guys may
know I have a movie coming up just gonna
wash the mask on everywhere all over
your face nose chin cheeks and forehead
and around your under eyes or eyelids
can you let it sit for 20 minutes I
think it probably says on the tube and
then you peel it off there so you kind
of put it on thick so it's easier to
peel I just like this is dangerous bro
imagine if my main chick is in the car
and my side chick is texting me oh okay
back on track do you have a movie coming
out this week with my friend my good
friend King batch and Kat Graham it's
called where's the money we're gonna be
doing some stuff for it this week like
the premieres this week as well right
now we're doing like some promotional
stuff which includes this Ryan Seacrest
Morning Show
your boys blown up route the maverick
enterprises going baby and with the
success of out of my hair music this
point it's got like 7 million views it
hasn't even been a day but y'all right
now I heart media your boy Logan Paul is
coming your worst nightmare let's do
this your mustache is my worst nightmare
[Music]
I always wonder when they decide to put
me on these shows are they like wow I
think this is a good idea in this little
room it's great apparently Ryan and team
have set up a like a surprise meet up
with a member of the low game her name
is
Emily so anyway she apparently thinks
she's here for a tour of I heart media
but at one point I'm gonna come up and
just be myself my chachi self and
surprise her and hopefully it can make
her day yeah she recognizes you Brennan
enough with the stache jokes bro no way
where are you 30
yeah hi hi Logan and we'll bring Emily
and she won't know you're here we'll
talk to her and then we'll have you come
in and surprise like freeze up and so
you sort of like surprise things always
make me a little like a little [ __ ] I
don't know how it's gonna go like Emily
I'll be like if you're not nervous like
I am bro you're inspired by Logan Paul
yes like you'd like this dude yes look
at her face just lit up we even when you
said his name I'm trying to understand
this guy I've seen him on you I don't
understand him sometimes what's he doing
being himself he's just being a busy dad
crazy
yeah he seems a little crazy do you
think he's cute of course would you open
the door mark for a second because I'm
distracted by the essence
she's got peach bubblegum he smells Mike
if you actually if you have more peach
gum I would love that peach gum peach
fuzz it's my big day
so Emily does he look like you who would
picture him to look like in person Yeah
right
what
even with the stache yeah I love Emily
so cool you so cool
are you like freaking out inside how did
you get a rose made of dollar bills you
should make a piece of clothing like
this make clothes out of money really a
dollar idea you guys take a little
picture and you know exchange numbers
whatever it is you're going to do right
secret that dude is a legend bro like
I've been watching him since like the
first season of American Idol it was
awesome that I finally got to do it
which just I guess goes to show guys you
know this I was a kid in Ohio never in
my life thought I'd be talking to Ryan
Seacrest and it happens someone be a
little inspirational here if you have
dreams and I say this all the time does
not matter where you live or where you
come from if you work hard and you're
not afraid to be different and be a
maverick I am sure you can accomplish
those dreams guys I believe in you and
always nice to meet low gangsters um I
know but I'm wondering Emily was very
quiet which like again May it makes me
think am I just like is it the stache
maybe like do I just create people out
or like am I too 1503 everybody I don't
know but I'm gonna figure this out I'm
gonna keep the mustache your friends our
friend please shave the mustache what to
reply no yeah we're by right now whoa
the mustache stays Brendan new messages
yo Sears being a [ __ ] this morning all
right guys let's go to the cool bus cuz
as you guys know we have been having a
very unfortunate poop problem not
personally but somebody has been pooping
outside of the cool bus like do you see
the row of poops they're like because
like I said this man is over it but stay
on me bro don't put a booth disgusting
and as you know we set up a camera last
night it's up there however I try to
catch this [ __ ] person poopy butt
since the bus shut off the Wi-Fi shut
off
and it didn't work guys we didn't we
lost the funds we don't have anything
well it turns out that was a problem
no no they unplugged it someone
unplugged it we failed on so many levels
low gang like I thought for sure I was
just gonna find the booper it's
unplugged my thing they got no Wi-Fi
who's to say this won't happen again
right the plea for the unplugging both
both from poop
unclogging it's a [ __ ] disaster so
this is the fence we climbed over
yesterday but frickin lock is open so
someone who works here must have
unlocked it unplugged our thing but I
bet they do that in the morning so
hypothetically we could be streaming if
we got a hot spot all night might be the
move bro huh cuz though even if we do
get Wi-Fi and then we plug it in
someone's gonna unplug it which the
camera won't work we need a surveillance
camera that doesn't need Wi-Fi that just
records and doesn't need to be plugged
in can you make that happen
Lydia's enthusiasm is contagious
what just like that wait like have you
ever had someone like poop outside your
bus and if so which one of these would
you use these are wireless yep
oh my god it could be my big day sees
every single boob that's coming I'll
take five so right now look Lydia's got
all the camera equipment lady you don't
want wait Lydia just turn around Oh
oh wow okay sassy now all we need is a
mobile hotspot we should be good to go
oh yeah the deed is done
mobile hotspot Wi-Fi patch exactly is
all coming together bro like look at all
this I feel like a spy rabbie Logan your
your Wi-Fi box still needs to charge
yeah uh so I got a movie a portable
charger to plug this and charge it
overnight 100 hours of charge not a
brandy Mophie you owe me money Jesus
mother of god bro I hope this is worth
it bro like at this point I didn't want
him to poop outside my bus I need him to
please sir man poop outside my bus again
bro I can't believe you're asking
somebody to do that I know I know guys
are you doing it's me Logan here my cool
bus yeah not so good news guys run
everything through the bus solar panels
cameras everything we sent Lydia to the
store because we realized that these
right here this is ridiculous connect to
this thing right here and this is an
Ethernet cable we have to get it dongle
to connected this right here and then
plug it in the mobile hotspot which I
don't even know this machine works
ok so we have this right good news but
Brendan it's gotta be plugged in
Wireless which brings us back to the
problem of having to hop and plug it
legit card why is it so hard okay so
here's what's gonna happen low gang has
to be plugged in there past it I'm gonna
put this on the roof assuming that this
my fight won't die overnight that's
where the mochi comes in broke [ __ ]
skin confusing technology technology
2017 you've done it again you son of a
[ __ ] back to this again bro is to look
you guys saw this morning this was
unlocked now it's locked which I'm
assuming means this place is probably
gonna be safe overnight wish me luck
that might be the guy you think that's a
pooper
oh I'm saying that who knows it could be
anyone it could be you you could be the
poop I'm not the pooper
bro you promised you know me my poops
you know my poops
no you
I'm so sorry if you guys aren't in the
technological just which I understand
I'm sorry I'm dragging you into it but
here's what's going down we got two
different types of cameras as you know
so right now as of now using the hot
spot this one right here that we set up
last night is working this is a live
feed and we'll be able to see this
overnight
it's just [ __ ] this guys getting
me worked up bro just this morning warm
he wants to break me down man Julie what
is happening cuz I'm already messed up
my who else Rock a mustache this stupid
gotta be I bet you swear to God if I
gotta check my live feed later today and
there's like a long-haired hippie uber
next my bus bro I'm saying oh man okay
this is the final setup if you look to
your left to the top of the bus over
here got camera numero uno connected to
the extension cord connected some more
plugs connected to the mobile hotspot
that is charging by the way connected to
camera number two bangs so yo let's see
if this puppy works
yo holy sorry for swearing so much but
it's working literally I'm I open it up
to start the vlog from here from home
saying it's working and the guy just
walked by and a guy just walked by bro
oh my God look you can rewind it you
could look look right there bro you can
hear them and see them coolest thing
ever I'm so happy this word we're not
just gonna catch poopers bro we're gonna
catch lo gangsters gangsters yeah coming
for you with that said lo gang that is
the vlog it was a fun day I feel like
and you guys probably know this too when
i have stuff to do and i don't have to
just like make stuff up for the vlog
like that's when i thrive that's when i
have energy
or maybe it's just a mustache i don't
know but if you're not part of the low
game make sure to subscribe turn the
strongest family on youtube check out
the help me help you video out of my
hair video if you haven't yet bobble I
gotta for me we are almost at 1 million
likes also the videos trending number
one
on YouTube so let's go baby low gang for
life cop your maverick merch Logan Paul
cops last shop or linea description
don't be afraid to be different don't be
afraid to set up cameras to catch pooper
do your thing haters
[Music]