you should kiss me
[Applause]
[Music]
good morning little guy was Bob good you
like your eye feels good oh my god I
can't tell if it's cuz I'm wearing the
hottest softest merch in the game and it
looks freaking sexy by the way how you
feeling bro I'm a little bit should we
tell them what we've been doing for all
is bad yo hey guys it's me voiceover
Logan so you may have noticed an audio
is starting to go bad yeah yeah well it
gets much worse trust me but anyways I'm
just gonna narrate what's happening here
so this is me laying next to Kong
telling you guys that I'm gonna be
streaming live on Twitch for the first
time ever this Sunday at 2:00 p.m.
Pacific Standard Time that is it's gonna
be for a candlelit guys my handle is
Logan Paul was taking cousin Paul take
so yeah add me on Twitch at Logan Paul
was taking guys this Sunday 2 p.m. PST
you do not want to miss my first live
stream on Twitch I'm gonna be streaming
for tonight right rolling heads on for
Nate I may add okay anyways ladies and
gentlemen we were just getting started
now here's what happened this morning
we're supposed to be a boxing chain
right now I get in my desk putting on
these overalls I like that what are
those apparently this is what was
happening he was told that if I put the
chute on I'm gonna get doughnuts I don't
think so I think he meant to say maybe
put the suit on he's gonna get attacked
by a dog weird cuz that thought I was
here to box oh no honey look you guys do
you think I'm actually gonna train to
train now we're back in the real world
yeah yo what's good today well what's
good today
oh isn't gonna be a thing called I can't
because I'm angry right but he's looking
at me so cute anyways now thrown back
into the real world and good stuff
there's some bad stuff that's happening
one guys I feed my babies later when the
cameras are off my fornicate now yeah
what was that huh fornicate it's when
you build forts in fort night well here
let me bring you around the back because
look I got custom license plates guys
can't read don't worry
says I'm Yeti because Yeti was taken the
Yeti was taken high yet he was taken but
I'm Yeti so Yeti was taken yeah that's
looking good and then okay bad news
haven't quite unpacked yet from the
Yosemite trip which by the way
yesterday's vlog you guys saw Andy and I
almost drowned in a river trying to
kayak
fortunately my fault all my fault
probably shouldn't have done that but
hey content oh yeah
whole reason we went to Yosemite in the
first place because guys I'm 23 now
quick the cool bus is a mess I need your
help
Lydia well you're about to see well like
what you're about to smell all scents
are gonna be reached this is the seventh
sacred it's one of the seven sacred
ascends and a seven a second sense when
there's eight people urinating inside of
a bus for three days in a row and you
don't properly flush it out therein lies
the problem
how you doing by the way okay here we go
yeah well look look you don't have to
clean this up I'm just showing you this
is what we are dealing with it is gonna
be a team effort well I mean we're all
gonna do it
that was my grandmother's sacred size
like a pedo media quick tomato sauce on
my
[Music]
Slippery in session just a minor tip I
mean I like Doritos hey hey there hey
there here's hey hey there here's us
watching the footage to see if the audio
work something must have happened with
that microphone there okay now what
point does it break through this sucks
bro this is like half the vlog No hello
let's try it
did you guys hear it I guess I'll never
know no what if we do like the crappy
like voiceover you see like old Chinese
movies oh yeah we will try to match our
mouths away to switch it half positivity
hey easy Christmas card or voiceover
session the latter oh my god we got it
we gotta go from like ground zero
cuz the next scene is a four-wheeler
scene here I'll make the sound effect
I feel you're never gonna work hey what
are you doing she's incredible the
growth job of Management
hey Jeff Jeff Logan you can't be riding
your ATV around the yard you're gonna
ruin your grass login poet Jeff you must
have thought I was responsible right sir
I was thinking bro we could put a
tracker on the entire yard do Logan but
you have neighbors Logan Jeff what are
you crazy imagine the litany slugging
this is a horrible idea
Spenser I have an idea who says the
track has to be outside oh so you're
gonna make a track inside your house
that's crazy
okay maybe cut the Australian good call
I'm not going that way on the inside oh
[Applause]
don't worry Evan I got this down like my
Bolognese whoa you see that manager Jeff
skidmark street cred Logan I mean yeah
we could we get a scrape up the floors
or we could just sell some more merch so
many voices broke and they were the best
part about it he's literally outside oh
yeah it's got back from the gym these
pecs oh yeah I used to see them in the
camera oh yo what's up you see that sick
dark abyss oh yeah I totally got my high
school diploma I uh I went d1 one year I
got kicked off the team because my palm
me but it's alive
I just came a youtuber now and I just
think oh yeah it's really good you know
the merch is good I got this house I
wore I just I feel like yeah I'm getting
a rose like everything you've ever
wanted to say to me
alright I got this we got to get this
bike downstairs just give me a first aid
kit all you did was just walking there
with steps no oh look Logan your bike
leaked more Gatorade
oh let's taste test it again definitely
Gatorade yeah a quick dodges catching on
fire oh my gosh this marriage is gonna
blow it all up
I'm Evan I love the way you look when
you're topless Wow if you just put your
nipples all in and around my mouth I
love you I'm not I hate you don't even
be in this room bro I haven't even shown
it on the vlog yet a secret like this is
the worst fog ever alright guys that is
the vlog you're gonna hopefully fix our
microphones all right guys thank you for
watching if you are not a part of the
low gang make sure to subscribe join the
strongest family on YouTube we're doing
voiceover both OH
they also guys if you have not yet cop
you're mad former jihadists softest
merch from the game link in description
or Logan Paul calm slash shop this fire
anyways guys you know I love you okay I
will see you tomorrow
[Music]
so well he doesn't my voice over anyways
night