all right it is insane I'm not gonna
hate it ah good morning little gang okay
I said hey what's your deal bro you good
bro we need to give you the you good bro
survey think I do man here we go you
good bro now I got something calm down
here you good bro guys so while he feels
that I am actually about the head to set
for yet another day of valley girl
there's a big day for Mickey it's like
yo are you oh he finished it well you
good bro oh you sneaky son of a [ __ ]
ah my new roommate oh this is weird bro
I didn't know you were naked
guys he wasn't making I maverick okay
talk to you later bye Hollywood I'll see
you later
Mickey's coming back watch out can she
come back
Mickey's back bro yeah yeah yeah as you
know in recovering sorta from a little
sickness I took a lot of pills today but
look yo hello thank you need me on set
boy nobody got time to be sick your boys
gonna push through in this outfit little
like cotton candy ice cream type out
fish sucks because this long-sleeve
Brown if you look outside it's hot
oh yeah bro as I step outside my first
daughter yeah yeah yeah good morning bro
touch my knuckles it's not awkward bro
I'm gonna still do it oh you stole it up
to the CEO we about to shoot the first
scene and by that I mean block the first
scene up point to a park or my car guys
I'm telling you this is Nikki's day like
when you guys see the movie you'll
understand but I gotta go I'm gonna go
get today we were hurt it was great
we're making the movies all talk about
last can't do it bro can do it bro I
came back in the trailer I made eye
contact me
[Music]
[Applause]
if you want to talk to her about it
you're welcome to but she liked it I
would get to I'm kind of pretty hot it
couldn't be so like it's going to be
destroyed and probably 50 MIT unless I
have someone like Fanning hit that level
after we're broke admit your pips
forgive me I'm just going to got some
now on the vlog in the bottom left
corner of the frame okay be with me this
time of me oh my god already getting hot
I'm sorry I'm going to ruin the sound
air conditionings going on at all I will
say this shirt is dope
hey I'm Mickey B I might be a pimp see I
might be a drug dealer I don't know
point isn't the only problem is that
it's hot yo so we're here on location
this man is going to stay here and be
the air conditioning vent
bro you're my hero okay domi dun dun dun
dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun
dun oh my god Oh peace money
yo wait what hold on are you vlogging
for my vlog camera are you a vlog or bro
yo notice how I'm just like posted up
inside advance cuz I'm not stepping
outside this here's a little gangster
right there I think that's a lucky I
don't know I know the body language look
I think that's her I'm vlogging you she
knows I'm vlogging her so she's hiding
the mom is a low gangster - I can tell
ya ya oughta do that to the dab ya lo
gang his family I'm gonna risk my
well-being and get hot to go say what's
up hi how are you hi how long have you
been here it's hot no two hours an hour
oh my gosh are you okay
okay I'm not I'm Mickey right now I was
a Mickey's back yeah hey guys it's me
Logan okay so the audio in this bathroom
was way too echoey and you literally
couldn't hear anything but here's what
tap after freaking out a little bit I
introduced my friend Brendan he's behind
the camera there but yo I got more than
one friend I got a second friend too and
his name is dwarf mama and the last and
final friend we got my girl annular they
came to visit me on set yogurt
kinda hard let notice I think I was
really truthful vlogging on set itself
absolute you have seen right now so I'm
gonna let these guys take over I hope
it's not please don't block up to me
yeah I just like can't be working on it
is I'm out look what's it so Logan is on
set today and clearly we were like I
mean let's just long for you right it
would be better anyway we were better
anyway once listed in English all the
time great okay guys that was probably
terrible being a vlogger as hard a lie
you should just stick to being pretty
you're doing good just stay like that
great also guys if you couldn't tell the
boys came to visit me on set listen to
the song a little pretty good bill no I
like this rendition bro hey mickey hey
hey oh this is good I wonder how long
ago four years later good guys whoa whoa
okay five hours later taking that
station Oh whoo oh I wish I had talent
like this boys mother of God
[Music]
hey can you two do the thing no you
could do without or we could do without
or we can do without where you at ladies
yeah oh whoa oh this speed is unreal the
coordination is off but this speed is
unreal oh I'm back on set nice to meet
fine I'll do it I got I got a movie to
show
oh don't is 19th birthday yeah happy
birthday
Zack you're 17 17 I don't think he is
anyway score Devon what mom wait there's
something we'll have to tell you you're
Gregory I knew ed today today today had
rehearsal today and their songs are not
playing I'm free I'm free I gotta go I
gotta go shoot a movie I'll see you
later
yes I want to eat okay guys back up
Sebastian Bella girl and we are now
obviously inside the school it's only
getting hotter I swear to god guys as
the day goes on to get more and more
days we cool it up and just a days the
cool I'm going to make an abort as well
seconds later guys nothing has changed
it's night time but it's still really
hot woody bro you crazy you brought what
are you crazy
everyone as you can see like this man is
losing their mind guys you might have
one more scene to shoot this one takes
place in a locker room and I'm not gonna
like is even hotter in here bro
you've got this broken come on baby TPP
will see you guys in a second yeah dude
okay guys we were a super long dance
that it's like 11:30 p.m. right now lets
me out like a 1340 14-hour days but I'm
feeling good bro it's time to get spicy
I got something plans you guys know I
gotta spice it up energetic so yo you
ready to fight he'll go what are you
ready to fight aliens you piss you off
if he makes you angry right
oh yeah bro get another Gator be shot
blue stop stop I would say I got I got
something Brendon from me bro cousin
good good brother chicken except we are
not fighting huh yeah y'all hiding no
they look Simon to do this I can't make
this really fabulous are they doing
ironing process outcomes Oh
officers love halo comes it up hey hey
okay guys it's Friday night it's fight
night here enough I don't know we have a
name for our place but in here we got a
makeshift ring right here we put
cushions out of the edge so they can't
escape we got an audience right here and
talk stop biting me bro yeah so he's
getting widely for the fight okay
introducing your competitors standing in
the green corners standing at 4 foot 11
foot tall we have a little wood wall I'd
say in the blue corner we have every
night you rode hailing from Maryland a
college dropout cuz this douchebag
blogger friend convinced him to do it
and pursue Internet and today this has
got involved too much of Milo it's time
to fight three two one
how does your Christmas
look like you're whispering which is I
didn't kill anyways guys that's the blog
I hope your joy gets your maverick merge
your low game works whatever you want to
call it link is in the description or
you type in logan paul comm flesh up i
really give make sure your merge and do
not subscribe make sure you subscribe
because we're lit I will see y'all
tomorrow take it easy take it easy Sam
[Music]
my my