hey Jay I made one phone call I got the
same house as you same cars too it's
really not that hard
oh hey by the way welcome to the top
little brother feels good huh
but let's not forget how you got here
[Music]
I'm your new puppy call you come let's
talk about your garbage that you call a
song it should be every other day just
some strong advice I made you famous
once it's the bus that happened twice
yeah you want Disney but who helped you
read all your lines me don't forget or
you were my shadow on bus now you've got
a few subscribers and you think that
you're the [ __ ] I'll admit you got money
you got bars you got [ __ ] but you're a
dick
you ain't thankful for your fans it's
kind of funny do your investors know
team 10 ain't making any money see it
starts with an Italian but it's hard
when you got none I think you kind of
salty cuz I'm the favorite son I'm a
maverick you're a sidekick yeah I
brought you to a light if there's one
thing you should know the firemen throw
is looking at your face you don't know
when the music low trying to sense an
actor classes do with nothing now you
tried to rap come on
catch the full you can't know the
kimchi's guys I mean that's how you grow
but you still can't sell out any shows
no you still can't find some matching
clothes you're just killing the vibe you
ain't doing it right trying to play ball
with the does you don't know what you're
done you just ruin your life here you
killing the vibe in you ain't doing it
right trying to type out with the dogs
you don't know what you've done you just
ruin your life after all we came from
the same
biologically you know that makes us
brothers so much negativity it really
makes me want to like feel like you just
need a maverick shirt in description you
in Sami jakey
it really hurts sometimes I wish my real
brother was dirt but now I gotta go put
you in the dirt go away what hold up
hold up bought the music stop
there is a second verse but I'm not
gonna release it Jake owned up to his
mistakes this morning and he apologized
to me
us the low gang and why don't we so
sorry low gang and sorry Logan again and
I also uh apologize to the wide don't we
boys
I took Jake's lyrics very personally
like they upset me they really did and I
don't I don't like I don't get upset
often but as someone who is a the bigger
brother as someone who wants to be a
role model I'm going to step down before
the damage is irreversible I love my
brother Jake I love you bro I am so
happy for your successes but it is
taking every fiber in my body to not
release the second verse but it is the
right thing to do I do everything that I
do for the fans and it means so much to
me when I see you guys wearing my merch
when you greet me in the streets and the
fact that you guys give me the most
precious commodity that humans have
which is your time it means the world to
me guys and with great influence comes
great responsibility and I want to be a
role model for the world solo gang ah
we're getting deep bro this is weird but
thank you guys for giving me your time
day in and day out
I am honored to have you in my life and
Logan Paul for president 2032 it lets go
I want to address he has way more
followers than me when you add
everything up together and so I thought
people would think it was a joke like by
me saying like I have more subscribers
than him like that's literally the only
platform I think I have more followers
on
[Music]
the