raise your hand if i've been inside you
today
i hate you so much
i'm laying in bed this morning and i
hear like shuffling so i look at my door
and there's someone's like throwing
something under my door
there's 52 cars all of them say paul on
the back but when i open the door
there's no one there i'm like who
did this so i go to the security footage
i check the camera and it's my boxing
coach milton i see him running down the
stairs and like hiding behind a wall
must have been some sort of practical
joke it was kind of funny but here's
where he slipped up now we can literally
frame him for anything
make my heart just like so sad i'm gonna
have to be in a different room
for a sec yeah buddy
so this morning um i noticed my rolex
was missing
let me watch yeah i had set it on the
chair outside of my room
so i went back and i looked at the video
footage
and i saw you i have reason to believe
that you may have
taken my rolex well i would never do
that that's the first thing
if you look you see i was throwing the
pole cards
what you know what the cards you had
your name on it
yeah but i have footage of you like my
rolex is missing yeah
and this footage of you running and
hiding
it's not funny but what i'm saying it's
not it's not fun i don't know
60 000 rolex i don't know where it is
you just need to play your cards
what playing cards i was putting the
playing cards into your door
i love you milton
special delivery for chase hero oh my
god what's up
i wanted to give it to someone who's in
the mapper club i figured why not give
it to the inventor of the maverick club
chase here ladies and gentlemen
oh cheers you're an amazing human being
this is this is on you straight up been
in the game 13 years i don't think i've
ever seen in a non
anonymous anonym that that thing like
this guy oh come on
chase take my horse you poke your finger
you're gonna do that too with the other
thing it's a blood test so you're gonna
know when if you have had coronavirus
why does chase have coronavirus
because i'm smart man i'm like an end of
the world guy protected
you go all the way in poking hard like
[ __ ] you
all the way in like a psychopath that
hurt
that was a pretty good sample i'm not
gonna lie i want the c c doesn't stand
for coronavirus
no wait that means we're good right
mom girlfriend close your eyes raise
your hand
if you love me
raise your hand if you've seen me naked
raise your hand if you like what you saw
what the [ __ ] that's backwards okay that
was weird raise your hand if you've done
drugs
mom what the [ __ ] raise your hand you'd
smoke a joint with me for the maver club
yeah well guys sign up for the mavic pro
you can see my mom get high as [ __ ]
raise your hand if you let me have a
threesome pam don't put your hand up
raise your hand if i've been inside you
you really did that logan didn't you
today i hate you so much
i just want to see how connected we are
let's like kick the ball back and forth
see how many times we can keep it up
okay this is proof that you love me more
than jake ready one
two three uh try to get a little more
towards me
one do it again what was that
please mom one jesus i was good mom you
hate me i'm starting to
take the ball and kick it like this oh
um i feel so bad what did you do
your so my friends are making fun of me
because i haven't actually worked out in
two months why do you look so skinny
though i'm like the skinniest i've ever
been because i lost all my muscle
literally it's all gone so mac and i
you've gotten a little spat on impulsive
because it's not like i'm out of shape
no you are you guys look out of shape
five minutes 30 second mile yeah
shake my hand hundred dollars i could do
it we're going right after this podcast
we're gonna see if i can run a mile in a
minute or sorry that's pretty fast
five minutes and 30 seconds meaning i'm
running at an 11 mile an hour pace you
have to do
one minute and 22 second laps that's the
time yeah
oh you're ready yes i think get set
go go that's a good pace already that's
a good stride
you're tasting good you're fast 105.
there's zero chance i'm telling you
right now there's no way somebody's
winning somebody's lose
i think he's struggling you're probably
no this is where it is over
he's barely at the pace are you cramping
yeah breathe
breathe yo you can get this last lap you
can get it sprint it
oh he's cramping come on buddy go
go girls have cramps once a month you
think this is what they do
if you really sent it you might be able
to get this all right
look at the times hey man where's my
money 5 30.
i knew it winner i lost me
make me like i think they should take it
as a lesson like
sometimes you might think you're an
athlete but you're not like boxing
running yeah yeah you make a good point
take me you don't
have to be carried thanks boys hi
youtube thanks for watching
oh yeah i got your hair it's okay