good morning gang what's poppin okay
quite honestly going down going down
that sometimes you don't like to see for
example this broken window oh oh you
don't know let me show you oh yeah
selfie selfie vlog it's all Logan Paul
today bro I'll explain why in a second
it has to do with this merch but yeah
okay so you know how we got this
basketball hoop installed in the house
[Laughter]
you know what they say though Evan you
break one glass yeah baby I'm ready to
mom all right
if you ever plan on robbing my house
now's the time anyways guys why my
selfie blogging and also why do I look
so gosh dang sexy look alive you look
good too though it's that new skin out
of a job oh yeah yeah you are
yeah yeah you're fired thank you for
your work here at the Maverick house
have a nice life it's cuz you know it's
time for Monday today we are doing as
you guys know it 20 to 70 percent off
sale on all Maverick my Logan Paul gear
the link for that is in the description
but we just dropped like a line of the
original hoodie but like this is like a
cutoff long-sleeve there's obviously the
original favorite hoodie that was in the
help me help you music video
I hear you maverick I'm comments min a
minutes as we talk to maverick what's
poppin how are you I know I know it's
it's like oh it's a bit you don't like
it what were you going don't be mad okay
I'm here today we're talking we're
having fun he likes the merch yeah just
like alterations of the favorite hoodie
line it's sick
do good problems okay don't it's the
last days of these deals so make sure
you hit up the site slash I know I'm
doing it yeah been having a severe acne
problem recently I think it's cuz I grew
out the beard you think it like holds
oils on my face either way it's [ __ ]
good news is it could get worse here's a
picture of me in high school
uh yeah hate to see it but yes since I
got ugly again if I go out or do
something in public I'm not gonna my
mom's gonna say it I sometimes put
makeup on my face now you see this road
where's the cameraman wait Spencer you
know what a Negro right now I need that
the James Charles palette just stress
not easy being more than Paul are you
sure about the beard bro nice thing I
should keep the beat or not I'll put it
I'm gonna put a poll on the screen that
was your opportunity to answer
I am so deep into this makeup game I got
one of these like I'm sure girls like
you know what these are these little
puff things that help like spread the
makeup if you're a dude like I'm just
gonna show you
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
oh god awful bogging to go right now
hi it's me dwarf mama excited about this
Chargers game tonight oh no come back
Evan I miss you what did you tell them
that we're already late
[Music]
I parked so far away from the stadium
Evans about to run a 5k to get there I
am so sorry
you're sure it says it all though this
merch is so hot what does it mean when
you take the hottest merch off and you
have the hottest merch under it alright
if you make this you'll find true love
sports I love sports because of the
athlete I love sports because of
Splendor I like sports because
excitement I like sports because
friendship hey man I'm friends yeah go
yeah go team how much fun is that Mike
sports
hey wrong team buddy now I don't think
they're playing today how does it color
blind what what's that kid doing I see
you kid let that out kid that's my thing
and also is that Mario Lopez no that's
that dog hey I'm gonna keep it real with
you guys that so I play football high
school and then just to put it quite
simply I'm being humble about this I
wish there was to be a bum knees you
would have gone through I peaked in high
school it's always that crazy person at
the football games and I think I've
spotted in yeah
yeah definitely definitely found him
sports sports sports
[Applause]
hold on get in the car yeah all right
okay all that happiness was pissing me
off
I'm too serious guy it felt really
refreshing to do handheld vlog today
took me back to the old days I hope you
guys enjoyed it as well for my original
little gangsters out there I will say we
have been working literally on so many
projects Evan and I shot an entire show
called best friends shot a documentary
about the Flat Earth with like a full-on
movie we're doing the impulsive podcast
as you guys know Monday Wednesday and
Friday I'm gonna put the channel name
for that in the description it's poppin
guys it's so much fun it's so fun I wish
I knew who it was we don't invite her to
canta have animated storytime series
coming very soon the point is I'm very
busy and that's why the constant output
has been low however what you need to
remember and this is it's always gonna
be facts right is that the lokay just
tons of stuff tons of stuff that keeps
me busy we are we're trying to elevate
the type of content that we make cuz
it's dope being a youtuber and some
youtubers do this better than others but
they grow with the platform and with
their audience it's obviously important
to innovate and stay up-to-date with the
trends and not only innovate but almost
sometimes be the pioneer as to what type
of content is coming for the future of
the platform big boy words real big boy
words big boy talk but yeah I just
wanted to close out and say I love you
guys thank you for sticking with me and
as you know it's Cyber Monday and we are
doing a 20 to 70 percent off sale on all
maverick by Logan Paul gear the link for
that is in the description Logan Paul a
comm slash shop also free shipping on
orders of $100 or more and as you know
gonna be flying out to people come and
hang out with us on the set of impulsive
and as always if you guys are not part
of the low gang gang gang skirt make
sure to subscribe see you next time
[Music]
what why is the cover for the broken
wind on the other side of the broken
window that window broke - that's not
possible
it did no it did not
[Music]