[Music]
let me just start off by saying I think
my brother's an idiot but he is my
brother's gonna have his back and you
can pay this month's rent
we know you call in your lawyers yeah
that's money well spent
cuz yeah my brother messed up but he
still got his Disney contract see me in
person I guarantee you won't make eye
contact don't the best
[Music]
but we just having some fun
and it was like 30 and their names
really worthy to roll the tongue cry
never stops only two ways to make it to
the top one be at least gain your faith
from the great one soon be America leads
the pack like the polio I choose to you
can ride on my Caravan plenty of room
and everyone got a life span
I'll Logan this is like hypocritical
because I just made a video about not
hating on people yeah I know I saw the
video yeah oh yeah I can I'm bored bro
roast videos are fine no they're not
[Music]
you'll be making memes bus stop Logan
the second first could never come out
but bro don't you think we should
address that one thing that everyone's
like wondering about no I'm not talking
about that anymore bro but like I'm just
saying oh there's two sides to every
story and it's not gonna go anywhere
well it is true so like you don't know
who is telling the truth and who's lying
essentially hey guys make sure to LIKE
and subscribe we're literally at 6 a.m.
and we're making this music video I'm
gonna go to sleep
get your maverick merch link in the
description I love you Logan for life
booze