so I was wondering how long would be
until you actually realize that you
weren't paying attention with you so I
[Music]
know like the mic maja I knew is too
good to be true Matt Ohio was too nice
yesterday it said oh and now it's
raining the day of the charity softball
of it how are we supposed to do charity
or softball in the rain like why did we
fly to Ohio this is their hangout in the
house and drink and party yeah go ahead
man was going hard Logan I can't stop
drinking I'm like one please please stop
now
[Music]
Oh tiny room there's been shuffles in
the back row same team what are we not
on the new ball Rob yo I look good bro
I'm gonna hit a home run
I'm manifesting it how many naps can we
do right now real quick
we did that for real this is a joke we
shoot for dick fallen cover right now
it's really hard to build a business the
cold Kerrigan is a lot to do a fox news
[Music]
I spent the whole morning giving notes
on the JK Logan video our Channel
I took it and it's public now you know
why cuz I did it cuz I'm a spin
meanwhile what look at you bro water
bottle hanging out the side of your
mouth hello my brother shot getting a
beer oh wait can you wait no no right
time because of the softball game you're
a disaster
Oh yo at least take this place out to
dinner before you switch everything
[Music]
[Applause]
and all he was worth signature I'm
literally just scribbling on this hat I
tried the markers dead camera so they're
gonna get kicked off a guy's you're
gonna give yourself incredible otters he
goes I remember you from third grade you
were my teacher right mr. lone and she's
like I'm very fuzzy
nothing like a little american him to
get you going
[Music]
[Applause]
things I love include sports I love my
sports
you're a ball
[Music]
go charities up all sports events
oh my big big
he's a fish get off each other but the
ball ah you tried to bunt the ball
you're a cheater
oh my cheater my TV you came to a
charity softball game and your hammer it
doesn't get like you're at rock-bottom
guy you're alcohol you're an alcoholic
come here come here anyway I'm just I'm
really not I know you gotta calm down
I don't want to be that guy that's
telling you this we hear that drunk guy
on like 10% 10% you're hammering bro
you need to take a deep breath go get
some water okay go back to your side bro
and just suck on some water and or a
suck some ass because we're gonna beat
you in this game
he is plastered you're plastered you're
you are plasma I'm not plastered bro you
I told you you're the you're the
alcoholic coach that's you and here's
the issue you're like 12 years old it's
only gonna get worse no please team
center-cut rehab Jake goes to rehab
hey bro bro you're just here the thing
is they focus well on what son
stay focused easy with the proximity son
I will get all up in your purse easy
with the proximity yo you've got some
mega balls to come in my charity
baseball event hammer hit my face Mike
what would you Mike stop
[Applause]
[Music]
what I do my brothers that degenerate
what's new
[Applause]
this is not which boss well I can't
believe it
we've lost it's over for me
[Music]
[Applause]
happy Father's Day
hey why do you have oh no there's more
this opens up to a full shower in less
than 30 seconds little shower pan you
just stand on the toilet what's going on
here Greg this is a midlife crisis if I
have a friend that wants to join me with
the friend be a girl in less than 30
seconds girl in here hook up with her
can you drive us around in the Ford
Raptor yeah whatever you want to do
Merry Christmas dad what yeah you got
the key boy oh you're not driving that
why are you in this reclaimed motor home
hey I have a better question just and
I'm just I'm just going off on a whim
good would you still have that truck no
I don't want me this and my BMW
motorcycle on all the trips that go with
it
I told you this but when I was telling
you well you were drunk no in you
weren't and you weren't paying attention
so I was wondering how long would be
until you actually realize that you
weren't paying attention with photocell
you you sold the pickup truck but for me
how did you know that I didn't know for
sure I kind of can I do that David Ober
can get my dad a truck by the way with
my own money he was a sponsor and you
just sold it you're just in sold it
I sold for something
that you gave me that is so much better
you say that a bike in your driveway
dude i you love that that's how you
bought that bike
yeah and I'm so happy I can't stand it
you gave me a gift that is so bigger
this is really bad I love that boy you
know what my turning point was with the
truck
I was trying to cry my chair where is
the pickup truck you gave it back to the
dealer
how many dollars 60 K yeah I was
wondering how he was financing all dish
why didn't i connect the dots
how can you just buy a sprinter van
thing bro trips across the country you
bought him this is how you don't give
people gifts bro because they will turn
around and sell them behind your back
and then use your money to buy things
that they actually want hey I never came
from your balls
here's the thing room is yes like you
got first yeah but you got your clip
wait so my dad broke my heart oh you
shouldn't feel broke you're giving me
Adventures of a lifetime
guess where I'm going out 2,500 mile
Continental Divide ride on your bike
that you bought me that you paid you
bout to tell me this on Father's Day
yeah I didn't tell you Jake brought it
up that little fuss oh my god I don't
know how to feel right now hey do you
ever dad do you love him
must be nice
[Music]
it's like my heart's been ripped out of
my body
[Applause]
[Music]
got his mom's car oh my god