you as an [ __ ] I'm gonna kill someone
it's going down as usual here i'm logan
paul vlog channels hot road the channel
hop legit guys which off the music
videos will jump in fire vlogs we're
ending in starting drama it's beautiful
it's all amazing this is my dog calling
if you guys do not know also if you do
not know that means you're not
subscribed which means you should
subscribe yeah like it subscribe like he
said are you excited for what's
happening today yeah I know you are it's
a big vlog today as you guys know and it
probably seen my brother and I released
it what my brother and I released to to
my brother and I released two music
videos one for his channel one from my
channel is this called I love you bro
and it's like sentimental and deep and
it talks about loving each other again
and how would you describe mine Brendan
who though like go answer the question
that I'm gonna answer the question that
we go
yours your video kind of attacks YouTube
again I start the pot I make waves it's
what I do anyway you love calm everyone
loves calm he's the young dog you know
usual tears actually is actually crying
normally she beats people's ass like she
cuts is making this is the first time I
haven't seen you cussing
all that it's cute right - yeah you
don't make me cry like that yeah I do
what oh you did get certified right what
do you got them certified tell me what
you got song certified for yours like
your service service dog identification
Kong the savage handler Logan Paul okay
you can take him everywhere now wait
like I'm please yeah trained yeah
automobile yeah yeah what are you doing
to my dog you cannot take it home known
five for Kong you know let's go let's go
holy shells coming out oh my god
Wolverine over here why don't you fight
him for what has come done to this watch
that's the video it's about know why
watch it we are currently waiting on one
more special guest oh you know it you
saw the thumbnail it's my brother we're
waiting on Jake to get here this will be
the first time that Jake and I have
spoken in front of the eyes of the
internet people are confused about all
the beef and drama and all that just
don't like why don't we have Danielle
here to mediate a therapy session
between us I'm not trying to get cached
outside but I thought it would be fun
look I am gonna need your attention you
have a very important job today
whoa oh
I the first time I want to see the
camera I understand why it's like this
intense because we literally shot a
whole music fit two music videos
yesterday together
[Music]
forget it
all right guys this here's what's going
down our blogging blogging can you just
stop down I just wanted to make Jan with
their last time we made a video give me
the face of spoons and [ __ ] this is the
worst thing I figured since Jake and I
were beefing and stuff and we may or may
not have settled in the music video this
will be the first time that the internet
sees us together interacting for the
first time we had two other questions
about all the drama all the books diss
tracks that are going out all the none
that fall seven solves falses losses
because there have been lies in all of
this but I brought in the most qualified
person the most to help us do that you
want to introduce yourself me
this is [ __ ] I need full sidebar we are
not gonna have overlapping questions so
half of the questions will be on my
channel and half will be on my brother
Jason are you sure this is like a god
turkey gotcha this is a building process
Logan how long are you talking smack
[Applause]
[Music]
I like Jake I like my brother I love my
brother hello hello Jake I think they're
our times whoever get way too
competitive I think that's it bro yeah
like there was a spot where like a
literally for me was not even a
competition anymore and that's where I
think you like try it super hard like
yes all right pass what fast pass what
I'm about the patch screen subscribers
no no pass you you said catch up Jake
brawlers growing more than 80 K no 150
million monthly views a hundred and
fifty million
oh there is a tweet that went sort of
viral from a kid you went to high school
with rice can put it in his song like
they're trying to make you seem like a
bully bro that's you know you're not a
belief I know but you were smaller
that's I'm saying I'm just a little kid
with a dream but I was like you know
what you know what else I was in fifth
grade I was ignorant I was talking I had
braces here's how you guys are [ __ ]
I'm gonna kill someone let me finish the
question
whoa there's me boy swearing you're 14
that's you yeah you're 14 you should
watch honest except nobody knows you're
dizzy show what I'm saying is I was a
lot of things in fifth grade and all of
those things I'm not now so why
recommend right
yeah be closer as a person as a
and I also just want to say like where
is the validity in that accusation if I
said oh that Justin Bieber just shot
some 100% true and there's no proof of
hundred percent in Justin Bieber shoot
no I was not people liked the idea of
the drama the idea that it might be true
I know jig wasn't a bully because he
didn't go through puberty until last
year and I yeah yeah yeah exactly
yeah dude he was 501 and I beat his ass
people can paint any picture of you as
they want on the Internet but where's
the validity so yeah what the [ __ ] you
were started it well I made a comment
you're saying I'm your blood from your
ears well this ain't dumb Trump hair
must you bro I know I people that were
sitting around me let me teach these
viewers about demographic maybe stuff
you know they were like you know this
song sucks yo screw this cute remember
guys when baby came out with Justin
Bieber everyone was saying you the next
Justin Bieber but no but I'm not saying
is that's what I'm hearing Justin Bieber
did that down Suge there you ugly ass
mother I think I'm old we won't have it
broke the wind is a gallon do it again
are my Schwartz coming up to mine cuz
wow oh can i address that can I adjust
that hey look can you hand me the camera
you got a tattoo of pewdiepies dick on
your leg he said that well I think that
the reason why I got a tattoo of a few
devices no because the me looks like a
gun
but Beauty by that said his dick looks
like that the reason why is because I
wanted to pay homage to him Oh ask me
why why why his most viewed video in the
past like five months of me and I was
like I need a pan back
so much you goddamn folio sir not
fooling yourself then who will be how do
you feel about youtubers exposing and
dissing and using your name and title
why did you I had a line in my music
video put Jake's name in your title and
you can pay this month's rent it's true
everyone everyone's doing it so let me
respond and by saying yo I'll respect
you yo if you do get your views cuz
however you might want to do that yeah
but just now something's no no I just
respected so what I want to say as my
last word all right
like there has been a lot of drama hate
again
I'm busy it's crazy stuff going on in
the past week if you make a lot of
mistakes in life and and you're getting
hate it on in blah blah blah don't let
any of that get to you as long as you
grow as a person and you learn from it
so I want to say this past week has
really changed my life because I
realized that I hate the hate again you
don't know when that hay is gonna be
directed towards the wrong person and
they might end up damaging themselves
emotionally
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I love you my bro and I want you to
know that I'm so sorry but things that I
said I just want to be friends so let's
make amends and be bros million
[Music]
[Applause]
that was really therapeutic for me that
was done thanks for coming over my parks
go and and like I finally the Internet
can see us loving each other again well
I love you I love you too
I read this comic today yeah and I liked
it because obviously we just released
our music videos and mine is kind of
cocky ya know it's out there yeah yeah
but the comments said as long as the
Paul bros stick together when people try
to roast us like you they're not gonna
dent us who's not gonna invent us that's
not saying it doesn't even matter like
no I was playing along that's uh you
judged on a funny bro yeah I think this
is why I'm catching your subscribers I
[Music]
am really excited for tomorrow I think
I'm going on a date or like I'm at least
meeting the girl I think it's gonna it's
gonna be fresh so make sure you're
subscribed if you're not subscribed turn
your notification not if you don't have
monster you don't miss that and yeah I
hope today's vlog cleared up any
questions you may have had I will see
you guys tomorrow take it easy
[Music]
No however say if I put everything in my
blog that we I did I would go to jail
you would