in the house in your life your character
you're not wrong I look I have an idea
yeah you got duct tape oh stop exposing
my storyline
oh wait let me act like it's brand-new
what do we do today will be be know how
we made the duct-tape bridge you Logan
today we're gonna make clothes out of
duct tape and see if it works
look at me choke me god damn wall really
do it done
I swear bro it's physically impossible
broken law - I broke your [ __ ] that's a
fact but must be nice for you this is
hard
you had like fits perfectly into the
nook of my neck I know it comfortable
[Music]
yeah I'm not proud of my hair look it's
not great it's not great but look at him
you look like a homeless Adam Sandler
your head looks like a poorly crafted
sandcastle built by blind looks like
someone shaved King Kong's pubes and
glue them on your head it looks like a
work in progress - the progress last
time you got his haircut Lana Rose who's
graduating grade school your head looks
like a deflated kickball you know I did
a movie that was inspired by you what's
called the thinning really gets so just
now that serves in the house you look
really just crawled up on my lap
obviously we're trying to acclimate them
so they could be friends going pretty
well every time he licks him I get so
nervous never harmed anything I'm gonna
be honest he's kind of a [ __ ] ideally
we get to a spot where sir can ride on
broglie's back good boy good boy you
guys are both such good animals I get a
wife and kids where you could just have
a bird in a dog that's just as good
right right never do it today marks the
day we found a buyer for the Mercedes
couches
said no only by the couches let make you
eat your words mark I didn't say anyone
will buy the couch yeah
flashback like nobody's gonna want to
buy these as soon as you sit on him you
want to automatically drop yourself into
a pit of acid I feel like you're sitting
on a bed of nails this is uh one of my
biggest regrets in my life
$90,000 for both of these and I'm not
saying that - Beau's saying that so you
understand how dumb of an idea that was
he's been trying to sell them forever
and we found someone who is gonna buy it
for seventeen thousand five hundred
dollars seventy two thousand five
dollars honestly I'm just happy to get
rid of them call them my instinct says
he's good but I've dealt if they're fake
buying this couch just to be in a
YouTube video I'm gonna be [ __ ] pissed
[Music]
you know that can't do that is little
back story first in Miami and my
brother's fight he came up to me and so
he was a disowned reporter so I ended up
doing this interview with him and he's
not does no reporter then he showed up
at my house to tell me he was gonna go
to Dan Bilzerian Park you're going to
dance party tonight I actually kind of
got mad at him cuz he showed up at my
house I think they're charismatic I have
a general rule of thumb understood
lightly yeah I guess he did sneak into
Dan's party cuz I saw him there and now
months later he's at my house buying my
couches you're the most persistent in
person I've ever met in my life
you don't give a [ __ ] about the couch
I've heard these couches suck what's the
deal why don't you know they're not the
most comfortable couches
they came with [ __ ] cash in hand these
are my couches now I'm just gonna sleep
on these now here so it was fine until
you said here you can sleep on it but
you can't stay here I'm not gonna lie
when you show up to my house at one time
kind of piss me off
you know a lot of youtubers are really
clear about people not showing up to
their houses and it kind of rubbed me
the wrong way but but but this rub me
the right way you're rubbing me the
right way now
because he came with $70,000 remember my
one birthday wish that I actually wanted
was for someone to buy these coasters
and you did it now maybe you got a
problem contract maverick team listen I
came here to do whatever interviews I
need to do in order to become someone
who is collaborating with this team on a
regular basis hold the couch is up into
the freaking bed let us through talk for
five minutes bring me to the meeting on
sugar hi guys good two four six eight
ten thousand dollars I know these are
hard Financial Times for pretty much
everyone and Quarantine sucks and
honestly you guys could definitely use
this money more than me because I would
probably spend it on something dumb as
[ __ ] so I'm gonna give away $10,000
thousand dollars to ten people all you
have to do is retweet my last tweet and
I'm gonna randomly select ten people and
as far as ten winners who ordered a
maverick pandemic mask
congratulations to the winners their
names are right here you guys need to
get $1,000 a lot of names I'm not gonna
say them all but here's what they all
sound like if I said I'm at once so
congrats guys we will get through this
quarantine together
I know it's [ __ ] but I'm doing my best
to keep you entertained hopefully you
like these vlogs and also when you guys
give these videos thumbs up and you guys
interact in the comments trust me that
does not go unnoticed love the feedback
love the positivity everything's great
with that said I was you guys on Monday
go to Twitter retweet my tweet and go
get yourself some Monday
know my bird I don't know if he makes
like nest or not but you could always
use your hair
[Music]