josie how you doing not good dog don't
touch me
wait but i'm holding your boobs for you
hey everybody hope your quarantine's
going super great but also awesome i've
been forced to do some stuff
that i'm just not proud of some of which
you'll see in this vlog today but before
we get started these limited edition
maverick hats just dropped these things
are
awesome they're sleek they're athletic
caps and that's no cap
then we're not gonna use that to go to
maverclothing.com check it out grab one
before they're gone then also the
maverick club i gotta mention it i've
been silent about it for a minute but if
you are not part of the maverick club
here's what you've been missing out on
he needs some more millennials i need
wi-fi get your ass off
oh okay sorry and we're gonna be giving
away another ten thousand dollars soon
so make sure to go sign up for that join
the party the link is in the description
now enjoy the next four to five minutes
of absolute [ __ ] let me show the
apple off your head with me
yeah exactly nope you trust me
you might want to close your eyes you
might want to close your youtube after
this all right let's do this
oh no no no f f f oh my god
oh my god evan evan wake up hello i shot
my friend in his face
sorry i'm i'm i feel [ __ ] horrible i
trusted you all right i've seen this
trend on tick-tock you gotta be with
your girlfriend hop on the phone then
say you're with a friend and then see if
she breaks out but you or like kicks you
the balls or doesn't give you [ __ ]
for a week but i'm about to do it to
josie uh
chilling with a friend right now we got
food coming
knew what you're doing
i know a lot of jokes about retired
people okay but none of them work
well yesterday at eight o'clock it was
really time consuming
no it was it was especially when i went
back for seconds
stop it josie's never done cryotherapy
before this is a bonding experience like
this is the whole point of it you got to
feel safe with me i'm way too
claustrophobic already
come on close it dave shut the [ __ ] up
come on baby babe i'm closer
wait wait what do you mean you don't
know
maybe you can open it i'm claustrophobic
no you're not it's all mental it doesn't
stop to me
all right now time to do it for real
yeah i'm not going with you i'll do it
babe come on
come on come in no
come on do it with me
wait i can't see you little baby movie
josie how are you doing
not good dog don't touch me wait but
i'm holding your boobs for you i look
like mary had a little i am i was scared
no that's what i'm saying you gotta
overcome your fears you're doing great
[ __ ] and she's doing great she puts the
woe in woman
i'm pressed up against her right now her
nipples are very hard they're cutting me
across
my chest hey can we find here yeah yeah
go ahead
how you doing working hard good good so
check this out i have this piggy bank
but i haven't been able to open it if
you crack it
again you can keep what's inside it but
oh [ __ ]
that was hard there we go
you can keep that man i see you working
hard is it like a miracle something
a miracle bless you guys god bless you
you guys may have seen this before but
i've never done it you know i love art
so we're gonna start with a little blue
pop some yellow stripes in there gotta
have a little pink circle red oh that's
a lot of red
finish with some black all right three
two one
all right that should be good ow ow ow
ooh that hurt
wow that is sick bro look at this [ __ ]
that is [ __ ] cool all right so this
is julio i'm paying him cash to streak
my house
hey how you feeling anxious but
you know is that why you're doing this
oh i'm just doing this because i was
bored
nice we met through craigslist yeah
that's weird yeah that's super weird you
just have a craigslist stranger in your
house
naked all right sounds fun
oh sh oh my god baby baby
oh my god oh no no no
[Music]
oh what are you doing not the naked guy
drop the naked man i'm fine stop the
naked guy hey
goddamn
what are we doing in here why would you
ever introduce us to your boyfriend like
that are you
actually [ __ ] kidding me i saw him
that's low-key cheating i'm
upset with you why are y'all looking at
me like i had some part in this
maybe i didn't do it to just you don't
be selfish
just tonight right before you give her
the business you're like i got one more
thing
he comes
you