oh my god
[Music]
it's October it's spooky season I think
I'm gonna be a condom for Halloween but
that's a side note anyways y'all
remember when I blogged we did a vlog
last year with a giant pumpkin I think
it was actually the biggest pumpkin in
the United States it was so big that I
was actually able to do a 24-hour
challenge inside the pumpkin he's nine
times better when you're inside a
pumpkin then we made the world's largest
pumpkin spice latte oh no it's actually
working just some real basic epic now
you can bet your bottom dollar I did the
same thing this year except the pumpkin
is literally 500 pounds heavier so we
got the necessary equipment to lift it
up yeah dude that's right it's a giant
forklift that one's specifically built
from raising pumpkins so do me a favor
hit that subscribe button and also yo we
got some new maverick merch with this
job I'm wearing one of the pieces right
now but yeah I'm talking so fast I'm
wearing one of the pieces right now
hoodies are $38 and the t-shirts are 18
so scoop while you can't look appalled
calm slash shop without further ado I
think the pumpkins behind me I've been
drinking last night
thinning premier you know Hugh how much
does it weigh total 2,200 pounds oh my
god this is literally from last year
look at the size of the studs crazy
are you a pumpkin expert are you a
maverick that's my boy I almost got
kicked out of my neighborhood because
last year I took the forklift and went
down the street within the first month
of living here
but that was the old me
that was the controversial Logan Paul
I've changed things are different now I
have a beard beard is weird yeah man now
I'm gonna use my car and you make sure
to hit the truck with my cup my car okay
I that's it was a joke
its neighbors shoes is it bigger Suzy
Logan just moved in before last year's
pumpkin I said that and I also told them
that I almost got kicked out of the
neighborhood for the forklift festive
time man October is just so great this
is a nice just awesome time with friends
family and splendor
[Music]
we think maybe a tractor hit it or
something so just be gentle it so it has
a soft spot yeah we got soft spots my
heart I'm recently single
hashtag Logan's over pumpkin family my
pig at Pearl Bingbing on Instagram by
the way do you know who I bought that
pig was good I watched using the camera
she's so cute oh it's it's oh it's
breakup season Pete and Ariana broke up
by the way they bought a pig together
and now Ariana has the pig and I have a
pig if you look to my right you can see
the pumpkins rectum okay I have no idea
what I'm doing
[Music]
this is the hardest part is is sticking
it in the hole tends to be my biggest
issue all right Logan you just got to
put it in the hole
[Music]
Oh
I'm doing it he's doing it
yes yes and yes I'm just gonna fist the
pumpkin we're gonna Stan's bro freakin
Stan's like that oh my god just turned
into a prostate exam I told you to
poking at a rectum oh and I still ended
up getting the merge to hurt you damn it
listen to this sound the shell is so
thick man yeah that's amazing look at
that oh my god yo what's happening bro
hey man so guys these are the seeds how
much did you say these can sell for five
hundred fifteen hundred that is amazing
[Music]
this pumpkins literally gonna be gone in
like two days
hey Dad can I ask you something do you
think this pumpkin is a sociopath it is
right cuz the way it's sitting there do
you think that forklift is a sociopath
that's what I was just saying okay hi
guys that's about enough October
splendor for one vlog we currently have
the world's largest pumpkin that's how
we do it we do it different we're a
family of Mavericks and sometimes you
gotta buy a pumpkin that gives birth you
just thank you guys for watching if
you're not a part of the low gang gang
gang make sure to subscribe and also
squash that like button
head on over to live all that calm slash
shop ink up that new hot soft is merch
in the game it'll never get old watching
exit this pumpkin this one's a crazy
this popping cocking dragons give you
the heat career on Sam this kind of man
that's never gonna stop those my eyes
flow away hold him tight way stop the
lights numb the pain hold my breath