hi Lydia give me the details how much
was the final cost of the snow today we
are shooting a music video at my house
well finishing the Christmas distract at
my house and I don't even think Brendan
knows this we shift 30 tons of snow to
my house 30 to 30 tons bro 60,000 pounds
winter wonderland in California who's
doing it broke them every movement baby
okay obviously you guys know we're lit
with the strongest family on YouTube so
make sure to subscribe literally punch
the button in the face through me let's
give it a nice little tap but there's a
lot of stuff going down today anyways
right now in this studio I made a song
my boy Frank Frank had this idea show
you it was so easy
oh man what a good start to the day
so beautiful he's done it again all
right let's go playing so we had to park
the cool bus outside cuz the snow is
taking up the entire driveway braum
nervous go get the ice job you're
wonderland weirdest thing ever see snow
in California case Oh
Lydia sent me this picture of this snow
I was like wow Lydia that's great but
what am I not a maverick Lydia who I had
her have these guys go back and get some
more snow 30 tons more guys this is like
SEVIS yeah obviously
look it's dope it's just not enough cuz
that's just not how we do things can I
ask how much no cost $10,000 just giant
shove him into a grinder it's a wood
chipper on steroids it's my neighbor
the neighbors love is in the low guy has
Bert no this is crazy
honestly vlogging so if this is my new
job
Wow no hi guys I'm from Ohio is amazing
know what I'm realizing though I forgot
snow is cold I'm getting cold I have the
perfect solution so soft it's warm
winters coming up you miss the Black
Friday Cyber Monday sale don't worry
it's okay still be a maverick copy
Merkel male cop / I'll burn link in
description lot of people are joining
the Maverick movement at this point it's
like like who's not any type of
situation
anyways realize I'm spring snow doing
right now I go that's this kid I
could've easily killed mom but she looks
like worse call her mama cuz she's
pregnant I feel so bad if I killed mama
hi guys this sucks kind of sad but I
think it's safe to say I'm was gone rose
he's dead
don't know that I know I just wanted to
roll the montage I've been waiting for
that moment she could be alive guys I
don't know but we got more importantly
yo this is the second truck they have
another truck about three truck for
doctoral scale the house is look we got
our Christmas stuff out crackers and
watch your balls bro doing it forest bag
as with most of the things in my life I
tend to think of the consequences after
the fact all like let's take this garage
door for example there's snow if there's
snow break in this garage door brace bro
that's my title of thumb nail you make
your oppressor that it's holding him
this far yeah look bro I don't see any
leaks I do nice security camera to
capture the action about to go change
red drop drop table look up all that
counselors shop right out for today
first yo Kong is not a Midwest dog he's
never seen snow when I got this dog I
promised I would give him the most
exciting life ever so be free young
doggie guys he's never seen snow ever
oh this is hilarious it really has no
idea what he's such a Cali dog hyung
that snow can you say snow no it's okay
your dog I get it you just get off of
you oh oh you free my little maverick
dog
he's cold I never loved me Oh baby the
rut is back you and I got makeup on I'm
Hollywood right now yo I'm fakers and
glowing Brandon okay look I've been is
dressing up as an elf right now so we
have to decorate my house so it looks
like the North Pole get all this cute
stuff we got brought to North Pole to
here Judy topper this looks like the
North Pole I mean yeah that house were
like okay the first seat is up as you
guys know it gets dark in like 1 p.m. 4
p.m. here you have about an hour to
shoot we're just gonna start banging it
out such a troublemakers now it's time
to pull the big boy in I'm talking about
that Yeti baby I woke up
and all of the really cool oh my god
think we put a big red bow on the front
we had some snow to the Yeti gonna make
it's gotta make it snow let's do it by
this is beautiful literally we call the
Yeti cause it's an abominable snowman
and I'm covering the Yeti in snow she
got that ice how much was that y'all
that Isis you're doing good that time
it's getting dark up when it's time for
the epic group shot all gonna get in it
just dance with that new maverick Red
Rock merch on baby
y'all know ever was the hottest person
in the game yo Christmas dis track feel
bad for my Victor like seriously no
holding BAM coming for you you know who
you are
California Friday did you come to Minkel
but did you come to chinko you know I
got that baby it's cold
good job everybody let's code hi Lydia
give me the details how much was the
final cost uh yeah you subscribe during
the low game not a part of the family
subscribe now this man's a legend shot
the most epic music video ever top your
math and merch guys you can still get it
even if you miss to say a long pause
icon slash shop or link in description
trust me you're gonna put it on and
you're gonna be like damn I'm hot and
I'm soft at the same damn time it's a
good feeling it's like it's like after
you take a shower and you clean it here
with a q-tip it's kind of like that
quickly also I want to say well after we
do this no thing I went on the street
and it came across one of my neighbors
there was a huge snowstorm you just
missed it was great yeah
look it's crazy stay safe stay warm
oh my neighbor's love me I'll okay I
love you
is family on you too if you're not a
part of the looking you shucks