here's the deal and it's a big deal this
is literally the most player doggy lair
I'm leaving Ohio I'm leaving my home
look there's my mom came out her vagina
it's time for you boy to go back to
Hollywood quite simply I got to do a yo
good morning don't worry don't worry
though oh you thought it was sick no I'm
not sick I'm sure don't worry the whole
gang I did say my goodbyes
goodbye no goodbye Jake goodbye room
goodbye goodbye me normally I don't
sound like a hooker on bath salts but
it's the morning I'm like I just hit 16
million on Instagram at Logan Paul we
about to have 15 million on this channel
so if you're not a part of the Logan if
you're not subscribed okay you can live
a better life it's possible to subscribe
I know it's okay I'll do anything for
the low gang now let's do a little recap
show yesterday Christmas Day I bought my
dad a new truck Merry Christmas dad what
yeah unbelievable Wow
yeah it's pretty manly and then the day
before that I made it rain $10,000 on my
mother needless to say I'm the best
thing ever
right mom hear that Jake okay I love you
and your yo the kids Santa Claus came
through so many of you tweeting me
pictures of getting the Maverick marches
Christmas first off again
congratulations enjoy the moment my
voice is oh my god this daily vlog life
is no joke anyways yeah you're all
Mavericks you see the hottest sauce is
merchants thick but something surprising
there's a lot of Tears when you got the
merch I was like I was like what hey hey
don't cry it's okay lucky dogs and Kong
are here for you no you guys are the
best reactions ever
you're goddamn right you did Mandy Logan
Paul cos look guys the point is we're
out here changing the world and at this
point it's like hop on the train or get
off Scott oh boy
what do you want from me bro I'm
literally I'm dying over here my voice
has never been this gone you'll excuse
me and lo gang if you'll excuse me I'm
gonna go try not to die on this flight
to Los Angeles
wow that was quick I'm just kidding guys
that was long and painful literally
almost died on the plane okay being 100%
honest with you in my 430 days of
straight vlog every single day I don't
think I have been as sick where my voice
has been as gone as it hits right now
like it it hurts to talk and I promise
you I turned this camera off I don't say
a word to anyone cuz it hurts so bad and
I'm starting to wonder at what point am
I gonna need surgery on my vocal cords
or just straight up lose my voice
forever like I don't want that
oh thank you uh Patti but something
happens when I turn on this camera and I
got actually though I kind of have an
answer to this question oh I've been
saving this footage I would do a throat
doctor and she checked my vocal cords so
let's flash back to that footage to see
just how I am
this is crazy yeah you knew it go down
your throat
yeah that was not golden so these are
your vocal cords damn is sexy no vocal
cords are supposed to be nice and sharp
at the edges here so this is what kind
of like normal looks like see how they
come together oh those are beautiful
Oh so for you to look at these
side-by-side your vocal cords actually
at the edges are not as nice and smooth
they're starting to kind of pay a price
on your vocal cords so you can see here
you see how they're not as like edge
over time you couldn't risk scarring
them at that edge no that's disgusting
that's inside my body yeah I don't like
that I just don't even want like dab on
them vocal cords yeah okay so not as bad
as I saw oh my gosh
I will say that why this is a problem
now hey guys I'm going to Tokyo tomorrow
it's just another 10 hours on a plane
surrounding my other sick people I'm
sure I'm gonna be vlogging and screaming
then my voice needs to come back from
that no hello hello hello hello are you
good bro I feel like I just swallowed a
couple of gonorrhea pebbly really I'm
dying bro so no please I have a question
you're the most clutch guy I know you
always do it stuff I even look now what
do you hold to do it see look look how
much fun Wow I'm struggling for content
today not to mention I feel like my
heart's gonna stop please tell me we got
something bro do I have content okay
okay oh okay I made a promise we're sort
of vlogging I'm gonna come through hey
god damn it I'm gonna entertain you oh
my god first Chad from California
waterscape hey Chad he's got the
backyard lit yeah it's a little not only
that oh wow like you can't control you
got an app you can literally control the
litmus of any color you want what we
should cut to that now hey yo
and hey we're back backyard
Oh they'd finish the path y'all this is
perfect it's not like Japanese like
Asian style and I'm going to Tokyo
tomorrow this is actually done it's
perfectly I'm perfect guys we all have
imperfections and I'm egotistical mania
but that's what makes us perfect so
that's what I was trying to do with this
how it's a little bit off but the path
is still good oh my god I miss you quite
fun hello koi all of it leading up to
the gym oh man it's perfect perfect when
I left the smashed room was like kind of
done how is it bro honestly is the 100%
down show me the way I'm ready you know
I like to do the countdown three two
and the right mother durdane so there's
a lot of smashy going on yeah for sure
yeah bro these are like eye quality ass
punk [ __ ] Armani what's in here oh oh
this is great for storage yo Casper
Casper I guess as usual Casper hooking
up with the mattresses that are
seriously amazing oh god I can't stay up
here too long I was gonna use this to
fall asleep because I think as soon as
this ball can support a bat oh yes oh
this is seriously so nice Casper want to
see something else yes
yo this is so sick your head looks more
like a penis now than ever that must
mean he's happy that's my boy my Chinese
albino softshell turtle yeah this is
amazing oh honey what did you do what
did you do I'm calling the most savage
dog house Lee what oh my god covered it
he's just yet help me
Wow he loves you as much as me but it's
still love yo guys look it's Frank hi
Frank okay so listen Logan my boys funny
my boys funny please not just funny you
know you're funny but my B also makes
music and I know you know that cuz
you're you my boy just dropped a single
it's called bad tattoo I just you love
it I still love it so I'm gonna use it
as a soundtrack in this vlog yeah yeah
yeah guys it's called bad tattoo check
it out you're about to hear it good
stuff guys the Frank is gonna go far our
music so it's give him a follow check
him out what's you really great stuff
right guys the link for that is in the
description
be holidays yo you know what they say
sometimes you got to die in order to die
yeah yep Frank's wise words of wisdom
bye buddy
hi guys last thing before I actually go
die when the vlog ends talk to me what
the list did you do this was a fireplace
here's the deal and it's a big deal this
is literally the most player doggy layer
on although I haven't looked at this
yeah I'm looking at it oh my god this
used to be my fireplace
Armani Yugi he comes up to me one day
he's like yo you use that fireplace I'm
like no he goes Kong layer I'm like yes
this is amazing first thing we have is
the welcome mat a place where you can
draw his paws from running outside or
you into your play earlier then we got
this step here I see also storage for
all of its outfits and medicine as he
collects his wardrobe we have the store
it's quiet but it's also a step up into
another world we started off with a
dinner for two oh my god candlelit
dinner for two
yeah with a refill of nothing but the
best for going buggy it's a buddy this
is your lair car Kong you look perfect
and then what is this the dog bed like
seriously like this was the dopest dog
bed that we get possible how much was it
oh my god oh my god you are perfect Kong
and you know what brought all this on
right
no it's the fact that yeah I saw he was
on a date the other day oh he's got a
girlfriend got a girlfriend named Lulu I
also made sure that her picture was on
the wall when she comes over so no it's
real Kong actually called me while you
guys were in Ohio yeah how to do that
with his paws EDM me from his girl I got
you yeah is Instagram at Kong - Savage
oh my god this is so this was our first
picture con we were so cute on top of
these little drawers condoms
international
he comes brother this is actually
amazing earlier we talked about being
perfectly imperfect this is just perfect
it's good to see that he actually likes
it like this is crazy
he's literally he's the perfect dog I
need to see you at meetings yep kickin
it and calm Congress goes and steps in
car guess my boy lookin good you're the
perfect dog Kong did it again respect
bro guys looking I'm not no that is the
vlog I'm gonna go sleep hopefully I wake
gotta go to Tokyo bright and early
tomorrow morning that guy I get to go to
Tokyo I just want to be better New
Year's Eve in Tokyo it's gonna be crazy
if you're not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe normally we're
more less than this thank God for our
money keeping me later also I know
Christmas is over if you didn't get your
maverick March or you know what even if
you did get your mater word swag
yourself out get the entire Alpha you
want to be sexy and it's the hottest
softest merch in the game the Maverick
movement is real a movement of people
are a different passionate unique people
who build dogs for their dog who's doing
local ball that cops a shop or a link in
description low gang I love y'all I'll
see you tomorrow hopefully take it easy
doing me I couldn't see that she want to
hit me from the Fiza so then I had to
hit it with the C and they seen this
have to do with in the paper never idle
gotta ask for faith and welcome to the
Maverick match