I've been having a debate between my
friend and I you just wanted to know if
you could help us figure out who has a
nicer but I'll say it again all this 12
p.m. weight cups all this gallivanting
around with your little girlfriend is it
always watch last night's off your dick
he's kind of right on micro I noticed my
productivity is I gotta tell Josie to
take a hike I gotta break up with her by
maverick clothing out be honest if you
keep doing that I might be able to stay
cute change of plans I'm gonna have my
manager break up with her do your worst
boys not work it out do I know what he
does his life has become simply that of
giggles business very seriously is that
time for giggling Jeff ones last time
you giggled okay so me either but
apparently it's a thing he will actually
use it
I seen it on 90 day fiancé that really
good-looking guy put it in his hair my
pocket app in your pockets are deep
that's cuz these new maverick shorts are
a one watch it come out me hey some are
mayonnaise hey Cordy brother needs to
stop immediately I'm doing things that
I'm gonna be ashamed them for the rest
of my life memories yeah man
I guess how much do you manage sandwich
off your head a few hundred done have a
shower today's
[Laughter]
sirs gonna be pissed this is a kind of a
violation of space this is squirrel I'm
gonna open this door that moment you run
out I'm like a plan guys I don't like
the way he's looking at me I can't do it
went over the eggs if you speak English
go down and then I'll we happen to have
any of those tranquilizer darts was just
ran out actually yeah
oh there we go come on you got it you're
so close - hi how are you okay so I've
been having a debate between my friend
and I who just wanted to know if you
could help us figure out who has a nicer
but okay okay this is my butt and this
is my friend but like what you see now
all of them have been that successful we
have had quite the omegle journey
tonight
how many penises have you seen on this
website what you guys want you to what
do you guys think about Logan Paul tell
you something that was three years ago
[Music]