three what
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
hey let's go
[Applause]
oh good morning okay was Bob Haissam
keeping it contained right now but today
is a big day Kong today is a big day
buddy mark my words this could be the
biggest day of 2017 that's not a joke
hahahaha oh they're making the gym
amazing but mark my words low gang is
the day we're dropping maverick bottoms
this is no joke I couldn't make this no
I'm not okay this is the day that
maverick apparel officially goes from
merged to actual a pair of Nike had this
moment Under Armour had this moment
Aidid has had this moment today is our
moment the quality of the apparel we are
releasing today is no joke guys we have
black Morel joggers no man brendan is
rapping no but you're rapping the gray
Morrow jog oh oh wait oh great maverick
athletic short we're not racist black
maverick a pleasure and we got the shot
who's in my mind and the light gray
version of the shorts too yo oh and
ladies we didn't forget about you we
understand it's 2017 right gender
equality so we got the black white and
gray leggings for females different
women of all ages and sexiness look at
my mom over there now you're kidding
that's the first thing to have entered
the pool Brendan and I haven't even gone
swimming yet
well a boon oh my god the gate guy is
like little dog we ran down the street
oh what the heck and I look around he's
literally down the street you're gonna
get eaten by a coyote you're gonna die I
saw a big coyote right there
last naturally yes like a German
Shepherd coyote we can't bro listen
listen open these ears got to stop
running away bro I love you if the low
gang loves you anyway so you thought it
was over ha and ladies we know you're
busy right you got stuff to you you got
objects we know that so we put pockets
in the leggings joke
who's putting pockets in the leg nobody
all sorts of things in these pockets put
dis banana you can put macaroni in the
pocket and as if it couldn't get any
better yo the joggers the shorts they
come in youth sizes so if your youth if
you're under the age of 10 we got to go
and if you buy march in the next 72
hours I am gonna uh technically I guess
it's like a FaceTime so Instagram live
you can like bring people in now I'm
gonna choose five of you to FaceTime on
instagram live in front of 60,000 people
let's go yeah 72 hours y'all know where
to get the merch slogan for that con
slash shop or link in the description
okay it's time to get into the vlog
itself which today actually is a big one
Armani come on I didn't say mommy I said
Armani Armani talk to you about this
thing bro
so we may have ordered 3000 pounds of
dry ice hahaha how we bro need a giant
cauldron dry ice to make a giant
cauldron I was like I like you a lot
could destroy the pool
buzzes the exactly
montage ruined what happened there
Brendan I wasn't doing anything that
sticking drone just decided to fly to
the right where is it he's going boy
he's straight monkeying this true
[Music]
timber
what is the ice as I see as the change
are we gonna move the ice which weighs
more than the pumpkin and that was a
[ __ ] to move the nose dry ice that
anyone's ever put in a pool was 1,400
pounds and we're more than doubling that
our mom like you guys know Yeti is like
an abominable snowman so we're just I
see right now let's go if we were to put
these in a pool what happened
[Music]
yes I'm sitting here and I'm like I'm
mom I'm like she's a nursing like mom
I'm out of breath
and brain is like yo me too I felt like
I was having a heart attack he serves
our all fuses guys it's killing us bro
okay we're dying but yo do not sit in
the closed car with dry ice you will die
kids don't do this no I wonder what's
more deadly bro the dry ice or the
Maverick bomb baby
this is no joke right you literally
froze my window shot and if you notice
we just put the shirt jabu jabu darkest
oh good there's some bad news though
I know we're supposed to have this for
one day we extended it for like a week
just like the pumpkin we've exhausted
the forklift of everything you can do by
baby
I love you uh the guy that I was talking
to him maybe we'll buy one down the road
right now we got something else to do
Oh cabin bro run pack a nice weight you
didn't even put it in yet Oh pool is dry
[Laughter]
we got the whole squad here is my
neighbors love me okay I think the plan
is to count to three and then you know
why don't I just show
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
there's so much smoke everywhere oh my
god ha damn I like my leggings a moment
like the leg in order to have to do as a
maverick as the maverick I always have
to elevate go to the next level it's
money
that mother
all jokes aside I'm this close to
passing out why from inhaling it yeah
how much just died I mean like I'm some
real live there's a lot of carbon
dioxide like brought like it's
immediately like real friends do dumb
things with their friends so y'all have
you guys jump it I'll tag you
Hey
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
we drop bottoms that's what we did okay
so things are calming down calming I'm
still alive yet another epic day i'm
logan paul blows oh i'm just 3,000
pounds of dry ice who's doing it who's
doing it guys nobody god damn it
maverick bottoms we just Armani brawl is
such a good idea
oh and these guys are gonna be done with
the gym tomorrow it's gonna be the full
gym painting reveal so yeah don't forget
guys if you buy maverick bottoms or any
merch on the site logo Paul that cop
slash shop or a link in description if
you buy any of the merch on the site
Matt bottoms that are you should get the
Maverick bottoms of the best in the next
72 hours I'm gonna bring you into an
Instagram live and FaceTime five of them
five of you I was never good at math
wait yeah so I want to meet you guys get
your merch Logan Paul calm slash I just
say that the merch game has officially
been changed forever if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to
subscribe cuz I love y'all I was here to
make it easy
[Applause]
I met my pride