dude he's soft and squishy no chew it
otherwise he will she was way out of you
[Music]
coming to you to read 2018 yeah it's
funny as you can see everyone's fighting
here I actually just got done beating
some ass myself today's been crazy guys
let me rewind back to 7:00 a.m.
[Music]
[Applause]
if you guys don't be merged look up all
that calm / job everyone wants to be a
maverick everyone's joining the movement
now know what you're thinking what's
going on guys we haven't learned by now
but my vlogs don't really have a rule we
kind of just do whatever whatever we
want it's a fun life so today I brought
the squad to do some acting I don't know
if I want to tell you just yet some of
you probably already have an idea why
I'm going to set today so they're gonna
be working the whole day my voice is
gone up in sky for my movie the thinning
- it's that actor life for you okay this
is this is the pause good to see you hey
man you made quite the entrance that was
nice we woke up the neighborhood you did
the shout out I got 30 certified
aquascape characters from all over the
country coming in and these guys know
what they're doing like it's weird is it
not it's a little weird what you got in
that I'm just one part of a team here I
can see that we're outnumbered yeah hey
guys so first off thank you all for
coming man I know this projects gonna be
amazing for the next like two days or so
you boys an actor I'm shooting a movie
it's called the thinning - you can watch
it next year I need to Britt I will be
with you in spirit I'll be watching you
on the camera so don't steal my
this is gonna be so cool and to have
this be a part of already like a dream
house of mine is gonna be amazing so
thank you guys that's not bad for a 22
year old with a dream house oh wait hold
up hey are you guys like a part oh
you're helping them or what do you what
are you doing saying
[Music]
[Applause]
go get them guys opposite that I do when
I see people yeah I'll take care then
okay here's the thing this is a big deal
Oh gang we've added a new member to the
family team maverick is exclusive guys
we don't just add people you gotta be
top notch you gotta be next level you
gotta be the highest look and I think we
did just that so this guy's got some
sort of animal I'm not scared now he's
got a pig this is a Chinese softshell
turtle now this dude actually was
confiscated at JFK Airport right why
because people were gonna eat him dude
no well what's your finger dude because
he will bite it his head looks like a
penis it's true and the nicest way
possible this is going in the pond it's
gonna go on the phone I wanted to make
sure you had some special one Greg told
Bob this whole deal cog look if I come
buddy
it's got a really long he's gonna bite
himself here this is a 2,000 dollar term
this is dough thank you to both of you
don't worry guys look he's got a soft
shell oh look at this the shell is soft
normally they are a tan color that dude
is a so this is like a super rare turtle
no we gotta come up with a name and a
and make sure we mean the turtle and a
no hello gang I want to know what you
guys think comment what should we should
name this super rare Chinese softshell
albino turtle well under debate oh man
sexual organs are in there you guys hear
that everyone the boys got a penis he'll
come out oh my god I didn't realize it
and here's an even more ridiculous
factoid you ready softshell turtles can
breathe through their cloaca so when
he's underwater and he's chilling out he
can actually pulse this and absorb water
please oh there it is Logan
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go over that way oh no you know
okay so uh just so you guys know when
you guys comment I read that and I know
you guys have been missing maverick the
parrot it's my bad we haven't talked to
him in forever so I did I went to go say
what's up and I got some bad news
hey maverick hi buddy it's been a while
buddy I know there's a lot of people
here there are they're actually they're
building a pond it's gonna be super cool
we got a new pet is no his name is
pancake he's a turtle oh wait a second
look again cool diamond ring bro whoa
gang if you remember we put a $5,000
diamond ring on my Birds ankle and if
you look it's gone look closely it's not
on his ankle the other day I was walking
around my room and I saw it just laying
on the floor this is the ward dudes ever
hurts I know okay look it fell off white
gold and diamond ring that's supposed to
stay on for the rest of his life came
off of his ankle guys this is supposed
to be permanent that sucks bro like I
literally don't know what to do I mean I
guess we're gonna have to put it back on
look it's probably just gonna come up
again I'm lucky I found it this time hey
I'm in charge I'm King Guapo Oh hottest
in the game but it's unfortunately it's
not a functioning myrrh stove it's just
like you cuz it's like I don't know so I
got a challenge for you you're a
maverick right you want to be in this
summer yeah so every time we get a new
teammate on our team when we find this
in the ground we eat it this is living
on your property so what you want to do
is you got to don't swallow it because
he will try to chew his way out
[Laughter]
this is worse than being robbed yes I'm
rather they robbed me they're making me
eat bugs
big girls also drinks his own piss bro
I'm Logan Paul dude he's soft and
squishy you know the other thing they
got a creamy Center are you talking
about ready you have anything to wash it
down with
cheers to it otherwise he will she was
way out of you
[Laughter]
sorry yeah
that's disgusting hey ladies if you want
to kiss me right now it's the time my
life I can't believe you just did that
yeah that bug was almost as good as this
onset meatloaf to be honest guys I was
literally too tired to realize that I
was eating a look I'm a savage all right
I'll do dumb thing but I can't say I
like eating insects now at this point I
realized it was gonna be an interesting
day you just ate a maggot yeah you got a
new pet yeah there's it's a good day
mine is the birding thing and also oh my
god okay yo so look at my gog look at
the Yeti real quick what is this stop
song this morning I woke up and I saw
this before I let them in and I'm like
what is happening and even if you look
around like everything's just like foggy
and ashy look look you can literally see
ash flying through the air this is from
a fire apparently there's like a fire
really nearby like a giant forest fire
and we are like the blunt of all the
ashes my pool is disgusting
it makes me so sad not to mention my
snow baby yepp guys I'm pregnant
oh my gonna sleep in here no this sucks
this is miserable like how do you how do
you fix something like this look at just
layers of ash so bad this sucks
ash I saw a guy smoking outside over
here where's your killer this is
actually horrible this leg dude my
beautiful car okay ash okay oh wow all
right Oh mother nature why are you
leaking on me I don't want to say this
but you've been a real [ __ ] Lyla what's
he leaking on you cuz Phil Ash's leaking
is like water though job guys can he was
being the vlogger that I am guys I
wanted to cover all the angles so I sent
in my ground team to get the real deal
cover all the forest fire action see
what's really going on trust me these
guys are the best in the business
so let's cut to the ground
okay it looks like they've caution tape
this area off it looks like there's
actually firefighters up there so we're
gonna go check this out this is the day
the world ends all my belongings belong
to McKenzie my little sister my stuffed
animal George that goose my love gonna
die and we're not gonna die real live
fancy anything oh there's a crew up
there actively working to put out this
fire and teleport media we're here to
report for the people of Los Angeles
Italy we're giving you exclusive news
here reporting maverick live news
channel like and subscribe if you
haven't done that yet cuz guys we're
give me a real-time
[Music]
all right we are here live on the scene
maverick media do we have any live
updates on the scene
we should leave shop be a maverick baby
down reading I'm tagging that Chester
intense stuff man those guys are really
something you know I heard that started
from a cigarette
so don't smoke because you will either a
die or be start a forest fire not cool
so at this point I'm like yo this day's
crazy bro I got away Kevin up and then
say goodbye to the pond guys bro you
have no idea where we now this morning
we got a new pet his name is pancake you
broke my vase yeah well why is now a
good time
Stokes Q while I was sleeping I heard
like I heard you people just clap just
like 7:30 a.m.
I'm like no I'll sleep why you just no
hands in Congress our bro this is so
unsafe all right guys I'm late to set as
usual by an hour
good job Logan Greg the pond guy bro
it's nice huh
[Music]
yeah bro you guys are going to work the
bridge going right across it here no
they've been here for I think 40 minutes
you're amazing bro fact alright later
and okay lo game that is a vlog unwanted
a bro crazy we did so much stuff I ate a
bar girl if for whatever reason you're
not a part of the Logan stuff that's
weird subscribe for me we are the
strongest family on YouTube just like we
did today on set and also if you haven't
yet copier maverick merch the Maverick
movement is very real everybody want to
join everybody want to be of abric
everyone wanted an albino softshell sea
turtle everyone wants one of those name
pancakes so cop your maverick merch ah
looking Paul back on slash shop with a
link for that is also in the discussion
christmas is coming up it's winter get
your merchants war it's soft you get
sexier these are facts locating I love
gone I will see you tomorrow actually no
way when the pond is done oh my god
that's gonna be amazing guys
[Music]
[Laughter]