oh okay wait listen we could all have
herpes right now bro STD results came
back
nah the STD results are you nervous no
you know why the day we got it I was
like I'm chillin bro Frankie like did
you give me a pillow to snooze on [ __ ]
joke anyways the point is I was not
nervous now that it's the day I'm like
Bruno sexually transmitted diseases they
are no bueno
basically you get them by just being a
dirty hoe it's a goofy one today guys
you could probably tell by now but yeah
the other day we got checked flashback
I'm positive I'm not positive she's got
a roll up my sleeves on the March yeah I
was rocking the merch made made sure the
nurse knew that he actually ended up by
some yeah she was quite the maps
breaking all that bro I woke up today I
woke up every day and I say the
following they throw up BM I raise it to
the roof and I say how can I change the
world today that's what we do that's the
goal every single day trying to change
the world somehow that is the Maverick
spirit it's why I spend a lot of money
making custom necklaces out of diamonds
but yeah y'all know where to get the
merge Logan Paul calm slash shop link in
description it's not it's not a movement
it's a revolution hop on the trailer get
out of the way anyways yeah the results
are back my man are you nervous no
you're good no we're like let's see if
Evans never am bro your STD results are
back you nervous bro
[Music]
alright never come never come come at
least I have one pet that likes three hi
hi Kong
come here baby that's my boy oh we're
gonna have a talk Kong is it something I
said or what's going on
good stuff but I know for a fact my day
one maverick loves hey baby that's my
boy
so yeah I know oh my god
give him a logo name a brand after him
and this is what I get
I wanted me a good bad and Romana well
at least I know the low gang loves me
alright guys
hey no God Brendon hello gang
hello gang come on guys ten minutes
later
hi guys Brennan I have to go to a
business meeting with manager Jeff Roe
so for the next hour so you could take a
nap nap whatever you want to do it's
nothing you're not invited you're just
like you can't come I get it all right
so we can go hi Brendan I do love you
bro
I'll see you later I about to hop in
this over the door's locked I'm
embarrassed is people chasing me what's
up do you have a son is the loser but
hopefully not loses nine like me you
don't want him to turn this into me okay
I mean I'm just trying to educate moms
to educate their sons about sex all
right boom and just like that we are
back home I planned on vlogging with
manager Jeff but we got caught up in the
conversation we business stuff bro
changing the world dancing the universe
yeah Brendan's inside but I just wanted
to point out where I was looking around
I'm hungry boy hungry boy over here I'm
like dude we reckoned we don't have
snack you know it's a sad day when
you're only snack is doing like what are
you hoping I'm not gonna lie I miss
selfie vlogging I can do frick and
control the camera in front I'm into
this more but maybe probably on the
bigger camera song help us pick up the
all you know how why is this dog perfect
why does he know when he's on camera and
what jokes to me it's not me it's here
wait watch out that's win I'll help you
come here see we are now you come to
help yeah you take your seaweed I
remember when I first got calling I was
like this is this is so dumb I don't
have any time for myself even a
girlfriend but I got a dog okay thanks
man
look boy was I right back to Brendan's
camera hey wind hey window listen to me
you son of a [ __ ] you can take all the
seaweed you wanted I got you in our debt
Wow we had this much seaweed Lidia
[Music]
one minute later
two hours later ten seconds later I know
you want snacks always girl always have
asked you guys what do you ask
I've asked like a long time you guys
remember this question be good oh my god
loves burritos dude really yes please
yeah we traded him in for snacks yeah
cuz we could probably get a lot of
snacks kong is worth a lot of money why
do you think they call it Trader Joe's
22 years later no Brendan look point the
camera between that cut I went to
business meetings Oh can't you see all I
wanna do is smile oh yes honey yeah
heaven is still in his room oh this kid
is a gamer also I think this is why I
have more energy today cuz like I just I
get caught on these new high kicks bro
hi
[Music]
so I don't tell you seaweed all of your
bedroom that's just a hassle look at all
this seaweed everywhere no no no piss my
bait seaweed it's it's seaweed bro I
didn't I didn't know I know seaweed
sucks what I didn't know who's gonna
like it everywhere
for two reasons one this video seaweed
so I know it's the second it wasn't
intentional I didn't know they were
gonna I didn't I didn't know the seaweed
was gonna frickin sputter like dandelion
[Music]
what is this vlog dad come here we got
STD check oh Jesus
yeah and we have we have the results we
said Brendan Evan and I we've made a
pact that we were gonna just share the
results no matter what probably wasn't a
good idea huh I'm confident I am what do
you want bro we got we got to see if we
got STDs what are you doing yeah you got
clothes on the floor now I can just yo
he even took the sheets off the bed I
wish we had a camera in here that just
like watched Evan just temper-tantrum my
room the good news is he didn't spill
the milk so that's a good you son of a
[ __ ] many more practical ways to clean
the milk
things I mean calm paper towels and more
subscribers so if you're not subscribed
make sure to join the low back dog thank
you everybody
what's the milk good good for your bones
this is no small thing
this could mean drugs and buy drugs I
mean medicine by joke to me medicine yes
exactly
yeah outside whoo we made this a big
deal we put on the giant TV 90 inches of
SG what's next well and that's fine now
going over to health records here lab
test results Oh
what do you mean media amplified p- all
your negative for chlamydia alright yo
your negative for gonorrhea and our PR
sts now reactive oh oh yeah oh oh sick
son anti what does it mean bro it says
the standard range is less than 0.9 and
you're at 0.06 does evan have herpes
probably not right like whoever has the
highest number is one who has herpes
nice yama go next Brenner
what no what does that mean I don't know
if that means you have more her because
you're taller and you weigh more you're
gonna have more of the 0.03 206 no that
makes my G okay wait listen
oh wait standard range less than ninety
Brendan's at point five four so we could
all have herpes right now bro like a
little bit like Evan has the littlest
bit and then me and then you or like I
literally actually though I want to make
a call and see what that means this vlog
is gonna take a pause right here
tomorrow morning we will call the center
pick up divorce I'll pull the vlogs each
other's name
now is closed and that'll be the vlog so
uh yeah looks like we're going to sleep
not knowing great it's gonna be a fun
night okay tomorrow morning go to sleep
oh my god this transition to 2017 I
don't know I can't wait anymore
Lydia make the call hi there I brought
my three kids in there to get STD tested
and all three of them have a figure out
what that means
[Music]
okay awesome
thank you so much
[Music]
the Fisher were clean not just us
everyone should this is like it's a good
thing to do it just when it comes down
to it so nervous bro so that's good okay
it's always fun when you do this cuz
like I'm starting tomorrow's vlog in
like 30 minutes anyways ah thank you for
watching guys if you are not a part of
the logging y'all know what to do hit
that subscribe button bro I'll wait here
did you hit it yet do it baby if you
have not yet copter maverick merge death
the universe with us Logan Poldark on
flash shop or link in description the
hottest softest most comfortable merch
in the game is that effect of courses
that's so fresh I love y'all I will see
you tomorrow take it easy
[Music]
get away with your words