go for that Oh God the kitchen right now
is the man literally Lydia what's wrong
this table to make cake hi morning
pancakes as you know we got this new
turtle named pancake cuz he looks like a
pancake
we have like eight people saying the
house was right now seven here's real
life pancake his head still looks like a
penis but guys I do have good news why
would you do it let's see guys is the
disaster but the good news my lord and
savior's are here the May
I love you guys thank you seriously so
much I will say we're expecting another
guest and he's actually here the cool
boss came right up to the front door oh
cool
did you hit your house with the cool bus
yet my bus death universe bro
it's the Maverick move mr. brand pros
the hottest merchan the game pro no joke
we restock things and they're gone in a
day that right there maverick
enterprises it's a movement if you
haven't joined it yet you show G&P
aol.com slash shop or the link is in the
description guys christmas is coming up
I just made this trending number one low
game we've done it again
I was the strip for a reason thanks for
your assistance Lydia I love how
enthusiastic she is well yeah we're lit
bro the low gang the strongest family on
YouTube up up up up if you're not a part
of the low game make sure to subscribe
and if you're looking at the subscribe
button and it doesn't have the D at the
end it doesn't say subscribe to do that
you could subscribe right now now back
to the cool bus uh yesterday you guys
know we bought a thousand dollars worth
of Christmas lights we also got rowdy at
Home Depot I had this idea I want to
wrap the entire cool bus in Christmas
light know who needs a tree when you
have a bus bending you took the words
out of my mouth Mavericks bro like
everybody else got a dream right put it
on my bus so I think we're gonna add alt
for one second and wash the bus
for cleaning Brenda member this footage
Logan you'll never see this again that's
my oh yo this is the first time I've
washed
I think anything at my house including
your body yeah I think so
the rules are kind of like this right
you want to come over my house yo that's
great but you gotta clean my bus good
job guys oh my god guys the bus is
looking clean on the front is gleaming
but now we have to get this thing lit we
have to wrap it with light and I have to
leave her set in like an hour and a half
so you're so tiny you start being more
careful like where your body is you know
I think just because I was given this
tall slender perfectly shaped frame like
that
don't try to reverse this now let's get
into the montage I know that it's a
holiday but I ain't the same without you
babe it's been a while since I saw your
face it's an avenue see you remember
when we copped on me in December when
the winner came it's been a while since
I saw your face wish I was kissing you
whoo baby we're making progress I got
the side of the bus hi man yo I don't
even need to make a little look at the
top we got the big light bulbs draping
the cool bus and guys we still have at
least half a million more lights so I
have to go to set right now uh you know
shooting other 32 available on the next
year on YouTube right I'm gonna take the
squad y'all ready to go watch me be a
movie star
guys thank you I will say I want to make
sure my house is clean what I've learned
guys is when you make a mess is gonna
have to pay for the consequences of your
actions
or you pay people to pay for the
consequences of your action which is
what I chose to do that's good yeah come
on in mister how much you could just get
him a bus I'm gonna be late hey mister
do you have any candy yeah and two
Hannah Montana tickets come on in come
on the boss he barely even talks easy
Joe Montana yo enough with these
pedophile jokes I'm gonna be late get it
so I think this is actually good that we
get to see the lights on the bus in the
daytime he oh we look so stupid right
now what I've said it before guys it's
okay to be different I like being
different ever me that's fine boy I'm
the map when people are looking at you
weird they're actually just admiring and
that's a fact now let's see how this
puppy performs on the roof who's that
sound of looking at take your gifts and
give them back fabric merch is where
it's at got the hoodie
what's up sailor look in that you should
remove my Belfast
you should get my new backpack throw
away that 37 yo-yo arriving in style the
only way I know how to show up I will
say on the way here I crashed the drone
trying to get drunk shot Dennis ok Nick
haha what's new also this was an hour
drive were literally in the middle of
nowhere have a helicopter coming to
sensitive and on the way here she did
that one part exactly look at what
happened to the court
oh my god how are you supposed to plug
if your blog looks like this you can
always plug oh we know we say always
plug but I don't know alright the good
news is they don't need me acting for
like another like two hours so I think
we just get to fix the whole thing my
sub bank so hard the ground is with it
take my dog as sacrifice don't think the
helicopter is trying to kill you hi guys
back to the bus car we are putting so
many lights on this thing they're
literally shooting the movie right there
like we always some point it becomes a
fire head honestly bro if like a fire
were to strike or something the bus is
already fired to get cool things done
but now guys it's time to be an actor we
got a helicopter on Sempra who's doing
it friend you gotta go we gotta Holly
God said Brothers City too
yeah I'm obsessed with this movie guys
I've never had this much fun shooting
anything
20:18 you to read the thinning to
Mulligan the love it bro and it's crazy
that the helicopter wasn't even the most
fun thing I've done today let's talk
about the completed boy guys there are I
think fourteen point eight million
lights on this bus one for each of you
guys in the loop okay now that it's all
done I think we light this baby up we
got y'all I'm actually nervous like what
if one of them is like broken and the
whole strand doesn't work Christmas I
cannot believe this work I don't even
have to say this but if you're not a
part of the Logan make sure to subscribe
because as you could see with Lily we
are gonna go drive this around except
while I was acting I heard a little
aggressive Lydia don't you think I don't
even know I wasn't even there no one's
saying you're lying
alright guys well the vibes are kind of
weird right now except that's not what
Christmas Christmas is about savagery so
let's drive home and do the most lit
Christmas light up but the montage
[Music]
epic bro just a piece doing it bro loves
Christmas except that Santa guy okay
alright guys it's like 1:00 a.m. we're
all exhausted if you're not part of the
low gang first off you go brah make sure
to subscribe literally smack the button
in the face for me a copy maverick merch
the hottest softest merch in the game
looking for calm /ja orling in the
spirit or league on the wheel store in
the movement bro you can still get your
toughest tough tough tough stuff stuff
in time for Christmas with that set low
gang I will see you tomorrow which is
actually the last day on set of the
thinning okay
[Music]
I check out the side of the bus honey
sorry that was so it was like okay go
yell at him bro he's fine mister being
in focus but like just I'll go again