there is a lot of big things going down
right now I didn't even know who's gonna
vlog today but something amazing okay
guys today is a big job we just was
right here the m4 the Maverick with
little Mavericks breaking off Spencer's
wearing the red block maverick this
morning everything happened so fast that
literally just grabbed like the
old-school selfie style vlog camera this
is a real life what are you you have a
duck you have a dog no and I saw duck
just like no doing by himself across the
yeah across the yard all by himself I
was looking for his mama hey bro his
family abandoned him you you've had
ducks me too I've actually I grew up
with six ducks what do you think his
name is duck but what do we do I know
someone who may be able to help we need
help Jeff we have an issue it rhymes
with duck yes what do we do is it row
I'm gonna find mom
yes I'm saying row duck duck goose duck
for the duck sir are you a duck no it's
just a fish duck duck duck Duck Duck
grew up raising ducks I don't know what
we're gonna do with this one also the
fact that he's alone is kind of
worrisome I'm hopefully he has like a
sibling here somewhere doc if you're a
duck raise your hand you know I'm mating
call or something I could draw this for
a duck absolutely
I don't think it works well we got well
we have a very scared terrified
separated potentially orphaned duck oh
no we have to be realistic
no no reason why a duckling would be
separated as Eva the mother hasn't made
it or the mothers abandoned Hayden knows
his ducks might have a responsibility to
take care of the stock I've raised ducks
well yeah I have yeah yeah I grew up
with the most adorable things ever so
what does he need like right now I think
people really need some warmth some was
a height so we can calm down we need to
get him some him or her some food sounds
like a plan chicken feet if you get
chicken feet of protein they can grow
really strong unless we want to make our
duck vegan well not liking food I think
it's what a chicken eat I'm gonna get
this duck some protein he gonna be too
gnarliest duck in the land we want this
dipole to be a bro bro our dog is an
animal he's a lion I'm actually gonna
take care of the dot no I know what how
many ducks you have Brooke yo why are
you in the merch store bro the hottest
softest much in the game oh my god we're
using the hottest softest nurse in the
game tomorrow
he's already calm down bro there's no
way of telling if it's a male or female
you have a false look for his dick dicks
hide inside that body oh my god hey
that's a dick duck okay so now we're
back in real time we have to figure out
what to do with the duck which by the
way bro I know I said I wanted to name
him duck though but I got a better idea
what if we named him Huck dude Huck the
duck bro cuz he's looking sitting on the
hockey t-shirts befo
it's Huck the dock is so perfect no
because it's the ship's yeah so look
until I guess we figure out what we
actually want to do next we have to take
care of this duck so I think we're going
to go to the store and get some duck
stuff to take care of hook what yeah
wait what what do you know dad first of
all you can't just eat a duck a baby
duck especially you need the eggs maybe
second of all Jesus dad not eating the
duck man I called you to ask for help
what are you saying right now you know
how we had ducks growing up but like how
what do we need seems pretty
self-explanatory wow thanks for help dad
well we'll talk to that all right your
dad is a SMAW might be the most
counterproductive conversation I've ever
had in my life
Nick GP yeah great stuff I did try to
eat the duck and told us he needed food
thanks dad alright guys so I'm about to
become a dad for the first time that I
know I'm early er I did call someone who
knows a little bit more about this stuff
and like if it's legal or like what to
do and how to do it he's calling me back
right now his name is Jed he's a good
dude brother talk to me bro I'm glad you
reached out we we contacted our people
from the city and the state your
inclination was correct we wanted to
make sure that we followed all the right
steps to make sure we protected this
takling in the state of California ducks
and hawks are protected by a federal
reserve and what that means is that you
have to have a federal rehabilitation
license to keep and presumably heal up
baby huh claims he spent a great time
with you but here's the bottom line he
has to go as soon as possible to the
West Valley Animal Shelter
which is our local shelter and I mean
it's a bummer but it's it's the best
thing for him it's the most humane thing
for him and it's the law and you want to
make sure that we do all of those things
so yeah I'm gonna text so I'll text over
the address to you they're waiting there
they're really very cool yeah of course
they're grateful they're about to take
the greatest rock on planet Earth
Paquette it's so good oh yeah bro he was
a maverick but I understand I understand
we're just gonna have to wing it
duck my ass dude these puns are really
quacking me up yo real talk this sucks
bro only cuz oh I do he's like he's like
falling asleep bro you so you look at
him
oh he's just a little ugly it's okay
Huck you're gonna be in good hands that
are probably better than Hayden's
currently all right okay guys the West
Valley Animal Shelter
I'm a little sad bro cuz I'm looking at
the sign here says get a great new pet
here was a great new guys a yond on my
Instagram story look duckling so many
good memories
[Music]
huh hi guys
hey to stop
we can't foam inside itself let's do
this myself
[Music]
well he's not dead so I don't why I said
rest in peace but it's done Hayden I
gave him to the center I get I gave him
I gave him to the people better people
more responsible not well they're not
better
well maybe probably more responsible for
sure yeah yeah bro yeah well they said
they're gonna take him to a first to
rehab center because he's been doing
like drugs or something they said and
then they're gonna get him accustomed to
the wildlife and then too sure about the
drugs they said rehab center as he needs
to
well they said a rehab center so he
obviously was doing some sort of hard
drugs he must have a wild night if we
ended up in our guy yeah you come in the
maverick is crazy
he must have this said though maybe we
could visit him at the Wildlife Center
as she grows into a nice chuckling so
that's cool and I guess with that said
low gang blood a fun unexpected surprise
when today we are here shave and duck we
are here drop a new t-shirt side it's of
this merger to you make sure you guys
get yours join the map movement be
yourself be you do it different blue you
maverick guys Logan Paul icon slash shop
or link in description last thing if you
guys are not part of the low game make
sure to subscribe we're your super ultra
win we saved duck life's and also ksi
won't beat your a slow gang I love y'all
oh oh wait I'm still saying tomorrow you
gotta stop doing eyebrow
[Music]
to be obvious
they display with me
wannabe
[Music]
that's my boy humping a rock