Gaja ladies on your new baby it's your
baby
[Music]
[Applause]
Sunday hey yo good morning little guy he
made another trough it's so good
what does this man do wrong it's your
big day all my talking Hales me ho gang
you should know today is the day we set
the internet on fire not today is the
day the Christmas district is dropping I
know the Internet's been waiting for it
so turn your notifications on subscribe
to the channel join the loge English -
wrong yes family energy but you do not
miss the diss track I think it's gonna
come out in a couple hours do me a favor
when it comes out just drop it a like
instinctively just press the like button
it's no bueno but I'll tell you what
what is bueno guys today is not about me
if you know I have an assistant her
name's Lydia and she's pregnant
yup guys I'm pregnant kind of funny cuz
she seems to think she's not pregnant
but here's proof ya up guys I'm pregnant
she said it herself like no one made her
say that so she's pregnant yup guys I'm
pregnant today we are gonna throw a baby
shower for ya
the biggest in all of California what do
we got coming bro we got belly dancer
snake charmers we got hey we got
maverick much dad is marching the game
christmas is coming up babies are being
popped out of vaginas everybody wanna be
a maverick
so get your merch for you baby and your
cousin your Grammy your aunty your momma
your mammy up those grandmas zebra
jammies it's Macklemore so yeah dude
Catherine have emerged love all that
come to our shop we all do it it's good
stuff now we have to get supplies for
the baby shower
I gave Lydia the morning off cuz it is
her big day she's gonna be here like
1:30 so we have to get everything set up
before she comes I'm just excited to see
how awkward Lydia becomes yeah they call
me LP this my holiday single did I
mention that we're single I might've
like
that's here the christmas district yet
yeah big moves money moves guys we were
going to get props here's the issue I've
never had a baby personally I'm so I
don't know what to get for a baby shower
we need those need flowers named
charmers again not sure about the
necessity of those hater the diapers
that you know you don't have to clean as
much because Lydia never cleans it we
should get baby clothes but not for the
baby for Lydia I should get the baby
a Rolex at the party store every day's a
party what do we got poppers here man
when the baby is born he's not one right
he's zero really on a percent bro let's
get let's get cultural with it bro let's
get some cuz the baby's not born yet bro
so the baby won't see that mass bringing
a belly dancer we need to call the baby
out we go what did the party so lit the
baby's like y'all I'm coming out four
months early yeah it's me mini Lydia
2017 yeah who needs gender to identify
human beings bro come on disco ball sure
you just don't want that for yourself
this cone in my room has nothing to do
the baby shower diapers in case of
emergency break glass Oh
have you ever had a baby well can you
give me advice on how to have a baby
wait balloons there we go let's get
enough balloons to tie to Lydia and she
floats away bro I love it so like like
three formulas
hi guys we got the supplies the balloons
don't quite fit in the car so we gotta
go on top there they are feel like this
is a nice little like cherry on top for
the Yeti it's so cool that I get to live
this experience with Lydia it has her
boss it's my job to make sure she has
the most fun and this is the most
memorable experience it can be
now Lydia's gonna be here in about 45
minutes so we have to set up quick also
I think the belly dancers here hi oh
it's not my baby oh no I can't
physically cuz I'm a boy no it's my
assistant it's my assistant a spherical
so she's gonna be here about 45 minutes
we're gonna set up you can feel free to
kiss my dog whatever you want to do okay
[Music]
this would be a true baby shower without
some luck
we find him at the party store thanks
for coming guys Logan bought my coffee
shop very easy sold out seven sweatshirt
and your dog is I need them you think
you're dying I'm dying wrong I want to
supply the myrrh
hi guys Lydia's here everything is set
up this has gotta be the baby
[Applause]
wait then what is in that bag you told
me right yo does she have baby why would
you have baby food oh why would you
bring baby food if you're not pregnant
that doesn't make any sense it when you
bring baby food we go not gonna do a
baby food challenge today not say that
I'm at 130 I was like honey it's your
big day
cue the belly dancing music
[Music]
seeing Lydia this happy seriously makes
me want to shut it to you oh dude you're
such a brave young woman so brave so
admirable admirable that's a good
question I have no idea this is fake
what then why would she have said this
yup guys I'm pregnant oh wait I mean
what you didn't say this yup guys I'm
pregnant
oh you're talking about the video where
she says I'm pregnant yup guys I'm
pregnant what I'm sorry you guys went
there's so much effort and spent all
your money on this for me
you made employment we pay for a belly
dancer you lied why would you lie
[Music]
you mean to tell me you don't have a
human inside your belly right now it was
lying I'm not pregnant okay I need my
baby shower turned into a shower and
[Music]
Happy Hanukkah happy Kwanzaa like and
subscribe and Happy Easter
told you she could kiss my dog so things
have definitely calmed down gotta say
I'm disappointed Lydia's not actually
pregnant now that I think about it
though it does make sense cuz she kept
telling me she wasn't pregnant it's
confusing cuz she said this yes guys I'm
pregnant
anyway Logan you've done it again one
thing we did not think about honey the
Queen no good girl do you do stuff like
that you know what this is low gang we
did it I didn't want to do it but I had
to we work together and we clean the
space look around no confetti maybe I'm
responsible after all but probably not
oh my god that was a fun vlog but it's
not over just yet
I think it's better okay if boi is high
y'all remember I went to Dubai and I
bought this roller that's the Platinum
presidential Rolex I make a bunch of
pretentious cocky rich jokes with it cuz
I'm a choch but when I bought it I was
told it was I bought it for $40,000 but
my business team suggested that I get it
appraised in America to find out the
true value of it we got it
a priest today yo ho man look at this
pipe oh [ __ ] can you can you be a girl
close what his number for me Brent
appraised value let's go down $62,500
watches were $63,000 yeah maybe Rolexes
are different in Dubai but Tambor lifts
freakin awesome but something that's not
so awesome my boy Andy it's a mini it's
a micro SD card it's like this big all
right okay that is the flaw if you're
not apart from me smack the button in
the face or kiss it on the mouth
whatever you want to do point is you got
to subscribe do me a favor slap a like
on that I'm telling you to slap a lot of
things slap it like on that it's wet I'm
lint we're lit and the merchants late
looking for that cops last shot be a
maverick join the movement y'all look
different sound different smell
different I love your house - Tamar take
it easy
[Music]
this is gonna be so good