big day come you're getting clean one
day probably in the very near future I'm
going to be doing this with my own I get
even better than I think you do it well
it's definitely not better than me I'm
the goat anyways yeah it's going to
savage how are you this morning puppy it
wish did
good talk speaking of pets and being
unresponsive bro how's your new pet bro
that I got you oh pretty good yeah it's
pretty loud oh really
yeah it can't be up all night really
weird cuz he's a fish yeah I guess I'm
just confused how that animal right
there could be loud and kept barking
it's just I feel like you're talking
about the dog I could be wrong it's just
like biologically you know like fish
don't bark
its scientific alike you me I know how
to trick people into into subscribing to
my youtube channel a lot of things in
dog I have to leave this place this is
an absolute mess I cannot live in this
house anymore
what do you mean no you are guys we are
getting a new house new house it's true
it's true and just like I cannot wait I
just want to move in bro unfortunately
you still do cuz we'll still be
roommates but okay exactly stop it just
stop it whoa whoa whoa guys I got a
phone call yesterday yeah like that if
the house has like a number of it oh
sorry here can I fix that it's fake the
house is like a number of issues with it
yo can i I'm vlogging for one second the
house is the number of issues the
inspection impala blossom vision just
went out here bro how much longer bro I
don't know I don't know but you look
when it comes to problems bro stick to
what you're good at right me personally
not wearing pants and plugging my merch
that symbol right there baby the
Maverick everyday people roughing that
logo people reppin the Maverick movement
we're changing the world guys we're
working hard it's the crazy ones who
dent the universe and that's what Dawg
I'm trying to be inspirational listen
Logan Paul cop / opera link in
description y'all know where you can rap
yeah be inspirational always grow we
looking up here check is over what is
the average lifespan of a dwarf
yeah bro I feel like oh oh how long are
you gonna live it I need to know how
long I have to put up with your [ __ ] it
says in general these people may live
approximately 10 years less than the
general population I'm not making this
up approximately 10 years left brom I
gonna die eventually yeah what 10 years
sooner than me it looks like I'm good
thanks for asking it's such a sunny
Sunday you already knows bro like oh
crap yeah Cole watches all of this hi
you good you approve of this message we
have a house full of fun pets we really
do look at this slow game we got Oprah
the fish we got Kong the savage we got
maverick the bear call me maverick still
have to work on their bonding skills ah
she's mainly just maverick bro he's
aggressive be free what's your deal bro
go back to your cage or not hey hey hey
hey jus listen I'm at number four
workout number five combats right buddy
that's her Go Go you can't run away
you're all that God knows you're a dirty
doggy we gonna clean your ass up calm
yeah it's been a while since I gave Kong
a bath but I first I feel like working
out bro so let's do this baby
mad boy yeah I actually don't feel that
good yeah I feel like I'm gonna throw up
that's when you got a dig deep push
yourself Brian damn be a frickin
maverick and do it
[Music]
for me or for like you know the toxins
out of your body the bad energy sweating
also just relax abroad
it's Sunday Funday and I talked about
that smashed t-shirt available now I'm
looking for that calm slash shopping
talk about that sweat well I went and
branded Bennett you went in oh yes this
kind of sucks
oh my god Evan the world doesn't revolve
around you he's small
you don't have enough gravity call me
Pluto [ __ ] Luna the dwarf planet I
don't know I don't know I'm just saying
he's a fish what is he gonna do swim it
is food bro I'm ready oh oh oh Oprah
breathe breathe breathe breathe
Oh help us find it why how is it Kong's
here in the book Kong have you been
swimming you know a human
revolve around you Brendan are you done
complaining Evan good I have a lot of
stuff it makes me feel good but one
thing I don't have that doesn't make me
too happy I don't have a frisbee I don't
and I really want one so Evan it's gonna
drive and we're gonna go get a frisbee
so I deal with it in a minute
feeling naughty less than a week been a
week
[Music]
well we going oh we're getting it freeze
me I know that where do you get a
frisbee bro do I I don't know I'm not
afraid to be God I'm pretty close but
I'm not how could it be pretty close oh
oh whoa that guy was racist
it's dwarfism a race bro I'm pushing for
it for it to be how do you need my help
signing a petition I would help a lot
cool cool we can make that happen when
you die look like an idiot
get out hello all right sorry I need to
be in the car to go Oh bro bro bro bro
hold up hold up bro everyone stop pause
yeah I got some more why would you give
me the city pants why would you not hand
me that you know worse
you know what you're great at
complaining besides nothing yeah oh oh
don't yell at me while driving don't
yell at me when you're drunk
don't yell me what I'm telling me you
let you yell at me all right oh snap we
made it bro do you want to do the thing
you wanna do thing but we got distracted
by these dill glasses I look like a dumb
version of Harry Potter a big blond chop
see Potter
things that I will spend money on like a
lot of money on our sunglasses or
glasses it's a known fact that can find
the dopest awesomest best is pair of
flats it's true it's the only reason
he's my friend really oh can you please
this time not lose the matching glasses
that we got yeah yeah no I know last
pair glasses have been lost and it
pretty much ruined our friendship so not
this time cool buddy wait what
back to the real mission frisbee bro you
think I know the guy he's a great guy
okay it doesn't look like a frisbee
store but never judge a book by it's
cover do you guys have any frisbees
[Music]
no Michael I do it Michael bro you I do
do you know where the frisbees are no
the frisbees no the frisbees he speaks
no English damn it dude no one knows
where the frisbees are oh look look my
friend shot on his Instagram so - me
kiss you he'll get you on the mouth he's
a good kisser what in times of struggle
it's important to keep your friends
close I'm going through some stuff right
now I really just want to frisbee go to
the next door if they don't have it I
might throw Evan off the balcony I'm
just kidding I would never throw wasn't
me I would never throw you off about him
seems pretty believable no no I wouldn't
do that never but something I would do I
would potentially replace you what maybe
with like one of these roads like if you
start acting up this little scare coat
could be my new friend okay I feel good
about this section oh it's a frisbee
with no internet in ur inside yeah oh
I'm working on it look at this no we
give the holo frisbee a face this is
looking up after all wow I'm glad I
spent the majority of my day buying that
I'm actually let's frisbee isn't being
used to his full potential
[Music]
[Applause]
said I was gonna do it I'm gonna do it
Kong he's been a naughty dirty Charlie
I'm vlogging please second thing he's
been a dirty dog lately he's been
humping a lot of stuff so I'm gonna give
him a bath problem is my boy here
doesn't love water it's okay it's your
big day calm
you're getting clean one day probably in
the very near future I'm gonna be doing
this with my own bebut hopefully not the
near future is on me he's on you
maverick has landed on Brendan I repeat
the eagle has landed
actually maverick AIDS Brendan duty
attacks her to meet horrible no he's
gonna put my neck it's gonna be funny
kinda hurts so much oh damn oh gosh okay
we're safe we're fine Kong is being such
a good dog right now look you know I'm
only biding my time
good dog comes wouldn't be a sexy puppy
maybe you won't have to hump his toy
anymore and you're gonna get some
real-life girls babies also quick shots
to my dog for making my left boob wet
good job what's gonna work teamwork good
job this could mean drugs outside off my
blog and I want to hold you please
okay guys that is the vlog if you're not
a part of the family make sure you
subscribe join the love gang yo we're
freaking profit copier maverick merge go
out today be different do what you got
to do to achieve your goals link for
that is in the description bar y'all
know it look and Paul that cars last
shops I love y'all I will see you
tomorrow
[Music]