every time you kiss a dog you exchange
about ten million bacteria it's probably
twice that amount if you kiss Logan Paul
bro what done hey I know what you guys
are probably thinking
Logan you were not in the Yeti I don't
think you're in the Challenger and that
is definitely not the cool bus what are
you in I am driving a Rolls Royce ray
whoo that's a tongue twister rolls-royce
Wraith rolls-royce Wraith roll the
camera hi how are you mom you're on the
highway right now but I got to show you
this car guys I'm pulling over oh yes
honey
this thing is so beautiful sorry I'm in
love with this car sorry I'm actually
obsessed with yo-yo we look good driving
this thing
there's the Challenger with the maverick
on s'alright we got places to be
so okay you guys know my birthday is
coming up this Sunday April Fool's Day
and it's also the one year anniversary
of the Maverick brand which folks use so
much information by the way this week
only until Monday the original Maverick
t-shirts are only $10 guys we're never
doing this again off the hottest merch
in the game while you can't lo compile
that calm slash shop or link in
description also gonna be doing a big
drop for my birthday cuz it's we've gone
global at this point and the love that
you guys have shown me and the brand not
being afraid to be yourselves embracing
your differences truly from the bottom
of my heart incredible you guys inspired
me every single day but I wanted so
badly to get myself a nice gift for my
birthday so I decided to buy a Rolls
Royce but it's not this one actually I
haven't even made that decision yet guys
this isn't mine the point is I'm gonna
go to my brother's house and make my mom
and Jake think that this is a birthday
gift that I bought for myself and really
I don't even know owns this vehicle I
CEO Paulo brought it over to my house
and now we're Hawking it okay back your
brother Jake's house last time we were
here we were hugging it over the cool
bus right there
[Music]
pretty sick dude look for street cred
pretty freakin credible hey yo you can't
say what an entrance
I got show you something I wanna see I
drove that here you drove it here who
got where'd you get it
you know Sunday is your birthday no you
bought yourself no no you can only make
those jokes on April 4 other stars on
the room I could probably do donuts
right here you want to say that from
when you get one maybe bro this is I'm
this is a cool spot cool car cooler
umbrella slot oh hey yo you can drop in
oh you flash back to yesterday
my podcast coming soon on Sunday always
plug you aren't really buying this this
dick this is totally joking well he is
vlogger you know who would be really
good angle why did you drop KS eyes
YouTube channel mom you look good I'm
90% there yeah should we get Pam getting
out of the car in slow-mo yeah oh I
think yeah we have to do that I think
[Music]
and the one-year anniversary of the
maverick I come to jigsaw by yourself
Rainn Bros and other unnecessary extra
vehicles where are mine oh hi love yank
switching gears a little bit I was
browsing snapchat and you guys know they
have articles right like there's stories
topical events about pop culture etc
anyway I was looking at one and it
involved a dog like kissing a girl in
like the exchange of bacteria and it
said this every time you kiss a dog you
exchange about 10 million bacteria it's
probably twice that amount if you kiss
Logan Paul bro what done I read this and
literally I I double took I was like
what huh why don't they come after me
because of those luscious lips it's
gotta be man like look at this guy's
[Music]
anyway bro so I'm gonna see what my mom
thinks about this I have something to
show you
can you see it he put you on it over a
glass I can see hey what I say that that
was an article on snapchat why oh no I
thought it was because of his luscious
lips
they call him Lexi combination is
luscious and sexy Oh Lexi yes okay so I
sent him out if you kissed Logan ball
why why why what you're super clean wait
how do you know he's cleaned uh because
my mom raised us for one second how we
just let this slide huh no I already do
I took this matter into my own hand and
I got a doctor to come over to the house
and swab both my mouth and Coggs mouth
and see just how much bacteria is
factually exchanged
so let's flashback to when that happened
oh and so the inside of the mouth okay
and what it's checking for is overgrowth
or what bacteria right exactly how much
bacteria I have what about the dog we do
the he's pretty chill there's not much
going on in there yeah all you gonna do
is just just bend over right I don't
know yeah no hesitation there okay you
really went after it when humans and
dogs kissed do you know how much
bacteria is exchanged how much is
exchanged I would have you know I don't
have an exact number but it wouldn't be
entirely different from the exchange of
bacteria between human and human like
really making out with someone oh they
just have different bacteria because
their mouths are a lot dirtier than
human mouths yeah I would hope so I take
pride in my hygiene you know so like if
someone were to say like I would kiss
like a dog or like I have the same
bacteria in my mouth as a dog I would
like try to
not say that's true thanks bro yeah
further White's saying now we gotta get
the dog dog did his swabbing like a good
book yeah doc says I need to make out
with you to figure out the exchange of
bacteria when people kiss they exchange
bacteria right how do you how do you
figure out that number the exchanges I
read a thing that's been when humans and
dogs kissed they exchanged ten million
bacteria when the number and then and
then it's Alice who said which is
probably less than Logan Paul which is
me all right so they like hurt my feet
yeah it's never going for you yeah so
I'm just trying to like prove them wrong
do them wrong you know what I have a
feeling and you'll have a scientific
proof okay yeah because like you know
like I don't want girls singing like
it's like bad to kiss me or there's
anything because I like kissing girls
the results are in the doctor just
called me John I'm gonna call him right
now it's the doctor the good-looking
doctor oh hey what's up doc it's me LP
what's cooking good looking
I heard the results are back you that no
organisms Thank You doc doing that suing
defamation of character
I'm high genic okay check your inbox for
an email from our lawyers huh
with that said guys I do know I need a
thumbnail where I gotta get people watch
this video gotta get clues anyways I
have an idea quick though almost kiss me
but don't we're gonna black your body
out what Jesus welcome to you
the vlog have a weird one today it's not
a part of the Logan make sure to
subscribe not only do I want you to
subscribe though do me a favor also ring
the bell next to the subscribe button
because literally otherwise you might
not be notified one in both videos and
that is just no bueno
also copy yourself some maverick merge
jake has some of his closet I see over
there low calm slash shop or link in
description you guys know the original
t-shirts are $10 only now through Monday
so top the iron wallets the Rose is mine
this is a cruel joke what Evers you're
gonna leave a little believe it anyways
oh wow hey what's up good-looking oh hey
okay locating letters of luck I love you
I will see you tomorrow
[Music]