it sounded like you just said this for
six thousand dollars forty to five sixty
dollars away from six thousand dollars 6
sit in here right I'm thinking guys I
put this giant bounce house in my house
yesterday literally right at the foot of
my bed we put balls y'all quiet down I'm
vlogging you guys so yesterday's vlog
when I went to jump in I miscalculated
and broke my $20,000 chandelier yes my
how did I know I wasn't using my brain
oh yeah it's been rendered useless
because there's shards of glass at the
bottom but that's not gonna stop ya for
sure there's glass in my back if you're
not a butt of the low gang make sure to
subscribe - my name is Logan Paul my job
is to out / everywhere it's to distract
you from your daily life y'all got busy
life and I'm here to hopefully make you
laugh and smile now today's vlog have a
weird one guys because if you haven't
noticed it's kind of dark out we are
starting Lee had meetings the whole
morning kind of build the Maverick
Enterprise you know how it is House
immersed in the game look at all that
come / ah good morning boy you guys saw
yesterday we got a maverick desk in sup
oh honey got the reclaimed wood we got
the metal leg we got Kong the savage
good moaning dougie
we got Evan ever come back come back
everybody moaning Mike we got Colin
again good morning but ya new table is
coming in the garage you guys know we
are starting a talk show a podcast soon
it's called impulsive because I'm
impulsive it also calls my last name Oh
oh my god so yeah you guys would do like
a full garage Oh mom I gotta keep this a
secret this show is gonna be so good I
shouldn't even be showing you guys we
got blue carpet was doing stuff all day
I worked out this morning 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
8 9 10 11 12 13 14 for my body and it's
Logan I know you're having some trouble
today and there's a lot of people out
there who will say no you can't
yes
sometimes the vlogs where we just mess
around sometimes they're the best
there's a game that's called fortnight
now I know someone actually one of my
best friends who plays it every single
day and it's that what did you say to me
like a week ago I said Logan do you want
to change the do you want to let's dream
game Oh
video game so Evans like yo you should
stream on Twitch
I'm like bro dude I don't play video
games Evan for a very good reason back
in the seventh grade Evan I was addicted
my parents would beat my ass with belts
I'm exaggerating that's what it felt
like when they would rip me away from my
literally rip me away from my computer
bro I was up to video games but then I
see Drake playing for night on Twitter
with the student ninja he's a ninja he's
very good at fortnight who did G bro
what I want to play for tonight with
Drake how am i screw it I haven't been
telling me to do it whoa stop torturing
my dog he does yeah I just feel like
he's sexually frustrated yes bro Holmes
right there is Kong and Coco to be
honest any one of these rocks I feel it
could be dog coming off the blue rope
Logan throws a right jab let's pick up a
case I thought AJ I am gonna knock you
out
I also think we finished the contract
today that's good I'm sure you guys will
hear about that in upcoming days or so
what I want to say is the point of this
is we're gonna go to the store and
actually get equipment for me to I guess
start to try and game again I want to
build his PC you're gonna build me a
computer yep yeah ro I my grandfather
plays PC video yep what can we just talk
about this in the car could we go okay
yeah by the way you guys know what that
means
[Music]
this could be a bad idea dog like what
if I get addicted what if the daily vlog
stop because I'm addicted because of
your recommendation yeah what if you
gain like 200 pounds this could destroy
me get on the road gives us so much
camera what's more important getting us
there live or capturing constant for the
best blog chatter yeah guys make sure to
go subscribe to my twitch channel at
yeah I don't have a twitch handle we
gotta get one by the end it's foggy in
here bro I have to keep the air off so
we can do it for the vlog oh you know
you've been complaining a lot about us
filming oven I'm leaving the interior
subscribe man twitch look I thought I
would come up with it out there that was
my motivation this place is pretty tight
lights green whoa
[Music]
an electronic store or an art exhibit yo
seriously this place is crazy what are
these installations
Evan since I have no idea what I'm doing
and also I'm very confused why this
store looks like an art gallery do you
want to help me out at all you know what
are the chances of these turns into like
a transformer or something this one
looks like a stormtrooper
yo that'll be rode forward how much
money he won't spend I don't know looks
like a child locator Mike see if those
are there I'm following you have I'm
close behind you bro I'm pedaling right
now I'm pedaling I'm so excited to gain
this says gaming on it gave me 300 you
have you ever game yeah it's extreme you
dummy we'll take five anyway more this
is like the brain alright of your PC
this is where everything connects to
somebody's got to have a brain cuz you
know it Amy am i right whoa gaming
motherboard bro it's like the mother
I've never had morning family
good morning family so funny is this the
type of technology that I'm dealing with
he's that glove this is truly remarkable
and the mice
mouse a miles and a mouse that doubles
is a cell phone mom oh good morning
family good morning Pamela hey Spencer I
noticed you've been getting close to my
face and I have a rash as you can see
guys I don't know a rash has been
breaking out so maybe just stay wide all
right okay maybe stay there making me
self-conscious
oh god no what's going on over here
Jesus no you can't your dog is just you
brought a pee pad for her justkeep maybe
put on the floor not on the desk you
know subscribe to me on Twitch at let's
stay wide stay wide stay wide Stan why I
lost my freakin child I didn't think
this would happen you hear about this
and the stories help me find my child
child locator they're grenade shaped
ketchup and mustard dispensers and these
things are about to blow up stay wide
Spencer got me the tower oh this is
crazy
yeah so you see like these bubbles and
like this too [ __ ] yeah don't put that
in please oh my god oh you're right yeah
it's true kids the dream is coming true
as we speak it's me Logan Paul in to my
left to work mom would you guys like a
picture or maybe some merch subscribe me
on Twitch
I don't have a twist name bro what's the
beaver Dorf underscore mama I'm plugging
my Twitter this is bull you've been
taking those acting classes do you
actually good came in as Logan's new
roommate I'm finished friend
so that was sick oh you're my man dude
super pumped which one do you want yeah
like one what your buttons on well you
can call your mom hello good morning
Pamela good morning Pamela come on oh
you know about the game get serious look
at this one this is truly remarkable oh
look it's Mike hey Mike
just looking at my smashes I don't know
I don't know we're looking at things
wrong I gotta be a gamer yo Mike ever
had something to say to you doc
complaining or you're walking home yeah
I'm kidding guy this is like one of the
hardest decisions of my life choosing a
keyboard using a mouse using all these
different things and Evan said he would
help me I feel you to close the gloves
oh wow Gaming is so fun oh my god I just
feel like I'm in over my head
we got two carts full of stuff or a game
that I don't even know if I'm good at I
don't even know if I'll like it like I'm
not gonna be good right away but like a
vegetable I'm gonna aim for the top of
those fortnight ranking eventually bro
I'll be number one guys you can
subscribe to my twitch
[Music]
I'm sorry sounded like you just said
this for $6,000 42 560 dollars away from
$6,000 sick bro think about me bro I'm a
gamer first sure I'm a gamer and you can
subscribe to my twitch chat we've been
here for like two hours yeah I really
hope this pays off I really hope I like
this I have all you gotta do is ask for
help
I got this come on let me do it put it
back I'm growing gray pubic hair I've
ever smelled
[Applause]
[Music]
dirty husband so you got cuz you have to
build this thing for me yep all of this
Jesus Christ also guys my name is Logan
Paul right but Logan Paul was taken so
then I made my twitch handle Logan Paul
was taken oh yeah guys subscribe to my
twitch which is now yeah Logan Paul was
taken as Evan explained to me you will
have a chance to not only talk with me
but you guys can play with me so that
should be fun I uh first got to get
pretty good at this game and I'm going
to yell when I dive into something I've
become the best
I'm just saying bro ninja I've done that
bro I know the gamer community goes hard
yeah
hello gang that's the vlog like I said
but
weird one today a lot of stuff going on
if you're not a part of us make sure to
subscribe join the family smash that
button copy yourself some have emerged
on the hottest softest merch in the game
we do it a little bit different right
when they go right we go left when they
go up we go right so we're not expecting
that we're your local ball knock on /off
make sure you subscribe to his twitch
link for that will also be in
description oh gee I gotta get better at
this Logan I love you
[Music]
female you find yourself if you find
yourself female