bah-bah-bah your boy is getting fast hey
oh good morning low Gregg what god damn
it's good to see you guys YouTube has
been boring lately I am not gonna lie so
a lot of updates guys I will get into it
but first if you are not a part of the
low gang make sure to subscribe smash
the button hit it in the face like I'm
going to make ksi in the face on August
25th hey also a little news flash will
update the Maverick hoodies are 20% off
for this weekend holiday things sale all
what I'm trying to say is maverick
hoodies and you guys know they go fast
are 20% off for this week only is that
fourth of July sale yo respect give me a
little uptown right here
hot damn hot damn I'm feeling sexy oh oh
mercy so hot it gives my videographer
direction oh man Logan Paul iconic slash
shop or link in description anyway
speaking of ksi
do you guys remember last year I had a
meet-up in Dubai and looked like this
yep you know the low gang is strong well
anyways guys recently JJ had a meet-up
there as well and it yeah just was not
the same
[Applause]
Oh not a good look man that's
embarrassing and it's a make it even
worse the low gang showed up and started
chanting Walmart at him
yeah man that's rough that's rough
August 25th is gonna be rough for you
honestly guys I came to a realization
lately he's been doing a lot of talking
I've been doing a lot of talking I think
I'm gonna take a step back a little bit
cuz I'm extremely confident and I'm at
the point where I'm gonna let my actions
speak for me now and by actions I mean
my fist punching JJ in the face
repetitively over and over again get
your fight tickets Lincoln bio ok
rewinding a bit more a couple weeks back
I went back to my hometown of Cleveland
Cleveland Ohio and I visited Jake while
he was on tour
[Music]
what are you doing I don't know I heard
you're performing in our hometown and I
used to live here with you actually so I
figured I'd go back and say what's good
bro wait the real are you performing
tonight yeah are you gonna perform on me
before but you have to perform if you're
here you have to perform they are love
your own the 11 you remember lyrics
he'll know how Joe so let's make amends
and be bro silly about the wall sleep
bro I was on a fight the bowl gosh-darn
day and they expect me to come here and
sing a song that I don't know the lyrics
to I can't even speak because I was
yelling at [ __ ] boy oh it's family
[Music]
we gotta go on and look a 5min finish
I'm learning the lyrics prom night this
is not a joke like I forgot all of them
I'm not gonna move on and so should
y'all I will pick them up if he falls
after all it's the rise of the pawls bro
what's up guys got a maverick in about
I'm gonna beat his ass
[Music]
[Applause]
know that I'm so sorry
but things that I said I just want to be
friends so let's make amends
[Music]
[Applause]
so that was pretty cool guys I gotta say
growing up there I never expected to be
where we are now I always believed in
myself but doing that and performing in
front of our fans in our hometown that's
some magical that's the magical right
there
and then while I was there I went back
and I visited my old high school
wrestling coach you guys I don't know if
you know this but we're actually filming
a documentary about everything that's
happened this year all the stuff that
went down in January where I was at in
my life and kind of the psyche of what
actually happened which includes my
upbringing so I visited the high school
wrestling team give a little speech to
the kids Logan what are we about to do
right now you know back in the old high
school I just say we're up to the old
code to check out the way we roll by god
it's really remarkable you know when I
was at school
[Music]
I didn't think I'd ever get to meet you
well let's going down right now kids
nowadays need inspiration right there
need people to look up to people to
motivate them I'm about to give these
these youngsters some words of wisdom
coming from YouTube's biggest charge
hello I was honored to have and I mean
it like that my staff we were honored to
have Logan on our team not because of
his talent as a wrestler because his
talent is as good people when we went to
the state tournament his junior year on
the way down to the state tournament in
the van
Logan was studying the entire time time
I'm not this it's giving me goosebumps
he was one of our best and he rustled
well to get a four a Ford truck a full
ride scholarship and the University his
very hard right coach you don't give him
out Logan got all his money to go to
college on his academics but could have
been football and wrestling too so Logan
it's on you now
hey guys what's up
yeah thanks for the thanks for the
phrasing hi guys
I think wrestling was about setting
goals it depends it depends what you
want to do if you me this sport was
about working hard pushing yourself
being the best you can possibly be and I
set my goals high right away right off
the bat I said I wanted to be the state
champ
that's the session what happened I
trained my ass off on Sunday when we
didn't have practice I was still working
out when I wasn't working out I was
studying because as as much as you don't
like to hear it it is important to
balance both school and athletics if you
feel yourself liking the sport and
feeling it feel yourself growing as a
human being because of it stick with it
yeah it's hard but it was easy everyone
would do it so stick with the sport and
you guys do great things
and then you know you know we're taking
no days off
[Music]
oh no no but he don't know what he's in
for
he think is a joke what we're gonna do
we're gonna joke around your joke ksi
you ain't working hard you don't know
how to throw punches you don't hit hard
you ain't strong you went fast
you ain't good-looking most importantly
I'm good-looking
I'm the greatest I don't multiply Oh got
our ass in the gym trained my dick off
uh yeah no longer having so working on
it and then lots of travel guys our next
stop was a for a bachelor party for my
friend Hyundai
Hey next stop Sun Valley Idaho for my
friend Andy's bachelor party I've never
been to Idaho I know it's the home of
the potato so yeah really looking
forward to a lot of fun
ha
[Applause]
Wow
it's my first bachelor party girl no I
ain't getting married dude I'm in the
wedding I'm so excited this is like a
great bachelor first bachelor party only
if you have potatoes oh holy crap I know
it's amazing
get us all in this sweet pea it's good
old Roadmaster she always takes care of
this is how you pick up those Idaho
potatoes is this how you pick up the
Idaho's
finally here in Sun Valley Idaho home of
the potato did I mention let me show you
what outside looks like damn Andy this
is amazing
must be nice to be rich skew Annie it's
my bachelor party here thank you I'm
actually very poor ah it's really just
stunning I don't know what else to say
powers can actually appear and some have
been known to float oh you can actually
feel the CH I don't what the hell is
this oh my bandana smells like ah Andy
no crystals
what doesn't Idaho have women women
Idaho's stop it no no no they got
everything including Hot Springs I don't
know it's weird for me to not have done
something but I've never been in a hot
spring Andy what is a hot spring
so basically kids it is where the water
Lee the Science Guy and they cause it's
sulfur right from the earth it's like
science lessons kid hey don't let your
parents say you don't want anything from
these vlog soulfood it's almost as worse
as can't sighs bandana Oh solver no way
it's hot in there it's about to get
steamy
[Music]
no no this is like burning fat what's up
fast oh this is crazy I will say good
thing I still got some of the hottest
march in the game on otherwise I would
be freezing how does the earth decide to
make my ass hot hottest thing in this
where you can see the heat coming off
the mobile yeah that's a hot spot and I
ain't talking Wi-Fi
[Music]
that's your party just kind of real with
that
[Music]
well after running through the river
naked and singeing our asses off we
figure the next best thing to do was go
out and shoot some skeet that's some
good form it's all about the form after
all I do play fortnight so I know what
I'm doing he's already got the redneck
in him got news for you anywhere in
Idaho huh mom Jake boo I'm not gonna
[Music]
want you to do on this next one let's
just hit the target okay that's it
that's it Wow thanks for the advice well
nothing like golf and a bachelor party
ain't that right on day Sportiva well
activity aren't we doing this is the
best bachelor party yeah yeah they
didn't do you have it do you even have a
driver's license bro no you driven one
of these right
Oh is the whole idea
[Music]
we gotta save it yo you gotta get off
the course this balls coming over here
it's not safe here Oh attacking me ah
oh hell the dogs are attacking me I have
a dog I know what'll get them off the
course simple dog behavior dogs love
balls
[Music]
how to trust the British kid drive
mister y'all be careful
[Music]
that stance is truly truly magnificent
Wow there you go yep that was actually
good your shirts off now so it's more
aerodynamic I hope it helps you feel the
wind on my ballsack well your pants are
still on so I'm not sure how that's
happening holy Sh
Logan if you get on one I'll hire
someone to personally please you the
level of suck today is general we all
need immense amount of work
oh yeah this round has gotten out of
hand
Logan what just happened bro rogue drone
chase nice job there's golf courses
right there bro that's Andy's drone that
changes everything bro he's been flying
it around the whole time like just
watching us play golf that's weird
you know what respect thanks keep the
safe got you bro you know what happened
to the driver though oh no II know I
thought it was chasing us I swear Andy
Andy Andy working my wing no you you I
look yes with the propellers no yeah
dude chop suey
I thought I don't know bro you know me
always trying to protect the herd no but
one thing about Logan he always gives
you a new drone if you bring yourself
gotta be adults about this right I'm
actually proud I'm actually not angry
I'm actually very proud that like the
drone was able to actually like do that
deal what about me my sniping dude yeah
what you hit it missing the day broke
Bad News Bears fella
nope not good you know the driver you
gave us that was not cut in half now if
now it is cut in half okay clean clean
in half drone came and I was dabbing and
who knows to know so how can I pay here
be gonna be around tomorrow
well he's supposed to leave tomorrow at
11:00 but I have friends here yeah that
was a crazy weekend we did leave some
stuff off camera Andy I have a question
he's right here by the way guys um what
did you figure out the club situation
did you pay the guy back
he's in it oh no where you go back then
I'll show my face yeah we'll work on it
anyways guys that is the vlog I'm sorry
that I've not been posting as much I've
been training my ass off and this
actually little vacation here is the
last little bit of fun I have before we
go into a SuperDrive mode tunnel vision
mode focusing on the fight so guys if
you're not part of the low game make
sure to subscribe to end the strongest
family on YouTube and also copied your
maverick merch slogan fall back on slash
shop or link in description it is the
hottest softest merch in the game is 20%
off on hoodies this week as you know our
hoodies are lit and we just drop five of
t-shirts and a brand new blue hoodie
anyways guys I freaking love you bro
and I'll see you next week yeah we stand
oh we do it's done all we do is done
yeah we start all we do is done all we
do is done yeah we start all we do is
done all we do is done doing stunts only
all we doing boys ready over here