are you okay hi yeah i had a question i
know this is like
pretty weird logan said he's with you
right now i just had like a super weird
feeling about it are you with him you're
telling me you don't think i could do
this that's a big
hop you can do this man that's my own
dad saying i could do it
we're going all the way up
[Music]
have you ever used a telescope before
you should look into it
okay did you hear about the kidnapping
at school
i'm not even taking part of any joke
that has to do with kidnapping
no no it's okay it's okay he woke up
kidnapping
there was a guy whose whole left side of
his body was cut off is it because
he heard your joke no he's all right now
you know this game no oh my god kevin
you go like this
i see lance 210 do it this is where
we're at with content all right
boys i spent 750 on rubber chickens
[Music]
i've decapitated them hey can you guys
say this for me
sign name cuff no no you say it then you
say okay psy name cuff
sigh name cuss you're gonna play
backwards
[ __ ] me and y'all what do you think you
said [ __ ] to my eyes
[Laughter]
you wouldn't ask baby logan get out of
here
we about to test the loyalty of the
[ __ ] boys i'm gonna have josie call
my friends
and basically ask if i'm with them and
if they're my boys like hopefully
they'll have my back and like live for
me i'm gonna call mack first
my [ __ ] best friend since
kindergarten hold on
hi uh so super random logan said he was
with you
and i just kind of have a weird feeling
are you with logan right now no i just
uh just happened to shower
i'm playing video games right now as in
like you're not
with him no i was with him before but we
went to
uh me and amber went to dinner and so we
left you so at the house i don't know
what he did that's weird he said he was
with you like like recently
like within the past like 30 minutes
do you know where he is oh i literally
just got out of the shower man you [ __ ]
do you possibly know where where he is
or oh sorry i'll be playing video game
hey evan it's me everybody loves me
george janko you [ __ ] don't let me down
hi you okay
hi yeah i had a question i know this is
like pretty weird logan said he's with
you right now
i just had like a super weird feeling
about it are you with him
yeah but he's taking your [ __ ] are you
good i've never had you call me yeah
you're with him you swear
yeah i mean he's taking a [ __ ] on the
phone if you want yeah can you can you
handle the phone yeah
this is for the vlog
[Music]