[Applause]
[Music]
hey yo what's up lo gang welcome to
YouTube jeopardy that is right trivia
about your favorite YouTube social media
network categories including music Jake
Paul drama more drama and viral this
might be one of the best videos we've
ever done on this channel so make sure
to subscribe also you might notice we're
sitting on the set of our new podcast
called impulsive hop coming very very
soon so also make sure to subscribe to
the impulsive podcast channel the link
for that is in the description we're
gonna be doing three a week about
awesome anyways here are the rules the
contestants are gonna pick a category
and if you win you get the point if you
lose you get waxed waxed that's right
every single hair who's that woman
oh oh that's gonna be the lady waxing
you hi armpits chest hair leg hair
everything's getting waxed today also if
a maverick sticker is revealed under the
question as seen here guys if you get
the question right not only do you get
the points but then I get waxed as well
incredible idea whoever gets the most
points wins one of our brand new
maverick rows hoodies as seen here on my
boat where all my Mavericks out there by
far one of the sexiest pieces of clothes
we've ever dropped available now and
Logan Paul calm slash shop I'm not gonna
lie folks it's a big deal okay it's a
big skinned ale what a second place get
absolutely nothing
contestants include the entire Maverick
house aka my roommates film dispenser
dwarf Mamba and at hey Big Mike
Alex call me Alex one more free time I'm
a millennial Brahma dumbass let's get
started
let's start it off the right way I'll
take drama for 200 Alex drama for 200
who was the most hated youtuber of 2018
based on who's is calculate at Logan
Paul dude that is correct that sucks
that sucks okay all right Evan what's
the category bro I'm gonna go with more
drama for to woo PewDiePie was almost
passed in subscribers by this YouTube
account this sounds like a wax to me bro
you super vegan wax I don't know I mean
answer I need an answer TV T Fuu blows T
series so sorry Evan hoppip on the table
you're getting waxed friend yo T Fuu you
ready to come waxes
[Applause]
and okay moving on your ups I'm ready
Jake Paul for 200 solid Jake Paul
recently beat who in a boxing match
who is dead G oh sorry the correct
answer is K s i--'s little brother next
question
400 in the viral category please viral
for 400 ooh what is the most viewed
video on YouTube the most viewed video
on YouTube is charlie bit my finger
sorry that is incorrect the correct
answer is despot Seto oh wait that's me
Seto how many like four billion bro
sounded like you like you sound like a
turtle when it's mating I'm going music
for 400
I'm never stickers so guys if Evan gets
this question right that means I get
waxed what is the official name of this
diss track I'm gonna play it for you
however due to copyright I'm gonna play
about one second of it into my eBay
channel later this evening to buy this
strip of logan paul's armpit hair for
starting bid of $1600 all right I'm
gonna go Jake Paul for 600 what is the
name of the hottest softest merch in the
game is it this can't be like a trick oh
it's under Jay Paul maverick by Logan
Paul
I hate this game girl this is a horrible
idea
does that mean the lead that does put
you in the lead Spencer has 600 points
evan has 400 and mike has 200
I'll take viral for a thousand Alex whoa
he's really going for it on there that's
three times in a row what is the word
stated in this 2018 popular soundbite
you know how much trouble I've had with
this in the past
oh I know is it is it that is incorrect
like the creatures Laurel everyone knows
that hop up on the table under chin no
Mike's got some brows why dude he's
getting nervous I do i what are you
doing eyebrow you do I would do two
strips do two strips two strips
[Music]
go to drama 4000 oh my god bold
statistically that that doesn't make any
sense
oh my god this is an easy one to name
the most popular YouTube breakup of 2018
odd who is david dobrik and eliza oh no
this is so close to my wiener and i
don't like it i don't like this one bit
[Music]
Danny said there's six there's two more
maverick stickers aka
me bro if you get another one dawg
straight up I'm quitting YouTube you're
up spins I'm gonna stick to the trend
I'm gonna go Jake Paul for a thousand Oh
[Music]
thank God all right here's the question
actually Jake is here because this house
is currently burning down in Calabasas
can we get Jake in the room for this
question welcome to YouTube jeopardy
describe three of Jake Paul's tattoos a
sword is that correct that's correct
yeah
a bow and arrow oh he got two out of
three that's correct the third is the
t-rex Thank You Jake appreciate your
help man hope your hostel stays up Jake
Jake Jake Mike once again it's all on
you viral for 200 viral for 200 what is
the name of Shane Dawson's most recent
documentary series that is incorrect the
correct answer is inside the mind of
Jake Paul you said part of it
a little more drama for downs dang bro
you're already in the lead that's not
true
dang bro the popular gamer called ninja
recently came down with what deathly
illness what is that is correct
let's spice it up I'm gonna go viral in
2007 which animal dramatically reacted
to this sound squirrel so close the
correct answer was chip
dude way worse Sam that is clean I'm
gonna take viral because I've been so
good in that category up-to-date for 800
please what is the name of the viral
sensation known as the Walmart yodeling
boy Ramsay Reverend Ramsay that is
correct
music 4,000 big bows on this one huh
finish the following song lyric I got ha
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm gonna do music for 800 England is
who's the city Nick Crompton who was
responsible for little taze horrible
behavior her brother
Wow to be more John Myatt on let's go
big I knew it was bad I knew so sure
you're not gonna get this which youtuber
made the worst apology video ever
the correct answer is laura-leigh that's
not the one where there's like spit
leaving her mouth yeah Rosie was like
crying and it's bad
[Applause]
film dispenser Europe I got a knock down
the last 800 so Jake Paul for 800 please
name 4x members of team 10 Cade Tessa
Brooks
Alisa violet
Nik Crompton good job that is correct
Wow kid went to Jake Paul University or
something he's gotta have a freaking
answer with that correct answer and this
just got really interesting Spencer you
have 3200 and Evan you have 3400 it's
tight bro it's real tight like Evans now
cleanly shaven butthole I'll take more
drama for 2,000 please in what country
was rice gum accused of being a racist
ladies and gentlemen the answer to that
question is that is correct
how second in third place for your
[ __ ] so Mike's in the lead actually
with 3,800 now honey of music for 600 Oh
complete the name of this song it's
every day that is incorrect
the correct answer is it's every night
sis rice comes dis track against Jake
Paul right Spence your turn good call
good which Paul brother recently got out
of a relationship that is incorrect the
correct answer is Jake Paula
can we eat it Webster that mention for
reason recently at a recent time come on
[Laughter]
you're an ace okay with that guys we are
going to cut to a quick commercial break
we will be right back
[Music]
introducing the all-new maverick by
Logan Paul roses hoodie available in
multiple sizes ed we're back with only
four questions left to go I'm not gonna
lie I'm a little nervous there is one
maverick sticker left Mike you are up
like drama for 400 when you hear that
this youtuber laughs you want to cut
your ears off that is incorrect
the correct answer is ksi and here's
this poor old man spends his entire life
discussing drama between Millennials
[Music]
it's tied Mike and Evan both have 3,800
Spence you have 3,200 it's your call so
he can't win so technically should we
each do one more no why don't we give it
Spence the chance to tie it and give him
both those okay and then we while we
split the hoodie three ways yeah Jake
Paul for 400 Jake Paul became notorious
last year after doing what yeah that's
correct okay so that's that's 400 points
when Jake Paul with his pull I'm fine
do you understand if you get this
question right it's a three-way tie how
did that how did that work I like that
it's weird it's always a tie with you it
seems like what is the stage name of
this rapper
it's big but it's not good all right
guys thank you for playing YouTube
jeopardy I'm honestly gonna wax to my
other arm papers yeah I did this really
low gang I love you guys like it
subscribe go for it
[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations to the winners you each
get to somehow split three ways this
maverick Rose hoodie available now if
you're not a part of the low gang gang
gang skirt make sure to subscribe and if
this video gets half a million likes I
think we're gonna do another one of
these next week with a different
punishment thank you guys for watching I
will see you next time do not forget to
subscribe to the impulsive podcast
channel link for that is in the
description we are starting a podcast
very soon I love you guys and I will see
you soon take it easy
[Music]
introducing the all-new Brava