do I hate you back to another episode of
YouTube jeopardy my name is Logan Paul I
am your host we have our contestants
including Spencer Taylor dwarf Mamba and
Mike may lack pays off fish
[Music]
got our lovely lady hos GG what's your
Instagram G what just say it Juliana
Rossi me hit that subscribe blend if
you're not part of the low gang gang
gang skirt this is a big YouTube
jeopardy today guys the winner of
today's youth through jeopardy gets an
all-expense-paid trip to a destination
of your choice what an all-expense-paid
trip true dip the stakes are very high
today if you get your question right you
get the designated points however if you
get your question wrong I have here dog
shock collars all of you to put around
your necks really quick that's my god if
the winner doesn't fuss to get a free
vacation I'll put that shock call up
your ass you guys reveal a maverick
sticker under the letter under the
number and you get the question right
and I get shocked do you have one -
where - yeah man that's why there's four
your hand why'd you have the trigger the
Maverick House for 200 name of the slap
champion who I would have faced off
against in Russia whose dumpling that's
correct
do enter points to Mike
have your up you [ __ ] up 200 you've
stuck for 200 let's go so if advocates
this one right and I get shocked in the
beauty guru who gave some bomb head on
the coachella ferris wheel that is
correct let's go messed up press the why
on the right no I put it way too high
[Music]
bet sir you're up Africa's for 400 the
Maverick ops for 400 color of the new
maverick hoodie drop and we're king
consumers find it read and Logan Paul
calm /op god that's easy stops emerging
the game
Oh champ you're up Mike well get your
foot band off the trigger loss we ought
to control your concerts our youtuber
put it down please I'll take drama for
200 Jimmy Charles will be boxing who on
the next case Ivers Logan Paul undercard
Tati that's correct
use it for 200 which famous
atlanta-based rapper is actually of
British descent correct
[Music]
maverick house for 600 please which
roommate [ __ ] on the roof last week
mmm I know it wasn't you unfortunately
you're unfortunately it wasn't you was
that man right there
Andre that's correct hey congratulations
by the way on dragged you hear it no you
didn't hear it I'll take more drama 800
what's good oh you're really going for
it what is the birth name of the gamer
who recently filed a lawsuit against
faze clan Turner that is correct
I hope that all gets worked out guys Wow
Wow
this MMA fighter who just broke his face
in 90 places bird next question maverick
house 800 got a set of balls on you kid
within 20,000 how many followers does
our new puppy at ginger the Giant have
on Instagram oh oh god this is not good
360 that is incorrect or drop 4,000 name
a washed-up youtuber jenna Marbles
five years ago check your views Ertz
they're still very high congratulations
Jennifer you should have kept in your up
more drama to honey or drama for 200
name the animal that took the life of my
beloved Pomeranian song to savage
absolute I goddamn [ __ ] coyote that's
correct
good job and by the way by the way if
there's any coyotes watching this bus
coming for you I will find you that will
kill you that's all right I'm gonna
redeem myself the Maverick house for a
thousand please the Maverick house for
one thousand according to the internet
see what is my net worth 19 million
that's correct yeah
[Applause]
that's not true maybe at one point for
this man I just need monetary things hey
Google talking to you
so far the current standings Spencer you
have 2000 way to go
Evan 200 man not really sure what's
going on there and Mike you [ __ ] out
the first one and I didn't have that one
third standing Spencer you have 2000
Evan you got 600 points and Mike you
have 2200 Mike is in the lead right now
and we got a Mike you are uh I'll take
drama for a thousand Alex drama for 1000
the name of tannaz ex who wants to box
my brother is what is how you're asking
me the name of tannaz ex wants the box
my brother who is Brad Souza okay Justin
Bieber all I can tell you sit down I
need a final answer
who is Justin Bieber that is great you
you said Brad Souza I clicked it and he
held it off his neck because I changed
my answer I said final answer you gave
me the chance
I'm actually not gonna give you the
points but you got you to get shot I got
a half a shot stakes are high on this
one Evan if you get it right I get
shocked
what rapper is facing the death penalty
for alleged allegedly murdering his two
friends YB and Nelly Y&W Melly first
where's the walk from the set of
impulsive let me tell you something I'm
still what you'll step in my editor is
gonna step in forever it's my other
Haden you're editing this video yeah
yeah exactly
oh great better up music for a thousand
please alright music for a thousand
Mavericks there we go
so I like to see ah miss Billy Eilish is
full name I'm screwed absolutely screwed
her full name Billie Jean Eilish your
full name is actually Billie Eilish
pirate bear dokkan shut the [ __ ] an
okay it's a question asks a lie you're
lying man take drama 300 Alex drama for
the gamer Pro Jared cheated on his wife
most likely because he resembles which
creature yes this is the only question
and I have more drama
six-hundred please more drama for 600
what is wrong with the popular extreme
youtuber mr. beast what is wrong with
him what's wrong with him there's
nothing wrong with him that's correct
you [ __ ] up for 800 you [ __ ] up for
800 a scientific term for an extremely
small penis my craw penis that's correct
yeah I'll take music for 800 Alex music
for 800 what can people tell lil nas ex
can't tell him they can't tell nothing
that's 400 please I'm not getting hurt
so bad I haven't seen someone hit the
ground like that since I got the dude
you slapped NASA recently announced
humans are headed where to the moon
that's great one this socks dude who
voiced Pikachu in the new Pokemon movie
Ryan Reynolds that's correct
I'm lucky on that one Spencer 3418 1600
Mike 3,800 you're also in first place by
400 coin dropped eight drama for 600
it's the only way Spencer could beat me
if I win it it's a trap cousin of Rob
Dyrdek drama
was a guest on impulsive what is his
real name hey no why Chris Chris I'll
give that to you I'll give that to cuz I
feel bad he's name is Chris Pass good
job good job good job
they'd be consistent gonna go with more
drama for 400 more drama for 400 named
Jake Paul's new girlfriend / side King
not a monkey yes no nose no nose
scholars maintain the translation was
lost years ago my arch rival ksi is
currently on tour for his album why are
the venues so small
he's [ __ ] that is true but the correct
answer is actually music but he is a bit
well that's not the reason the reason
the product isn't there hi there's one
question left
I'm just gonna shout it out loud if you
say if you get it right without getting
around I'm not gonna shock you if you
get it right I'm gonna give you a
thousand points a thousand points that's
a little ridiculous I've been working my
ass off I know yeah well rules are rules
drama for 400 this cyberbully recently
got confronted by Jake Paul alright
final score Hayden with 2000 Spencer
with 3400 and Mike coming in first place
with 4400 [ __ ] that's incredible via
metrics a stuff never won anything about
life I want to take my mom I want to
take my dad for the intelligence on
things for the
I'm like you get all-expense-paid trip
to wherever you want where you gonna go
well I Drive dancers right now now but
can I trade it for a pair of off-white
sneakers I wanna prescribe but if you're
not subscribed we love you we hope you
love you too jeopardy if you did leave a
comment below tell you like give this
video a thumbs up so I can please get
back
[Music]