hey everybody
it's me YouTube's bad boy I know I need
to shave my beard I know I look like a
homeless man I know I've been gone for a
while but I'm back with bad news um my
appeal got denied I can't say I did not
see this coming and for those of you who
do not know my appeal I appealed the two
points that the ref took away from me
and my boxing fight against ksi which is
the reason I lost so ksi has officially
without a question or doubt won the
fight against me you know it's not great
I mean you know if I'm being honest it
stings I hate to lose it mostly stings
though because I shot myself in the foot
like I quite literally only lost because
of my actions shoutout to Andy Foster in
the California State Athletic Commission
for giving this the due diligence that I
think it deserved but even they said in
their denial of the appeal I followed
some of your comments in social media
and you stated that you don't feel like
you lost or something to that effect
this may be because you won the rounds
with points by two judges you lost this
boxing contest due to the files
committed in the subsequent point
deduction ksi won the match under the
rules of the Commission you were ahead
on two cards thank you for the chapstick
Danny
but ksi won the net points due to point
deductions from the PUF productions from
the files you committed just yet another
case of like literally it's I took an L
in life only because of me and I even
said this before the fight I understood
that case I was in the ring with me but
the only person I was really fighting
against was myself and I lost that fight
so I'm optimistic for the day where I
can stop being my own worst enemy and
become my biggest supporter because once
again I've shot myself in the foot you
know it's disappointing but I'll move on
I'll live and I will be fighting again
and next time hopefully I don't make
myself lose the fight so ksi congrats
bro anyways there's good news this video
is sponsored hey I got a sponsor this
video sponsored it brought you by raid
shadow legend right is the sensation of
the mobile world it's gonna they're
calling it the RPG that changes
everything it's super popular it got
like 50 million downloads in the last
six months it's a hero collection
turn-based game with over 400 champions
for you to collect and personally
customized raid is also one of the top
three ranked rpgs on the Google Play
Store and it's just been nominated as a
finalist for Google play's best of two
nineteen user Choice Award you could
gather orcs undead Knights elves and
more assemble a team from 16 heroic
factions explore 1 million + champion
build and claim glory in the PvP arena
there's the best part dude it's free
some extra cool features in the game
multi battle auto mode weekly
tournaments and events the game is
growing super fast and check out the
school roadmap that they've published
they actually have huge plans for
updates in the game for over six months
a new faction a tag team arena feature
and even a new clan boss you can fight
with your clan mates so guys go to the
video description and click on the
special links and you will get 50,000
silver and a free epic champion as part
of the new player program to start your
Jordan wow yeah ok so this video I
wanted to show you guys or tell you guys
what I was thinking on the night of the
fight I knew if I don't make this video
now I probably never will and for
everyone wondering what it's like to
compete in what might be the biggest
internet event of 2019 boxing
professionally for the first time in
front of like what like 15,000 people at
the Staples Center it's absolutely
insane also there's some things that
we're going through my head that you
definitely didn't know about that I'm
gonna tell you about now and just kind
of iterate my thoughts so I go to do my
ring walk Bieber's behind me but somehow
he gets like drowned out because every
everyone's so tight it's such like a
tight walkway and I'm trying to like
stay focused but at one point I'm
literally almost walking sideways not to
mention if you look in my eyes you can
pretty much see death I'm sick as
[ __ ] like under my eyes like blue and
purple ksi does his ring walk he's got
this big big red cloak and a face mask
he's got you can barely see him I'm
literally out here first professional
boxing match representing my country
wearing red white and blue and I'm
getting hella goosebumps and also
wondering how the [ __ ] am I about to
pull this off given the fact that I can
barely breathe this is super telling
right here and I didn't see him at this
point but just looking back right here
it's so obvious to me that he was in the
zone like my man is in flow state he's
focused he's locked and he's even
talking to himself right now
it looks like he's saying I want this I
want this and I've always said this
about ksi the dude just like he's got
this like sick mental toughness that
probably contributes to a lot of his
success and his success on this night
but this man just wanted it and look
it's just evident how focused he is so
they bring us to the center and I'm
definitely locked in it I'm not not
focused like I'm
looking at his body I'm trying to figure
out where I'm gonna pick my shots and
where I'm gonna hit him and then this is
it dude this is the big moment months
and months of talking the first fight
was a draw this is the moment that the
whole entire world has been waiting for
and then I just went I can let everyone
down I was just kidding not really
anyway robbed one who's the king of
social media man comes off jabbing right
away
he keeps jabbing at my body he lands a
couple good ones trying to feel each
other out a little bit right there that
he throws a big big overhand right which
by the way is what we trained for we
know that's his that's his bread and
butter punch and it misses and and as
soon as it missed I realized that not
much really has changed with his
fighting style last year I had one hand
down that was fought with my hands down
and this year you know I'm a little more
up a little more like cat-like ready to
take on punches but he was still
throwing these big wild punches which i
think is actually why he got tired much
quicker than I did finally these two can
get it on faking a little bit and he
keeps throwing in my body which made me
think he was he was setting something up
a little bit and yeah just getting a
little scuffle here I'm trying to hit
his kidneys in his liver
again just can't side with them with the
big overhand right not much is really
happening here this again this round was
kind of slow but I gotta say it's crazy
this is my first time actually watching
the fight in full and it is crazy to see
how packed this arena is just watching
two youtubers beat the [ __ ] out of each
other I knew that when I would throw
case I would throw too so I was a little
hesitant to use my right hand cuz every
time I did he would go crazy and I'm not
really an emotional fighter on more
strategic so I didn't want to get caught
with some stupid yeah I mean this dude
is everywhere it's like you you you go
for something and he just starts
flinging his arms everywhere
yeah so I was while I was looking for
that check hook a lot and he managed to
avoid it but uh I got close a couple
times it's clear to me that ksi is
getting tired and to be honest I like
that I like that but yeah it's the end
of the first round and I noticed he was
breathing heavy and in the press
conferences he was talking about how
hard he worked and I did that last year
I worked incredibly hard but I was
cognizant that he might have over
trained and I think he did cuz he got
tired after like three rounds and I
think you start to see it there but he
definitely won that round for sure he
was more active than I was before the
fight actually I told my team I was like
hey guys I have to start slow like I
need my adrenaline to kick in probably
around like around 2 or 3 because I just
I don't feel good and I'm not gonna be
able to like go hard right off the bat
so ya know first around the cavitation
Braun 2 begins kind of the same old like
still figuring each other out I'm still
slow I'm using my jabs sometimes and I
connected a couple really good ones this
boy
swings who big punches and he shows them
so they're pretty easy to dodge but I'm
telling you if he hits me with one of
those you know my head's flying off so
just a little jab there let him know I'm
still here like don't another jab to the
face another jab my friends made fun of
me that in for my right hand in there
and watching back there absolutely right
like I'm literally only using my left
hand so I'm aiming for the body right
now kind of tricking him and then a nice
jab to the head and like I said I landed
a lot of jabs in this fight there's a
lot of pictures that came out of his
face just like crumpled up and my left
hand just planted right in his noggin I
just wish I would have done that with my
right hand
no I'm saying so it's starting to heat
up a little bit again I'm just I'm jab
central just jab as much as I possibly
can cuz it's like I'm still waiting for
my body to wake up
[Music]
bro I'm barely barely missing these
punches which is my style I'm a counter
puncher kind of and so when I slip or
move I'm purposely like you're missing
me by like this much watching it back
announcer set it right there I know I
know he keeps throwing these wild
punches and I don't care who you are you
cannot do that for six for six to twelve
rounds he's not using his energy well
and I see he's getting tired that's true
I'm a believer now it's in my Instagram
bio Thank You Justin I love you bro so
in the replay yeah check that out that's
it just that just to just two real good
jabs and a third one and then we're just
it's just a swing fest
and then this punch right here that was
the first punch where I was like I was
like ah ten ounce gloves no head guards
I see round three starts this is where
it gets interesting case I just missing
punch I could see him running out of
energy he's breathing heavier that was
weird he looked to his coaches for some
reason which I've never seen any boxer
do in the middle of the round he just
like looked at his coaches and I don't
know why I didn't like punch him in the
face but it was also like a body
language thing like it was a sign of
retreat and assignment that he was
exhausted and even like he's against the
ropes and everything I like I literally
hate myself for not capitalizing on that
I know I got in trouble for the foul
later but this kid kept hitting me in
the back of the head when we would lock
up and here was the ears I think one of
the first time she did it like just
laying in the back a head so I tell the
ref Jack Reese I'm like yeah hit he hits
me in the back of the head and his
response was in hindsight completely
[ __ ] inappropriate and Jack Reese I
want you to know bro I'm not happy with
you that's wrong it at all oh yeah he
yells he yells at me in the middle of my
the biggest event of my life he goes
relax
did he kill you I got you relax box he's
D treated it like two youtubers fighting
instead of like a typical boxing match
but anyways I'm being a whiny [ __ ]
let's watch
not looking too good here okay so right
here right here yes I swings in me and
then he swings again and he hits me like
kind of in the back of the head and I
grab his legs and he pulls back and I'm
on the floor it looks like I'm about to
take him down and obviously this has
never happened to me before
so I look up at Jack Reese oh my god was
that a knockdown I'm not really sure and
he's like no get out cuz like I was
waiting for him to start counting but he
did it and I got up and I was fine but I
was just sort of confused at what just
happened
knuckle I am I'm holding a lot did
boxing boxing is tough for me dude I got
it I said I still have a lot to learn in
boxing I'm just like an MMA guy and I
think my wrestling background lends
itself really nicely to just like
clinching people so as round 3 is coming
to a close KS eyes movements are getting
a little slower he's breathing heavier
he's not punching as fast and then it's
live this happens in practice all the
time I have long legs I took a step too
far back and there was nothing I was off
the the mat but yeah round 3 is clearly
not not a great round for me so check it
out I get to the corner
Shannon cook you can see he goes he goes
what are you doing I'm like what the
[ __ ] are you doing and I tell him I'm
like I don't know I just still like
wasn't quite present but I knew he was
tired and I knew I was gonna have to
capitalize now so yeah this was the
knockdown yeah he got me like in the
back of the head and I sort of grabbed
him it's so funny I go I go immediately
back to my wrestling roots yeah I'm
actually to be honest to be surprised
that Jack Reese did not count that as a
knockdown you know I'm not the ref but
also like like I'll um I don't know how
you make that mistake all right
the controversial round for
[Applause]
you know in the corner nothing wrong
with it ah that was literally I think
the first right hand that I threw in
this fight it took me four rounds to
throw one right hand
anyways I can tell JJ's getting a little
sloppy with it he's getting a little
tired he throwing lazy punches lazy jabs
okay so right now I'm setting him up and
I'm waiting for him to do something dumb
and he does right there connect with a
beautiful uppercut and then k scy gets
up he stumbles to the corner he's
complaining cuz I I had tapped him in
the back of the head Jack Reese he
brings me to the neutral corner and yeah
this this is this is was the most
beautiful uppercut thrown that night
just like absolutely devastating and I
and I have done this in practice a lot
you slip a jab and come underneath and
that one connected my left hand was like
happened to be around his neck because I
think I threw a hook that failed and I
just kept it there and then hit him
again with our uppercuts which by the
way that's like a legal punch we've seen
in boxing it's probably not it's
probably frowned upon but if you do it
like once in the heat of the moment like
this I shouldn't be penalized for it
this is the one he goes down and he's
like still on my legs so I tap him in
the back of the head
it wasn't crazy hard but still I did it
and yeah that did that quite literally
is what cost me the fight so Jack Freese
tells me he's waving it off and and by
the way when he does I'm I I I'm I see
JJ recovering sucking air and I also saw
him get up and stumble to his corner
like this was my opportunity and I know
time is ticking he's probably still not
quite present and this would have been
my opportunity to to finish him off but
yeah myself two points Jack Reese the
ref is apparently one of the best in the
game but uh you know quite honestly I
beg to differ
Jack I'm sure you're a great guy but you
missed ksi is knocked down earlier and
this two points thing was
[Music]
I know you're a realtor bro and I want
you to know I will never be buying a
house from you yeah so the fight the
fight picks up again and and to be
honest with you I should have gone balls
to the wall here I know for a fact case
I was not fully recovered and for some
reason I was still holding back I will
quite literally never forgive myself for
the rest of my life for not just
unleashing on him yeah you could tell
like his movement he's just he keeps
walking back and back and back and uh
girl yeah bro this uppercut oh boy you
got [ __ ] up oh my god I just have a
problem with okay so boxing right it's a
fight but also not really there's some
rules there's a lot of things you can't
do which is why I truly believe I I need
to do MMA so you know Dana White
Bellator the zone set it up here we go
so round five starts you can see I'm
picking up the pace a little bit and
throw some more punches but still not
enough not like I should be and my
conditionings pretty good to be honest
with you like I'm okay
I noticed he's tired and he's probably
still not really 100% there whew jab jab
jab okay aside with the big punches he's
missing I know he's getting tired and at
this point it's hard for me to get over
the mental mountain that the two points
were taken away like that really me up
which is a lesson for me like I can't
let I can't even if an obstacle is
thrown in my path and you think I know
this by now I can't let it get to me and
I still got to keep fighting
yes sir round 5 ends sorta uneventful
we're at around 6 the championship round
so yeah in the corner before the the six
round
Shannon's telling me he's saying yo you
want to go home tired and he told me
this in the locker room too no matter
what happens tonight go home tight don't
go home with energy know that you you
left it all out there in the ring and to
be honest with you I didn't and I don't
know why because it's so unlike me to to
half-ass something but quite literally I
was half-assing this fight this is one
of two moments in my life where I felt
like I was watching my life happen like
a movie and there was nothing I could do
about it like an out-of-body experience
almost last round championship round
round six do we get the stoppage it well
just start swinging for the fences it's
crazy we both know we gotta activate
pretty solid in the money that punch
right there I remember it was it was a
body shot and I really liked that punch
it's a hook to the body but I remember
it connected he goes kind of like I did
last year but he did a good job of
hiding it I know I know he felt that one
see this is like right there it's clear
that ksi just he wants it more that's
all there is to it that's what it came
down to like we're both moderately good
at boxing
we're both we both got massive egos but
this night on November 9th case I wanted
the win more than I did so there's about
10 seconds left in the fight you know we
both just kind of like start lazily
swinging holding each other waiting for
it to be over and then
he's gonna have to do it bell rings
round six is over and I I knew I didn't
have it to be honest with you I looked
at Jake and I was like yo he he won that
one right and he's like nah man you did
great I was like yeah but he met he won
it and he was being weird with me and so
like oh look watching this fight right
now even is making me extremely hungry
and like people warned me about the
dangers of boxing but like I really do
love the sport and I unfortunately I
can't end on a loss so I mean whoever
wants this smoke who could come get it
in case I is a tricky person to fight
because it's it's hard to train for
someone who doesn't really have any
technique he's just got a big heart
Logan wall so the one judge had me
winning by one point another judge had
ksi winning
scores the contest 5655 and the last
judge decision victory ksi so just a
hella hella emotional celebration he
falls to the floor and and you know
that's super cool to see like this man
this might work just as hard as I did to
get this victory and I I'm incredibly
happy for him and I I'm like I said I'm
excited to see what he does next and
it's weird like you can see me like
register the loss and I think at one
point I like grabbed my chest and I'm
like how how cuz I literally just like
if it's stung especially cuz I I was
doing the calculation in my head if I if
I did not get the two points taken away
from me I would have won the fight but
again what a shoulda coulda next time
I'm not gonna be an idiot and then you
know everyone saw ksi and I we'd apt up
at the end we settled the beef although
it still might be half I don't I don't
know dude I'm on the ready to move on to
the next portion of my life which will
most definitely include fighting because
it's super exciting and I think you guys
like it but I'm being honest with you
come on back to vlogs dawg come 2020
we're doing three vlogs a week two
podcasts a week and a buncha tic TOCs
that I love you guys as you know thanks
for watching the 20/20 is gonna be crazy
we're gonna be expanding team maverick
looking for talent and just fun people
to join our squad and really gonna
revitalize the movement cuz like what it
means to be a maverick truly does
resonate with me and does mean a lot to
me the idea of being independent and
being different and being okay with the
and using it to fuel your goals and
drive your success so you're gonna be
seeing a lot of me in 2020 I think
that's it I'll see you for the next
video I bought a ranch with the money
that I want from the fight and it is my
favorite place on planet Earth which
you'll see I got a girlfriend that's a
lie
anyways I'm out
[Music]