yeah like I've really wanted to meet
this guy for a long time
I came here and to be honest I had 99
cents in my bank account
he just challenged me to do something
that changed my life like it's gonna
really go far for my family you won the
craziest weekend ever
I posted a picture on my Instagram I
said something like I lost all 12 of my
brain cells at Coachella and that's not
a lie that's a hundred percent truthful
I am mentally clocked out so listen if
you're not subscribed make sure you
subscribe throw the little Gang Gang
skit it looks like I peed my pants
and to be honest I'm not sure if I did
or not I don't think I did Coachella was
awesome I met a lot of cool people we
had a really crazy fun like magical sort
of experience at the end of the vlog
that you see before you watch the vlog
make sure you guys know we're doing a
one-for-one sale on the new merch
actually everything on the site you get
a piece of merch and you give one to a
kid meet somewhere that said I think
you've been prepped exactly the way you
need to be enjoy me being a [ __ ] I
coach other I'm going to go cha artists
they're VIP hey guys welcome back to
Coachella what's wrong no fashion if it
slapped you in the face I mean walk you
do this out this shoe exemplifies how
society is constantly getting stepped on
and this shirt shows that it's just an
imbalance in power
next fight this could be my boxing
outfit like I pushed it out like this
all right maybe I should take this off
maybe
I love you love you bro you're so
good-looking man look at him bro got
good looking he is man brother like
subscribe bro this is my guy are you in
love you could tell me yes I really
enjoy this real love yeah if you like
someone that you love
[Music]
already got fired or Acuna kidding
because the only a VIP sorry Ari
Andres my new camera man who made Andre
lose it he's my cameraman honestly dogs
gonna pass this in subscribers soon you
need to put that camera just a camera
down you up another one ha ha
putting shine a beefy Braille said he
brought the barber chair to the team 10
hours bro challenge yourself beef we
were filming today and he was working
out and he challenged your dad on video
I so much love splendor friendship
kinship we're in the artists VIP section
so super bougie and it kind of sucks
there's no because I met this guy what
is five I want to pay you $1,000 if you
jump in what about the potential legal
fees what legal fees don't let the
cameras got deep alright I've been in
this situation before
will you have one opportunity to do some
coke like think about you only going to
jump in one time we're in the artist VIP
section no one's watching
get the watch I'm going holding hands
right here
welcome back with having filled the
water oh my god it's like bathwater
oh my god that's crazy
I'm living so livid cuz I have been in a
committed the writtens and given my
winnings just to be losing confusion
surrounded by sitting there evils want
me to give in the industry sick and it
feeds off a profit that sells Richard
said that you cheated copper that you
did to stop as a disease and musics
about antibiotic I got it doctors are
live everyone's buying frequencies keep
you and me hide in fear and what's
sonically put in our ears and the
media's controlling her mind nothing is
real not even the right actors are paid
to be crime we buy it it's buyers who
are under the spell of stories of crime
all the innocent die and that's why I
put it in my prime that's why I don't
judge who did time that's why I'm not
gonna remember Ken night all that stuff
with Americans fight folk to fight for
the light on the mic in not to be
spiteful when I'm right or my life will
recycle when I say okay nothing is Dale
how do you represent culture by putting
the voice to the people up on a shelf
Tom an angel then I fell from hell
leaders had me convinced I'd sell if
only I leave the MC that blessed we
acknowledge yourself nah well lo gang
you're the lyrics though Thanks yeah
what that we don't really have the money
[Laughter]
real sweet a crazy little chain of
events don't even you want to give it to
you
that's a Louisville is is dude he's one
of the most important people in my life
to help me get her out personally I live
for this type of spontaneousness just
want spontaneity this is the step people
are uncomfortable with just everyone's
afraid to do and personally like this is
the one thing I'm gonna actually
remember from Coachella the only thing
that I'm gonna actually take why don't
you plug yourself in case anyone wants
to find your case my name is Mike nappy
aka egg nappy music at nappy music
everywhere I wanted to come up to him
and tell him I'm a little older but I
salute his hustle he changed the game
for all ages and if you're my age and
you're not paying attention to what he's
doing you're an idiot you're also how
crazy would it be if people find you on
memo and said you money I'm saying like
locating if you're feeling generous that
B you deserve everything that's coming
for you I love your vibe I love your
energy
I'm glad I got the capture on camera
today then something universe will
happen today you're lying
how comfortable do you feel saying that
you will have to I'm comfortable to say
can you tell me ever what you just told
me yeah yeah I I've really wanted to
meet this guy for a long time I came
here and to be honest I had 99 cents in
my bank account
he just challenged me to do something
that changed my life like it's gonna
really go far for my family
[Music]
I'm done [ __ ] it up for the last time
feel it I'm stuck living rough with no
cash to touch relied on a miracle and
dumb luck I can't stay in the same old
rut every day it's the same thing but
I'm getting better progressing the
manifest and everything abundant with
everybody a question I fight him and you
got it
[Music]