and you heard it which means you're
gonna have trouble with focus and
forethought and follow through an
organization planning empathy so for
lazy god and learning from the mistakes
you like to call mornings with my to mic
sleeping right now and we're gonna go
make a vegan sandwich on his face the
vegan sandwiches crumble much easier
than regular quickly yo if you're not
subscribed hit that subscribe button
yeah one day ahead of us will me
actually I'm getting my brain skin today
why do you ever look at me and you're
like why is that guy so [ __ ] up
exactly and I ask myself - so today I'm
gonna find out why okay you guys you
guys with the Sun this one or did I
overdo it he went lighter than I
expected so let me know if you guys like
it I'm gonna go get my brain scanned so
quickly Oh
[Music]
all right go get my brain scan I will
see you guys later
look at this this is what he does in the
brain scan today they'll explain while I
could play with you no more [ __ ]
it's been like 30 minutes if she told us
to get it appraised but nothing I needed
to let's go get this brain scan I'm a
little nervous
deal it's natural I can't hide anymore
this brain scans gonna tell me why I am
the way I am why am I so controversial
why I detest cancer I am incapable of
maintaining a committed relationship
most importantly oh I'm so [ __ ] dog
I won't figure out why I'm so why I
think it act the way I do I am
emotionally unavailable when that works
right people tend to work right when
it's trouble people have problem because
I'm a bit of a hooligan a troublemaker
person ever since you were looking yeah
up until fifth grade I was I was in a
hole and I was good from then on up
until fifth grade I was just like a
little troublemaker I didn't apply
myself I was one of the kids I just
didn't focus or a care even understand
why I was in school and then fifth grade
hit and I shifted from being a hooligan
to actually literally only studying I
became a good egg but um man something
happened in the past four years or so I
just who I'm a rebel rouser so what are
my prayers for my young stars or dear
God don't let me be famous before my
brain is finished developing cuz fame
just does a whole number on
yes it does since the chronic stress and
the whole world knows about it it's hard
they diagnosed you with a VD as a child
never officially diagnosed I'm almost
positive I have some mild form of it but
we never saw it as a bad thing you know
a lot of my creativity is fueled by that
have you ever been treated for your
brain I had a skull fracture
I have a millimeter skull fracture when
I was in the seventh grade
so anything that fractured her skull
generally hurts the right so her my
brains I have a titanium plate in my
head ashes I'm really glad you're here
this could be a would be helpful really
do so we'll look at your brain I'll put
the information in the context of your
life and if we get your brain better
your relationships are better your
judgment is better everything is better
when the brain is not good
you're not good so come with me this is
amazing this is great
[Music]
oh yeah like open that yeah yeah hot
chocolate can you explain what this is
actually doing is gonna make a nice 3d
model of your brain showing us on the
inside what parts are active what parts
aren't which one should be which one
shouldn't be see if there's been any
damage from trauma chemical exposure
like that amazing
[Music]
looks good oh great
that's kind of nuts I could see it I
could see my brain from here all right
well we're truth we have some answers oh
we do oh come in Oh so the study we do
is called suspect and speck looks at
blood flow and activity it looks at how
your brain works and here's you see you
had actually a very significant injury
he broke his skull he was in the seventh
grade and he goes but I didn't hurt my
brain and you see these holes
I know parts of my brain are missing
well but this is it's not missing but
it's hurt and this is really important
because right here is the most human
thoughtful part of us shut the it makes
you human shut up so it's called the
frontal cortex was in humans than any
other animal so it's 30 percent of the
human brain and you heard it which means
you're gonna have trouble with focus and
forethought and follow through an
organization planning empathy so for
lazy God and learning from the mistakes
you make we need to fix us if we don't
fix this no matter how successful you
are it's going you're not going to make
the decisions you need to move your life
in the direction you go so there's there
is a reason yeah we either letting the
rest of your life with this brain is not
going to be a lot of fun for you or for
the people who love you okay because
you're gonna have trouble connect this
is the possibility that your brain could
look like just a fat full brain thick
with 2 C's type of brain starts with you
have to love it it's like no I have to
care about my brain because if I don't
I'm not going to
you have to avoid anything that hurts it
drugs alcohol are you doing anything you
shouldn't be doing I drink a lot yeah I
drink like once a week but what I do I
go hard alcohol is not your friend
it actually takes this and makes it look
worse imagine Mike's brain broke we
don't do the right oh my god
I don't want and when you drink your
brain probably looks like that and
that's why people don't act right when
they drink because they're damaging
their bra are you doing any high-risk
behaviors quite often yes so why don't
you really think about it your problem
is I need click me yeah no you're gonna
be smarter about getting clickbait if I
fix your brain ah because I tell you to
but you already know some of the things
that work how can you be more thoughtful
blue is average red and white are the
most active parts of the Brandon and
your cerebellum which is right here is
really good and this is the area right
here that according to a study from UCLA
it goes with intelligence they're smart
ah you're just not making the kind of
decisions help you yeah that sounds
about right
our question is well can we make it
better are you like permanently messed
up or can we make this better
we've got to fill in these holes I think
it's more traumatic brain injury really
needs to be rehabilitated get rid of any
high-risk behavior this can put you at
risk for another head injury because
this brain is not going to tolerate a
lot more brain injury what about boxing
not if you're getting hit in the Hat I
do have to kick one other youtubers ass
and I have to box him one more time I
don't want you hurting your prey right
so if you fight that guy you have to win
and you have to protectors yeah oh yes
I'll win for you doc I'm gonna win I
promise I won't damage my brain any more
than it already is and very few people
know that the trouble they have in life
is related to a head injury that
happened years ago every year he's in
the United States there two million new
head injuries like the chronic effect we
shouldn't let kids hit soccer balls with
their head or play tackle football when
I have kids I'm gonna make sure they
know like how dangerous football is
American football what position did you
play linebacker and running back I was
always getting like his hiddenness you
didn't tell me that I thought this was
just the trampoline thing oh no I am I
was like the the Katie with the coaches
like when the coach types me up about
basically sacrificing my body for the
sport I'm like okay high school coach
and I'll never see again after these
years of my life and I listen to him and
I offer up because of it and so the high
school coach is not really thinking
about what kind of husband you're gonna
be oh yeah dad you're good he cares
about the game yeah people aren't
thinking about them yeah you have your
brain for the rest of your life yeah and
so if you don't do anything this is just
gonna get worse but we know we can make
this better
yeah we love that please fix me doc
we're put on a supplement to packets add
a high dose official a really great
multiple vitamin and then a brain
formula to optimize max focus and energy
and get him in the chamber you get in
this we blow it up for our hour and a
half and I want you to do 80 of them 80
hours of sitting in that we have a high
school course it's called brain thrive
by 25 and when we teach the kids okay
love your brain avoid these things
invariably it's boy never girl it's
always a boy who goes how can you have
any fun and then we play a game with
them called who has more the kid with a
good brain or the kid with the bad brain
who gets the girl and gets to keep her
because it's not a joke ah who gets into
the college they want to get into who
makes the most money takes the coolest
vacations is the happiest most
purposeful person right when your brains
not right I got the tea boys so as you
guys know I got my brain skinned and man
you ever bring it turns out I do have a
brain first step so far so good this
actually Wow this is a regular brain the
color doesn't mean anything it's about
the shape this is my brain right this is
activity right I don't actually have
holes in my brain I don't think but this
monitors the activity of my brain this
part of your brain right here the
prefrontal the prefrontal brain while
you can't speak this party of rain the
prefrontal cortex controls human
connection and empathy
this is obviously lacking and it made
like so much sense I'm like that's why
I'm what do you got to do to like tap
into that all I have to do is sleep in a
oxygen chamber for 80 hours and take
pills every day this was good see on
this one the activity here shows that
I'm a [ __ ] yes as well that's what he
said I'm using his words not mine
guys that's a blog thank you guys for
watching if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe good weekend
of vlogs real solid for all the members
out there do me a favor stop me in
northern average and never ever be
afraid to be yourself brain scan on
three one two three
[Applause]
[Music]