[Applause]
it's an honor to be here tonight to
roast my best friend oaken I left the
Elauf because you took the biggest L of
your entire life on Saturday night where
did you learn your boxing skills UPS or
FedEx my question is there was a fake ed
Sheeran at your boxing match why didn't
anybody let us know that there was gonna
be a fake boxer fighting in the boxing
match oh okay that was you by the way I
mean I thought I was a real boxer I
thought I was like I am like technically
a professional boxer are you happy
maverick died before seeing you ruin the
maverick name I would keep it short and
sweet just like you like me just like
you yeah I don't get it sure sweet you
probably don't know this but I wasn't so
good for your fight thank God
being a dwarf in oil they sat me in the
front row so I could see after the
second round I politely asked him if
they could move me to the back i sat
next to your divorced parents and I
think they knew right away watching her
fire was the worst decision they ever
did together I saw Justin Bieber walked
out with you did you think he wrote the
song one less lonely girl about you or
the hit song I'm sorry
[Laughter]
you didn't have sex for three months
leading into the fight was that actually
your way of saving it all for when you
[ __ ] yourself me and your entire fan
base on Saturday night yeah I'm sorry I
you Mike I'm sorry for that one before
how does it feel knowing that Jake and
tannaz marriage is more real than you as
a fighter we talked to a few of your
ex-girlfriends and they all said he
never lasted more than two rounds in
some ways was this a win now it's my
turn
hmm my dear friend Mike you know I may
have lost the fight but at least I
didn't lose my girlfriend to david
dobrik Mac you're my best friend from
Ohio but I've actually decided to
replace you with Justin Bieber and send
you back to Plymouth Rock you if I'm
being honest guys this whole training
camp has been a like a rollercoaster
ride for me and for everyone at the camp
except for Evan of course because he
wasn't tall enough to get on okay I get
it
I'm the biggest [ __ ] on the internet I
know yeah III lost
I took the El okay I bested me in the
boxing match but you know what for some
reason I've been saying this in my
interviews you guys may have seen I just
don't feel like I lost and how could I
JJ and I came together to literally
shift culture this event was
unprecedented we showed the world how
strong this new age of digital media is
and you guys us the YouTube community
how strong we are when we come together
this fight was the most successful
boxing
zone has ever had even more so than
their like traditional boxing fights and
we started from YouTube like I'm a proud
of us the community be I think we made
huge strides for boxing as well brought
a ton of new eyes to it and took it
seriously like we gave the the sport the
respect that it deserved see we put on a
sick show like that that was it's
entertainment right and I might be a
little biased but our fight was the most
entertaining fight of the night and then
D most important I'm healthy JJ is
healthy like it doesn't look like I just
got in the fight and beat the [ __ ] out
of another human being for 6 rounds my
face is still good my body's not started
and break any bones my brain is not
damaged I think it's all good stuff
great stuff really so god I mean bro I
want to do it now round of applause for
myself and JJ and the whole YouTube
community so yeah dude to win it's a big
win like I like yeah I lost I lost the
fight wink face and quite possibly one
of my favorite moments of the night and
I said this in my win speech I I don't
like being a dick I'd like I'd do the
press conferences and I turn into this
like witty [ __ ] to put on a go to a
good show and entertain you guys I don't
like beef or drama and at the end of the
day ksi and I we made up we shook hands
in the ring and we settled it you know
it's weird how it took bashing each
other's skulls in to do that but we did
it yeah that was a sick moment for the
first time in my life when the announcer
told Jay Jay he's like oh is the beef
settled then and I remember just looking
at him like you look at a girl when you
ask her on a date and you're like
waiting for the answer and I was just so
excited when like we'd apt up and and
squashed it and then also Bieber came to
the event like Wiz Khalifa rick wob'
rick ross dan Bilzerian like you guys
gotta understand I am at the end of the
day like call the followers not you guys
like I love you guys like the number
like the fact that I have a following
that all this like stuff I have money
friends girls like all that I'm a kid
from a town in Ohio who planned on being
an engineer for the rest of his life and
I thought that until I was 19 years old
I'm 24 all this has happened in five
years of my life like a small-town kid
like like Frogger almost like I'm like
jumping through traffic
I just keep making it to the next level
and next level and so this is so surreal
for me all of this is so surreal for me
and like Bieber came into the locker
room beforehand he said a prayer with us
and then he walked me out one of the
coolest things ever and his public
support for me is like that means the
world the fact that he's able to to put
his neck out there for me and like just
keep supporting me no matter what he
posted me on his Instagram tour twice
now which is crazy Bieber I [ __ ] love
you bro I changed my bio it's just as
belieber now and it's because I believe
I believe dude like how is any of this a
loss like what cuz I didn't get my hand
raised yeah yeah okay here's the new
think a new rule I'm making it right now
winning is for losers and losing is for
winners you think people would buy that
but yeah nah I just don't feel like a
loser there's a lot of content I want to
do around the fight like a proper
breakdown behind the scenes stuff that
happened it was quite the day like this
this whole training camp has been
absolutely crazy like I said this before
and I know it's been memed but I woke up
sick that day and if I'm being honest
completely destroyed my morale trust I
do not want to be the guy that's making
excuses but I'm gonna make excuses if
you guys saw the fight the whole two
points thing was one of them and okay
this is that kind of delicate and a bit
sensitive so I didn't like prepare
anything like I do for normal videos I
normally have like beats to hit so I'm
just gonna speak from the heart I asked
my videographer Andre to leave the room
because I don't know where this is gonna
go but you know I've been saying I I
don't I don't feel like I lost because I
really don't like I'm I'm smiling I'm
not like depressed I don't feel like my
career is over like which was the big
threat or like I was made into a meme
the only mean that happened was because
I said it sneeze three times so like I'm
going out I'm enjoying my life again and
every day I get passed by people I get
phone calls I get taxed tagged in some
video online that that says like y'all
Logan you didn't you didn't lose that
fight that was [ __ ] the ref made an
erroneous call or it was like and
misinterpreted by the judges I thought
you won the fight
the fight whatever just like a slew of
extremely one-sided opinions about the
outcome of the fight being 100% honest
with you I have not heard or seen one
comment not even from ksi side or like
the British fans that have said the two
points was the right call and to give
you guys some context as to why this is
such a big deal I'm gonna try not to get
like too technical with boxing scores
but we might have to so bear with me the
fight was a split decision the two
points that were deducted from me in
round four let's say he let me off with
a warning by the way I think he should
have done because he had not given me
any prior warnings to prior to that if
that had happened I would have won the
fight it would have been a split
decision with two judge's ruling it in
my favor now let's say the ref deducted
only one point for the tap in the back
of the head on Jay Jay it would have
been a majority draw but the two-point
deduction was the reason that I full-out
split decision lost the fight to the
winner by split decision from the United
Kingdom
this is tricky for me because I my
initial reaction was and I sat with this
for a little bit my initial reaction was
to fight it and and contest it and you
know try my hardest to make this right
but I decided to let it go and give JJ
the benefit of the doubt kind of go
hands-off give the man his his win like
he deserved it
so fighter he's a [ __ ] warrior a true
animal and so I posted on Instagram
publicly I'm like yo Congrats to the
champ and so I took the back seat and I
was gonna let life work itself out and
then I'm just getting bombarded
thousands of people fans boxing fanatics
friends random people on the street I'm
driving by me in cars or it's the
restaurant that I'm at telling me that
the outcome of the fight just wasn't
right I did some research and the last
time two points were taken away from a
professional fight was like over a
decade ago doesn't happen a lot one of
the times that it happened was when Mike
Tyson bit Evander Holyfield's ear off
and spit it on the floor which is one of
the nastiest thing that's things that's
ever happened in boxing and Here I am
getting two points deducted from me for
like a like a like a love tap in that I
was like a heat-of-the-moment just like
a pissed off I'm in fight mode it's one
of those situations where the punishment
just simply did not fit the crime this
is pretty funny this is a still of the
rough deducting two points and I'm
standing there and I know this is like
probably ruin the fight for me it is my
first professional debut to be honest
with you I have no like real ideal what
I'm doing and it's a six round fight you
know how hard it is to earn back two
points in a six round fight
assuming no one's gonna get knocked out
or knocked down it just put me at the
bottom of a mountain that when I looked
up I wasn't sure I could overcome it and
horrific ly I was right and Jack Reese
who is the ref is apparently like one of
the best the California State Athletic
Commission has and one of the best
boxing reps so I don't want to like I
don't want to dog the guy and I don't
want
I don't want you all to blow up his spot
he even said it in the locker room after
I spoke to him at length he said if he
if he if he's made a mistake he's down
to correct it and that's I wanted you
guys to hear this from me first my team
and I have decided to file an official
appeal for for the fight because we just
don't believe that the outcome was right
and that that is it strikes me resonates
with me to my core and one of my biggest
fears with this whole thing is being a
sore loser and that's why I'm making
this video a week after the fight is
because I really had to check myself and
make sure I wasn't doing this because I
was afraid of losing and historically
we've seen guys like I've taken big L's
massive elves by no means am i afraid of
losing I've in fact I welcome it because
it's the only way I tend to experience
growth in my life but I truthfully 100%
believe I did not lose this fight if I
am harassed and belittled for speaking
my mind or speaking out about something
that I think is right like again God
strike me down for doing this horrible
thing but I have to ask myself often in
my life because like I I've reached this
weird point where I like you too
nonchalant about things sometimes like I
just like don't give up to be honest and
at first I was definitely like this and
then my stomach just started turning
over the fact that like I don't believe
the outcome was correct on this and I
think if I stood by and didn't do
anything about it or at least I cry I'd
be I'd be way disappointed with myself
I'm making this video for two reasons
one to man up and say I'm doing it
versus standing by and you guys finding
out via Twitter and it becoming some
sort of meme like Logan Paul's a sore
loser like I'll tell you right now like
I just don't think I lost and I would
like for the outcome of this fight to be
dictated the way it should be and then
be this is a just a a plea to the
California State Athletic Commission I I
would just hope that you guys give this
the weight that I think it deserves
because I fear that since we aren't real
professional fighters it may be
overlooked but I know this means a lot
to me I know this means a lot to my team
my fur
most importantly my fans and the fans
that watched the great sport of boxing
in the event that we put on on Saturday
Andy Foster I'm talking to you man I
know you're a good guy and if even if
the outcome does not come back in my
favor please treat it as a normal boxing
appeal to be completely transparent with
you guys I have gone back and forth on
this video for this whole week I've been
losing sleep over this it's tough
because like I don't
again I don't mind losing especially to
Jay Jay like that is a worthy adversary
that dude is of is a G he's an animal
and like I said in my tweet like I
cannot wait to see what he does next I
wish him only the greatest success but
if I don't stand up for something that I
feel is right what kind of can man am I
that is not the type of man I want to be
it's not the type of leader I want to be
that's not the type of father I want to
be so yeah i'ma fight for for what I
believe in again I think I think I said
everything like I said this video is
delicate and it is just super
unfortunate a split decision and we're
back here with this with this
controversial wind that Jay Jay had I
said I was done with controversy and all
the headlines are like open Paul
controversial split decision loss like
why can I just not avoid some sort of
controversy ah life dude this is a weird
one for me it is tricky this is tricky
regardless we put on a [ __ ] good show
you saw the beginning of the video like
you know I'll be alright I'll be back in
the boxing ring boxing it's where I'll
be in the ring pocket all right dude we
passed 20 million subscribers that's
dope but if you're not subscribed
subscribe and I'll be doing a proper
boxing breakdown review later and maybe
a mini doc about the day the whole day
leading up to the fight cuz it well I
mean it is it was horrible but we'll
talk more about that later all right
um I think that's it I probably just
stay here until I decide to stop the
camera from the
okay