[Music]
[Applause]
back in the saddle welcome to another
vlog this was gonna be crazy shut the
hell up
freaky got you bro welcome back guys
it's good to see you Logan Gang Gang for
a life if you were not part of the local
gang make sure to subscribe sorry for
being so annoying and cringe it just
happens sometimes stop shadow shut up
and stop and we're back it's a big
weekend I'm actually kind of nervous
so right now you got to set Evan pulse
it we got Spencer Taylor we got hate big
mind it's got me Jay Paul's brother
together as you guys know we are in Paul
so that's our podcast channel if you
haven't heard of it
or and I subscribe to that channel make
sure you go subscribe here are some
highlights of some of the best stuff
that happened this past week because to
be quite honest bro you have the most
famous dick on the Internet
yeah I like I envy you oh yeah told me
when I was young he goes yo girls gonna
try to convince you not to wear condoms
and whenever they do that picture me
behind them going like this lotta
idiocracy we talk about a little more
mature stuff on there so if you're young
maybe don't check it out boy this
weekend y'all this is it I can't stop
smiling oh I'm so excited my boys are
gonna meet my little sister and it's
time we're meeting Mike's family I might
like to hit on your sister my
brother-in-law's a Navy SEAL bro cause
you kill people right yes okay I'm not
brother we just landed are you kidding
are you sleeping right on everyone can
you guys can you guys wait one sec you
have to do one thing real quick just go
ahead and go pee and I'll be right here
when you need me what he's just I'm
waiting for Khan to go to the bathroom
and then I will go ahead and get out of
here I was gonna say didn't he go before
we left
great job what are you doing lady you
want a pillow you can buy a luggable my
house laughs hey all jokes aside I'm
seeing some comments on Twitter like why
is Logan making such light of Kong's dad
let the dog recipes he is someone even
said he doesn't even care the Kong died
first off you sick
shut your mouth second off I want to say
everyone deals with death differently as
you guys know my way of dealing with
pretty much anything serious is
deflecting with comedy is it healthy I
don't know but regardless that's how I
react that's my reaction I'm a human
just like you and I don't think anyone
is right or wrong to say this is how you
should deal with trauma so just be
comfortable knowing that your feelings
are valid and for everyone saying like
whatever they're saying about how I feel
about how I should feel about my dog's
death in the most respectful way
possible suck the fattest sauce from
district and fine now with that said
since my dog has lived a legacy and made
so many people incredibly incredibly
happy I'm gonna go ahead and do whatever
I goddamn please with my dog pillow
we're meeting the family Abbi I gotta
tell you something okay I hate your
brother too so well put together
I told Logan Logan I think I could hit
on your sister and I said well my
brother kind of gray when he looks at me
no I will come with you guys I'll be his
deviants crazy imagine how you said that
you're going to potentially cheat on
your girlfriend my sister but I didn't
know you're a complete skank
I'm sorry angel this is great I'm having
so much fun
[Music]
we're late I'm giving my family the
wrong impression bro
dressed for brunch not the homeless
shelter Spencer what you do at homeless
fire easter color running a marathon get
in the car [ __ ] if he's pissed I'm
sorry I'm late I mean Kong partied last
night oh yeah that happened to me one
member how we had that conversation
about my ex-girlfriend last night he
loved just moments after we had that
conversation I discovered this on
Facebook that easier for me it's worse -
I just remembered those are my glasses
so I'm awesome
happy Easter bro yeah it's it's fun
we're at the fam fam BAM that's my
sister dude he's a Navy SEAL he's gonna
kill you now you're so alike trash last
night but we got here our hands a dirty
boy bro I don't want to say he's crazy
he's crazy my trash last night dude I
already said this bro now I just want to
do it again but you already said it and
it was done so well now I want to do it
again all right you know what we're
gonna film this a game but what's
keeping the first thing yeah but hey you
choose thing the first tape was better
right there just being what you're very
disrespecting now the words controversia
no I I think you're being very
disrespectful in my house do you know
what I've learned about being in Logans
vlogs as you can never say he's done
anything wrong because the low game will
come for you
I'm sure that much under our bed I was
tired and somehow I ended up here and
I'm sorry for putting my on your couch
saying like to be honest I'm not sorry
yeah we're not like I don't know what
the same like sister I don't know what
the flat-earthers do but that is not
welcome in my home so I got the merch
hold on easy tiger when I tell you we
will just when the maskers some of the
eyes oh oh my god you killed your
brother for the podcast
[Music]
this I think is gonna be pretty romantic
did the same thing with the Andy 600 I
love McKenzie I'm actually in love with
McKenzie and he doesn't like that very
much
sorry Kate I like the way that wind hits
your hair I like the way you walk hey
hey I like the way you watch you guys
look so much alike
who's dick eating is bigger and a micro
influence this bridge reminds me a lot
of you long beautiful and stable I saw a
joke bro it's just for the vlog yes I
can hold the comb like uh are you crazy
barely know you late I'm not as stable
as that bridge you got nothing to worry
about happy you got no Jake wha no Jake
wall take one big thing off okay Maya
that's my bed crazy oh gosh
keep up with it don't watch out ever
[Music]
[Applause]
we applaud calm / shop to buy this
pillow all the proceeds are going to it
with the West Valley and West Valley
Animal Shelter for our awareness
[Music]