[Music]
we are headed to Dubai
hello gang I am so excited this is
literally the the number one city that I
want to visit in the world I've never
been there we're flying a United Arab
Emirates first-class like at $21,000
seat guys it's no joke
so I'm very fortunate I'm happy I'm
excited hey yo good morning low gate was
poppin we're gonna be gone for like a
week so before I left obviously I had to
say my goodbyes
goodbye young doggy goodbye goodbye
goodbye plan five mr. bamboo and the
rest of your place goodbye goodbye Eddie
goodbye and hello Dubai well what we got
is that passports and bag manager Jeff
yeah ask him what his name is
what's your name bro yeah I have a lot
of stuff in my bags because as you guys
can tell from the title of this video I
need a lot of props
not first time try to get it be said
that at the gate we can try
are you joking brother wait hold up I
have a whole plant I got bags and merch
just they have the little cubbies in
first class
I need otherwise the floor would work no
just like expedited like I'll be
skipping security have you ever gone
downstairs to go to security go do this
is like he just roast me I'll respect
him if you can give me secret access in
the airport skin rosary all you want
yo-yo oh is this like is this like for
celebrities they didn't like the world's
biggest chops through these locks oh
[Music]
this is merch that's merch and that's
more merch literally just stuffing these
bags with as much much as I could
cuz I am gonna make the most beautiful
high-profile merch closet you've ever
seen cuz that's what a maverick does
which is actually perfect cuz you guys
know we just dropped a bunch of new
stuff we got hoodies we got backpacks we
got everything Logan Paul a cop slash
shop or link in description by the way
this is the line we skip up dude I would
rather watch my brothers vlogs for 20
hours straight than standing that line
in the Emirates lounge right now yo this
is a beautiful view I can almost see my
house from here I'm really hoping this
vlog works out guys I've never been in a
first-class seat that's um $21,000
literally the only thing I know about
this is the one case you nice tie video
which I'm sure you've seen my cubicles
gonna merge closet I got might want to
act like this in Dubai bro is this gonna
be Italy 2.0 that's member Italy where
they hate cameras they hate cameras they
hate long blonde vlog boys Dubai just
please accept me I'm really hoping they
do cuz we have the world's biggest
meet-and-greet to throw that's why I'm
going November 11th 5 p.m. at the Dubai
Mall which apparently is not a mall it's
like a city to any given point there's a
million people in the mall that's at
once that's that's 20 times as big as
the city I grew up in yo this is what
I'm saying it's literally gonna be the
big
Smeaton gree ever and I'm gonna be
speaking at the ICP live conference and
just I'm gonna teach everybody how to be
I've seen the videos I've seen the
commercials but I've never been in an
airplane where you can shower on the
airplane my only wish is that I had a
girl so one thing I noticed
scientifically guys heat rises and in
this room it's a little hotter that's
because we are on the second floor of a
double-decker plane floor one and floor
two oh mylanta I hate you so much
oh this is I mean you're still in
business class Brad yes I was actually
reserving that space for Evan oh he's
he's actually doing it do you actually
think I'm gonna make this much closet
room and they're gonna like peek over
the edge you do it they got a little
like beauty wait I have a question
you guys have showers she hits me with
the of course we do like like every day
you go out you go on plans that don't
have to go what am i a peasant just so
much space look you can't do this a
normal plane
my only concern genuinely is like I
thought the Cubbies like we're closed
and I'm sure there are planes with
closed cubby they're gonna see me just
literally just building a merch closet
on the plane also I feel like now is a
good time to say if you're not a part of
the low game make sure to subscribe
because we are the strongest family on
YouTube bro look at those guns the
Strongs yeah subscribe for me I think
it's time to get this flight underway
[Music]
[Applause]
okay so we are in the air I'm still like
embracing all of this there are so many
things that just like shouldn't be on a
plane or shower a stair kick me but we
all here baby anyways I think the doors
are gonna it's my own little section to
be an idiot yeah okay but I'm still
wondering about this merge closet thing
like whoa I'm not hiding from anyone I
just feel like if the flight attendants
walk by look over and just see like
merge everywhere that could get me
kicked off like this is a good spot to
hang stuff that's a good stuff down
there I brought hangers as well I look I
brought duct tape we're not messing
around Oh
however I think I want to go explore a
little bit
no I'm with the ladies right now as you
guys where are we are we like this is
the stairs here why are there stairs on
a plate where of the your stairs death
wait at the shower so break my camera
broke hitting here we go yo guys this is
absolutely my Sydney oh my god it has
two lids and there's the infamous No
[Music]
okay I kind of have an idea I feel like
this would make a much better merge
closet it's bigger it's close but yeah
this is the mood I just I have to figure
out how I'm gonna get the merchants here
they don't give you that much time so
I'm gonna have to hang the stuff quickly
but long story short this is amazing I'm
gonna see what Geoff Grendon and Paul
are up to
[Music]
are we not there right now we're going
to bark bark doesn't make let me get
Brandon how you feel I feel good there's
a bar in the back why are we still here
that's a good question
[Music]
I'm losing my mind yo
we should shoot our next music video
here I'm gonna play they got pretzel I
don't play but why not
nacho girl with no handlebars no
handlebars
I was thinking bro I'm thinking I was
thinking weird Thank You Bakul I don't I
think it's too small I think I'm gonna
make the merge closet in the shower but
I haven't see the shower so it's big
like so when you guys come to buy your
merch like go to the shop that's where
the pop-up shop what happens if it's not
the merch and it's somebody that's
showering please walk into the right
shop
hi boys this has been fun lamb so I'm
gonna go he did
[Music]
three years ago I was studying to be an
engineer in college how fortunate enough
to be able to live a life like this and
have you guys do it with me and I'm just
like eating crab on a plane with a
shower and it this is crazy everything
literally everything about this is
amazing I am going to inhale this meat
and uh oh my god I think it's go-time
gonna be interesting turning the shower
into a merge room but vlog like ok guys
I'm in the shower this is like I have no
time I cannot waste any time right now
when the flight of things were gone I
put my put my bags in here yeah it's a
bit weird walking into the shower with
two giant bags yeah I'm gonna get right
to the setup so yeah
marcus garvey I'm blacker the berry the
sweeter the juice
I didn't move
was they maintaining a crime go to jail
think I might say like post your bail
[Music]
yeah oh no this
one shooter win wants you to win people
died in the streets all due to skin
science this Africa's the birthplace of
me
you see in a sense I see a nurse in
Sinking asked if you'd like to stop
blasting sick away everybody start
thinking we occupy the spot lead em up
guys I cannot believe I did this
let me introduce you to the first ever
an average first-class pop up
[Music]
we can rise
[Applause]
[Music]
not easy guys they're only allowed 30
minutes in here oh we got everything bro
the pink hoodie selling like a god shirt
a famous maverick performance source the
joggers the shorts the favorite but the
brand neon hood so many things probably
the only thing we're missing is um
customers obviously if you couldn't make
it to the first-class maverick pop-up
shop you can get your merch on Logan
Paul calm slash shop yo this is that
maverick stuff bro who's doing if
customers owe you customer you paying
customer come in yo you can get your
surface 20 but I mean look honestly bro
they're a little more expensive but
maybe you got 20 you know maybe like 50
for sure cool thank you Yemen you're a
go performance shorts bro thanks for
shopping at the first-ever maverick
pop-up shop lame
low gangsters on the lane go send them
in bro cinnamon this isn't safe
all right look guys I'm not saying I
want all of you to be a maverick don't
be afraid to be different be passionate
be unique look weird I think it's the
crazy ones who changed the world now I'm
not telling you to fill the first-class
bathroom with your merch that's I feel
like just leave that to me but I do
encourage you to be a maverick rep the
logo and do what needs to be done to
accomplish your dreams and this is
apparently one of those for me well
welcome to the first ever maverick first
class pop-up shop how do you feel that's
it you just feel good pick up some merch
my man what do you think bro this is a
small this is the exclusive and it's as
much my favorite piece next to the
bottoms of course but yo I mean you got
that you think it'll fit all right you
got it bro you don't even need to pay
cuz we're in the low game oh you want
the favorite hoodie it's a little big my
man you got the favorite hoodie boy
knuckle-touch t yeah we'll see you
around bro take it easy love you hey how
are you oh we got another customer wife
young lady welcome to the first ever
maverick pop-up shop you can have
whatever you want there's youth emerge
over there yeah okay to be honest this
has gone a little too far that she's
like actually like browsing for stuff
yeah this is just I didn't realize it
would be this much of a success I'm
gonna pull the plug on this operation
soon
okay do anything yeah we got everything
but I mean like yo for you you're my boy
whoa I'm not gonna charge you girl in a
boy yeah yeah what about you miss do
anything yes coming right up
I just don't kick me off your flight is
free okay I'm gonna go ahead and clean
up soon thanks for coming thanks for
coming the first-ever member bobstine
what's happened bro this is legit come
on welcome to the first-ever I'll clean
it up please don't throw me off the
bling we were told obviously that we
can't do this
didn't see that coming anyways
everything is cleaned up as you can see
Bank Bank bank clue what you guys know
there's one thing I haven't done you hey
how you doing
this is just another day in the life of
a blogger know this oh my god oh oh
snappy always actually hi okay hello
gang that is the vlog super crazy what
today I'm showering on a plane I gotta
say life is amazing look this is
incredible right now obviously guys you
cannot make it to the pop-up shop
picture maverick March Logan Paul that
come slash shop or leading description
if you're not part of the low getting
make sure to subscribe
with this Chagas baby we got you to and
we're absolutely can't maybe that's just
me you bye I will see you tomorrow
also quick shots to Everett thank you
for letting me turn your bathroom into a
closet I know I went maybe push the
boundaries a little bit but I appreciate
it and I mean you guys no disrespect
with that said though gang I love y'all
now see you tomorrow
[Music]
so I think I'll take it the whole time
but yeah