guys this is Dave Dave he stands out
there four hours a day and he's diabetic
and he's struggling right now so I
figured why not get someone who actually
probably needs the money to play with us
Dave I'm gonna throw the money in the
air the fans going to blow it yo
whatever you get good morning no gag
what's pop big news some dumps happening
I'm on my way to my first audition in a
year and the Hat I got sighs real talk
to my agent called me he's like yo it's
been a while and all the controversy is
kind of past sort of not really we
should get you back in the rooms because
I think people forgot that you're also
really good at jhana
IV bro Charlotte this actually feels
really good I want to nail this audition
for you guys anyone knows maybe I'll be
in some movies again now there is one
problem I noticed some of you are not
subscribed you okay do I need to [ __ ]
you up I don't want to I will do go
ahead and hit that subscribe button now
I'll wait here for you to do it I'll say
I'll be right here did you do it okay
though now that you're a part of the
local gang skirt will be honest that
they're all this what this vlog is is me
being honest sharing my life with you
I'm hungover I made a mistake last night
and I'm like trying to wake myself up
right now this is all fake energy
fashion OVA party yesterday I went I got
turnt with Jake I want we do a little
flashback like oh I pull up with the
gang pull up with the gang all of the
ice bro you guys look like you're bloody
tampon gay hey fun fact I hate red
carpet I ride much either be chopping
wood in Ohio from being honest
[Music]
this is a mid party break to study lines
my first audition in 1.5 years 2019 I'm
not doing lines I'm studying lines okay
III thank the audition guys I chose I
did not do that well that
year-and-a-half got me rusty down the
part of that you guys all probably did
not help I gotta make better decisions
oh okay of acting get the cobwebs
distribution forgive all of that we got
something else to do bro I have good
news and bad news which one you want
first the bad news this one's weird the
midea my dad GP GP is coming at you just
sent me a picture no context what is in
my dad's cab that I think this is
varicose veins what does that mean is
that it comes from Latin Avera which
means wild coast which means holy we're
doing a giant fan video with
oh my god
never Suzie on one of our biggest fans
in the building I love these puns - this
video is dubbed I'm exhausted
so something about the wind like
literally blows the oxygen away from
your mouth so you can't breathe when
you're in the tunnel Alex said we have
ok great got some stuff and George is
here and I was gonna throw some corny
jokes about the fan no need bro you
about to be blown away I guarantee you
you guys are gonna be a fan of this
we're not gonna blow it the neighbors
don't catch wind of this
buddy close youtuber porn to you that
can't breathe really takes your breath
away
not quite a pun really took the wind out
of me yeah it's crazy how the fan took
my belt off
that's wild he was trying to blow you
blogs pretty fire he got subscribe
button Real Talk we need for this fire
out ASAP are you out of your mind you
know this is a fire hazard yeah um I
need to put this out you stay there Oh
but with the candle oh I think God oh so
close
it's disgusting ha ever since that fume
every time I stand up for - I'm about to
tip over you're just playing a lot of
symptoms of being a little [ __ ] so
recently you guys know love is in the
air pacifically with my brother in Tana
by the way Oh kill me
congratulations Jannah we're gonna
celebrate today by hitting pictures of
that
hey Sarge a catana I really hope it
works out though no you don't know a
channel is now the Paul fam our new Paul
family YouTube don't you need a family
to have a family channel you can't just
take two people's kids and get some
hottie Instagram girl
Sarris han I'd make it a family channel
smart bro he's playing the system wife
and two kids
[Music]
oh man oh it's delicious
oh they're great I love that too
shots all over your face actually I
actually got to go somewhere real quick
just stay here I'll be right back
this is where the vlog gets fun and real
now that was all fun you know by the way
thank you for bringing a fan over to my
house I want to do this thing I thought
how great would it be if I get all my
friends to come over take $10,000 cash
drop it in front of the fan the money
goes everywhere and everyone just like
runs it collects what they can we're
going to get cash right now we already
have the cash we are going to get
someone else right now okay there's a
homeless guy or girl oh there's like a
spot where they where they post up and I
always drive by and I see them but I
figured what if we like how do I said
it's like kidnap one not kidnapping like
say yo trust me this is gonna be a fun
adventure get in my car and like maybe
have a chance to win some money yeah if
my friends aren't [ __ ] they'll
hopefully just give the homeless guy all
the money got one what's your name Doug
game Dave Logan nice to meet you is
crazy I have a crazy proposition for you
boy you gotta trust me I know we just
met but I'm a good guy I promise I'm not
gonna kidnap you or hurt you how do I
shake it I Oh would you come with us for
a crazy adventure where you you have a
chance to make some money earn some
money it will take a second 30 minutes
max it's down the street trust me it'll
be worth everyone cash
it'll be cash today right now okay I'll
do it what makes you say that let me ask
you a question bro tell me tell me about
yourself
where you're from and what's your
situation I'm diabetic you have a family
or anything no I've never been married
how come I've just never found someone
yeah so were you will you collect the
money on the corner there like how long
were you out there I worked there and I
worked there occasionally when it's open
and I and I usually work at least four
hours how much want to usually collect
in a good day I'll make 40 bucks I feel
good I feel like we could beat that
today what's the most amount of money
you've made in a year five grand well
let's see if we can beat that today
[Music]
gathered you all here today for a good
reason like I'm at a funeral yeah why
who's died in March our Channel besides
my youtube channel there's some fun
things today but it's gonna get even
more in my back pocket I got $10,000 and
thousand dollars cash watch this video
give it a thumbs up so it finally is the
trending page I'm dubbed uber on
Thursday here's the thing we got a guest
a surprise guest imma go get him y'all
stay here don't move
follow me my friend hey so here Dave go
ahead and stay with my friends
guys this is Dave we picked him up off
the off the 104 for some highway I don't
know Dave he stands out there for hours
a day and he's diabetic and he's
struggling right now so I figured why
not get someone who actually probably
needs the money to play with us so Dave
was gonna play the game with us here's
how that's gonna work Dave this giant
fan that you see here is very powerful
500 horsepower to be exact I'm gonna
turn it on a light setting there's milk
in my I'm I'm flustered I guess I can't
even cry Dave I'm gonna throw the money
in the air the fans gonna blow it yo
whatever you get you keep it's $10,000
here y'all got a chance to make some
money today so it's a mix of 20s and
hundreds you just got to be strategic
[Music]
thank you it's gonna take one if one
person gives it to Dave everyone else
will follow I wonder if my friends wait
no no technically I made zero because
I'm giving all mine of yours but Wow
thank you give somebody else's money or
720 bangies law to you my guy
[Applause]
so so far all of the men have given up
their boys are so nice
you can't take everybody to McDonald's
dude yeah just don't don't buy drugs no
I don't dude your eyes only reason not
mad that I didn't take part in that how
can you live with yourself after you got
the money and didn't give it to me I'm
had to be one of the people in this
crowd or now who didn't give their money
to the homeless guy break
oh you at that point you might as well
not even be a human like stare people in
this crowd around us earn our money what
a dude who has no food or home it lives
in a brain I really thank you guys for
what you did for me you guys are really
cool what are you you know what you're
gonna spend that money on I'm gonna get
a few pairs of shoes a radio have you
ever considered by some maverick merger
at Logan Poldark I'm / shopper no like
boxing gear yeah no why would I care I
don't even drink wine thank you dude
thank you for trusting me today okay
yeah don't spend it all in one place and
good luck with everything your email
[Applause]
cool that's crazy hi Yolo gang that's
the blog I guess thank you guys for
watching been out front of the little
Gang Gang Gang skirt make sure to
subscribe hit that button for me do
something nice today that felt really
good I'm gonna try to do more like real
life based stuff like that actually we
made Dave's year or at least half years
I think Davis is really happy and I
think he appreciates it
with that said lo gang skirt I love you
guys now see you tomorrow taking these
fan
[Music]
ever gotten blown by one of your fans