I need that
I need that in my life Oh was he doing
that
yo this is so cute
[Music]
I just want to own this dog and their
happily forever after how much for the
dog
yo yo dog for 5 minutes and we are
[Music]
here we are this is it
I hate these videos every single one you
sit down and you talk to a camera about
some sesh that just happened the
unexpected videos but I believe I owe it
to you guys to talk about what happened
because Kong the savage as you know
played a huge part in my life these past
two years I'm gonna try not to get
emotional but it's just it's this was
very unexpected it's it's incredibly sad
everyone in the house there's their
heart is hurting today and we've heard
reports of coyotes in the neighborhood
neighbor Susie is always like texting us
when the the neighborhood gets an email
about some sort of coyote wash mitt
whether it's a street over or somewhere
in the city I just feel like it's one of
those things where it's impossible to
happen until it happens to you which is
what happened last night
I took a moment to think about how I
wanted to make this video obviously
because anything involving death given
my past is gonna be a bit tender and
difficult to navigate and as a content
creator
I wanted to let this one digest a bit so
I could really collect my feelings
before I drove into it
yesterday was a weird day in general if
you guys follow me on Instagram you
probably saw the story we're in
pterodactyl type bird came into my koi
pond and actually killed one of my fish
and didn't kill it for consumption
literally just killed the fish it's
almost like all these bad things happen
at one time I don't know what it is if
it's like a universal like queue to me
or what it is but anyways I'm at dinner
later that night my neighbor Susie
texted me and she says coyote in front
keep calling inside and I said where and
so I I screened shot this and I send it
to my boys who are at home Andre and
Mike so Andre might go out to look for
Kong and it's the classic group chat
panic where everyone's starts to freak
out because not only do they not hear
him which is unusual but they don't see
him running around the yard either Kong
just ran away before guys if you're like
oh gee lo gang you know Kong has ran out
the gate like three times before
we got a fence to stop him but he's a
[ __ ] like a little adventure dog so
who knows maybe he was somewhere in the
bushes or somewhere in the trees but as
time went on and they're sending me
videos of them looking for Kong I
started to worry a little more mind you
I'm at dinner I'm looking at the the
security cameras but it's so loud and I
can't really see what's going on somehow
I I'm at this freaking crowded
restaurant Beverly Hills and I'm on the
kick security cam footage and I see one
of the biggest coyotes I've ever seen in
my life and I'm from Ohio like I I grew
up around coyotes I know what they look
like and one of them is just stalking
right outside the gate just lurking and
you you know you heard Kong bark a
couple times and then I saw a second
coyote like equally the same size and
these [ __ ] are bad they are
aggressive they've killed dogs in our
neighborhood before and they're right up
against the gate and so I'm starting to
freak out I am the one in the group with
the level head but I'm at dinner with my
friend and I'm looking around I started
to get a little antsy and we're all
hoping so badly that we go outside the
gate and we just see Kong sitting atop a
dead coyote tongue hanging low chest out
oh I gotta kill boys but it just seemed
a little far-fetched and then I get the
call from Andre and Mike they're like yo
you got to come home we have really bad
news so I got my 30-minute drive home
and I'm freaking on the car and I'm
asking I'm like yo II like it where's
the body is he potentially still alive
somewhere what they do
and Andres showed me the the footage
when I got home and I can't like coyotes
are so slick I can't help but feel like
this was premeditated like this is the
most cunning abduction plan I've seen in
my days the whole thing lasted about 10
to 15 seconds the coyote jumped the
fence Shay's Kong around a car and
grabbed him actually right here the
coyote took Kong there there's
no remains like they straight-up
abducted him
and like I said like these [ __ ] are
so
man I don't like not like this I hate
making these videos he didn't stand a
chance and I hate how naive he is and so
mindless like he had no idea what was
going on like he was on the other side
of the gate literally barking at the
Coyotes taunting them and he's never
really had any taste of danger he
doesn't have any predators here so we
didn't know what we didn't know what to
do and again I just want to iterate how
how quick all of this happened and so we
searched the whole neighborhood for
about an hour we spent the whole morning
looking for anything we could find and
there is nothing there's literally no
sign of him and these coyotes are still
out there and we still have more pets
like we have Perl the pig we have Raya
I mean if give one snuck into my room we
got maverick and who knows what these
these things are capable of at this
point you know they pulled the [ __ ]
heist of a century they literally
snagged the most famous and loved dog on
Instagram I have had Kong since almost
since I like started vlogging and during
our search last night by the grace of
Mother Nature the universe some sort of
magical ether we go and in mind you I'm
gonna show you he was he was literally
snatched right over there and right
there when we're looking for him
yesterday we find a little tennis ball
little chewed up tennis ball and this do
you see is this like real life right now
it's seriously says Kong it's obviously
the brand but this was the last thing
this is the last thing he was playing
with and it was like his this is his
final note goodbye and it was just his
his name
Khanh I wish you would have given me a
little more to work with here ah [ __ ] I
don't think it's fully set in yet that
he's gone I'm so used to him waking all
of us up at 7 a.m. and peeing on my
floors and licking my fingers until they
dry up crack and bleed a little tongue
that little stupid little tongue is way
too long for its own good I think
something needs to be done about the
coyote problem in our neighborhood some
sort of protection because this is
getting ridiculous
like I'm not the only one in this
neighbor who's lost a dog I just can't
believe like what the why me thank you
to everyone who's reached out to me and
wish me condolences it seriously doesn't
mean a lot and I know Logan you guys
loved Kong he loved all of you anyways
Kong to savage you know I love you
brother
this one's for you
[Music]
raise the glass tonight from where is a
glass for conch tonight for meelo gang
I'm gonna go listen to Sarah McLaughlin
and cry for the rest of the day we're
gonna bury these flowers right where
they're he was snatched and yeah if you
have followed me for the past couple
years you will recognize a lot of these
moments with Kong - Savage I Love You
Man I miss you and here's to you buddy
[Music]
coming up does that feel good yogi hello
call your dog
Oh kissing oh my god is a cutest [ __ ]
I've ever seen
the boy the boy smashing interests
[Music]
[Laughter]