[Applause]
today is the two-year anniversary of the
Maverick brain that is a statistical
analytical of actual fat can not believe
the Maverick movement guys the movement
we started literally took over YouTube
but alive now for two years it's the
hottest softest merch in the game you
know the drill as you guys know love
gang up
I've done a lot of [ __ ] in my life
but recently I came to the revelation I
want to do some good go for this drop
it's the yellow hoodie and the black
maverick hoodie you're doing a
one-for-one so you get one and you give
one I am a ver Cody's lowball calm slash
shop and you give a hoodie to a child in
need good some good [ __ ] bro I figure we
can actually do some some good things
with our YouTube channel now as much as
I want to sit here and be the guy who's
like we could change the world although
we can I'm not gonna do it like that I
want it to be in an organic way
something that's true to me and
obviously the Maverick brand is
something near and dear to my heart
guys know how it is you know what it
means people who do with different
people who go right when other people
don't lab those who are not afraid to be
unique those who see life through the
lens of possibility it's going down move
now we are on our way to pick up
something skinny no but first let me
show you how it nearly broke my arm this
morning what are you trying to hit stay
hit my arm hey my four oh yeah I just
heard me that was a stupid thing to do
oh my it's been 10 seconds bro this is
only gonna get 12 times worse oh no wait
in the wall who the matter of backpack I
do we just leave it an arrow through the
movie I think
oh you eyes look oily getting my tan on
Instagram
Instagram Instagram shoot the lady in
the pink yeah you got it
Oh couple of sharp stupid you guys know
the Flat Earth documentary I proclaim
that and rightfully so there is no earth
no there's no earth what are these guys
doing need $10,000 proving Logan 400 oh
my god it's gotta be fake that's clearly
the whole thing is photo shot all want
me to show you that there is no we're
gonna prove it right now
I'm sorry let's go now there is still
earth
hey any any random rows splice it in
between like locations that random
enough or like a Donald Trump hair on
Spencer's never kind of [ __ ] that this
become my life so we've actually got an
incredible vlog coming right now so
we're about to go buy a dinosaur head
because this is really the roommate that
he lives with his birthday
where we are I found this story three
years ago he won't shut up about it
because they have like like look there's
a Jurassic small right here no that's
crazy
71 million years old sounds like Mike
how much is the Triceratops a million
dollars I'll take it what's wrong
look at all that console a shot downpour
please put him back on Google prefers in
fact I ordered an uber last week and
Logan picked me out he's really
struggling right now yeah after hours I
do over 135 why is this so small he was
born that way I'm not talking about the
dinosaur the sticker the sticker that's
not dope this is the noise that this
animal made right before he killed you
he go I would I sit out you make this
white gold guy will do it for three
negotiation I'll give you a hundred
don't think he's taking this seriously
I'll give you 200 I'll take it all right
it-it's just
yeah ladies and gentlemen I think we've
done holy [ __ ] the yellow drop it's
literally the same yellow I had ride
from West Coast Customs sampled this
color probably like disappear on this
car right now
weird where did he go from here okay
crazy right that's right like the zero
I'm yellow drop this is no joke get one
give one hoodie look it roll these are
sick hoodies honestly my favorite design
we've dropped it's a little more mature
it's a little more skin radical and
retro we
oh damn this puppy just got faster think
cuz it's yellow like lightning we all
want to say something it's nothing
feeling inspired lately so we just
dropped these new hoodies as you guys
know that the Maverick yellow hoodies
retro drop you get one and you give one
to a child in need but one of the things
I think people are forgetting about is
what this what this shift actually means
math maverick slept on I even changed my
Instagram bio to y'all slept on me and
now I'm mad
cuz I'm mad dawg let me ask you
something when you woke up this morning
did you look in the mirror and say oh
I'm a trick [ __ ] hmm I doubt it
something you may have said though was
i'ma be in maverick today I'm gonna
change the world today and you're not
gonna do that if you're comfortable
you're not gonna do that in your safe
zone this movement to me is something
that everyone can do if they just
embrace who they are push the boundaries
push the brown brownies brownies push
the brownies push the boundaries
push yourself get creative and be
comfortable knowing that people might
look at you weird people might not
support your goals but that's cuz your
goals are probably too big for them
little people simple minds that's not
you I know because I was once that kid
oh why am I saying all this is because
like I said guys we've done I've done a
lot of taking I've done a lot of
entertaining and a lot of giving but I
feel like
I've not done enough giving and you know
I saw so stupid when I'm trying to be
genuine but I really do mean it
I want to start using this platform to
inspire and create change when I can and
that's what this get one give one
movement is because I do want to spread
the Maverick message I want to inject
that into people's brains again because
it is powerful when people believe in
themselves and I feel like it's starting
to happen less and less including me I
was just in a little bit of a rut this
past month or so but now I'm hungry
again
and I want you guys to get hungry with
me so we can achieve our goals together
low gang thank you guys for watching if
you're not subscribed make sure this is
good thank you for watching this vlog if
you're not a part of the squad and make
sure to hit that subscribe button and
you know how it is yellow hoodie black
maverick retro drop these little [ __ ]
good-looking boss slash shop get one
give one to a child the neat lokay turn
to 24 tomorrow oh [ __ ] I'll see you guys
tomorrow take it easy
[Music]