and I don't want to keep doing what I'm
doing for those reasons let's unload and
go blow the hood what'd you say what
what'd you say I said let's unload our
packages okay where are we say we
promised we would not break dance yeah
yeah yeah fun fun he tried to get the
house we stayed in the last time I came
to Hawaii you guys remember that
well we actually couldn't because my
brother destroyed it Dhananjay
appreciate you guys bro all I do is take
it off it's not gonna say just say just
leave what kind of structural this is
not my fault did you see what I did I
just want to put it back on it where's
the engineering here like what is
engineer dog figure it out suck my
despite that was a rare occurrence but I
got faith we are gonna stay safe and
keep this house intact
[Music]
ships like these that make me realize
how pale and thick I am think with two
seas to know why I'm from Ohio
subconscious I really am like people
ride buying their bikes and there's you
you look good from this angle I'm not
gonna lie you guys like that buds it's
right at the crotch of the mountain if
you look closely you can see the edge of
the earth our mic keeps falling off
Andre this is serious rock look I'm here
with Logan Paul of the Flat Earth
Society ask a few questions how have you
been since the conference that has
broken the interwebs
I can't iterate how much I don't believe
there is an earth at all hold up hold up
stop that's great let me just add
something do what they do this is don't
you just get the post up all day if I
could come back as a hermit crab in
another life I would it's ergonomically
correct with my body who thinks they're
faster than me listen zoom in 1 ek if
any youtuber could beat me in a race 20
K this is breakaway speed ready we're
gonna do an event for charity to make
this happen yo if you want the smoke
give me up
oh and if you look under you'll see the
beautiful Walla Walla Falls and an
Instagram model in her natural habitat
working girl
[Music]
when I was running around in the golf
course earlier I was just doing my thing
I was running around put my hands up I
was doing cartwheels and you know I felt
good I felt liberated and then just got
to thinking like why would I not do that
right like I just don't feel like people
are living to their fullest potential
everyone is so used to going through
motions why would I not go out on the
golf course and just dick around for a
second was beautiful raining in Hawaii
so the message of the day is live life
live like old live like new things that
like hands kind of weird like how come
it's all your hands in the air breathe a
little bit and have some God dang fun is
my skin bed you look at tomato at my tan
yet well that's not being made fun of by
my comrades people have been saying i
have a drinking problem but i don't have
a problem with drinking it's working
back like that would working
[Music]
you're gonna be bumping up and down
bodies flying through the air okay
waving at us dreaming in terror or
excitement
depending on how you guys feel oh I'm
gonna puke 100% of Tanya right question
do you think this will get us back onto
Google preferred boat faster than me
probably not the fastest youtuber around
20k - any youtuber I could beat me in a
race real challenge scheisse
[Music]
I'm gonna be quite honest with you
goddamn we've been having some fun but I
know for a fact we could be having more
fun if we had a fridge so we're gonna go
get one
I pad pictures only my mother uses an
iPad before it's mine my mom was the mom
at leg wrestling tournaments with the
iPads is blocking this a man we need a
not fall into this trap I'm gonna go buy
a frisbee this place doesn't have a
frisbee bro I'm not Jake balls bro worst
case scenario we could use the IO label
as a frisbee hair shampoo we're getting
close yo crotch is heating up that's how
I know
that's my target the 34 year old cheap
plastic CBS frisbee oh yeah my job hello
anything until the girls start taking
pictures of their by 10 to 15 oh my god
I was right yeah it's actually
incredible feel like maybe I should get
in there and start doing that if I start
posting pictures of my butt I think I'd
go back up to 60 mm yeah you gotta pull
down your pants just like that 2019
Millennials actual people living a
peaceful lifestyle which group are you
you got magic bows harmonizes and
balances your energetic feel absolutely
not
oh I feel it now oh yeah I'm hard I'm
are you out of your godforsaken I was
incredible yeah your journey I could do
some cooler that's a pretty strong vlog
everyone knows the only thing I actually
matters is the thumbnail while we're
here Daisy do you mind
how's the thumbnail good everybody we
got it
[Music]
yo someone is gonna fall I just don't
know who this is insane fog is literally
enveloping the mountain swallowing it
whole nothing to be seen except nothing
I could be a narrator do the math it's
all completely invalid by the [ __ ]
Josh's camera dear well you doing it
careful Jenna careful
[Music]
all right a lot of cool stuff going on I
got something to say and not to get
cheesy but might get a little cheesy
guys I put out an Instagram story the
other day explaining how I feel and
where I'm at in my life when it comes to
being a youtuber and an Internet star I
don't love it I don't love this stigma
that comes with being a youtuber when I
was on vine
I was the vine guy right when I was on
u2 or Facebook it was like the Facebook
star now I'm the controversial youtuber
and not that I don't love YouTube I
think being a creator on the platform is
absolutely amazing we are we are
extremely blessed as youtubers to be
able to build an audience on a platform
that is incredibly dedicated to to be
able to create and do what we want
whatever we want but I just have this
deep desire to do more like I see people
doing stand-up comedy like I want to
dive into stand-up comedy I want to do
music I want to do acting writing
producing directing and I'm just not
sure if being a vlogger for the rest of
my life will allow me to do those things
I don't believe you can become the
biggest entertainer on the planet by
just being on YouTube does that make
sense and and I'm 23 years old I
definitely don't want to fall into the
trap of instant gratification which
social media provide you make a vlog you
get views you get likes you get
subscribers and you get money and I
don't want to keep doing what I'm doing
for those reasons I'm looking for a bit
more of a creative fulfillment and like
it's so funny because every vlogger I
feel like reaches this point and they
all make this video I like I've seen
Casey do it I've seen I think [ __ ] do
it it's me now god dammit I'm lost guys
and I'm not hiding it I'm literally
capturing my Instagram photo before like
I'm long and I'm just looking for the
next step the next thing that I want to
do we did the Flat Earth documentary and
as crazy and weird as that was I loved
it I loved making films I love doing
long-form content so we're probably
gonna do more of that but I don't know
what it comes down to is it is cheesy as
it sounds at the end of the day I have
to live what I've been preaching from
day one and that is do it different and
be a maverick and again I know it sounds
cheesy but it's true if I can embrace
and not try to run away and go do
stand-up comedy or try to like be an
actor if I can embrace what YouTube and
the Internet has blessed and given me
with and innovate and make content in a
way that people haven't seen before
awesome different
I think that's the key I think that's
the key to the success and fulfillment
as a creator that I am looking for Logan
in the past two and a half years we have
built one of the strongest families on
YouTube it's not the strongest family on
YouTube I don't want to let you guys
down you know when I see you in the
streets it's love baby I dig around I
treat you guys like friends your family
like I say it and yeah it's cheesy but
we're family and I do not want to let
you down so embrace and innovate that's
that that's the conclusion I think we're
coming to hear with that said yo what a
fun trip this place is absolutely
beautiful live your life do something
crazy push the boundaries and be a
system maverick low gang I love you guys
and I'll see you next time
take it easy
[Music]
Oh