uh-oh was good low gang so bit of a
crazy vlog today we'd actually finished
shooting for the day this happened about
a week ago and we lost power in the
house we just started randomly shooting
just in case something happened and it's
a good thing we did because something
did have dice that hit that subscribe
button and get your merch looking for
that calm slash shop guys enjoyed this
video it's skin a while and please flat
earthers or the Russian or the Russian
platter
oh oh this is where we die if so you
know as well outside and check out what
may have caused this you know why stuff
is like when my brother does this it's
fake this is real you see that the tip
of the shadows in my face right there
I'll take care of this Mike oh my god
bro the gas tank obviously of a
sharpshooter I'm Katniss Everdeen hey
hey stop uh are we still alive yes cuz I
did this shoot oh no when did that doing
it yeah watch out I got the door right
y'all again I just wanna reiterate I
feel like we should have security doing
this no it's good content all right I
got you I got you
all this is in there I feel like we
should have brought more than one arrow
I broke it know that action oh yeah
first the gas take thin glass think
you're the real criminal I'm being off
the log
Bali's in the pinna bathroom
ambiance bro look at the arrows not even
in the feel like the only thing making
this like scary is that you have like
spotlight it's really without it be like
a regular knight in seeing like we go to
the fuse box we turn on the power and
everything's back to normal back on
Google preferred we aren't losing
subscribers every month okay I don't
know about the last tube first what's up
don't do that hey Mike listen dog fix
that I'm after shooter with a bow
there's nothing trick something goes out
one of them ago is the opposite listen
are we haunted or not exactly doom I
just stared at it buddy you know maybe
do something at least for that vlog
exactly there's something wrong with the
power oh my god Mike how did you know
that I found more bro oh you
oh look like sister not again how do you
keep begging these things out you turn
the lights agree on the lights turn on
he goes yeah you turn them on
yeah what do you expect I think we're
fine I think there's just some sort of
power malfunction hopefully no one's
with us with that said I'm gonna go to
sleep I hope you all have a beautiful
night
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys thank you guys for me
did you like put someone up there some
[ __ ] I think there's someone in the
house
I don't know I swear to God I got him oh
this is not
grab grab grab the air hole for the air
or in the closet no well right now good
rub my office you know these boys out
yeah I think we're gonna rob right now
well okay
[Music]
[Applause]
let me go cops are on the way cuz on the
way you know goddamn well the world it's
not royal shut up bro Arthur's rule
whatever Drive bro we got your sheep the
truth will set you free shot Oh
was this worth it to you
was this worth it to you guys like I
don't know why that other government you
got the evidence what everybody's
pulling rolling your eyes you're already
ran my career got my bro there's nothing
you could do oh hey are you guys out
here hey you got it back up hey do not
turn around
[Applause]
[Music]
put me in the car now you open the door
to tell the cops I literally saw my life
flash before my eyes they popped out
around the corner with guns pointed at
me
I like froze bro I didn't know what to
do guys we could get you in here and I
need you guys to close the doors cuz you
still have one outstanding suspect okay
okay y'all find him please
[Music]
ha Sheriff's Office we know you're
inside the pink pot lettuce there is
right now
come on your heads up
[Music]
no flat earthers do that with their
socks I heard one day I'll a minute if
you say you're sorry I'll omit the earth
display he'll do it that's a good deal
you should have taken that road why he
got so many sucks why you got so many
sighs no he's got no socks look like
Mike's why are you located
obviously the hard drive and we located
the camera it's in the koi pond do you
have to flex a bro that's why you play
an earther like Nicole to race is this
cop or why do you have cameras you have
your follow us around we arresting up
with his and we put it on YouTube for
them do you know get embarrassed and
stuff subscribe yes
you [ __ ] fear dog you told me
[Music]
and that is the vlog so guys if you're
not subscribed to hit the subscribe
button join the low gang gang gags get
so also as you know the Maverick
one-for-one giveaway is happening all
this month you get any piece of
Mavericks from Logan Viacom / shop and
you give one to a kid in need somewhere
as part of our new retro drop and the
new direction that the brand is headed
with that said low gang I love you guys
and I will see you tomorrow we're
actually it's a it's a horrible horrible
vlog yeah calling passed away as some of
you may might know so I'm gonna kind of
just explain what happened cuz it's
extremely sad and we're dealing with
that today but obviously I still wanted
to deliver you guys some piece of
content cuz this one had been scheduled
to go out today anyways I hate to end on
a bad note but yeah I will see you guys
tomorrow
[Music]