nice to meet you both the guys that
survived you are infected he's been
coughing a lot we don't know who to
trust what if you're new here hit that
subscribe button for me we're up your
walls to get as much toilet paper
you're like you do not look good no I'm
talking about like in general like you
you're ugly ah trust me I'm getting
better I'm feeling all right all jokes
aside I put on it too we asking for
advice because I really do feel vastly
under prepared for this pandemic and
thanks to you guys I got some responses
back break a hundred plates
kicked mike Mayock out of your house
lose a boxing match been there done that
but then I found some real solutions so
here's a quick guide to stay healthy and
level-headed at this time wash your
hands with soap and water for at least
20 seconds avoid touching your face with
unwashed hands put distance between
yourself and others if it's spreading in
your community and please stay home if
you're sick
okay back to the bar spit it into the
garbage except you might why is my why
they don't know I know what I did you
know when you're holding like two things
and one is like trash but ones your
wallet and then you throw the wallet out
and you put the trash in your pocket
this is vector you know walked upstairs
I was wondering why I had a napkin in my
pocket I just thought you guys know this
fella Thorne is a dear friend of mine
but you're gonna say it dear for some
reason no she's not a deer anyway she's
directing a music video for our other
friends Chico's have I been doing this
whole scene like that like Alana doesn't
spit like that she's different I'm Lana
with the less ass not as big as Evans
but you got a dog did you guys like that
picture we say you last night Mike sent
a picture of him with a lot in the
background her butt was out and then I
was home alone with Evan so we sent a
picture back here it is in the back this
one's new to me this is how I feel after
all my relationships can't take that
with you that belongs so homeowner panic
David have you seen an angry bella
thorne cuz I have I ain't going back I
could get this dog to chase this for
years it's very very dumb watching
farting slides
he's like a heroin addict trying to get
his face at some point you would realize
that he's not keeps trying oh this is
one of those situations where he's
actually never going again what did you
just say dude this is all making sense
now I DM that girl randomly I forgot
that she was moving in with you and so
when she responded like I guess I'll see
you in my closet I had no idea what she
was talking about oh shut up
no way I had no idea I don't know I
thought maybe you're trying to insult me
or something I don't know now that you
got a cute roommate I'll see you soon
both the guys I explore page clicked on
that photo that's not what I responded
to was that an inside joke did I say I
was gonna live in a closet
so I thought that was a good thing and
then I opened my closet anywhere in
their closet this is like your bed you
can like just like lay it out not a bad
place to be quarantined I'll see you
guys later I don't like bringing it out
cuz Mike does it too Wow