holy sh
this is nice
you know i was just thinking about i
would put money on it i have the nicest
fee on social media watch this
catch the sun i wish i could catch the
glare but what do you mean it's not
possible
i offered well i didn't think it would
be shiny for this long look
especially against this backdrop suck on
that grayson dolan
listen the point is this subscribe so
you can see more of my feet logan paul
would jump in this
i know he really would so you got old
and now all you care about is your feet
[Music]
all jokes aside guys this is the most
intimate team experience that exists on
the internet this is for the people who
really [ __ ] with me and some massive
giveaways in fact the first thing i'm
giving away and actually kind of pains
me a little bit to say this is my dodge
challenger my yellow dodge challenger
was the first car i ever bought it's the
car that i drove from ohio to los
angeles in there's a lot of history
there for me it's a very special car and
i want to give it to someone who
appreciates being in this club
do you know why i'm calling you did i
win the car you did
congratulations brother that car is
yours
maybe we come out to colorado for your
birthday
[Music]
give me a second i'm not moving i'm not
taking off either
[Music]
i'm sorry i understand how this seems
invasive and it is but that's fun i mean
that's [ __ ] hilarious
just buy prank toilet paper to [ __ ] with
me yes yeah colorado
yeah i hope they don't think they're
getting like
the 10 000. like do we like right like
because every
phone call now has been like a hey you
want a car
hey you want 10 000. this one's like hey
you want to come to dinner
hey you want to come to dinner with us
tonight
let's go let's go
we're in colorado do you want to come to
dinner tonight
yeah that's what we're here we're
delivering it to joseph
[Music]
would you like to come to dinner with us
tonight
this is my last drive it's a little sad
but it's also a very special moment my
baby's moving on to
bigger and better things we're on our
way to joseph's house right now but
first there's a couple things we got to
do
[Music]
listen to this [ __ ] horn they told me
this was a train horn
are you you're kidding me are you
kidding
me bro we should drift in there we
drifting in there do i know how to drift
look at this thing let's go
holy [ __ ] this is nuts
i don't know a time where i did not
enjoy being around cars when i'm
in a car driving fast that's when i'm
truly happy what are the eyes that's
what i'm saying
feel real to me it does not feel real to
me up until this moment
i thought i was dreaming i'm having fun
with it while you're here
this thing's got a mean train horn on it
i love it dude take good care of her bro
[Music]
my last kid i love you baby you served
me well
[Music]
everyone we're here to celebrate not
only the maverick club
but joe's birthday happy 22nd job
happy birthday brother happy birthday
let's give it
so i'm just sitting
[Music]
darling
you're giving this to him yeah why i had
the best night of my life
it's your birthday you won the car
you've made my night
and you've made my night and all of you
that's great so you're giving this to
joe as a birthday present
[Music]
oh