keep us in your life we all love you and
i'm gonna i'm gonna be excited to see
what you do next
[Music]
[Applause]
it's a pit where people have
conversations it's gonna be worth it
mike you gotta trust me
all right i'm about to paint this zebra
if you saw the last vlog it used to be a
horse a black horse and before it was a
black horse it was
actually a lamp it is the most
functional lamp in the world i don't
care what anyone says
i'm about to make it cool as [ __ ]
well hot damn ladies and gentlemen look
at that that's a horse if i've ever seen
one hey jokes aside i'm actually really
happy with how this turned out it took
about three days to paint there's a lot
of really pretty colors in there none of
which i can see of course i'm actually
kind of embarrassed to say this but i
bought this horse lamp for about eight
thousand dollars but now that it's in
our piece i could probably give
one one to two million dollars i bet i
might give this to someone from the
maverick club you don't know what that
is i'm gonna be honest you're missing
out we do a lot of giveaways we do
exclusive content giving away my dodge
challenger soon we do members dinners we
do members facetimes just a lot of dope
and i'm gonna be putting a lot of energy
into making that the most intimate
curated
special experience on the internet y'all
can head over to maverickclothing.com to
find out more now if you'll excuse me we
gotta go horse around
hey don't touch the ride oh yeah you're
right my bad
excuse me sir can i have a minute made
blueberry slushie please small can you
give me
coke medium diet coke all right oh do
you have carrots
no we don't ah no carrots how much
[Music]
really oh thank you i got it i got it
i got it yeah you got it ah [ __ ] i don't
have cup holders this model doesn't come
with those
oh damn it all right all right see you
boys
thank you
[Music]
oh
she got her wisdom teeth pulled out bro
she's a real mess
no blow jobs huh well they just said you
couldn't drink through any straws but in
all honesty with my dick it's pretty
much the same
i woke up and like i was like all tucked
into my blanket i'm gonna be honest i
don't know what the [ __ ] you're saying
subtitle it down the bottom say go ahead
and say something no because you guys
are just gonna change it into something
else that you wanted you never did that
yeah
says that
better than you
i know i don't know if it is anymore so
much louder than i thought i said
they're going to be here for two weeks
who links my ass no please
it's a conversation pit
[Music]
andre what what are you doing what
moving what the [ __ ] are you doing too
loud here bro andre you lived here for
two years what are you doing too loud
for two years
andre we're building a conversation i
don't even see it i can't sleep
i can't answer phone calls andre please
all i hear
you're actually serious yeah oh [ __ ] at
least let us throw you like a going away
dinner yeah
yeah that'd be nice
[Music]
i mean i'm always excited for like a new
chapter and and what for what's to come
i am going to miss you guys and it feels
good like i am walking more and more
towards
uh what is like my life's purpose i feel
like what's called like my dharma
really [ __ ] enjoy the past few years
here it's been an amazing time without
getting too cheesy and i'm still going
to be here
to see you soon dinner like you said
i'll be here next
tuesday yeah yeah it's true shoot some
pulses andre so
personal thanks for how you've helped me
these past two years
both privately and publicly you know i
told you like my resources are your
resources keep us in your life we all
love you
and i'm gonna i'm gonna be excited to
see what you do next
for a second though i was like damn shy
should we kiss but it's just a thought
it's andre's going away dinner hey hey
george invite me to the party next time
[Music]
you