[Music]
saturday august 22nd 7 42 p.m
am i gonna text my old pal gary v yeah
you've seen this sports card thing
of course side note he's talking about
the recent booming sports cards sports
cards sports cards
apparently there's a lot of money to be
made investing in sports cards but
unfortunately i don't know anything
about sports cards but i did collect
pokemon cards when i was younger i told
them
brother it's the new art pokemon
ironically at the top get educated on
pokemon
all right [ __ ] it i'm gonna do it i love
pokemon shouldn't be too hard
and it wasn't turns out pokemon is the
highest grossing media franchise of all
time coming in at over 90 billion
dollars ahead of hello kitty star wars
mario harry potter and marvel and with
the 25th anniversary of pokemon coming
up next year i don't see that changing
anytime soon
now i've left pokemon my whole life
literally played the games all
throughout high school made a couple of
vibral pokemon videos on pokemon art and
i only have one tattoo on my body it's a
pokemon named squirtle next to my penis
so i knew there was a lane here that i
did indeed have a passion for
so the first thing i did was find an
expert crazy bro i feel like i'm you're
delivering me drugs this feels like i'm
trafficking a kilo
but like the price is actually probably
more than that's what i'm saying
look at this look at this meet jake a
collectible guru also known as
collectiblesguru on instagram
he was nice enough to sell me seven of
these little pieces of cardboard for
fifty thousand dollars
yes i paid fifty thousand dollars for
seven pokemon cards and it gets worse
just wait all of the cards have red
label red label is our ps4 this one
is bgs base set first edition shadowless
first edition thin stamp thick stamp
okay so what is this guy saying
psa9 bgs10 std69 blah blah holographic
first edition bsa charge
what let me break it down when it comes
to card collectibles there are two main
grading services psa and bgs
grading means they rate the card the
higher the rating the more valuable the
older the card the more value and the
rarer the card the most valuable
this dark blue shadow behind it
decreases the value and the only
difference on one you go to stamp on one
you got a shadow all right i'm gonna
keep this simple
pokemon first released what is called
not surprisingly the first edition base
set indicated by
the little first edition stamp on the
cards these have the most value the
second release did not have this stamp
and is also known as the shadowless set
still highly valuable because of the
lack of shadow behind the pokemon which
the following set the regular base set
did have
so first first edition stamp second
shadowless third base set
has a shadow got it this is beautiful
this is the one
yeah this is the one the holy grail of
cards this is a nine it just broke
twenty five thousand this card is a
twenty 25 000
piece of cardboard and you will
literally be able to sell it probably
between
35 and 40 000 by christmas
what the [ __ ] bro now i could already
tell that i was gonna like this
it's nostalgic it's a strategic
investment and most importantly
i was having so much [ __ ] fun so
i started buying more and more
[Music]
and more
oh these are so cool one of my favorite
pokemon gengar also one of my favorite
pokemon of all time
first edition yellow cheeks pikachu
three thousand dollar card right here
don't mind if i
do i'm like officially a collector
as my collection grew so did my
excitement for the hobby i started
watching pokemon professionals doing
advanced research on ebay and even met
up with some pretty passionate
collectors
slabs on slabs look at signs signs
signed and sketched top one pop one this
is the only one
in the [ __ ] world i found out instead
of buying the cards outright you could
even buy what's called the booster box
which comes with 36 packs of cards 12 of
which are guaranteed to have a
holographic card in it
if just one of those cards is a
charizard you hit the jackpot
in fact josie actually pulled one from a
random base pack eyeball
[Music]
don't touch it don't even look at it
don't breathe on it and then she ended
up doing it again
shut the [ __ ] up shut the [ __ ]
up but yeah at the time base set booster
boxes were going for about fifteen
thousand dollars so i bought one
i like this little booster box so much i
decided to buy another
and another and then two more
i was a bad boy in a booster seat buying
base that booster boxes [ __ ]
but i admit i was in too deep and my
obsession was growing i was about to hit
the pinnacle of the pokemon pyramid
period and look what's on my screen this
is a first
edition booster box and it's a lot of
fun money and uh
i'm about to bid on it you don't think
i'm gonna do it dude
watch this place bed
the auction ends in two days let's see
what happens
again i want to reiterate if you pull
one
just one first edition psa 10 charizard
aka the holy grail of pokemon collecting
it's worth two hundred thousand dollars
just look at how excited this guy was
when he pulled one
[Music]
hey congrats man now you're rich logan
you're gonna pay 165 000
on something you don't know no logan you
can't do this this is dumb bro bro you
think that's dumb
that's the current bid that's going to
go to 200 000
you've lost your mind oh [ __ ] when he
does something
stupid he always puts time into it you
have to make sure it's not that stupid
look at the condition
[ __ ] it's so too much money one day
when you sell enough teddy bear merch
you can
drop to it it's not teddy bear emergency
you diminish our friendship but you
diminish my brand no you diminish this
pokemon but that was me being a good
friend
no he was pokemon all of you guys
terrible friends
all right guys the auction's about to
start let's do this
first edition first prince these cards
are in very high grades
close the [ __ ] bid bro do i hear 170
no you don't it's only five thousand
dollars more
last chance
[Music]
000.
do i support logan spending 200 000 on
pokemon cards
no and it's getting pretty serious i
called him the other day dressing up
josie as a charizard i caught him
painting all the racquetballs in the
house as pokeballs
no one in the house even plays
racquetball who the [ __ ] buys 200 000
in pokemon cards dumps himself in a
[ __ ]
bathtub with bubbles and scrubs them
dude
you're ruining tub time i didn't invite
you here get rid of it now i was there
when he got that squirtle tattoo in
miami i told him not to get another
pokemon tattoo what does he do he goes
and gets one already sketched out
it's on his back he's gonna [ __ ] do
it how the [ __ ] is this guy dating a
victoria's secret model right now what
the [ __ ] is happening
yeah [ __ ] they said i'd never be
nothing but look at me now [ __ ]
look at this
i am holding in my hand the rarest most
expensive box of pokemon cards on the
planet this is absolutely insane look at
how beautiful this is
all right so obviously a box of this
caliber when open deserves to be a
spectacle and that is why on october 9th
at 6 pm pst
i will be opening this world record
setting 200 000
box of first edition pokemon cards live
on this youtube channel and here's the
kicker i am selling
all the packs well it's like 35 of the
packs i'm gonna keep one for me and
opening them on behalf of the buyers
with a shout out we're going for that
and charizard is a two hundred thousand
dollar car or maybe a couple i heard
there can be anywhere from one to like
three in these boxes
if you're a serious buyer go to
loganslivestream.com
pokemon or the link is in the
description this is going to be
historical so again october 9th next
friday 6 pm pst
live on this channel so hit that
subscribe button turn your notifications
on and we will see you then i got two
more awesome pokemon videos coming
yes i'm obsessed but i love you guys and
i'll see you next time
[Music]
i caught the kid the other day he was
dressing josie up like a charizard it's
pronounced charizard i don't
care what it is bro stop wasting your
[ __ ] time and money on this [ __ ]
bro