can i get a few seconds of your time
there's something i need to tell you
yeah can i ask you to devout i'd rather
just tell you
hey guys welcome back first things first
hit that subscribe button while you do
that i'm gonna go ahead and help myself
some cold brew
i'll wait
all right now that you're subscribed we
went into town last night we had the
quite the interesting experience with
some of the locals
oh this is happening we're in
idaho wild my hometown yeah with a hand
celebrity are you guys going to lookouts
or anything tonight where are the
lookouts can i show you
oh [ __ ] look at that
oh [ __ ] david dobrik's here
i brought you up here for the reason and
you say it's the worst thing ever the
best place amongst the shittiest of
places
because this is your shittiest i don't
know what is happening
yo yo i can't do this anymore i can't do
this anymore you're just drunk and like
just kind of being abrasive and we're we
came up here i'm wasted
being as i'm sober four and a half years
wait what
that's where this is the best view
and you wanna
for the first time you had a little
incident two nights ago george walked in
on me and josie having sex
i thought you guys were calling me do
you know what position you walked in on
us cowgirl
no reverse cow girl oh [ __ ] nice
she hopped off it was so funny she
didn't know which way to go
it looked like she was going down the
hill skiing
i was payback i think you should do
reverse cowgirl on you
all right no no no no not a boy
[Music]
i've been doing youtube for so long i'm
gonna do a classic prank got a fake
snake right here and i got this
clothespin attached to my friend's
clothes let's see what happens snake
snake snake snake snake georgie run run
you guys they still coming for you dog
hey belle there's a snake behind you
you gotta love it yo how about that rain
though you can literally see the wall of
rain that is so [ __ ] cool yo that's
the dopest [ __ ] [ __ ] this thing
[ __ ] rain you're just showering these
people with content man look at the rain
i think it's coming this way yeah i'm
hammered i drink too much cold brew
that's it i'm doing my [ __ ] rain
dance
bro it's happening
this is sick i should reenact a notebook
with my girlfriend
[Music]
i would immediately want my money back
if this was fun
just look familiar oh my god
i thought we could reenact the notebook
all right back at home baby did you have
fun at the ranch this weekend yeah i did
maybe
all right good can i get a few seconds
of your time there's something i need to
tell you
yeah can i ask what it's about i'd
rather just tell you
all right baby i gotta tell you
something what is it
okay so this is gonna sound so stupid
but the other day i was fixing that hole
in the well
when all of a sudden i felt a presence
so this is one of your like stupid ghost
stories but then it started to approach
me
she grabbed me she grabbed you yes what
do you mean she grabbed yourself
logan how could you [ __ ] do this i
don't know baby
but it gets worse what do you mean it
gets worse
she had a friend
so then what happened nothing really
but baby i am so sorry it's fine
because i actually have something to
tell you too
what do you mean
some laughing what's so funny