[Music]
they uh six in quarantine you saw the
last log losing my mind and the worst
part is honestly I'm lonely mike has his
pornstar girlfriend running around their
house say you got that girlfriend
running around
even Andre the vegan has his vegan
girlfriend must be nice doing your lowly
man and a boar dish so hit that
subscribe button for me I'm gonna try to
find love during social distancing I'm
being a [ __ ] at this point dude stop
I'm painting micro I made the garage
my canvas does anyone have a problem
with that say what sad Logan
[Music]
hell yeah it's perfect
my boys don't go Finny a lot of them
anyways your mic impersonation is scary
good
that's what happened chef Katie she
opened the door and she said this house
I'm sick of it and smashed the glass
right on the ground yeah it did feel
good though that's what we call a
confession room I get yelled at when I
break you break all of it every single
one Jesus Christ Katie you're fired
you see these giant teddy bears if I had
to enter this bear is the best spot
through the but can I get in trouble
from PETA for doing this he - cause it's
horrifying in there I hate today marks
the day I entered a teddy bear through
the body
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone it's your friendly neighborhood
teddy bear feel free to send nudes as
long as you're of age Shay healthy and
stay home
[Music]
[Applause]
what are you doing it's a PMO I always
hold my ass bro this is my guys
girlfriend I love Maya my god do my best
I put the sign outside hopefully I get
some some oh I actually got at the M
yeah I got my first new do check this
out look at it see how crazy my first
nude guys taking the internet by storm
if you haven't seen this man who are
missing ow
surely he's showing up in your group
chat or the most [ __ ] up friend that
you have sent you this man he's a legend
and so is his I'm getting nudes and I
got one like so two blocks ago you guys
saw a mysterious masked man vandalize
one of my art pieces not like 2:00 in
the morning let's be honest Mac we all
know it was you my roommate my best
friend since first grade he ruined my
masterpiece obviously I have to get him
back so Mac is actually an artist
himself and he has this one piece it's
his favorite piece of work it's his
masterpiece so a Mac was distracted we
took some high-definition pictures of it
we digitalized it and then we made an
exact replica this is identical now in
this very moment Mike is distracting Mac
I am swapping out his priceless real
painting for my exact replica I'm
bringing it to the backyard and there I
will destroy it with a flamethrower here
we go
[Music]
oh are you [ __ ] kidding me man and
there's other things you can do
that's [ __ ] [ __ ] you do you know how
much I love this [ __ ] painting this
hurts me this is not this is what you
like you like this painting man do you
like this one I would never ever destroy
your art I know I like it wasn't me
prove it was me original literally took
me like two months to mate so if you
destroyed the house like there's nothing
that you could do to repay the two
months of like time that I put into one
of those rocks and throw it at your head
bro like a base you're my best friend in
the world and you tried to kill me yeah
I know I protect my children at all
cause
make direct eye contact with it Evan now
kiss it whoa hey I hate to do this to
you please don't send me nudes oh yeah I
don't want to see you naked any of you
I'm sorry just don't