did you may have hired one why we should
have kids why are you down okay well
before he's anything else I want you to
see my pitch before this video starts we
are choosing the winner of this month's
$10,000 giveaway and beginning the Dodge
Challenger giveaway so go join the
Maverick club this week and get
automatically entered maverick clothing
calm okay enjoy the vlog [ __ ] these
dangers for us yeah oh yeah anytime my
hairline gets exposed I know it's fast I
mean not ladies one girl I have a
girlfriend
[Music]
[Applause]
the best part about this is you got a
bunch of grown-ass men each with like
multi-million dollar businesses monitor
out little dirt attract a lot of time to
think about growing out I don't ever
want to do that discuss if you know me
I've had these slippers for two years
these slippers have more mileage than my
[ __ ] car I've had sex in the slipper
people have had sex would be slipper
coronavirus started indeed slipper and
I'm ashamed to say I've never washed
them and needless to say they smell
absolutely [ __ ] putrid oh my I'm
gonna offer my roommates and friends
$100 to smell both of them with a little
twist
oh gotta test the sample the question is
more oh it's not that bad
yes it is I hate me too if that helps
it's like a prank boys one of the many
bonuses of the Maverick Club today we
took a couple members out bike riding
here in Santa Monica if I'm being honest
with you is cutest faux Danny something
horrifying this happen you're not gonna
believe it my chain fell off my chain
broke my chain today Manny what you
think got so much better days what you
think yeah
go to jig punk he's better alright
thanks guys nice why are you down okay
well before he's anything else I want
you to see my pitch why you should have
my baby by Logan Paul you're pretty hot
and I'm like I'm alright and I think
together we'd make a beautiful baby look
how cute she is it's not at all your dad
is Jose Canseco the homerun header and
my dad is well he's great Paul I have
reason to believe we'd have an athletic
baby just because of my dad well cuz
he's athletic what about your dad he's
great and then our athletic baby could
ride the horse I just got you I also
think a baby would make me mature faster
interested so far but I think you'll
like the next slide as you can see by
this chart income on the vlog channel
decreases over time but if you look
closely the income on the family channel
increases over time do you wanna have a
kids you can make more money yeah
take the ACE family for example they had
a good run they're really entertaining
and awesome but step aside A's family
it's time for the Paul's all right I
feel like do you think I don't know
there's only one way to find out baby
what do you say
you know what you might have changed my
mind really kid by myself you stick your
face in the dog poop baby you smell too
inside then smell that
[Music]