you all right dude just try to get like
you said you're full blood I was his
blood not mine
shut up oh there's my big man oh my god
were you lonely were you lonely fun
everyone ditched the house for fourth of
July
he's been so lonely and depressed I
caught him howling alone on the security
footage it literally broke my heart but
I back home back in and see no we ready
to [ __ ] some [ __ ] up okay it's about 85
inches I that's right about 86 that
should be good
[Music]
if you wanted the whip yeah for the
music video you said yeah yeah I guess
so you gonna back me Friday shoots on
Saturday can you get back to me Monday I
got you okay hi thanks for right now
spoken Josey it looks like you're wrong
knows you said that no one ever want to
see me eat I had a letter so I tweeted
it it looks like a lot of people
disagreed with her just as I thought I
hate lettuce I feel so bad for you just
get woken up by a morning sucks but you
know I owe you like morning lettuce my
stomach's starting to hurt I brought an
emergency supply of balsamic really
great started off so funny and now I'm
just kind of miserable
oh no you gentlemen want our head of
lettuce down the hatch I'm gonna go
throw up poop and make out my girlfriend
in that order look at this sad in dying
plans does this look like a healthy plan
to you no no bro this is a flaccid penis
plan where am I going with this okay you
guys may know we were stalked her
maverick crew necks hoodies and shorts
and I don't think people truly
understand how high quality of these
garments sells we're gonna do a little
product test cuz it's literally nothing
like this on the Internet this material
is thick way thick so Danny's gonna pour
some water in here just watch what
happens with that look at that look at
that okay now if you look closely the
waters holding the waters get holding
after a little bit of time the water
will start to seep through buying little
droplets Wow that is absolutely
beautiful now I'm gonna use these
droplets from the Maverick clothing to
water this poor dying little plant now
if you do this long enough eventually
because of the magic of the brand the
plant becomes once again big beautiful
elections yes it literally can revive
things just like it did with my career
back in 2017 join the movement maverick
clothing calm this stuff will sell out
quick so congrats if you can get one
before time went down oh [ __ ] what is it
a big box oh not a big crate you got a
crate you're doing great oh my gosh you
should have said you're doing crate
with Karen oh I wish I would have read
that before we carried it it can shark
it should go in the ocean don't you
think that kind of defeat the purpose of
taking it out of the ocean and then
making into a mouth out of the
hammerhead shark do on this test nailed
it
you guys remember I actually caught this
shark when I was in Miami that's the
joke it's not the same shark actually
this is plastic PETA you can shut it
Charlotte already from King sailfish
Malan this thing is actually beautiful
how the only question is what are we
gonna do with it what are we going to do
with it you [ __ ] stop oh there it is
now oh my god
[Music]
I'm sorry to bother you but there's a
shark in the neighborhood so just be
careful oh my god you should probably go
back inside
no you just say it for safety reasons
wrong way yeah there's a nine-foot shark
right here so just be careful oh there
it is now there it is now
George George like don't like lick your
lips really do anything if you have
blood on you yeah don't lick your lips
George everyone knows that's crucial
he's bleeding now so I'm gonna turn the
key 1 1 9 you're a dude just try to get
his blood not mine
listen he got mouthy with me and he
tried he didn't just try to fight it out
like why don't--you're not can get rowdy
there's no water first of all who the
[ __ ] is this I don't know if they've
been sitting there forever
y'all make a noise like I'll roar like a
lion sharks don't make
[Music]