can you draw my but I know he got a
happy Mother's Day mom happy Mother's
Day I love you Jake and I got some for
you what
Trish oh yeah sure as long as you put on
your only fans ma like your girlfriend's
up to something I want to facilitate
it's totally gonna be worth I'm sorry I
don't like the feeling of this need you
to get your camera I didn't take the
pics - I told you it's a girl that's
amazing
ma'am your baby I hate to tell you this
is obese little baby you look like a big
baby Marc I knew I was not the only one
losing my mind in quarantine
I come to chases warehouse today and
he's got a full-on play table sumo ring
knows about me I'm sumo wrestle in the
past this is one point that I won't lose
oh no this could only end badly this
Lord as well
whoa get this is for the kid
oh yeah hey here's the key bro cookie I
don't do anything chef Caitie does it
all things I did some nice I actually
have a confession the other day when you
made egg and I made the bread I made it
look [ __ ] going in and I said no it's
the look and feel of the food he's smart
made the food that chef Caitie cook to
look bad so your girl would think you
cooked it then you brought it to her
while she was in bed what have you
excuse me how bad is it give me better
tell me tell me now right everybody
finger yep right yep that's the spot yep
I said parsley what is that no I was
just saving it for later hey I'm 25
years old I'm basically an adult let's
cut the immature [ __ ]
please help me put these small ball pit
balls into that giant clear bowl
above you
oh it is real sturdy you could probably
take some serious listening to music for
two hours two hours straight
[Music]