[Music]
she called me four times during a
four-minute period I didn't that's crazy
Tom angry yeah that crazy [ __ ] Alana's
problem is that she's so hot she's also
so crazy she's in the upper right hand
corner of the hot crazy major she's
right on the edge of danger zone and
date zone I've been doing great I've
been doing a great job been supportive
I've even done a few things for her only
fans with no pay to me what are we done
on our own i glaze the doughnut oh oh
you're a secondhand porn star look I
hope it works out
honestly I give this breakup 12 hours I
was wrong it took them 14 hours to get
back together I want to ask you a
question where do you think you lie on
the hot crazy major all right guys you
could be right I might be the crazy one
because I love Mike told you this
tomorrow we saw aliens that was why she
blocked me because we went out and saw
the aliens I'm so happy I'm single right
there right there oh you can see that
you can see that going behind the trees
right there that right there is gonna be
a stone okay there's no star in the
world did it just get higher so long
right here look there's another way lose
my [ __ ] minds
seeing aliens is on my bucket list I'm
not joking worried about my anus heard
they probe your anus you know I like to
spoil my children we have been building
this cage for our new bird get a side
egg on the nose Wow not even a birdie
you've still got a beak hahaha
spread your wings and fly into this
prison this is your new home at night
we're going through my room and this is
where you'll sleep this is so weird
warrantees forces to get more creative
cuz we're bored ish I've had these
bungee cords for two years put them on
the ceiling and across notifications on
to I'm gonna do this this is the best
idea we've ever done on this channel are
you
[Applause]
[Music]
overcome his fear of heights a real time
that was a good exercise
[Music]
basketballs nerf what whatever might as
well finish him off and want a game
[Applause]
[Music]
maybe you trade