[Music]
you all see Evan take a tumble
[Laughter]
yeah sad is one of the fakest things
ever seen everyone knows your and
they're just trying to bring me down
you're already I've called together this
house meeting because there's something
about locking down the house like for
real for real talking about containing
the virus should lock it down but first
make sure we get our girls in here
poorly quarantined by like Monday we're
like you can't leave your house yeah
Soler cuz the corona virus affects
electricity he does oh my so should we
go somewhere the corona virus has a
fatality rate in people my age 0.1% you
know what the fatality rate of spending
the rest of my life with gets like this
zombie apocalypse is happening this is
insane we need him up
our generation has never really had its
disaster like the boomers had the real
estate market crash our grandparents had
like the world wars and the Great
Depression and I think this pandemic
might be ours this is crazy I feel so
dumb like getting ready for literally
doomsday oh hey I'd hate so much if we
did nothing and then they turn into like
a zombie apocalypse and I'm stuck with
my hands down my pants nice work
everything that's in my pocket if you
make it in that Cup
[Music]
okay can we talk about for one sec like
bunny rabbits how many times have you
had sex today like 1:00 p.m. we're gonna
play a little game today it's called pin
the tail on the donkey you know this
game the rules are simple you pin this
tail on the donkey you get $1,000 except
there is a twist I gotta trust me I'm
gonna move around a little bit you got
nothing to worry about Mike you're right
where I put you go
[Music]
it's so soothing to me yeah I don't know
why it's just like I don't have to think
about the world's problem
look at the speed look Dave yuzu man and
I know look at this is strong look at
this is very Shawn I probably pull some
like Rapunzel's like with this
[Music]
oh my god that's a strong brace let it
touch my braids bro really tight really
yeah
strong right no she is
[Music]