you're already so hyper tonight you're
comforting me like that
so we're driving on the highway right
now and you guys know this sometimes you
look off the highway you see some pretty
weird [ __ ] well we just saw this little
lone chair
sitting on the side of the highway it
was all by itself and mike said yo we
gotta go stop we gotta go sit on the
chair and i said no we both can't go
only one of us can go sit on this
there's only one [ __ ] chair this is
stupid
i'm gonna find this [ __ ] chair and
you and i as men as brothers as best
friends we're gonna play musical [ __ ]
chairs on the side of the highway mark i
see it
it's right there what the [ __ ] what the
[ __ ] is this place i heard my name we're
almost there mike you got it it's right
behind you
wow there it is two competitors one
chair let's [ __ ] do
[Music]
oh man i'm this fun are you [ __ ]
kidding
me
i got something i'm really excited about
guys piano but you play tunes with your
feet
i think we should do like a beethoven
[Music]
symphony
[Applause]
all right in the next 24 hours i'm gonna
make my best friend mike the happiest
he's ever been in the entire
world and then i'm gonna crush that
happiness into a million pieces
literally all right so if you guys
follow mike you know that there's been
one thing that he will not stop talking
about i have to have it
right now yeah that's right he ordered
an 1100
industrial grade slushie machine except
i talked to him yesterday and apparently
he's run into a massive problem the
machine's held up in customs man it's
not going to be here until august 16th
we have all the slushy bags yeah so they
accidentally sent like seven gallons of
slushy mix but no slushie machine for
another three weeks
it's like having a bunch of condoms but
no dick
yeah yeah i feel that i knew mike
couldn't wait that long so i went ahead
and bought him the same exact slushy
machine as a backup and mine happened to
arrive this morning
oh this is amazing oh my god i've never
seen something so perfect in my life
besides you babe besides you babe nice
save so i'm gonna give it to mike and
then when he's gone take it to an
industrial warehouse crush it with a
hydraulic press then shred it into a
million pieces
and make a slushie out of his slushie
machine
got something boys so this is for
everyone but really mike
it's just for you
how i come into the house today and mike
goes yeah i made one of my first big
purchases
ever it's a slushie machine now i got
stuck at the border right or so you
thought
shut up why don't you taste one
come on drink it drink drink up first
[Music]
there's no way that's real i just always
wanted a slushie oh god
boys the blue [ __ ]
oh my god it tastes exactly like
carnival slushie yep
how do you think i made this
let me show you something now let me
show you something come on
[Music]
it's beautiful why did you buy a slushy
maker before i bought a slash
no no no i bought it for you because
yours wasn't coming you bought me a gift
yeah why would you do that remember the
gift i give you is terrible i know but
you're my friend and i love you you got
your own slushy machine michael
yeah yeah yeah that a boy
come on there's gotta be a catch bro
there's gotta be a cat there's no catch
this is your machine
[Music]
i'm about to email those people and tell
them i don't need the other slushie
machine right now
wouldn't do that just yet if i were you
michael
there we go
ready to get it smooth actually you know
what
forget the smoothie i think i will get a
slushy
what's this what happened to my slushy
machine
it's out of order what happened
my god i've never seen a slushy dream
die so quickly
[Music]
i lied bro there was a catch good old
logan paul
how would you do something like that
it's not funny that's mean
yours is coming i just no i cancelled it
yesterday
they took me off the waiting list yeah
oh [ __ ] oh now it's just sad michael
please
i'll leave back mike please
[Music]
if i told you when i splooged now it
shoots out blue slushy
i'll probably leave now you guys can do
your thing