Oh who the krusty krab pizza I'm
watching you stick your gum under the
desk so as I hopefully the world is my
scrape it all off and then and then give
someone in the house like 5k to start
chewing on a friend oh I bet David the
jury would you want would you guys need
to do it for 500 this is so gross and we
haven't even seen the gum yet how long
have you been putting down into roughly
198 episodes of impulse
this is wild Mike making one big love
you're the new Willy Wonka making the
first Everlasting Gobstopper 30 seconds
like you really have to sink in there go
post hide in Warwick Knights speed
you're enjoying it 30 seconds for
another 100 baht I want to see you two
in bro goo you're about to hit a minute
for 600 bucks another hundred dollars if
you could blow a bubble tea maverick is
disgusting my powerpoint still didn't
work and Josie will stop her birth
control baby come on let's do spider-man
kiss yeah welcome to life of being a
blogger [ __ ] you dumb [ __ ] for content
now sit your ass that what the [ __ ]
Peyton Peyton my editor will see your
boobies your tits are out
oh I'm already grumpy but the good news
is we're going to Vegas I got cash on
back I'm pretty sure lose all of it
girlfriend sizer boobs out the animals
George has animals covered I got a fun
game for us to play on the plane super
original youtubers have never done this
before it's called bean boozled
I cut the giveaway oh yeah these
pictures don't correlate with any okay
look they're kinda random we're working
on it you could install a home screen
[Music]
yeah by the end of this weekend we will
have selected the first winner for a ten
thousand dollar monthly giveaway the
exclusive piece of content is going out
this weekend is also sick if you guys
aren't members say I'd go sign up the
links in the description or club not
matter clothing calm definitely one of
the coolest things in the world getting
to connect with you guys in a more
intimate level and I'm excited to see
where this goes now gonna end this vlog
with a bang you've probably seen this on
tick-tock you're about to see it on
YouTube the Krusty Krab pizza is the
pizza for you in
[Music]