it is not enough to be not racist you
have to be anti-racist yes believe it or
not this is progress but Logan if you're
gonna talk seriously about racial
injustice King move squirtle all right
jokes aside guys as you know we took
last week off from the vlogs as we tried
to push the message of equality in case
you didn't see my video I'm stunned that
we even have to still push that message
but apparently we do and I will not be
on the wrong side of history I'm gonna
make sure you people vote because we
made a lot of noise last week we went to
the protest we had the viral videos the
biggest thing to actually enact change
is gonna be meaningful follow up so
basically if you see a racist person
punch them in the [ __ ] throat don't
do that I actually probably do that and
then we just got a vote cuz the correct
thing to do here is make sure we're
putting people in office that will give
us the change that we so desperately and
unfortunately need so yeah register to
vote I'm gonna do it I know it's kind of
tedious we gotta [ __ ] do it I'm done
preaching thank you guys for listening
if you listen it's not you I'm sorry
what having phone sex with my girlfriend
last night and I'm going down and I
moved and it threw my back out she's
like I did you finish I'm like no no
don't tell that story to anyone please
George apparently learned how to do a
back flip yesterday he's convinced that
he could do it right now
[Music]
watching you do this makes me want to
see if I can still do it last time I did
a backflip my brother still had a Disney
show actually the last time I did a
backflip I was on his Disney show it's
been like three years old man now I'll
be honest all the reason I think I was
able to do that is because of my mad for
clothing it's a two-dimensional painting
yeah I had a 3d artist by the name of
Tracy Lee stump come and paint this do a
little interior renovation here because
we finally got rid of the $90,000
couches thank god you're not worth
having next to nothing because the dude
Eric who bought I went couchsurfing
literally dropped them out of an
airplane and then blew them up but now
we got this hole in the ground so I
don't know if you all know that during
quarantine Nintendo switches have been
like really hard to get all of my
roommates and friends have been bored as
[ __ ] and they all want one but they
haven't been able to find all no I'll
take it where did you find that I want
to get everyone together sit them all
down and then I'm gonna put a note card
in front of I'm gonna count down and
have them flip it over now whoever
reveals the black circle gets a switch
little do they know if you reveal this
black circle you get the Nintendo switch
[Applause]
[Music]
as I love you people absolutely right
but I still love you past week all I've
done was getting trouble for my girl
[Music]