oh I'm sexually frustrated
[Music]
hi boys I got something good more boxes
sorry this box this is a male fertility
test we're gonna be able to measure our
sperm count you can finally see how many
sperms are in your penis no I'm tired of
jizeen trying to count there's a bit of
bad news actually the exact opposite we
have to jerk each other off I need y'all
to stop a Jackie lady for 2 to 5 days
I'm looking to you Mike I'll look at you
all masturbate all right boys
your dicks are officially out of order
hey hey don't you touch I don't doesn't
yours to the point we had to start
checking do I see if you're looking a
rugged like someone's been tugging on it
I'll do those checks don't worry boy
[Music]
we're just watching chef Katie beat her
meat I gotta say I'm pretty jealous hey
hey hey hey got your hands off the extra
garlic I thought you knew Mike and we
did it twice you two need to get you
together cuz I need you to fill this up
tomorrow completely I just thought a
calm that for a young stud like me look
at what Evan just texted what I mean
what do you mean no no like this David
he said yo can we go until tomorrow I'm
cramping bad I need to nut stop the door
[Applause]
what do you mean you're cramping where
I'm a ball so you're not cramping in
your vas deferens it's a part of my
balls I have removed coz dead only 15%
ladies you are so close all of us are
[Music]
[ __ ] look and you stay away from that
[ __ ] you're weak
okay you're being a little [ __ ] snap
out of it Logan I'm sexually frustrated
[Music]
all right boys congratulations the time
has finally come
what attended highly impressed and proud
of all of you it's been 48 hours minimum
so feel free to go ahead and go Chuck
your ticket into
[Music]
[Applause]
dollars that's all you say it this is
valuable semen most importantly what
everybody would everybody watch this
morning you know that uh the girl who
sucks off the bananas
she makes real porn now she's talking
real dicks now instead of fruit I
haven't you one of the people that
watches poured for the storyline find
out a nerdy joy
let's go ship these out
all right the results are in are any of
us infertile I know none of you are
infertile
Oh 1.5 milliliters in their semen sample
10% of their sperm was swimming and you
had 21 million swimming sperm in your
sample of my sperm are swimming that
means the other 90% have died from bong
rips and coming in just just above mic
coming in just above my guys you had
three male milliliters of semen in your
sample 75 percent of your sperm were
swimming and you had 30 million swimming
sperm David no it means you have 30
million healthy German sperm swimming on
your balls third place is three
milliliters of semen 73 percent of your
sperm was swimming and you had 94
million sperm second place three
milliliters of semen 133 million
swimming sperms in your sample whopping
well you only had 294
194 fell well I do it I do it last [ __ ]
I'm the most [ __ ] fertile dude I know
see this squirtle that's a fertile
squirrel
[Music]
[Applause]