When you ask somebody: "What do you want for Xmas?"
We all have one friend that give you that SMARTA** answer and says something completly out of your price
well, now it's your chance to give a smarta** answer back
here at fuzzbee we compiled the list of 10 most highly requested gifts that are out of your price rate and how YOU can steel get them in the cheapest punny way possible
Hey, merry Xmas man.
Is this just cardboard
Yeah, but it used to be a BOX, see? Now it's an XBOX
Big MAC? Is that MACklemore? What is this?
It's exactly what you asked for, MACBOOK
Here you go, man
Why did you give me a picture of Ariane Grande
Well look at what she's wearing.
What, FURR?
Yeah, cause I know how much you wanted that FU/ERRARI
I know how long you've been waiting for one of these, so
OMG
DIAMOND RING
Yep, biggest one I could find
What are you smiling about?
Oh, ah
Is that? -Yep, fresh new PAIR OF JORDAN
BEATS? -BEATS BY DRE
ROLL-X
I didn't even know you knew how to sew?
Oh, it's not sewn, I KNITed it, it exactly what you asked for, remember?
I don't recal asking for the letter O and E
Yeah but you did ask for a NINTENDO E (KNIT AN O E)
I know how much you love the movie, so
Here you go, it's a DVD
FROZEN
THAT`S NOT FUNNY, RYAN!! YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE THAT MOVIE!!
C'MON, it was JUST a joke, maybe you should just LET IT GO
CAN YOU STOP?!! CAN YOU JUST BE SERIOUS FOR ONCE?!!
YOU KNOW I ONLY WANTED THIS MOVIE SO WE CAN WATCH IT TOGETHER!!!
Oh, don't worry, we can still WATCH IT, the DVD IS actualy in there. we just have to be careful when we're cracking the ice 'cause we don't wanna scratch ('cause we don't wanna be watching it and then halfway through the movie it's freezes)
FORGET IT!! -C'MON, G IT WAS A JOKE!
You know what, if you not even going to try, I don't even know why I bother
OK, look, I was gonna wait until after the joke but...
You actualy DID get it
I wasn't gonna NOT give you what you wanted for Xmas
here let me put it in...
Where is the TV??
Yeah, about that, I kind a sell it for all the puns in this video and I need to buy materials
WHAT?!! WE CAN STILL WATCH IT ON YOUR MACBOOK!!
Wait, where is the, where's all the ma...
Oh, you know what, this MACBOOK might be FROZEN 2
FROZEN 2!!
TEEHEE