Alright. Who's first?
Me.
You can call me Sam.
Uncle Sam.
Okay, Uncle Sam. Let's see what you've got.
Do the Uncle Sam
The Uncle Sam (X3)
Do the Uncle Jim
The Uncle Jim (X3)
Do the Uncle Sam and the Uncle Jim
The Uncle Sam and the Uncle Jim
Look at my feet, baby.
Look like I have four feet, like an animal.
Everybody to the dancing
Before you do romancing
What the hell was that?
I was dancing!
Pong, was that dancing?
It was kind of-
You shh, and you, get out.
Next.
Hey, guys.
I'm Duke. I'm here to dance for you guys.
I hope you guys like it.
Don't worry, I saw this guy dance before.
He's really good.
Oh he'd better be good, Pong.
'Cause If he's not, I'm ripping up that drawing you made for me this morning.
(Electronic Dance Music starts to play)
(Gasps)
Hi, I'm Vanessa, and I'll be doing my routine.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Give me a B!
B!
Give me an E!
E!
Give me a-
Get the hell out of my office!
Next.
What- What are you doing here?
What do you mean? It's my first time!
We just saw you five minutes ago.
No, that was my twin brother, Uncle Sam!
He doesn't have the mustache like me!
You're clearly the same person you're wearing the same clothes.
What do you mean?! My brother's not as handsome as me!
What's that one?
Next.
I don't need that girl in my life
I don't need that girl by my side
I don't want-
This is a dance audition!
Oh, I'm s-
You're right, you're right! Okay.
(Clap hands) I don't need that girl in my life
I don't need that girl by my si-
Get out!
Ow!
(Breathes Deeply)
I'm here to do the dancing!
(Stomps Foot)
(Grabs box out of person and box on the ground)
(Screams punches and lands)
Hi, uh, we're here for the audition?
Whatever.
Five, four, three, two, one
(Heavy-Bass Techno Music starts to play)
Wow, that was- That was amazing!
Stunning!
That was incredible!
So beautiful!
You guys are exactly what we don't need.
We're on Youtube.
We wanted a third member, not a fourth.
Nothing good comes in fours.
You know what comes in fours? Squares.
We'll take one of you.
One of us?
Na, we don't need them.
Y'all are whacked.
Look at those stupid bumblebee outfits.
I don't even know what that is.
You call yourself a crew?
You'll never be a crew.
You shut your dirty mouth!
(Both make mocking noises)
Rave, don't listen to them.
As long as we believe in each other, right?
I don't believe in you.
But I believe in you twice as much.
(Hands right next to him and hands backs up)
Who are you?
Are you here for the audition?
(Awe-Inspiring Music starts to play)
You're in!
Mm, thanks Rave.
This is the best day ever.
Hey, you guys like ice cream too?
Teehee!
Uncle Jim! No, he's...
I'll find out.
(Laughter)
(Laughs)
(Mutters)
This is the best day ever.
It's fine, right?
Yes, Kevin. It's fine.
This doesn't go on the Internet, or anything, right?