Alright...
Fandom name, group color, new song
That's all we gotta figure out today. Easy!
Why're we doing this again?
That's what we need in order to be a K-pop band
Says who?
Everyone! The comments, uh, Google?
The hell's a fandom name?
A fandom name is basically what the fans call themselves
Right
Y'know like,
Justin Bieber's fans are called Beliebers
Uhm, don't we all ready have a fandom name?
The BgA ARMY?
According to the comments,
That's already taken by some other group called, like,
"Behind the Scenes" or whatever
Well, since our first and only song is about poop...
Again, thank you for that David
What?
Maybe sumthin like uh...
K-poopers?
Yeah
Yeah, that makes sense.
I don't care.
That's pretty cool, but uhm
Do you think the fans would like being called poopers? [Well,
FUCK YEA!
Uhm, okay
Yeah, most of the fans are girls and girls like poop jokes so...
Cool. Alright, we got our fandom name
Uh, next thing on the list...
We got group color
I'm just gonna throw it out there
I personally like silver
I could do silver
Right?
But that's like, second place.
What?
Gold is first, silver is second
*snaps fingers* Gold, GOLD THO
I look good in gold, ya know what I'm sayin'?
Y'know, you know what I mean
No. No, I don't know what you are saying
So what color do you wanna choose?
Gold
Oh, me too
Okay, we have two for gold, two for silver.
Jun, be our tie-breaker.
I'm- I'm fine with either
Yes, so which one do you prefer?
Yeah, which one is better, gold or silver?
Obviously gold, right?
Don't you dare convince him
Pick one, you idiot
C-can we do both?
Yeah, I don't see why not
Actually, I've never really thought of that before
Yeah, I've never seen two colors...
Yeah, we could have, like, the glowsticks that K-pop groups have?
Like, a silver and gold option...
Yeah, and then we could have our logos like "BgA" or sumthin' like that
Oh god, that is the dumbest idea ever
Silver and gold doesn't even go together
Who's gonna buy these glowsticks?
I'm not putting my money in for that garbage, man
Look, y'know what? We'll just come back to it 'cuz it's not that important.
What we really need to figure out...
New Song
We've haven't had a song since last year
Well whatever it's about, I better get some lines in this one because you took all the lines last time
Obviously. I'm the leader
*scoffs*
You're the leader?! Are you kidding me? I'm obviously the lead
Have you not read my Twitter feed? They all say so
Have YOU read the comments? You're like everybody's least favorite
Yeah, because you hog all the lines!
Okay, I'm pretty sure Jun is everyone's least favorite
I don't care about being the leader. I just better be higher than Jun, 'kay?
I think I'm about the second place 'cuz I like silver
What, silver?! You just said that you like gold.
Now you're flip-flopping but all of a sudden...
*random gibberish*
ALRIGHT, alright!
okay
We're not gonna get anywhere like this
There's only one way of figuring out who the leader is
How?
We make a song, with everybody in it, equally
And then we just see what happens
Okay but what's the song gonna be about?
Exactly what we've been talking about the entire time
Who's it gonna be?
Oh. My. God.
That better not be the name of the song!
That is so chees-
*song starts*
K-poopers, where you at?
BgA
Let's go
*door opens*
Jun? Is that really you?
Wait, what are you guys doing?
Why do you look like that?
Look man... we're happy for you
We really are.
But, ever since you left the group
It's been really tough for the rest of us
Yeah, we've just been doing what we all can to get by
But, it's only been one week
Oh
Well, it's been a really tough week
Yeah yeah, seven days, long time
Why are you even talking to this traitor?!?!
HE LEFT US!
YOU! LEFT! US!
We know all about your talking to the manager and your little contract
So why are you even here?
Actually...
That's exactly why I'm here
This pretty much guarantees me fame, money and everything that we've been working for together as a group
But it says I have to do it alone, without you guys
Which is why I felt the need to come here and... do this
What's the point of fame and fortune if it's not with your guys?
Dude
The hell were you thinking, man?!
What?
Yeah, you could have taken the money and shared it with us!
Why would you even rip this man? Come on!
What're we gonna do now?
Do you think we can put this back together or what?
Like, if we could tape it
Glue! I have some glue in the car
Do you? Okay, then let's try to see if we have all the pieces like...
Hey.
Are those- *shocked* - Are those the glowsticks?
Told you... gold and silver...doesn't match
Tch, idiot
Aah, aah
Aaand it's--- SIGN SIGN SIGN SIGN! Sign right here!
Sorry guys, it's-it's gone
There. It's good. Let it go
Guys, it's in my email, I could print it out.
You're so--- *smacks*
TEEHEE