Dear Ryan, can you defeat a real ninja?
(ninja music)
Purple shirt guy appears
Walk so fast across that field
Who is he texting
Be free phone
Look of distaste
Needs new pair of sunglasses because he can't see a foot away in those
Baby who just ate a sour lemon face
Twenty goat
No no too much goat
Dramatic
This much goat
Anime movement
Strange ballerina movement
Intimidating fight the air movement
Non-intimidating fight the air movement
How do that
Magic
Fight the air
Gooooo air!
Air wins
W
O
WOW
Whoosh
pop
(crying)
Do you need me to call a WAH-mbulance
NOPE
TEEHEE
So leave a question in the comments below and you could be responsible for the next video
(laughter)
Okay one sec. Serious face.
Dee doop!
(laughter)
Okay, I think we got it