Every year of every day, each month of the week,
thousands, millions, even hundreds of people
continue to fall victim to FWPs.
I'm so sick.
I have no place to sleep tonight.
So hungry, and there's nothing to eat.
Also known as, first world problems.
I'm so sick of these routine doctors check ups.
There's never anything wrong with me.
I have no place to sleep tonight.
My friends took the bed and the couch.
So hungry, and there's nothing to eat.
I mean on this little carb diet sure
I can have all the steak I want, but a steak without the potatoes.
Hi, I'm Ryan Higa.
You may remember me from the first FWP campaign.
When not only are FWP's still around,
but they're getting much, much worse.
My phone always dies at my friends house,
and all he had is the old iPhone charger.
Too much clothes. Drawers won't close.
It's like having a mountain in my way,
and every time I get over it, there's always another.
Why did God even have to make speed bumps?
Ignoring the problem does not make you go away.
My hands are so big.
I can never reach the bottom half of the Pringles can.
These people are continuing to suffer every single day.
I just bought this dress yesterday, and now it's on sale?
These FWP's, first world problems,
whatever you want to call them, aren't going anywhere
unless you do something about them.
My boyfriend didn't text me back,
but he just tweeted.
It's like everything I built came crashing down all at once.
The poop already began. Phone not in hand.
I'm so hungry. I already brushed my teeth.
The pool was too cold. The Jacuzzi's too hot.
I ordered the salad. Now I'll never taste the soup.
My owner got me bacon treats,
but they're not even barbecue flavored.
But now there's a way you can help,
by calling the number 1-800-www.FWP@gmail.org/
:) / :( /dancing lady in red dress//
We'll send you the FWP helper kit, which includes an open book.
Here's an open book. Now shut it.
(Shuts the book)
A miniature batch of wine.
Here's a mini batch of wine.
Now you can stop being such a little winey batch.
And a complete poker set,
including a case, chips, cards,
and not to mention, poker sunglasses.
I don't mean to be heartless, but welcome to the club.
In case you didn't notice, there's no one here who gives a chip
so if you could just cut it out,
grow a four king pair, and deal with it, that would be just amazing.
With your help, we can put an end to FWP's for good,
and focus on the real problems, like
violence, or drugs, or people who still
don't know which you're to use.
The Biebs, Crocs, yellow starburst.
The real issues at hand.
So please, join me. Help a soul, and help us all.
The heck is that...
Oh...
My internet's so slow it always has to buffer first.
Teehee!
So thank you guys so much for watching.
If you want to see bloopers and behind the scenes, click on the left.
If you want to see the previous FWP video, click on the one on the right.
And if you don't want to click any of them at all,
then that's kind of a problem,
and that'll be sad for me.