Every year of every day, thousands of people fall victim to FWP.
I'm so cold.
I'm starving.
Nobody cares about me.
Also known as First World Problems.
I'm so cold.
Somebody set the A/C to 72.
I need it at 73.
Starving, all we have is leftovers.
Nobody cares about me. Nobody commented or liked my status.
Hi, I'm Ryan Higa.
And for just five hours of attention a day,
you can help somebody with FWP.
Everyone keeps putting so much pressure on me.
I don't know what I want for my birthday.
I have too much chips for my dip.
But if I open a new dip, I'll have too much dip for my chips.
Why does Apple keep making new iPhones?
Now I have to get another one.
They've been through so much struggle.
The remotes over there, but I'm all the way over here.
So much hardship.
My iPhone 5 is too big for my skinny jeans.
So much attention.
(Attention X3)
I poured my cereal without checking to see if we had milk.
We didn't.
So please. Show your support, and send them this video.
And show them how much we care about their FWPs.
I bought so many groceries.
Now I'll have to make two trips.
All you have to do is call the URL, 1-800-DOT-ORG.
And we'll send you the FWP Helping Kit.
Which includes a bridge, a straw, and a full cup with the cover.
Here's a bridge. Now get over it.
Here's a straw. Now suck it up.
Here's the full cup. Now shut the full cup.
(Closes the lid)
With your help. we can put an end of F.W.P.s.
And focus on the real problems,
like starving children, or homeless people.
Because if you're complaining about something as silly as the iPhone 5,
just wait until you see the iPhone 6.
Oh this? This is the iPhone 5s.
This is the iPhone 6.
(Screams & Bams)
Teehee!