Hey guys, so I...
Wait, why does it look so different in here?
huh
Anyway um, hey guys so over the 10 to
almost 11 years that I've been on YouTube, I've gotten to do a lot of things
that I never thought I'd be able to do before and I'm sure if you ask any other youtubers that I've been around
for that amount of time, they'll agree with me when I say that people start
treating you like you're some kind of genius professional
social media expert and I'm sure it is true for a lot of those youtubers
who actually do consider themselves geniuses.
But for me even after 10 years of doing this, I still don't think
I know exactly what I'm doing. I'm borderline dumb when it comes to this stuff. I just make the videos that I
like making and luckily people watch them. I don't have some genius
strategy or like expertise that I could share with everyone which is why I
bring this up. I get asked all the time to attend these like
huge business conferences and meetings where people
pretty much just ask for my expertise on social media
and they treat me like I'm one of the all-knowing of social media and to be honest
when I go to these things, I feel completely out of place.
People that attend these things are like millionaire billionaire men and women
that own multiple businesses and they're all taking notes and
advice from this 26 year old college dropout with
stupid looking hair talk about YouTube and all the
expertise and knowledge that I have to share with them.
I mean I don't like to brag but I think I pretty much killed it.
So tell us Ryan, how does one get started on YouTube?
Um...well you see you have to make an account by clicking the sign up button
Okay are there any complications or problems that one might run into when starting a channel
and if so, how do you solve them?
Well I mean sometimes your username can already be taken so you solve that by adding like
a number to it or you could you know change a letter like you can make an e into like a 3
like backwards e.
Alright, one last question. How do you come up with your ideas?
Well, ideas are just thoughts
and everyone has thoughts. I mean I have thoughts right now, this meeting
could be a video idea. You know, like I could make literally this meeting a video.
Well, lets hope you don't do that because this is a very confidential meeting.
I mean it's already happening.
What?
Writing the video right now.
You really can't do that
It's too late. This is gonna be a video.
We can and we will sue you if you make a video about this event.
Okay, sure.
Oh yeah, that's why I have no stuff.
Ha, I'm just playing
But in all seriousness, having to hang out with these uh
Maybe we'll call them graduates
I started noticing some patterns between them.
Not just the successful ones but more so with the unsuccessful ones
that are appearing to be successful.
and today I'm gonna be teaching you just that.
How to sound smarter than you really are.
One of the easiest way to appear smarter than you really are is to dress the way they dress
but you see if you dress poorly, you'll look stupid.
For example, if you dress like a hobo or like a poor person, you'll never get any respect and
people will never think you're smart.
I mean take a look at this guy, you think people actually think this guy is smart and successful?
No
Or even if you wear like a plain shirt like this guy, you think anybody's gonna think you're smart and dress like that?
No!
If you want people to take you seriously, if you want people to think that you're smart
you have to dress smart.
Dress for success and only then will people believe that you're a genius.
Like this.
Pretty self-explanatory.
Normal people like you and I have a dictionary
they have a thesaurus
A lot of people just like to use words that people don't use as often.
For example, if someone is giving you the choice to pick between two options,
rather than just saying which option you want, you say "I'll take the latter".
So, which one would you like? A or B?
You know what, I'll take the latter.
Uhh but which one would you like?
The latter.
Oh, the latter. Oh ok, so you want the second one?
No, the ladders.
Oh, you want the first one?
Just the ladders?
So you want both of them or?
Oh my god, I'm just gonna get them myself then.
The letters!
Smart people always want to know what you do.
They always make their job sound way more important than it really is.
School janitor? More like certified educational hygienist.
Cashier? More like financial trades and delivery operator.
Stripper? More like prostitutional entertainer that does not engage in sexual activity for money.
See? Any job can sound important.
Even if you're not employed right now, it's 2017
everybody is working, they think.
What did you say you did again?
Oh, I am a freelance independent entrepreneurial leader in social media, marketing and research relations.
Meaning you're unemployed and you post and read comments on facebook?
and twitter too.
I see.
Well congratulations, you're hired!
Really?
Yeah, you can start as early as this evening.
Oh? this is a night job, what exactly was my job title again?
Oh well a prostituitional entertainer that does not engage in sexual activity for money.
Oh
Except minus the latter part of that.
The latter part? What does that
You'll probably have to engage.
Doesn't matter how smart you are if you hang out with people smarter than you
you're gonna be the dumb one.
So it's simple. Just hang out with people less intelligent than you.
If you think you're the dumbest person out of everyone you know
then well..you still have options.
Hey Marley.
You want bread? You want the bread? Go get it!
Hahaha idiot.
Wait, what?
Dumbass.
The real test to show that you're really smart...
Art.
Truly intelligent people can see art in everything
no matter how hard it is to see for the rest of you dummies.
Oh my god, it's so beautiful.
It's a masterpiece.
How is this part of the art exhibit?
Don't you see? This represents life.
Life itself. You start from nothing and you slowly make your way to the top.
For only a moment before falling all the way back down..
to nothing.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Wait, are you guys looking for the art exhibit? That's across the street.
I've come to find that this last one is 100% accurate.
All smart people must talk about politics.
And if you're anything like me, you probably know very little to nothing about politics.
So if you ever happen to get caught in a discussion with a smart person talking about politics
just agree with them.
That way they'll just keep talking and you won't have to.
-What's the deal with that? -Yeah it's pretty crazy
What do you think Ryan?
Um, I'm sorry what?
You know, about Trump and the wall between us and Mexico
What do you think about it?
Well, I mean like clearly we're...
it's talked about all over on the news and we're all
three of us are talking about it. 3 guys at a table during the day
so obviously yeah like 100% agree yup
but yeah, Trump is doing goo..a great job.
A great job?
At being horrible for the economy..just awful.
Well, I mean some people think he's actually helped the economy since he's became president
President? Right? He's been awfully great.
He's..he's a man that I just love
but come on? As a president, he's..
sucks!
killing it right now.
Yes ful..successful man that I just love love love!
He's killing all of our international ties.
..to make fun of because he's just so..
bad!
Right?
ass
He's a badass man.
That's why I completely support
that no country is gonna work with him
The other guy that he was running against
What?
I support the guy he was running against
Are you talking about Hillary Clinton?
Exactly! Right, Hillary Clinton.
Bill Clinton's mother..sis..
Bill's fam.
You know? But Obama tho
Right? Everybody loves him
He's got my vote locked in if you know what I mean
But you do know that he's not gonna be in the next election?
exactly what I was just about to say.
He can't run again.
He should not be running. He's getting old. He should be walking.
This is his final term. He can't have a third term.
Exactly why he needs to ace it. I mean
You know the finals are always worth more than the midterm.
Yeah, I can't really tell if you're joking or if you're just stupid.
The latter?
The latter!
Funny
Oh latter
Definitely gotta keep in touch. We'll see you later.
See you guys.
Oh my god, did I really just pull that off?
Oh my god, do you think he knew?
What the hell does a latter mean?
I don't know!
But again, with all jokes aside. It doesn't matter if you talk about politics a lot
or if you use big words like "the latter".
Everybody is different. Who's to say what's considered smart and what isn't?
Yeah maybe you did grow up being a straight A student your whole life
and you got a perfect SAT score
and maybe you did graduate from Harvard and got a PhD
and yes maybe you did start your own billion dollar company from scratch
Let me ask you this.
Do you know how to get your hair to this colour and how to maintain it?
Do you know how to cook and prepare a 3 course meal?
Do you know how to change a tyre or fix a leaking toilet?
or write, film and edit a video that's not too long and keeps the viewer's attention all the way to the end
without anyone clicking away because if you do...
I would love to learn.
Please teach me.