Hey guys!
So first of all I wanna say that I am sorry that I haven't posted a regular video like this in a while other than the podcasts.
I have been extremely busy the whole beginning of this year,
working on something I kept a secret for a while.
But I guess if you watch the podcasts or follow me on my Instagram,
you already know what that secret is.
Also, if you read the title, you probably know what the secret is as well.
I just released my own energy drink! *yay sound effect*
I didn't have the drink in my hand. I just released my own - oh, that's open. Own energy drink...energy!
It's too bright - you can't even see - guys, I released my own energy drink! Isn't this crazy?