I'm sitting on my bed
I'm contemplating life
All the struggles in my head...
I've been waiting for so long
Had time to write this song
What did I do wrong?
(Did I do wrong?)
I'm like a ghost in your chatroom
(Ghost in your chatroom!)
No-ones talking when I do
(Talkin' when I do!)
I'm always send in the best troops
(Send in the best troops!)
I got our clan name tattoo!
So why!
Does no-one like me!
You never invite me to war!
(To war...)
And I!
Wish you would send me!
My castle's empty!
I'm feeling so ignored!
Whoa! Woha! Woha! Whoooooooooa!
And I...And I just go to you?
Never missing your requests
That ever came from you.
(Came from you...)
Raid!
I'm raiding everyday!
As my archers die away.
I hunt elixir for your base to improve!
Another war is declared!
(A war is declared!)
But I'm not there!
(An' I'm not there!)
I quit my job for this crew...
(Got no mo' money!)
I got more clan name tattoos!
So why...does no one like me?
You never invite me...to war
(To war...)
And I...wish you'd send me, my castle's empty!
I'm feelin' so ignored!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoooooooooa!
My shields...are coming to an end...
My walls are broken in, I can't defend
from your negligence...
and right...right before my eyes...
I got notified to my surprise for the first time in my life!
I see troops! My castle is full!
I was wrong!
They cared all along!
But then I checked,
now I know I have no friends..
Cuz a real friend wouldn't send
Level 1 Goblins!!
So why?!
Does no one like me!?
You never invite me to war!
(To war!)
And I...wish you would SEND ME!
My castle's empty!
I'M FEELIN' SO IGNORED!!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoooooa!
Feelin' so ignored!!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whooooooa!
See, that's why no one plays Clash of Clans with you.
Oh...
So..
Game of War then?
YEAH!!!!
Oh... wait, our phones are broken!
So why...does no one like me? You never invite me to war...