First there was the board
Then, there was the skateboard
Then, there was the skateboard with steering
And now for the first time ever
It's here!
The cardboard!
The cardboard also know as the Cybord, Airbord, Rolling Device
Is the future of transportation
Why walk when you could be not walking?
Step, after step, after step
Aren't you sick of it yet?
Don't you rather just be on wheels all the time?
Well, with the cardboard,
you will never not, not be on wheels again
So what will it cost?
Similar products will cost you an arm and a leg
But thanks to the cardboard's advanced design
It won't cost you any body parts at all,
Just cash
And did we mention that the cardboard is completely customisable?
Of course we haven't, we're only at that part now
Well, the cardboard is completely customisable
You'll never have the same cardboard as someone else
With are crazy selection of colours, such as,
And for the really daring, you can even get it in, red,
Yellow,
Or, blue
All mixed together to create a nice, prominent brown
But that's not all!
You'll also be able to customise the safety straps aswell
And not to mention the headlights and tail lights too
So, how does it work?
Now i know what you're thinking,
The cardboard literately defines gravity
So does it really work?
Well the answer is simple,
Definitely maybe it might...
You see, gravity is nothing more than a science word
And so is the word oxygen
Also know as O2, to most scientists
Meaning there's two o's,
Tools!
And tools are what makes things work
Meaning that the cardboard, indeed works
The only place that the cardboard wouldn't define gravity,
Is in space
Because there is no oxygen
So how could you get the cardboard?
Well, unfortunately it is not available yet
We've been having a really hard time funding our kick starter campaign
Because all of the homophobic commenter trolls,
that keeps saying the cardboard is fake and gay
But before you type that in this video let me ask you this,
Does this look fake to you?
Exactly, fake and gay?
More like real and gay!
So how can you help?
Now that you know all of the facts and information,
you know have a choice
Nae
A decision
Nae!
A responsibility
Nae Nae
To help us make this world a better place
By bringing the cardboard to a reality
All you have to do is go to our kick starter campaign and donate as much as you can
Whether it's just a little bit or a lot,
As long as it's alot,
We'll take it
Because without you, the cardboard is just silly nelly
It's only just a dream
So donate now and bring the cardboard to life
And before you know it, we could all be looking like this
(Music by - Jack Elphick – Stadium Anthem Nr 08 – Alternative)
Oh yeah, it's a transformer as well too