- Hi sisters!
James Charles here and welcome back to my YouTube channel!
Oh my god you guys today's video I am so beyond excited
because as you can see I have
two very very iconic sister special guests!
- Jake
- And Riquelle
- You guys Jake and Riquelle are two of my favorite artists
to follow on Instagram right now.
They are both super young, Jake is 15, right?
And you are 17.
Both young and both killing it,
literally both of their looks are so insane,
so creative and they are just both so talented.
Both have been amazing friends and inspiration to me
and for today's video I wanted to bring them here
on my channel and do a beauty battle,
which I am so excited for because as you guys all know
this is a series I do here on my channel
where two different people take half my face of makeup
but in the past though, all the episodes
have been with friends that don't really know a lot
about makeup, but this is different
because this is literally two artists
who actually know what they're doing, doing half my face.
So the three of us are just gonna play in some makeup today,
Jake and Riquelle are gonna split my face right in half
and give me an iconic signature look in their very own style
and at the end of course all you sisters will decide
which look was your favorite in this little friendly
beauty battle, we're gonna talk about all things
in the beauty industry, what it's like being in the industry
at such a young age, because obviously you guys know
I came in when I was 16 years old too,
so right smack dab in the middle of you guys.
What it's like being a small influencer,
what the community can improve on,
and of course too you guys obviously know
I'm always here for you as friends
and I'm sure so many people watching this video
want to be an influencer one day
and really wanna join the makeup community,
and I feel like you guys are both
absolutely killing it right now
so it could be really fun to ask some questions as well
and I can kinda answer them and give you guys advice
and some other people want your advice too!
Sound good?
Okay - Let's do it
Without further ado, let's jump right in.
(uplifting music)
So do you guys have any ideas
to what look you wanna do yet?
- Since Valentine's coming up I think I wanna use
some inspo on the look I did.
- Okay love that, love that a little hearts moment.
Are you single?
- Yeah.
- Same - Fortunately.
- You?
- I'm just gonna do something rainbow, colorful.
- Okay, love that.
- Inspired by these.
- Ooh the rainbow nails, okay, down.
(tongue pop)
Love a good tongue pop moment!
That's good I feel like nobody can ever do that!
Wow that's good and fresh!
- Yes.
- Sorry Jake you're out of the picture now.
(gasps)
Replaced.
Well I feel like this is gonna be quite a long day
of lots of glamming, this is gonna be a little bit
of an unusual beauty battle, slightly longer than normal
so should we just jump right in?
- Yes.
- Alright go for it.
- Okay.
- My face is your canvas.
- Just go?
- Yeah go for it!
- Okay I'm just brushing out the hairs
of James' brows just to start.
- Okay so I am so excited that you guys were able to
join me here today, both from the Bay Area actually
so both of you traveled quite far and wide.
- Yeah the last time I was here I was at James' launch party
- Oh yeah for the palette!
- Yes it was honestly so much fun,
being a smaller artist it was really nice to meet
bigger influencers that were there
and be able to talk with them.
- Was that your first makeup event?
- Yes.
- Yeah me too.
- Wait was it really?
- Mhm
- Yeah
- Oh my god!
- For the first one, that's like crazy.
- A pretty good one
- Yeah - Yeah
- A pretty good first start, huh?
(laughs)
How did you both get started into makeup?
I want Riquelle to answer first cause I know Jake's answer.
- Yeah
- Okay well I liked art when I was little
- Same
- And so pretty much just like it came from that,
like I always drew starting when I was like four or five.
And I just got into makeup when I was in like middle school.
- I love that really early start, okay cool.
- I started my Instagram because people from school
and like different clients asked me
to like start posting makeup looks.
- Yeah, that's how I got started too.
- I started posting just clients
and then I started posting my makeup,
then I was like, oh, people like this better than clients.
(laughs)
Because nobody wants to see the same nude ass eyeshadow look
- Yeah.
So Jake,
- Yes.
- How did you get started?
- Well I think it's very clearly obvious.
- I think this is literally the cutest thing
in the entire world.
Can I just say it?
- Go for it.
(clapping)
- Okay so Jake, when I first started on Instagram,
Jake was actually my first ever fan page.
- Mhm.
- Literally, it was James Charles
with two z's after it right? - Yeah.
- And I always just thought he was so sweet,
he always left the sweetest comments
and then eventually he like posted a picture of himself
- Yeah
- Like wearing makeup and I was like oh my god
this kid is so cute and so talented
and then you eventually left the page
- Yeah
- Really rude, it's okay there's lots of other
sister fan pages now, but you started doing your own
stuff which I thought was so incredibly cool
because you literally are so incredibly talented.
- Thank you
- And I feel like we definitely look very similar
and have similar styles too so everyone started saying
like you're my son which I thought was so cute
- I remember seeing the Covergirl Ad,
and I remember just seeing James
and then I was like wow, this is such a beautiful boy
like I'd never seen that before.
- Yeah.
- And it just like opened something in my mind
that was like boys can wear makeup too.
- So Jake definitely does a lot of creative looks
kinda like how I first got my start on Instagram
and it's honestly funny too because you've done so
many looks that I had written down in my notebook
to work on but I'm always like filming all the time
and I'll open Instagram, and you'll post the most
beautiful look and I'll be like I was gonna do that one!
Like holy crap!
So I feel like you definitely have a very similar
style and mindset when it comes to makeup
of like just creating a really beautiful like art pieces,
and then Riquelle does literally some of the most
insanely blended, like colorful looks
I have ever seen in my entire life,
like I feel like your work is just so immaculate
and you both have such an attention to detail
it's really exciting - Thank you
watching both of you guys come into the industry.
When did you guys actually start posting on Instagram?
- So I think I started in like the summer of 2016,
that's just when I started like, I don't know
I guess getting like good at makeup.
- Mhm, okay and Jake what about you?
- I started posting like summer of 2017,
but at first the looks weren't even of mine,
my sister would do my makeup.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh my god!
- And then I just started playing with makeup,
watching tutorials, obviously James' tutorials
and then from there on I just started
being consistent, just started posting.
- So as like newcomers into the social media industry,
what do you guys feel about the industry space right now,
like what are your thoughts on the makeup community
and what do you feel about your experiences
and influencers so far?
- I think it's pretty difficult just because
a lot of the smaller artists are kind of in on eachother,
I personally feel like from personal experience
so I try to stay secluded from a lot of the smaller artists
so I like to keep to myself and I'm not like in it for
anything else I just am here for the makeup
and for the artistry that comes with it.
- Yeah, I really like that.
I definitely got involved with a lot of drama
when I first started in the beauty community.
And I've since like obviously learned my lesson
and there's literally no point and it's just such a headache
so I definitely keep my circle very very small
and I'm like very happy with the circle that I do have.
What'd you say that having a following
and being an influencer is what you expected it would be?
- Definitely not. - No.
- Okay, why?
- First of all it's not as easy as I thought it would be.
Like I thought people just like did their makeup,
took pictures and like
- Called it a day. - Got money, nope.
It's not that easy.
- It's not.
- It's so stressful, especially cause I'm still
in high school, and you too - Me too.
- Yeah it's a lot to handle - It's hard to balance
On top of like schoolwork and everything.
- Yeah cause they're two different worlds.
- It's still like a really cool experience,
to have the opportunity to do this.
- I'm guessing you barely even have time to film
a lot of videos.
- It's hard, I mean when I was in High School
I did make it work but it was literally like
I would wake up every single morning at six in the morning,
and then I would go to school until two,
and then I would literally set up my little table
in the basement with my two soft boxes
and film a video for like three hours
and I had to finish by like 5:50
because I would have to wipe my makeup off
and then drive to work at a frozen yogurt shop
which was five minutes from my house,
I had like 10 minutes to wipe it all off,
take everything down, get my makeup off and drive there
and clock in by six.
Then I'd work usually from like six til 10 every night,
and then I'd have to close, then I'd get home
and then I'd do my homework until like one or two.
And then I'd go to bed and repeat.
And that was for like, a good like half a year in school.
- Oh I don't think so.
- Yeah it was definitely like, it was a lot
and it was, I was getting very little sleep
and I got sick a lot, and it was not healthy.
- You're also super motivated though.
- Yeah, but it's cause like I was really passionate
about it and I knew that I wanted to do it
and I knew like I wanted to make it happen,
and I also knew that I wanted to graduate early
and that like I had to prove to my parents
that I wanted it and that I was taking it seriously
and that I wanted to have this be my full-time job as well.
And if it were not for those sleepless nights
I would not be here today, so.
- But that's like also what inspires like me
and a lot of people, like because you're so driven
and to like what you wanna do inspires like me
and other people to do the same.
- Aw, thank you.
- Yeah. - Mhm.
- That means a lot thank you guys for saying that.
Alright guys so we're gonna start off with an eyeshadow
and of course we're going to be using the
James Charles X Morphe Palette, mine is slightly busted
because I've been using this literally every single day
but, let's jump right in.
- Use code James for ten percent off.
- Yeah. - Yes, thank you.
- I can't believe you forgot.
- Sorry, well it's sister sold out everywhere, so.
Maybe it will be back by the time this video goes up.
- I'm gonna dip into pinkity drinkity
and just put this in the crease.
- I love that, little valentines look.
- Yes.
- Oh yeah, highlighting his brow bone first.
- Wait so are you guys on a lot of PR lists then?
- I mean, I'm starting to get on a lot,
but it's not like - It's like yeah but no.
- Yeah.
- Like I still wanna get onto ABH's.
- Me too.
- Neither of you are on ABH yet?
- No.
- Oh I'll be fixing that immediately.
- Stop!
- Gotchu girl, gotchu both.
- Oh my god.
You do not understand.
- What?
- How long I've been like, I was literally
there was a time where I would literally like
just go on their Instagram and scroll for hours
and just see what they reposted
and just do that.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I was trying so hard just to get them to like my stuff
like I would do neutral looks and stuff,
and I hated neutrals.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I was like I just wanna be on their PR list.
- ABH is on of the first PR lists I ever got on
and they, working with them has been so incredible.
So speaking of being on PR lists
and getting brand deals and stuff,
there's definitely been a major shift in the industry
this past year with like creators and coming and going
and growing and stuff like that,
how do you feel about the state that the industry is in
right now when it comes to growing as a small creator
and do you feel like it's easier or harder
to be recognized by these brands?
Like how do you feel?
- I would say it's definitely like easier than it was
maybe like two, three years ago cause just like
the amount of people doing Instagram and makeup
has definitely like gotten bigger.
- Yeah definitely.
- So do you think that makes it easier?
- Didn't think of it that way.
- I would say that it, yeah.
- It does make it harder in terms of like
getting yourself out there and
trying to separate yourself from everybody else.
- I agree in the sense that I do think it's getting
easier for smaller influencers
because of the fact that the community's growing so fast,
but at the same time that also makes it so much harder
because there's everybody there are to compete with
and you do really have to stand out.
- Mhm for sure. - Yeah.
And I think we're moving in the right direction
when it comes to like diversity and showing inclusivity
in the beauty community, but like there's definitely
a long way to go when it comes to like posting
people of color, - Absolutely
and people of like different economic backgrounds
and everything like that.
- Yeah.
- One other thing I've noticed is also that
brands don't necessarily just pay attention to
people that do neutral looks or warm smoky eyes
and all that, like I'm so happy that these brands
are finally noticing all these creative people,
people that do all of these out of the box things,
tutorial makeup, and not just like the same stuff
over and over again. - Yeah.
There was a time when I would just be like,
really mad over like not being reposted and stuff,
but like once I actually thought about it I'm like,
if I want this to happen I actually have to work for it
and not just like think that just because
I'm suddenly getting followers like
everything's gonna happen - And it's not an overnight
thing.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Right, I think that is a very good point.
I definitely used to be very bitter
when I first started as well,
and I think it's also important to know too
and you mentioned this earlier
before we were even filming you said that
when you first started you had an attitude with people
- Oh my god.
- Talk about that for a minute.
- Yeah I can touch on that, yeah.
So in general I have like an attitude
and I can be kind of like, what's the word?
- Blunt.
- Yeah, yeah, blunt and like very honest.
- Yeah.
- So, I kind of come across as like rude sometimes.
Really early on I had to like realize that everything
you say and do can be taken out of context,
people can misinterpret things all the time,
so you kinda have to really be aware
of the image you're presenting.
- I think too like I definitely do see a lot of
small artists that are really talented and
absolutely killing it but maybe don't have the best
attitudes online when it comes to interacting with others
or with brands, I know ABH just had a scandal
a few weeks ago where they posted on their Instagram
asking for people to tag different people in the comments
to be added - Oh I remember that
to their PR list and one girl asked her followers
to comment on ABH's thing, and when her name was being
spammed in the comments, sometimes Instagram will mark
that as spam, and then she literally started a whole rumor
that Anastasia hated Hispanic people.
Like of all brands, Anastasia, who has done so much
for the community.
I was like oh, absolutely not.
But I think it's that level of entitlement
that I think is the issue it's like aside from the whole
comment being deleted thing I think it's crazy
that instead of just thinking twice and being like
what could of actually happened here,
the rationale went right to oh this brand is racist,
they hate Hispanic people they're not reposting me.
It's crazy and I think that mentality's something that
a lot of artists have and it's selfish
and it's entitlement and I think like you said
- And if you wanna get somewhere
- And if you get somewhere, yeah everybody's watching.
Both fans are watching and of course drama is entertaining
every once in a while but for the most part,
nobody wants to watch somebody get in fights all day long
and start things and attack others,
and also the brands are watching.
And if you're sitting there fighting and leaving comments
on a brand's post and starting scandals like that,
nobody's gonna wanna work with you because you're
unreliable and who knows what you could say about
another brand later on.
You do definitely have to be careful
and I'm glad that you learned that lesson early on,
I think it's really dope that you were able to actually
self-reflect and like learn from that.
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna use this, okay what is this brush
because I've been looking for this.
- I don't know but I love it though.
- It's a Morphe M554.
And you've never done this.
- Wait so what are you doing?
- I like to put it in there to brighten.
- Canvas.
- Yes.
- From the palette?
- Yes, I do it all the time.
- Wait really?
- You don't do that?
- It's like peachy.
- No but the thing is, like it doesn't come off that peachy.
- Wait that doesn't look like.
(gasps)
- That looks so pretty.
- I'm sorry, what?
It looks like it would be so much more like,
- Orange.
- Pinkish.
- Well because when you swatch it and in the pan
it does look peachy,
- I was about to use my knuckle.
- But then it doesn't really.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- I've never done that before.
- I do it on everyone.
I like to brighten it under the eye,
especially if I do a lower lash line,
you want that to be bright.
- When I did my full face of makeup using only my palette,
I did no foundation at first because I didn't think
I was gonna have a shade,
but then at the end I started using canvas all over,
and it looks really good for foundation but I never
thought to use it - See how brightened it is?
- Yeah!
What has been your guys biggest accomplishments so far
in the beauty industry since you guys started?
- This.
- Really?
- This!
Duh!
- Are you serious?
- Yeah cause honestly - Yes!
- Oh my god what the heck!
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like for me it's like it went from like fan to
literally like being your friend.
- Yeah.
- Which is like so crazy, and like I never thought
I'd literally be here with you.
Like we never get to talk like actual friends and stuff.
- I know same, literally the exact same.
- Aw that's so cool.
- I never imagined any of this to happen.
- Like I went to watching beauty gurus,
and now we're like - Yeah
slowly but surely becoming one.
- Isn't it cool because that's kind of like how I was.
Not as much of a beauty guru, but like in the YouTube
community in general.
Like I was a fan of so many of the beauty gurus
but I also watched so many other youtubers
that it's been like so cool to meet in person now too.
- Oh yeah, so recently, not recently, no actually
it was like months ago, James invited me to be part
of his campaign for the Morphe palette collab.
- Oh yeah!
People don't even know about that!
- No yeah, so it was, you filmed it twice right?
- Yeah so the sisters know that I filmed the Morphe Campaign
actually twice I talked about that before
but I never really mentioned I don't think
what it was the first time.
- Yeah.
- And the photos are actually on the website
so a few people did
catch on - Okay, yeah.
The first time we actually filmed it,
I was only in the last shot, which was like the picture
that made it to the palette but every other color
of the palette was assigned to a different friend or artist
that I have looked up to for a long time,
so my mom was in it, Ethan and Grayson were in it,
Jake was in it, a few different artists from Twitter
and Instagram that I've been following forever
were in it as well,
Briquelle, literally flew all the way from Australia
to be in it, my literal favorite artist of all time.
- Same.
- Unfortunately the footage wasn't high resolution enough
to be used in commercial format,
so we literally had to redo the entire thing
which sucked, but regardless we still got amazing photos
of it, it was an amazing day.
- Yes, it was just so fun to have like so many artists
in a room and just like such positive energy.
- Yeah.
- It was my first time ever doing any photo shoot
and it was for a big brand too.
- Yeah.
- So being there really meant a lot to me.
- Aw!
- Thank you so much.
- Of course sister!
Okay what are you using?
- I'm using face,
- Same. As a highlighter.
- Love that.
Oh yeah.
I feel like I've asked you guys quite a few questions
now about like your experience in the beauty industry but,
do you guys have any questions that I could answer for you
about being an influencer and what it's like
and like how the behind the scenes work
or how like literally anything?
- Yeah,
- Cause I'm here, always.
As a resource, and a friend, and somebody to be there,
and somebody whose experienced it all,
and whose learned the hard way.
- Yeah.
- And I feel like I'm always down to like help everybody out
I feel like when I first came in,
there weren't many people that were willing to give me
honest answers and help me out but like
I wanna be that person for everybody else
who I really believe in,
so if you guys have any questions for me,
I'd love to answer and I'm sure for anybody at home
that's aspiring as well would love to know, so.
- Well I have struggled with responding to emails
when I get asked about ratings.
- Oh like rates, money.
- So I think that would be cool to know, and
- Like how to charge.
- Yeah.
- Touchy subject, but definitely down to talk about it.
I feel like rates are very very controversial
in the sense that, we had the whole situation last year
with Marlena talking about influencer rates
and when 60,000 dollars was dropped and everybody like
went crazy but in reality,
60,000 isn't like a lot of money for the influencer space.
It really did turn into a witch hunt against influencers
and I definitely did react very harshly first
but Marlena and I did talk behind the scenes
but regardless, I think it one turned into a witch hunt
because people heard that and they assumed that
everybody was charging 60,000 dollars
which is definitely not the case.
And I think it's important to know that everybody's rates
are different depending on what they offer.
- Literally everybody, yeah.
- Because not only are the paying for of course like
the followers number is there but at the end of the day,
what you should be charging for, and what brands should be
paying for is the engagement.
Because you can have five million followers
and be getting 30,000 likes.
That person should be charging a fraction of what
somebody with 5 million followers that's getting
a million likes should be.
Because those people do exist.
I feel like demographic is also a super important thing
as well because like you can be like a 15 year old boy
in makeup, but like if a sports brand reaches out,
the chances are it's not really gonna be a good fit
for you because the chances are our followers are mostly
young girls that might not be interested in
- Sports - that type of stuff.
I feel like the best way to go about it is
talk to other people in the community for sure,
like I said it is a community
and it's important to treat it that way
and to communicate with your fellow artists
and see what else is going on,
and also two, like it's important because
unfortunately a lot of brands do try to take advantage,
especially of smaller artists who are kind of like new
to the game and don't really have others to talk to,
and they'll try to underpay and the unfortunate reality
is a lot of these brands don't wanna pay, even period,
which is horrible because no matter what it is
you should always be paid for doing work,
so it's just a very tricky subject
but it's also up to the influencer too
to know your worth and not be afraid to negotiate,
but also understand what the offer is too
because sometimes a major brand can be reaching out
and I'll see influencers negotiate for thousands and
thousands and thousands of dollars, when I'm like
your engagement isn't even that good one, and two
this is a really great opportunity.
Some things are just good learning experiences too so,
it's really important to just like kinda talk to others
and talk to role models around you and talk to your parents
and people who know and have a had a little bit more
experience and get that type of help
because I'd so much rather have people be
safe than sorry and know what's going on
rather than potentially sign a contract
and get way screwed over later on.
- Yeah so I'm gonna be doing like some little
heart freckles, like inverted ones,
so they're like blended out.
- Love that.
- Yeah.
- Okay, great.
For a little Valentine's Day Moment.
Okay.
- So, I'm gonna be stacking two pairs of lashes together
so I don't know they can look more dramatic.
- Okay, I'm so down. - Like Mine.
So the lashes I'm stacking are
- Lilly, so extra Miami's.
Use code James for 15% off.
- And then I'm also using that bitch by Crvstal Lashes.
- Oh and what I like about this is it totally looks like
our looks like on him.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like, holy shit.
- Does this look like something I would do?
- Yes!
- It looks like you would post like a sunset picture
like just the eye.
- With a good, approximately
- Yeah, right there.
- Just crop right there.
Lip time.
- Lip time.
- What liner are you using?
- I'm using Curvii by iluvsarahii x ColourPop
- Literally my favorite one.
- Me too, you got me on this one.
- Love that.
- I feel like it can be used on any skin tone.
- Yes.
- Which I like about this, it's very versatile.
- Wait was that the right word? Versatile?
- Yeah.
- Okay I'm using some big words today.
(laughs)
I'm two years old.
- What are we doing for lips?
- I'm gonna do
- Wait so should we do different on each side or the same?
- Up to you.
Do you wanna do a matching nude?
That could kinda be cute guys like the color would
look good with both looks.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
- Wait do you both mutually agree
on this selection of this fun gloss?
- Oh let me see, yeah.
- Fun gloss. - Wait okay I picked out,
- Riquelle picked out four options for everybody.
- So we have wait should we go through all of them
or is that doing too much?
- What gloss is this?
- That's a Katy Dose of Colors.
- Yeah! - I love that.
- You have Dose of Colors, also in the most,
we have Anastasia in pearl, and then Kylie in
- Always shining.
- Love that.
- Shinin, shinin
- Shinin, I was gonna do that too!
Shinin, shinin, shinin, shinin, yeah
- So you can sing and I can't?
- Well that's not, singing so.
- I can sing.
- You can?
- Mhm, but I have stage fright so no more singing.
- Oh, how rude.
- I'll sing once you stop filming.
- Okay, okay which one?
- Okay I'm stuck between that one and I like the
pearlescent one
- Wait what?
- That one, yeah.
- This one?
I think this would look really stunning.
- Yeah just because I feel like that's too like,
- Cause this would go with my side
but I don't know if it would go with yours
- Yeah.
- Cause yours is more pinky.
- So wait, you said this one?
- Yeah, just a dollop of daisy.
- There we go, so we're done with the lips,
and there.
(laughs)
(light music)
- Ready?
- Okay.
- Spray me good.
Lock it in place.
- Okay.
- Ooh that was professional!
(dramatic music)
- Alright sister then I think that is this beauty battle
between sister Jake and Riquelle all complete!
Oh my god thank you guys so much
for coming on the channel today, both of these looks
are fantastic. - Amazing.
Yeah they look so, so, so good and fresh
oh my god you guys do you like how they turned out?
- I love it, both, amazing.
- Yeah this was so fun.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Mhm!
- This was both of your guys first YouTube video.
- Oh yeah.
- Mhm!
- That's so cool thank you guys so much
for coming on the channel
- Thank you for bringing us - It really means so much
to me like you guys have been such a major
source of inspiration to me and I know so many other
small artists out there as well
who are just trying really hard to get
into the community, you guys are absolutely killing it
and thank you for sharing your art with me
and also all the sisters and the entire world as well.
You sisters at home, I really hope you guys enjoy this video
and please do me a favor and go check out Jake and Riquelle,
they are so incredibly talented and truly I think
are the future of the beauty industry,
if you guys like this battle please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below and also leave us a comment
and let us know who you think won, literally I have no idea
I think both sides are so beautiful in their very own way
but of course we really wanna hear
what you guys have to say.
If you have not already, don't forget
to click that big red subscribe button down below
and come join this sisterhood we are over 14 million
sisters strong - Damn!
and would love to have you guys join the family,
and also don't forget to click that bell icon
so you can get a notification everytime I upload
a brand new video.
If you like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram or Twitter
they are both just jamescharles my snapchats more
behind the scenes, it's James Charles with an extra S
after Charles.
Where can they find you guys?
- You can find me at snatchedbyjake.
- And makeupbyriquelle.
- Yes go follow them sister support and say hello.
This video's sister shoutout goes to sister Jeffery,
thank you so much love for always following and supporting
you know I love you literally so so so much
and if you at home would like to be the next video's
sister shoutout don't forget to always retweet videos
when they go live on Twitter
and also turn on my YouTube post notifications.
Alright guys thank you so much for watching
this episode of beauty battles I had so much fun
with two of my favorite artists in the entire world
thank you guys for coming,
we really hope you guys enjoy this video as well,
I love ya and I'll see you in the next one.
Bye!
(dramatic music)