- [All] Hi Sisters!
- James Charles here,
and welcome back to my YouTube channel.
You guys, for today's video I am so beyond excited,
because this is a collab that I've wanted to do
for a very very long time.
Today we are joined
with Mr. Kate! - Oh my God!
We're having Sister Kate and Daddy Joey over here, and
you guys-- - (gasps) Daddy Joey!
- Yes, definitely Daddy Joey. - Oh my God!
- I'll take it. - Okay, good.
We are together today,
because we are doing a collab
that is not makeup related for once,
it is house related. - (laughs) Yes.
- Because all you sisters know,
I recently bought a house
a few months prior, - Mm-hmm.
and I moved in.
I've been here for quite a while now,
and by the time this video's going up,
it is, I believe January. - Yes.
- Maybe. - Yes.
- That means I've been in the house
for about four months, now. - Mm-hmm.
- And that means that you guys still
have not gotten a house tour.
(laughs)
- He's been busy, okay! - I've been a little bit busy.
- Palette, merch, traveling the world (laughs).
- A little bit, yes.
As soon as I bought this house,
Kate was like we need to do something
and I was like oh, absolutely
because I've been subscribed to Kate and Joey
for literally years now. - So sweet.
- For the longest time ever.
I stan you guys, I think you guys have one
of seriously (laughs)
the coolest channels on YouTube.
I've been there since like before even, like 300,000.
Like, the longest time. - Wow, oh my God.
- Swear to God, the longest time.
Like I said, as soon as we moved in,
Kate hit me up and was like we wanna do a makeover,
and I was like please,
I need help. - (laughs) Yeah.
- But, I wanted to do something for my channel, too,
because like I said,
this collab I've wanted to do
for a very very long time now. - I know!
And he's so passionate about interior design,
which is so cool.
- Yes. (laughing)
So, for today's video we are doing something
that Kate and Joey have
never done before, actually. - Never.
- And I am so beyond excited, because
we are obviously going to do the
full-room transformation over on Kate's channel.
We'll talk about that in a little bit while
we're going through the house, - Yep.
- And you guys can see that
video over there. - Yep, yep.
- Go subscribe, please.
But over here, because of the fact
that so many of the rooms are
in the process, not done but also not the worst,
we figured it'd be--
- Started! - Yes.
Sister started.
- Sister--
(laughing)
We figured obviously we want to let Kate shine
and do her makeover,
but for my channel we want to do a more
collaborative type thing. - Mm-hmm.
- And work together to finish
a lot of the rooms that I've started
and kinda show you guys what the process looks like
of actually taking a room
and doing it from start to finish.
So, this might be a little bit of a longer video,
but I'm so excited to just take you guys through it.
There's gonna be a full production, HGTV is shaking.
Mr. Kate and James Charles are coming for you guys.
So without further ado,
let's walk through the house,
show you guys what we have going on,
show you what we wanna do,
and let's decorate together.
(Katie shrieks)
(calm music)
Alright sisters!
So we're here at the front door
and we thought we'd do a little bit
of a walk-through through the house
to show you guys what is done,
what isn't done and what we really need to work on
for this little house makeover.
I'm gonna be really honest with you guys,
we already filmed this entire thing a month ago
and the footage is nowhere to be found
but would it be a James Charles video
without a technical difficulty?
No, so we're going to redo it today.
- Redo it, we've already rehearsed.
It's going to be way faster.
- [Joey] Kate's a month more pregnant.
- I'm a yup, bigger belly.
Thank you, disclosure.
- I know we've had over a month to think about space
and order some stuff as well. - Yeah.
- We though we'd walk you through it, again,
but this time kind of talk about our thought process
as to why we chose each thing
and what the room is going to be--
- The plan. - as apposed
to our initial first reactions.
- Yeah. - So this is like a review
instead of our first impression.
- It'll be better.
- So without further ado,
let's walk through the house.
- Let's do it. - Again.
- Again (laughing).
- So room number one is my PR package room.
(laughing)
- This is like the big,
like it's really your entrance room in a way.
- It is, and this is the most office we've ever had.
We did the list already, spoiler alert.
We've already ordered
a majority of things for this house makeover.
- And they've arrived. - And they've arrived.
- [Both] Clearly!
- So actually, we'll be able to execute this.
- Yeah, but for right now,
we're keeping all the boxes in this room
because this particular entrance foyer,
living room space. - Formal living room
- Is not going to be in my video
because-- (Kate gasps)
- We're going to be doing it
for an OMG We're Coming Over episode
on our channel. (James shrieks)
- All of the boxes are being stored in here
for every the other makeover
so let's move on the the next room.
The dining room
is probably most unused room in the entire house.
- Really?
- Well yeah, I don't really eat--
- Yeah you don't eat-- - Here.
- Oh right, you don't eat or ever dine
but people sit here sometimes. - No, but does anybody--
- And work sometimes. - True.
Does anyone really eat in their dining room though?
- Depends.
If you have another eating room,
which you do, - Which I do in the kitchen.
- Yeah, we're gonna style them
so that this doesn't become an area
where crap gets collected.
Like it is right now.
- Drag me. - Oh my God (laughing).
- I want this to feel like a fall family room.
So let's talk about what we need in this room.
First of all-- - Lighting.
- This light is literally the ugliest thing I've ever seen
in the entire world.
I want it gone immediately.
- Yeah, it's like very spider, spideress.
- It's gross. - Yeah.
- And I feel like they use like sconces
also really tacky. - Sconces
Right, which you specifically didn't like
that kind of plasticy look to the shade.
- And it looks like the cups
if you got to your grandma's house when you we're younger
and she would serve drinks and those,
you know what I'm talking about?
- Like the weird, like right, yes.
They're like the hard plastic cups.
- Yes! - Yes!
- Those exact cups. - Yes I know.
A fancier one. - Yes.
Those just aren't it.
- We talked about anchoring this table with a rug
because-- - Yes.
- You have the dining table
as very much kind of feels connected to that other room
- Yes.
- So in order to make sure
this really feels like its own space
- Yes. - An area rug is key for that.
- I feel that way too,
and as well the table is wood
and the hardwood floor is also wood,
which for me, I don't like. - Right.
So we're gonna separate it. - Then it'll separate it
which is really really nice.
- And you already have some awesome plants
you can work with.
- Yeah. - We can order
some more planters and stuff.
But really this room is pretty straightforward.
Great, so let's just start simple moving on.
- Yes.
- Sisters scoot.
- To the next room! - Yeah!
- So the next room in the house is our Sister Office
which needs a little bit of work.
I will say we do work kind of all around the house
but I definitely want a good anchor point
in the home for everybody to just come,
just get everything done
and to just really focus it.
- We talked about you wanted to do the neon sign.
Right? - Yes.
- Just the Sisters on the outside here.
- So I really want to get a Sisters on the outside
and this was Kate's idea
but I though it would be so,
just so cute and fun and chic
just to light up everything in the mood.
We're doing white of course, duh.
- Yeah, that's already ordered
- Yes.
We've already got a lot. - On its way.
- We have some art we want to hang--
- We talked about doing floating shelves here
just to have additional area
for storage but also for some display stuff.
- Then we also ordered three stools
which was your idea - Yeah.
- And I love it so if you want
to talk about a little bit.
- Sure, well I was just seeing you have
the two chairs in here
but because you want to maybe have some meetings
or you also we're talking about how you want
to put your calendar on this TV.
- Yeah, so there was a TV in the triple
when we first moved in
and I live my life by my calendar--
- Yeah.
- So I really want to have it displayed
on the TV at all times so I can come in here
check everything and we can have team meetings
and schedule videos and basically everything.
I definitely think some subtle changes
in this room will really take it
above and beyond-- - Yeah.
- And it's for the perfect sisters workspace.
- Great, love it.
Yeah, organization, functionality, no rug,
it's less about design,
it's more about just pulling it together.
- Yes. - So it is petite but--
- Yes. - A lot has happened in here.
- Yes. - Okay, done.
(claps) Yes!
- Alright, so coming out of the office we have one
of the main foyers.
Coming into the kitchen and living room,
these are more of the spaces I'm excited about
because this is where I spend 80% of my time.
- As do most people. - Right?
- Right, living room and kitchen
is where everyone gathers.
- Yes, I will say,
out of all the spaces that I've done,
this one is obviously not even
close to being decorated but--
- But you did them both in here.
- [James] Yes, but I do like how it looks.
- [Kate] I mean you picked the most amazing,
comfortable couch,
- It's a comfortable couch. - It's gigantic.
Like you're just drawn to it over here.
The hard part is when you have such a big sectional,
you want the rug to
match the scale of it.
- [James] Yeah, and this rug is not the right size.
- [Kate] We got a way bigger, like jute,
but white jute rug-- - Yes.
- Which will be so nice and homey.
It's right off of your backyard,
so it has that almost beachy feel to it.
- Right, which I love. - It's cool out there.
And then we talked about getting more accessories
for these built in shelves
because-- - Yes.
So basically-- - They're amazing!
- They are!
And what happened was
I literally propped up all my decor pieces
from my old apartment
and whenever we moved in the first day,
I just unpacked them
and put them all on the shelves randomly
to move around later and never moved them around.
And then people come and go
"Oh my god your shelves are so cute."
I'm like, what?
So this definitely needs to be filled way up
and what's cool too,
is we have a lot of shelf space to work with
so definitely allows us
to get a lot of really amazing decor pieces.
- Yes.
- Kate and I are about to go shopping in a little bit
actually to get some fine pieces
so you guys will see that in a few minutes.
So that's pretty much the entire shelf region.
- Yeah.
- So what I'm really excited about
that you actually suggested that I was a little bit--
when you said it, you were like
oh I feel like you need a different coffee table
and I was like-- - Excuse me,
I love this coffee table.
- I love this coffee table
but your thought process behind it
I actually really liked.
So why don't you talk a little bit about that.
- Sure, so I was just seeing
that you have this large scale sofa
that creates almost a square here.
So seeing a square coffee table seems
to be the more organic choice. - Yeah.
- And it'll be just that more accessible
for people sitting on this arm--
- Because if you're here--
- Right, you can't...
- Not going to. - And he has long arms.
- I'd say.
I really like this table too and what's cool for
if we're actually not getting rid of it,
- No. - We're using it upstairs.
Which we'll get to in a second.
- And then you have that amazing picture that you took.
- Yeah so-- - Right over there.
- So Joey if you want to rotate yourself around there.
We have this huge wall which is blank
and needs to filled pretty badly.
We took a few different pictures
that I've took on my travels
and we blew them up in black and white.
We're getting them framed,
so I think they'll be so chic on the walls
just to kind of separate everything.
- So we're just decorating this room, literally.
Bringing in the coffee table, the rug,
shelf accessories, art work on the wall,
just pull it all together.
Just jump off from what you've already started.
Alright, the Sisters.
What do we call it? - Outside.
- Sister Outside (laughing).
- This needs a lot of work.
- Working on that. - Let's be honest.
- [Kate] Yeah.
- [James] I feel like once again,
one of those places that with a few minor changes
will really make a big impact.
- [Kate] Yeah.
- We do already have a TV and a cute fireplace out here,
so I feel like just a little seating moment, maybe?
- And then - Yeah.
- Maybe some shady lounge like lawn chair vibe
like right over there. - Yes.
- Like either in the grass
with a side table in between.
Really just something for you
to come out here and actually sit down.
- And relax, yeah.
So that's pretty much the outside.
- Yeah. - All done.
Next place, breakfast stuff. - Yeah.
- [James] Kind of tiny
but I feel like it's important considering
it's literally what you see when you walk in the front door.
- Totally, right.
You see right down into it - Right smack dab.
- And into the backyard.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
So you eat here, and there.
- Yes.
- So you actually use this table a lot.
- We do actually.
I just think this space can be a lot more welcoming.
This light is literally, it's 10 best.
(Katie Laughing)
It looks like it was a three dollar lamp from Walmart.
We have another chair somewhere in the house, I think.
That will be brought back down.
- Okay. (laughing)
- To make the set.
And then I think the same thing here,
just a centerpiece on the table.
- Right. - So they go together.
- We also talked about doing another piece
of artwork there. - Yes.
- To just mirror image.
and then curtains here too,
just to bring in a textiles. - Yes.
- So the majority of the windows you have shades
and you also have a lot going on
that curtains don't make sense,
but here they make sense.
You can see how they frame nicely.
- I think they're going to,
yes that's what I was going to say.
They'll make it feel like a lot more comfy-cozy,
- Yeah. - which will be good
because this space definitely needs it.
Great.
So that what makes breakfast so easy.
Kitchen, next.
I don't think there's a lot
to be done in here which is great
because I feel a kitchen is a place
where you don't really decorate that much.
- Well I mean, you have beautiful kitchen,
with the finishes and everything,
so you don't have to distract.
But yeah, I think a centerpiece there.
- Yes. - Something
which maybe we can pick out of the collection
of the beautiful, tall, lengthy,
so even if it's just white ceramic
or something, so pretty. - Yeah.
So that's pretty much the kitchen as well,
- Yeah. - so it's simple.
- Now we just have upstairs, right?
- Should we head up?
- Yes. - Let's go.
- More for our glutes.
Up the stairs, we're doing butts.
- [James] Ready?
(laughing)
- Oh God, I've got to hold my boobs.
This is my first time doing cardio.
- (laughing) It's great.
- Oh great, this is a paramount.
- Okay, welcome to the upstairs.
I'm very very excited about this
because the to of my favorite rooms
in the entire house are up here;
my master and the Sister Studio.
So-- - Oh my God.
- You good? - Sister winded please,
I'm what can we do about it?
Yeah, so this landing is great
because it's wide, it's epic,
you got your bedroom here,
you got your beauty room over there.
- This all is going to my least favorite wall
in the entire house.
I think these built ins are so ugly
and I just don't, like why?
- Well we just talked about doing pillows here
- Yes. - on the benches.
- And once again somewhat similar to downstairs,
there's just lots of shelf space
that we should fill up with some cool pieces.
Just so we can be a little bit more put together.
We can't get rid of this
so we may as well make it look great
while it's here.
- Yeah.
- So this wall is completely blank right now
and that's because what was here
is currently being customized.
So you guys know as YouTubers,
when we hit certain milestones,
we always get our little plaque
which is always super super exciting-
- Really exciting.
- And an amazing this to work towards.
So I have my one million plaque standing right here
but I just got my 10 million plaque
which is so crazy. - Oh my God such a milestone!
- That's crazy! - That's so awesome.
- Oh it's been so exciting-- - It's so cool.
- And obviously that took a lot of time
and a lot of hard work
and I want to display it in a really cool way--
- But, it was a really cool idea that you had
because the plaque comes as,
it's just more as a trophy. - Right.
- Kind of thing, right?
It's like that big play button.
- Yeah.
- It's not framed like the one million plaque--
- Right, so--
- But this designer right here was like,
"let's frame it!" - Let's frame it!
So I really like how the one million plaque
was displayed like the gold play button
inside the big shadowbox.
So I took both the one million and 10 million
to a custom framer here in California
and we are getting them both reframed
because I even though I like the one million one,
I didn't really like the grey background.
Kind of ugly.
- I love how you're customizing your own plaques.
- We're going to cut it open-- - Sorry YouTube!
Let's redesign everything- - It's hilarious.
Cutting it open, taking the one million out
and were also getting the 10 million
huge diamond play button costumed framed
so they'll be in matching frames
and there will be the one million
and the 10 million,
right here, exactly matching.
Looking beautiful and fun and fashion chic.
I think it will be a really amazing way
just to look back at all my achievements right
before you come into the Sister Studio.
Which brings us to the next room in the house.
The Sister Studio. - Sister Studio!
Oh my gosh, this room is so important.
- So-- - It's crazy.
- The Sister Studio is probably,
honestly my favorite room of the entire house.
I love equipment and videography and lighting
and just trying to see how I can really elevate myself
and make my content that much better.
So for me, this studio has like
a dream project of mine forever
just to really have the best production space
humanly possible to make my content the best
for all of my sisters watching.
- Totally.
- As you can see, there's a full on metal cage
that we built in this room-- - Which is rad, yeah.
- [James] Which is so cool.
And basically that's where basically all the equipment
hangs from which is amazing because it takes everything
off of the floor,
which makes the decorating way better.
It makes it feel a lot bigger
because this room was very very crammed at first.
- Yeah, I mean you host people like Kim Kardashian
in this room-- - Yeah.
- So you want to have it be
a little bit more like a studio feel.
- Right.
- So like this table and the table below--
- Has to go.
- [Kate] We talked a lot about this table.
- This table has been at the source
of so much stress about this--
- [Kate] Our most emails back and forth have been
about this table. - Literally, let me finish.
So for me, this table is literally from Ikea.
I got this when I first moved here
and It was great at first-- - Yeah
- But my videos are just getting bigger
and bigger production wise
and if had any other videos,
this entire table would be like,
if I pick anything up everything else would fall off.
- Absolutely. - Like it's bad.
- Yeah.
- So a bigger table to work on
and to not feel so cluttered.
- Is going to be great for your brain.
- Biggest thing. - Yeah.
So we found that table with--
- We found the table, God bless.
Thank God. - Yes.
- We really wanted a seating area on this end
because like I said, we do film a lot of bigger collabs
and if I'm bringing a celebrity client,
sometimes they bring their team or their manager over
or even if its like bigger collabs,
and only one person on the screen,
friends will be chilling here.
- Right.
- And all time time I'm filming alone
and my manager and my assistant and my writer
will all be here watching.
I just want a comfortable space
for everybody to just once again
have it feel like an actual studio.
- Okay so we were going to do a little couch,
like a little, almost like a bench
with a back on it. - Yeah, for the sitting area.
- And then, you texted me around Christmastime.
- Yes.
- We met over Christmas
and you were like this is the plan.
And you were like,
"Okay Ethan got me a custom bench."
- [James] Which is literally so cool.
- So cool. - And so sweet.
If you guys saw my collab with The Dolan Twins and Emma,
this is just fun for our Christmas video.
Ethan got me a customed Sisters bench
which I think is so incredibly cute
and he literally got it for me
because of the fact that we've filmed
so many collabs together
where our butts are literally broken by then end of it
and we cannot feel it either. - And you all have
very small butts.
I mean, well I mean thick,
thick, thick butts, but not.
Well anyways.
You all have lovely thick butts
and we need a think bench for support.
- Yeah to sit on
so we don't literally break our backs
by the time we're done filming.
But since we thought
since it's usually just me filming,
we could really easily use Ethan's Sisters bench
and put it against this wall
and decorate it with pillows
so that everyone is really comfortable
and then that way too,
we can also see the custom Sisters
on the front-- - Exactly, beautiful, lit up.
Because it actually lit up, right?
- Yeah it's actually full LED. - Yeah you can plug it in.
- It's so cool. - Yeah.
- And of course if we have a bigger collab,
then we can move the bench quickly
over to there-- - Swap them out.
- So we can sit more comfortably.
- Yep I love that.
So this is the wall when you walk in the door
to the Sisters studio, you see this wall.
- This is what they see.
Kate had this really cool idea.
- Well we were just talking about doing a custom sign.
You wanted to use Sister Studio.
So you did kind of like a splatter paint thing.
- Yes - With Sisters Studios
and then we're having it custom made
on acrylic with then a stand-off
of the Sisters Studio
so it's going to be black and white
of course-- - Of course, duh.
- Keeping with the aesthetic,
but then you'll walk in
and see this big, giant Sister Studio.
- Should we got to-- - The Master's?
- The last and final where all the magic happens?
Hmmm not a lot magic happends there let's be real.
- We're working on that. - We're working on that.
- Once we figure out that room there's going
to be lots of magic.
The Master.
(laughing) Yes!
- The master bedroom.
- Oh my God, I've never seen someone
back that ass up into the bedroom first.
- So the last bedroom I'm very very excited for
because this is the space I'm in.
- This is your Sisters Suite
- Yes.
So luckily this is really just an amazing suite
for me to kind of unwind at the end of the day.
So we already have a few major pieces
and here is what we got started.
Spoiler alert, if you'll notice I have no bed right now.
- Yes because Joey took it.
- Yes Joey stole my bed.
So as soon as we walked in here, Joey noticed.
- So your bed was a little bit small, right.
Just four-post bed.
Four-poster?
Four-post?
- [James and Kate] Four-poster.
- Four-poster bed
and because your ceiling goes at an incline,
it just-- - It does.
- [Joey] It looked a little short.
So we're going to keep it platform
but I'm basically just going to rebuild all the posts
and make it that much taller
so it looks that much more grand.
- But keep it in the platform style
which is the style that you like.
- [James] Right, for sure.
- Kind of like that lower, more minimal vibe.
Okay so what we talked about in here obviously
just really completing the space.
- Yeah.
- Because you have your bed
that's being augmented,
but this side of the room is pretty much good.
- Yes.
- But this side of the room is totally empty
It's like the ottoman
- Right. - needs has space here.
This wants to be a living room.
Like in order to make it a suite,
you have a living space attached
to your sleeping space. - Right.
- It's going to be so elegant. - Right.
- And cozy.
- So Kate had the really really good idea
of putting a full-on, third living room
in the house with a sofa and two chairs.
Which I think is going to be so cute.
- So cute.
- We picked out literally the best stuff ever
and CVQ is literally right downstairs
right now delivering everything.
#nosponsored but please.
- But it should be! - It should be.
I think that will have the master bedroom feel a lot more,
like you said, like actual suite,
for I can like relax and chill in.
In summary, we're building you a bigger bed,
we are having this be a modular piece
either here or there,
we're creating a living space anchored with the rug,
we're bringing the coffee table from downstairs up here,
and we're style the shelves
and just making it a Sister Suite.
- Is all the from the shelf store?
- I think so.
Are we done?
- Are we done?
- [Joey] It's time to shop.
- James!
(upbeat music) (laughing)
- Alright you guys.
So we just arrived at HomeGoods
and we're going to be basically do decor shopping.
All day today. - All the accessories.
Thankfully we ordered all the large items online
which is great because we don't have
to cram them in your Tesla.
- Right.
- They're being delivered.
- They're being delivered, thank God.
- So we are here for all those accessories,
the shelf items, the table top items,
trays, centerpieces, faux plants galore.
Like, we're just going to fill it up
because you can always return
so I always say,
buy more than you need. - More is better.
- Yeah, see what we can get here
and if we need to, go to another store.
But like-- - We have lots of options.
We have all day. - Yeah.
- [Joey] Perfect, totally your aesthetic.
(laughing) - Joey you're fired.
- This one for your master.
Because you have the smaller ones right?
- True, yeah.
I feel like this actually is not bad.
- Cute, I love it.
Like a little topiary.
- Just super simple and minimal.
- I mean, I love crystals.
What is that smear?
(laughing)
- Okay, so we were talking about doing
like a gathering of taller vases,
like maybe on your kitchen island--
- Yeah, or somewhere.
- You have centerpiece situation potential
for the dining table.
- Do you like this?
- I love that.
I love like also mixing it with,
there's this other textured one up there.
- Ew, it looks like octopus tentacles.
- Got it.
No octopus, okay.
What about this one?
- Oh I like that. - Right?
- Pretty, that will be pretty.
It has a little bit more of the natural tone
coming through, look.
Sisters not twins. - That'll look good together.
Right, I love that.
- Too thick?
- I do love a thick sister.
- We do like thick sisters.
- That'll be good actually. - Here, okay.
- Oh I was saying this is like your aesthetic
on the globe.
- Yeah. - Right?
- Do you like the smaller one better?
Because I love the accent of the gold.
- Okay well actually the smaller one is probably good
because-- - It'll fit on the shelf.
- Oh, love that.
Perfect, geometric-- - And oh--
- I think that's their display.
(Joey and Kate Laughing)
- We can take it, what are they going to do about it?
- Yeah, let's be like, put a price on it.
We'll take it.
An hourglass?
- Ew, that sand is disgusting.
- Okay, rude.
What about this?
This is a chic.
Is it too gold?
- A what?
- It's too gold for you?
- Oh, I thought you said a pa-too-gold.
(laughing)
- I could just make up words.
This is a pa-too-gold.
- Yeah, I actually don't mind it.
- Right?
I don't mind it either.
I just love, love, love the shape of it.
Very much-- - What would you put in there?
- It could be anywhere,
depends on where you put it;
entryway, keys, whatever, on the coffee table, remotes.
- Let's do it. - Let's do it.
- I'll trust you on the gold.
- Great.
Oh my God, is this a freakin' silver slinky?
- That's what I had in my hand.
- And do you really like it?
- It's kind of cool.
- I love it.
- Kind of fun right?
- It's a silver slinky, yes.
Wait, this was before your time though.
You were born after this was popular.
- I know what a slinky is!
You watch your attitude.
(laughing)
I'm not that young.
- Do you like crystals because you know I love crystals?
Do you like them white? - I do.
- I think they're pretty. - I love a white crystal.
- Yes.
Did you grab one of theses?
- Ew. - Too hammered?
- Hammered, I love that.
- Oh wait, there's a sleeker one underneath it.
- Do you like that?
- For like down like the dining room table potentially
or even under the vases
on your long weird shelves
under your TV in the family room.
Not weird, glorious.
- They are a little strange.
- Right? - That could be good.
- You know, 'cause then,
'cause even just having something reflective
under something else, is nice.
It just kind of amplifies. - Okay.
- [Joey] And to finish it all off.
- [Kate] Oh, burlap elephant!
- [Joey] Totally your aesthetic.
(Joey laughing)
- What is this?
- I picked that up.
I don't think it will really fit anywhere
but it is kind of chic.
- I like it.
- It could be on the coffee table by itself.
- Or on, do you have a mantle in your bedroom?
Or no?
You don't have an actual mantle.
- No.
- But you do have a counter ledge.
- Oh on the side!
Yes we do.
- Yeah - Yeah. Okay.
We can do this.
- [James] Look at this?
- Oh, I love that.
Yeah, a nice, like aged patina to go with that.
'Cause that is-- - (laughing) Patina.
- But, what? Patina?
- I'll put too gold.
- No but I-- - Patina's a real word.
- Patina's a real word.
- I'll put too gold and patina.
I like that a lot.
- You like that, okay.
- Let's grab that. - Okay.
- Ew. - Yeah, that's a little gross.
- This is kind of chic though. - Yeah, love that.
That's very, at the farm house vibe in your house.
- I really like this a lot.
- Yeah, I love that.
- We can put a beefy candle in here.
(upbeat music)
- [Joey] I found the perfect one.
- Oh no, Joey. - Joey why?
- Oh my God. - So-
- [Joey] T, T? (laughing)
- I'm so scared for these little kids.
- What about a simple frame with a matte?
Because this on its side I think would fit
within one of the shelves.
- [Joey] Wait, where's our other cart?
- Oh, right.
James!
- Oh it's right here, I got it.
This says create, its kind of cute.
- That is cute.
I love how simple that is.
- Look at this. - Create.
- This is such a chic little pencil holder.
It's at an angle. - Yes!
That's so your vibe. - Let's grab this too.
- Look at these together.
Oh my gosh. - So good.
- Coming together.
Oh my gosh, I love this.
This is so fun.
- Just left the doctor,
let me know what you think.
- Like what about up on the desk?
- I don't know if it would fit anywhere.
- Let's get it.
(laughing) - Great.
- [Kate] Alright, here's what we got so far.
You can see Jame's aesthetic
is apparent
in the shopping cart.
Face tuning in the aisle.
- I just posted on Instagram, Kate.
- [Kate] Well I know, we're in a long line.
Do it.
Alright, the load in.
Let's see how much this Tesla can handle.
- Probably a lot.
- [Kate] Probably a lot.
It's an SUV.
- How many pieces did we end up picking up?
45 I think she said?
- [Kate] Yep, 45 items.
- So we're definitely on a good path to decor.
- [Kate] Yeah I think that,
let's stop by Target really quick
and grab just some other like throw blankets
and other doodads and we're good.
- We're going to target.
- We're going to Target! - Oh we're going to Target!
(clapping)
- Alright, so we just loaded the car,
we loaded our bellies plus one
- I was just about to say that!
- Oh my God! - Love that frost.
- I do love that frost.
And we have Drew joining us too at Target.
- He's in a separate car
but we're heading over to Target to get more bits and bobs.
- Yup.
And items that have jacks.
- Yup throw blankets and trays.
- See you there. - Decor.
- So we want some more options to find that much.
- Yes.
- We want throw blankets
and let's just get some more. - Everything.
Bits and bobs.
- Bits and bobs!
- Oh yeah, so cute! - It's a good pillow.
- [Kate] Good pillow.
- [Joey] And I should be able to pick on thing
from every store for you.
I think this is totally you aesthetic.
- Joey I-- (laughing)
That's disgusting.
- [Kate] One minute in.
- That child needs to stop screaming immediately.
- [Kate] What about this simple bookend?
- No. - No, okay.
- This is much better than the other one.
- No but it's not-- - That one looks cheap.
- Different.
(gasps)
- I like that one.
But you can have two.
Remember how many shelves we have.
- True.
- [Drew] I think we probably need this.
- [James] What?
- I don't know, to put options in.
- Oh yes! - That's kind of cute.
- Yeah. - No, I like that!
A simple tray.
- See you questioned it and then you liked it.
- Yeah, good, good, good.
- Yeah. - Great.
- I like both of these - Yeah, Yeah.
Love that.
- Oh it's heavier than I thought.
- [Kate] Love the matte
because we got some shiny finished ones at Homegoods
- I like these a lot.
- So those are beautiful mixed in.
(upbeat music)
- Oh look how chic these planters are.
- Love!
- That's the best planter I ever did see.
- Oh, perfect!
- We'll be needing this. - Yeah.
- Oh look at those baskets!
Those cork baskets are so good.
- (gasps) Ooh.
- Wow, that's the best purchase ever.
Wow, the cart got closer than I was expecting.
Should we buy it? - Yeah.
- Oh wait.
- Oh my god you said that about the fake plant
and the baby just kicked me in my belly,
so he approves of the fake plant.
- I like this a lot.
- Leaning in the family room.
(laughing)
or when you're having a Sister Santa moment
when you just want to mount here mantle.
- I love mounting my mantle.
- Okay, great. - I think that's good.
- I love it.
(upbeat music)
- Here are things James will never use.
- [James] This is so true.
- Do you want a rolling pin? - Definitely.
- I really love those, the felt.
- That's such a good item.
- [Kate] That's cute.
That's even cuter.
- Okay, so we're about to check out right now from Target
but I first want to pause
because look at how good, go, pull back.
Look at how good these carts look together.
These carts look so chic. - So good.
This is my favorite thing
when you start seeing the room come together
- [James] Yes.
- [Kate] like in the shopping cart.
- [James] Look how at how good everything looks
like are you even kidding?
- Yes.
We have all the textures, we have the soft,
we've got the plants,
we've got the wood elements.
- This literally looks the best in the entire world.
Like are you kidding me? - I know, it's amazing.
- Well Kate, we're really talented.
- Full car-- - Getting there.
- [Kate] But there's still room for us.
- (sighs) That was a lot.
(laughing)
I'm Mr. Kent
I'm here
I'll take a look at your place
We'll stop by for a while
And help you find your style
We'll laugh at full payments delegate
- [Kate] I love you! (laughs)
- [James] Hey I told you I'm ready
for you to go on maternity leave.
So focused.
- I know you're already remixing me.
I'm scared.
You're coming for me.
- [James] I really am.
You guys, the new table is literally already here.
- It's so beautiful!
- [James] It's so big and beautiful.
- [Kate] It's also going to be so easy
to also clean thankfully.
- [James] Wow this is the most she got
for this entire room I think.
- [Kate] Yup. (laughing)
- Wow good morning world and to my luxury bedroom.
Wow I don't know where I would go.
Maybe I'll sit on my nice luxury couch
and watch my luxury television
and put my luxury feet on my luxury table.
- [Kate] Okay, so I don't mind the mirror there
but it would also look amazing right there.
Pretty!
- [James] That's a good background.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
So good!
- [Joey] That's a good fake plant.
- Really good fake plant.
A fake agave.
So cute.
And then a taller one over there.
- Yeah definitely.
Something for the--
- [Kate] The bird of paradise maybe, right?
- Should we get that too? - Yes.
I like this birdseye.
- [Drew] Oh look at all those balls.
- [Kate] Decorative Balls!
My favorite!
- [James] Look how cute, balls!
- [Kate] I know, look at all those decorative balls.
- Our decorative balls.
- [James] We need a good pot for this.
- [Kate] We need a good pot,
You also need to flare those out a little bit,
but you don't want them too flared
that they slap you in the face
on your way to go pee-pee.
- Ow! (laughing)
Can you watch where you're flaring that?
We should put the concrete balls in here.
- [Kate] You want to decorative ball room?
Yes!
- I don't even know decorative,
I just love decorative balls.
I love big round balls.
- [Kate] Yeah, put balls in your room
and it will summon more balls.
- Oh, Kate. - Yes, auspicious.
Let's--
- [Joey] Here's your smaller ball.
- Thank you so much.
- [Kate] Yeah, let's see what the decorative ball
look like next to it.
- The decorative balls.
- [James] Okay, I don't think this should,
this doesn't look good here, the big pot.
- It's too tall. - It's too tall.
- Okay ready for this design magic
that's about to happen right in your eye.
- [Kate] Can you grab, sorry a million another thing,
there should be some Target, maybe...
- [Joey] That was good James.
- Is that better? - Yeah.
- [Kate] Yes!
- Okay and that goes here and then we put--
- [Kate] A decorative ball.
- [James] This bowl right here.
- What if you do the bigger grey one too?
I like that better because it look more random
and sometimes you just have to throw stuff.
Hello sisters! - Hey guys.
- We are back at Jame's house today.
Jame's is out at a bunch of meetings today
but we are here to pull more stuff together.
We just got this new rug down in the living room.
- It's glorious - It's beautiful.
So we have so much to do.
We've got signs being delivered today.
We've got so many things to hang on the walls.
Let's do it. - Here we go.
So we got this awesome rug in.
- This is a great rug.
The rug that was in here before was too small
for the scale of the sofa.
So now we've got a rug
that actually the matches the size of the sofa
and the size of the room.
Just makes it that much more established
and it's also a natural fiber.
And then we're gonna get the coffee table,
the glass and the concrete coffee table in here
which is going to be so pretty.
- [Joey] Wait, since James isn't here
do you think he'll mind if we rug cuddle
on his rug?
- Ah!
- The rug is great,
is blessed
with our love.
- Alright we have this entryway mirror
now up right by the front door.
Look how beautiful, because hello.
James definitely needs a mirror
to check his
snatched self before he leaves.
Update in the office.
The shelves have gone up now over the desk
which is going to just make it functional
and beautiful over here.
We can display things like, oh I don't know,
James' People's Choice Award.
Should that be the first thing that goes on the shelf?
It fits
I'm just bringing in some accessories,
of course I'm going to final style with James
when he gets back,
but I'm just kind of bringing
in some items that we would style
on these office shelves
because they're a little bit more utilitarian.
And then this amazing lamp, which we couldn't resist.
The neon sign is going to go here.
He's going to have a whole new editing setup here,
but the office is coming together.
Oh let's bring in the stools too.
(upbeat music)
- Oh--
- [Kate] Oh my God
- [James] Holy crap.
- [Kate and James] That looks so good!
- [Kate] Oh my gosh it's in there!
They mounted that beautifully.
What with like glue or something?
- [Joey] Yeah I don't even know.
- I love when we mount YouTube's plaques
better than YouTube does.
- [Kate] Yeah YouTube, take some cues.
- My picture looks so good there.
Look-- - Let's just pause .
- Look at what you people-- - Look how good this looks.
- You people are standing here, holding it.
- [Joey] No it does, it looks so good.
- Kind of fun.
Backstory, we took a picture that I took
on my Africa trip were my favorite weeks
of my entire life
and Kate wanted to frame it for the middle
which I love the idea.
- Well yeah I mean-- - It's great.
- [Kate] I love the idea
of the black and white photography
breaking up the text art.
- [Joey] Yeah, that's chic.
- That looks the best. - That looks good and fresh.
- Yeah, I think it makes the most sense.
- Yeah, I like that.
- And look, we're ending it right there--
- Right at the end there. - At the end of the beam.
- Uh-huh. - Perfect.
- Shall we right now standing in the Sister Studio
where I film all my videos all day long,
every single day
and like what we were talking about,
we needed to add a few extra fun things
to make it feel like a full production space.
- Legit. - So got to have some sign.
- Yes, it's going to be-- - Wanna see it?
- Yeah I wanna see it!
- A custom sign that James' designed.
- I did. - Yes.
I haven't seen it though. - I know.
(shrieking)
This is a real friend.
- Oh my God, that looks so good!
- It looks so good! - Oh my God!
- Oh my God, I'm obsessed with these splatters.
- That literally, turn around.
Oh my god.
Wow!
- Will you go stand by it James?
Go stand by it.
Oh my God!
- [Joey] There's going to be a lot
of studio selfies in the,
like whenever you have guests come over,
you have them take a selfie in front of that.
- [Kate] Oh yeah.
- [James] On the acrylic and the trace too.
Wow, that's so dope.
- [Joey] Good job team.
- [Kate] Yay team!
- Hello Sisters!
It is late afternoon because this morning,
Kate and Joey did their reveal
to me for their room and spoiler alert,
it looks absolutely amazing.
You guys have to check it out on their channel
but-- - Hopefully you like it.
- It's literally the best
but now their crew is on the way out
and we have the house to ourselves again.
First time in a while, - Yeah.
- And obviously we have the entire rest
of the house to decorate.
So-- - But the fun stuff.
- But also fun stuff so,
we have all this decor bits and bobs
in front of us that we picked out at Target
and saved to all the places
that you guys saw us Sisters shopping at.
So we figured we would show you guys how we want to style--
- The shelves. - The entire house.
At the start of this,
we had 873 items
in our car approximately. - Yeah.
- And now looking at the table,
we have like 12.
So slightly concerned.
- [Joey] We also brought some things
up to the landing already.
- Yeah, we brought some stuff up there already.
We have the boxes to fill in space.
We we're going to get some coffee table books
but that sort of halfway happened.
We got it for the coffee table
but we don't really have any shelf books.
- Yeah.
- [Joey] Which room are we trying to decorate right now?
- Let's start this one. - Yeah.
- Let's just knock it out.
- Love it! - Let's go bottom out.
- Okay, I'm ready.
Do you want that in here?
As a layered moment or over the beanbag?
What if you put sheepskin over the sack bag
or whatever you call it?
- [James] Do you feel it with clash with the carpet?
Oh let's talk about the carpet!
- (laughing) Let's!
Sister standoff.
- I am not loving this carpet right now
that we have underneath our feet
and the new one-- - The new one.
- The jute carpet.
- [Joey] What is there not to love about it?
- [James] Its, I think it's too yellow.
- Okay, here's my thing, okay?
- [Joey] It's natural, it's natural white.
- It's natural fiber.
You wanted the layered colors,
the layered tones. - Yes.
- Right, going with minimalist design
you have to layer different tones
to create complexity
because you don't have wham-bam contrast going on.
- This is true.
- It's also been the rainiest week ever
in L.A. history. - It's true.
- Don't quote me on that but it's been really dim outside
so you had the yellowy lights on it all the time.
You literally haven't seen it in
full on daylight.
- [Joey] Yea or nay carpet?
- Nay.
- Yea or nay? - Yea.
(cheering) - Yea.
- I feel attacked.
- People do this.
They buy big items
before they finish the rest of their place.
They become fixated on that item.
They change it out-- - Smart.
- They return it and then they just become hung up
and three years later they haven't decorated their room
because they haven't found the right rug.
Whereas, let's live with this.
Let's get the rest of the room put together.
Let the sun shine
and then call me.
- I'm going to give the benefit of the doubt
because I trust you. - I know, I know.
- And your opinion is very good, not wanting it right now.
- I totally feel you.
It's a good life lesson. (laughs)
- Likely this isn't part of the initial shown
in the video because in the designer process,
not everything always works perfectly.
- No.
- Like there always needs to go wrong.
Sometimes you pick things
and then they look good online,
they don't come the same way.
Me, before I put FaceTune on Instagram.
It's just like, sometimes you need to switch it up
or wait until the end and see what it looks like.
- I feel like that should be in here,
once we move the folding table.
This is the room
where you most readily wire throw blankets
available, right? - Yes definitely.
- And we got so many great options.
We've got this kind of one-- - That's a good one.
- This is good for look, don't cuddle.
- Yeah nobody's ever going to cuddle with that.
- This one will be the one
that's permanently on this ladder.
- Okay.
- The rest of the will be rotating.
- I feel like we should put this marble chain
underneath the TV.
- Yeah, I'm trying to clean.
What we need is,
we need a box for it to drape on
so you can see the movement of it.
Exactly, great. - Beautiful.
- Two of our four books are already stylish.
- [Drew] Do you think it's too much marble options?
- [James] Yeah, we need some other color pops
to offset it.
- So maybe layer it with this guy.
- [Drew] How's this?
- I mean that's cute there but now--
- This.
- [James] Drew, did you just take this
out of my centerpiece.
- [Drew] Yeah I did but it's still full.
- [James] Drew!
- [Kate] Okay James, here's options.
Plant? - Yes.
- Or sculpture?
- Oh that's kind of good. - Right?
Because we'll have a lot of plants going on
in the shelves.
- I just want to say this doesn't even look good.
- [Joey] We're not even on that room right now.
- Joey!
- [Joey] Come back.
- Hmm that mirror look not good there.
- [Kate] No?
- Yeah it does.
No.
(laughing)
Yeah looks nice, maybe something at the end.
To literally encompass it all.
- [Kate] What about this little dripper?
- [James] Oh yeah, I love a little dripper.
- Like if we have a little dripper coming
plain with the...
Let this not be so straight. - Perfect.
- Perfect.
- [Drew] No you have to put it on this shelf James.
To make it look like you water it,
because you can't water it up there.
- [Joey] No one will believe it's real.
That's a good tip.
- That is good to know.
- I would never think that deep about it.
- You should probably quit your job then.
- Yeah.
James what do you think about a frame,
resting frame moment.
- [James] I love the resting frame moment.
- Okay.
Do you want him still over there?
Because obviously he has been living over there.
Do you want to change him up? - Let's switch him up.
I think we need something actually tall here, though.
To balance out because it likes tall, short, short, tall.
- [Joey] Well, what was wrong with that?
- Hmm. - Too tall.
- Kind of ugly.
- It looks-- - Not ugly, but I feel like-
- [Joey] Doesn't fit.
- [Drew] Oh you probably meant a decorative ball.
- Decorative ball. - Did you try the ball?
- [James] I was thinking about it.
- Try it!
- [Drew] That looks nice.
- [James] It's actually kind of good.
- [Drew] Very curvy.
- I think its good
and I also kind of love the bookend.
The subtle bookend of the silver sculpture.
It's like this is-- - I like this too.
- A magnified version of that.
Okay, I'm taking the price tags off
because we loved it.
It ain't about the money, money, money
Unless it's coffee, coffee, coffee, table books
(laughing)
- Oh wow Kate, you are getting brave tonight.
- [Drew] Look how chic that it.
Two boxes for the price of one.
- Whoa, Whoa, Whoa.
You're going to use all four
of the remaining books? - All four.
- [Drew] It actually looks good.
- It looks good but we don't have any more
for any of the other shelves now.
- [Drew] Oh well, this is a main room.
- [Kate] I think we need a candle on it,
we need a candle on it. - Oh, Please.
- That looks so good.
- [Drew] That's a nice aged, mercury glass bitten bottle.
- Isn't that so good?
I found it at Target on sale,
"I think we're purchasing this right now."
- [Kate] Since we don't have the big, beefy glass tray,
maybe we use the mirror tray here?
Or do you like it-- - I don't like--
- Clothing.
- Well I feel like those two vases are the same height,
so that needs to change.
This is so hard.
- [Joey] I think you should take away the lantern
and the white vase.
Just leave the cool vase and the plants.
- No. - No.
- [Drew] That's illegal.
- Just take the watering can away.
- [Joey] No the watering can is the best piece.
- [James] No, the watering can should be on the shelf.
- [Joey] Okay, fine.
- We need a pot to put this in.
- [Joey] Why?
It's in a pot?
- It kind of looks chic in that pot.
- Yeah. - Yeah I like that chic pot.
- [Joey] Perfect.
- Some little stubs.
- I think that can go up, up.
- [James] Yeah, up up up and away.
- Joey can you do it? - Mmhm.
- [Drew] That's a nice bold spot.
- Yeah, that is good.
Wait give me the small, Joey, give me the small one.
- [Kate] No yeah, that pot is thick
It's got a thick booty on it.
- [James] That's good.
- [Kate] Yeah, we like that there.
- What about all the way at the top, this vase?
With the light shining on it for glass floridity?
- So will we find a rainbow when the light hits it?
- Yeah. - Let's try that.
- We're going to need a step stool
to put that up there.
- [Drew] I'll just throw it.
(laughing)
- [All] Ooh.
- Inspired moment.
- [James] That's luxurious and ratch.
- Yes.
- We have lots to do still.
- He sounds really-- - But guess what?
We get to do it all over again.
Here's your accessory table!
- [James] Oh my god.
It looks like it filled back up.
- [Kate] It does look like you have a lot now.
- Wow, you should leave that bowl there.
That looks so good.
- [Joey] Why did we set this up down here
when we got to go upstairs?
- Joey, always looking-- - That's what I was wondering.
- [Joey] Do you think I always look at the negative?
Is this stupid?
Should we repo all this stuff upstairs?
- Yeah. - Yeah?
All right, here we go.
We get to do it again.
- Every place we put the accessories it looks good.
- [Drew] Look at this door.
- Okay, get excited.
James!
- Can I do the desk area
and you guys can do the other ones?
- Sure. - Okay.
- [Joey] So just this is all we got to do
and we're done?
- Yay!
That's baby.
Do you want the globe for the top of the piano?
- No. - Or do you want it here?
- [Joey] I don't think you want it on the piano?
- [Drew] I don't think Sisters candles.
- Yeah candles. - Yeah.
- [Drew] No idea.
Wow this Tom Ford book is so very chic.
- It's the chicest of the chic.
- Over there. - Yes.
- [Kate and James] Bam!
- [Joey] I don't think you need anything else on the piano.
- No I agree.
Maybe put it by the little side table?
- Just a floor sitter?
- [Drew] A floor sitter option.
- I think we should put the table over here
and instead put the large sculpture maybe here.
Or switch it?
- [Kate] I don't think Joey's loves it.
- [Joey] When you walk up the stairs
and see the wire sculpture, it's amazing.
- But that mirror's for our own TV.
- [Joey] Oh that's true.
So you want it in the pics.
Yeah, well it's going to be better
than that table for your pictures.
- So true.
- [Kate] Does that fit up here?
- [Joey] So are we good?
- I think we're good
and moral of the story is we got enough stuff.
- Yeah we did.
- Could have done with the coffee table book or two but...
(laughing)
- [Joey] Alright guys.
Did we do it? - Are we done?
- Think we're done. - I think we're done.
- I can't believe it.
- Sisters. - Sisters.
Is it sleeping time?
Oh my god, we're such sleepy sisters.
- I'm supportive.
It's been four days
and we've had literally the time of our life
and we just finished literally
the most beautiful house in the entire world.
- I agree.
Yes!
- Ah, daddy Joey.
Should we head to the beauty studio
to say goodbye?
- Yes, I'll go in the room and say goodbye.
- That's so true.
- But I'm so glad that it's done.
- Okay, so let's do it.
- Let's go. - Alright.
- Oh my God you guys!
We are done. - Done.
I really am going to miss you.
I've gotten so, I mean I was already obsessed with you
but now I'm attached to you.
- Same sister.
I feel like literally this collab
has been in the works for so long now
and I've been subscribed to you guys for so long
and this just meant so much with you
that you wanted to come over and work together
on this project too,
which was so cool.
I know that it was something very different for you guys
but I feel like it turned out so good
and I'm just very proud of what we did
and thank you guys for being the best ever
and for being talented and for helping me out.
- We're so impressed by you. - Yeah.
- Like you've done so much in such a short amount of time.
- Aw, thank you guys.
- We talk about you all the time.
I just love watching your growth
and I'm just so proud of you
and really, truly so happy for you
and so excited to always see what you're doing.
- You guys are my favorite!
Thank you guys so much.
You guys are literally the best in the entire world.
I hope all of you Sisters
have loved this decorating video.
Obviously we're done,
but you guys have not yet seen the finished product;
my final house tour
that I've been promising you guys forever,
is coming this upcoming Friday.
The house is done,
so I literally have no excuses now.
So stay tuned this Friday
and I hope you guys enjoyed this little decorating video
and got lots of tips from Kate and Joey and I.
This was so much fun to do
and I know you guys are going
to love the finished product.
I know that I do.
And if you did enjoy it,
please don't forget to give a big thumbs up down below.
And it you have not already,
come join the sisterhood.
We are 13 million sisters
and I would love to have you join the family.
Click the bell icon so you can get a notification
every time I upload a brand new video.
Also, like we talked about,
the front living room was very much covered
because over on Kate and Joey's channel--
- [Kate and Joey] We did it!
- We took it from empty to full
we surprised you with a design.
It was the only part of it obviously
that James didn't have his digits in
and you we were like fully surprised by it.
So yeah, if you want to see James be sister surprised.
- It's up right now. - It's up.
Also go subscribe to them.
Kate and Joey literally have some of the best content
on the entire YouTube platform, in my opinion.
I've been subscribed to them for over four years now
and just like they said for me,
following their growth has been so incredible
and I'm so proud of that
and doing this collab was just such a dream come true.
So you Sisters need to go support them as well.
If you like to follow me on my makeup journey,
you can follow me on Instagram or Twitter.
They both are just jamescharles.
My Snapchat for behind the scenes type stuff
is Jamescharles with an extra S after Charles.
If you guys want to follow them, MrKate.
- Yay! - Group hug.
- We love you, our baby.
- This video is sister is Sister shout out
goes to sister Evelyn.
Thank you so much love for always following
and supporting.
You know I love you literally so so much.
And if you at home would like to be
in the next Sister Shout out
don't forget to turn on my video post notifications
and also retweet links that go live on Twitter.
Thank you guys so much for watching this video.
We love you and we will see you in the next one.
- [All] Bye!
(upbeat music)
Been a little too nice to y'all
Now I gotta up price on y'all
Snake eyes