- [Together] Hi sisters!
- James Charles here, and welcome back
to my YouTube channel!
As you guys can see, I'm joined today
with a very iconic sister special guest.
- I'm a famous beauty guru.
- Jenna Marbles!
You guys, today we are here for an episode of
James' Ratchet Beauty Salon, and I am
so beyond excited, because I have wanted to do
this video together for so long now.
You're one of my favorite YouTubers literally
of all time, and I have so many,
come on!
I literally have been watching you since I was
a little kid.
And this means so much, and I'm already so excited
for you to be here today.
- [Jenna] I love you.
- I love you more!
We have so much that I want to talk to you about today,
and you also,
I'm serious here.
On your channel, with Jenna's Ratchet Beauty Salon ...
- Yes.
- With some pretty good makeup tips.
- Thank you.
- Questionable sometimes. - Thank you.
- But pretty good. - Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Yup. - So I figured ...
- I'm a professional.
- You are definitely a professional.
We just had our Valentine's Day video-versary.
- Happy video-versary, James.
- Because last year, you did a video following
my Valentine's Day makeup tutorial, which I was so shook by
because I think the first time we met was at Playlist.
- You were ... - It was.
- So tall, so gorgeous, legs for days,
and I was like, oh my god, that's James Charles.
- What? You walked by and you were like, hey James Charles.
And I was like, oh my god that was Jenna Marbles.
I was like walking in and you were walking out,
and it was literally just that, a quick three-second moment,
and I was like ...
Oh my god.
And then you did the video following my Valentine's Day
makeup tutorial, and I think I was only at like
2 million subscribers at that point, so I was shook.
- I love you.
- But I was so excited and so happy,
because, like I said, I've been watching you forever,
you've inspired me and so many other people,
and I figured for today's video--
- I'm gonna cry.
- We should get together,
and open James' Ratchet Beauty Salon.
- Yes.
- Talk about all things YouTube, the beauty community,
love, I feel like we should definitely talk about
finding me a boyfriend today.
- James! James!
- Because it's been quite the trending topic for you.
- You literally just posted a video that was like
I'm gonna be sad and alone forever.
- Yeah. - James.
- Well it's true. I didn't lie.
- Boy, I swear to god.
- I feel like we have so many things to talk about,
should we just jump right in?
- Yeah, let's just jump into it.
- Okay great.
(upbeat music)
We're gonna start off with two different foundations,
and I'm not even sure which one we're gonna do,
I think we're gonna try mixing together
Fenty and Too Faced.
We know that it's a trend for me to not be able
to do this very well so,
we're not really expecting much here.
But everything else will be good.
- It's okay James.
I never match anything because I'm always different shades
of fake tan, so.
- Same!
I actually just got tanned again for the first time
in a while a few days ago, so I am feeling
my bronze fantasy.
My foundation actually matches pretty good today.
- You look beautiful.
Ten million times even more beautiful in person.
- Oh thanks angel.
- You're welcome.
- Okay, so I am so excited for today's video
because I have wanted to do this forever now.
- Because you just want to do a nice lovely look
on mature skin?
- Yes.
You've been on YouTube for a very, very long time now.
- Yeah.
- Like one of the OGs. Day one. How many years has it been?
- I've been making videos on Jenna Marbles for nine years.
Almost ten.
- Oh my god. - Yeah.
- That's so cool.
And you still love it as much as you did before?
- Yeah, I mean it has its ups and downs,
some days it's the best thing in the world,
and some days it's really stressful but yeah I love it.
- How have you been able to stay motivated
and inspired to keep making content after ten years?
Because I've only been at this for two and I'm like ...
I constantly am like, oh god what am I gonna do next?
- Yeah well.
I feel like that never goes away.
- Yeah.
- I just have a schedule, and it forces you to create
on a regular basis, whether you like it or not.
It's your job, go do it.
- Yeah. - And have fun.
Do the best you can.
Some days you're gonna kill it, and some days you're not,
so, just be with yourself through the good days
and bad days, you know?
- Right.
How would you say the platform has changed
over the past ten years of being on it?
- Oh so much.
When I started it was weird.
It was just a weird place for people to post whatever.
- Yeah.
- Like on my first channel, I had a bunch of videos
like from college that were school projects.
Now you hear kids being like, I wanna grow up
and be a YouTuber.
- Which is so cool. - Yeah.
- But also scary. - Totally.
- But it's been really cool to watch the evolution
of Jenna Marbles and see you here still making content
today, and just like ...
- Awe, thanks. - Killing it.
It's really cool.
- I have always thought, like this will probably end someday
and that'll be okay, but I still have a job, so.
- Right.
- So it's really amazing.
Ten years ago when I started, it was kind of difficult
for anybody to write something nice about YouTubers.
- Oh yeah.
- Because it was a joke.
- Well even still, I just got back from London
a few weeks ago when I was traveling there
and I got mauled.
- I saw that.
- By the British media.
- Although I've heard like from some of the UK YouTubers
they get treated a lot worse over there.
- Yeah.
- But here it's getting better, you know,
if you work with a traditional celebrity
in the past sometimes it might have been like
oh a producer has brought you on to be the social media
person but the talent doesn't really know
who you are-- - Right.
- Or care. - Or care.
- But they're still nice.
- Right.
- But now it's different.
People know who you are and they value
what you bring to the table.
- Which is exciting.
You kind of started on YouTube
because a lot of your videos all went viral.
Like, really, really insane crazy views
which is super cool to look back at like
all the old drunk makeup tutorials, and
literally when you were sitting in your bathroom
and filming on ...
- My laptop.
- I don't even know what, yeah the laptop.
- It was a laptop.
And I would film and edit at the same time.
- What?
- Yeah.
I would open up my laptop, and shoot on iMovie,
and edit it as I was filming it.
Yeah.
- Why?
- I don't know, that's what I did.
I didn't have a camera.
- Yeah.
- So I was just filming it with what I had.
Yeah, all of my raw files are me just like ...
Click ...
And then another thing!
Like half the time my arm's coming in and out of frame,
because I'm stopping it.
Yeah. I didn't have a camera.
- That's like everything to me, though.
That's so cool to see the evolution.
So what would you say is what the differences is
between going viral then versus now.
- I feel like ten years ago, when something went viral
it means that everybody saw it.
- Right.
- Whereas now you could go viral on Facebook,
you could go viral on Instagram,
or the word is sort of lost a little bit
of what that means, because so many people's attention
is in a million different places.
- Is in a million places, yeah.
- So, I feel like things go viral less often,
but more often at the same time.
- Yeah. That's a good way to put it.
There's so many more people that have access
to everything now.
I've had a few videos now pass like 20 million,
which has been so crazy.
And they're always ones that I least expect, too.
- That's how the internet works.
- That's how the internet works!
But even then, I'm like, oh well okay 20 million.
But it's like 20 million people watched that.
That is insane.
- I especially relate to the videos that you feel like
are whatever are the ones that people really like
and respond to, and the ones that you put all your energy
into and you really enjoy, people are like,
hmm, I didn't like this one.
Like shit, sorry.
I don't know what you guys want.
- My second most viewed video on my channel is literally
my FAKE Palette video where I bought the fake palette
from Santee Alley and reviewed it,
I hated how the video turned out, I was like
this is gonna be a horrible video, I don't even know
if I want to post this, and it's at like 25 million views
now. - Yeah.
That's how it always works.
- I was like, what?
- The green screen video that I filmed
literally after I was done filming it, I laid on the couch
like in full green-face and I was like
Julien, I'm not gonna upload it, it's terrible,
I'm just gonna tell people that I ruined my videos.
- That's one of my favorite videos from you.
- But I was so defeated by the end of that,
I was like, this was a horrible video.
I hated it.
- Really? - Yeah.
- I'm just applying a light coat of powder all over.
- Oh I feel so powdered, I'm baking.
- I wanna use a little bit of a lighter bell
because we definitely put on some foundation, duh
and concealer, and I don't want anything to look
really cakey.
- Cake me.
- What are some of your favorite channels to watch
on YouTube?
- I watch a lot of beauty videos.
- Do you actually?
- I really like them.
- Okay. - I always have.
That's the channels that I first got into,
Juicy Star, oh my god.
- Yes.
- I loved the old school beauty gurus,
and I'd never seen so many people with on-suite bathrooms
in their videos in my life, I couldn't believe it.
I was like, oh my god, these people are so rich
they have their own bathrooms.
I feel like they've just gotten so much cooler
and better with time
- Yeah.
- People are just so talented.
Like when I was a little girl I wanted to do makeup.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I had all the books, I had Kevin Au-coin
and like the Bobby Brown.
- Who?
- Au-coin? Whatever his name is?
- Kevin Aucoin?
- Whatever. How do I say it?
- Kevin Aucoin.
- I loved his book. I loved his book.
- Yeah, he's iconic.
You grew up in New York.
I, for some reason thought you grew up in
I knew you lived in Rochester, but I thought
you grew up in New Jersey, but you grew up in
New York.
- Rochester New York.
- And I grew up in Albany New York, which is literally
like three-ish hours away from each other?
- Yeah.
But that's why I knew that I liked you.
Because you're normal.
Because people from upstate are normal.
- Are normal, yeah.
- Really normal.
- What made you want to move to LA?
- Well I lived in Boston for about 8 years.
- Okay.
- I went to school there.
I started doing YouTube after I graduated
from graduate school, and it sort of took off,
and I was like, I guess I'll just go down this path
and see where it goes for a little while, and ...
- Yeah.
- Here we are ten years later.
- What has been one of your favorite lessons
that you've learned over the course of the internet?
- I guess just to be nice to everybody.
You know, because you never know what someone else
is going through.
- Yeah.
- I've never watched a video and left a mean comment.
- Ever! Ever!
- Yeah.
And so I just try to remind myself that even if someone
writes something like that, that's not a representation
of who they are either.
Because I don't know maybe they're just having
a really bad day and they just want to take it out
on your lash tutorial.
- Right. - You know?
Oh my god I look so beautiful already.
I feel like the amount of hate that I've gotten too,
if this is any hope for you, does die down.
- Over time?
- Yeah, like I've been on the internet for a long time,
so all the people that really wanted to be mean to me
were that a long time ago, and then they gave up
and they moved on.
- Yeah.
- I would also say one of the biggest lessons
that I learned is being okay with having me time.
I mean it, and not like a, I'm gonna cover myself
in paraffin wax kind of way, like ...
You know, have your weekends, and time off,
because it's really good.
It's nothing, but it doesn't serve for nothing.
Because you're so busy, you're gonna get tired.
You're gonna need some me time.
- This brings us into my next point that I wanted
to talk to you about.
You have been such a cool, like indirect role model
to me I feel like, because in so many videos that you have
mentioned me in, I feel like you're always
giving me some sort of advice.
- It is officially February, which means this month
is Valentine's Day.
I'm not excited, it is my least favorite holiday
because I've been single for it for 17 years now,
and ...
(laughs)
Let's be real, it's gonna be 18 in just a few days.
- Oh my god!
It's gonna be okay, alright? You're gonna find your person.
- It's so funny that it's worked out that way,
either whether it be mentioning it in a video
or on Twitter, I feel like it has been really cool
hearing from you as someone who's been in it for a while,
giving your perspective and helping me out,
because that is something that I struggle with a lot,
is taking time for myself, and forcing myself
to take a break, and that is definitely
one of my biggest things that I'm forcing myself to do
in 2019, just because 2018 was such an amazing year
for me, and I'm so proud of everything that I achieved,
but I was really burnt out.
I tried to deal with it publicly too, because I feel like
it's important for everybody else to know that like
this isn't easy all the time, it is really challenging
to come up with new concepts and new ideas.
- That is something that I appreciate about what you've done
and YouTubers from I guess your generation of YouTubers
have done, is that you've sort of normalized,
I've seen you tweet out like, which thumbnail
would you like, or what do you want?
- Yeah.
- Which is something that just wasn't a thing for it,
no one cares.
No one cares about the meta of brands, or you know.
It was just ridiculous for me to ever think about that,
and I also come from a time on the internet where people
would be mad at you for taking a brand deal.
- Yeah.
- You were a sellout, how could you?
- Well that happens still a lot
in the beauty community today ...
- Does it really? - But it's better
- At this point, your generation of YouTubers
have normalized that, and your audience celebrates it
for you, like when you're doing well, which is rad.
- Exciting, yeah.
- I'm so excited to see what you're gonna do with my brows
because I get roasted everyday.
If you can't tell, sometimes I shave off the ends
because I get bored with the tails.
- I love that. Mine are shaved off too.
- Really?
- The ends of them - It's fun, right?
- Yeah, it is.
- Everyone thought I was crazy when I did it.
- Okay, so.
Speaking of you giving me advice too.
The one thing that you've harped on me for
for a very long time now is my love life.
- James.
You're 19, you're gonna find somebody.
- No.
First of all, how did you guys meet. Tell me the story.
- Julien worked at a bar at the end of my street,
and I went in and relentlessly hit on him.
- So was this when you were in Boston?
Or were you in LA at the time?
- I was in LA. - Okay.
For me, finding a boyfriend has been challenging.
- James! You're gonna find somebody!
- From watching my channel, and from hearing me talk about
boy stories and stuff, do you have any advice for me
when it comes to finding love?
- Well, so right now I feel like your energy
is a little chaotic.
- A little bit, yeah.
- So I brought you a plant.
- You did?
- I realize you have a couple plants.
- Got me a cute little housewarming gift.
- Yeah.
But I feel like when you're looking for love,
the more love you put out into the universe,
like if you care for a plant, or like someday
you get a doggy or a kitty,
I don't know if you like animals.
- I cannot wait, I'm getting a dog soon.
We're adopting.
- So if you put love out into the universe,
and you focus on yourself, you'll find a love.
You'll get that love back.
Focus on putting some love out there, and less of the
I'm alone forever energy, and maybe you'll find somebody.
- I feel like whenever I do get the busiest
and I'm not thinking about boys, is when I find like
three all at once, and then I'm like ...
It's just not fitting well.
- But you're also 19.
Like that would be the same as someone finding
the love of their life in high school.
Which happens, but you know, not always.
For most people that's not really a thing that happens,
so give yourself some time, be patient.
You don't want to be with somebody right now
that's not right for you, your person's gonna come to you
when they're gonna come to you.
- True.
Brows are my favorite part because they can really
make or break a makeup routine, but it's so ...
- If you don't like them you can just shave them off.
- Okay great.
- I'm dead serious.
(clapping)
I'm so excited!
- Alright you guys, we are back
and both eyebrows are now complete and looking
pretty good and fresh and beautiful and snatched.
How do you feel?
- Feels so fresh and beautiful.
- Okay good. So famous.
- So famous. - So famous!
- That's so funny.
- You know what else is really famous?
- What?
- Like ...
Really famous?
- There she is. I've never seen her in person.
- What? Really?
- Tried to order 'em, couldn't order it, you sold out.
- I didn't send you one?
- No.
- [Julien] Tea.
- Tea!
- Nobody sends me anything.
- Do you want one?
- I want to buy one with my own money.
- No.
- I want to support you, I don't like, no.
- You're the cutest.
Jenna just told me when we walked in that you guys
ordered Sisters apparel, why didn't we just--
- I was trying to get Sisters apparel
for when we filmed together, so we could show up
in our Sisters clothes.
- That is so cute, you guys are the best.
She sold out too.
- Trying to support people, you know?
I don't want you to give me one, I want to buy one.
I'm gonna go to an Ulta and buy it.
- Okay, I'll text you when it restocks then.
- Thank you.
- I'll also give you one, too. For the meantime.
- No, no, no no, no, no!
- We have the James Charles X Morphe palette here today,
and we're gonna do a fun and fresh eye look on Jenna.
- Unleash your inner artist!
- Yes!
So I wanna do something like, kind of fun,
because I feel like when you do do beauty videos,
they're not bad.
And I think you make fun of yourself all the time
for sucking at makeup, but you don't,
is the truth tea, sister
- Awe!
- So I feel like we should do something like ...
- Whatever you want.
- Something fun, right!
- I'm down for whatever.
- Okay. I think I know what look I want to do on you.
- What? Tell us!
- I think I wanna do a purpley-blue on the lid.
- Fun.
- With a good sunset ... - Love a sunset.
- Moment. - Love it.
- Yeah. - I'm ready.
It'll match my aura.
- Yeah.
Like, you have the orange on, and I have the blue and pink,
so like, sunset.
- Perfect.
Oh I know what I wanted to say to you.
I think it's so cool that you're sober.
- Oh!
- And you don't drink or do any drugs.
- Yeah. A sober sister.
- I think that's really wonderful, James.
- I think it's also because I have a major fear
of getting in trouble.
- Me!
- I always like, going to the principal's office
was my worst nightmare.
- I'm scared of authority.
- Yeah, don't like getting yelled at, don't like
being in trouble, don't like breaking the rules ever.
And obviously when I was in high school, I was very much
underage, and I would hear all the time about people
getting arrested, and people getting stopped by the police
because the police in my town were pretty intense.
I would go to school and people would be like
so mad about it, like oh I got busted last night,
and like, hey you're breaking the law.
- Yeah.
- Like, duh, of course you're gonna get in trouble for it.
I don't know I just never wanted to do that, and I think
also because even before I was doing makeup
I was doing hair for girls in my school,
I was trying to do social media.
I was just never interested in doing that,
but I think it's because I had so many other things
going on.
- I think it's really admirable, and really cool.
- Thank you. - Yeah.
- I really appreciate that.
- Yeah.
Did you ever play any sports, James?
- I did actually.
- What did you play?
- I played baseball.
- Ooh, me too!
- And basketball, and soccer.
- Ooh, can't relate to basketball.
- And hockey. - Whoa. A jock.
- I was so convinced that I was so straight.
I'm not athletic, but I am competitive.
- You're athletic.
- Not really. - Yuh-huh.
I've seen those legs.
- I've always been very, very competitive,
so even through sports I didn't really like playing them
but I did like winning.
What did you play?
- I played softball all the way through college.
- Okay.
I can totally picture that.
- Yeah.
- Oh my god, how are your dogs?
- They're so good.
- Are they?
- I was gonna ask you if you wanted me to bring any of them
so you could hang.
- Yeah, you should have!
- Damn, I really blew this, didn't I?
- [Julien] They would've been crying.
- Oh.
I want to adopt a dog so badly.
- What kind of dog do you want?
Big, little?
- I want a medium sized dog, like not as big
as a lab, just a little bit smaller for sure.
I grew up with a border collie black lab mix,
and he was literally ...
- Smart.
- The best, and I miss him so much.
- He was a smart boy.
- Yes, he was super, super smart.
I've been really wanting to adopt one, I've just been
traveling so much recently that I'm like,
I'm not gonna put a dog through that until I know
that I'm home for a little bit.
Which sucks, but I know is obviously for the better.
But my traveling is coming to a half very soon,
so I'm starting to look.
- That's good. You need to look out for yourself.
- Yeah.
I love dogs, and I'm the type of person that likes
to be with people at all times, like I love having friends
and family over.
- It's cause you're a Gemini.
- I am.
Why do you say that? Is that a quality that Geminis have?
- I don't know.
- So I like being around people kind of at all times,
and I feel like when I'm not with people, it'd be good
for me to have a dog around.
Would you get another dog?
- Yeah, we talk about it all the time.
- Really?
- We're gonna rescue a big greyhound.
- So you do want to get another one?
- Yeah.
- Okay. And would you want to get a girl or a boy?
- Well, I think we'd get another girl.
And so we'd have two boys and two girls.
- Okay.
- And if you ever need a dog-sitter, I'm not kidding,
just drop your dog off at my house.
- Really? - [Julien] Yes.
- I love watching other people's dogs.
- Okay. Definitely will do.
Okay I'm gonna grab a little bit of Artistry
from the palette, and I'm gonna put this on your lid,
I think.
Let's see how this looks.
Oh wow, look at that!
That color is so famous!
- Oh my god! It's gonna be a whole femur!
- I'm gonna add a wing liner.
- Ooh!
- I feel like we have to do a wing, it's like staple
Jenna Marbles.
Right? - [Jenna] I'm ready.
Pretty much. - [James] Okay.
- [Jenna] I like it.
- [James] Okay, I'm gonna take a deep breath.
- [Jenna] It's hard.
- [James] I know.
- [Jenna] Okay.
(inhales)
Based on my personality and what you've seen of me
on YouTube so far, what type of dog do you think
would be good for me?
- Something that is playful.
Honestly, if you were looking for a little dog
I'd say a Jack Russell terrier.
Something that you can just throw a ball with all day,
because you're high energy.
You have a lot of energy, a lot of love to give.
- Yes. This is true.
- You could handle a very high energy dog.
Except for the fact that you travel.
But just your personality.
- You think?
- Yeah, something really fun.
- Look forward.
- Any dog would be lucky to have you as a dad.
- Thanks sister. - Yeah.
- That wing looks awful.
- No it doesn't! What are you talking about?
- It looks really good when you close, but.
- My face is hard. It's a challenge.
- Where do you usually put your wings?
- Everywhere.
Like this one I have to do differently, because it's
I got wonky eye.
- [James] Uh-huh. I'm seeing that.
Uh-oh. What do I do?
- [Jenna] See I get roasted all the time, I'm like, you guys
don't understand.
This is a hard face.
- Oh my god, it worked.
Oh my god I've never done that before.
For people that have hooded eyes, sometimes people
will draw a wing, I don't know that's like
it goes in and then ...
- It's like a hook.
- Yeah, kind of.
And I did that shape and it worked
because of that eye flap.
- Flappy.
- But I still need to clean it up, because it still
looks horrendous, but give me a second, and it'll look
better.
- There's hope for us people with flappy eyes.
- Yeah.
- I never have this many colors on my eye,
I'm very excited.
- Do you like it?
- Yes. I can only do one color at a time.
- Really?
- Yeah, because I'll start blending
and then before I know it, it's just in my eyebrow.
- Oh that's good.
- And all your brushes are really soft,
and mine are all sharp and owie,
and this is just really nice.
- Are they really?
Why?
- I don't know. Probably just washing them
and pressing on them too hard.
- Do you need new ones? I can hook you up.
- No stop trying to give me stuff!
- Why?
- Because I pay stuff with my own money,
I like to support you.
- You need the James Charles X Morphe brush set.
- Hell yeah.
- If you think you're leaving here without it today,
you're wrong.
- I'm leaving here without it.
- No you're not.
- Mm-hmm.
- You brought me a plant, I can bring you a palette.
- Mm-mm. - Yes.
- Mm-mm. - Yes!
- No.
I suddenly don't know how to use my hands.
I can't leave with it.
- Julien can carry it, it's okay.
- [Julien] Okay.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Don't sabotage me like this, Julien.
- Hide the inner corner for a nice little pop.
- Oh my god, pop.
- Okay so I'm gonna apply a lily lash
in the style Yass Queen.
- Wow.
- Who's been some of your favorite people
that little James can't believe that you got to work with
so far?
- So many.
It's honestly most of the people that I've been able
to work with.
You and Shane I grew up watching, so like this is
super cool, my video with Shane has been amazing.
- Shane's pretty wonderful.
- He really is.
Demi.
- Ooh.
- We haven't filmed together yet, but like
she's just my favorite person in the entire world.
And I have had so many dark times, like her music
has helped me get through.
And now her and I literally text every day.
And it's so cool just to have that with somebody
you've looked up to forever, because she's just
literally the nicest.
Kylie and Kim, super, super dope.
They're like two of my favorites ever.
Pretty much everybody, like,
my subscribers are super supportive of me
so I don't really do a lot of collabs.
And if I do do them, it's people that I've really
looked up to and respected for a while.
Like I refuse to do a collab just to gain subscribers,
I would never, because I don't need it.
My followers will still watch my content regardless
which is amazing.
So pretty much everybody that I've collabed with
has been somebody that I've loved.
- That's so cool.
- Which is really cool.
It's like my favorite part of the job.
Okay, we're gonna pop this on here,
and hope that looks good and fresh.
We're off to a good start now, do you like it?
- I love it, it's so pretty.
- Okay, it's looking good now!
Wow we love a good eyelash.
Okay great!
- That's something I learned many years ago,
like if you mess up on your eyeliner a little bit
just throw a thick lash on there, and it's like
it never happened!
- And it's gone!
That's such a good makeup tip, we're professionals!
Okay.
Alright you guys, so that is pretty much one eye
on sister Jenna all complete.
We're gonna go ahead and do the other one now
pretty quickly, but we'll be right back
to finish off the rest of the look.
Alright sisters we are back with both eyes all complete,
how are you feeling?
- Amazing, beautiful.
- I like how it's turning out.
I feel like it looks really stunning and good and fresh!
- I've done so much work here today.
- Alright you guys, we're gonna move on to the next step
which is of course going to be the glow.
Just a little bit of highlighter moment.
So we're gonna still stay within the James Charles palette
I'm just gonna grab of course Face.
- Ooh.
- Just grab an M501, I'm gonna give you a quick ...
(clattering)
Oops.
A quick spritz of some sister setting spray first,
just to kind of melt some of the powders in
now that we're all done with the eyeshadow.
Jenna if you were not doing YouTube, do you have
any idea what you would be doing right now?
- Well I mean I went to graduate school
for sports psychology, so ...
- Oh!
- I would probably honestly be working with kids.
I worked as a camp counselor for years,
and in graduate school we did ...
Oh my ...
Oh! Oh my goodness! I'm gonna pass out!
It never looks like that when I do it.
What? (gasps)
Oh, sorry. Goodness.
We did a program where we taught social responsibility
through physical activity for kids that
lived in underserved areas, and I worked
for the Boys and Girls Club for a lot of years.
- Oh my god!
- So I would probably work with kids.
- I could see you definitely being like
an elementary school teacher.
I could definitely see that.
- Oh my god, it's so beautiful!
- You look so smooth and buttery!
- I am so smooth and buttery!
- So famous!
Okay, I'm gonna grab a little bit of Literally,
on a Anastasia A23 brush, this is like my favorite
shade in the palette for using a blush, highlight
mixer type of color, and I'm gonna use this
to blend together.
Oh that was a little much.
I'm going, look to your left, and then I have
one last question for you when we're done.
Gonna do a good little nude moment.
- What would you be doing if you weren't doing YouTube?
- I have no idea.
I think about that all the time.
I would be in college right now, for sure.
- What would you study?
- I don't know.
I think because the fact that I did get into makeup
and hair right before I was done with high school,
I don't know.
Because it did take up so much of my time and interest.
I've always been very into business and marketing,
that's always been my biggest passion
and that's always been what I'm really, really good at,
and still am good at to this day, that's what social media
is at the end of the day, is marketing and knowing how
to do it right.
So I feel like if I wasn't doing this, I'd be studying
marketing, but at the same time too, because of the fact
that I already did have so much experience, I definitely
feel like it is one of those fields where you can
really learn a lot better when you're experiencing
those type of things.
When I was already doing social media I took
a business marketing class at my high school
because we were offered it, and I was bored
out of my mind.
- Well I think what's cool about social media now
is that you are the expert.
- Yeah.
- Someone in the generation above you
probably wouldn't do as good of a job teaching it
than you, because you're sort of shaping the field
as you work in it.
- Right.
I think that is what is so cool about the YouTube world
too, and I think that it is really cool
because I'll get emails from professors all the time
or from different colleges that will ask
like influencers that come in and speak,
and that's dope, me being a 19 year old kid
like gonna come in and teach a class on that.
That's like so cool, but it's really exciting for me,
and I love giving advice to smaller influencers
and other creators, and my friends about marketing
and how to do brand deals, and who to work with
and what to post on Instagram.
I don't know I just feel like I really have
a knack for it, which is why I think I would definitely
want to work in beauty consultation once I'm done
being a guru and stuff, I don't know I just
really like thinking and analyzing and seeing
what's next, and figuring out how to stay relevant,
which actually brings me to my last question for you.
As someone who's been around for so long on the internet
and has inspired people left and right, for the
younger sisters that have been out there watching
who may have been subscribed to you or me
who want to do YouTube one day, what is one piece of advice
you would give them in order to stay inspired
and also stay relevant for a while.
- Just do what you are excited about, you know?
Like for you that's makeup, and when we talk about
what you'd be doing or what I'd be doing,
the world would be like, we would miss you
if you were doing that, like you could do that
and you'd be really wonderful, but what makes a bigger deal
or difference is when you actually do what's in your heart.
- Right. - Like what you want to do.
- What you're passionate about.
- Yeah, like a world without James Charles
not doing makeup would just be really weird
and not my favorite world, I like having you here.
- Thanks, angel.
- Yeah, so when you actually do the stuff
that is interesting to you, it doesn't matter really
what platform you're doing it on,
or where you're doing it, as long as you have
a passion for it, you will find an audience for it
if you're coming from a place of genuine fun and interest
and having a good time.
- I always say that.
It's really obvious who's in it for the right reasons,
and who isn't, and at the end of the day
it's always the people who were doing it because
they really love it that stay around for a very, very
long time, which is why ...
- I just want to laugh.
- You're still here.
- I just want to laugh, so I've just been able to do that
and if I don't have a job anymore that's okay
because I'm probably just gonna keep laughing.
I look so beautiful, James!
- I think we're about to be done, sister
I'm gonna give you one last spritz,
and we'll show the final look.
(upbeat music)
Alright sisters, so this is the final look
on sister Jenna Marbles!
- I love it, James.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah. (squeals)
It's really sweet, thank you so much for doing this.
- Thank you so much for coming to my channel,
I feel like this has been in the works for such a long time
now and you've been such a huge role model to me
and so many other people as well,
and it was truly an honor to be able
to have glammed you up today
sister, I'm really glad you like the look.
- Thank you James, that's really nice of you.
And I have a lot to learn from you as well,
and it's been really nice to spend time with you.
- You're my favorite thing ever in the entire world.
Well I hope you sisters enjoyed spending time with us
today as well and learned a little bit more--
- I'm gonna end up ruining the makeup look
by being an emotional mess, I'm sorry!
- I really hope you guys enjoyed the video,
and if you did please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below, and come subscribe
if you have not already, we are literally 14 million
sisters strong, we'd love to have you join the family.
If you'd like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram or Twitter,
they're both just jamescharles, and my Snapchat
is more behind the scenes type stuff,
it's jamescharless with an extra S after Charles.
Also go subscribe to Jenna, she's absolutely incredible,
has been making videos for almost ten years now
but they have not gotten any worse.
(laughing)
That was a weird way to say that.
They have-- - Thanks James!
- They stayed good!
- Thanks.
- What, how do I say that?
- We all know what you mean, that's really nice of you
to say, thank you.
- They've been consistently good over the past ten years.
- Thanks James.
- And they're just getting better and better,
and crazier.
- Thank you.
- This video sister shoutout goes to sister Kelly
thank you so much love for always following
and supporting, I love you literally so, so, so much,
and if you'd like to be the next video's
sister shoutout, don't forget to always retweet
or leave us a like on Twitter, and also turn on
my YouTube post notifications.
Alright sisters, thank you so much for watching
this video today, I love you so much, and I will see you
in the next one!
Bye!
(upbeat music)