- [Crowd] Hi sisters!
- James Charles here and welcome back
to my YouTube channel.
As you guys can see I'm joined
with quite a few sister special guests, the Vlog Squad!
- [Crowd] Woo hoo!
- Oh my god you guys I am so beyond
excited for today's brand new video
because I feel like we've been trying to plan
this for a long period of time.
- I'm surprised you got all of us in here.
- I know.
- That's tough.
- And Jonah was almost on time.
(laughing)
- He was earlier than all of you
- I know I just wanted to make him look bad.
(laughing)
- So for today's video I have a very fun and fresh
make-up challenge planned that I just thought of a few
days ago and I was like wow,
I think this needs to happen.
And that is a new challenge that we're doing here called
make-up relay.
- [Crowd] Oh.
- Thank you so much for all the special infatuation .
(laughing)
- So basically you're all working together as a team
but you don't really get to actually work together
and you just have to hope that it all comes out good
in the end.
So like you're only as strong as your weakest link.
- Oof Jonah.
(laughing)
- Basically what we're going to do is we have nine of
the Vlog Squad members here,
we're gonna put everybody's names in a hat
and pick everybody at a random order,
and each person is going to have five minutes alone
with me.
- [Crowd] Aah.
(laughter)
- Jeff gets 10.
- Jeff gets as much time as he needs.
(laughter)
I'm gonna lay out all the make-up products that I have
in my everyday make-up routine,
and you all will have five minutes to do
as much as you can.
- Done
- Easy peasy baby.
- Let's do it.
- Five minutes that's nothing.
- Everybody will rotate in and out while I ask everybody
questions about being in the vlogs.
And that's about it.
(laughter)
And also just glamming me up, but hopefully
by the end of this we'll see if the Vlog Squad is able
to work together,
to put a beautiful make-up look on me.
- You're gonna look like a clown.
(laughter)
- I actually want you guys to try really really hard
to make it look good.
- Uh huh.
- How does everyone feel about their skill level
when it comes to make-up?
- I'm a solid seven and a half.
- I'm a three and a half.
- He's just really good at painting.
- Okay.
- I feel like out of the entire group I'm the worst at it.
- Really?
- Yeah, because Jeff does like beauty stuff.
- Did I tell you guys I'm the number one stylist
on Famous Birthdays?
- Holy shit.
- You're so famous.
- You said it like four times on the way over here.
- I think, I think, I think you'll be pretty good
because you always do your make-up for when we
film with you.
(laughter)
- You're just so pretty.
- Oh my god.
- We have numbers one through nine listed right here
in the original James Charles disgusting leather
baseball hat that I wore on my head for too long.
- Cool, I almost looked, I almost ruined it.
- We're all trying to pick at once.
- Okay who's going first?
- What's the best, one?
- One.
- Woo!
(screaming)
- Lucky bitch!
- Okay Heath is first.
Okay so we might be off to a good start then.
- That's pretty good.
- Yeah.
- You can play with the foundation Heath.
- Carly's two.
- I'm scared.
- Who's number three?
- I'm three sister, it's me.
- Wow, Zane you're the best, okay four?
- Me.
- Perfect.
(laughter)
- Five?
- Me.
- Okay Matt, six?
- Okay, so famous.
- Seven?
- Oh sorry, me!
(laughter)
I'm seven!
- Eight?
- Me.
I'm nervous.
- Am I nine?
(applause)
- Alone time, alone time.
- You get to spend the most time with him.
- So your make-up is perfectly done for our date after.
(laughter)
Without further ado are you guys all ready to race?
- [Crowd] Yes.
- Alright you guys so Heath is starting us off today.
- Oh my god.
- We have five minutes on the clock.
- Did you do a start yet dude?
- No, no.
- Okay, okay cool.
- Are you ready?
- No, let me just scan this real quick see what we
got to work with.
- I'm gonna give you a hand and say that the first
step is easy.
- Primer foundation we got this.
- Okay, okay.
- I've seen a couple tutorials maybe.
- Okay, okay ready?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- My guilty pleasure is like watching Instagram like
quick makeovers.
You know like the minute long - Yes!
- I don't know why, that and haircut videos I just I'll
just end up like - Wow, so this might be okay!
- Maybe this is my calling it's my first time.
- Okay, yeah you're gonna be so good at this.
Are you ready?
Five minutes on the clock.
- Okay.
- Ready, set, go!
- So today we
- Oh my god you're so professional
- Thank you.
- Oh wow.
- Oh shit!
I thought it was clean.
Lather this up.
- Yeh.
- That was a lot.
We'll just smooth it out, we'll smooth it out.
- Okay, okay I love it.
- Hang in there.
- I love a good smoothing out.
- Sorry I'm pushing really hard.
- It's okay, how do you think you're gonna do with
this make-up portion today?
Like, are you excited?
- I think I'm gonna do good,
I feel like I would really shine in the like
color popping, getting around the eyes you know?
- Okay.
- But, I mean you know this is the
key starting point right here.
- Ow!
- What?
- I think I just broke my toe.
I really think I just broke it.
- Oh a little dabble here and there.
- We don't wanna cake it on
- No.
- We want a nice simple clean look.
- Of course, of course.
- So right here we're just gonna go around the brows.
- Yeah.
- Just tying that in, we don't wanna get to far in there
but then kinda blot it,
you don't want it to smear.
- Right, Heath?
- Yeah.
- How long have you been in the Vlog Squad for?
- Literally since the beginning, I was in
David's first video.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So who was in the original, original?
Like who were the first ones.
- It was like me, Zane, Alex
- So you're an OG you've been there since day one?
- Mhm.
We used to Vine together and then all of a sudden he got
this camera and was like I'm gonna start making
YouTube videos and we were like oh wow.
He's like I don't know how long I'm gonna stick with it
but I'm gonna try it out.
- Yeah.
- And then he just did it.
What's great is that we're all actual friends.
- Yeah.
- And we would stay friends, even if we weren't doing
social media which is really cool.
- That's so good.
Even from being around you guys for a few minutes it's
very obvious that it's not just an act.
- Yeah, I love my friend group, they're the best.
- Go.
- Very nice.
- So you were telling me you watch all of those Instagram
videos?
- Yeah I just like scroll through like and not even on
purpose I don't look to find them but,
I'll just be going through and like one will pop up.
Then I'll get sucked into this world of like 30 minutes
and like, wait, what?
- The make-up videos on Instagram are stone-age.
- Yeah, I like seeing like a start and a finish.
(alarm)
(gasps)
Shit!
Speaking of finish.
- Oh that's so good, okay well Heath
your work here is done.
Thank you so much for your five minutes of time.
- Oh my god, thank you.
- Unfortunately we now have to move on to team member
number two and let's see where they start off.
- Thank you for having me.
- Thank you.
- I can't wait to see the finished product.
- See you in a little bit.
- Number two has arrived!
- Welcome sister!
- Hi
- What do we think so far?
- I don't know
- Okay.
- I think he did your foundation,
well he definitely did your foundation.
(laughter)
- Okay, so analyze your canvas, this is what we have
going on so far.
You're about to start in the relay race.
Carly, we're putting five minutes on the clock.
- Okay.
- Are you ready to go?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Me doing my make up every morning, five minutes.
- Would love to relate, okay ready?
3,2,1 go.
- Oh god bitch.
Okay, so he did your foundation I think I need to
do concealer after.
- Okay great.
- Is this true or are you not gonna tell me?
- I can't tell you.
- Oh, that's not concealer.
Where is it?
Oh, I've never seen something so beautiful in my life.
- Okay, love that.
- It is a Too Faced Born This Way we stan Lady GaGa,
I don't know if she made this, I would assume
- Yeah?
- I don't even know if I'm doing this right.
- So you and Erin are kinda like a duo?
- Yes.
- So like how long have you guys know each other for
and what brought you into the Vlog Squad.
- We've known each other for like five or
six years probably.
- Okay, cool.
- And we started on Vine.
- Okay, love that.
- So that's how we know everybody.
- So everybody in the Vlog Squad started on Vine?
- Most of us, like
I don't think Jeff,
I don't know if Jeff did,
I'm sure you wanna know all about Jeff.
- Yes I do.
- Sister snatched, like this probably doesn't look good
in real life but to me I'm killing it.
- All that matters is that it looks good on camera.
- I don't know I was really close with Zane,
like I'm so close with Zane, he's probably my
best friend out of,
like besides Erin.
Is this, am I doing this right?
- I can't tell you.
- But does it feel right?
- Yes.
- Like in your bones?
- And on your face?
- Yeah, my face feels amazing.
What would you describe the filming process of the vlogs
looking like?
What I've noticed is that even from being with you guys
quickly like everybody's very very quick on the spot.
- Yeah.
- But I also saw David redo a few takes which,
duh, happens all the time in production.
- Right.
- So like how would you say the filming process goes and
like how's being funny on camera?
- It's weird.
- I'm so bad at it.
- So like, it's weird because everyone vlogs so differently.
- Yeah.
- David is very like funny, quick and then.
- Super fast.
- Like honestly, most of the things happen actually happen
it's just that he didn't like catch it on time.
- Yeah.
- Or like someone's interrupting, so we do it again.
- And then if it looks scripted, that's probably why.
- Well yeah.
- I dunno, it's kinda stressful cos he's like
can you say that again?
And then everyone is looking at you and you're like,
I don't want to, I won't sound natural.
- Yeah, it's always awkward yeah.
- I think I need to bake you but I don't,
I've never baked.
- Okay.
- Well not in this way.
- You got one minute to figure it out.
- Um, okay.
Oh, this is probably it.
Laura Mercier come through girl.
(laughter)
- Come through girl.
- I watch a lot of your videos I always see this
happening so I'm just gonna do this and pretend
I'm on the same level.
- So you're already a sister?
- I'm such a sister.
- I always see you guys tweeting me and it's
always so cute.
- Oh my god I'm obsessed with you.
- Like this is like stressful for me,
like I'm nervous.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I'm just like a fan too.
So it's just like what am I doing right now?
- Aw, do you watch a lot of make up videos?
- I do, I think they're really soothing.
I like watching cos it's so interesting what people can
do, like it's literally an art form.
- Yeah.
- And so cool.
(alarm)
And I like how yours is like no!
Can I finish my sentence?
- Yeah please.
- I like how you're
very like, you don't need make up.
It's just like something to.
- It's funsies.
- Yeah.
- It's just art.
- Alright, well thank you for doing step number two,
but alas, your time is over.
So we have to move on to Vlog Squad number, number three
and continue this make-over.
So we'll see you in a little bit sister.
- Okay
I'll go get him.
- Okay.
(thumping)
- Come out, come out wherever you are.
- Zane, are you ready?
- Hi, hi sisters I'm here.
It's nice seeing you again.
- I know I've missed you a lot.
- Missed you too.
How've you been?
- I've been the best in the last two days
since I haven't seen you.
- Good.
If I do the eyebrows I'm safe because
you don't have to really do anything to
the eyebrows before you draw in the eyebrows right?
- Correct.
I can't tell you but that is correct.
(laughter)
- Yeah so ill start on the eyebrows.
- Okay ready?
5 minutes exactly on the clock.
- Okay
- 3, 2, 1
(screams)
- Okay, do you have that Anastasia Beverley Hills
brow wiz pencil?
- Yeah its right there.
- Oh my are you serious where is it?
- Right here.
- Oh you do have it, perfect.
(laughter)
- Oh my god, are you nervous?
You are shaking a little bit.
- A little bit, oh my god this does wonders huh?
- Are you just choking me a little bit?
(laughter)
- Stand still, stand still.
- So after we did our collab did you feel a little bit
more prepared for this makeover today?
Where you paying attention at all?
Well I can't really pay attention to my own face really.
- Okay.
- Because when I was editing the video I didn't know
what you where doing so like it was just I was looking
for the funny moments
- Right.
- Or like the very genuine moments no really what
you was doing to my face.
- Okay
- That really didn't.
- So no you are not prepared.
- No I'm not prepared at all.
I don't want to touch your face but
I need to touch your face.
- Go for it , go for it.
- Okay.
- I don't want to touch your face, I don't
want to fuck it up.
- Why don't you just put your hand around my regular neck?
So we have been bonding recently because I am in love
with Jeff I think.
- Yeah
- If you think there's the possibility of me hooking up
with one of the Vlog Squad members who would you say
it would be and why?
- Hmm.
- I don't know about Jeff, I wouldn't put Jeff on the
top of the list.
(gasps)
but, I know somebody else.
- Who?
- Want to make a guess?
- Dirty Dom?
- Yep
(laughter)
- No you know though when I went to your birthday party
which we talked about it your video?
- Yeah.
- Dom tried to make out with me.
- He, are you serious?
- Yeah.
- That's really funny but did you, did you let him?
- No!
- Why not?
- Its disgusting.
- I know that's disgusting.
(laughter)
You have standards.
- I have standards.
You know James, you know what this is starting
to look like how you used to do your eyebrows
like three years ago.
- Zane!
- Not now.
- Don't do that to me.
- I know but I have to, I have to.
- What was your first impression meeting me?
- I thought you where actually going to be kind
of like stand offish.
- Really?
and a little like Zane are you ready?
wow you didn't come prepared, I can't believe you didn't
come prepared, kind of very just like not mean but kind of
very very businessy and like alright come on Zane
I can't I don't have time for this.
- That did not happen though.
- No I thought you where going to be like that.
That is what I was saying. It though you where going to
be like that.
- Oh
- But you ended up being the complete opposite and
I felt really comfortable when I was in here and
I was really happy you are very nice.
- Oh you are.
- I remember on the way home I was telling Natalie
dude I can't believe he was that nice, I thought he was
going to be the complete opposite.
- Really?
- Yeah just like seeing how much you cared about what
was on my video, I don't know you just like cared
about what I had to film,
- Well yeah it was so fun. - Which was really cool.
- Speaking of being nice you and David have a lot
of guests in the Vlog Squad videos.
- Yeah
- Who has been your favorite guest or celebrity that
has made an appearance.
- That I have met,
(alarm)
Oh in Davids videos.
Ah in Davids videos was Howie Mandel he's so sweet
- Really
- He's really cool yeah.
- Okay
- We actually went to his Superbowl party, we went to his
Superbowl party.
- Love that
- Last week and he was like so nice to us.
It was awesome.
- Great
- Yeah. - Okay
- Really cool - Love that
- Yeah, Is that it damn that went by really quick.
- So fast
- I though 5 minutes was going to be like a long time
- Dammit - No, Did you do good?
- Well I'm kinda happy with it how do you think the
- They're not that bad
- Oh come on it wasn't that bad
- Well regardless I think they are off to a great start
and who knows maybe Vlog Squad member number 4 will
adjust them or move on to the next makeup step.
- Oh my god let's hope they, because that Jonah
- Oh god!
- Alright well
- Thank you
- Love you James
- Love you the most see you in a little bit
- See you soon bye sisters
- Where is he, hello
- Hi I'm here for the appointment
- Uh oh.
- I'm number four.
- Yeah.
Hi Jonah.
- Hey, what's going on?
- So let's start by analyzing the face.
- Uh huh.
- And see what's done, and what you wanna what's next.
- There's a lot of powder on your face.
- Okay.
- It looks good to me.
- I've got a feeling I gotta make it look better.
(laughter)
- This is so true.
- Okay.
- I remember when everybody said you were gonna be the
weakest link in the intro you can't listen.
- Did they say that?
- You where right there.
- Who said that?
- Everybody.
- What do ya mean?
(laughter)
- Did you miss that?
- Did they actually say that about me?
- Yeah.
So like, you're only as strong as your weakest link.
- Jonah.
(laughter)
- Just, just run your clock and I'll tell you what
I'm gonna do.
- Okay, ready?
- Yeah.
- Jonah, you've got five minutes on the clock.
- Oh Jesus, don't hate me, don't say it like that.
- Ready?
- Yeah, ready.
- 3,2,1 go.
Okay I have to tell you something funny okay?
- Okay.
- When I first saw you in David's vlogs,
I never watched any comedy ever.
So I really thought you were Jonah Hill for a second.
- No.
- I was like oh my god, David has Jonah Hill in his video.
- You actually thought that?
- Yeah, swear to god.
(laughter)
And then I realized, not Jonah Hill.
- He's a cool guy, Jonah's a cool guy.
Never met him but he's cool.
- Okay.
You know what else is cool?
Only having four minutes left.
Four minutes left.
- Are you serious?
You started the clock!
- I told you
- No, you're cheating.
You were literally just in conversation with me.
- You were supposed to be going!
- James, I have 4:21 now, come on.
Do we use water?
- No!
- Is this perfume?
- No.
- What is this stuff?
Your face just melts?
(laughter)
It says.
- Go, go do something.
- You know what bro, I honestly do think you wasted
my time.
And you asked me questions.
And you really tricked me into this.
- I told you I was gonna ask everybody questions.
So what would you say was the worst thing you've
had to do for the videos?
- Jumping the moped over the pool.
- That's dangerous.
Good, good, good choice.
Why do you think.
- Is it?
- Yes.
Why do you think you're so down to be
to do crazy things for the videos.
- I don't know dude,
it's just like to the camera,
my blood just boils and I just wanna get really really
good content.
- Okay.
- It just happens,
this is for the eyes?
- Uh huh.
- It feels like it is, cos there's like a little brush
on there.
Is it?
- Yeah.
- You just didn't wanna say?
- I'm scared.
Okay, from what I've noticed from a lot of the videos,
is that, out of all the people I feel David tends to
surprise you the most with pranks and bets.
Do you live your life in constant fear?
- Absolutely.
(laughter)
I feel like this is a prank right here dude.
- What do you think is gonna happen next?
- I'm not sure.
- Oh my god the audition prank was,
broke my heart.
- Yeah, that shit prank broke me as a human.
- So you actually do do acting right?
- Yeah I'm an actor.
- Really?
- I do comedy act, I mean yeah,
it's what I'm trying to be I guess.
- Okay.
- A comedy actor.
- But no, the um.
(alarm)
No, are you serious?
I was almost done.
(laughter)
Stop, give me the make up!
(clapping)
- Oh my gosh, who.
Oh no.
- That's not good to hear.
- I don't know I'm really a bit concerned about
they eyes, I don't know.
I'm guessing Jonah did the eyes before this.
- You'd be guessing correctly.
- Oh no.
They're terrible, I feel so bad for you.
Okay, I'm nervous, but I think I know what I'm doing.
I like to convince myself I know a lot about make-up.
- Okay, so what, where you paying attention during
me and Zane's video?
- Yeah a little bit.
- Okay, professional MUA.
- So, I'm looking at you now,
I don't think you've done bronzing or contouring,
or even highlighting.
But, I think we have to start with bronzing first, right?
Right?
- I can't tell you.
- I think what, I think bronzing is when you focus
on the areas where the sunlight hits your face.
Or like where you?
Am I right?
- You're a professional make-up artist Matt!
So you have five minutes on the clock.
- Okay.
- Ready to get started and get as much of my glam done
as you can possibly can?
- Alright.
- Are you ready?
- Yes, yes.
- Are you sure?
- Yes James I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
- 3,2,1 go.
- Okay, I'll open up this palette and,
okay, well it seems like you use this one a lot though,
so actually I'm gonna go with this one.
- Okay cool.
- Alright.
- How long have you been in the Vlog Squad for?
- I don't know, like two years?
- Are you shaking?
- Yes, I'm shaking!
I don't wanna mess up, I don't wanna make this any worse
than what it already is.
- Okay, okay two years now?
- Yes, two years.
- And how would you say it's changed your life?
- It's changed my life,
in many ways.
I'm so happy that I'm surrounded by friends,
who have such a great sense of humor and like love
and support each other.
It's honestly like one big family.
- Yeah.
- And I can't complain.
- Well speaking of something good like what's your
favorite part about the blogs, cos I noticed
David likes, you guys definitely like to do lots of
positive things too.
- Yes.
- Lots of free cars, lots of makeovers, fun things.
- Yeah, I think.
I guess my favorite thing is just having everybody laugh.
I don't know.
- Yeah.
- All the laughter and stuff, it's just non stop and
a lot of people say, oh no this is all fake it's just
all about the laughter.
No this was a genuine quick comedic.
- Quick quip.
- Yeah.
Everybody is, I mean it's like straight up like improv
and I love that the Vlog Squad keep you on your toes
and stuff.
- Yeah.
There's so much footage in one video.
It's always entertaining to watch.
- I feel like I'm wanting to do bronze but I'm like
contouring you with bronzer.
- It's okay.
- So don't hate me, don't hate me.
- I love you.
- I like that face, I keep thinking you're trying
to kiss me right now,
but you're just.
- That's number nine.
- Maybe like a little bit of your chin.
It's important to also contour your jawline right?
To hide double chins.
- Definitely.
- We need to teach Zane that.
(laughs)
I've done like okay on this side,
this side is looking pretty rough.
- Okay you have six seconds to fix it.
- It's not balanced, It's not balanced out.
- You have six seconds to fix it.
- Okay, okay, okay.
(alarm)
There we go.
- Are you, ok
(laughs)
Time.
- You know what I'm proud, you know?
Dare to fail.
- Right.
- Thank you James.
- Thank you so much Matt.
- Thank you.
- Okay bye, will you grab the next one?
- Yes.
Number six.
- Clean up crew is here.
- We need it.
- I liked you better without the make-up.
(laughs)
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, analyze your face.
- Oh, it's kind of a mess.
I didn't realize it was gonna be this bad.
Who screwed this up this bad?
- A lot of people.
- Okay.
- We started pretty strong.
- This is why I didn't wanna go after Jonah.
Yeah, I have a lot to do, well.
I'm glad I'm here.
- Me too, thank you so much for joining us here today David.
- I see the foundation is set.
- Yeah.
- A little bit of eyeliner.
I don't even know anything about make-up but I know
this is completely wrong.
(laughter)
Is there an eraser?
Where I can just erase it all.
We do have make-up wipes if you want something.
- Okay, I'm going to
- You're gonna have five minutes on the clock.
Do you know what you wanna do next?
- Yeah, yeah.
I wanna put something under your eyes.
- Okay.
- Because there's a lot going on,
and I kinda wanna balance it out.
Cos right now I don't know where to look but I wanna
just be looking in your eyes.
- Okay.
Well David Dobrik, you're about to have five minutes
on the clock for this make-up relay.
- I only need two.
- Great, are you ready to go?
- Yeah okay.
- Your time starts now.
- This is what I need.
- Oh the James Charles X Morphe iconic palette.
- I use this at home actually.
- For what?
- For everything, every morning.
I'm glad you have it here because.
- Okay, great.
- Oh wow, yeah.
- David, what made you wanna start the Vlog Squad
and do daily vlogs with everybody?
- I mean.
- Well almost daily.
- I didn't go in thinking starting we're gonna make
a Vlog Squad.
- Really?
- This is so funny, I'm about to screw this up even more.
- No don't, make it look good.
- Cos we were all doing Vine together.
- Yeah.
- So then we kinds just started YouTube just naturally.
- Yes.
- Liza actually got me into vlogging,
because she had a vlog camera so I like wanted to
give it a shot.
When I started vlogging, like,
it wasn't really forced.
Like I didn't feel like I had to do YouTube,
to like survive.
So like, we were just literally just having fun
and filming everything, so it was great.
- Then it just turned you into a big squad that films
all the time.
- Yes, 100%.
- Speaking of, what does your normal filming schedule
look like and also how long does it take you to
edit your videos?
This is interesting to me, because you seem to film
a lot.
- Sure, sure.
Yeah, so I have three, three and half hours of footage
every vlog.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna go up top a little bit.
- Okay.
(laughter)
- I love going up top a little bit.
- It's also so crazy having a serious conversation
with you while I'm literally going
(shrieking)
Yeah, so about three to three and a half hours of footage
of vlog, then it takes me like 12 hours to edit.
Maybe 14?
This is so intimate.
- Yes.
- Like doing somebody's make-up is like,
I feel like I'm on date with you.
- Oh hey, I love that.
- It feels like we're having sex.
- Oh.
I don't know about all that.
Suddenly your time is up.
- What was I saying before it got so hot in here.
You looked like you just got socked in the face.
- David.
- I screwed it up, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Let me fix it real quick, how much time do I have?
- Keep going, don't worry about it, just keep going
you have about two minutes left.
- I just need to blend it in that's honestly,
all I need to do.
- Okay, okay.
So it seems like when you're filming skits you tend to
just record everything and take the best footage, right?
- 100%
- So how do you even plan all the stuff out in the videos?
Like what does the creative process look like, that's
what I wanna know because as a beauty guru it's hard.
- Sure, sure.
- To come up with new ideas all the time, but I feel
like you all do the craziest things every single
time it's a new vlog.
- Yeah, no there is no creative process.
We literally have no ideas going into every video.
- Okay.
- It's kinda just like you record whatever and then
you turn your days into a trailer.
- Yeah.
- So you just put the best moments in.
- Okay.
That's such a fun way to look at it actually.
- It's like, it's like.
I always say if you edit the movie Titanic down to
three minutes you can turn it into a comedy movie
and that's like what my life is.
It's not necessarily, we're not like funnier than any other
- A sinking ship, but you can make it funny
- friend group.
- Exactly.
We're not like funnier than any other group, but , I
We just know how to put a funny video together.
Sometimes, and sometimes they suck.
- Cool I love that.
- Honestly, I think this is better, do you know why?
- Why?
- Cos when I walked in it looked like you messed up
your make-up on accident.
- Yeah.
- But now it looks like you messed up your make-up
on purpose.
(laughter)
- I have a very quick question for you by the way.
- Yeah.
- How's the Adsense?
- Brutal.
- I mean brutal.
- I love how the first time I met you by the way
at Zane's birthday party you asked me what does your
Adsense look like?
- Dude, because.
- And then you saw it.
- Yeah, I saw your Adsense.
- I wanna see yours!
- I went home and started crying.
I'm gonna show you right now.
James Charles reacts to how much money I make.
(alarm)
- Oh god. Perfect way to end your segment.
- Here you go.
(gasps)
Yeh, it's not good.
- Why is it that low?
- I don't know, can I have a job?
(laughter)
- We are Sisters sister LLC
- Guys, go buy the merch.
Maybe James will give me a percentage of the proceeds.
- Definitely not.
Well hopefully the person after you will come and
kill it too.
- I hope so too.
- David, thank you so much for taking part in this process
today.
- Thank you for having me.
- All jokes aside, I really enjoy your videos and you're
one of my favorite creators to watch on this platform.
- Thanks.
- And thank you for creating such entertaining four minute
and twenty second content, three times a week.
- That's really sweet, thank you.
- Yeah, I'm being serious.
- See, now I woulda done a better job if I knew you
were gonna gas me up like this at the end.
(laughter)
- Okay, I'm gonna bring in the next person.
- Okay great.
- Thank you James.
- I love when your first sentence is oh no,
this is bad.
- It's really bad.
I don't even know how to fix it.
- Everybody please welcome Corinna.
- Hello.
- Are you ready for this glam today?
- I don't know where to go.
- Okay.
- I feel like I should try and fix the,
who did the eyeshadow?
Okay.
- There's a lot going on here.
- Can I take make-up off?
- Yeah, we have make-up wipes if you really want to.
- Wait, really?
- Yeah, I mean yeah.
You're actually gonna, okay ready?
- I don't know I feel like this is whatever.
You look like you have pink eye.
- Okay.
- Right?
I mean.
- Well I feel if anybody is gonna be able to make
this look OK it's you.
- Well my biggest thing was I felt like I could do
everything except for eyeshadow.
- Okay.
- But now I'm coming in here feeling like I have to help
the eyeshadow but I don't do eyeshadow.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna wing it.
- You're gonna have, okay great.
Just like Jonah did.
- Oh so he did?
He's the weakest link!
He's literally horrible.
- Okay, Corrina you're gonna have five minutes
on the clock get as much done as you possibly can.
Are you ready for this make-up relay race?
- No.
This is bad, I'm sorry.
- Three.
- You look the worst.
- Go sister.
- Okay, I'm hoping this doesn't stain.
(laughter)
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
- I have a real question for you.
- Okay.
- So, one of the kind of running jokes in the Vlog Squad
is that you hook up with boys.
- Okay.
- How many of the Vlog Squad members have you hooked
up with?
- But like hooked up as in?
- At least like made out.
- Okay so, one, two,
three, four.
Four, I think?
It could be more.
- Okay.
- I'm trying to think.
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- I'm looking at you and like this is the worst.
There's like, someone that I'd ship you with.
- Okay, who, who?
- I'd ship you with Jeff so hard.
- Okay.
- But I don't know,
wait, can I use this beauty blender?
- Yeah.
- I feel like I made this look even worse.
- Oh god, okay.
- Oh no.
- Okay, question two because obviously people do make
the jokes about you hooking up guys a lot too and
obviously I just made a joke, but
I don't know if anybody even remembers but we used to be
really, really close friends and we hung out for a long
period of time. - We did!
- Obviously me and your friends make those type of jokes
all the time, but is there a limit to what type of jokes
you let people make in the vlogs?
Like, is there even a limit?
- I don't really care that much because like I know
who I am and I know that,
they're not true.
They were probably true at one point.
(laughter)
I'm not gonna say there's also stuff like he's been like
please let me put it in, and then like paid me
to put it in.
What's the most amount of money David has paid you to
put something in the vlog?
You have to tell me that.
- I don't remember, probably like a thousand
or two thousand dollars.
This was like, this was like when I needed money and
I wasn't making money.
- Okay, no I love that though.
- Now I'm not.
- You gotta do what you gotta do.
- Now I'm gonna unleash my inner artist.
- Okay, please do.
- I actually bought this palette.
You know that right?
- Did you?
- Yeah.
- Did you use code James for 10% off your purchase?
- That's a thing?
- Yeah.
- Oh no.
- Wow.
- I'm so fake.
- That was good timing, I can't believe you were that fake.
- Yeah, I'm kinda fake.
- This collab needs to be over right now.
- I'm sorry, wait I didn't know that!
Well, I mean I just gave you extra money.
- Yeah, thanks girl.
- I did not even contribute other than like fixing
other people's mistakes.
- You always contribute.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- At least I took the bottom off.
- Hey, it's a team effort at the end.
- Yeah.
- The end product is all that matters it's not
what's in between so you gotta hope that it looks good.
- I'm praying that Erin can pull this together,
cos Erin's next.
- Erin's next?
- Yeah.
- Well thank you Corinna for taking part in this
make-up relay. - Thanks for having me.
- Love you the most sister.
- Thanks good luck, I'm so sorry about your face.
- I'll see you in a little bit for the reveal.
- I'll use code James for 10% off.
- That's right you probably should.
Hello.
Come in.
Hey sister.
- Oh my gosh.
- Hey girl.
- Who did this to your face?
- Great question.
- Oh no.
- What do we think so far?
- It could be worse, you've looked better.
- Okay, welcome to the make-up relay race.
- I'm so excited to be here.
It looks like a two year old took a crayon and
colored your eyes.
- That'll be David.
- Your eyebrows are definitely done and you have
all that other stuff on your face and your lip.
- Okay, you're gonna have five minutes on the clock.
- Okay.
- Do you know what you're wanna gonna do?
- I guess I'm trying to fix your lips.
- Okay, cool.
- Maybe.
Fix you're eyes a little bit?
I don't know if I can.
- Okay.
- And then maybe some more highlight.
- To really pop, I love highlight.
- Okay great.
- That's like all I wear.
- Love, love, love.
- Look at your eyes, who did that Jonah?
- David.
Ready?
Oh, I love how we're also wearing our trendy hoodies.
- Yay.
- Available now at sisters dash apparel dot com.
Okay, ready?
3,2,1 go.
- Close your eyes.
- Okay, my eyes are closed.
Well speaking of sister Erin,
I have a good question for you.
- Sure.
- How was the Superbowl a few weeks ago?
- Oh my god it was so fun.
It was the best.
David just like,
I'm gonna like cry, no.
But it's just so crazy like,
it's not that I don't feel deserving of it
but it's just like why?
And I know that I even said it to him like I
wrote him a thank you note like,
I know that for you it's just content but like,
that's life changing stuff like,
I would never go to the Superbowl if that weren't for him.
- Yeah.
- It's really crazy.
- That's so cool like, you guys are always doing like
awesome stuff like that.
- Yeah.
- What has been the best gift that's ever been given
for a video?
- Ever?
- Yeah.
In your opinion.
- Well David's given me three.
So I may be a little bias.
- Okay, love that.
- He got me a car.
- Oh.
- Which was great for me.
I don't know, I always cry at all of them,
for anybody no matter what it is.
- Okay.
- I just love surprises in general, like for other
people and like coming home videos.
They all just make me sob.
- Yeah.
- So, especially seeing someone like David who's
like so crazy and wild,
just be generous is so nice.
- Yeah.
- Little ambidextrous action.
- Are you really ambidextrous?
- No.
(laughter)
I just didn't feel like using my other hand.
- Okay so what was your first impression of me?
- Today?
- Well, I guess.
- Or in general?
- Cos I always see you and Carly tweeting me.
- Oh my god we love you.
We love cos.
(alarm)
- That was so fast.
- Guess I gotta go.
Carly and I like,
we don't like know much about make-up at all.
Like we use drug store make-up.
- Yeah.
- We think it's so interesting like,
the craft that you have, we're like oh my god.
I'm like this is beautiful, Liza had it at her
Christmas party and I was like, I don't know
what any of this does, but I want it.
- The, the shadow palette?
- Yeah, it's so pretty.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, of course.
- You guys are the sweetest.
Well sister, our time is up we're already..
- I hope Jeff saves you.
- Oh, I hope Jeff does lots of things to me.
- Me too.
- You ready for me?
- I was born ready for this, hi Jeff.
- Well, well, you look great.
- Do I?
- You look like a Victoria Secret angel.
- Wow.
You're the best.
- Oh stop it, I'm blushing now.
Can I get some make-up before we start or are
we not doing it like that?
- Do you want some make-up before we start?
- I got a pimple right here and its, I'm gonna
be staring at the screen the whole time.
- You have the one pimple?
- Yeah, can you get that for me please?
- Yeah, of course.
- Can you do it with one of those spongey things?
I love them I just wanna squeeze them.
- Okay.
- Can I squeeze it.
- You can squeeze whatever you want.
- Oh my god, it's gone.
- You probably need some areas so I can do that every day.
How tall are you?
- I'm like six one,
six two maybe?
- Okay cool.
- How should I fix this?
I have no idea what I'm doing.
- Yeah, so you're last,
so getting ready for our date.
- I'm here to clean up this mess.
- You're going to clean everything up.
- Okay, so all I know is that they finish you with
a little spray.
- Okay.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
You're gonna have a good five minutes on the clock.
- Okay.
- So make any changes that you like, to really
pull the look together.
- Okay.
- And to add that signature Jeff touch.
- And then you'll, we'll do the final reveal.
- This is the mic that you guys use?
You don't have like lab mics on?
Are you wearing a lab mic under you?
- Do you wanna check?
- No?
- Can I check under you?
- Yeah, you can check under there.
I got nothing.
Okay, okay.
(laughter)
This is one of those videos huh?
Alright, alright.
- You ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Okay, ready? 3,2,1 go.
- Aren't you gonna coach me through it.
- No, you have to do whatever your heart desires.
- Where's the spray?
Let's do a little bit of this.
- Okay.
- I've always wanted to do this,
a little bit blending.
- Yeah, I love a good...
- This is a blender ball?
- Yes, please.
So Jeff, you're pretty much the newest member of
the Vlog Squad.
- I guess, kinda like, I didn't sign any contracts
or anything.
- Do you like it so far?
Tell me the vibe, what do you feel?
- Yeah, they're great.
They're all great guys.
You got a little crew yourself here.
- I do.
- They're all beautiful by the way.
I was looking at that picture of you guys outside.
- The family photo.
- What a better looking crew than we have.
We gotta pretty good squad.
- We should probably marry and retake the photo.
- Can I be in that photo?
- 100%
- Oh my god,
I'm telling David I'm done right now.
- Great!
- I'm going downstairs and saying David we're finished.
Do you shoot people with paintball guns?
- No.
- That's great.
- So Jeff, you're from Staten Island right?
Did you know that I grew up in New York too?
- Did you?
Where?
- Upstate.
- Really?
- Right outside of Albany but I went to visit the city
all the time.
- What nationality are you?
- Caucasian.
- Yeah, very.
- You look so exotic.
- Okay, thanks.
Is that a good thing?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- You got the face of like, a supermodel.
And the body of like a triathlete.
- Oh okay.
- You do some swimming,
and some running.
And a little bit of weights, just a little bit
just to keep a little bit of muscle.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Is that good do you like that?
- Yeah I love that.
When you were living in New York where you working
there as a barber too?
- I was a barber there up until 18,
then I moved to South Beach, Miami.
I lived there for two years, I don't remember
any of it but I..
- You know what I remember when you was living in Miami?
That you were a member of the Bad Girls' Club.
- No, no, no.
Come on, whatever.
Alright, I made some stupid choices to do TV shows
and I'm not exactly proud of.
Let's put this spray on there.
- Yeah.
So now you've moved to LA and do you have your own
barbershop or do you work in one?
- Let me get a little closer here.
- Oh please do.
- I have a barbershop in my house, that you're
gonna come to right?
- Oh definitely.
- Yeah, do you trust me to cut your hair?
- I don't know.
- It's not like make-up you can't just was it off.
- That's true.
I'd trust you with anything at this point.
- Anything huh?
- Yeah
- Do you wanna just, do you have any like oils?
Maybe we could do like a full body massage here.
- No but we can definitely find one.
- Okay, we'll save that for the end.
- Okay, great.
- After the video ends when we cut.
So we'll put this on and then that's it right?
- Yeah.
- The make-ups done.
- I guess so.
- You look like you're going out to the Grammy's.
Are you going to the Grammy's?
- No.
- You would be doing something its,
like a crazy event after you've filmed this video.
- I, with this make-up on?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna be my plus one, my date on the red carpet?
- I would love to.
- Wow, that's really cute.
- I've never been to the Grammy's.
- Me either.
Who's your favorite person that you've gotten to
cut so far?
- Oh that smells nice, can I have some too?
- Sure.
- Oh wow, that's so refreshing.
- Yeah.
- So my favorite person I've got to cut so far
that's a good question.
I actually gave a homeless guy a haircut and it
was awesome to see how happy he was after.
- Aw.
- But also you know, I'll drop a few names since
I'm here.
I did give Amber Rose her shaved head.
- You did?
- Yeah, she's so sweet, she's the nicest person.
- Yeah.
- Then next up there's you, that's all I care about.
After that I'm retiring.
I'm giving my clippers away,
that's it I'm wrapping up the show.
- Okay, I love that.
(alarm)
- Yeah, that's it, we're done.
You look great.
- Thanks Jeff.
- I hope I didn't mess up too much.
- That's okay, you could have done anything
and I would have been happy with it.
- Are we done?
So can we cut and do the massage?
- We can cut and do whatever your heart desires.
- Yeah, what do you say we get out of here and we
can talk about that massage a little more?
- We can get out of here and talk about
whatever you want.
- Let's go, hop up here.
- I'm so ready for this!
- You must weigh about 80 pounds.
- Wow Jeff we're going to get married.
- Okay are you guys ready to see?
- [Crowd] Yes.
- That you all did as a group?
- 3, 2, 1
- [Crowd] Oh!
- You look so different!
- It's okay.
- It's definitely not that bad at all.
- It looks like you got,
it looks like you got bad lip injections.
- You look like you're 20 years older.
- I'm just, it's weird seeing what it went to after me.
- That eyeshadow looks a lot better than when I saw.
- Okay.
- Can I say, can I say something?
After I did the coloring to your eyes,
a lot of people came down and was like,
someone really fucked it up!
(laughter)
I guess it was me?
But now what they did with it, it looks really good.
- Oh yes, professional.
- It's like lighter, I love it.
Who did the worst?
- Do you actually want me to tell you?
- Yeah.
Don't get offended.
Who was the weakest link?
- [Crowd] Jonah!
(laughter)
- Who was the best?
- James is like the best kisser, that's Jeff.
- Is that why the lipstick's messy?
- Okay, so I was really impressed with Heath, Zane and Matt
all knew what exactly what to do.
(cheers)
They all knew exactly what they needed to do,
like Heath was I'm gonna do primer, then foundation
- Looks like there's a new Sister Squad.
- I was actually really thoroughly impressed,
I mean obviously Zane and Matt had a little bit
of an advantage because we had just filmed a video,
but it meant a lot that you were paying attention.
Well regardless you guys, thanks so much for coming
on my channel today.
Thank you guys.
- James, you're welcome.
(laughter)
- I told David in all seriousness, you guys do have
some of the best content on all of YouTube and it's
always a pleasure watching all four minutes and 20
seconds of your guys's videos.
- Congrats on this.
- Yeah.
- This is nuts!
We're sitting in your office, just going through
your stuff like..
(laughter)
- That's good, thanks guys you guys were all the
absolute best.
Well if you sisters enjoyed this video today please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up down below,
leave us a comment on how you think the Vlog Squad did.
Who did the best?
Who did the worst?
I'm sure they're definitely wanna gonna know.
And if you've not already, don't forget to click
that big red subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we're 14 million sisters strong.
Also hit that bell icon so you can get a notification
for every time that I upload a brand new video.
If you'd like to follow me on my make-up journey
you can follow me at Instagram or Twitter they're
both just James Charles and my Snapchat for
more behind the scenes stuff is James Charles with an extra
s after Charles.
- Tea.
- Everybody's channels will be linked down below if you
want to check anybody out and also don't forget to check
out everybody over on David's channel.
- Please subscribe to me.
- David doesn't need the push.
- He definitely does since I passed him.
This video's sister shout out goes to sister Carrie Grace.
Thank you so much for always following and supporting.
And if you at home want to be included in the next sister
shout out, don't forget to always retweet the
video links when they go live on Twitter and
also turn on YouTube post notifications.
If you guys like all of our hoodies that me and my new
Vlog Squad friends are all wearing, don't forget to
shop now at sisters dash apparel dot com.
- They feel incredible.
- Oh, I love that.
- Wow.
- Let's get outta here.
(cheers)
- Alright sisters, thank you so much for watching this video
today, I love you and we'll see you in the next one.
Bye.
(Chilled music)