Hello sisters and welcome to Messy
Makeup
Trivia
the game show where no matter who wins
we all lose
lets meet today's special guests
our first contestant left his eyebrow in 2018
and apparently all of his friends too
please welcome JefreeStar
our next guest is back and better than ever
with a slightly better foundation shade
we'll get there one day
please welcome James Charles
our last guest has been around forever but somehow has not had a scandle
so we've got
literally nothing
joining us in the studio after filming her 87th video this week alone,
Tati Westbrook
Hi Sisters
James Charles here and welcome back to my YouTube channel
As you guys guys can see i am joined with two very very special guests.
Sister Jefffree Star and sister Tati Westbrook
Jeffree:How are ya
James:You guys for todays video i am so beyond excited.