hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see right now i have no
makeup on and that is because
today's video is actually going to be
quite a little bit different but i'm
honestly excited to try something new
out with you guys and i really hope that
you enjoy it i don't know if any of you
have seen it but gq does a really cool
series on their youtube channel with
different celebrities called 10 things
that blank cannot live without and so
many my favorite people have done it
such as magnum stallion and nick jonas
phineas shawn mendes has done it pretty
much like literally everybody and
basically the series name could honestly
not be any more self-explanatory
guests just go on and literally showcase
10 different items that they cannot live
without but a lot of people that have
done the show's list have contained like
kind of more obvious things like their
phone family members their dog or their
favorite snacks and obviously those are
all items that i could not live without
either i wanted to make it a little bit
more fun and i wanted to show you guys
10 different things that i have found
while online shopping that i didn't know
that i needed
that now i cannot live without hope so
without further ado
let's get started
okay you guys so i have so many products
i found me today that i'm so excited to
show you some of them are really weird
some of them are really really cool and
because i'm a beauty guru i really
wanted to focus on non-makeup related
items for today's video to keep it
interesting
but i did want to start off this list
with only one thing that i really
recommend you guys
try and that is the mario badescu
drawing lotion now this isn't a makeup
product it's more of a skincare type of
situation if any of you guys suffer with
acne out there
this has literally become like my
favorite product in the entire world
obviously i'm not a skincare expert i am
not haram you definitely should check
him out if you guys need any skincare
advice and just because this works for
me does not mean that it'll work for you
but i just wanted to show it anyway for
anybody out there who may suffer with
acne just like i do as you guys can see
i have
quite a large breakout going on right
now on my chin and on my forehead as
well this stuff works really really well
to dry out and minimize the appearance
of
pimples overnight so basically all i do
is just grab a little q-tip like this
dip it into the bottle and then i'll
just put a dollop of the product
right over top of any breakouts usually
i put on however many dots i need let
them dry down
then go to sleep and wipe them off in
the morning when i wake up and it
definitely does help reduce the redness
and the size of the pimples it usually
does not get rid of them from me i
should clarify that as well
but this really really does help and i
would definitely recommend any of you
guys out there oh this is also probably
a good time to mention too none of the
items in this video today are sponsored
i'm not being paid to promote any of
this stuff in any way
shape or form and i truly do love them
and just wanted to share this for a fun
little video today however there are
links in the description box down below
if you guys want to get any of these
things and they
are affiliate links so i just wanted to
be transparent with you guys the next
item that i want to show you guys
also relates to a drawing and it is this
right here which is a
portable battery operated fan you
literally just click the button
and then it has three different speeds
and like uh
speeds and strengths would you call it
intensity sure it has three different
speeds and intensities if you will and
this third speed
let me tell you is actually producing
quite a lot of air this is actually one
of my newer additions to my things that
i cannot live without list but oh my god
i cannot believe that i didn't actually
buy this sooner this is
literally everything i always have it
next to me on my filming desk one
because it gets very hot in here but
also it helps
so much when it comes to drying setting
spray or if you have lashes then you
need to dry your lash glue just pop your
fan on literally this has come in
so so so handy also you can travel with
it too so when it's a million degrees
here in california because it has been a
heat wave recently you know that this is
in
my purse okay so speaking of things that
i'm carrying inside of my purse the next
item that i want to show you guys
is arguably the thing that i use most on
this entire list and that is this baby
right here which literally looks like a
brick
but it is my anchor power or
anchor portable charger it comes in a
box just like this and i think that this
one is the 26
800 milli amps megawatts some sort of
electricity power measurement i have
literally no idea what it is i will
clarify for you guys these are
very very expensive but you don't
necessarily have to get one this strong
they do have several other versions as
well that are much more affordable this
has literally been like one of the best
investments that i have ever made i
carry this with me
literally every single place that i go
because this keeps my phone alive
like literally forever this holds like
70 million charges in this and is
actually insane
70 million charges yeah sure basically
you just leave this plugged in overnight
so it can get fully charged up and then
there are three
usb slots right here that you can plug
your phone charger into so you can
charge your own phone
and two other devices at the same time
which is so lit
these have saved my life so so many
times now to go along with your portable
charger the next
that i want to show you guys is one that
most of us probably already have but
not this version and that is a 10 foot
power cable now you probably already
know this and a lot smarter than me but
there was a point in time where i
unfortunately was convinced that the
only place you could actually get iphone
chargers
was from apple which is so stupid i know
but just in case you didn't know that it
is in fact incorrect and you can get
really really cheap chargers that are so
good on like amazon for like
six dollars and not only is this one
cheap it's also 10 feet long which is
literally the most convenient thing in
the entire world so you can have your
phone plugged in literally
anywhere and be able to walk around with
it plug it into an outlet that might be
in an
inconvenient location and still be able
to charge your phone or you can plug it
into your portable charger in your purse
and walk around with it you can put it
in your backpack at school and be able
to
loop it around and hold in your hands i
don't even know literally nobody in this
house anymore is wasting
thirty dollars on three foot apple
cables that are definitely going to
break or get lost i do not regret this
in any way shape or
form okay so the next thing that i want
to show you guys is another one of those
items that is in my purse literally at
all times
some people actually might already know
about this but i've also met a lot of my
friends who had no idea so i definitely
want to show all of you today and that
is this right here which is called a
tile now if you open a box basically it
is like these little
plastic cubes and this right here is a
tracking device you can buy them
individually but you can also buy them
in sets of i think two four
six and eight obviously right here i
have my set of four and two of them are
missing but i have like ten more of
these boxes upstairs because i have
so many of these tiles because they have
literally saved my
life they look just like this they're
very small square and thin and i think
they also come in black or white they
have a little hole in it so you can put
it on a keychain but they're also thin
enough to where you can literally put it
anywhere so i have one in my wallet i
also have one in my
backpack in my suitcase and also
literally every single purse that i own
and then you sync them up to your phone
on an app just like this basically all
you have to do is
register your different items so right
here like i have my louis vuitton wallet
oh speaking of this charger i need to
use it because my phone is dying period
and then it'll tell you the tiles
location so obviously right now it says
nearby because my wallet is
right here in my very hand and if you
click find on the app
the tile will start ringing which is so
beyond helpful if you lose your wallet
within your own house or if it falls
between your couch cushions or under
your car seat all you do is click find
and it'll ring right away
but if your item with your tie liner is
not nearby if you happen to
lose it it will tell you the exact
location was last seen which is
so incredibly helpful i have lost this
way more times that i would like to
admit in fact i literally lost my wallet
two days ago my tesla was in the shop so
i had to get a rental
car and i accidentally left this in
there when we gave it back which was
a really really stupid mistake and i
couldn't find it i was looking
everywhere throughout the house then i
was thinking oh my god let me check my
tile and low behold it was at the tesla
service center and they drove it back to
me right away which was super super nice
but literally without this i would have
never probably seen this again like i
said i have this in literally every
single bag
purse suitcase that i own and it has
made things so much easier to keep track
of
although i've lost my wallet a bunch of
times like an absolute idiot the one
item that i never lose or misplace has
got to be
my iphone actually fun fact for you
though if i did happen to lose it you
can also
tap on your tile and it'll start ringing
oh hello
there you go oh my god it'll start
ringing your phone
just like this which has also come in
very very handy
shut up stop again stop
i know it's right here stop ringing
i know i have you in my hand but as i
was saying okay i never lose my iphone
and that has got to be because it is
literally locked my hand at all times
using a pop socket now i feel like
everyone in the entire world knows about
a popsocket and also has this on their
phone so i'm not going to be including
that in today's video but the one item
that i do want to include
that goes along with these pop sockets
is this right here it is a pop
socket holder now this probably looks
really stupid to you guys but these are
so incredibly useful it is not even
funny and i have so many of these lying
around my house and i wanted to take one
out and show you guys just how they work
today because
i accidentally happened to break mine a
few days ago so i ordered a bunch of new
ones
this is nothing revolutionary or
groundbreaking in any way shape or form
it is literally just like a round piece
of plastic with a little bit of sticky
tape on the back but
these come in so handy because all you
do is just place this somewhere where
you want to have your phone so you can
get work done hands-free so
the one that broke i always have stuff
to my mirror where i do my makeup so i
literally put it on here
just like this and it'll literally stick
anywhere oh
so while i'm sitting here at the studio
i can put my phone right here on my
makeup mirror so i can keep focusing on
getting glam but at the same time i can
make a facetime call if i need to this
is literally so helpful i also have one
of these on the dashboard of my car i 1
would never ever ever condone texting
while driving but it's super helpful to
have your phone right there if you need
to make any phone calls hands-free
or for gps directions as well okay so
while we're on the subject of things
that can hold your phone
the next item that i want to show you
guys is honestly something that i use
every single day and has
changed my life for the better and that
has got to be this little iphone
tripod ring light thing right here that
i got from amazon now i think this one
was like 60
which is definitely on the pricier side
but there are so many of them
online that i would definitely recommend
checking out and these are so
so helpful it is not even funny
basically they come just like this it is
a ring light a thing that can expand to
hold your phone no matter what size it
is and then a
expandable and collapsible
tripod this is like literally the
perfect all-in-one item for any form of
content creation
personally i like to use these whenever
i'm filming my tick tock videos but
this could be good if you want to film
different youtube videos if you want to
rotate it horizontally
for instagram videos for taking selfies
of yourself because it comes with a
remote as well
i think at this point i have like two or
three of these sitting around the house
for different tick tocks or videos and
stuff but at the hype house they
literally have like 97
okay not 97 books like they literally
have one of these in every single room
because they are so so helpful and i
would definitely recommend checking
these out if you were any sort of
content creator the next item that i
want to show you guys
is not a phone holder in any way shape
or form but
it is what we use it for just bear with
me for a quick second okay you guys
obviously saw the house for a video and
you saw the massive pool in the back
it has been very very hot this entire
summer of california and we have been in
it literally
non-stop swimming and just chilling in
the water which has been absolutely
incredible and one thing that we have
gotten
from amazon that has changed our lives
for the better is this
right here which is a float a floaty
a floaty yeah a floaty
tray we're gonna change the lighting for
one quick second so you guys can
actually see this but it is literally
just a white
floating trap but it has raised a border
so it's really really hard to sink or
get water inside
it comes in a pack of three and
technically these are supposed to be
used for serving food
but we use these smaller ones to put our
phones in so therefore we can enjoy our
time in the water but if we get a ding a
notification
or a phone call and we have to answer it
we can easily grab it without having to
worry about getting our phones wet
or reaching over the sides i know this
is like very very like first world
type of problem but these are coming
very very handy and anybody out there
who has a pool
might love this as well so i just wanted
to share in this video
this next item that i want to show you
guys is 150
of purchase that i made because of tick
tock but it has been so
so much fun to have and i do not regret
buying it and that is this baby right
here which is a
uh like star it is like a star light
projector
basically you plug it in you put it in
the center of your room and you turn
your lights off and it creates the most
beautiful
gorgeous like blue galaxy lighting all
over your ceiling in your room and it is
such a cool vibe whether it be late at
night and you're chilling in your room
or for even a party as well
obviously not during the pandemic this
would be so
so helpful and also this is what i used
to film my euphoria transformation tik
tok a few weeks ago as well and if you
guys saw that
it really looked super super cool so i
would definitely recommend checking
these out they are such a vibe
there's quite a lot of brands that are
like capitalizing on this right now and
selling these for like 120
which is absolutely ridiculous you can
get this on amazon for like
20 bucks so if you want to get it get it
for cheap there's literally no
difference in the quality at all and
this works
really great okay you guys so the next
and final two items on the list are
definitely two
that are like 18 not 18 up but
definitely two that you need to be
careful with i'll say that for sure and
the first one that i want to show you
guys is this right here which is an
electric
lighter this might seem like it's
something that is so ridiculous to you
but i really like these
one because plastic lighters are just
like a waste of
materials that are gross and you have to
throw them out because they don't get
many uses whereas this
can recharge so you can keep using it
literally forever and it's honestly just
like
kind of fun to play with it's a little
electric oh my god that's crazy looking
oh it literally creates an electrical
current so let's raise that back up
that's scary-looking so if i open up my
crisp morning air candle just like this
power it on and then if i hit my little
button
i can light it super super easily just
like that so once it runs out you just
plug it in and then it'll be ready to go
lighting things up again please be
careful and smart whatever you're
deciding to light on fire it'll never
run out of lighter fluids and it's also
not a waste of plastic and materials so
definitely recommend checking these out
if you want to okay you guys i've showed
you a ton of my favorite things
throughout this video so far
but the number 10 last item on my list
is
not only thing that i use every day but
something that i use probably 50 times a
day
and that is this baby right here which
is an electric
fly swatter now when i tell you that
this thing has changed my life and the
lives of everybody around me
oh my god i have made so many people
order this and not a single person
including myself has regretted this
because these are so
much fun it's not even funny basically
it looks like a tennis racket just like
this but it has a button on the side
and if you press on it it looks like
nothing's happening but oh
let me tell you something is happening
in here and i will tell you what it is
it's electrical okay i don't have any
flies here in the studio right now but
if i take like a makeup brush
oh they're up there oh hey oh there's a
fly
that's a birthday
oh my god oh wait here oh oh it's up
there it's on the it's on the microphone
oh it's right there right there right
there i just flew around um
um i can't i can't find it oh oh oh
there's a flight
why don't we just continue the video and
then if it comes back
he's getting this out yeah they end up
in literally everybody's houses and this
is a really fun way to just zap them and
get rid of them and also scare off their
little friends so they do not come
back obviously you guys well yes they
need to
flies are demonic they do not they they
need to go
literally louis are you is this the fly
committee are you peta i also need to
clarify as well i can't believe i almost
forgot this
as fun as these are these are so
dangerous so if you do get one of these
please please be careful do not get this
anywhere near your fingers
babies pets children with flies those
can go
alright you guys and i think that
officially completes my list of the 10
different random gadgets and gizmos and
objects and
fun things that i could not live without
i honestly had so much fun filming this
video today and i really hope that you
guys enjoyed it as well this is
obviously very very different for me i
don't know
how you're going to like this but i hope
that you do and if you did
please show it to me by giving it a big
thumbs up down below let me know if you
want to see more videos like this in the
future as well
also click the big subscribe button down
below and finally click that bell icon
so you get notified every time i upload
a brand new
video if you want to follow me on my
makeup journey all my social media
accounts are gonna be linked right here
around the screen and also if you want
to text me on my personal phone number
for updates on videos photos merch and
so much more my number is
310-905-8746 this video's sister shout
out goes to sister ali thank you so much
love for always following and supporting
i love you so so so much and if you
would like to be the next video sister
shout out don't forget to always retweet
my video links when they go live on
twitter all right you guys thank you so
much for watching today's video i love
you and i will see you in
the next one bye