hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you can see I'm not in my normal studio
setup and I have an amazing beautiful
amazing brother Itachi Westbrook you
guys this woman literally is the woman
of the make up community and well many
of you guys do not know is that we
filmed together 12 films on my I got on
your channel several times yes this is
like a first time for me yeah yes it's
been meaning to hop in for way too long
we've literally I don't know how it's
literally was an accident so talk to you
I have actually been friends for like
two and a half years now probably she's
they've been here since the beginning of
my makeup repair she helped me move out
to Los Angeles I went to her in James's
wedding in Hawaii literally they flew me
there and bought me pants because I
could not even afford to be there which
is so crazy that like how far you have
come like honestly it's been like okay
like I'm gonna break about you on your
channel for most places who texted me I
remember I'm about to get married and
I'm all like ah you know and James was
so sweet he did my makeup it was such a
beautiful experience but you could not
find pants and you were so stretched
then you know YouTube hadn't become a
livable paying job yet
so it's just you know it's so insane to
see how far you've come and how far
you've grown and I reached out to James
you know way back when because he was so
mega talented and like it's so cool to
watch you know what we mean that so we
just have so much love for each other
and like I'm so happy to be here we've
been friends for three years for some
reason it literally this happened by
accident swear to god she's never been
on my channel before I haven't on her
staff you times we thought it was only
right to do something iconic for today's
video thank you for being here this idea
is actually taught to you so I live here
so Tati actually came up with the
craziest idea ever I have a younger
demographic so they were probably not
alive yet I don't know if I was alive
yet for this you don't know how many of
you remember supermarket sweep but it
used to be this game show where people
would have time to go like down the
aisles and they'd like you know knock
over things from the aisle into their
cards and they'd have like 60 seconds to
do it and
I was seeing a bunch of memes about this
and I was like oh my god it would be so
fun if we went into a Sephora and had 60
seconds to literally just like grab grab
grab grab grab to get our entire
mentality yes and sit down and have to
create a look off of that I'm nervous
I'm so ready for that like when you text
you this idea I was like oh my god we
have to do this right now
such a cool idea like a blast from the
past I watched a few clips of it last
night from YouTube and it sounds like
it's gonna be so much fun so for today's
video
sister talk today we're gonna be doing
at Sephora sweet and we are going to go
to our local Sephora and we're going to
run and we're going to have a 60 seconds
to grab as many products as we possibly
can for our makeup routine have you
thought about this though oh you have a
game I do I have a Saturday I have kind
of a small one but I'm I don't think we
should share it with each other no I'm
not going to but I was actually kind of
stressing out about this because I was
like I need so many things like I need I
I'm high maintenance high I'm so high
maintenance
I love thought for you wait our brush is
included in there no can use around
Ashley's right we're making our own
rules it's our own challenge yeah
whatever
we need to go we're gonna be going do we
need to go do some sisters shopping at
Sephora bye
[Music]
if there's any sisters
it's like a speed bump there's so many
points
[Music]
we're
Oh
[Applause]
you got so many things I don't
understand all right sisters we are back
from Sephora and I have one gun of a few
things
Chucky has two entire bags of product I
would love to know what your strategy
was what I did is I went in and I knew
that if I grabbed my foundation then I
could go to like this sample type area
and just be like oh that's smart okay
but then I had this moment where I
totally forgot like what I had even
picked out where I kind of almost like
blacked out in the middle of Sephora and
I was like time's running out and it got
really dramatic and so I just started
like grabbing things and in the back of
my head I was like you know what I'll
just put this in a giveaway like that
low good thinking right so I was like
just go ahead overdo it because you have
no strategy you suck at this and I
really thought that you were gonna be
like well I did have a shot what was it
products you watch your opposite ma'am I
wanted to go I was gonna go right to
two-faced and then Stassi which I did
but it took me probably 20 seconds to
find the anasazi encounter which is an
issue but I knew by hitting them both I
could get foundation and then concealer
and then powder all from Too Faced
because I like the whole line the Born
This Way and then the peach powder and
then Anasazi I can get contour in brows
and lip did you I misled from Anasazi
but I have everything else so I'm gonna
have a really good base going on today
but I don't know about much else but
that's okay yeah I can go for a nice
natural look I can literally recreate
this exact oh I don't have a highlighter
I do oh wait how how did this even
happen that I this I think has a harness
does it oh yeah it has a highlighter
okay dude I have highlight liquid and
pressed from Becca what and
lashes I don't understand how you even
grabbed that many things like that
stolen my makeup look so pretty right
now to take it off and make it look I'm
actually having a good makeup date our
legs are so hard why because I feel like
you've gotten very advanced very
creative with it because I always stress
a little bit I'm like oh I hope my wing
liner is suitable to be in public with
James I won't embarrass oh my god
well I mean you don't see my red carpet
in this way throwing everything on and
hoping to try to sleep eyelashes on
leave the lashes on I will allow that
and permit it in our fake challenge of
no rules what you're kidding I don't
understand how you got everything so I
have the Dior air flash which I never
touched on before remember
I love this so much and I needed more
this will work for me I knew what shade
I was I didn't have to like it's a
number so it's just like oh yeah 3:01 I
grab my paper on this one you guys I'll
just my all-time holy grail I hope this
isn't boring I grab all the products
that I normally used by I want to win oh
my gosh aid vanilla watch is my hey
where are we winning really nothing I
decided to look good I guess I know this
is gonna be like a light coverage look
so I'm not gonna use too much or I might
look a little crazy okay where's my
concealer I don't know if this is even
my shade I just kind of grabbed this is
medium from urban decay shoe this looks
dark oh that's not gonna work how was
that medium okay mmm that's a fail you
know what we're gonna do we're just
gonna take some more foundation does
you're not gonna concealer uh oh no we
talked about the makeup community sure
why not so if you sisters follow me on
Twitter which if you don't you
definitely show because let me tell you
my twitter is a good and first time I
voted smell some tea
so some Tati
so I was tweeting that I was working on
a really really big project and then I
tweeted saying that I wasn't gonna be
doing that project because it was really
risky and I never told you what it was
why did did I say what it was basically
right now the beauty community is in
shambles and talk to you I will happen
to be ones that are on the outside Chile
having a really wonderful time living
our lives love that frost okay basically
long story short I have not been doing
well this month for many reasons one of
the reasons being I spent an entire week
of my life planning a documentary which
is now never going to happen about the
downfall the beauty industry and why it
is everyone it involves fault and that
may sound crazy but me and Todd you were
actually talking a lot about it during
the planning process because it's
obviously a very touchy subject and a
thing that I am really passionate about
and I know he's really passionate about
so I figured for today's video while
we're like getting ready using our
products I thought it could actually be
really interesting since we're obviously
not doing like the full-on documentary
to kind of touch on some of the things
we wanted to discuss because I feel like
we're both so really polished about it
and like it could be fun to talk about
also you've been in industry for a very
long time and even someone that I've
looked up to obviously since day one and
I'm very blessed to call you a close
friend now but before I was here you
were here so obviously you know my
thoughts on all this but how do you feel
about it I agree with you that there are
so many different sides to look at it
and that in a way everybody could be
doing things better like you can't just
point fingers and be like you're doing
it bad you're doing it bad it's like
well everybody's at fault everybody's at
fault let's kind of see where we can
adjust things like this stuff actually
makes me super uncomfortable talking
about it but to me it's really important
to I've had to navigate through this
business in a very unique way I don't
have a manager I don't have an MCN I
don't have an agent
I do work with a lawyer if I need to go
through contracts like I'm smart about
it yeah and that's a very unique thing
most people do work with the team and I
do you know I do have people that help
me out but there has been no book like
you don't sign up to YouTube and they're
like here you go these are the rules
right so I think everybody's kind of
scrambling to do the right thing the
best that they can for their audience
for themselves
it's exciting to want to work with big
brands so I get all the excitement
and I get where people feel pressured to
not disclose but we're Adam no it's
really not that hard no it is I mean I
don't do sponsorships because really my
audience does not like them and they
feel that it cuts down on my level of
trust well that gets into the
conversation about the consumer for
influencers I'm saying it's not
physically like there's no challenge
behind posting a caption saying and this
is sponsored no but I honestly don't
think that I would have the success or
credibility that I have if I had done a
ton of sponsorship so I have been
someone that really has not done a ton
it's been challenging because there have
been people that will take sponsorships
and say that it hasn't been sponsored
and I know that it has because the same
we've seen the help in Atlanta it's
unique I think from our standpoint we
see it all and there's so much that the
audience doesn't see well I think that
is a huge part too in my documentary and
neces gonna come across as very
controversial but I believe there are
issues on all parts being influencers
the main thing being disclosing of
course there's lots of other factors as
well I'll talk about brands in a second
because that's my favorite topic but
consumers I think one of the major
issues is that there's really a
disconnect in the sense that a lot of
consumers hold youtubers to two
different standards at the same time and
I think that they hold youtubers at the
standards of celebrities and the sense
that they want them to have a perfect
track records perfect backgrounds behave
well be on a very very tight schedule
never mess up and just like be a role
model at the same time though a lot of
people completely disregard that
standard and then say that YouTube isn't
a real job that people should not be
paid anything and that people are money
hungry and then when people do do
sponsorships and disclose people say oh
we are selling out or oh my god like
well I do need money that badly or like
it's a little bit of a twisted system
and I think that at the end of the day
consumers are consumers and it sounds
really blunt and stupid to say but it's
like consumers get to choose what they
want to consume and at the end of the
day it's up to the consumers you sisters
at home watching to make an educated
decision on who you want to watch who
you want to support what brands you want
to buy from and that's that on that like
there's there's no I actually I feel
similar I
get that there's just no way to dice it
we are role models I think that's
something you do have to be mindful of
if you're in this business is that you
have a lot of eyes on you whether you
like it or not right you are in some way
shaping the world which sounds really
crazy but when you have millions of
people watching and you are you know
sharing your opinion and whatnot like we
are role models but yes
it is up to the consumer to really
decide and do research and not just go
down one Avenue I think that a lot of
people have gotten overexcited and maybe
they say yes too often like wait last
month you loved that Foundation and this
month you love this one and which one is
it right and if it's not just like
constant review constant review you know
I do a five-day week show so I'm
constantly in product it's not
necessarily stuff I use and travel with
every single day I'm just kind of
breaking it down and giving you my
immediate feedback so that's kind of my
gig so my whole thing is I wish that our
community was a little bit more
selective and I think sometimes it's the
managers that are a little aggressive
because they're making money off of us
too I'm gonna go to the peach powder
while we talk you brought our brands and
this is a topic that I am very
passionate about okay obviously you know
this and all the sisters on this too my
biggest passion aside from makeup is
marketing yeah and I really like
business it's like my favorite thing to
do I'm just very passionate about it I
like the inner thank you that means a
lot I just really like the inner working
as in things it's always very much
interested me and the business of beauty
is something that is really messed up on
a lot of different levels that's a very
broken system it sure is
I think the major thing with brands and
beauty is that a lot of brands and I'm
not naming anybody specific so don't
even try to start down with this I'm
speaking very generally because the
reality is this is - a lot of different
brands a lot of brands don't really know
how to target their right demographic
and therefore spend their advertising
dollars in the wrong way I can't believe
I'm even gonna discuss this on camera
but honestly might as well there was a
video that just went up recently by
Marlene Estelle the owner of makeup geek
and it was talking about her truth of
the industry it really created quite the
rock ass makeup gigas brand that I've
loved since day one I really were just a
lot of their shadows they're one of the
first bands that
I thought their shadows were phenomenal
over the past year makeup geek is kind
of like slowly slipped under the radar
and like the beauty fades people don't
really talk about them that much anymore
and Marlena made her video about her
truth for the beauty industry I actually
agree with a lot of the points that she
was making in the video wanting to
support smaller artists and like the
industry changing forget it and but
there was one thing that she said in the
video that literally like shook up the
beauty industry so much she basically
said that makeup geek is failing because
of the fact that she refuses to charge
big influencers 60 thousand dollars
which is the rate that she's been given
because of that personal thing that
happened and her being on video the
whole 60-thousand thing created a witch
hunt against influencers and i have
never had so many hate comments on
videos about product placement before
you really don't do that many
sponsorships I don't make it haunted
like because I was like gosh you know am
I am I in this like I don't really know
out of the past hundred and twenty
videos that I have produced look I
believe there is six maybe six maybe
seven yeah um you know and they weren't
and I I don't even think all of those
were dedicated videos they're just like
mentions yeah so I really I try so hard
to run my business in a way that makes
sense where I can support my own brand
which I invested everything in myself I
don't have any outside funding I wanted
to run it in my way so I've worked
really hard to be smart support brands I
love be smart about that know my worth
like I've done this in it in the right
way and like you have done this in the
right way to where you're so creative
you pour everything into your channel
you have to have financial support
somewhere because you do have to pay for
your team yes you do have to pay for the
lights you do have to pay for the makeup
you do have a lot of expenses so once
you get to this level it is it's very
expensive to run a business and I will
the reason I didn't do the documentary
is because I truly believe that this
industry is based on ignorance and the
people believing that this is just like
a really good time of people that they
love and look up to just putting on
makeup and calling it a day
when in reality this is a business if
you don't want to look at it that way
that's fine because you can just enjoy
the content we're working hard for you
guys we're obviously here to make
everybody happy like it's what we love
doing
you can't accept the fact that this is a
business I don't to tell you and the
60,000 was thrown around and it was such
a controversial number because $60,000
is so much money but I will say the best
way I can think about it is this goes
back to the consumers a lot of the
consumers say you tubers should not be
paid this they're just setting for
Medicare they don't deserve to make any
money okay fine you want to think that
great consumers are the ones spending
the money so consumers are the ones who
buy makeup and it's unrealistic to just
say if you hate the beauty industry stop
buying makeup because it's never gonna
happen it's a billion dollar industry
consumers are the ones who put the money
in the brands pockets and the brands
help to advertise brands that don't
advertise fall under the radar and all
brands have advertising budget every
single brand ever as a mine what
most brands well you're the advertising
budget but you just don't have to pay
for because it's you feel bad for me of
no budget yes
I've already been taking mine so I'm on
I only have a few days left in my bag it
is true though okay jokes aside most
brands have huge budgets and what they
spend in traditional media would be you
would just be Shh right so think about
it this way if a brand wants to do a
campaign right say influences are off
the table we hate influencers buy your
jobs over that leaves a brand to do a
traditional media campaign I'm going off
on this this is something I'm very
passionate about you want to do a
traditional media campaign you don't
have to assign the work to the people
that are in your internal team and they
have to plan the whole campaign great
once the campaign is planned you have to
rent a studio space which is very very
expensive in Los Angeles then you have
to rent all of the equipment you have to
hire a videographer you have to hire a
photographer you have to hire a producer
you have to hire all the models and pay
their day rate you have to hire hair and
makeup to do their entire faces to get
them ready for the commercial you have
to hire an editor to then work on the
finished product and higher probably
assistants to help you and make sure
that the set day runs smoothly that's
why we're gonna cost upwards of like two
hundred to three hundred thousand
dollars per day of shooting that's true
but that's not it because then once you
have the finished commercial fully done
it's not just gonna sit on your little
flash drive at your desk you actually
have to get it shown and that's what the
things get really pricey because then
these brands have to pay for advertising
space and let me tell you because this
is a constant battle that youtubers are
always fighting advertising is very ver
expensive to get ads running on TV
networks on popular channels during the
Superbowl it cost several hundred
thousand dollars for a few seconds so
you probably spent let's say five
hundred thousand dollars to get this
commercial made and now shown right and
your goal is to make a million dollars
of sales your profit margin has now been
50 percent this is a lot of math it is
and this model has been around for
hundreds and hundreds of years and it's
worked very very well for major brands
so a brand pays an influencer back to
the original decision brain wants to do
a campaign traditional media buy
influences are back you get your job
back you're welcome you want to do it
camp into that influence are great so
they say hey James we want you to do a
video about our product right they don't
have to pay for the studio space because
it's already in the house
and they'd have to pay for the equipment
because it's already in the house they'd
have to pay for the videographer editor
photographer or model because that's
already the influencers job they do that
already on YouTube once the video is
already fully produced they don't have
to pay for advertising space either
because the YouTube channel of the
influencer is already getting viewed by
millions of people say the brand's -
let's make a million dollars dr.
Martinez video they pay said influencer
at sixty thousand dollars their profit
margin is now at ninety four percent why
in any way shape or form what a brand
pay five hundred thousand dollars when
they could pay sixty thousand dollars
and get a very same if not maybe even
better because right now a lot of people
are looking to influencers for true
honest reviews result yes why it doesn't
make any sense
influencer marketing regardless of
whatever your personal opinion on it
maybe it's a system that works it's a
system that is very very efficient and
is a system that is very very cost
effective and it's probably not going to
go away for a very very long time
so I think it's up to the public to
educate themselves on it and not hate it
because it's not the influencers problem
that they're taking a deal if the fact
that advertising exists in every single
industry and the beauty industry is a
billion dollar industry and everybody
needs to make money and support
themselves somehow from the consumer to
the influencer to also the brand owner I
think that you have to look at the
realistic overall you know math of
everything and again it gets a little
bit cluttered when you look at one
person who has X amount reach another
person has a different reach
really like throwing out a broad number
like 60k made everybody feel like that
was just a universal number for every
single person words of content and
that's just not the case I was just very
irresponsible if I'm I yeah well I mean
I have to agree with that
I like Marlena I've loved her products
for so long you know I put in my truth
video an email exchange not wanting
money from her I think a lot of people
have loved her brand a lot of people
have loved her product I think she
probably has a lot of frustration with
you know relationships falling apart
like that whole behind the scenes I'm
not gonna get into no it's nobody's
nobody's business
I mean I have so much that I could just
lay out on my channel all the time but
it's just not appropriate because you
guys don't come to see me for that you
come for reviews you come to escape the
world right I do my best to not throw
all of that information that's private
your way to confuse you so I do agree
with that number being thrown around was
kind of like wait what whoa
it stirred up a lot of dirt it really
did it started this weird tension of
what's the right way to do this business
and everyone can do it their own way
yeah you know and as long as you are
being honest with your subscribers great
I think that the influencers need to be
more honest and I need to be very open
when they're doing sponsorships I think
the influencer should only take
sponsorships when it's a product that
they actually care about one I think it
makes everybody else look really bad
yeah - you're deluding everybody else's
rate card three you're gonna lose the
trust of your own subscriber so you're
yes there's my piece of advice for you
you're ruining it for yourself as for
brands I think that they need to do a
better job of educating themselves on
how marketing works and who they want to
work with hiring some five million
followers and they're getting 10,000
likes that engagement is very very low
and it's probably not someone who's
going to make you that money back
whereas you can hire someone with five
million followers that's getting five
hundred thousand likes 10% engagement
which is usually a very good a typical
number you're probably gonna make your
money back it's up to the brand make the
right decision do your research on who
is doing well who's name is being talked
about a lot and who has good engagement
and who can really convert to sales and
it's for the consumers make an educated
decision on the industry that you're
supporting pick people that you want to
watch that you believe are generally
here for the right reasons pick people
that you see working really really hard
there's nothing wrong with doing
answer ships as long as you truly
believe that they like the product and
one thing and that's up to you as a
consumer to decide how January they're
actually being also at the same time
though mine here on business
love you sisters the most you guys are
very good about this I'm not saying this
is you but it's a general issue in the
beauty community these numbers should
have never even been brought to the
surface in the first place
there were nobody's business and I think
it's very responsible no and I think
because it's out there that's why I feel
ok to discuss it it's a business whether
you want to admit it or not and of
course yes I'm here to inspire people
and to make people happy trust me I
would not be here anymore if it was not
for that because this job behind the
scenes can be so insane so I am gonna
touch on the whole you know this is a
job this is a business you know for me I
have employees I do have to show up to
work every day there's just no different
way to slice it so I do approach this as
a business and I take it very seriously
and that doesn't mean that I'm not
passionate about it that doesn't mean I
don't love it it just means that this is
something really incredible that turned
into the best job ever and I'm not
ashamed of that you know you shouldn't
be either but so many people are and
they're like oh I hate that YouTube
feels like a job you know and it's like
well but it's the best job it is you
know and I feel really privileged so on
one hand I feel like oh my gosh I'm so
grateful I don't want anybody to get the
vibe then I'm not but there are a lot of
things that are very stressful and they
give us just a feeling of pressure a lot
of the time and I think that number
being released kind of made us all feel
like oh my God we're all the bad guy we
should feel horrible when that was just
one isolated incident and I think as far
as ROI goes for business
you are so spot-on with that like I
really feel that brands need to do more
education don't be afraid to ask for
analytics they're there I think these
issues are all very fixable
I think everybody just had a little bit
more respect for everybody else
everybody did their proper research on
who they want to support who they want
to buy from who they want to watch
this industry would be much better off
and I really just wish everybody would
stop being greedy whether it be for
money for brand deals or for information
and just get back to what it really is
it's just makeup I think that we
move in a more positive direction and I
think the community it needs to be more
respectful of each other instead of
pointing fingers and playing the blame
game because like we're all in this
together and I don't like hearing that
the community is falling apart you can
only trust yourself like I try so hard
to not be jaded in this community right
like you have to keep some openness
about you yeah right and you have to
believe that there can be good and I
think we have the best job on earth and
it it's so exciting and we're so blessed
that doesn't mean it's not hard it
doesn't mean it's not a ton of work and
a ton of pressure but it is good and you
guys give us that and I am so grateful
and James is so grateful I just think
people are tired of being dragged you
know in every which direction it's like
hey let's all have a better attitude
about it let's all disclose let's all be
a little not honest and let's all see
you're a part of it instead of pointing
a finger at everybody else amen and the
setting sprays coming through that's
gonna say speaking of makeup let's go
back to our makeup I'm almost done with
my routine because I only have because
you only had three products and I
literally have a disaster in front of me
this is like chaos I will show you guys
I had a little liner set from Marc
Jacobs this was one of the minis I have
the TARDIS Pro to go that's how I did
this I look I have mini on honest Ozzy
what was your total don't ask me you're
judging me now well what's your total
well because I get $60,000 every time I
hold up a blush you know I spent $500 in
one minute oh one minute oh my god
you're literally kidding me no I'm not I
panicked I really wanted to impress you
I love that you know I just really
wanted to impress you because I was like
oh my gosh well you look like beautiful
oh thank you you really kill mr. James
his channel I want his audience to like
me and Legos I wanted to do a good job
and so I kinda I really like you guys I
like blacked out as for us I love how
you had 87 products on my head two three
and you still finished it for me I was
ready to talk to it how much did you
spend
I said 177
there's also my younger subscribers who
may not be an audience of Tati first one
you should be second of all this woman
uploads five videos a week aiya that we
have a mental breakdown over posting two
a week
okay so the limb just gonna take my
foundation off and I'm gonna use my
regular lip color oh I wish I could do
that actually all right you guys and
those are our completed looks with our
makeup fully done using our Sephora
sweep items you look so beautiful right
now thank you I'm so bad at you oh my
gosh like I had to look good for my
first time on your channel so I good you
would've looked beautiful regardless but
I'm very impressed you clearly do not
have a game plan and you still did
better than we you so thanks hey you got
some freckles do you look great so I did
I mean the items that I chose I love mmm
I may have not gotten as many items as I
wanted but the items that I chose I do
love so again I feel okay I'm a little
scared they don't have any holiday or
and I feel very very empty no I cannot I
can't see you I think you look good
thanks I'm happier the way it turned out
definitely leave us a comment down below
tell us who you think won at this
competition it's okay we're both really
really rich from our $60,000 from
everything that we did in this video
today if you guys into this video today
it please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and come show your
sister support subscribe it come from
the sisterhood it is an amazing time we
got eight million sisters that strongly
click the belt like them so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video
if you enjoyed my mother you guys all
have to go subscribe to her right now
please I'm gonna list her channel down
below my glam light guru at living
budget Oh living legend thank you yeah
Tata channel I turned her stepson into a
dry queen and it was his first time ever
wearing makeup so that was insane it was
so much fun so definitely go subscribe
check out that video this video is a
sister shoutout goes to sister Emma
thank you so much Lord for always
falling and supporting no I love you
literally so so so much and if you like
to be the next videos sister shoutout
don't forget to always reach it your
video links they go live on Twitter I
also really hope you guys enjoyed this
like little business conversation I know
this is not planned
like came out of nowhere I was like hey
I was thinking of this thing let's chat
about this is a topic that I know both
Dante and I are very very passionate
about this industry something that we
care a lot about I mean clearly it shows
this woman has been here for eight years
Asli killing it being such a huge role
model to me and everybody else involved
and it's an industry that we don't want
to see fail and right now I feel like
it's in a very very uncomfortable and
weird place and everybody has just a
little bit of a weird feeling in their
heart so I just wanted to address these
issues head-on because I went from being
someone who literally could not even
afford to buy makeup to being a smaller
influencer to being a bigger influencer
to then being at the level of literally
working on consulting and marketing with
these brands so I've seen all aspects of
it and I truly believe that it can be
fixed
I believe that we're all here for one
shared life yeah being makeup and I just
want to see it go back to that and
everybody has to work hard and put food
on the table and nobody can eat lipstick
forever so let's leave it at that
also amen yeah if you like my sister's
cruda don't forget to check out sisters
- apparel calm for all your cute sisters
gear I'm going there right now please do
okay all right you guys thank you so
much watching this video today we love
you and I will see you in the next one