definitely looks like I'm at the right
place you could see us I marked look at
how cute
wait that's definitely Kim Kardashian
jealous James James assume he's up there
exactly where I thought he'd be James
James hello good morning sunshine
it is Vogon we are here for your 73
questions somebody yes are you ready for
your interview no well it's 1:00 p.m.
what are you doing still asleep until
4:00 well around what time do you
usually go to sleep between 10:00 p.m.
and 4:00 well I guess you'd consider
yourself an i al over a morning person
mm not necessarily I'm more recently
have been but speaking of schedule what
days do you usually upload on YouTube Oh
whenever I have a good video right do
you find it difficult to come up with
new content consistently that's the yeah
the beauty community is getting really
boring oh well what are your favorite
types of videos to film I really like
well what video would you say is the
most favorite that you've ever done I
would have to say my singing my makeup
routine video ooh and what did you do in
that video how to improv my way through
the lyrics it was crazy but so much fun
so would you say music is a big part of
your life I would for sure I've been
singing I see that there is a piano on
the floor do you play at all playing
would not exactly be the word I would
use to describe it well how long have
you been playing for then oh I taught
myself kind of a right ear so I never
actually take it lesson well do you mind
playing us a little something I can try
let's hear it
give it all you got
can
understand
people
[Music]
Bravo that was amazing
who knew you have that all in E oh yeah
me either
well who is your favorite artist
probably Donnie and why do you say that
well she's iconic she's beautiful she
has some of the best vocals in the game
and we both had a pretty bad yes how
could we forget flashback Mary well
you've definitely been someone who's
caused quite the controversy online what
scandal do you think you deserve the
least oh and what about the scandal you
deserve the most
yes I mean it's super super important to
grow and learn from your mistakes and
I'm glad that you're doing just that
well let's go back to makeup for a
second what is the worst makeup mistake
you've ever made
oh when I first started makeup I could
not figure out how to put on oh speaking
of lashes it looks like you're missing a
little something
oh yeah oh my god I actually have not
put them on here today oh no and as
there a reason why you haven't done that
James
super super easy it is insane you're
very welcome
well if that's not your favorite what is
your favorite part of your makeup
routine mmm I said out just because it
boys allows you to be really really
creative hey see what is your favorite
eyeshadow palette probably my morphe 35n
is literally always ready at hand and
it's like my rainbow palette so I've
heard he had a Murphy code what is it
Colton's return first of all well have
you ever thought about making your own
palette absolutely it is deathly slang
what is on my bucket list for the future
that's for sure well do you mind telling
us a little bit more about it
no because if I did somebody
Oh Stewart this beauty industry is
ruthless have you ever had anything
stolen from you I've actually had my
wallet so in three different time oh how
did you manage to let that happen I'm
not exactly the most organized person
well if organization isn't a strong
point about you what would you say is
I'm always brutally honest love ah
interesting what is your sign
I'm a loud and proud Gemini yeah um well
how do you deal with the online gem and
I hate do you feel personally attacked
ever online regardless so I don't really
care about that type of stuff all right
well what is your least favorite social
media platform probably Twitter and what
about your most favorite probably
Instagram is where I got my start and
it's where my biggest fall I guess how
long ago did you get your start on
Instagram oh my gosh that's like nothing
how long have you been wearing makeup
for then also just over two years oh my
gosh I need to learn from you because
I'm still learning and it has been well
over two years but it's awesome that you
blew up quickly what is your biggest
achievement this year I just had two
million subscribers on my youtube
channel and what do you call your
subscribers my sister how cute but why
is that well I think the word fan is
ugliest word in the world and I consider
them like my family well having a lot of
people following you online is amazing
but does it ever become overwhelming let
us all know oh not gonna lie honestly
yeah it really does having two million
people watching your every move
is a huge weight on my shoulders but I'm
very very blessed to have the
opportunity of being a role model for a
ton of people so I love to be able to
learning
and hopefully provide them with good Wow
so what's your favorite part of having a
platform um sorry people I feel like my
favorite part is getting messages from a
little boy something inside of them
that's amazing but do you ever think
there will ever be a day where it's
equally as common for every single
gender to wear makeup hmm that's a lot
honestly I do think so but I think it's
definitely going to take a while
unfortunately we do still live in a
society with very very having
stereotypes but because of beauty
bloggers like myself and more and more
brands working towards gender equality
I do think they'll be a day in the
future where everybody gets rockin
beautiful glam amazing way to lead a
path by the way your lashes look
incredible thank you okay look amazing I
see you have heaps and heaps of makeup
how much do you think it is all worth if
you could guess a horse of a million
dollars some of these brands are getting
real no no that's okay well here's a
classic question I'm sure you've been
asked well over a million times if you
are stranded on a deserted island what
you are raw pencil translucent setting
powder honestly those are great options
those flowers by the way are gorgeous
who are they from
- peas actually sometimes we got are
hitting two million they're so sweet oh
so sweet
do you usually get a lot of stuff from
brands yeah these packages Lillie right
here from this morning alone oh my gosh
well first of all this is a gorgeous
photo of you thank you do you ever get
things sent to you that aren't really
beauty related no I'm not very often but
mama Christie B does send me the
occasional care pocket so cute or does
your mom live she actually still doesn't
upstate New York with the rest of my
family so you live in LA alone I do yeah
17 after graduating early well
congratulations on that but do you ever
get lonely or miss them well it's an ace
well what are you gonna see them next
I'm actually yes Thanksgiving what is
one thing you were think before that's
good what's your favorite holiday mmm
probably Halloween same what did you do
this Halloween well this year my makeup
was to do it because I spent the entire
day even in Grayson's makeup yeah I see
so let the world know are you an Ethan
or are you a Grayson girl I'm gonna have
to say well what is one thing you can't
live without
I don't you at pinkie trying to be from
Starbucks James that's two things
all right well are you seeing anyone
right now I'm actually not living the
single life not in Prague
proud okay Wow well when's the last time
you went on a date I wanna take two
weeks ago with a guy from tinder but not
gonna lie he was boy ooh
not fun well who's somebody that you
would automatically swipe right on Oh
saman des wouldn't we all
is this your closet yes it is gorgeous
and very huge would you say fashion is a
big part of your life uh kind of
I do wish it was a lot bigger part
though my followers are very used to
seeing me and hoodies and sweatpants at
this point amazing would you mind yes of
course of course I see there are a lot
of hoodies on this rack where are they
from you have so many sisters apparel
they are so cute are they like so
available No
within minutes but we didn't have a ton
of exciting stuff coming for the
holidays what is one thing you want
Santa to bring you this Halloween I mean
this Christmas oh yeah Jesus how did you
get that on without any makeup water
practice I see practice makes perfect
well I see you have a lot of designer
things in your closet what is the most
expensive thing you've ever bought ah
probably my Cartier Justin clue bracelet
but I happened to hit two million
Instagram 1 million on YouTube
ad with my birthday always in the same
day so he had a splurge a lot but I
usually do save my money that's good
what are you saving for run down watches
even for a house a house that's insane
where do you want to live probably near
the valley I'm just really over downtown
LA there's absolutely nothing here
unless you like to party okay so you're
telling me you're 18 years old and you
don't like to party yeah I actually
don't smoke or drink what's your
favorite or move it probably insidious
or sinister there to my all-time
favorite hiding their plot
insidious is amazing alright well
honestly it looks like we are running
out of time I'm so sorry but is there
anything you have to say or would like
to say to your sisters Wow if you guys
enjoyed this video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
and if they would like to follow you
along your makeup journey where can they
find you you can follow me oh my
goodness okay do you usually talk that
fast
yes but I'm working on it alright before
I leave is there anyone you would like
to give a special shout-out to yes this
big sister shot that goes to sister
Hannah thank you so much
boys falling out supporting you I love
you so much and if you'd like to be next
is your shadow make choice we chip it
but it's legal like amazing well what's
so good having you Jane chuckle course
have an amazing day
thank you so much you too bye sister bar
[Applause]