it's too early for that
good morning sisters James Charles here
and welcome back to my youtube channel
and also welcome back to sister upload
week today is Thursday I hope everyone
was having an amazing day so far if you
have not yet checked out all the other
videos that have gone up for the past 2
5 days still don't know how I've done it
make sure to go check those out and also
make sure you stay tuned for tomorrow
Sunday which is the final day of sister
upload week and it is flashbacks
brand-new acapella cover it's currently
7 22 in the morning I went to bed at 3
from editing yesterday's video so it
looks like I'm gonna be running on four
hours of sleep today but that's a
personal problem not your guys's today's
schedule is absolutely jam-packed we
have so many fun things to do and also a
lot of business to take care of but
unfortunately most of those things that
I have to do today require me to wear a
full face of glam makeup even though my
job is a beauty guru my heart lies in
doing creative makeup and fun videos and
not wearing makeup around for long
periods of time that is in fact one of
my least favorite things in the world
since I'm just gonna be doing my normal
everyday makeup routine that I've
literally showed you guys 64 times
already I thought I would try to make
this video a little bit more interesting
by making it into a vlog so I'm gonna
take you guys around with me all day
today and to make it even more
interesting we're gonna be testing out a
setting spray that claims it can last
for up to 16 hours I honestly have no
idea what time I'm gonna get back home
tonight and be able to do glam I am
praying it's not 16 hours at this point
if it is I'm just like going back to bed
but yeah if you wanna have any fun
little sister's day with me I'm gonna
get up right now because I'm already
running a little bit late keep on
watching
[Music]
tomorrow oh these underwear literally
work wonder maybe we'll go ahead and use
a code James for 10% off hoodies today
these officially sold out
on sisters apparel you guys are so so
crazy this video is sponsored by my
babes over to Scandinavia I am
associated to be partnering with them
for this video and you guys can now use
Co James return percent off your
Scandinavia products here welcome
hello excuse me
well sisters today is already off to a
great start
Oh
let's do this so before I go in with any
makeups now I'm gonna spread typeface
using the skin to Naevia the makeup
primer spray and this is the oil control
version the spray on this is literally
so soft and it's crazy and I gonna make
sure to concentrate most of this in my
t-zone region because but I'm wearing
makeup for a long way a lot of coat lead
time that is usually where it gets oily
the fastest as you guys heard earlier I
am partnering with skins and Naevia for
today's video so thank you very much to
them for sponsoring this you guys know I
don't really do a whole lot of sponsored
come to it's mostly just the coupon
codes they are so so kind and it's a
really really fun at brand to work with
they have been at literally such a
breath of fresh air and their products
are so incredibly bomb too so for
today's video I'm just gonna be doing my
normal makeup I have so many things to
do today I don't even know how I'm gonna
end up doing it I need to get Clair
really fast I have a new video go away I
have a few different phone call meetings
I have to go to Starbucks to get pink
kitty drinking at some point for today's
a new upload
I have to go get my nails done as well
because these look the most disgusting
ever and then I'm supposed to have
dinner with some friends tonight and
then I also have to go home and film for
tomorrow's video I already know I'm
gonna crash the second I finished
editing later on tonight I'm gonna have
to keep this makeup look on today for
upwards of like 16 to 18 hours and skins
the Navy oh setting sprays are known to
last for 16 hours which is so so crazy
so I'm gonna tell you guys on my right
of me today on all my fun events and
we're gonna put the setting spray to the
test
Canada Scandinavia makeup finishing
spray hold for 16 hours on end we're
gonna find out
[Music]
I literally wear the same pair of
eyelashes almost every time doing makeup
now like it's getting a little sad at
this point I mean should I stop probably
am I gonna stop absolutely not I just
went ahead and I quickly wet my bake off
and you guys know that the next up is
always Highlander we got to get the glow
on of course but before I do that I'm
gonna go in and spread a face really
really lightly using just the skin a
navy eye makeup finishing spray this is
not my Lexus final spurt obviously I'm
just gonna put a little bit of this on
to really like set all those powders in
place and make them melt together and
then actually I love doing this before
highlighter as well because it gets the
scanner ready and I feel like it makes
the highlighter stick a lot better and
just gives a more a blinding luck you
see what I'm talking about
whoa I'm gonna be out and about quite a
lot place so I do want to add some blush
just to add a little bit of color to my
face because I'm looking a little bit
pale and then of course a new lip to
finish off this look
[Music]
okay wow that s today's look already
complete we literally just did that in
30 minutes I have no idea how I just
pulled that together but I am so
impressing myself right now let's go and
finish this look off once and for all
using the skin tone a via the makeup and
finishing spray once again this is the
oil control version because the sister
gets a little bit of personal grab my
fan do the little warp and then Fanta an
if you guys can once you finish your
makeup and use the setting spray I would
always grab a fan or even like a big
pallet and use that to dry your face off
this is really gonna make the settings
right like melt into the skin and blend
all the powders together and just set
really really smoothly
instead of like setting all crusty and
dusty and vanilla cake looking like on
top alright guys and that is this light
glam look off complete the skin to
Maivia setting spray you supposed to
last for 16 hours on end that is a very
very hefty claim and a long time it is
currently 921 in the morning and I am
running very very late for everything
that I have to do today and there is a
lot on the agenda so without further ado
if you'd like to see me putting this to
the test right here and just follow me
around let's have a little bit of a
sister's day keep on watching hope you
think that was probably the fastest I've
ever gotten glam in my entire life oh my
god the iPhone X camera is like scary I
don't even know if I want to keep it I'm
so spooked it's like - good quality this
doesn't even look good anymore
regardless I have three phone calls that
I have to hop on right now that I'm
currently running a little bit late for
I'm they're all business calls one is
with a brand that I really really love
one is with a brand that I don't work
with yet but really want to work with so
I'm looking forward to that one hardcore
and one is with a brand that we've been
going back and forth with on email and
things have been going too well so I'm a
little bit spooked I'm really sure how
it's gonna go but I'm running late
my name is James Reynolds so nice to
meet you guys finally I'm so they were
able to get on the phone today oh no no
no no no for sure I just want to make
sure we're innocent it's like really
gonna get the scissors involved just let
everyone like has a really good time
oh my god you're kidding no way oh if we
want to do just episode it has to be Co
James I mean it definitely isn't the
most creative let me get this right here
you guys can't some of your products to
try out first to make sure I like them
before I make a video for my youtube
channel that almost 2 million people
watch a week rating so other managers
all of you know like the contractual and
legal boring of mumbo jumbo and then you
can always reach me on this number if
you have oh oh girl I do not work for
free okay YouTube another good day bye
sister this one but you guys think this
is email if you wanna reach out for any
future opportunities oh my god okay -
okay I'll take you later on
[Music]
toy color is actually doing just fine
usually I would say you win some you
lose most but today we won most and lost
only one and probably for the better
[Music]
okay sisters just doing a quick little
check in here it was probably 150 2 p.m.
I just uploaded today's brand-new video
with the Dolan twins it was so much fun
building and you guys are killing it so
far
I'm currently replying to a bunch of
different comments oh I don't know this
check and I'm gonna go back to doing
that but I want to happen because it has
been about five hours of writing this
now and look at my freaking face
are you kidding it looks so good my skin
is still extremely matte like you can't
see any oil or anything oh so good the
only thing is here there's one little
crease and then of course lip Krusty's
but that happens every time I wear my
makeup that's my actual skin it is still
not I see absolutely no oil I am a
little bit shook by this settings for
you guys this is working way better than
I even expected so I'm currently walking
right now in downtown only to get my
nails done
I need a fail so badly please stop
commenting on my videos and Instagram
pictures done in 81 I know that they
look awful I just haven't had any time
but I'm gonna go to my normal guy he
doesn't so good it get a nice nude set
it is literally so hot and sunny today
in LA but oh my god that how it looks
amazing
I feel really hot on the inside and I
feel like I should be sweating but my
skin is actually staying really really
dry
[Music]
you
so I just finished my nail appointment
it is currently 356 p.m. at my skin is
still looking so public okay's I'm
literally not sweating not only in the
slightest this looks amazing that is
probably the most needed fill like ever
of history my nails look so bad
thank God they are now on fleek and
ready to go I'm gonna head home right
now and edit as much as I possibly can
for a little bit and then head over to
dinner I need to see it's the sort Ana
Ana Mari and Trevor I have not seen them
and literally so long of course you guys
to be coming with me so let's go it is
really 7:30 at night and my skin is
still looking so so Bom
I am getting a little excuse me miss I
went the servo show I am still welding
my makeup today Tara do you notice
anything different on my face in a 737
where you might wake up for almost 12
hours now I think that is ten hours we
love a mouth but yeah it still looks so
good like I would have not done any
touch-ups
are you kidding oh so good this needed
hello sisters I just got back home and
it's currently 11:47 p.m. meeting I've
had this makeup on now for more than 14
hours oh my god I am being 150 % honest
by saying I have not touched up my face
once today and looking in the mirror it
looks still so good if we're being picky
here my lips are obviously a little bit
crusty because I was just eating I do
have a smile crease but literally I
always get that that's because I smile
all day every day and my under eyes are
creasing as well but literally like look
at my freaking skin it still looks
flawless if anything is looking a little
bit early I would say it's my nose but
like I'm not even mad at it that happens
all the time no matter what and usually
it happens within like one hour of me
doing my makeup it's been 14 I'm
honestly beyond impressed it out with
those skin and navy eye makeup finishing
spray this claims that it's supposed to
last for 16 hours and obviously I only
wore it for 14 but let's be real who's
gonna wear makeup for 16 hours straight
first of all not me I'll tell you that
right now I think it's very safe to say
at this point that this setting spray is
a huge huge win in my book as well as
the primer spray as well both the oil
control versions like I said my face
looks so beat still
14 hours I'm ready to take this off yes
but if I need it to keep going out with
this what I yeah probably if you guys
want to check out any skin the name of
your products I will list the stuff and
down below and of course you can use
coach James for money off your products
I just want to say a major major thank
you to skins nav for partnering with me
on this video
they were so incredibly amazing to work
with I cannot even begin to explain they
literally were like do whatever you want
make an amazing video and we'll be happy
with it I can't even tell you how many
brand deals I've rejected because brands
will literally request like a six page
MLA style format essay with like full
citations on things to say about their
product oh my girl it's a foundation
does it look good or does it not look
good it really it's not that deep so
major thank you to Scandinavia for
trusting me as an influencer and having
amazing amazing products alright guys
that is all I have for this video today
I really really hope you guys enjoyed
following me around and if you did
definitely leave a comment down below if
you like this more like a vlogging style
content I would totally love to do it
more of this stuff soon I do blog all
the time on my snapchat so if you're not
following me I'm there definitely go add
me on snap but I would not be opposed to
vlogging on YouTube every once in awhile
so definitely give this video a big
thumbs up and let me know because sister
loves a good vlog if you like to follow
me on a makeup journey you can follow me
on Instagram or Twitter they're both
just James Charles and my snapchat for
one hasn't seen that stuff is James
Charles the next your ass after Charles
this week sister shadow goes to Noah
thank you so much pain for always
falling in supporting you know I love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be next video sister shadow they
should always read to it but it links
when they go live on Twitter all right
guys thank you so so much for watching
and remember we are in sister upload
week I've been uploading videos every
single day make sure to check out all
the previous videos this past week
they've been so much fun and stay tuned
for tomorrow's video the final video of
the week which is the flashbacks brand
new cover I am so excited for you guys
to hear it and yeah I love you so much
and I will see you in the next one I am
going to bed good bye
[Music]