don't forget to brush your tongue table
kids
[Music]
here like once a week literally
hi dixie
[Music]
we're getting changed in the middle of
the road currently mr james hi hollywood
facts we need the tea
from you oh i don't deliver any tea i
drink
[Music]
good morning coffee james charles here
and welcome back to my youtube channel
oh gosh it is 8 in the morning my alarm
just went off a few minutes ago as it
does every morning you're probably
wondering james why do you look like you
got hit by a bus why are you still in
bed why don't you have clothes on i
promise those things all have answers
and that is because today i am filming a
day in the life
video and i'm honestly really really
excited for it despite the fact that i
am starting so early i
have wanted to film this for a really
long time now because i personally love
watching other people's daily life
videos i think they're super super
interesting and i really want to show
you guys what like my daily work life
looks like obviously it's no secret that
the whole point of these videos
is to make the audience think that your
day is like crazy i feel like you guys
have definitely figured that out at this
point
like what am i gonna do okay film a day
of life anywhere i wake up at 10 in the
morning and go downstairs eat breakfast
postmates
three meals sell them a tick tock and go
back to bed no because it's boring i do
have those days sometimes i'm not even
gonna lie about it
so i really wanted to film one of these
videos obviously where my day is crazy
and
actually let me put you on pause really
quickly and take a look at my calendar
oh wow
okay yeah um there's a lot going on
today that is for sure but we're gonna
get it done
together it looks like we have a call
with our production company for instant
influencer season two
i have a haircut this morning as well
let me on pause
i really really need one clearly as we
can see um i upload my video at 12 and
do all the promo and then we of course
have our everyday team lunch with
everybody
it looks like my stylist will be here
later on for a few different fittings
then i have to take some instagram
photos film a few different tick tocks
and then to end off the day later on
tonight is my friend larae's birthday
party which i'm very very excited for
well let me unpause you guys
so yeah that is pretty much what my day
is going to look like today i am really
excited to take you guys along with me
for the ride in this day in the life
video but that being said there's
obviously a lot to do on the calendar
today so i feel like i need to get up
and get started right now
okay i am up and i'm awake i have my
sister's bathrobe on
and now it's time to go ew did you hear
that noise oh my god what does even
going on with this video
it is no time to get ready for the day
i'm just gonna put my phone that looks
like
i didn't even put this if anybody ever
told me that i'd be hitting 20 million
subscribers i'd tell you that you're a
joke
don't forget to rush your timetable kids
okay so now that my teeth are nice and
minty fresh and beautiful i would
normally go ahead and take a
shower which you can see i desperately
need right now and want to take but
i'm getting my hair cut today and i also
have my parties tonight so i really want
to put on a little bit of
myself tanner of course from a bond nice
and if you guys want to you can use code
james for
twenty percent off all by my favorite
product so i'm gonna put this on
and then yeah all right you guys have
all applied i know that i still look
really really busted but please
just give it a few more hours um i
decided not to go downstairs and
get started on today's video before
everything else has to get started
before that though i have to head over
to finn's
food bowl and give him some food when he
comes downstairs um we have this like
weird
shaped food dish for him because he eats
really fast fun fact for you
we got him some water as well
oh
[Music]
okay hi lewis hi luis good morning
now it is time to get started on my work
um i've been doing this for four years
now
i'm so grateful to have an incredible
team around me that helps with all other
aspects of videos but for some reason
i insist i'm doing the thumbnails still
every single time so
i'm going to just head into google drive
go into the beauty battle and then we
took some thumbnails i always go ahead
and look
through them i actually really like this
one that's a little bit uncomfortable
um a lot of these are really smiley but
i think this one was the one
yeah this feels like an actual battle so
i'm gonna go ahead and download
this one and then i'll show you guys my
thumbnail process
i don't really do too much the
thumbnails to be honest i feel like some
people like go crazy which is
more power to them that's just never
been like our you know video style we
usually just do
plain white backgrounds not a lot of
text or emojis or anything so
all right so i'm pretty sure that's done
at this point like i said super
simplistic all i did was just brighten
the colors desaturate the background do
some slight retouching on any blemishes
or
any reshaping that i like to do for my
head personally so that is pretty much
my portion of the video process
all complete oh good morning olden thank
you so much
um my amazing assistant now is when i
give it over to louis and he always does
the end screen monetization cards and
everything else like all the technical
stuff behind the scenes
okay you guys waffles almost all
complete trevor is here
good morning we're about to have our
call for season two of instant
influencer
do you guys want to say hello to the
vlog
i will film some of this but i'm gonna
mute it so y'all can't hear what we're
talking about but
season two is coming very very soon
[Applause]
great thank you guys so much can't wait
for season two
ready for 11 o'clock dustin is here
we've got some work to do mom uh you
know we've had our ups and downs one
point doesn't did turn my hair blue
and then he was fired and then i didn't
tell him for a few months but now he's
back
because he does give me a really good
[ __ ] every time some people just need
to stick to their strengths you know
laurie's here like once a week literally
well i literally as soon as my hair is
growing i feel so ugly like i
faint is necessary for me to like be
about so
okay we are all set so now you can go
upstairs shampoo it get all your natural
oils out
then we'll get you a fierce little blow
dry
okay so it's currently 11 54 as dustin
just said i have to definitely
take a shower to fix my hair so you can
style and also um wash off my tan
but we have to upload the brand new
video in about five minutes from now so
we're gonna shut down here and we're
going to get ready
with all the promo stuff so come on so
now we go
here unlisted public done close
save on the video then i tweet
the link okay now we go to instagram
stories we do the
video paste the link i feel like this
probably seems like it could be a lot
more interesting than it really is epic
video uploaded
ryan can make it look like that true
ryan is a famous editor true ryan
[Music]
that i'll post a little bit later on
today let me send a link over to
charlie and dixie actually they send
them
hi beautiful sister how are you feeling
i'm feeling good
i'm really happy to hear that hi dixie
just wanted to call you both and let you
know that the new video is not
officially up in live
awesome tv just wanted you guys to know
hope you like it i love you both
love you too will i be seeing you later
on tonight yeah i'm going
okay love you guys see you later on hope
you like the video it is now time for me
to go take a shower
wash my hand off fix my hair get it
styled then eat lunch
we're gonna switch to the james cam okay
my tan has definitely started to
develop i'm looking much darker than i
started off with it is now time to
wash it off all right you guys i have
squeaky clean out of the shower my hair
is looking
so bad this is literally like if i just
let my hair dry literally look like this
like that's concerned um wash my hand
off and it's looking
gorgeous and i'm ready to head back
downstairs to hopefully eat some lunch
and finish up my
hair and then respond to some comments
on the
well the new is doing really really well
i want to go through and text some of
you guys back i
literally love doing this if you don't
have my number text me at 310-905-8746
yes it is really me it is on my actual
phone i love going through these and
texting you guys back and it's so funny
too because literally like nobody ever
thinks that it's real so
let's say hi to some sisters chloe said
hyphens do you actually text her is
automated
hi chloe let's send a little selfie
shall we
oh hopefully that doesn't get leaked
considering looking hit by a bus
do you do you keep saying sure in your
videos that's the truth oh my god that's
from trevor actually trevor was one who
started saying
sure all the time and now we are
literally saying it nonstop sure
sure sure ceo of not answering it wow
chloe that really
[Music]
looking gorgeous thanks gorge okay done
with my haircut officially notice i'm
seeing our lovely lunch i have to also
respond to a bunch of different types of
switches and emails that i just received
whilst doing this so it's not gonna be
as fun as the lunch as i had originally
thought all right you guys we're all
done with lunch i have some nice
spicy chicken robin i said much emails
and now it's currently 1 36 p.m
or not running a little bit behind the
schedule because of all the haircuts
but i have to go into the fitting room
before i'm fitting with my stylist
leah hello oh
hi you look so cute hello so we are
going to basically put together a bunch
of different looks and outfits tonight
because i have to film a few different
tik toks and take a few different
instagram photos
and we have the party later on tonight
survival outfits
hi finn
[Music]
come here do you want to do booze
let's try our different options and see
what else we got
zipper in the front sure that's what we
call easy access
unfortunately nobody will be accessing
good one that was good you're so mean
let me have a funny joke ha ha give me
laughter track ryan
oh sure oh what a little more cold
bloody
sunglass on the table oh my god yet oh
sure
this is so good what could ever be
happening in here
yes uh yeah yeah so let's do the
remainder of the offensive we'll make a
decision for which ones are instagram
photos
friends
[Music]
sometimes in the makeup look as well
yeah yeah
yeah for the second one cut the cameras
dead ass
cut the cameras
[Music]
[Applause]
here
[Music]
okay you guys i took a little bit of a
break to eat a nice uncrustable
counter and respond to a few more emails
that i had and take a business call now
i've gone to my laptop and i'm headed
downstairs
to the studio and i'm going to get glam
for our instagram
and a few more to talk photo shoots oh
nobody's in there okay i have my laptop
with me because i want to watch a few
youtube videos that i missed for some
reason whenever i like get ready am i
the only person like i cannot listen to
music i don't know why is anybody else
that way like for some reason i just
can't focus i much prefer to listen to
like podcasts or youtube videos
which by the way literally everybody in
my life is asking me to do podcast so
that's something that you guys are
interested in
please let me know because i'm actually
definitely considering it so i'm going
to watch a few different youtube videos
probably some minecraft stuff and
let's get ready are you going to film
like an actual video we can just
give you a good mirror too true oh my
god i can't wait to show them the actual
studio
on sneak peek you guys okay let's get
ready
all right you guys i just finished my
glam process it is currently 509 p.m so
i was down here for about an hour and a
half i watched some minecraft videos on
youtube catching up on my hermitcraft
series and now it is time to go upstairs
i just did a fun little cute neutral
look for today just so i can film tech
talks and take photos in a few different
outfits but i am going to come back down
later on
tonight and add a pop of color to match
my outfit for larry's party
so let's go so that's why i feel like
that works really well in the carousel
i think you should do both though like i
think you should this moment though on
the carousel with orange should make the
outfit look
so much better um because i look good
like this
[Music]
so this is the first look for ig super
super cute and we're also going to pack
the
next outfit that we showed earlier today
and we're going to change in the car
because our photo location is apparently
right across the street according to mr
lewis who did the locations
you look like you underdog so we're now
going to head downstairs into the car
and go take some
[Music]
she said i'm a natural tan mama come on
trevor trevor said instagram boyfriend
okay
two bottoms do make a top oh god
oh that is cute wow the lighting is so
pretty here
look at that gorgeous smiling lady that
looks like chris jenner at 16.
let's do a few more squattings i want to
i want a little bit more i need more
side profile once like we got glasses
oh yeah that's the best
we're getting changed in the middle of
the road currently
oh
maybe we're going to cut the camera for
this cut the camera we got into the new
outfit in
the car which was alarming considering
the amount of people that were staring
at me the entire time and walking
by see the problem is right now it looks
gorgeous but the sun
which is back here is not really like
out it's a very very cloudy day which is
definitely
good for some photography but not really
for makeup photography
so we're gonna try our best and see what
we can come up with
give us an arch give us a big arch
all right okay so we're back from the
photo shoot i just filmed three more
tick tocks and stockpiled for this week
which will be really good because we
have another busy week
up ahead with more filming stuff cassie
just got here ready for the party
tonight jesus is fully glam now i have
to decide what i actually want to
wear and look like for the party i was
thinking about wearing this like offer
that i haven't added a fun little like
pop of orange but i honestly feel like i
feel like i just like
need to do like natural which i honestly
love like i love that i've been
throwing less makeup and stuff so i'm
thinking that maybe like my more natural
moment should be just like a simple
outfit like sweat and a sweatshirt
instead of all this i don't know
you guys this is the finished fit for
larry's party tonight he literally just
texted in the group shot saying that
it's an all block party which
unfortunately eliminated my other outfit
but kind of made me go like that anyway
which is
great i'm wearing an oversized black
blenciaga hoodie uh these biker swords
which are also blunts yaga but they're
fun fact
kids just regular shorts but i wear them
as [ __ ] shorts and i'm nice and tucked
so you can't see anything don't worry
and then just the jordan one pandas it
is currently about 7
30. we have 30 minutes until we're going
to leave and head over to the hype house
with all my friends
and yeah it's been a crazy day so far
but we are almost to the homeless church
it is currently 8 32 p.m and larry's
party starts in approximately one hour
but it is all the way down to hollywood
so we're going to be running fashionably
late because
we are currently on the way to a lovely
dinner at california pizza kitchen not
sponsored but really wish it was
um but it should be a fun night you guys
were here at dinner i ordered a barbecue
with chicken
salad louis trevor both eating there you
go miss lena and miss anthony
jesus and cassie and laura are those
over there but anyway we're gonna eat
our dinner and hopefully munch fast and
get the bill because then we have to
move yeah i can't believe i just said
that
we have to go home and get into the
height house wow this escalator is
currently broken and we're having to
walk down it when it's not moving
i hate doing that more than anything in
the entire world that scared me
dinner is done checks have been paid and
we are now running late for larry's
party at the high pass we got to
call our ubers now get back to my house
get the gifts that we got and our cards
and then get in an uber oh my god not
again
it's not moving this is just wrong okay
don't laura don't touch me um i will
film when we get to work okay guys so we
literally have like three seconds
to run inside and quickly get all of our
stuff together and now we're in our uber
on the way to the
house that completes our work day
officially but now it is time to have a
little bit of fun and of course i'm
gonna take you guys along
how's it going absolutely not mr james
hi hollywood facts
we need the tea from you oh i don't
deliver any tea
i drink coffee oh who is the super hot
guy
that you would mention in your vlog oh i
would never tell you i can't tell you
that
people said it was noah it was not know
about it no it was not known about so if
it wasn't noah then we
like the first initial or the i would
never owe somebody like that because
obviously like a private situation like
i was super super nice
okay i was just more talking about the
experience of it overall rather than the
actual person
this is my uber i believe okay okay
thank you so
thank much james oh it's time to go home
okay so we're in the car i am currently
working on
oh my god get a ball pop out oh my god
it's a little bitter lace
okay
[Music]
anyway it is currently 108 in the
morning this has been one of the longest
days my entire life but it was
very very fun how did y'all feel about
the party we're in the clock
um same sure sure sure
today's been an amazing day it's been a
productive day it's been a fun day it is
so close to being over i don't even know
what i'm saying at this point
bye see you in a second you guys are
home coming into my room
there we go okay i'm so exhausted my
makeup honestly still
looks let's see why does my makeup look
so
good still are you kidding okay wow i
don't even want to take it off now
it's so late i'm gonna put you guys in
my little tripod right here and it is
time to
take this makeup off now normally i
would just grab you know my regular
makeup wipes but
i did want to share something very
exciting with you guys and that is the
brand new
one size and makeup remover by patrick
starr his brand new makeup line
just launched which is so very excited
patrick i am so proud of you this is not
sponsored but i haven't really been
dying to try these out because
they look so good okay i'm gonna use the
mist and i'm going to just spray this
that is it's crazy
how fast that what is in this how did
that even do that let's put these makeup
wipes and test that oh my god i'm so
excited for this okay
oh bruh oh my god it's coming off so
easily all right you guys that is my
makeup completely removed
using patrick starr's brand new one size
go off makeup removing
kit i am literally obsessed with these
and i'm not just saying it because i am
friends with patrick
although i do love him and i'm going to
tell you guys to support him regardless
these products are so bomb they did such
a good job of taking my makeup off i
love
how big these wipes are like this is so
good
you guys should definitely check it out
and support an amazing artist like
patrick you need to go off with your
makeup i'm pretty sure at this point
that is pretty much like all i have left
for today's
video i really hope that you guys
enjoyed this fun little day in the life
with me
i woke up this morning bright and early
and said that today is going to be
jam-packed and it definitely
was but it was so productive we got i
think like four or five different tick
tocks filmed which is
amazing i'll pick out two really good
instagram photos and i also took some
photos tonight at the party as
well which is just a super fun way to
end the day and i really really hope
that you guys enjoyed coming along with
me
um if you like these like more vloggy
style videos please
let me know i'm sorry if this like
wasn't the best this is obviously very
new to me i'm trying my hardest and i
just really hope you guys enjoyed
if you did please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below
and share love and support it really
does mean so much to me and also of
course click that subscribe button come
join the sisterhood i would love to have
you in the family
and also click that bell icon so you get
notified every time i upload a brand
new oops hold on if you want to follow
me on my social media journey all my
social media accounts will be linked
right here around the screen and also if
you want to text me on my personal phone
number uh my number is
310-905-8746 it's where i can send you
guys direct updates on new photos videos
merch and
so much more and yes it is really me so
send me a text i would love to
say hello oh shoot i need to go pick a
shout out one second
all right i'm back this video sister
shout out goes to sister bella thank you
so much love for always following and
supporting i love you so so so much and
if you'd like to be the next videos
sister shout out don't forget to always
retweet with videos like live on twitter
and also share my youtube
post notifications all right you guys oh
my god i thought this video was never
going to end but i really really hope
you enjoyed it i think that is all i
have for today
i love you and i will see you in the
next one
good night
[Music]
you