oh that's on camera let's go
perfect intro class hi guys its James
Charles welcome back to our YouTube
channel first of all I just want to say
holy crap thank you so much for 300,000
subscribers
wow that is literally so crazy and now I
feel like every single time I make a
video I have to make some type of little
snippet in the in chart where I say
thank you for some very very large
obscene amount of subscribers so that's
really cool you guys aren't slaying the
subscribing game thank you so much for
all the support on my videos as you guys
know and I said a lot of times already
so far I'm so excited to see like where
we keep going I feel like every video is
getting better and better so that's cool
also I have a microphone on hopefully
the audio is a lot better because you
guys have been dragging me for it so I
ordered a microphone so hopefully you
know I am dedicated to say the least
anyways we've been banging out tutorials
left and right so many makeup videos so
many different types of fun things but
what we have yet to do is a Q&A so I
'post on Instagram asked you guys for a
bunch of questions and now we're going
to answer them and let you know a little
bit more about me James Charles you
already know who I am or else II won't
be on this channel alright I have all
the questions ready on my phone we're
going to go ahead and get started
Brian asked what do you look for in a
guy a pulse any tips on contouring your
nose um cross your fingers before yet
and hope for the best
Dana asked what's your favorite snapchat
filter this one
Alicia asked is it really hard managing
a career and school while they're in two
separate places it definitely could be a
lot easier but it also could be a lot
harder
luckily my administrators and teachers
are all like super on board with
everything that I'm doing so they're
helping me kind of make it through
without having like emotional trauma
Tiffany asks what's your favorite thing
about your life now and how has becoming
basically famous affected you probably
the coolest thing about like everything
that has happened to me recently has
been getting to meet all of you guys in
like public places like Laos out to
dinner last night with friends and like
15 people like came up to me was like
you take the pictures I was like oh wow
I just want to enjoy my orange chicken
in peace but it was definitely like
really really cool to be able to like
see you guys and see everybody who's
supporting me so that's probably my
favorite thing about it
oh imagine my phone dying in the middle
of an Q&A oh it actually just died as I
said that that's fake Sam asked how long
does it take to create a simple look or
even one of your special ones well it
definitely depends like I threw this to
and probably like an hour but my like
more intricate ones can definitely take
up to like seven hours of my longest one
for Halloween this past year so I could
definitely be a little bit of a lengthy
process to say the least but if like
obviously what I love to do so I'll just
sit down hang out with friends
FaceTime people listen to music just to
like keep the time going but usually
it's like oh good time
clearly it's a good time or else I would
not be studying seven hours do Esther
says will you sing me a song you lovely
man oh no Maria asked James tell us
top or bottom well Maria when it comes
to my eyelashes my top lashes are
already pretty long so I would
definitely say that I prefer the bottom
and your ass how do you say happy and
confident in this world of haters love
you James Oh Andrew I love you as well
that's a great question that I get asked
all the time I really try hard to not
let hate bother me and I know that's
like not the best way to just be like oh
yeah don't let it get to you because a
lot of people can't really do that but
for me it's just like everybody has a
right to their opinion and that's
totally okay if you don't like me I
don't care also now that Instagram has
like hate comment filtering I have a
bunch of like target nasty words filter
it out so it's you can't comment them so
at this point if you do a hate comment
on my photos I'm like slow clap for you
because you really put in a lot of
effort so you must be really really mad
and it's a great thing to be opinionated
these days arrow asked what you hear a
flavor of ramen pork
people always say chicken I like the
program in JJ's ASMR channel coming in
2017 Christina asked how do you get your
teeth so white okay so this is actually
a question I get all the time it's
actually when I post my only pictures on
Instagram that I promise it's not the
face tune wait until I worked very very
hard for these babies right here I had
braces for a long period of time and I'm
not gonna let them get ugly and crusty
and old now I've been using a teeth
whitening kit from Smile Sciences now
for a few weeks I have not talked about
it yet because I really want to make
sure that it actually worked before I
went and promoted anything because you
guys know that I never want to promote
like a crappy product and I definitely
was extremely skeptical before in trying
this but I am very excited to say that
actually like really does actually work
my teeth look very good as you can see
hello right here there's meat it comes
with two little trays and like teeth
whitening gel and then
the classic blue lights that you just
and you let it sit and then you take it
off and bam your teeth are a whole lot
lighter
it is cruelty-free vegan USA made and
even though you're shopping a thing into
your mouth doesn't hurt no good catch
like I said I was extremely skeptical at
first but after trying it really does
work so it's like a great product of
course if you guys know me I emailed
spinal Sciences and I asked for a coupon
code shocker you can now use code J
Charles to get the entire set for only a
$29 definitely would recommend check it
out if you want to um yeah so that is
that on that Lilly asked why does James
Charles are makeup like when you get
married your wife will make a really bad
choice well sister to I have news for
you are you Virgin Mary asked ah
Stephanie asked will this be the last
question you ask yes thank God we're
done alright guys I think that is all
the questions we have for today
definitely some interesting ones and
some great ones as well as so I have
learned a little bit more about me about
being said if you guys did love this
video don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and subscribe if
you have not already I post videos every
single week and I'd love to have you
join the family if you'd like to follow
me on my crazy makeup journey don't
forget to follow all my social media my
Instagram and Twitter are both just
James Charles and my snapchat is James
Charles with an extra ask after Charles
okay guys thank you so much for watching
and I will see you next time bye