hi sisters before we jump into today's
video i wanted to let you know that
yesterday was the launch of the sister's
apparel classroom
collection we have four super cute
limited edition
color block sets so head on over and
shop before they're gone and sisters
dashabarrel.com
hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
normally in my intros i tell you guys
what we're going to be doing in today's
video but judging by the title
and my voice i think you already know
what's going on this morning i was
sitting with my team talking about video
ideas
and lewis was like james you need to do
an asmr video
and i was like i already did and then i
realized
i didn't so now we're here in case you
don't know what asmr is it stands for
autonomous sensory meridian response oh
look at me
a lot of different people love watching
asmr videos for different reasons
some people it helps them calm down and
help some people fall asleep
it reduces anxiety and a lot of times as
well there are certain
sounds
and there's certain sounds oh my god
there's certain sounds that give people
the tingles and can really help them out
which i think is
super cool i've watched a lot of asmr
videos i respect the art i respect the
youtubers for me personally
they don't give me those like tingly
sensations i wish that they did but who
knows i'm always open to trying things
and maybe in today's video i'll
experience it so if you want to
unwind if you want to relax and just get
glam together and asmr keep on watching
all right sisters we're going to go
ahead and get started of course the
first step to my makeup routine is
always going to be a primer
and today i'm going to grab the milk
hydro grip
what don't say that this needs to be
relaxing
i don't know oh
and i'm just going to rub this all over
my face
oh
i'm using some dragon beauty color
corrector to really get rid of my beard
here i would rather not as a viewer that
would make me rather uncomfortable
water bottle okay
that's a good one i'm just gonna take
some powder
and set that in place
patting it it's gonna be time for some
foundation and i'm gonna mix together a
few my favorites
the first one is going to be
this is dior air blush
they're gonna love that one
three pumps then i'm also going to add
in just a little bit of the maybelline
dream radiant liquid
i got this from gg id my dmx celebrities
pick my makeup video
if you have not seen that video yet make
sure you go click
right up here okay i'm just going to
take a brush and i'm really going to
blend that together i'm just going to
work on applying this foundation
really just blending all the colors in
together
let's full coverage that's okay if i
could use me for foundation i would
i'm gonna use my beauty blender
hey some artists is that what they're
called that's such a cute name to be
honest
what are some of your favorite sounds
that give you the tingles
like sexual
oh what is that like that you're getting
a facial i can honestly see if that will
be really relaxing
well look at how nice that foundation
looks right there with like that harsh
line i didn't even do that on purpose
that's good i'm gonna grab my fenty
beauty contour stick
and i'm just gonna take this stick and
start adding some color to the face
use a rare beauty foundation brush i've
been loving this brush recently for
foundation and cream contour it's
gorgeous oops
i'm just going to blend this in
okay thanks
i don't know if i was waiting to see if
there'll be bubbles i quickly need to
respond to this
snapchat
[Music]
stop taking my own
[Applause]
was actually good now it's time for some
blush so i'm going to grab
my favorite of recently which has been
the rare beauty blush in the shade of
bliss
this is also one of the recommended
products from an assessor selena gomez
and the damning celebrities video and i
have loved this ever since i tried it
out
finally i'm gonna grab some tarte shape
tape concealer
that's stupid
when i first started doing makeup i used
to use literally like an ounce concealer
every time doing the full-on like
stripes painting everywhere but now i've
really realized that less
is more dab dab dab dab dab it's not
good
if i give you the tingles yeah yeah
really
yeah okay okay this is looking beautiful
now i'm gonna cut my powder
okay and i'm gonna grab my powder puff
just to
puff this powder in place
it's okay the powder tastes good it
tastes like beaches
beautiful
on to the next step now i'm just going
to reinforce my contours and blushes and
highlights
quickly using a little bit of powder
[Music]
oh
why is it tricky
i just need to drive my settings by
really quickly
can you hear that all right sisters i'm
back
i decided to do my other brow off camera
because honestly i was getting bored and
whispering is a lot more tiring than i
would have thought
i'm back and we're gonna finish up the
rest of my makeup routine i'm gonna grab
my eyelash curler from mac
cosmetics that's probably not very
satisfying
and i'm just going to give my lashes a
nice girl same thing on this eye
and then i'm going to grab my benefit
roller lash mascara
i'm just going to carefully rub this
through the lashes making sure to not
get any on my eyelids
wiggle wiggle wiggle i was going to glue
on lashes but honestly
my regular lashes are looking so cute
today i don't even know if i need them
what do you think
do you think that i should add lashes
yes
or no yes
it's looking gorgeous gorgeous
the end is near you guys give me a few
steps left
so next i'm going to grab my morphe
prepping set
and then using my palette i'm just going
to dig into a little bit of face
just like this that was a little much
for a natural makeup look
oh my god what am i doing i think i
forgot how to do makeup
i'm adding a sound effect since it
doesn't already have one
the end is near i'm not going to take my
colourpop lip liner in the shade curvy
and line my lips
what then i'm just going to pop on some
gloss from lunar beauty
miss manny mua's line miss manny
that's a good one tastes like
cupcakes
can you imagine and last but not least
i'm gonna finish up with a little bit
more
morphe setting spray
all right says terrace and with that
being sisters this is his head
i think that is this asmr makeup
tutorial oh complete i know i went for a
little bit more of a natural
everyday glam makeup look today but i'm
still feeling very very beautiful
and i really wanted to focus on relaxing
together
i really hope that you guys enjoyed this
video and got some
tingles i did not but if you enjoyed it
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below to share love and
support if you have not already make
sure you click that big red subscribe
button
and come join the sisterhood and finally
click that
bell icon so you get notified whenever i
upload a brand new video if you'd like
to follow me on my social media journey
all my social media accounts are gonna
be linked right here around the screen
and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number
for new updates on videos photos merch
and so much more
you can text me at 310-905-8746
this
thank you so much love for always
following and supporting and if you
would like to be the next videos
sister shout out don't forget to always
retweet my video links when they go live
on
twitter all right sisters i think that
is all i have i love you
and i will see you in the next one
bye
you