hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel this
is the second time in something a video
intro in a car because we literally put
this video together so fast I cannot
believe I'm sure you've seen it the
title of this video down below I am
about to take a dance lesson with the
queen of dance herself Abby Lee Miller
now how do we get to this place you're
asking let me give you a very brief
synopsis so I have my Dance Moms fan I
am not afraid to admit it it is my
guilty pleasure I love the show I've
been watching it since season one I'm
mom the dancing of the drama
the moms Abby it's just like television
gold top siren is so rude a few nights
ago I was watching the season 8 finale
and there was a fight going on between
the bombs in the dressing room and I
noticed one of the moms slammed and
makeup palette shut for emphasis during
her fight and upon further investigation
a little bit of a I realize more people
I said oh yes Ashlee you close that
palate girl I was just watching one of
the recount from one of the fights last
night
and I wanted to swim inter and what we
just noticed look oh yes Ashlee close
that palate while you fight Oh Stacy
yeah thank you for that closer I posted
it on my story cause I just thought it
was so cool and a literally within a few
hours every single one of the Dance Moms
of girls and cast members and Abby
herself do young me saying how lonesome
if they love me and my makeup which
literally made my entire day I could not
stop smiling a few hours ago this
morning Abby Lee Miller herself GI me I
was like oh my god we should you're
saying together I want to teach you how
to dance and I said good luck with that
because I literally cannot dance to save
my life but I could not pass up this
opportunity I want to take a lesson from
the Queen Abby Lee herself if there's
anybody that can teach me how to not
have two left feet it is her I heard
that a few of the girls from the show
are gonna be coming to I'm so excited to
meet them and say hello and I'm gonna
take you guys how they started me
because it's probably gonna be a really
really embarrassing and I can't wait to
get yelled at by Abby
oh right
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
very for now like you should yeah so
feet together and you're just gonna jump
[Music]
now you just learned the transfer your
weight your one from the other and
that's what dancing is so now you
understand there's something copying
levy so when you jump do a straddle jump
for us just stand straight yeah okay
when you you took up two feet and later
on to feel Lily do an arabesque okay
parking that's all she took off my front
and she stabilized and just for our
camera that's leading from one quick to
the other part so what you just started
learning is like the building blocks
know you're gonna do squat to touch the
floor on one count you're gonna struggle
jump touch on two three and stride on
tour
[Music]
okay you keep your ready squat
that's what if you've been sued she's
going to come back this is hard
[Applause]
[Music]
right foot back and that's what we're
going to step on that first weight
thank when they're due for your walk
score work really sass it up watch the
girls and one two three we're gonna take
a giant step the thumb right out to the
side and we're going to reach up in the
air look up and then touch the floor
done boom then we go to the other way up
and yeah okay let's just feel like a tip
watch watch jitka up and down up and
down
five six seven eight
[Applause]
five six in one two five six seven just
you one two three four and just you one
two three four reach up and down up
then she would you just wanna grim will
get a walk walk cross walk dick ready
let's walk to the right and walk cross
walk Kentucky no way we're gonna go to
the left and walk walk ready 1 2 3 touch
1 2 3 & 1 2 3
[Music]
[Applause]
so your weight is on your left your
right foot straight and we're going to
circle to the right
[Music]
and all we're doing is making you swim
so pick your right foot up and sprint
together let's do that Circle Circle
[Music]
[Applause]
into him he's the star yeah yeah what'd
you turn be there so you need to be like
like you're the star this is your no
[Music]
five
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't even think that like this is
harder than I thought I would because I
knew this is gonna be so I probably felt
like I'm really trying to do this and
I'm proud of myself that I'm not like
completely messing it up
I could obviously be doing a whole lot
better but I'm like actually glad that
I've been able to like relatively
memorized the choreography and the
routine even though it's this is fun
though I'll be such a good teacher and
the girls are literally so nice oh I am
DC team John yeah Wow
Lillian Presley could never should we go
out ready duck down duck down
[Applause]
[Music]
for your similar costly also Jeannie now
the town's right now and all the sisters
that you and the to support the Denton
journey all right we have a lot more and
he's he's gonna go be lazy and soak in
the hot tub you think that he would go
practice in Ellison tomorrow morning you
better be here you better know
all right you guys beer back home now
after the dance class but I'm actually
filming this outro a few days later I
already felt mess but I wanted to redo
it right before I'm uploading this video
because you will not believe what my
body has went through in the past few
days at this point I don't even really
know if I can believe it I like very
very confused because doing the routine
was very very hard but it was hard
because I'm not good at like hand I put
full body coordination at memorizing a
routine like that and being able to put
on a performance at the same time is
very very hard I gave it the dancers so
much props it was also very very hot in
there so I was sweating in my entire
face and makeup off but physically the
actual like steps were not hard on my
body but for some reason I woke up the
next morning so sore but over the past
two days it is got so much I like people
literally barely even walk and I am
getting very very worried i sat in the
hot tub for several hours I've tried one
of the muscle rollers whoa my friends it
gives me massages
and my knees are just not exactly
functioning so I'm not sure if this is
normal because this is my first time
dancing but this is literally the most
pain I've ever ever been in and this
just goes to show how incredible and how
much work and love and physical strength
that goes into the actual art of dancing
I went to this challenge today already
having have so much respect for
everybody in the dance industry
everybody from the dancers the
choreographers and the actual teachers
as well there's so much that goes into
putting together a beautiful routine and
just getting to kind of see the behind
the scenes process and be a part of the
job 1 for a few seconds was so much fun
and just maybe respect it that much more
I'm very very grateful to both Abby Lee
Miller and the Dance Moms
and the girls that were there in the
studio helping me out and being so so so
patient with me I'm horrified to know
how much I would have gotten yelled at
if I wasn't a youtuber and I was an
actual dance student Abby's an
incredible teacher and it's really
obvious that she has so much passion for
these girls is wanting them to be the
best interest they possibly can be and
who knows maybe I could be a performer
one day probably not with that
performance that you guys just watched
but practice makes perfect with just
about anything if you guys did enjoy
this videos today please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below it
really means so much to me and also
click that big red subscribe button and
come join this sisterhood I would love
to have you in the family we are 16
million sisters strong also make sure
you click that Bell icon so you get an
ovation every time I upload our
brand-new video here on YouTube if you
like to follow me on my makeup turn you
can follow me on instagram twitter and
twitch or all just james Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes time
staff is James Charles so that extra ass
after Charles this videos sister Santa
goes do hi sis James thank you so much
love for always following and supporting
noir I love you it so so so much and if
you like to the next videos sister shout
out don't forget to always reach me with
another single live on Twitter and also
to my youtube at post notifications all
right you guys thank you so much
watching this videos today I love you so
much and I will see you in the next one
or rather see you at nationals
[Music]