hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
Before we jump into today's a brand new
video we are not going to notice that
this finger now but what we are going to
notice I said that that I am wearing a
maroon at sister's hoodie the color that
you guys have been asking for for
literally over a year now and I am so
excited to say it is finally here for
the fall season this hoodie and along
with the original taupe hoodie that was
oh this stain is not included this will
not come on yours I promise to buddies
are finally up and live on sisters -
apparel calm right now for you guys to
go a shop okay all of the video I'm just
gonna jump right into this video because
you guys have obviously already seen the
title and the thumbnail were adopting a
puppy and I am so beyond pumped it's not
even funny oh my god we've been thinking
about this and planning this for
literally almost idea now I almost
actually adopted during a Christmas time
of last year but with the palette coming
out I knew I was gonna be traveling up
so much and I really wanted to wait for
my a kind of life and work schedule to
calm down a little bit to make sure that
I was able to give at the right amount
of love and attention to a popper
joining the family and we finally have a
few quiet months and it is the absolute
perfect time to start looking at
shelters and try to adopt a new member
into the family I've already been
through raising and training a puppy
once it is quite the challenge but I am
so excited and ready to do it again and
have him be a long time a family member
and a best friend here in the sister
household and hopefully you guys will
want to come along on the journey with
us
burgundy spending the next few days
going to a bunch of shelters all over
the Los Angeles area and a few different
adoption specials going on to see if we
can find perfect pupper take them home
with us and if you guys wanna join us on
that journey keep on watching
[Music]
originating your hair at the Los Angeles
County Animal Care Center about to go
look at some of the puffers we're on the
way upstate earlier this morning and we
called and they do have a few different
pups that we were very very interested
in and that could have an amazing home
with us at the house so we're going to
go and make the stop and hopefully get
to play with them a little bit obviously
we're gonna go in and see the dogs and
we want to make sure that we have a
really good at connection and at the
puppies like us and trust us and that we
like them and wanna cuddle indeed best
friends so hopefully we end up taking
your dog home today but if not obviously
want to wait for the absolute perfect
match that'll be for us but who knows he
could be right here in the shelter and
I'm some fitted to go see so all the
puppies that are actually all the same
and then I think that one's tiny where
that one's tight we'll see I warned
stick those in Hershey
yeah Big Momma we call all Don's mommies
no ID why we started with our dog yeah
and like Oh your other people call their
dogs but your 20 Stefan calls his dog
vomit yeah
we have no idea where they started from
but
I don't know why I'm really feeling this
alright you guys see this - oh the
little poppers and I think that we have
a four or five we're gonna play with
we're not exactly sure because I know
one of them did just get spayed or
neutered so you might be in the clinic
and then also one of them says that
they're not gonna be available until
literally midnight on the 13th which is
in 8 hours from now so fingers crossed -
and let us get a chance to play with the
little peppers but every teacher
he really wants to pee everywhere
he's an acrobatic Seth is not interested
in you don't worry a lot of people are
in no all right you guys so we're
currently on the way home from the
shelter and unfortunately we are coming
home empty-handed like I said that we
are not an idea brush we want to make
sure we find the perfect match for our
family oh wow
okay so the three-year-old of life
pitbull that we had a chance to play
with really wanted no part of us at all
let's be honest what definitely did hurt
because he was so cute and cuddly in his
kennel but when it came to actually mind
exploring he literally just wanted no
part of us which is totally fine
obviously the vibe has to be right and
he was three years old as well which
there's nothing wrong with he so wanted
to give it a shot but we would prefer to
raise a puppy from puppy to dog and as
well we did ask about the other puppies
that I thought I had a special
connection we have like Snickers and
Zuma and Hershey's you just have to say
his name that was Emma and I firstly we
were not even able to play with those
puppies because they already had people
that were said to about them and a long
waiting list of people just in case that
adoption person didn't work out so all I
can wish is that those homeys go to a
really really amazing home when they do
get adopted and like I said we are in no
rush it is really about finding the
perfect pump to come home with us and we
wanna make sure it's a good vibe we have
about an hour-and-a-half drive home and
on the way home we're just going to do a
little bit more research into some local
shelters hopefully ones that aren't and
one half to two hours away we have
pretty much today tomorrow a on the
whole weekend dedicated to our puppy
search so who knows what'll happen in
tomorrow
good morning sisters hi hello James here
it is Saturday morning so few days after
our first vlog footage clips and
illuminae are currently on the way to
tomorrow because every single weekend
the world knew that we were I guess this
weekend yes it was a sarcastic okay well
I love waving you on and then going
anyways I people do not know how to
drive in Los Angeles but we've been - no
II know that's a cupcake truck
thank you all right you guys we're back
in the car again and pets Murr was a
bust
they're supposed to be having this like
major adoption event all weekend long
but there was literally only four dogs
so you might try to check out a few
other pet smart locations today I did
tell some my close friends that we were
planning on adopting a puffer into the
family and I'm super super pumped
because I just got a call from one of
that lover and so depends who are
waiting for the other ones to get there
saying that their neighbor's dog gave
birth a few weeks ago to a litter of
puppies and they are ready to go up for
adoption
they are not a breeder family they just
literally want to find a good homes for
them because they cannot take care of
all of them and we're gonna see if they
have time for us to go see them today
this literally could be perfect I'm so
excited right now I'm trying not to get
my hopes up just in case so you're there
see you guys and other adoption of it or
at their house all right you guys I have
a little bit of an update we weren't
really having much luck out the actual
shelters when it comes to hobbies so
getting a call from my family who just
wanted to find good homes for these pups
was like literally the absolute best
case scenario and so we drove over and
they asked us not to come in the house
which we obviously respected because we
just played with the whole litter for
like a good two hour trying to figure
out which one we absolutely liked best
and this angel right here come running
back to us we actually had up treats for
him and we were trying to teach him how
to sit and it seemed like he picked it
up really really quickly as well so
you're a smart little pup I get to go to
that store and pick up a collar and a
good food and the kennel and a whole
bunch of things but
he's perfect
that's the angle I want I want to see
him on this video and let us know
whatever dog you think he looks for him
he does have all the shots as well thank
God we do have to get them spayed or
neutered but hi buddy a little chicken
chop from our heart is pretty much fault
we got a collar a leash dog food treats
bulls and peppy pubs a little scene or
remover in case he decides to make a
mess some a few little choice we can
shove a little peanut butter in there so
it has no nice snacks some first stuff
because he is already shutting quite a
lot so nice dog brush the crates lots of
things we have a bargain food already
from the family that we adopted him from
but they do not actually sell the exact
type of food here if you order that from
Amazon the second week at home pressure
I can sponsor but hash tag really please
should be but I think that's everything
so little puppy is in the and we're
gonna check out and ahead home and let
him stay house the first time
[Music]
that's Auggie's me-byo in so bringing
this up and because he needs to have a
second water it is just a suicide look
at the little trot oh that's a good trot
oh let's go outside you won't go
anywhere unless both of us are good boy
scent scent
okay
good boy that's so good the first time
you went to the bathroom in this house
was completely outside oh yeah I think
he's done with stairs for now that was
not a that was not a dog park that was a
human park that was you probably smells
worse
we've already noticed he starts crying
as soon as either one of us were inside
okay
[Music]
all right II know you go to stay outside
booty you had to get trained he's gonna
be inside for the first few weeks but we
have to train him as quickly as possible
I deal with this a lot when we were
growing up with training my dog I'll
need to do is just bring him outside and
make sure that he learned to pee outside
instead and we can just clean it up
carpets can be replace the wall puppies
however it cannot be so it's fine oh are
you still so cute like the amazing
youtuber than I am but the puppy is his
first official meal with us we gave him
like a cup and a few little extra
kibbles of food and then a little bit of
warm water this one's nice and bushy on
his teeth and he literally ran I went up
to the bolt and sort of eating which is
amazing it year she just a little part
up and his bear over there for a good
like alimony and Louise came out the
house we have some folks that my
oversight that little poplar get to meet
but the first time and I think it's
going on so you're basing somewhere he's
loving the house
[Music]
okay guys it is the first night with our
popper and he is downstairs in the crate
and he is oh this breaks my heart but
crate training is so so so important we
are almost the time but of course we
teach I will have had to go to meetings
and total day it's most important that
he is crate trained and protected and
feels like his crate is like his safe
place whenever we are not here obviously
right now it's like very scary for him
but once you get to sleep it's all right
so we cave and we brought him upstairs
basically what's crazy is every time
either me or Luis I get within his eye
sight he stops crying which is like
really crazy he's definitely already
attached which is incredible but the
last thing that I want to do is like
create separation anxiety for him on the
first day especially so we were keeping
him definitely in the crate for the
night but he's here he can see us
he's still being a grumpy and quite
every few seconds but it's definitely
not nearly as bad with the holy instant
[Music]
oh you guys we were on a date to it with
the pepper we just got home off to a
little while he was in the crate and he
is literally solo with all the training
and behavior so far he has not gone to
the bathroom once and his crate which is
made me so happy he's only gone to the
bathroom twice in the house like I said
excuse me oh that's my entire arm oh he
is teething clearly as you can see we
did get him a bone and he's been tight
with that but when the bone is not
renewable on earth which is not
acceptable he's doing it really really
well where the potty trainer he wins
anyone's well side which we will
obviously teach who knew about that but
for now if they cease notify
I don't think he's potty-trained because
he's definitely not but like he's doing
really really well that's still my
finger we were actually loving him we
were hovering some friends over tonight
to meet him for the first time and we're
about to feed him some dinner so it's
really good so far
[Music]
[Laughter]
we tried let's read this one come on
boo-boo you got it
[Music]
you're watching James's livestream
you're watching minecraft Monday yeah
all right you guys thank you so much for
watching today is a brand new video with
our brand new family member he's
definitely made it a very very crazy and
hectic at the past few days but I am so
excited for the journey ahead of us like
a Hello okay like I said he is doing
really well this training up so far but
he has a very very long way to go as he
grows up and I will obviously make sure
to keep you guys posted on all my social
media accounts so you can watch him grow
old and I'm so excited for the journey
that we had ahead of us and I hope that
you guys are excited to come along with
that as well speaking that makes you
guys able to comment down below and let
us know what you think his name should
be
we definitely have a few ideas that we
really really like but we are not
starting so learn any of them and we are
really excited to hear what you guys
have to say and what you think this
little puppy should be named if you guys
enjoy today's brand new video don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and sister support us it really
does mean the absolute world to me and
help us help quite a lot and also if you
have not already make sure to click that
big red subscribe button down below
come join this sister we love to have
you in the family along with a new puppy
and also put the bell icon so you
academic each every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on my makeup journey can follow me on
instagram at twitter and twitch or I'll
just jam charles and they sad talk for
more behind the scenes I thought is
James frost the next to ask after
Charles I'm actually so excited that I
now get to post on sets of him because
we've been it's taking them and storing
them for the past we're gonna have now
any find it to be so cure I'm gonna comb
this videos sister shot it goes to
sister
Morgana thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting I love you
so so so much and if you like through
the next videos a sister shadow ifr like
hey don't forget to always reach it when
video is gonna go live on Twitter and
also to my youtube at post on vacations
all right you guys that is all we have
for today's a brand new video thank you
so much for watching
and I will see you and at the next one
[Music]