hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel first
today's that I have something super
super fun plan that I'm actually very
excited to do I don't know if a lot of
you guys know this but before I actually
was the beauty guru it was doing makeup
on myself as a full-time job I actually
was doing makeup on a bunch of my
friends from school
back home in my little salon and my
basement made by my dad and I really
really missed doing client work so so
much and for me I'm planning to do my
own makeup all the time I really don't
get the feeling or pleasure of being on
the other end of the brush getting my
glam done and getting to enjoy the work
of other artists I definitely have a
very distinct style of makeup that I
always do it myself I plan a shadows a
certain way I contour my face a certain
way I face to the certain way as well
and I was definitely bringing something
about different ways that I can get
gland by other people and I came to the
conclusion that the perfect way to do it
will be to get some awesome
transformations so I booked a play with
that the three most popular spots that
people go to get their makeup done for
different events being Mac Sephora and
Ulta and I went and I got my makeup done
at all three and I'm gonna show you guys
default transformation I wanted to make
this into a little bit of a challenge or
a miniseries so this is gonna be the
first video like I said of a bunch of
different transformation videos for each
different transformation I'm gonna give
each artist the same exact photo I
picked out this one of Jacqueline Hale I
figured this like warm tone bronzy
smokey eye is the perfect look for this
upcoming fall if features like smoked
out shadow which is definitely not the
easiest technique in the world gold
glitter as well as a lot of highlighter
definite full coverage skin as well as a
dark vampy lip I think that this look is
a really great challenge for us because
it's definitely not the easiest thing in
the world but it's definitely not too
hard as well I'm gonna give the same
exact picture to each artist and they're
gonna do their best job to recreate it
on me using the products sold at that
particular store and after each
registration we're gonna come right back
here and I'm gonna show you guys the
finished look obviously then we're gonna
talk about my experience as a whole how
the actual look turned out how close the
look was to the original photo and
finally what I recommend you to go there
to get your makeup done like I said for
today's the first makeover I booked an
appointment at Sephora and Hollywood so
let's head over there right now but
before this video starts make sure to go
give it a big thumbs up down below if
you're excited alright guys without
further ado let's hop in an uber and get
over to Sephora
[Music]
so immediately walking into somewhere I
was created - sales associate which was
really really awesome and she asked me
if I needed anything I told her I was
there to get my glam makeover done that
I was scheduled under a different name
for three o'clock and of course she knew
who I was instantly which kind of blew
my cover which I was definitely a little
bit annoyed about I wanted to do this
definitely on the DL and incognito but
so many of you sisters kept coming up to
me asking for photos as well which I was
so fine then because I love meeting you
guys anyway you guys blew my cover but
it's okay just as the little point
before I get started I think that the
workers knowing who I am definitely may
have made my experience a little bit
better than the average customer
obviously I cannot speak for every step
for an employer every Sephora store
because everyone's gonna have a
different experience but and my
particular visit they were super super
kind and accommodating and my actual
artist didn't know who I was so that was
great she treated me as a normal
everyday customer which is amazing but
that being said at the average Sephora
makeover is 45 minutes and I was there
for almost two hours so like I said
definitely pobably got a little bit of a
better treatment I can't speak for
everybody but my experience overall it
was good to get started on my makeover
the absolute first thing I did was show
my artist a picture of the look that I
wanted being that Jacqueline Hale smokey
eye and she said okay great let's do it
so that was awesome she was not
intimidated to is not scared she didn't
try to talk me into something else which
was amazing because I know a lot of
times hardest do try to do that to do
something easier I was like girl we're
doing this look and she was like okay
sister I got you the first thing that
she did was asked me for my skin type
and I told her that it was combination
and she pulled a bunch of different skin
care products to prep me for my makeup
and then as well she pulled out the
Sephora IQ color tester this is
basically a little machine that takes
tiny pictures of different areas of your
skin which then it matches you to your
foundation and difference to four
foundations that they sell in store
which i thought was so so cool I think
my color IQ thing was like - 7 qy or
something I don't remember off the top
of my head but my foundation was
definitely a pretty close match to what
my normal foundation would be so after
my skin was all prepped with a bunch of
different skin care products the first
is the artist Reynolds eyelid primer to
start off the eyeshadow base and for
Ashley doe today she used the Sephora
Pro palette which I think was the warm
palette and then a little bit of the
anasazi of blonde renaissance palette
for more touches of red and pink even
though my eyes were closed and I was not
turned towards the mirror I obviously
could feel what was going on and I did
notice and really appreciate that she
definitely spent a lot of time blending
she kept going back into the bunch a
different blending brushes making sure
that all of her lines are really
seamlessly
but it out which I definitely appreciate
as an artist obviously you guys know it
is super super important to always blend
your eyeshadows always go on those
circular windshield wiper motions make
sure there are no harsh lines and I
definitely think she did a good job of
achieving pot it's actually giving the
eyeshadow look that I gave her to do
next the artist went in and did my brows
using the Anasazi eyebrow definer and
then set all the hairs in place using
the Benefit Cosmetics 24-hour brow
center once the bronze were all slayed
and in place her next step is going to
be deep base and for today's foundation
she's the bare minerals performance
we're at liquid foundation now as you
guys know my holy grail of the Make Up
For Ever Ultra HD stick to face Born
This Way and recently the Giorgio Armani
luminous silk all of which are sold at
Sephora and bare minerals was definitely
not to be the first brand that I would
run to when it comes to foundation but I
do not say anything I was super super
careful to keep my opinions to myself
the entire time I did not look at myself
either I wanted a full reveal at the end
and it to be the full artist work next
for concealers she went in with the NARS
radiant creamy concealer in the shade
vanilla I believe and as you guys know a
shave team is now sold at Sephora so I
think the NARS radiant creamy was
definitely a really really great option
to use on me and is definitely one of my
all-time favorite concealers as well
then she set my face in place using the
laura mercier translucent setting powder
which is my all-time favorite I was
definitely really really glad about this
because y'all know flash shock is my
middle name so I definitely did not want
to have a powder that I do not like and
I was very very happy to see her using
this one on me and I think it worked I
was normal perfectly fine next step she
went in and bronze my face using a big
fluffy brush was obviously I have love
and she ended the hourglass of bronzer
which I was simply a little bit
surprised about being that benefit hoola
bronzer is the number one best-selling
bronzer in Sephora I believe don't quote
me on that but I think regardless it's
my number one favorite so I was
definitely little bit disappointed to
see her not using that the hourglass was
definitely an interesting choice they
actually did not even know they even had
bronzers I just know about their hominis
which are really really bomb so once
again do not say anything just let her
do her thing then she ran in with the
highlight and at this point I definitely
could tell she was a fan of beauty gurus
because after I showed her the picture
of Jacqueline Pele in the beginning for
Highlander she pulled out this champagne
pop which is Jacqueline's collaboration
with Becca cosmetics I was super excited
to see this one being used on me it is
definitely my all-time favorite
highlighter shades it is beautiful and
golden and she prob about using a pretty
big brush which I was a little bit
spooked about but once again it didn't
get to see until the very very end after
I was glowing for the goods she actually
went back into the eyes to finish
the mascara and lashes and for the
mascaras to use the Marc Jacobs mascara
which I was very excited off because
I've never tried it and she actually did
something with the wand that I was super
super intrigued by she took the top of
the mascara wand and bend it at a 90
degree angle and used that to do my
lashes instead of like the typical
completely horizontal wand I thought it
was a really really cool technique and
definitely made it really really easy
for her to do eyelashes this is
definitely saying that I'll be trying
with all eye mascara wands from now on I
definitely learned that as a really cool
trick and I can't wait to try it out for
myself for the lashes TV one on a pair
of Sephora lashes I forgot to catch the
name for them but they're really really
pretty and they're more winged out on
the outer corners just like in the
picture that Jacqueline had finally to
finish off the look she's the Kat Von D
Vampira liquid lipstick which is
actually the first ever liquid lipstick
I ever purchased with my own money when
I first started to do makeup so it
definitely has a very very special place
in my heart she did pick it herself but
I thought it was the absolute perfect
shade too back to the picture of
Jacqueline so I was definitely really
happy when she walked over with it and
she just put it on my lips
all right guys so now I am back home and
this is the finished look all complete
justice a little heads-up to you guys I
didn't have the entire portion of this
video filmed as soon as I got home with
the full makeup on and I film the outro
with the makeup on as well it was super
super cute and then of course I went to
edit it and the audio was completely
wonky and broken my microphone had
actually died so I had to go get a new
end which was very very annoying but the
make cover was obviously complete and I
already filmed the entire thing and I
definitely did not want to lose this
video because I was super excited to do
the rest of the series so I am sitting
back down after the fact I obviously do
not have the makeup on anymore
but I am referencing the pictures from
earlier on and I'm still gonna talk
about how I felt
so obviously the audio is not gonna
match up with what's going on in the
video but just please sort of pay
attention to what I am saying and just
use the video as like a reference point
to what I'm really talking about before
we get into the actual makeup my first
want to talk about my experience at this
particular Sephora and like I said
beforehand it was really really good now
obviously I cannot speak for every
Sephora employee or store and I
definitely do have a name in the makeup
world so the treatment may have been a
little bit biased but I've also been
very very poorly treated and a lot of
supports that I've been to as well
so I do think this particular support
did a really really great job of
customer service like I said when I
walked and they were very very helpful
they wanted to get me help as soon as
possible to give me what I needed and
they stopped me right down for my
appointment my girl was on time and she
was ready to slay my face all that being
said a Sephora makeover it's supposed to
take only 45 minutes and mine did take
almost up to 2 hours but there was not
many other people in the store getting
their makeup done so that might be a
reason why and also I'm sure that the
artist was making sure that she did a
really really great job which I very
much appreciated let's go ahead and pull
a mirror and super super close and
actually talk about the makeup so let's
go in with the same order that she
applied and starting off with the eyes
I think after looking at everything the
eyes are probably my favorite part of
this entire look like I said beforehand
she definitely spend a lot of time on
the eyeshadow probably the most time out
of anything in this makeup book and she
kept going back into the different
blending brushes to make sure that
everything was seamlessly blended
together which I'm very much appreciated
and I think that the shadow is pretty
accurate to the original picture that
Jacqueline Hale posted also the liner is
applying a very very evenly the line is
nice and straight and even throughout
which I love there's nothing worse than
a wonky liner and the lashes are glued
on very very comfortably I cannot figure
them which is the best if there's one
thing that I would change about this
look if I was doing it on myself I wish
he would have used a different shade of
gold for the actual lid
I feel like the shade that jackal news
on her original picture was a lot more
glittery and much more shade painting
toned whereas this gold shadow was
definitely little bit more yellow and
more a satin shade I wish you would have
used one like this tea light liquid
metals like you guys know I love or an
actual gold glitter on top but she did
just use the palette and I think it
still turned out equally as beautiful
the next stop being the brows I actually
really liked the way she did them they
looked nice and light and fluffy which I
love a good feather brow moment I like
the color she used in the Anasazi abroad
to find her if anything I wish you would
have defined the brow tail a little bit
more but I'm definitely not mad at them
the next that was obviously going to be
the base which was the foundation and
like I said the bare minerals foundation
would definitely not be my first choice
when it comes to a Sephora foundation
picking but like I said it wasn't gonna
say anything after looking at it in the
mirror I don't think it's that bad I
think that she definitely did a really
really great job of using the foundation
to its fullest potential
she did a really great job making sure
that it was even all throughout my skin
I definitely don't see any patchiness or
anything but I will say that it
definitely is creating a little bit
especially around my smile lines like
foundations normally do but this one is
pretty bad and as well it's definitely
not the most flattering on my pores I
don't think she did a bad job but I
definitely would not be choosing this
foundation again next is the concealer
and like I said we use the NARS radiant
creamy concealer and this is one of my
all-time favorites I have no complaining
to this I really liked how it made my
under eyes look and feel
next was bronzing and contouring and I
think that this is probably my least
favorite part of this look like I said
she use the hourglass bronzer and I feel
that this bronzer is just a little bit
too orange for my skin tone in the
picture that Jacqueline posted she
definitely doesn't have actually too
much of a defined contour going on it's
definitely a lot softer and I felt as
though the bronze and contour today was
definitely really really pigmented what
I normally do love but it didn't really
match that one with the photo and I felt
as though the bronzer she uses a little
bit to oranjee tones I wish it was
definitely a little bit more cool to him
to kind of sculpt the face rather than
just bronze and as well she did not
contour I know it's which I was really
really spooked about once I looked in
the mirror you guys know that my nose is
probably my biggest insecurity and I
really love to make it nice and snatched
so to see no contour on it was
definitely a little bit spooky I should
the highlight major props of this artist
for knowing different people in the
makeup industry and knowing about Beauty
influence or collapse I thought it was
so clever when she pulled out champagne
pop after showing a picture with
chocolate and like I said it is a
beautiful highlighter shade but how
there is applied in all the right places
being the brow bone the inner corner of
the tip of the
and on the cheekbones but it's
definitely a little bit of a subtle glow
there's absolutely nothing wrong with
that and it is definitely a really
really beautiful look on my skintone but
I do wish she would have applied a
little bit more with Ash's personal
preference laughs it finally not least
we finished off the look with the
ellipse and like I said we used the Kat
Von D liquid lipstick in the shade
Vampira after the actual shape of the
lips I think she did a really really
good job
my lips are actually uneven and one side
is a little bit bigger so I thought she
did a really really great job of making
sure that the two sides were even and
the lines were very very defined which I
love I cannot stand a blurry and messy
lip line even though the actual shape
was great the one thing I did notice
about the lips is that the product was a
little bit streaky
I really wished it would have applied a
little bit more product to make the
color a lot more even on throughout but
it really was not that big of a deal
overall I think I would rate this
makeover a 7 out of 10 my experience was
really really great and all the
employees were so beyond nice to me and
my artist was really really careful to
make sure that I got exactly what I
wanted she took a lot of time blending
everything and making sure that
everything was really really perfect
which I really really appreciate it it's
super important you have an artist that
really cares about you and your vision
as a client and isn't just gonna get it
done just to get it done and to get that
paycheck so major respect to her overall
I really liked a lot of different things
that she did with my makeups today and
definitely picked up on a few new
techniques that I definitely try
obviously there are a few things that I
would have changed if I were doing it
myself but every artist has her
particular way of doing things and I
don't think that the cons outweigh the
pros in this situation and I would feel
confident enough to wear this makeup out
and not like second-guess myself
all right guys that is all I have for
this videos today definitely make a
comment down below and tell me what you
think about this transformation do you
love it - hate it if you saw me in
public would you think I looked
beautiful or what do be really really
shocked I really want to hear your guys
thoughts if you enjoyed today's video
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and swear we have
not already I post three videos a week
and I'd love to have you join it the
sisterhood if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter at they're both
just James Charles and my snapshot from
overhead the scenes light stuff is James
Charles in the next row asked after
Charles this big sister shadow goes to
sister now thank you so much girl poised
falling - supporting you know I love you
so much and if you'd like to be next
week sisters not make sure to always
retweet my video links and they go live
on a Twitter all right face thank you so
much for watching don't forget to check
out the next upcoming videos where I go
to Mac and Ulta and get the same exact
to make over there will they be the same
will they be better or will they be
absolutely horrible you guys will have
to stay tuned to find out I love your
sisters so much and I'll see you in the
next one
[Music]