hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
I am so suited for this video because
today we are sitting down and we are
doing our next installment of the mini
makeover series this series has been so
much fun to film and if you have nobody
what I'm talking about
make shave like right up here to see the
first two episodes of the series where I
get my makeup done at Sephora and then
Mac and then for today's video we're
going to Alta to get a fault glam
makeover fedley reminder that at 8
different makeover we're asking for this
look that is on this photo of a
Jacqueline Hill it is the perfect bronze
e glittery smokey eye for this fall
season and it's not too hard but also
not too easy of a makeup look to
recreate for these various artists after
every single makeover we're going to
come right back here and show you guys
the finished look and then discuss it
and remember the point of this is not to
drag or pick apart any artists work it
is simply to show you guys what I would
have done differently if it were me so
you guys can make an educated decision
back at home if you want to go get your
makeup done for a special event and
don't forget to stay tuned for the
finale of this mini series where I do
this makeup look on myself and my
personal style using all my favorite
products and I talk to you guys about
what I would really recommend overall
after going to all these different
makeovers and yeah I'll write guys with
all that being said if you're from the
system head up make sure to go give this
video a big thumbs up down below let's
see if we can get this to 50,000 thumbs
up and let's head over to Ulta to get a
glam makeover so walking into also today
my foot was at 2:30 I showed up at about
225 and was seated right away so that
was really really great
they were definitely right on time and
ready to start working which I loved I
was told by the manager running the glam
counter today that my artist was gonna
be darrell and he came out and
introduced himself he was so so sweet
and nice and I'm gonna leave his
Instagram right up in here so make sure
you go check it out and show him some
love so the first thing that my artist
said today was apply some moisturizer
and he used the Peter Thomas Roth
moisturizer I was so excited about this
because you guys know the sister James
loves her moisturizer I literally
moisturize my skin like two or three
times a day it is so salt vital to have
clear and healthy skin so I love a good
moisturizer especially before I put on a
lot of heavy cakey makeup next Terrell
asked me about my skin and I told him it
was combination two now getting a little
bit dry because the weather changed and
he looked really really closely and
picked up these Smashbox pore minimizing
primer to apply over top of the
moisturize
but under the foundation as a nice
primary base I am definitely not proud
of my pores I try to pretend like
they're not there and I wish they
weren't there but I was definitely
really happy today to see that my artist
did recognize them and do his best to
cover them up and smooth them over for a
smooth foundation application after the
primer was all set in place he went in
and used the anasazi abroad to find her
to start defining and slaying my brows I
hid the brows in the mirror I really
really like the shape - my artist went
with I feel like they arched the way I
like them the tail isn't too long and
they have a nice shape to them I do wish
however they were a little bit cleaner I
think the lines could be a little bit
smoother especially on the top and there
are few places that I would have
definitely spoolie through or added a
little bit more product to just make
them more even throughout but I don't
think they're bad by any means next my
artist probably ions using the tar
shaved cave concealer which we'll get to
in a little bit and then he started in
with the eye shadow and for today's eyes
shadow palette he chose that Anasazi up
monitor - on Ashley palette which I was
so so excited for because it is one of
my all-time favorite palettes he first
served it by playing some orange
transition shades and really blended
them out very very well looking close up
the blend for the transition shades and
the crease are really really nice it
looks very very seamless and even leaves
a lot of room for the brow bone
highlight which I love I really can't
stand with eye shadow goes all the way
up to the eyebrow it just is really
really what do I make up pet peeves
sorry I really like the way he applied
the shadow today so next about it with
more tart shaped a concealer on a flat
top concealer brush and started to carve
out my eyelid for a cut crease I was
very excited to see him do this because
you guys know a half-cup creases of my
all-time favorite makeup styles and he
was actually the only artist to actually
define a crease with concealer before
applying the gold shadow on the lid Java
I think was definitely rocking a half
cut crease in her look so I think that
by him doing this by far but it has
looked the most accurate to the original
for the actual gold I'm the lady used
one of the gold shadows from the lorac
gold eyeshadow palette and looking at
the shadow close-up I think that this
gold on this particular look it's
probably the most accurate to what
Jacqueline's original color was I really
really like the shade of gold I feel
like it's not too orange and it's not
too yellow either it's a very very
pretty in the middle shade that is
perfect for this look however looking at
this actual crease close-up I feel like
the shape is a little bit weird for my
eyes I do wish she would have made it
more rounded following my natural eye
crease I feel like it is really really
high up and
which for some reason which doesn't
exactly flatter me the most and as well
I do feel like in the actual like middle
crease region the line is a little bit
messy I do wish it was a little bit more
defined but it's really not that big of
a deal I was just happy to see him doing
a cut crease once the eye shadow was all
complete he decided to skip lashes for
now and come back to it later on and
then we went on with the base for my
foundation today he went ahead and up
hide the two-faced before this way
foundation which I was so excited about
you guys know the vorlons mate it's on
my all-time favorites I always mix it
with my George Armani luminous silk or
layer on top of my makeup forever Ultra
HD stick so I was so so pumped to see
him using this he applied the shade to
natural beige today which looked really
really great in the store with the
lighting in there but I will say looking
at it now looks absolutely awful to his
defense I will say that in the store
letting the shade match did look really
good
so I don't think this is a fair thing to
bash him on at oh I don't know what it
is with these make up stories and having
the artist do makeup and this awful ass
lighting but we really need to get like
rain lights lay it up mirrors or
something because having this foundation
look perfect in store and then having me
walk out and look like this it's really
really not ok and genuinely worries me
for any of you guys going here makeup
done that's just so bad and nobody wants
to have either a flash memory situation
or situation where your face looks like
a completely different color that's so
bad and take it from me you will be
laughed at by probably a lot of people
unfortunately once again it's over to
the Mac video he used one of those tiny
drugstore triangular sponges to blend
out the entire face and we had to come
in the last video that it was really
really impressive because I felt like it
was but then after reading all the
comments everyone was like wait this
isn't even that impressed that everyone
did this do you guys work with the
tyrants or liberate those are the only
sponges and you had to use those for
every makeup application oh my god
now we have Beauty blenders kabuki
brushes and everything in between but I
feel like it's impressive now because
nobody no one uses them anymore but
maybe I'm just crazy definitely know
what you guys think
do you guys use if you do blender or a
makeup sponge I feel like at this point
it's like a necessity but definitely we
call it double Oh tell me what you apply
foundation with because at this point
I'm just curious
next the foundation was all applying and
by now it was time for concealer and for
today he is the Tarte save tape couldn't
sealer which you guys know as my
all-time favorite so I was so so excited
to see him pulling this out and getting
ready to use he's always that literally
everyone asked for it when they get
their makeup done also which is no
surprise at all and for today he used to
shade a light on me which is the same
machine that I use so I was very very
excited to see him using this I think it
looks as usual perfect on my skin once I
face is all
I used a big fluffy brush and went in
with the it cosmetics translucent
setting powder I've actually never tried
this one out before so I was very very
excited to try out a new product and how
about on my face and see how at war I
felt as though it did a really really
good job of mattifying me and keeping my
makeup in place and I didn't really get
a lot of Christ's either which is
amazing we were definitely stuck in
traffic for a pretty long time on the
way home today so it definitely did a
good job of long-wear he next butted in
contour my face and nose using anastacio
contour palette asked that the face I
have no complaints I feel as though he
did a really really great job he put in
all the right places and didn't put too
much on because you guys know that is
only big as pet peeves definitely did a
really great know of mixing the color as
well
I'm definitely chisel but I'm not to
bronze to either so I feel like it was a
really really great medium my nose
contour he used the same exact contour
palette which was fine but he also used
the same exact brush to contour my nose
which I was a little bit spooked about I
did tell him that I wanted a very very
pinched nose contour to begin with just
like I told all the other artists I'm
not even kidding guys it's probably like
this side it's like this is not a nose
contouring brush 3 this brush is what I
use for my nose contour as you can see
there's a very very huge difference in
the sides here and I was very very
spewed to anyway and with this you guys
know that a good pinch and snot nose
contour it's like my favorite element of
my makeup routine so I was a little bit
disappointed in the nose crunchers today
I feel like it was a little bit messy
and definitely could've been blended
more and also was a little bit too wide
or however said it he applied the shade
of champagne pop from Becca which is in
collaboration with Jacqueline Hale I
don't think he actually knew who
Jacqueline Hill was so I feel like this
is a complete coincidence but obviously
if you guys know this was a chocolate
Hey look so I was happy to see him using
champagne pop that's for sure and I do
love this how the door shaped I was very
very excited to see him using it today I
do feel like the application is pretty
good he did use a really really big
brush which once again i was a little
bit spooked about i don't know why he
did I usually use a very very tiny one
like this one the m5 the one from morphe
but I feel like he bonded out really
really well and it doesn't look bad I
don't know so highlighter is good next
was time for the lashes my artist Ashley
well style I wanted for this particular
look and I showed on the picture of
Jacqueline again and so that I want
something just like these wispy and
definitely laughs that get a little bit
longer on the ends he brought over four
different pairs for me to choose from
and I ended up picking the are gel
studio effect demi wispies before
applying the lashes I told you all that
I have small eyes and always have to cut
my lashes so they're comfortable to wear
and he decided to do that today
the lashes which I very much appreciated
he glued them on he's in the classic duo
lash glue and once they were on their
controlled wear and I could not feel
them which is it great and then the next
step was gonna be of course the ellipse
while he went to grab washes my artist
actually handed me a Ben of different
liquid lipsticks that I could pick out
from for today's look so this makeover
in general I would say was definitely a
lot more hands-on than the other ones he
was asking me a lot of questions which I
definitely appreciated but also asked me
to pick a lot of things as well which a
little bit defeats the point of the
video being that I wanted the true
artist interpretation but I picked out a
lipstick that I thought was pretty close
so I ended up picking the anasazi liquid
lipstick in the shade of trust before we
actually went and started the lip
application he asked me how I like my
lips Sean and I did tell him that I like
them a little bit overdone on the top
lip you guys know that this is a big
thing in lastik video where my artist
actually underlined them a little bit
but my lips are a little bit uneven so I
really really love over lining them to
even them out and make them a little bit
more plump on the top left but the shape
of the lips I really really love how the
top lip turned out I feel like he did a
really really great and clean tamil
overlining the top lip it looked very
very nice and very similar to how I
would do it and the bottom lip looked
pretty nice too although it was a little
bit messy on the very very bottom right
below like the center arc point I do
wish it was a little bit cleaned up but
it's not that big of a deal and then as
the color obviously was perfect but then
again I picked it not the artist last
but certainly not least finish I'll just
look by spritzing my face using the
Urban Decay all nighter setting spray
you guys know how to use this all the
time and then he even grabbed a palette
and used that to kind of a fan and help
it dry which I love by Fanning the
settings but you're really helping
everything amount together and really
get a smooth application so that is
something alternative techniques alright
guys and this is the final look from the
alta makeover today look at myself in
the mirror and thinking about my total
experience today at Ulta I would rate
this makeover overall a 7 out of 10 I
think my alter artist today definitely
used a lot of different products and
techniques that I would normally use in
my own maker patina which I was super
super excited about such as Too Faced
Born This Way Foundation and a Tarte
shave tape but there are a few things on
the stuff that I don't exactly love
being the shape of this crease the lip
shape the foundation shade and just
overall attention to detail like I said
the whole point of this series is to
have different artists showcase their
work and their very own techniques and
how they differ from my own all right
guys that is all I have for this video
today definitely leave a comment down
below and tell me what you think of this
makeover have you gotten your
before to love my makeup did you love
your makeup do you hate it definitely
let me know I can't wait to read all of
your sisters comments if you enjoyed
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and
Scrabble you have not ready let that
little bell icon so you can be notified
every time I upload a new video I've had
so much fun doing this series do not
forget to check out the last two videos
so I got makeup done at Sephora and Mac
this one is Ulta and then stay tuned for
the next video the grand finale of this
little mini series where I'm gonna do
this exact look on myself using all my
own techniques and then we'll compare
all the different makeovers and talk
about which one I would recommend to you
guys if you need to get your glam done
for a very very special event if you'd
like to follow me on a makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both just jams Charles
and my snapchat for more behind the
scenes type stuff is James Charles the
next to ask after Charles this week's
shout-out goes to his sister to bra
thank you so much go for always smiling
it's important you know I love you so so
so much and if you would like to be at
next week's sister shut up make sure to
always share my video links when they go
live alright sisters thank you so much
for watching make sure you stay tuned
for the finale coming up next I love you
guys so much I will see you in the next
one
[Music]