hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
2017 was an absolutely crazy here and I
am so beyond thankful to all of you
sisters chose to stay with me through it
let's talk about it
[Music]
ironically enough this year started was
something that didn't exactly happen
this year as most of you already know on
October 11th of 2016 I officially became
the world's first cover boy
we broke history by becoming the first
male ambassador for a major beauty brand
and the world was shook my mother's
event didn't take place in 2017
however this opportunity changed my life
forever and my year probably would have
been very very boring without it in the
beginning of the year I made a huge
change in my life by graduating early
and moving to Los Angeles at age 17 it
was a tough choice to make but my hard
work in school allowed for it and my
parents knew deep down that it was the
right decision for me I found my dream
apartment after only a few tours and
ended up moving in only a couple of days
later I literally had so much fun
decorating and making it my own despite
the fact that I never actually films an
apartment tour even though I promised
you guys a million times
oops coming soon baby not gonna lie
living alone at such a young age is a
little bit spooky I do live the freedom
and I've always been a very very
independent and strong person but it
does get lonely I probably would not
have been able to survive here had I not
met my best friend Laura Milano her
family took me in as one of their own
for almost four months before I
officially moved here and those people
literally mean the entire world to me I
also meant the original sisters who
became my close family security blanket
and security guards at my meet and
greets as many of you guys know from
following your favorite youtubers
personal lives and drama Ellie doesn't
exactly have the best track record for
genuine people but luckily along with
Laura and the sisters I've been able to
surround myself with some positive
hard-working individuals and make some
amazing friendships along the way this
year I met Tati Westbrook another very
special friend of mine she's the mom of
the YouTube makeup world and also like a
mother figure to me she's helped me
become a better and wiser person and has
given me literally all the makeup
knowledge I could ever ask for
last January talk to you in her
now-husband James flew me to Hawaii to
do her wedding makeup which is an
experience I will never forget a long
stead of Tottie's wedding video I also
cloud with some other really cool people
this year I did a few videos of Laura's
husband who you guys know as Danny the
road was also not ready for the
introduction of my little brother to my
youtube channel
better known as sister yet brother I am
truly blessed to have such strong
masculine men in my life that are
comfortable and loving enough to
publicly support me and my career
it truly does mean so much speaking of
masculine men I was graced with the
opportunity of filming with the loves of
my life and future husbands the Dolan
twins our relationship started from me
leaving Thursday comments on their
Instagram pages but it now blows my mind
to think that they are two of my closest
friends collabs are my favorite videos
to film and I'm very proud of the
content that I was able to create with
some of my favorite contact craters that
I've always looked up to not only did I
get to work with some dope youtubers but
I also got to meet a few celebrities
that have had a major impact on my life
I met Kim Kardashian and Ariana Grande
culture for the first time her makeup
artist and one of my personal role
models Margit Ivanovitch had told her
that I was there and she said her
security guard to escort me to meet her
my heart was racing at a million miles
per hour but I somehow managed to pull
it together and I couldn't stop smiling
for literally the entire next week I
must have been annoying enough that she
didn't forget me because when she lost
her beauty line at k'kaw Beauty I was
invited to her house to celebrate I've
always looked up to Kim because despite
what any tabloids or media has to say
about her she's a genius and a classy
businesswoman and genuinely a super kind
person I also made a friendship with in
my opinion the most talented vocalist of
our generation
Demi Lovato she followed me on Instagram
and I said him to her dm's and
miraculously she replied we started
discussing everything from her new music
to my new makeup looks too even on
internet memes how can we forget pute
Lovato she invited me to her documentary
premiere a few weeks ago where I finally
got to meet her in person and we took an
iconic photo and I could think her for
all she's done for me while this year
was filled with many highs and also had
some major lows and at one point I
quickly went from everyone's favorite
cover boy to the most problematic
youtuber of all time in February I went
on a trip to South Africa with some
friends from school that I had been
saving up for and looking forward to for
four years prior before the plane could
even depart the runway I made a joke
about
Ebola and my friend thought I was
talking about the food virus ecoli
I tweeted about her mistake without
thinking twice and the plane took off
when we landed just one hour later in DC
for a layover I remember checking
Twitter and my heart dropping to the
floor a news article was written and
went viral titled cover boy James
Charles says that the only thing Africa
has to offer is Ebola I was so confused
and my first reaction was to fight back
being that my tweet had no harmful
intentions and I was now under public
scrutiny I tried to brush it off and
make a quick apology but after 26 hours
of flying and no internet access about
the Atlantic Ocean I quickly realized I
had messed up big time and that there
was no going back I remember spending
the first day in my hotel room in Africa
sobbing alone thousands of miles away
from the people that I loved the most
and unable to communicate or defend
myself to the thousands of people
following me online it was a rough few
days but there was one day on the trip
that changed my life and perspective
forever we visited a high school called
edge Maine and I remember watching a
live drum performance for the music kids
at the school in the middle of
performance the principal came in and
interrupted pass for someone named James
Charles I vividly remember my heart
stopping and my first instinct was that
they heard in my tweet and we're gonna
ask me to leave but to my surprise he
opened the door to the auditorium and
there was a huge crowd of kids outside
that had left their classes because they
had heard about my arrival and wanted to
meet me I instantly started crying as I
took photos while smiling and meeting
all these kids we started off by talking
about how our school systems differ from
each other but we quickly got very very
comfortable and started talking about
everything under the Sun we talked about
our everyday lives what we like to do
for fun boy and dating drama pop culture
and I was even able to have an open and
honest conversation with some of the
kids about my tweet and how it affected
them from that day on at my life
literally took a 360 degree turn and my
Africa trip consisted of some of the
best memories of my life my tweets from
White House are definitely not something
that I'm proud of
but being called out for them has
allowed me to educate myself and become
a genuinely better person and are not an
accurate representation of Who I am
today
aside from me growing and becoming a
better person there is no denying that
I've become a far better artist this
year back in March I took a flash photo
with a sister named Pam a Tammy agree
and after being filtered it turned out a
little bit ghostly the photo quickly got
into the hands of Stan Twitter and was
Enter
and D saturated and thus flashback Mary
was born at first I was upset by the
poor representation of my makeup skills
and everyone laughing at me but I
quickly learned to laugh with everyone
instead
I turned my hate into profit by making
one of my most successful videos on my
channel of all time recreating my memes
okay flashback Mary flashback Mary
flashback Mary deep down I think that
flashback Mary was a blessing in
disguise although it sucked at the time
my recreating my memes video definitely
got my creative juices flowing and
therefore opened the door for more
entertaining based content on my youtube
channel I can honestly look back and say
that I am really really proud of the
videos that I put out this year the
beauty community can sometimes get over
flooded with repetitive tutorials and
challenges and I definitely set the bar
high and change the excitation for
beauty videos some of my favorites that
I did this year include my makeover
series where I got my makeup done an
Ulta Sephora and Mac which opened my
eyes to different styles and techniques
used by various artists testing fake
makeup where I compared knockoff
products to the real versions of the
most popular makeup items of the time
take her swimming on the first day where
I tested waterproof makeup products by
jumping into a pool makeup versus the
iPhone acts face IT where I tested the
capabilities of the brand-new iPhone on
the same day that it launched and
finally singing my makeup routine an
original challenge series in which I
improv through some of my favorite songs
allowing me to combine two of my
all-time favorite passions music and
makeup
speaking of music I also worked on my
voice a lot this year I was able to show
you guys a whole other realm of James
alongside a few fun Instagram carbs one
of my best friends Anthony I also
started an acapella group called
flashback we've only released two songs
so far but I've accumulated more than 3
million views on our videos that have
had a ton of sales and are so excited to
keep working on more music in the future
music plays a huge role in my life and
is now a huge part of the James Charles
brand if you will which is developed
immensely sisters has quickly become one
of the most popular words on social
media what started off as a term of
endearment between my close friends that
I
we became my catchphrase which I
eventually turned is my very own
clothing line sister's apparel we've
only had a few launches so far but have
sold thousands and thousands of sisters
gear sisters all around the globe and I
look forward to working at my fashion
sense and clothing line once more in
2018 I know y'all are getting a little
bit tired of me wearing the same for
Hardee's on a daily basis trust me me
too
I mentioned earlier that I graduated in
January but in June I flew back home to
little old Bethlehem New York to get my
diploma with the rest of my class I've
worked extremely hard in school and took
all advanced courses all while balancing
my at the time a small Instagram career
and a job at a frozen yogurt shop I
decided not to continue my education and
to work as a youtuber full-time but
walking to get my diploma and my
custom-made Michael Costello sawasdee
crystal jumpsuit was one of the most
fulfilling moments of my entire life
education is super important to me and I
am so thankful that I had a supportive
school system Laura's family actually
flew all the way across America with me
to watch my special moment alongside of
my real family and some of you guys even
snuck into I've actually had a lot of
opportunities this year to meet and hugs
so many of you guys face-to-face and I
look forward to so many more in 2018
I had an impromptu meeting great in the
middle of New York City and over a
thousand and you guys showed up even
though I only announced it on snapchat a
day before I also went to playlist DC
and almost got kicked out oopsies I
turned 18 this year and finally became a
legal adult which means absolutely
nothing because you guys know I don't
really smoke party or drink but I did
choose to celebrate my birthday with all
of you guys at the Murphy store here in
California and it was absolutely
incredible
working with brands such as Murphy this
year has been such a huge honor and has
made both my social media accounts grow
but also my knowledge of business it is
truly incredible to be working firsthand
and receiving products of some of the
most famous brands and beauty when I
couldn't even afford some of their
products a year ago I absolutely loved
working in all their products and you
guys are always hearing me to tell you
use coaches for tempers they loved your
purchase I even put it on a sweatshirt I
had an opportunity to model for a little
holiday campaign this year which was
super exciting my makeup was done by
lipstick Nick one of my all-time
favorite artists with the shoe and the
photos honestly turned out incredible I
was so happy to be the face of their
palette and you can now catch me and all
my favorites and all the different more
free store locations which is such a
huge honor although it wasn't a
collaboration who really knows that 2018
may have in store
I also worked closely with Benefit
Cosmetics one of my all-time favorite
brands they took Laura and I and a ton
of other influencers to Necker Island
which is truly one of the most fun weeks
of my entire life
I would talk all about it but the amount
of adventures we have could literally
fit in one video alone a few weeks ago I
was asked me one of their celebrity
coaches for the benefit brow search
where me a few other influences and the
entire benefit team spent a week on a
beautiful mansion in Lake Tahoe coaching
20 artists from all around the world
spoiler alert hashtag team sisters took
home the crown brows are not twins in
addition to winning $50,000 my artists
and now close friend
Rocio se house eyebrow is gonna be in
every single benefit Bravo or 2018 what
a cool opportunity 2017 started off with
me having 1.1 million followers on
Instagram and just over 500,000 on
YouTube but we're starting like 2018
with well over 5 million sisters
combined it's been a roller coaster over
here but I'm so thankful to all of you
who have chosen to stick with me and I
makeup journey and I truly do love each
and every single one of you so so much
I'm calling this look today blank canvas
inspired by Jody Hall but this look
represents the main reason they started
doing makeup in the first place
express myself through art 2018 is my
canvas and I am so excited to be able to
paint it in any way that I want Thank
You sisters for watching my year
interview video I really hope you
enjoyed it if you did please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and subscribe if you have not
already join the sister to click that
little bell icon so you can be notified
every time I upload a brand new video if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey and see what 2018 has to hold
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both just James Charles
and my snapchat for more my handsy flips
up is James Charles an extra ask dr.
Charles this week's Esther shadow goes
through every single one of you guys
watching out there I know that's super
cheesy to say but seriously I cannot
thank you enough for boys following and
supporting me throughout this entire
year special thank you to Brooke Zoe and
arrows for helping me film this video
today I love you guys so much but I will
see you next year bye
[Music]