Oh Lord here we go hi guys my name is
James for those of you who don't know me
I'm a 16 year old makeup artist from New
York and I run the Instagram page Jay
Charles Beauty lately literally 150
percent of my comments have been so here
I am on YouTube in front of my camera
with my lights with a whole lot of
makeup in front of me making a tutorial
and I can't believe I'm doing this but
it's about damn time today I did this
blue brown and green trio chrome look
I'm gonna call it serpent and if you
guys want to see how to recreate this
makeup look make sure to keep on
watching also if you like this tutorial
don't forget to hit that thumbs up
button down below and subscribe if you
haven't already for more tutorials
coming soon hi guys I'm gonna be
starting off today using my benefit
Porefessional primer I have a million
little bumps and pores all over my face
so doing this would really help me
smooth everything out and get an even
foundation application next I'm going in
with my la girl pro color corrector
concealer in orange just to color
correct my 5 o'clock shadow and my under
eye circles if you don't have this
problem obviously don't color cracked
because this is not pumpkin glam but if
you're like me and you get negative 15
hours of sleep this might be for you I
also color corrected my acne spots using
a green color corrector also from la
girl and then blended it out with my
Beauty Blender now I'm going in with my
Make Up For Ever HD ultra foundation in
the shade Y 255 and just putting a bunch
of little dots all over my face
obviously we're gonna blend these out
later on but it just helps create a
really even application when you're
blending don't forget to blend on your
neck and on your ears too we want a
smooth transition and the last thing we
need is Moses parting the foundation see
on your face to highlight my face I'm
using my la girl Pro concealer in the
shade porcelain I'm drawing little
triangles on my face in the middle of my
forehead into the middle of my chin on
my mustache area and just one line down
the center of my nose this will just
make all the high points of my face
stand out and then once again at
blending out with my Beauty Blender now
I'm setting my entire face using Kodi
Ariston powder because I am done with
the liquids and creams this will help to
set everything in place and to reduce
crease edge
to further highlight my face I'm gonna
use my morphe 48 brush and this light
color for my lunatic cosmetics contour
lab this color usually comes in the
contour palette but I actually deep
potted it and just put it in my Z
palette with all my other contour and
highlight shades once again I'm just
putting this on all the high points of
my face to contour today I'm using my
morphe m-52 3 brush and my makeup geek
contour pans these colors are literally
so good and they are so pigmented I'm
using the shade warm fair today just to
create a nice basic contour and I'm
going on my cheekbones my 5 head and on
my jaw line to really carve everything
out and make my face look super defined
[Music]
next to further define my contour I'm
using the same brush as before and
makeup heat cocoa bear it isn't
eyeshadow but I never use blush in my
look so this really helps to just warm
everything up next I'm just making my
face using my once again Cody airspun
powder and my powder puff I'm just
drawing two really harsh defined lines
from the tops of my ears to right above
the corner of my mouth
this will help really carve out that
contour and with whatever's left on the
powder puff I'm just gonna put
underneath my eyes and in the center of
my forehead because I literally use so
much facial expression when I talk my
face creases so badly so doing this
helps decrease the creasing if that
makes any sense now to start the eyes I
did my brows off-camera just because I
tried and the angles turned out so bad I
promise I will do a prior tutorial later
on but for now we're just gonna stick
with this so to start off I'm using
makeup geek Peach Smoothie and my Murphy
and four-for-one brush just to get a
nice transition shade going in my crease
for this entire look I use my morphe 35o
palette
since the shades don't have actual names
I'll just be like describing them really
all you need to know is that I used a
light and medium and a dark brown to
create the halo eye effect and then
obviously I'm going to be going into
blues and greens later on
to further define that halo i i'm using
my morphe m4 for one and once again just
a medium brown tone from the 35k palette
i'm putting that in the inner and outer
peace of the eyes and then just taking
whatever excess product is left and
going in windshield wipers just to
define that crease now I'm using my
morphe M 509 and a darker Brown from the
35 k just to further define the inner
and outer V's and once again the crease
same thing just really keep darkening
that halo eye and making sure there's a
nice even transition once I have nothing
on that brush I'm just going in my lower
and upper lash line just make sure
everything is super blended out now for
the pop of color I'm spritzing my flat
definer brush with mac's fix+ and then
going into the makeup geek houdini I'm
just packing this all over the center of
my lid and making sure to blend it up to
my crease but not playing it up too far
because we don't want it to get muddy
and gross looking next I'm going into
the typhoon it's a makeup geek dual
chrome eyeshadow it's just green and
blue and I'm focusing that right on the
center of the lid and that's just with
the tiny morphe definer brush I'm just
going back in with my M 509 and a dark
brown from the 35 K just to make sure
that all the edges are super blown out
and there's no harsh lines in the
waterline I'm just going in with the
Italian deluxe eye pencil in turquoise I
got this at the morphe store if you
don't have this eye pencil you can
easily just do black it's really up to
you but I wanted another pop of color on
the bottom I actually lost the clip but
I did use the NYX jumbo eye pencil in
black bean just to mimic the halo effect
that we have going on on the upper lid
and then once I did that I'm just going
back under the lower lash line to blend
everything out and connect it back up to
the top I'm just going in now with my
favorite mascara benefit roller lash
it's so good it makes my lashes look so
long and not clumpy so I would
definitely recommend I applied my
falsies off camera today I use the black
magic lashes in siren I ended up gluing
my eye shot what I try to do on camera
so definitely not going to do that again
anyway a lesson learned this is the
finished eye look sorry for the walk you
lash but I'm going to go ahead and do
the other one off-camera and then we can
go ahead and finish the face together
two highly I'm just fetching my brush
again with mac's fix+ to make it super
defined and then mixing these two colors
from my Anasazi aglow cap now we packed
out highlight on like there's no
tomorrow remember the goal is that your
highlight can be seen from space and
that you blind everybody walking by I
always highlight my cheekbones the tip
of my nose and my Cupid's bow just
because I think it looks cute for my
lips today I'm using Oprah Brooklyn you
guys always ask what liquid lipsticks I
like best and they're definitely Oprah
the formulation is so good and they
don't dry crusty and gross like so many
other brands do as an optional last step
I went ahead and I added Houdini all
over my lips just for a cool Joe chrome
effect and that guys is the finished
look I really hope you enjoyed this
tutorial and I will see you soon with a
new video bye
[Music]