hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel
warning you guys right now today's video
is going to be a very very long one
so grab your pinky drink goodies grab
your snack candy wackadoo booze and
brace yourself a few weeks ago I
uploaded a video on this channel where I
got ready but I went super super
in-depth of every single set of my
makeup routine and answered all the
most-asked beauty questions in order to
give you makeup beginners out there some
helpful hints and tips and tricks to
make your makeup application process
that much easier and better as you can
see I'm starting out today's the new my
base already done so if you'd like to
see how to get perfect skin every time
you do your makeup don't forget to check
out last video which is right up here
for today's video we're gonna be
focusing on this part of the face being
the eyebrows eyeshadow eyeliner and
lashes without further ado get ready for
a very very long video with lots of
helpful tips and tricks
grab your notepad and a pencil because
it'll be hopefully some really great
information to help you guys into makeup
routine and let's get started
[Music]
okay sisters hello so like I said I'm
starting off my veins already done and I
just went ahead and I did one eyebrow
and I completely off camera now you're
probably looking at this and saying oh
my god sister we were normal people none
of us want to rock a sunset half cut
crease at an everyday basis and trust me
I know I do not blame you but I do have
a reason for why I did such an intense
look today that we're gonna be going
through for today's though do I have a
lot of different questions and a lot of
techniques that I want to go over so
doing a look complicated like this is
really gonna allow my gonna hit every
different step in order to help you guys
step up your makeup routine since we're
only gonna be focusing on this area's
today and I really want to give you guys
the best view possible I'm gonna go
ahead and zoom you right in it so you
can see a super close-up so my first
step of my eye makeup is always my
eyebrows some people like to do them
first I really don't understand how they
do that hurry personally I always like
to do them after I base and before the
eye shadow and then carve it out Suika
are really really nice and even base so
I'm just gonna show you guys how I like
to do with mine today here in the makeup
community there's a very famous saying
about brows and that is that brows frame
your face and this is probably one of
the most true things I have ever heard
in my entire life the most common
question I get when it comes to brows is
how do I find at the perfect shape if
you guys want to start day for a very
very long time you would know that my
brows have undergone quite the huge
transformation
and definitely for the better when I
first started off they were super super
thick and had literally no arch to them
and this brow shape after very very long
time and a lot of nasty comments I
finally realized was driving my entire
face down no matter how hard I some eyes
or smiled it still somehow looked like
my brows were frowning and I obviously
realized that this was not the looks
that I wanted to go for once I solved my
pride and finally admitted that my
blocked brows were absolutely awful i
tweeze a ton of my eyebrows off to make
them a lot more arched my eyebrow
transformation was still not exactly
complete though I wore those eyebrows
for a good hot minute you guys love them
I love them but more recently I actually
changed them a little bit more by
tweezing off almost my entire brow tail
my eyebrows used to grow to around down
here so more recently I've been lifting
my tail upwards which gives my face a
more lifted and snatched look and also
gives me a more room for eye shadow as
you can see over on this eye brow shape
is a very very personal thing and of
course I'm gonna give you guys a few
tips and tricks in a second but I would
say that the absolute best way to figure
out your best brows is by taking selfies
it was through that that I realized the
errors that I was doing with my brows I
was able to kind of fix them and perfect
them through experimenting I understand
that you guys don't have hours every
single day to experiment
so I'm gonna show you one super helpful
rule / tip and trick that can really
help you shape your brows this super
simple Brown trick involves three lines
of reference and all you're going to
need is your favorite brow pencil today
I'm using the Anasazi eyebrow pencil in
the shade medium brown the first rule of
thumb is that the inside of your brow
should always align with the outside of
your nostril so if you can see on this
side right here it starts right when I
align it my brow pencil if we move over
to this eye we can see that they align
at once again perfectly so I'm just
going to draw one little line to mark
the center of my brow the next rule of
thumb is that when looking forward at
the beginning of your brow arch should
align perfectly with the outside edge of
your pupil and as you can see they do
moving over to the other side you can
see bingo right here
so I'm just going to make my mark and
finally for the tail of your brow if you
hold your brow pencil at the corner of
your nose and head it out the
of your eye your browser Tut's just like
that so once again coming to this site
if I hold my pencil right like this I'm
gonna my brow tail right there now that
we have all three of those points mapped
out let's go ahead and actually start
filling in the brow the most common
question I get when it comes to drawing
your brows is how do I make them look
define but still a natural and hair like
my answer to that question is always use
a brow pencil
I love broad pencils because the tip is
fine so you can really sketch in a tiny
little hairs for a natural and realistic
effect and you can also change the
pressure for a darker look on the tail
and a lighter look in the inner corner
so you still get that beautiful ombre
defined look to start filling them and I
always like to start in the inner
corners I'm gonna hold my pencil
vertically to my face and I'm gonna use
a very very light pressure and just
lightly place my pencil and just kind of
flick it upwards to create
natural-looking hair strokes you
definitely gonna want to start off with
light pressure and then press harder as
you get through the brow if you start
off too dark in the inner corner you're
gonna end up with the block broad which
is obviously not the look that we're
going for once the area is although then
I like to take my pencil and keeping our
guidelines in sight I just like to
underline the bottom of the brow and
just kind of map out where I'm going to
go once again using really really light
pressure and creating hair like little
strokes so it looks natural right to the
dot that we've created for the tail and
then once I have the tail I'm just going
to start by filling in that outer
triangle and start to bring it back
upwards right back into the eyebrow when
purchasing a brow pencil if possible of
course you should always get one that
has a spoolie at the end I freaking love
these things that they are still half of
while doing brows and throughout the
entire process I always like to go
through and kind of brush through the
hairs just make sure the product is
getting blended together so nothing
looks too intense and too harsh and also
moves the hair around so you can kind of
see areas that you missed I need to add
a more product to once I have the bottom
and the tail all sketched out and don't
worry if it's Bessie we're going to
clean it up later of course I like to
take my spoolie and brush the hairs
downwards and then I like to do the top
of the brow I always like to make sure
that I'm brushing my hair away so I can
really see the area that I need to fill
and because if I do it this way it's
really easy to
time's go above the brow and then your
brows just keep getting thicker and
thicker and thicker and thicker and that
is usually not the best look similar to
the front I'm using medium pressure and
just sketching in light hair like
strokes just to structure out the top of
the brow just like this and once I get
to the outer corner I'm just going to
connect it right into the tail and make
sure I didn't miss any areas filling it
and once I'm happy with how the brow is
filled and I always like to take a brow
gel now this step is totally optional I
would definitely recommend it for people
like me if you have a lot of brow hairs
and you want to make sure that they're
laying in the right direction up but you
can totally skip this and save a lot of
money if you have not a lot of brow
hairs totally up to you but I'm gonna
using the benefit 24-hour brow center I
really like this one because it is like
cement for your brow hairs it really
locks it in place and I'm gonna do is
just run through the brow hairs and
brush them right in the right direction
so they're laying inside of where I
filled in that brow as you can see by
doing that too and moving around the
brow hairs I'm definitely missing a
little bit of definition right up in
here so I'm just gonna go back into the
pencil and add in a few more light
strokes just to fill it in now the last
of my brow routine which is always my
favorite part is cleaning them up to do
this I'm just gonna grab a lot top
concealer brush like this this is the
morphe m-43 - and your favorite full
coverage concealer for me it is
heart-shaped tape and I'm just gonna put
a little bit of a dollop of this on the
back of my hand get a little bit on with
that brush and then I'm just gonna go
right in and start cleaning up the brow
very very carefully I really love
cleaning up the brows because not only
does it give them a much cleaner
appearance but if you make anyone's
takes while filling it it can see there
is the perfect way to fix them up and
make sure they are super super snatched
once I'm satisfied with the line I
always like to take the excess of that
concealer on that same exact brush and
put the remainder of it right on my
eyelid and I'm gonna use this concealer
today as an eyelid primer which is a
really really great hot because I do
almost the same exact thing so it's a
great way to save a lot of money in your
makeup routine with the dense packing
brush like this this is the morphe m33 5
this is my all-time favorite for setting
the eyelids in place I'm gonna dip this
into a little bit of my setting powder
pop off the excess and I'm just going to
make sure that concealer is right in
place because we
not one or I shadow to crease throughout
the day there we go that is our brows
laid and in place and now we finally get
to move on to the fun part the eyeshadow
for today's I try to look I did decide
to go with a sunset half cut crease
which like I said and I was a little bit
of a crazy look for most of you guys out
there but I have a lot of different
techniques and tips and tricks that I
want to talk about because a lot of the
questions I received it talked about
blending and using a lot of colors makes
it really easy for you guys to see how
the blending techniques work before we
hop into the shadows I want to quickly
talk about makeup brushes because good
working tools or an absolute necessity
to any successful makeup look you guys
know that I have an avid makeup lover
and when it comes to brushes I will
admit I'm a little bit of a hoarder I
mean this is literally my container of
fluffy eyeshadow blending brushes alone
but I understand it that is really
unrealistic for you guys makeup can be
ridiculously expensive so I compiled a
list of eight different brushes that I
think would be a necessity to any makeup
lovers collection and I think that could
achieve any sort of eyeshadow look
desire first we have the morphe m4 for
one this retails for $6.00 ition shades
next we have the morphe m4 is 3 3 yet
this is the best crease brush in the
entire world and you need this in your
collection I could probably do an entire
eyeshadow look with just one of these
brushes and I'm not kidding when they
say I have 27 of them in my collection
you obviously did not need 27 but if
your eyeshadow lover like me I'd
recommend getting at least 3 of these
because you can really use them for any
single look this is the amma 506 and
retails once again for 6 dollars and is
a fluffy pointed brush which i really
really love it for detailed crease work
or blending out an outer v this is the
amat 2 to 4 and it is a round flat
concealer brush and this is my all-time
favorite brush for either carving out
the brows or doing a cut creases this is
the amma 205 and it is also a round flat
concealer brush but it is much smaller
and instead of using this for concealer
i actually used this to pack shadow on
the lid finally this is the m14 9 it is
a tiny round and a bullet brush and I
use this for highlighting the inner
corners highlighting the brow bone and a
buffing shadow onto the lower lash line
you can get all eight of those brushes
for only $35 using code James and I
think those will set you up for success
with
any eye shadow look you want to do for
my silence today I'm gonna be using the
35 B palette I'm first ending at Miami
for 401 which is the biggest fluffy
brush and dip into the yellow shade in
the bottom corner
for this particular look our yellow is
going to act as our transition shade
holding the brush at an upward angle I'm
gonna go in right into my crease and
start using a circular motions to place
that shadow right up in there and to
blend it out when applying the shadows
I'm making sure to pack the color right
in the crease and then doing my circular
motions to blend them out this will make
sure that the shadow doesn't get all the
way up to the brow bone and look muddy
and unblended because that is obviously
not what we want you want to keep the
yellow up here in order to make a nice
transition between skintone color and
then your crease next we're gonna move
on to our darker shade which in this
case is going to be our orange so to do
this I'm gonna grab my AM 4-3-3 which
like I was saying is my favorite a
crease brush and I'm gonna dip into the
bright orange shade I'm still gonna hold
my brush at a slight upward angle but
I'm gonna hold this one a lot more
horizontal to my face and is staying
exactly where we want it in the crease
and the outside bristles of the brush
are gonna do the job of blending it into
that yellow shade without bringing it
all the way up to the brow bone so much
of the yellow shade I'm going to Pat
that shadow in there to make sure it's
very very pigmented and then just do a
mix of windshield wiper motions and
small circular motions to make sure it
is evenly blended out
it's really important to keep in mind
the pressure that you're using on your
brush throughout your entire makeup
process you want to use heavier pressure
when applying the shadows to make sure
that they really get pressed in there so
they're pigmented but when you're
blending them out you want to use super
super light pressure I mean I'm
literally barely even touching my eyelid
at this point it is just the tips of the
bristles that are running against it
that are really gonna make everything
blended together without placing any new
product on there once you're happy with
that blending to make sure it's really
perfect I'm gonna go back into my
original transition shade brush dip into
a little bit more yellow tap off any
excess and then go right over the border
between the orange and the yellow to
make sure that everything is blended
together and that the yellow doesn't get
lost in all of the blending and brush
work our next darker shade is going to
be our red so once again I'm gonna grab
another M 4-3-3 brush and dip into the
wrench
right up in here when I hide in this
color I am actually holding the brush
almost completely horizontal to my face
to make sure that the color gets
distributed into exactly the crease and
the crease only and doesn't get blended
anywhere upwards I'm next going to go
back into my empire 3z that have the
orange side on it and blend right over
that red in between to make sure that
the orange doesn't get lost and to
ensure that there is an even transition
between the yellow and the red it takes
a lot of practice a lot of patience and
a lot of time to really master the art
of blending and the best way to do it is
to really go in and make sure that every
color is blended seamlessly together and
not cutting any corners next is gonna be
our final color which is dark purple so
for this I'm gonna con Miami 506 which
is that tiny little fluffy brush and dip
it to the cool tone of dark purple shade
right up in here when I go into my
darker shade of eyeshadow whether it be
a purple black dark blue or even maroon
I always like to start off in the outer
corner because that's where I really
want most of the product to be a focused
and when I grab the product always make
sure to not really put a lot on my brush
as you can see I really just packed it
in there and barely anything showed up
but that's what we want my best i shadow
tip for you guys to do it would be apply
a little bit of product blend it out and
then see if you need more and if you do
that add more product and slowly build
your way up the worst thing you can do
is start off dark and try to fix it
because there's usually no going back
I'm applying the shadow carefully in my
outer V which is just basically like
this socket where your Jenner right up
in here where your eye sits I did get a
few questions on how to sketch it out
but literally just imagine that there's
a V from the corner of your eye right up
into your crease if they were to connect
and that is where you should have put
your outer V and then will the ever
excess shadow I have left I'm just going
to drag that into the crease just to
provide a little bit of dimension you
guys should know the joke this plant guy
with my red and 4-3-3 it gonna blend
right over the edge make sure that the
purple doesn't get too intense and we
don't lose that red and then finally our
yellow we get to take a break from the
shadow for a few short minutes because
now we get to the fun part cutting at
the crease you guys know I love about
half cut crease and is on my all-time
favorite makeup looks to do and I'm
gonna show you guys how I do mine today
the most common question I get when it
comes to cut creases is already put the
crease and that is a honestly really
question that I still at 100% not sure
the answer to if you grab the end of
your brush and lightly lightly poke
around your eye area you should actually
be able to feel your crease it is the
kind of squishy area that you can push
in right here right in between your brow
bone which you obviously can't push in
and your eyeball which you shouldn't
push in because I'm not trying to get
sued if you go blind tain once again my
full coverage concealer I'm gonna put a
dollop of it on the back of my hand and
I'm gonna grab a Miami two to four brush
which is that flat concealer brush that
I was telling you guys about I freaking
love this you can use this for concealer
or packing a shadow onto the lid or
glitter you just need one of these in
your collection I'm gonna dip it right
into that concealer and before actually
going into the eye I'm going to lightly
dab off any excess because the last
thing you want is to place it on there
and get a clump and mess everything up
it's happened to me don't do it
once you're all ready to go I'm gonna
tilt my head up and backwards so I can
look into the mirror and have all of my
eyelid a pletely accessible and there
are no wrinkles I'm gonna place my brush
right in there and I'm just going to
follow the shape of my crease once we're
happy with the shape and the concealer
is all tacky I'm gonna quickly grab my
Emma to a fire brush or just any tiny
packing a brush and go right back into
the shadow and I'm going to do the
eyelid I'm bursting they're gonna be
white in the top corner and I'm gonna
pack this right on at the inner corner
of the eye then with that same exact
brush grabbing the yellow and packing
that right next door do not necessarily
worry about the blending either by
tapping into the colors that Cleo though
they're gonna kind of blend naturally
and since the concealer is wet you have
to work fast then grabbing the orange
then the red and then finally the purple
connecting it right into that outer V as
you guys can see even while packing
these shades on there I still have my
head tilted backwards which might look
crazy but I promise you this makes it so
much easier to get full access to your
eyelid and make sure that you don't get
any shadow where you don't want it to be
and you get it right up to that crease
line similar to up here how we kept
going back in with each individual color
after the fact to make sure it was
blended I'm gonna do the same exact
thing so I'm going to go back into my
red and top
right over that transition area then the
orange before I do the yellow I do want
to add a little bit of a metallic shade
on the inner corner just for a little
pop of shimmer and for this I'm gonna
use the Tarte chrome paint in the shade
of top yacht I love this one I just
under grab a tiny little brush and I'm
going to get it right on there and the
one tip I have for you guys when it
comes to it metallic shadows is to give
your brush a good spritz a fix plus or
any setting spray and then it on
and it's gonna really make it shine now
I'm gonna go back into the yellow and go
right over the edge of the two of those
colors and you guys that is the upper
shadow I'll complete see not that that
when you really break it down we're
gonna take a break from shout out for a
second and move on to the winged liner
probably right behind a cut crease a
good a winged liner is probably one of
the hardest techniques to do and makeup
but I'm gonna show you guys a few tips
and tricks to really get your wings
snatched ready to cut someone and
hopefully very even there are many
different products in the makeup world
that you can use to create a winged
liner
some people like a pencil I do not some
people like a gel liner with a brush I
do not some people like a liquid liner
with like bristles I sometimes do but
really did not what I really like to use
is a felt tip liner for today I'm going
to use the Marc Jacobs felt tip liner
just like this and it's basically a tiny
little marker this one is $58 which you
definitely do not have to buy I get that
as ridiculously expensive
I know Maybelline has a literally good
and so does Kat Von D but basically
you're gonna want to use a felt tip
liner if you are like me and you
struggle with this because it makes it
so much easier the most common question
I get when it comes to winged liner is
how do you get them to be even let's be
real we all have days where our
eyeliners are like not even distant
cousins let alone sisters let alone
twins
but there is one half that I have for
you guys that's really gonna hopefully
step up your eyeliner game and that is
follow the shape of your eyes when
drawing in the bottom line of your way
you're gonna want to imagine as if your
waterline and continued so as you can
see here my winder line goes all the way
around goes up and then my winged
eyeliner looks like it's a continuation
and it follows that same exact shape and
is a slight angle upwards which gives my
eyes a nice left a lot of people tend to
draw their wings straight out which
done correctly can give a really cool
editorial look but often times on
certain shapes it tends to make the eyes
droop and look saggy for some reason a
lot of people tend to draw their wings
straight up which is literally
flattering on nobodies my shape unless
your eyes are literal like circles where
the liner would make sense to keep
following the shape please to not draw
your eyeliner straight up it does not
belong there
taking my eyeliner pen and giving it a
good shake make sure that there's a lot
of product in the bristles I'm going to
go towards the corner of my eye and I'm
going to kind of rest my elbow on my
chest to make sure my arm is not going
anywhere and I'm going to start right at
the outer corner and I'm gonna draw a
line upwards following the shape of my
waterline similar to the brows if it's
messy it's okay because we're gonna
clean it up after once I have that
bottom line sketch in it we are golden
we're good to go I'm just gonna take it
and I'm going to drag the line right
back down to the lashes once the wing is
in place all you have to do is lightly
place that felt tip right on the base of
your lashes and just lightly drag all
the way across to finish off that winged
liner with a general rule keeping in
mind that it should start off a super
super thin in the inner corner and get
thicker as it gets to this portion and
then of course thin out of the weight
once we're happy with the overall shape
of the wing following the theme of this
video now we get to clean it up I'm
gonna grab my flat top concealer brush
once again a little bit more shaped tape
concealer and I'm just going to
carefully go right below the wing and
carve it out I'm also gonna take the
excess concealer on the brush and blend
it downwards overtop of some of this
eyeshadow that ended up back here
you don't need to do this it's just
personal preference that I really like a
cut and clean line when it comes to my
eye shadow looks of this kind of style
the hard part is over
thank God jumping back into the shadow
quickly to finish off the lower lash
line we're just gonna replicate the same
exact colors that we did on the top on
the bottom grabbing a little smudger
brush this is the Emma 213 and the dark
purple shade I'm just gonna press this
right up against the waterline and then
making sure to lightly drag out and
connect it with that wing because
nothing it looks weirder than when you
have shadow blended out and there's just
like a harsh divide right here don't do
that I'm gonna grab that pencil brush I
was talking about and dip
into the red shadow and he's it to blend
out that purple and finally just gonna
give an emperor three three and two
potential a little bit of orange and a
little bit of yellow and just blend
right now the last and final step before
moving on to the lashes is going to be
water lines and if you guys are a true
sister you would know that I literally
hate them doing my waterline is by far
my least favorite stabbed and eye makeup
routine I hate it I have never liked it
and if you have sensitive or watery eyes
like me you might as well just skip it
altogether it has truly saved the life
of my makeup routine I have never once
wore a black eyeliner and my upper
waterline and not have it be
ridiculously uncomfortable and transfer
to my lower lash line by the end of the
night so just skip it most helpful
makeup tip you'll ever receive as for
the lower waterline though gal I love
her there are so many things you can put
on there a pop color for a fun look my
Priscilla favorite is a nude liner this
one is from pretty vulgar and I just
love this using a nude liner in your
waterline is gonna really open up your
eyes make them pop and make them look
bigger you guys know I love a good doll
like makeup look and I really really
love the new it aforethought as you can
see it just looks so nice you can of
course use a black liner as well for a
more sultry sexy look but just keep in
mind using a black is gonna make your
eyes appear smaller so line your
waterline accordingly
and last but finally certainly not least
is going to be the lashes the first step
of applying lashes is always to give
them a good curl using whatever color
you want I think this one was like $2
from CVS and the only tip I have for
this one is make sure you're getting
right up to the root of the lash right
your lash liner for the best curl our
next step of course is gonna be a good
coat of mascara and for today's video I
am so excited to be partnering with NYX
Cosmetics to show you guys they're brand
new worth the hype mascara this is just
launched a few weeks ago is available
now in most drugstores is literally
eight dollars hello and is so good you
guys know I don't really do a whole lot
of sponsored videos on this channel it
is pretty rare for me but I've been
testing this mascara out for the past
week or so and I really really like it
and I'm so excited to show you it today
going into the wand once again I'm gonna
tell my headed back so I have a really
easy access
my lashes I'm gonna start by bringing
this one in starting right at the root
of the lash almost in my upper waterline
and just wiggling it upwards going from
root to tip of the lash and wiggling
your wand all around you will also make
sure that all of ours are evenly coated
which is obviously ideal and as long and
beautiful as they can possibly be I
really really like this mascara because
it's of a luminizing mascara and
obviously who doesn't love a little bit
more volume a little bit more dimension
and their lashes I love a good
voluminous mascara but often times it'll
leave my lashes looking really really
clumpy but as you can see if I look down
they look nice and separated and so
beautiful and also the front of this is
really really black which is literally
the best ever
oh look at how good my bottom lashes
look oh my god NYX thank you for
partnering with you on this video and
sisters do you know what to do go check
it out it's worth the hype okay so if
you guys are looking for an everyday at
natural look when it comes to your
lashes at least you could totally stop
right here with just a good curl and
mascara and looks beautiful and stunning
but if you're like me and you want a
little bit more drama a little bit of a
bigger impact today we're gonna do some
falsies for today's look I'm gonna go in
you guessed it the Lily lashes in the
style of Miami these are my all-time
favorite false lashes and I really
really like them because they're super
super wispy they're not too dense so you
can still see the eye shadow underneath
and they're also not too long for my
eyes it's really important to keep your
actual eye shape and the shape of eyes
shadow that you're planning for in mind
when picking out a pair of lashes
obviously there are millions of
different styles of lashes out there but
I like to group them into two different
categories which I like to call either
symmetrical lashes or asymmetrical
lashes Lily lashes miami's are
symmetrical lashes in my book because at
the longest point they are all the same
exact length an asymmetrical ma should
be a lash that is small on the inner
corner but the lashes get longer and
longer and longer as they go out towards
the outer portion of your eye and they
flare up I definitely prefer wearing
asymmetrical last because I feel like it
gives a very very doll-like appearance
it makes your eyes look very very round
whereas an asymmetrical lash really
accentuates almond eyes and makes them
kind of look more like snatched and
pulled which is also a really beautiful
look as well it just depends on what
kind of look you're going for once you
have your lashes all picked
and ready to go I'm gonna grab a pair of
tweezers and I'm going to pull them out
of the package very very carefully
most lashes are pretty expensive so
you're gonna want to be gentle and
pulling them out of the package because
the last thing that you want to do is
spend thirty dollars on a pair of lashes
and then rip out half the hairs each
hair is like 50 cents in here now the
absolute biggest mistake that people
make when putting on a pair of falsies
is taking them right out of the box and
popping them right on the eye please do
not do that if your lashes are poking
you if they are tickling you if they are
flying off in the inner corner it is
because you have an eyelash glued on
where there should not be an eyelash
glued on nobody has big enough eyes to
ever glue on this big of an eyelash to
your eye trim your eyelashes and your
application and your entire life will be
a million times better the best way to
figure out how to trim your eyelashes
and what length is going to work best
for your eye shape is to take them out
of the box and put them on your eye but
without any glue the tackiness from
whatever was sticking at the lash to the
box should be enough to keep the lash on
your eyelid and kind of get a sense for
the measurement grab my lashes in the
center tightly by a pair of tweezers I'm
gonna grab my tiny pair of eyelash
scissors and I'm going to trim off the
ends for me personally I like to trim
off one spike on one and two spikes on
the other end which deathly made a huge
difference in the size and although this
may look small the other lashes that we
put mascara on are gonna do a great job
of blending together the false lash with
the real one and this is gonna look a
whole lot better than that
overwhelming lash from before to final
lashes today I'm going to be using the
duo brush on adhesive I love this lash
glue this stuff is so bob you need it in
your life I'm just gonna go ahead and
open it up and paint a light layer of
glue right on the lash band this glue
dries pretty quickly and it goes on blue
so once it turns clear you know it's
ready to apply so I'm just gonna shake
it around a little bit and I'm gonna
hold a mirror and just like this one
kind of below my face at a very very
weird angle trust me on this I'm gonna
look in my mirror from below me and I'm
gonna place the lash on top of my lid
from an upward
angle I'm gonna go to my tweezers and
then just pull on both ends and make
sure that the actual lash band is in
contact with my lash line
that's why holding the mirror from below
is super super helpful because you can
actually see what you're doing is that
I'm just trying to estimate it once our
last band is all glued on there we have
our last step but probably our most
important step and please be careful
while doing this do not poke your eyes
out go in super close up to your eyelid
with your pair of tweezers and go in and
pinch together right up against your
lash line the false lashes with your
real lashes and doing this is not only
gonna make the lashes blend together and
look more real but because the mascara
is slightly tacky still it's gonna
really stick the lashes together so
you're laughs and will stay on all day
long and there you go guys our lashes
officially on secured pinch together not
going anywhere and looking so so so good
lashes like I was saying is by far one
of the hardest steps of any makeup
routine I struggle with them for so long
can't even tell you how many times I
glued my eye shot far too many and
flashes are saying that you struggle
with literally just grab a pair of
falsies from like CVS or Walgreens and
just sit in front of your mirror and
practice gluing them on with no other
makeup on so you don't mess anything up
and I promise if you try out these
strategies and tips and techniques you
will eventually get way better at it but
once you have it all down we love a good
sister lash where their lashes done I
think that actually completes our eye
look for today so I'm gonna quickly
throw on a lip on some setting spray and
I'll be right back to finish off this
video all right sisters then here is the
finished completed look from today's
eyeshadow tips and tricks video you guys
know doing a crazy beautiful and
colorful eyeshadow looks is by far my
favorite partly makeup routine I had so
much fun filming today's video if you
guys did enjoy today's video and you
learn something new please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below it
really really helps me out and if you
haven't already make sure to click that
big red subscribe button down below as
well come join this sisterhood and click
that little belt icon so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup drawer you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes site itself is James
Charles the extra ass after Charles this
video sisters shadow goes to sister 8 in
it thank you so much for always
following against the party
you so much and if you'd like to be the
next videos sister shadow make sure to
always reach me maybe dueling something
go live on Twitter
alright guys I know this has been a
really really long one you are a true
sister if you made it all the way right
here to the end thank you going to NYX
for partnering with me on this video I
love you guys and I will see you in the
next one bye
[Music]