hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see today i'm joined with
two
very very special guests the developer
hi
hi i'm trying to look at the camera not
at this
i am so beyond excited because for
today's video we are doing something
that i have not done in
so so long now and that is a beauty
battle this is one of my favorite
segments that we do here on this youtube
channel but it has been a long time
because i have not had an iconic duo
such as the demilio sisters you know to
fight it out yay
do you guys have any idea what the
beauty bottles are um have you seen them
yeah i'll do one half of your face she
does the other one
sure and i win great she's probably
gonna win
but i'm not gonna quit okay sure that's
the good attitude to have
so we already obviously filmed a
collaboration together where i did your
makeup do you think that's gonna give
you an advantage in today's challenge
i think that definitely helped as well
as
the fact that i've been watching your
videos for a long time and
i know a lot of your tips and tricks
charlie watches videos and practices but
i'm going to do my best i'm going to
make you look pretty that's all that
matters at the end of the day
you already look pretty so just like
charlie said we're going to split my
face in half charlie will get one side
and dixie will get the other and in the
end it'll be up to you guys to decide
who did a better job climbing me up
we're going to talk all about their rise
to fame dixie's new music everything
going on with charlie and
also morphe 2 which is the brand new
natural beauty line that came out from
morphe with charlie and dixie are the
face of which is
super super exciting so if you guys want
to see this beauty bottle keep on
watching
[Music]
so today oh my gosh all right you guys
let's go ahead and get
started
we're starting off by using the brand
new morphe 2
skin tint that's such a fun name before
we even jump into anything like person
with this video i want to talk about a
little bit about this line because this
is really exciting to me i know this is
morphe's like
natural beauty line right yeah i haven't
heard it too much about this because
this is obviously a secret
when we're filming this and this is
still secret it will be coming out very
soon
so i'm going to let you guys tell me a
little bit about the line so basically
for us we have always been
just put up i'm so scared we have always
been into
a little bit more of a natural look
because i feel like that's what i really
enjoy wearing and
full glam is definitely out of my
comfort zone so
when morphe showed us the collection it
was like everything that i had wanted
and that was something that i
really enjoyed seeing so and like every
time we're in a meeting talking about
how everything happened the first thing
we say is charlie's natural and that's
what people like they like seeing her
personality i mean i feel like there was
a period in time on the internet for so
long where like
everybody was like full glam and i mean
hello obviously like i'm
one to talk and like still very much my
style but more than ever especially with
tick tock there's a huge emphasis on
like natural beauty which i really
really like
like i was really excited when i heard
about this line as well because like
sometimes i still want to get ready in
the morning and look cute but like not
have
fallen on anymore i love the natural
makeup look
like on you really so much yeah like
even when i started on tik tok like i
would get people saying like she doesn't
wear any makeup and i'm like no i do
it's just
very very natural because that's what i
like i also i'm a dancer
and dancing with heavy makeup is
sometimes a lot that's why i've
literally stopped filming dancing tick
tocks with makeup on
because i'm awful at dancing
and it takes me like 30 tries to
actually get the choreography down and
by the end of it i'll be literally like
wet with sweat which is
disgusting it's so bad i just can't do
it i mean i didn't even start wearing
makeup till
not even two years ago i would wear it
to like dance competitions but that was
really it
because i i also didn't feel comfortable
going out with makeup on because i was
just
so not like me but then i found products
that really worked with
the style that i was going for right how
was it working with morphe on the line
i think everything the shoot was one of
our first
like big professional shoots like that
so it was something really was it really
that we were able to experience together
that's so fun it was really cool seeing
everything come together
because we were putting on the
jelly shimmer well obviously this is a
project that you guys got to work on
together but one thing that i definitely
want to talk about since charlie and i
already did
our video dixie speaking of doing
separate things
you just released your hit song called
mary's buddies just kidding it's called
being happy
i want to hear all about it how was it
how is the reaction been okay so
i started recording um like a couple
months ago and this was the first song i
recorded and
so i grew up singing and then it was
like when this all started happening
my manager was in the music business and
he was like if you grew up singing like
you should sing
right oh no and then finally my dad was
like just do it like it's worth like
there's no point in not trying it if i
don't sing in front of anyone like
i heard you thinking like under your
breath a few times when we were hanging
out and i was like wait a second you're
like kind of
good i was like oh my gosh she's like
kind of it i literally had a panic
attack releasing the song or like
yeah in the videos i posted on take talk
i would freak out and shut off my phone
after i posted them
as an influencer it is really hard
because of course you have a major
advantage when you release a song you
know it's going to be supported and
that's an amazing thing
but you're now opening up the song to
criticism from millions and millions of
people
like that's why i haven't released a
song yet because like music is such a
huge part of my life but it's also one
thing that i made fun of so often
because there's so many awful videos of
me singing online so like if i was to
ever release music it would have to be
like the perfect
and it's so easy to lose a passion for
something if everyone's like
yeah and that's what i didn't want to do
like i didn't want to take something i
enjoyed and share it and then lose the
passion for it because
of hate comments yeah personally i think
it's a bop like i
at first i was like oh this is like a
cute little song and stuff and then i
noticed that i literally was singing it
nonstop
like i was literally just sitting in the
kitchen like sometimes i don't wanna
be oh obviously the whole like bars nice
thing has become a meme but i love that
you like joined in
on it as well like at this point you
just have to know like people just
want to make jokes i don't like it
doesn't bother me experience she's a
singer
does this look good yeah it does um also
miss charlie
you just hit 70 7-0 70 million
followers on tick-tock like that is
absolutely insane that's literally more
than the population of italy and the
population of france and the population
of australia and so
to me how like is it even possible to
process that number i feel like
in my head it's just like it's so weird
to even think about that
that's a literal country an actual
country that's crazy i want to ask you
guys as well because when we and charlie
last filmed our video
you had like just gotten here but we
were visiting but now you guys are
officially moved in
to l.a you're like girls like how is
that and are you liking it so far
um i love living with my family like i'm
glad i came out here with them
because they'll keep me from being
stupid
i like it um i mean i obviously miss my
hometown friends
a lot at the same time i've been able to
make so many friends here and i
just i can't wait to bring them all
together and like see that happen
okay so charlie you're applying the
highlighter right yes this is the
face gloss look your face that way
oh that's kind of fun yes
the lip gloss looks so good my lip gloss
is cool my lip glosses pop in
that was before your time how can i i've
never said that sentence my entire life
you said it backwards no wait what my
lip gloss is popping my lip gloss is
cool
did i say backwards oh before your time
did you ever dance like me actually oh
baby girl
have you seen my dick talks charlie do a
good interpretation of
dancing don't be rude
my body literally does not move in that
way
how would you guys describe your like
relationship living together
and also working together the worst i
literally went into her room last night
when she got home
no to show her the clothes that i got
for her
and i opened the door and she closes the
door in my face but
yesterday morning i was sleeping my
first day off in a very long time i was
sleeping it was
charlie's mad i was sleeping it's a
saturday morning and she goes
dancing knocking on the door super
exciting and i cared a lot
to let her and it was something so
stupid oh my only problem with her she
doesn't apologize
oh god i shouldn't have to apologize no
when you do things wrong you never
apologize until i forget
i'm always like can you at least
apologize she goes i'm sorry
okay which is an apology but it's not a
real
i don't know so really good is to answer
that question no no no it's the best
i like working together because we're
like there for each other because if
people like like if we don't want to
speak up for ourselves on something like
the other one can
when we're like doing stuff if like i
don't know what's if i'm not like
comfortable don't like have a personal
experience with like whatever
like she can talk about it we don't
fight that much but when we do it's bad
i see that all right well charlie and
dixie i guess that is this
beauty literal battle at this point all
complete
thank you guys so much for coming up
have my face how do you feel about your
finished locks
for me i'd say that i'm very very proud
of it and i feel like
the base super super natural which i
love but the eye i did a
little teensy bit of a glam moment i was
very very proud
sure they turned out great sure i think
mine's perfect
okay and i would take off that side and
finish it if i could and you could wear
it
great i think that both sides look
beautiful but it's going to be up to you
guys in the comments down below to let
me know whose side you guys like better
do you like charlie's or dixie's leave
us a comment down below and if you guys
enjoyed this beauty battle please don't
forget to definitely leave it a big
thumbs up down below and show your love
and support it helps us out so so so
much also click that bigger subscribe
button come join
the sisterhood we are 20 million sister
song which is
i can't even with that sentence leaving
my mouth right now i am so grateful turn
on notification bell as well so you get
notified every time
i upload a brand new video if you like
to follow me on my makeup journey all my
social media links will be right here
around the screen and if you want to
text me for updates on new videos photos
merge and so much more my phone number
is 310-905-8746 make sure you guys check
out charlie and dixie as well
hi hi i'm this video stickers out goes
to sister cherry thank you so much love
for always following and supporting i
love you so so so much and if you'd like
to be the next video's sister shout out
don't forget to always read tweet video
links
live on twitter and also to my youtube
post notifications all right you guys
thank you so much for watching this
video today i love you and we will see
you in
the next one bye
[Music]