hi sister James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel
as you guys can see it's that I have two
very very iconic and legendary special
of course this is Catherine and Austin
the ACE family and what's going on
sisters you guys excited I'm so excited
so pumped for today
really yeah artists could be good in
frogs by the way guys he just did my
makeup we did oh my god yeah I'll run
the HTML channel we just decided to give
Katherine a little bit of my sister
surprise because if she just gave birth
spoiler alert or talked about that
probably and we also just wanted to make
her feel beautiful and fun in French
with a glam but makeover and I think it
turned out so beautiful so now we need
to do a video for this channel of course
just to keep you sisters happy and for
today's video you guys are asking for
this for so so so long and it has been
way too long since I've done with these
videos we're doing a beauty now now this
series I do here on my youtube channel
where I have two special guests each
take one half my face that makeup with
the same exact product to compete and
see who is the more talented makeup
artists sisters you already know the
answer to that yeah he's pretty talented
all the same I'm saying you're pretty
talented oh well thank you
this is a competition don't try to give
me credit interesting do you know do you
know about makeup products no well I
know about this is very artistic
artistic than I am so the filler reason
why I'm saying is talented but
confidence is always key I mean I do
love a confident man okay not gonna lie
exactly but how can you obviously know a
little bit yeah I do and I just watched
do you listen to you doing my makeup
yeah I know so I feel like the playfield
is probably pretty even how do you judge
this like the sister style oh this is it
leave a comment down below let us know
who they think won
[Music]
I'm really excited okay I'd be honest
guys one thing you must do is be honest
okay don't say you know Catherine won
because she's beautiful you know honest
so do we only have one foundation how
we're running a little bit lower she's
on a bunch I was like oh sorry
we just get started no you just gone to
your into your house there's no clock
that like when you ends and another
thing don't judge like this our first
time probably judges and don't like make
fun oh yeah sisters be nice a nice
family okay we're trying our best
so where do we start so that's your
problem
all right so there's nothing not to get
the oil off first before I proceed oh
okay
I love when you get my oils off before
you proceed my favorite thing that you
do Ostend so how do i do my side of the
nose if there's just one nose and one
the middle first of all you to
congratulations on the beautiful baby
sister la ah thank you so much wolfies
headed in the entire world
yes more kids oh let me already we do
really not right now like five kids
i just literally just birth them at I
was gonna say damn let her run a weeks
ago about some letter but at least like
four minutes come on like I'm gonna be
quiet sometimes somebody taking this
issue seriously so don't mind me
we love a concentrated me I'm very
determined when it comes to a
competition awesome what's that finally
gathered how many kids do you want I
want just one more boy I'm done okay so
the brother is me
not literally to sister out Louisville
area she's obsessed with her really he's
actually too obsessed with her it's
almost scary I feel like we give her so
much love that she just knows she's
she's good does have a reason to be
jealous I was not excited my mom told me
we were having another one in the family
accessories I decided as I need to be an
only child did you just take this
foundation I'm not sure we're sharing
cousin how is it adjusting to like not
paint pregnant anymore
honestly yes just cuz I was so over it
really um I don't know how to act though
like I forget that sometimes like I
don't have a baby in my belly and I like
grab my belly yeah but it's okay because
I'm like at that awkward stage right now
where I don't close right where I'm not
pregnant but I look like I may be
pregnant still sound like it's okay like
people don't know oh my god damn I'm
good
don't look at it hard yet okay just I'm
not I'm a shot being fix I can always
pay sighs yeah a little beauty mark in
the middle of your chin
I have beauty marks all over my face
yeah but you guys don't don't we trying
to get along we're best friends now you
can no you relax
so I've been just having you guys for
literally over a year now and I it's
gonna be really embarrassing
I just realized probably about roughly
two weeks ago that a family was like
Boston Kathryn my mouth oh my gosh
really
so what do you think Iowa I generally
don't know no I didn't think that you
thought that we just picked that like
who's and then it all hit me nothing oh
wow
will you be changing the name no the
sister-like is here no so that was like
a question but acfm oh no no no
so we were thinking of names
with either a C or an 8 because we
didn't want to change the name yeah if
we round exactly campus our names are
used a three way yeah so we thought of a
so the aim just goes in with my a and
yeah is the same okay what if we have a
boy hmm it could potentially change like
really change this time that's all I can
really say because we already had the
names picked out before Ace was even
nothing we love a branded family
honestly you know I think I would read
in family because I just think this is
so cool awesome even they're talking to
you today when we were shopping earlier
you were very into like obviously
contact pictures but also the business
side which hello I love the most you
guys joined YouTube how many two years
ago yes and you're now at 13 million
correct love that for you that's good
and fun and fresh Thanks same for me I
just joined two years ago when I'm about
to have ten kind of I'm not for us
so fun how was your guys's life's
changed drastically and a lot of good
ways and a lot of
not-so-good ways but it's changed for
the better I definitely think that
really we enjoy what we do so it's just
a blessing to be able to wake up and do
what you love every single day but
sometimes it does get a little bit
overwhelming just little incidents here
and there that happen and you're just
like well this is my life now my life
has changed mainly because we show so
much I think right just like our daily
lives like we show like our daughter
people see us like that day and they're
like oh I know what you wore yesterday
saw you yesterday so they really feel
like they know you which is amazing but
sometimes it can get a little scary
giving it giving you a little plump so
don't don't mind it I'm gonna jump in
adjust it I love with the pump it's okay
so yes I'm thinking it a little scary
because you're showing things that maybe
you shouldn't be showing so that's one
thing that we've had to learn along the
way I think everyone on social media has
to learn that at some point like when I
first started out I was posting
everything and I also got them all a lot
of drama
and my like community as well and would
always tweet about it and I was like oh
I need to stop doing that probably
immediately right now since I've kind of
matured and grown up in space and just
gotten older and really figured out like
what I can and can't be posting because
obviously there's a lot of people
watching my life is not like way better
after figuring that out yeah it's
definitely learning as you go you better
give me those angles in order to be
successful I love giving you a goes in
order to be successful well has been der
guys's coolest like fan experience we've
had a couple everything I brought our
fans our woosh furnace sisters even come
from my best friend's father help me
make a Halloween constantly here and
when he did when he finished that I
literally said thank you sister Marco no
idea why I really could not tell you why
and it just wait I can use his brushes
as well yeah of course what has been
Durga's his best like a family member
experience definitely the East family's
Eskimo Joe yeah I was gonna say that and
you were there yeah I was there I was so
excited to go because that was my first
time getting to meet you guys Alison I
don't know if you remember this but all
I saw you guys at Coachella and this is
what I haven't really three or so
million I know I didn't you grew that
fat ass yeah just happened yeah gee kind
of fun you guys were running into the
artists area I wanted to go say hi you
did because I was already following you
guys but you I missed you you already
gone even Louis yeah really
my best friend Laura's been watching you
guys literally since you started and she
has the baby as well as so she like is
obsessed with just keeping up with you
guys so she actually introduced me to
your guys's channel and I just thought
you really liked this vide as ever
so I've been also subscribed for a while
too and I knew they
what's happening on I need to come what
I want to be you guys yes it was so fun
literally I showed up there yeah I'm
Rena what Wow as soon as I walked him I
was like oh do not know that I have a
similar demographic it's a lot of
talking to CID sisters there yeah the
boss will get him hello not my usual
surroundings right but it was so fun
like I thought it was such a cool event
I saw so many it like amazing people
that are and how they the best time and
often as well I could be a cheerleader
on the side cheerleader yeah you perform
probably shows mr. song yeah sing a
sister song I'll sing the national
anthem by the way you guys Austin and
Katherine are using Oh tada my palette
with more oh hello it's definitely worth
it I will say no I'm not just saying
that we do Katherine's eyes using a few
of the warm tone shades in the top few
rows closing my eyes turned out pretty
good in French if I do say so myself
and he used the highlighter called face
and it's part of the palette he used
that for this part of my face that's
like shining shimmering splendid awesome
walk us through your luxe what do you
want to die so right now I'm going for
looks like rose a rose petal look Erin
as if you're going on a date really
romantic I love you been here for my
relationships all day yes so okay good
also you're talking on white boy
problems earlier and he was doing lots
of good advice it's very like this
sentiment to look romantic I love them
want him to feel like you appreciate
know I definitely do alright so you want
to almost give him your old everything
you have to offer that's okay I love
that what are you going for sister well
I'm going for the Lego
astronaut
for the brunch and I oh I love it about
brunch by date cell it's like normal to
get a snack no I'm going for like a vibe
we're like you're gonna take Instagram
picture
oh that's a good both good bonsoir I
just want you to know that what I'm
gonna do there's gonna be a couple
things there you never be used to but
it's so scary to hear what the sentence
is gonna finish but I just want you to
know that people are gonna think it
looks good okay so it just becomes roll
with whatever you you know you're the
artist tonight the whole motto of my
campaign is to unleash your inner artist
and I think that's what it's going on
here it's very pigmented belly is mm-hmm
have either one of you ever done
somebody else's makeup before no what it
all will start experimenting with makeup
will you let her and at what age do you
think she's gonna be 30 I'll definitely
let her for sure she watches me do my
makeup every day as far as like her
wearing makeup I don't think I'll let
her until she's learning dirt I started
wearing makeup at like 14 and it wasn't
like obviously wasn't heavy but I wear
like some eyeliner some lipstick
brighter like lip gloss I don't want to
be that contradicting like tell her she
can't wear makeup and Here I am I
wearing right well awesome there's a
reason why you say older because she
won't be dating until she's probably 30
so I think everything will happen when
she's 30 okay my parents now are like my
biggest fans in the entire world but
well I first sorry to cut you off I
don't like that the sisters can't really
see what I'm working with
I'd like to just show first we get okay
cuz when you look straight you can't
really give him the full sauce whatever
Saturn what is this it's just it's calm
I said he's gonna feel comfortable bit
when I'm done okay it's not fully
finished
yeah I know when I first are doing we
can my parents were definitely like
concerned they want me to wear either
just because they thought that I was
using it that's like a way to like
validate myself or feel good but I kind
of explained like it is hard to express
yourself next off you're messing up my
side I guess
not being touched do you have a little
sister chapstick thank you nothing judge
just yet I know I'm complimenting you oh
well thank you give me to look real good
I'm looking for the glow uh-huh the
global scigirls crystal thanks oh I love
scripts I need I need a little bit well
there is a beautiful red shade in the
palette I see okay awesome obviously
sometimes when you DM me about what like
we wanted to do a video together I was
excited
cuz I think you guys don't really do
collabs that often I don't really see
you anyway
yeah youtuber s you guys obviously live
a very private life right who like are
some of your favorite people to walked
in the community I think since I'm like
all about like learning I love to learn
yeah I love to keep up with like what
everyone is doing
i watch everyone I got watch people from
what you do you're all people from doing
like parkour from doing like the eating
challenges like literally everyone even
little baby kids channels yeah I do my
research I studied I'm not really a fan
of nobody or watch like someone specific
or just watch people over and over I
just study the entire market so it's
important to be knowledgeable of the
space that you're working at exactly
yeah I watch a lot of people too
so when people say like oh do you know
about this person yes I know about them
because I study what they do right and I
feel like everyone should because you
should be up-to-date with what's going
almost a new trend
ya know it's definitely stressful it
takes how are you like he'll be like Oh
H like this is a cool idea or like hey
did you know about this and I'm just
like my phone's dead
my biggest thing is like trying to stay
ahead of the curve like one step ahead
saying what's out there you know and by
doing that you should you have to know
what everyone else is doing right is
there anybody that you like watching for
the inspiration there's anybody that you
like think is really killing it right
now you you for sure I was trying to
hire you myself but you over there doing
a damn thing a slightly busy I know I
was like I'm Keith you might wake up
again and he's like um I'm available
outside we look so close to each other's
and now we have no what is going to
spice your look up a little more you
don't have to add my favorite color
which is the color of what your car your
car basketballs and my god yes yes right
air is gonna really bring your presence
out because sometimes in like that's
gonna give another one side mcbroom
touch the touch but also when you're
with someone or going on a date you can
are like you don't really like give them
that like all yeah kind of like has its
it a little bit but this one's gonna be
like I'm here okay right they're gonna
top that off a little bit it's a really
big motel just okay damn my site looks
beautiful
how long have you guys been together
four years
[Music]
how do you guys meet we met at a party
we met at Johnny bucks did you really
she delivered my hamburger really oh
that would've been some few so we met up
event right and I seen her for the first
time
uh-huh I mean already before not in
person I seen her on social media mm-hmm
and I was like this woman is absolutely
gorgeous right yes I seen a person I was
like how does it even possibly be more
gorgeous than new pictures because
usually it's the other way around yeah
you see like a pictures picture the hi
pictures hot and the person's like you
not you know
so I seen her out I was like yo this
woman is absolutely delicious but I
didn't ask the number because I was like
I want scene with a creeper kind of keep
it cool for the first school the crazy
thing was before I met her we already
phone each other on Twitter I was
applying don't Instagram no Twitter
because I didn't join
Twitter in order to be epsilon xx before
I was something following like tech
people
exactly exactly already on I thought it
was funny on vine he already had a vibe
so so I DM her you know I had to resort
some deal yeah even though I got a slide
in North you always have to sign them
and so I slid in about a week or two
after I met her mm-hmm and was just like
yo would you like to go to dinner and
she kind of said no no I so then I kind
of was like okay whatever so then we did
talk like a couple weeks after that so I
was persistent to hit her again huh and
she was like well I'm not doing anything
tonight Sol's okay you know what be
ready by 9:00 and sure ass is ready me
literally saying yeah I love so you got
to be persistent and you've got to be
confident and that's what I was so I
picked her up and I took her to Nobu for
those don't know Nobu is a sushi spot
I hate and yeah we come to find out we
boudin sushi which in a working on so
that's so cute we had a great
conversation uh-huh you know and then
after that we didn't talk for a month
I thought listen I thought like okay how
it was - I did a great job I thought you
know I have a good conversation and I
thought she was filling me so I dropped
her off I dropped her off she'd even get
out and give me a hug she said she said
I was like old house and creative hard
because I was like no so then we didn't
talk for like a couple weeks a month and
then out the blue she hit me up was like
you wanted one a hike and I was like and
then
from that day forward we've been
together ever since every single day
every single day ever since she won't
let me leave
that is crazy okay so you like the chase
then like you were down for the
hard-to-get moment you were ready to
fight the battle yeah I'm not really
about the chase I like I think what I
like and I know what I want yeah and I
knew that she was playing hard to get
so I did get her so you're playing so
you were gonna chase I was in the chase
okay I want to make meola Jusuf I sorry
Liv I'm going for the choice that we
have to be ready clean like the chase
yeah really good really see you like a
little rabbit might even just like chase
the Chola forgot we had these to work
you're gonna want to turn these a little
bit they don't eat your own they do
natural is the best way to go it's all
gonna fall together
don't even look okay what do you mean my
little way better than yours this is a
continuous saying this this is to give
away all of the hate I'm gonna be lost
about time
okay you guys upload three days a week
man and they're all like pretty lengthy
vlogs right and you edit them yourself
how they said three times a week we
literally just film edit pull same day
so what is so crazy to me
so we'll wake up around like man o'clock
we'll make sure all the girls everyone's
ready by 11:00 we'll start filming by
11:30
don't fight from 11:30 to about 4:30 and
then I'm literally right after 10:00
filming I get straight to editing it
takes in two or three hours and I'll be
L by 7:00 and my side let me just clear
things up good something's up it's hairy
controversy is there another sister
scandal so I'm done with this site it's
very like natural fairy dust like okay
one last time of the hairs sister spray
and call them correct yes thank you
sister settings right are we done we are
done oh yeah Austin I love this approach
that you went with right here
I remember remember remember what I said
this look is very like you want that
person to feel oh you don't want like
that sighs more like soft like oh come
to me
Catherine loving the foundation on your
side looks beautiful the laughs the plan
oh you apply the logic down right on
there from my angle is a little tilted
so it's definitely not in the middle of
your eyeball so I don't know where
you're getting real brave critiquing her
over there if he ever needs his
eyelashes supplies okay I'll call you
from looking beautiful I'm kind of
looking beautiful looking nice
yeah cousin you did a really good job
thank you love this foundation looks
pretty good okay love this eyeshadow
color choice I'm assuming you I would
probably you're kidding and then some
good 5:08 your favorite orange shade
yeah that's the Lambo correct that you
almost killed us and earlier my favorite
part is the eyelash that was glued to
the middle of my eyelid
I really love the lip application okay
so back to what we're talking about yeah
you want to be aggressive with it so the
approach is really like just ready like
ready for a boy to come over yes that's
night is very so besides like he walks
in these and you guys both look each
other like what are we doing tonight and
this I don't know he walks in and you
want that you don't want someone who's
just laid-back Oh y'all need that okay
no we love we're sending a message with
these guys laughs okay so what do we
leave it up to the society ah I love
both walks and then I think maybe serve
to have like a story behind they do and
that I love what Simone that's what it's
about truly thank you guys for joining
me today on this amazing video talk
about young you guys are a little advice
if I has been a huge inspiration to me
and the YouTube community
congratulations on 13 million
baby on all your amazing growth I think
it's been that such a pleasure to watch
you guys that I cannot wait to see
everything that is in store for the
future
we appreciate it thank you so much for
having us Thank You sisters for having
us
and all these sisters as well as Jane
Charles are a part of this family
yes a lot about you guys if you enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give a thumbs up down below and
definitely the comment let us know who's
side and you think one sister Katherine
I need you I want you you know what I'm
gonna give you bigger subscribe button
down below as well
come join this sisterhood we are so
close to 10 million subscribers click
that like them so you can get
notifications every time I upload a
brand new video exactly get your best
friends get your granny's everybody to
hit that subscribe button because plenty
of 10 million so so much time so you
don't excited I cannot thank you guys
for all your support
speaking of support tomorrow's the
release of my first ever make a product
with Murphy it was a beautiful palette
that I've worked hard for so many months
now and you can check it out at morbid
can I open it maybe give you their every
color of the rainbow it got it all okay
you guys can check it out on warm calm
and youth coach James fort ever saw off
your purchase as me 10% oh yes a good
sister discount oh I'm gonna order and
it'll also be available at Ulta on
November 16 if you like to follow me on
their makeup dirty can follow me on
Instagram Twitter they're both the same
Charles my sound check from or or how
this deep sites up is Jane Charles the
next request after Charles we're hang on
you guys and I'm really got around I'm
good at that I know do you want to tell
the sisters where they can go join the
aged family as well yes all you gonna do
is type in that ace family on YouTube
and hit that subscribe button over on
their Channel and me and sister Austin
decided together sister Katherine and
beautiful faux clambake or the tune
right right now so appreciative love it
Oh
I'm taking around good whenever we want
to go out again we might need you
you have my number now it's gonna be
good and we're only a few minutes away
we're make it look right here hmm I want
to get you okay you look at like a big
snack that was an awesome bag this video
is sister shadow goes to sister Debbie
ah thank you so much for always
following and supporting noir livid
literally itself so so much and a beauty
to the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always reach me we're
bitterly something alive on Twitter all
right you guys thank you so much
watching this videos today we love you
and we will see you in the next one
[Music]
[Applause]
unleash your inner artist