hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 channel as you guys can
see I am not exactly in my normal studio
setup the white wall and beautiful
lighting is nowhere to be found
I am currently outside shocker I left my
house for once a beautiful pool behind
me at nature trees Birds Plains you guys
it is literally the best weekend of the
entire year because I am an in do
California with all my best friends here
for a coach I am obsessed with Coachella
it is by far my favorite time of the
entire I've been looking forward to this
for 365 days now okay like I don't know
why it's just such good vibes I love
being here I love listening to the music
I love spending time with my best
closest friends that mean the absolute
world to me I love taking Instagram
photos if you guys remember last year we
kind of shook up the nation just a
little bit with the outfits the
Instagram photos and the lookbook that
we posted and if y'all thought that was
crazy
oh we're kicking it off just a few
notches this year y'all know that I did
not come to play and I am so excited to
show you guys all my looks and outfits
which you will see at the end of this
video but for right now I just wanted to
sit down and do a fun little get ready
with me it is so beautiful outside so
we're just going to chit chat I was the
makeup and get festival ready
[Music]
super-quick Before we jump into the
video I want to give a major shout-out
to Sikhi for sponsoring this video and
also my overall Coachella experience I
reached out to them and I was like
listen guys I want to bring eleven of my
best friend's to VIP I Coachella how do
you make this happen and they said
sister absolutely and I am so beyond
grateful for working with them in case
you guys do not know seeking is an
amazing app that basically puts tickets
to all your favorite live events or
concerts all until one place it makes it
so easy to shop so you can actually
focus on what's most important which is
being there and having a really good and
fresh time I am so grateful that I got
to work with them on today's video and
if you use code James on the app you get
$20 off your first set of tickets thank
you going up for them to sponsoring it
check it out download it using the link
below and let's jump into the video all
right you guys so the first step of my
makeup routines today is of course going
to be at moisturizing it you guys know
my writer diet is the tatcha dewy skin
cream the air here is literally so dry
like I am scared then again we are in
the desert so I should have expected
this but like it's borderline gross I
feel like my lungs are being filled with
dirt which is not fun feeling just in
case you've never experienced that
before I wouldn't recommend 0 out of 10
there's gonna grab a nice little
generous glob on my fingers and really
brought this in for a real one jumping
right into foundation I'm gonna grab my
Too Faced Born This Way in the shade
golden for today at quite darker than at
the normal Charles skin tone I did get a
spray tan of course to be nice and
golden for Coachella it's literally so
hot here though that I've been sweating
it off in my sleep that is so disgusting
you probably do not want to hear that
but we're gonna try our best to
much I said try I didn't say try
dispatches will a knock though perhaps I
shouldn't mix in a little something else
do you smell that
I saw scandal ok flake this is actually
a pretty decent color for my skin
honestly and the sunlight like it's
really hard to even tell us a lot really
good
but luckily most have like my neck and
my top it's gotta be covered in the look
that I'm wearing today my bottom not so
much but we can definitely get away with
a little bit of a color match I mean
we've done it and everybody on the path
so who's stopping us now I think we
should just like chitchat and catch up
while I'm getting ready today because I
don't do these like very often and it is
always so fun to just catch up with you
guys and talk to you and now UN on
what's going on in my life right now
pretty happy
not gonna lie I've been able to say that
in kind of a long time now which
actually really excited things have
finally been looking up going in the
right direction I'm working on a lot of
really really exciting things and if the
business world that I'm super pumped for
I'm just really really excited for this
weekend and to see everybody that I love
and know and honestly for the future too
it's been a rough past couple of weeks
or something with a lot of stuff but
truly like Coachella was like the thing
that I was looking forward to the
absolute most and I am just so happy and
thankful and blessed that I get to be
here with literally like every single
person that means the absolute most to
me in this world obvious you guys have
met a lot of my best friends from the
best friends expose video but I'm here
with Laura and Cassie and hay-zu's and
drew and Elton and Victor and Louis my
editor who you guys will meet definitely
very very soon
even though this is a music festival I
obviously am here for work I'm filming
this video today and Alpha Chi Coachella
are very very important for influencers
love to be honest even though I am here
for work it is like a mini vacation at
the same time and it just feels so good
to take a little bit of time off and to
just focus on the people that mean the
most to me and just have a really really
good time that was so good
speaking of that being so good you guys
oh my god yesterday I announced that I
deficiency be performing on the
Coachella mainstage on Sunday at the
closing day right before Ariana my brand
new hit single a wolf won't won't um
literally bigger stage I've ever been on
it's so exciting no but can you actually
imagine a house before that go tell like
how Lent and
that would be holy crap this one band
called razor bumps actually it's
performing at Coachella and I tweeted a
few days ago because obviously if you
guys were here last year you would know
that I didn't exactly have the best luck
when it came to shaving my you know down
there and it turned into quite the
controversial topic on of social media
which first of all is so crazy literally
every single person in the entire world
has gotten razor bumps at some point in
their life let's be honest if you're
telling you that you have not then
you're a liar it's a very very normal
thing but this year just let you know
I've been getting laser hair removal
every six weeks and down there it's
currently completely hairless we're
ready to go ready to be out and revealed
and there will not be a scandal this
year but oh my god when I tweeted that I
was actually performing like that as a
joke so many people thought I was being
it serious that my name James Charles
was literally trending number three
worldwide on the Apple music charts
because people were looking for my
single that I was gonna be performing
like this actually happened which I
thought was literally one of the
funniest things in the entire world you
guys always that shocked me and how
powerful you are like I always forget
that making jokes like that could
actually lead to something very very
serious I love being an influencer when
using my platform for the right things
but those are the mr. crazy so I love
you so much
all jokes aside unfortunately I will not
be performing at Coachella this year but
you never know what next year has to
hold it's not a Coachella performance I
guarantee you that just contains a quick
spritz of the morphine prep and set
settings right and then I was gonna be a
little bit of the laura mercier
translucent setting powder and sat in on
my face I could literally just sit here
and stare at the camera for five minutes
and my foundation would completely dry
down that's literally how dry the air is
here but I do want to make sure I set
like under my eyes and then or my
forehead just to avoid a creasing it
because I will definitely be sweating it
later on and then once that is all set
in place I'm just going to use my usual
Anasazi Beverly Hills contour kit and my
morphe
for all five just to chisel off my face
but sense my foundation is a little bit
darker I'm just gonna go a little bit
heavier this time that could be
literally the worst mistake of my life
oh my god we just like what this here's
actual like music lineup for the
festival - I'm so pumped for the last
few years I'm not gonna lie I definitely
was more in it
Instagram photos just because even
though I love music and it's such a big
part of my life there are not that many
artists that I like specifically listen
to I definitely the type person that
just turns on the radio and just sings
along with whatever is currently on and
enjoys it
but this year I think there's so many
artists that I was actually looking
forward to getting to watch last night I
watched Burbank for the first time and
it was literally like a life-changing
experience I announced on Twitter a few
days ago that I'm officially a Stan okay
I'm a fellow blink and I got to see them
live last night in the artist section 2
which was so crazy because they were
literally right there I am beyond
obsessed with black pink Jenny at least
outros a jisu I love you guys literally
the obstacles in the entire world just
truly one of the most incredible
experiences and performances I've ever
seen the dancing the choreography not a
single beat mess not a single word miss
not a single note mess like absolute
perfection I am beyond obsessed Kacey
Musgraves perform yesterday I heard to
see a little bit of her set bazi
performs today I'm so excited to watch
him Billie is on stage tonight and I am
so pumped oh my god this is gonna be my
first time ever seeing her live
I am a true Billie I list and right now
I am like obsessed with her brand new
album I think it is so beyond incredible
I just discovered her music a few months
ago but I've been listening to it
literally non-stop and I think her vibe
is just so what different and so cool to
watch she really inspires me I would
love to video with her one day I think
there'll be the craziest thing ever I
know she literally never wears makeup
but like just imagine a one-time full
glam moment would be so fun and fresh I
think tame impala is later on tonight as
well tomorrow is ariana grande oh my god
I cannot wait to see all of her newest
songs performed live I was gonna try to
go to her la tour saw but unfortunately
I'll be traveling when she's here so I
get to see her at Coachella which is so
fun and so fresh Ariana's definitely my
favorite performers as well I went to
her concert a few years ago and it was
just absolutely mind-boggling so it's
just a really really cool year so I'm
really excited to actually go and be
able to listen to the music and watch
the performances rather than just be and
Instagram body which is like what
everybody makes fun of Coachella for
definitely can admit that that's been me
in the past but not this year
she's a body and a music lover Trudy
want to say hi hi everyone
I like a little crusted and dusted but
that's okay though everybody's James
looks good so all the matters who are
you most excited to watch black/pink
yeah black paint box well Emmitt little
over today I know I'm Silas today around
the house were you I love working out
for everyone in the back like this
- ciao for now alright you guys I am
back and my browser all completed I just
went ahead into the off camera quickly
using my Anasazi Beverly Hills at brown
products as always the lighting out here
is a little bit wonky and I kept making
them uneven but regardless we are here
and we're ready to move on to eyeshadow
I'm going to be using the James house
isomorphic palette of course my look
today is all white so I do want to do
something with a fun that pop of color a
good little rainbow look I know I did do
a rainbow look last year and my
Coachella corrected me but you know what
we're gonna do it again and y'all are
gonna do with it and it's gonna be a
little bit different but still fun and
fresh and very pretty so let's jump
right in I'm gonna first artifact our
Miami Ducks dogs birds what planes what
else dunks I'm gonna first know if I
could Miami 4 3 3 brushing I'm going to
first start off our guy from I am 4 3 3
brush and dipping to be the bright
yellow shade of the palette and I'm
going to pack this in the inner corner
and then grabbing another Emperor 3 3
I'm going to dip into skip the bright
neon pink in the bottom hand corner shut
up dog and I'm just going to put this in
the crease right next to be all they're
not I just realize I'm literally putting
my mom and my dad right next to each
other on my eye for beat and scab
legends I'm gonna dip into a little bit
more of B with that same M 4-3-3 brush
from before and just go back over the
top of it and blend over the skip as
well just to make sure they're nice and
blended together and to create a little
bit of an orange shade gonna grab a
little bit of five 1/8 and put this
right between as well next to the 4 5 6
I'm gonna dip into a little bit of it
single and put this right next door to
skip just a very very little bit of this
shade and then finally with one more I'm
four five six just going to dip into a
little bit of both Cola and playground
and mix those together and use this to
create an outer
wait wow I'm loving how this is turning
out so far oh my god
thank God okay cool now I'm gonna grab
me a little bit more of a cola on that
same brush and start talking this right
into the lower lash line a little bit of
single right next to it a little bit of
skip and then finally a little bit more
of B to bring it full circle I'm gonna
use the Jeffrey's our drug lord liquid
lipstick to cut my crease before that
I'm gonna got the m45 sticks that I had
at Cola on and dip into a little bit of
a playground and use this to blend
together the white and the dark blue and
then just using a little bit of a
flashback on a flat paka brush to set
the rest okay guys I think that is
pretty much the eyeshadow portion of
this look all complete literally so easy
only took a few colors from the palette
still very very colorful but not exactly
rainbow last year's look was definitely
way darker and waist fougere where's
this here as much brighter more vibrant
and I absolutely love it
I'm gonna head in grab my lash curler
and get my lashes a nice curl and apply
my favorite mascara knock excited to
play and then get ready to pop on a pair
of lashes all right you guys and that is
one eye of my drag inspired colorful
festival makeup look all complete I'm
gonna go ahead and do the other one off
camera quickly and I'll be right back to
finish off the rest of the look all
right you guys we are back and both eyes
are all complete I am literally obsessed
with house look at turning out I'm now
going to quickly go ahead and spritz my
face using the morphe preppin set
setting so I just because it is so so so
dry and then of course using a face to
highlight could end up into a little bit
of literally on my eforp blush brush and
use this to blend together our face and
my contour because I really want this
look to be nice and blushed just popping
a little bit of glitter over top of my
highlight just for an extra fun little
pop I'm gonna pop on my favorite nude
lip combo the color pop I love Satta a
liner in a kirby and finally the ofra
liquid lipstick in the shade it's a palo
which you can use go James for 30 for 30
and finally the last step with this
makeup routine it just a little bit of
the mac fix+ and the shade of gold Lee
not only to kind of set everything in
please just add some hydration but also
a little bit of pop of gold glitter so
we are turning heads everywhere that we
go
although with the outfits that you guys
are about to see in the lookbook portion
of this video I think heads are about to
be turnin regardless all right sisters
and that is this colorful festival drag
inspired makeup look all complete this
is actually so easy to create and I
would love to see if you
to recreate this on your faces today I'm
about to rock this to the festival but
although my makeup may be complete I
cannot show up to the festival without
an iconic outfit to match we did not
come to play this year if you guys
thought last year was crazy oh you just
wait my channel is normally pg-13 but
viewer discretion is advised for the
lookbook that you're about to see
[Music]
all right sisters thank you so much Raj
in this vessel get ready with me and
luck luck I've literally been looking
forward to uploading this video since we
uploaded the same one last year this has
been such a fun tradition I would love
to keep on doing this with all of you
guys I am so thankful to be able to
attend these festivals with all my best
friends and to see you at sister's there
if you did it or this makeup book and
all the looks that we came up with
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs out down below until your sister
love and support it truly does mean the
world and helps me out a lot and if you
have not already managed to click that
big red subscribe button down below and
come join these sisterhood we are 16
million sisters song I would absolutely
love to have you join the family and
makes you click that belt it comes to
you get notification every time I upload
a brand new video
if you like to follow me and I may come
turn you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both the same Charles my
snapchat more behind the scenes side
stuff is James Charles the next to ask
after Charles this video is sister shout
it goes to sister julienne thank you so
much love for always falling in
supporting you know I love you literally
so so so much and if you like to the
next videos with sister shadow don't
forget to always retweet my video
leastly go live on Twitter and also turn
on my youtube post notifications
alright you guys thank you so much
watching this videos tonight thank you
again to see keek for working with me on
this I love you guys so so so much and I
will see you in the next one five
[Applause]
[Music]