hi sisters to use Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you can see I'm done with a very very
special guest today with my best friends
in the entire world Amanda and saying
wow I mentioned I have been friends for
a very very long time and we've been
trying to film for a very very long time
and saying we are finally sitting down
and doing so thank God if you guys don't
know who Amanda is she is amazing beauty
guru on YouTube but she's also my
closest friends we have been friends for
a very very long time like I said we've
been trying to film has never worked out
until today so we're friendly coming to
you with this video she has been with me
through so much she's giving me so much
advice and helping me through a whole
stuff there's something with a lot of
boy stuff as well which we're talking
about later on in the video so
definitely stay tuned for a lot of
really deep and fun conversations with
stuff that we've encountered and like
stuff that we've learned from our
experience dating in the beauty world
and all that type of stuff I have a
confession
what this is only the second time
anyone's ever done my makeup what oh my
god oh my god this is so exciting so I
put together this look on Amanda's face
today any killing it we came up with
this cut crease chartreuse liner type
situation we really want to just think
out of Amanda's comfort zone she does
tend to wear a lot of very very
beautiful and like glam natural style
makeup but I really wanted to like for
sure and do something that she would
never normally do bolt them in and I had
very very straight brow shape and she
said that creases are not saying that
she ever does so of course that's what I
put on her face today that's looks so so
Bob if you guys want to see how I
created this super fun and easy look and
hear all about our lives and all the
secrets and all thirteen all the cough
make sure you ready again for this keep
on watching the benefit Porefessional
primer
mainly I use hourglass mineral veil NYX
angel ville the Porefessional is great
it's my favorite
Amanda has like deep most perfect skin
in the history no way yes sister
so Mays row nation today we're using of
course my holy girl and apparently this
is Amanda's too because she brought it a
makeup ever Ultra HD foundation shake in
the shade why 2:45 I was hoping it would
be Y 315 that's what I should
I go by the number of mines 120 I don't
know donation is the best I've liked
everyone so miss Amanda do you have a
new man in your life I do
so I started dating someone about 7
months ago actually did every week it's
been 7 months I was in a relationship
for such a long time that you get so
guarded it's so hard to let someone back
into your life and your social media
your followers like people who watch
your videos they're your family so I
don't just show them anybody right so
and I wanted like time to be with myself
and work out myself and then we met just
randomly like at a Halloween party and I
was like I wouldn't date him that we
were friends for a while and then it
just like happens to me at least expect
it yeah those of you guys who don't know
if you follow me on Twitter or snapchat
you know that I get myself into boy
drama quite often like it really excited
over like a straight guy and then I get
my heart hurt for no reason when I had
no chance in the furnace place I'm very
very bad knocking this but recently
however I've been getting myself
involved a lot of like guys so we're
kind of on the DL or more like closeted
or not really kinda rolled their
sexuality but at the same time like
still are talking to you which is fine
but at the same time it's like it's a
lot to deal with in it's something
that's very very powerful just because
like I'm so open and comfortable myself
it's totally okay but it's frustrating
for me at the same time and it's saying
that I don't really know how to handle
and and I have had to sell money like
late night like two hour-long FaceTime
calls where she's just like listen James
get your together but like oh my
gosh she's been like my see it's really
not your fault like I mean you have to
keep yourself guarded right and it's
hard because you wanna believe that
someone's nice and they're so nice at
first and everything's great like how
could it go wrong and then they're
immature or it's I mean I can't relate
to the closet thing obviously because I
haven't been with that but I just have
one of my best friends and he deals with
that too and it just sucks because it's
like okay well then what are you doing
like I'm not something you can hide
right like if you're with me or with me
like I want a normal relationship and
you deserve that but you deserve so much
better and like I've told you like it'll
weed out all the bad ones to try to
waste your time but when I first moved
to LA I didn't go on a date for a while
I think I only went on a couple
and they were not good and it was just
like I wish I could like write a book or
like do like story time videos on all
the stuff that would happen I don't know
I how many things that would get I know
but I feel like a lot of them still
watch my stuff which is super weird and
I don't get them it's like they don't
want you but then they don't like don't
want you to move on as anybody thought
for a reason though when I look at all
the relation to work out I'm like no no
I'm happy that it didn't work out hmm
that's one thing they would be every
time I've like got into like a weird
thing where I've like called you at like
three I mean the world a week later I'm
like oh my god I think I got something
it's like it's almost like it
rose-colored glasses on or something
because they seem so amazing and you put
them on a pedestal and then you get out
you're like no I'm poppin to collect
remember space today I'm using the Kat
Von D shade and light palette my Holy
Grail and my morphe Anna 405 brush for
the first time ever if you want to get
money off your order at morphe brushes
you can use cone james or quote amanda
for 10% off so what's the T with the new
boys oh my god well I just got back from
playlist in Orlando which you should
have went to buddy well I'm crashing I'm
like I'm million different people right
now that's the team but I'm trying to
keep these ones like on the DL they very
very like just like let it happen
actually if it's supposed to happen and
don't if it's not gonna happen only in
the past me to be like over excited and
like getting my hopes up really quickly
has it not worked out see this is my
once you get them home the control it's
like they know it I don't know what it
is they love the chase and then once
they know that they have you they're
like play games see because the thing is
I like the chase like that's me like I'm
barely competitive like I like a good
challenge and stuff so like that's what
gives me and then it me over every
single time do you feel like whenever
you're darting someone like they know
you like them like you're very open
about it yeah I usually I'm like very
ferocious no you ever as empower wins
you have to keep the power yeah I'm like
flirting though I was like thinking oh
this movie there's gonna let my flirting
is so like strange like I'll be talking
to some guy and he'll like say something
nice and be like I hate you so much died
like that in my language that's like I
want you to make out me like more than
anything in the entire world I don't
know why I do it I I don't know probably
so ugly I don't even know we're gonna
Amanda's face make for a few minutes now
while we do that we're gonna move right
on to it the eyebrows those are a pair
of bras right there so people ask you
like wine growing recently do so much
with them I feel like my forehead is so
big to it five to you
we're gonna take a little bit of a cut
crease line or situation here on Amanda
so we're gonna be something off with
deep morphe 35o palette and once again
code james or code amanda for 10% off
I'm gonna start off by grabbing this
liner brush from the morphe rolls gold
collection and dip into this warm brown
shade right up in here so Amanda's
latest face is very very similar to mine
in the fact that we both have a pretty
straight brow shapes and not much like
the way when you actually open your eye
so I'm gonna have to do a little bit of
a low cut crease here but that's totally
okay and it will doubly look regardless
there just won't be a lot of like space
to blend but we're gonna make it work
as always I'm gonna grab this morphe r39
brush and dip into this light warm shade
right here and I'm gonna blend out that
light a little bit how do you do your
cut creases do you like start off by a
blending a lot together then deepening
and then cutting it with concealer
yeah usually I'll blend everything and
then I'll go in with like Paint Pot or
concealer and then carve it out okay cuz
I do my cut crease is in a really really
different way I will actually like start
off by drawing the bottom line and then
just blend upwards which I've never seen
anybody else do it that way but I feel
like that gives me like a really really
clean that's smart
crease I don't know if you are someone
if you're definite like wanting to do
more cut creases you should try it out
let me know like how it works
yeah angled brush first yeah that's
what's always worked for me I like that
technique really really well I'm next to
grab my morphe M 213 and dip into this
warm up dark brown shade in the bottom
I'm just to deepen up the crease line
[Music]
an understanding of this Anasazi a for
brush limit more of that shape tip
concealer just too hard out of the
crease this is also why I like starting
out with that line rather than just like
putting color on there and then cutting
it later because this kind of like gives
you a guide of where to like cut the
concealer as well it's like the crease
is basically does there you just need to
clean it up I guess yes do you do the
other way around
I need stupid and now I'm kind of
switching a little bit to face first if
I there was a big did you see the debate
about this on Twitter today it was like
yesterday day before it was everyone got
like popping off about it I'm most so
mad as like eyes it's never that do you
think we all do people were literally
saying that some people like funny
Instagram people do it this way our time
I had my girl need to show it's really
like never I'm not her that's her it's
like when was makeup makeup Elyse was
like out make a place with other like
knives arresting everybody has a girl
just put on your products and as long as
you look back full of matters we want to
do a cool little liner pop on Amanda's
eyes and I want to do a chartreuse with
this and this is inspired by a barber
cow and Instagram she's taking my
all-time favorite artist she did a
chartreuse liner I don't have a
chartreuse anything actually
so movies in the Anasazi at lip pal I'm
gonna miss together with the yellow
shade with a tie there we go tiny little
dab of the blue to make our chartreuse
liner I'm gonna use this liquid liner
brush just to sketch in a liner this is
not as bright as we wanted I'm kind of
added like more of a neon situation so
we're gonna try to set it with a little
bit of eye shadow after but we're just
going to get in this liner person see
how it looks
[Music]
we were just thing about how I was
having some bad Leonard a seriously no
matter do some liquid liner on Amanda so
please pray for me we're gonna be using
the Mac rapid block penultimate eyeliner
that's a mouthful that's right we using
[Music]
putting back on the 35 I'm gonna pick up
my are 39 again I'm gonna dip into the
same warm up brown shade and I'm just
gonna really really lightly dust this on
Amanda's under eyes dropping a dark
brown shade of Miami to 13 I'm going to
smoke out the wing just the slightest
bit planes out from the other so when
I'm blending this I am going right over
the bottom edge of the wing up blending
that black into a deep brown and then
into the orange to chrono create a
smoked out effect on at the bottom of
the wing we want the top of the way to
be obviously except for defiant and cut
because it's a cut crease but then we
want the bottom to be like really really
smoky and not defined next I'm just
gonna grab a black single shadow for
this one I'm just using my one from
Anasazi and my custom palette and my
morphe Emma - one - and I'm just going
to darken up the view wing and the
smoked out bottom wing and I am putting
this right up to the lash line as well
her lashes today is it really the James
Charles video if we don't use the House
lashes on eye contact I always use
either one I'm going cut creases I feel
like they just frame the eye really
really well when it comes to countries
just because like that the outer part is
a lot longer I don't know I just like
other likes fiery too like they're
different lengths so it just looks at so
much dimension it really does I mean
tried goddess no those are my favorite
now the band's a lot more flexible to
you of course I got my benefit roller
lash mascara and pop this onto the upper
lashes now to mix the two lashes
together alright guys and those are both
eyes all completely are now gonna move
on to declaw and for a glow theorem
using the over highlighter in a Rodeo
Drive just like my all-time favorite
gold highlighter and I play gold will
suit this book probably very very well
[Music]
I'm just under grab my morphe m31 brush
and that same highlighter to a snatch
Amanda's nose as our last and final
touch I'm gonna go to the kylie matte
liquid lipstick in the shade plumberry
prepping set setting spray one last time
code James or code Amanda alright guys
and that is the completed look over on a
sister Amanda I absolutely love how it
turned out we came up with this like cut
crease neon almost neon you thought what
we're doing it a little good it's not
like anything I've ever done and you
said you wanted this I was like okay I
trust you and it's just like grocery
stores natural like for school you know
I honestly really like it I probably
will end up doing it later on this week
for my almond surgery it looks you guys
enjoy the city with Amanda please make
sure to give it a big thumbs up down
below and start with you have not
already I posted two times a week on
Mondays and Fridays and I would love to
have you join it the sisterhood have you
enjoyed me in a band together please
actually go check out the video weight
on her Channel we're about to take all
this beautiful makeup off after pictures
of course and do it the 5 minute makeup
challenge well we look good No
well I look okay maybe you will look at
myself here I'm gonna look but
definitely go check out the video we did
on her channel if you'd like to follow
me on my makeup journey can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they will just be
James Charles and my snapchat and you
know who work behind the same size upper
James Charles the extra ass after
Charles if you like to follow Amanda
search Amanda M Singh between of YouTube
she's beautiful grow ever and like I
said before it she's one of my closest
friends we've been together for so much
she's helped me fighting at the film
again she's helped me through so many
emotionally hard at times and this girl
always has such a positive outlook on
life I always I'm so excited so
definitely go check her out I've been
have not already all right guys thank
you so much for watching and we will see
you in the next one
[Music]