hi guys this is James Charles welcome
back to my youtube channel today I'm
joined with a very special guest Victor
okay daddy jonas halo so what daddy does
my voice our video did extremely well
I'm so about all of you guys enjoyed it
on the channel it caught like several
thousand beef a lot of you guys are
saying you really really loved Victor
and I wanted to pull him back for
another video as well so today it's so
bright
Thank You king of observations today
we're gonna be doing a daddy does eye
makeup video it sure knows absolutely
nothing about makeup the only knowledge
he has is from watching me allure do our
makeup when we get ready for like events
and stuff that we dragged him with us to
talk about your makeup knowledge
foundation so basically we packed up all
my favorite products that I would use on
like an everyday at glam makeup day and
Victor has no idea what any of this
stuff is so let's use all of this I mean
most of it I would use normally oh so
they feel like you just gonna be
throwing all these products on me and
we're gonna see how it looks on the end
can't you do it yeah I love the
enthusiasm okay if you want to see how
are you created I don't think you
brought everything I did know like I
feel like I'm missing some oh no wait
the stick I know we're gonna use this
and then I know you kind of just write
whatever so this is please don't shoot
you can't just write whatever so this is
me writing whatever struggling I think
that looks pretty good
alright oh and then compliments to Laura
we're going to use it clean
how about me what the she packed it
yeah sheep active but you probably
brought the dirty one you're definitely
right what no no sponge it is
technically a sponge I know but can you
guys call it something else you said dab
remember that yeah but in get you a man
who pays attention to our tutorial we're
Iranian move on the next step but king
of blending I think I'm gonna take a
chance to kind of just do a little bit
because it's a little red in there all
right if I could remember correctly
Jesus all right so I did the cloud did
one side of the wings I I did the clouds
and rain drop thing sculpturing job job
how I wish I do it stop stop
yes please yes please what I'm lost I'm
not to do negative to watch more videos
[Music]
dizzy or something oh wow your little
your left side on your lips alright
so I think I'm supposed to use this next
camel product every time wow that's
pretty good that was pretty good I got
that one pretty good thanks put on your
nose too
I had let's do it right this is my
makeup tickles if you do whatever I want
alright it's called a freestyle makeover
oh no this is definitely not right I
feel like I'm supposed to do something
with your nose on it I don't know which
product I thinks this stuff no I'm gonna
lift up some things and you kind of just
tell me no we're going to tell you
anything that the people watching will
tell me too late I'm already gonna be
destroyed that's how that was kind of
you I've never done makeup this worse I
think it looks pretty good use something
to connect his brows down his nose
[Music]
watch your screen I broke your mirror
first I was so ugly that when it left
him to it
Oh shadow right that in there you sit in
at me
in the last video a lot of people didn't
get the whole daddy thing
pictures not my of your eyebrows when
you saw sorry Victor's not my actual
father he has Laura's my best friend's
husband but he is my daddy science
that's why I'm sorry guys my voiceover
are never doing that he doesn't make up
do you see me doing makeup so many times
no I don't know watch you you're always
in the room with us yeah my phone up a
real tattoo you would know every single
step I know a lot about clothes tell me
about that cotton polyester blend
babycakes now I'm gonna clean up the
line I wish these have directions think
about how could his father look when I
do them just a little less barely
concealer I wish my brows were like
vectors really yeah she basically can
make your eye brother name shape that's
okay yeah yes this is the morphe 350
pellet good it says so it's also very
dirty I leave all my pellets for easy
access you should wash them you're not
wrong
and then these are the colors I go with
king of product placement the first
color is pretty good so now I'm gonna
use this second color so I'm a different
brush keep in mind guys I have yet to
see anything that's way out of my face
alright so before I do it I'm gonna like
the glitter stuff might be a little wet
so maybe he really does watch my videos
this was sitting here
this I think this is the drop she use
for the glitter put this on there right
that Alright dropped off I wish this
video would stop stop I think you should
have wore this look - like that like a
cocktail party mingling to people - sure
it's pretty good
maybe suckers sorry good boy
Oh Kat Von D please good directions so
people like me have a chance
I'll make sure dying they say her name
elevator hot all turns like from the
last video you kind of put it in your
hair a little bit less I remember Sam I
know that's right come on my contour hey
that's pretty good
you're mumbling I don't talk loud not a
loud person and actually it's working so
this shows you how much you know that's
like your freckle look you do that and
just make it a freckle look to blend it
in even when you mess up just hope I
don't have any good look stop smiling
you're creasing
[Music]
and now you're supposed to dab these
real creases because I see you do that
in your photo shoot sometimes for a few
smiles you kinda like asks for all
Beautyblender that says oh there you go
oh wait 30 minutes into the video oh
shoot what I'm supposed to use this too
let's let's get that stuff back to that
actually please but you know oh my god
please be careful don't be scared that
glow that is what that is
morphine 501 use James Charles nope
that's not my card these chambers
10% off oh I know I put some you got the
smaller punch
maybe the same brush
I really this enough at this
point you just kind of go all out and be
extra that's how we do
yeah like welcome you Mertz coming out
buzzes sneak peek
all right lipstick lipstick oh
no that's not that's not my sir and
those crusty lips over here said crusty
[Music]
every time hey ya think so
oh thanks great ha ha ha Wow is it on
your face
no you do you do this little thing so I
figured doing it oh you blew all right
Eileen it's enough do I take a look I
yeah Tijuana
that is a look at least you're glowing
it's not it's honestly not as bad as I
was expecting
I'm pretty proud of you daddy good Tom
my face my face oh man transfer damn all
right guys and not as the completed
daddy doesn't make up video did you have
a good time amazing if you guys did
enjoy this video with Daddy Victor
please make sure to give this video a
big thumbs up down below subscribe if
you have not already I post videos every
single week and I would love to have you
join the family if you like to follow me
on my makeup journey you can follow my
Instagram and Twitter they are both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes type stuff is James
Charles the next row ask after Charles
and Vic to toe if you guys like this
video and you want to see more videos
with Daddy over here please make sure to
give it a big thumbs up down below maybe
we get to 50,000 I'll do Victor's makeup
that a lot 50,000 that's a lot yeah make
it a hundred thousand it's not gonna
happen that's the point
all right guys thank you so much for
watching and we will see you next time
goodbye
[Music]