because another funky daddy
[Music]
hi boys and girls welcome back to
James's YouTube channel alright so
today's gonna show you how to do this
makeup look right here so if you're
interested keep on watching alright so
we're going to start off with this
product we're just gonna rub it all in
the whole point is to get your face nice
and red alright then we're gonna use
this Mac product so we're just gonna use
this brush in or Anna
I guess focus just on the nose so in
this case for James is big nose you're
gonna put a lot try to cover it up and
make sure you make it nice and small
then we go in this product we're going
to cover the rest of our freckled face
with it and we're just gonna put it all
over I guess so we're just gonna blend
it in with the brush make sure you get
every nice little freckle and you're
gonna cover up that double chin go nice
and underneath the neck
we're gonna use this product this
product is to cover up those bags
so go ahead and have fun with it you're
gonna create this little bird sculpture
a little nest underneath little branches
on the cheeks and then the cloud on top
it looks like it's raining now so rain
drop drop top I wish this video stuff
stopped then we're going to use this
candle product and it looks like we're
just gonna put it underneath eyes gonna
do much now we're gonna go back and
tickle our neck some more alright next
product James thank you alright so we're
gonna use this dirty pallet kind of put
in our cheeks a little bit our forehead
and in your hair a little bit it doesn't
look like it did much but we're gonna
use it anyways alright now we're going
back into our big nose we're going to
blend it with our big eyebrows so we're
going to connect the two you're gonna do
that by putting a straight line down
your nose trying to make it look skinny
but we all know it's not skinny then
we're going to reinforce it with this
dirty sponge again make it nice and
straight lines good job James so it's
good encourage yourself alright now
we're gonna use this baby powder on her
cheeks and our ear a little bit and then
we're going to put underneath her eyes
kind of basically cover up all the work
we just did and we're gonna I guess
we're gonna just let it sit there and
now we're gonna go into the eyebrows
again all right so you're gonna draw a
nice little straight line all the way
across underneath your eyebrows then
we're gonna fill in those caterpillars
continue that straight line um you don't
want to forget those stragglers off to
the side so make sure you go back and
get him and kind of push them all over
there you go
all right so James [ __ ] up so he's
going back to those lines and he's gonna
make it nice and perfect and then this
next product so I guess we're gonna use
this mascara for his eyebrows yeah I
guess that works
yep ones done not done and then now
we're done I wish it was that fast when
it took him six hours to do makeup now
we're gonna go into another dirty
palette we're gonna start with this
peach color and I put it in our eyelids
pretty pointless doesn't look like you
did much then I'm gonna use this second
color I'm gonna try to blend those two
colors in together to make a new color
whole point of this is you know to get
that unique color so in this case
there's like 60 different colors because
I brushed it really dirty Oh 61 I guess
this is the burgundy eye look we're
going for it and then we're gonna use
some of this glitter that he got and
we're gonna put it just in the corner of
the eye yep looks good James all right
now we're going to use this little
marker we're gonna make a nice little
triangle point on the corner of your eye
make sure it's nice and straight and I
guess now he's going ball a cross into
the glitter pretty pointless what's the
point of putting on the glitter if it's
gonna cover it James all right now he's
gonna finish this look off by making his
whole eye look purple and they're gonna
use this new clean brush finally to put
the rest of the glitter then we're gonna
put these bad boys on these big old
butterfly lashes make sure they're all
nice and straight you don't want to be
at a party and dangling off that guy's
gonna say bye to you all right that side
is done this side is not thank you for
pointing out Captain Obvious all right
now we're gonna use this product I think
it's time for James to do a singing note
so glazed donut is being finished by
putting on your forehead don't forget
that nose you want to make sure that
nose looks nice and skinny even though
it's not then now we're gonna go into
the lips this should be really quick
since he doesn't have much lips to work
with yep we're all done all right now
we're gonna spray yourself with some
water get it nice and wet and we're all
done
alright guys so thank you for watching
this makeup look give himself a thumbs
up and subscribe down low he's talking
way too quick I'm pretty sure he's
saying use his morphe code for 10% off
James he knows how to count to 2 and I
guess we are basically done James thank
you for these hand gestures and continue
talking alright I guess I'm done bye