hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel last
year i filmed a youtube video where i
reached out to some of my favorite
celebrities
and asked them to recommend a product
for my makeup routine we got so many
responses from a ton of
really really cool people it was a fun
way to try new products and
you guys loved the video and it became a
trend within the beauty community if you
guys have not seen part one you can go
ahead and click right up here
but it's been a full year since that
video came out i have met so many new
people made so many amazing
new friends so for today's video i
thought i would do a little bit of a
part two and dm a whole different group
of celebrities and ask them to pick my
makeup routine i have quite a lot of dms
that i need to now slide into so let's
go ahead and get started
[Music]
all right you guys we're gonna start
setting a few different dm's in the
order of my makeup routine so of course
we first have
foundation and i have a few people in
mind that i want to reach out to
starting off with the pregnant
soon mother to be miss gigi hadid i
literally love her the absolute most we
were actually damning back and forth
this morning hopefully she'll respond
and be able to recommend a really cute
foundation to get that pregnancy glow hi
angel i hope you're doing absolutely
amazing all of your pregnancy photos
have been so beautiful and i cannot wait
to see you be an incredible mommy with
your gorgeous baby
just thinking about a baby between gigi
hadid and zayn
like that baby is going to be a
supermodel one day i'm filming a video
where i asked my favorite celebrities to
recommend a makeup product that they
love do you have a favorite foundation
that you love that emphasizes your
pregnancy glove just in case miss gigi
is too busy being a mother to be i
thought it'd be really cute to deal with
somebody else that i absolutely love
that always has really flawless skin as
well
miss miley cyrus hi sister the night sky
is such a bump i've been listening to it
literally non-stop
do you have a fave foundation okay
scent next for concealer i definitely
want to mess with somebody that always
has like a painted and like
beat face so i think i want to damn it
mara carol g
perfect okay just in case carol doesn't
see i feel like it could be funny
devices somebody that would have like no
idea what concealer even is
should i message like diploma okay
i know you're always on stage performing
do you happen to know of any great
concealers you've had on
that i should try out he's gonna have
literally no idea
okay so while i'm on the topic of my
favorite hermanas i thought it would be
cute to dm miss
rosalia oh my god i've seen her live
before and her performances on stage are
so
like crazy and beautiful so she
definitely has to have a powder that
locks her makeup in
all day hola rina i'm filming a video
where i ask my favorite celebrities to
recommend a product for my makeup
routine
do you have a setting powder that
you love love you okay so for contour i
definitely want to reach out to people
that have like very structured beautiful
facial features
and the first person that comes to mind
has to be miss alexa to me from euphoria
she's one of my favorite people i think
i actually may have reached out to her
last year for the savings like video and
did not get a response but she did have
her collaboration with mac in the
meantime and euphoria season two is just
starting right now
so it doesn't hurt to at least try to
shoot my shot again
oh my god she hasn't posted on instagram
since march 5th she's not seeing this
okay well considering miss demi has not
posted on instagram in almost four
months now i definitely want to reach
out to a few other people
just in case she doesn't respond so i
also want to dm rita ora
do you have a contour product that you
love that i should try out
her night rita and i have dm back and
forth a few different times out and i
love her music so hopefully i think that
she probably will see this okay so now
for blush i definitely want to try
something new so i thought that i would
dm
somebody very very legendary that also
fun thought happens to be my new
neighbor
and she's coming out with her own makeup
line very very soon selena gomez i've
seen an interview that she doesn't use
for social media but hopefully her team
will be able to pass the message along
or i'll literally just go knock out the
door myself
hi never hope you're doing amazing i'm
so excited for rare beauty do you have a
favorite
blush that you think that i should try
out
scent okay so for bronze study i
definitely have the perfect person in
mind that has to be
doja cat if you guys have not yet seen
her nice collaboration together click
right up here it was
so much fun to film and the look was
absolutely sickening also if you
remember from the video she was
extremely
particular and specific about how she
wanted her eyebrows she almost didn't
trust me in the first place to do that
oh
i like to do my own brows usually oh but
she's a
she's an mua now we ended up slaying
them in the end so i know that she'll
have a really good recommendation hi
babe hope your is speaking
english spanish and french
and i know you're super particular about
your brows
so which product should i use to slay
mine next in our makeup routine is going
to be the highlighter and i have the
perfect person in mind that i want to
reach out to for today's video and that
has to be the queen herself
jlo i think that i dm'd her last year
for this video and she did not respond
but regardless i'm going to ask her
about my highlight
just in case jayla does not respond i
definitely want to reach out to somebody
else that is known for having a
beautiful
glowy skin i've talked about her many
different times in videos but i've never
actually met her before
but i think i want to message miss emily
ronachowski
so for the eyeshadow look today i
definitely want to reach out to somebody
that is going to give me like a crazy
fun suggestion not just like oh put a
neutral brown in the crease
so i need to think of something that's
like crazy and the first person that
comes to mind
has to be cardi b so i'm going to reach
out and say hi
sister how's your whop doing today
hope you liked my danced video
oh my gosh she quote tweeted it and i
was just so embarrassed for myself
party's makeup artist erica is so
talented and always puts really really
beautiful looks on cardi
so i feel like she should have a good
suggestion okay so once the eyeshadow
portion is all complete of course we
have to move on to the next step which
is going to be
oh selena just responded she said this
is so cute let me facetime you
oh what the heck oh my god fun
hi sister hi honey how are you i'm doing
good how are you
oh doing the absolute best that was such
a fast response queen
literal queen well selena i'm currently
filming a video where i dm
my favorite celebrities and ask them to
pick a step in my makeup routine and i
know
that you have something i can see in the
background you have something very
exciting coming with miss
rare beauty i know and i'm more excited
just to like give it to people
have it in their hands and just to see
what you know these artists are going to
do and i'm so so excited to see
you know what we could do together and
like how you're going to turn it into
something
beautiful for all your sisters dude we
have to film a collaboration together
soon when i glam you up it'll be
so good yeah wait and i know that i'll
maybe i'll just drop off some stuff
because they live like five minutes from
you oh my god that'd be literally
perfect well i need a blush
recommendation for this video do you
have a blush with rare beauty yes i do
so this one is my absolute favorite
okay so i've been using this
all the time okay it is so yummy because
it's
very it's super pigmented oh love that
wow love this live application
right there and blend and add as much or
as little as you want
i'm very proud of my blushes so this
one's the matte
and then we have some dewy ones that
we'll share with youtube oh my god wait
so am i gonna be the first one to get
the pr packets then
oh wow this neighborhood thing really is
coming in handy hot when does it
actually launch
so by the time that this video goes live
then it'll be out oh my god period well
make sure you guys go shopping beauty
right now
no thank you girl see you soon bye after
eyeshadow of course comes our mascara to
finish off the entire eye look and pull
it all together so i definitely want to
reach out to somebody that is known for
having
really really good lashes and i think i
want to dm
kourtney kardashian i know you're all
about natural makeup so i was wondering
if you have a favorite mascara
that you recommend okay so our makeup
routine is almost done we only have one
step left and that is of course going to
be the lipidy doodahs i want to message
one more legendary person to end off
this video and that has got to be
miss naomi campbell first of all she
definitely knows her way around the
makeup chair and full glam considering
she is literally the most iconic
supermodel in the entire world
but i was also a guest on her show no
filter with naomi literally this morning
coincidentally that i'm filming this
video she was literally so nice and we
talked all about beautiful makeup looks
so i feel like she'll have a really good
recommendation for lips to finalize the
whole look
all right you guys we are back it has
been about a week since we filmed the
intro to this video i thought i would
give you a cute little
update because we've had this one for
several days now and he may look all
cute and innocent right now and a lot of
the times he is okay but i am
very convinced at this point that satan
himself is literally inside of this dog
because he's still nibbling on all of us
he's gone to the bathroom inside
several more times very much unlike finn
finnegan on the other hand is a little
angel just sleeping on the filming room
couch could not be any better behaved
and this dog
he's really giving me a run for my money
but theodore will become trained and he
will be
a good behaved member of the charles
family huh
all right you guys i am so excited ready
to jump right in for a final makeup look
today my skin is not having it so it is
time to move on to our first step which
is going to be a foundation
and we did get a response from the queen
i keep saying the queen the legend that
i found like shut up james
shut up i reached out to a few different
people and i got a response from gigi
hadid she said hilah thank you so much
we are so excited oh my god i am too
my favorite right now is the maybelline
dream radiant liquid a couple drop mixes
in really well with my moisturizer but i
can also use more and layer up if i want
more
full coverage and feel so smooth and
light on the skin i went and picked up
the maybelline dream radiant liquid and
i grabbed shade number 50 for myself
which is a creamy
natural so i'm just going to go ahead
and apply this just like normal
and see how it looks okay we're just
going to go ahead and apply that right
onto this
[Music]
oh that's one of that's literally one of
the best foundation matches i've ever
had in my entire life oh
my god are you what are you literally
kidding me that little oh
i'm literally so excited right now not
miss gigi i did give me my brand new
favorite foundation are you kidding me
okay i'm just going to go ahead and
blend this all over the face
moving right along to our next step of
course you guys know it is going to be
concealer and we actually got two
different responses for
concealer the first one being from diplo
which i honestly was
not expecting at all he actually sent me
back a video which i will apply for you
guys
so you said this one tart this is
obviously shape tape which i use
all the time so i think for today's
video actually going to go with our
other suggestion
which comes from miss carol g and she
said she said babe i use a concealer for
urban decay that i love by the way i'm
flying to well late this weekend
okay first of all i grabbed the
concealer right here that i'm going to
go ahead and use but also
please let me know if you guys want to
see a makeup tutorial las panolo parte
dos featuring somebody
super cool like imagine like carol g or
like rosalie or like kimberly louisa
another youtuber let me know if you guys
want to see that video down below wow
this color is really
really light for me but that's my own
fault not carol g's i'm definitely gonna
have to make this work
okay well the base is looking really
really cute so far and now it is time to
set it all in place with of course a
setting powder and for this i got a
response as well from
rosalia and she said hi i love this one
hope you're doing well
celia i love you the most girl i hope
you're doing well too and she
recommended the
mac blot and plus the mac blot and
pressed powder which i've actually never
tried out before
but definitely i'm pumped to try i
am not exactly sure how a blotting
powder is going to work to set the
entire face
but open to everything okay i'm not 100
sure how i'm thinking about this whole
powder situation that being said i have
a feeling that this would be a really
really good product to use once your
makeup is already completed
like if you get oily or anything to just
like get rid of the natural oils but it
did at least lock my makeup in place now
that the base is all done it is
definitely time to add back some color
and dimension to the face because we
definitely need it right now and miss
rita ora did come through with a
suggestion she said hi beauty first of
all i love your videos i watch them and
obsess with your face rita i am obsessed
with you and your face and your music
and she recommended
the tom ford shape and illuminate
bronzer aside from the eyeliner which i
do actually use all the time i don't
think i've ever actually tried any
tom ford like makeup products so i'm
definitely excited to dip in and
oh it's a cream bronzer
i don't know what this means you can't
really put creams over top of powders it
like doesn't really blend well and i
just set my face in place
okay let me just try this i'm gonna grab
my rare beauty foundation brush which
did come from
the selena package which is the next
step um i really like this brush spoiler
alert and dip into this
[Music]
product this is not weird as well this
is my fault
um wow okay i'm just gonna really pat
this product in and try to blend it down
as best as i can
what child chat i mean that looks okay
yeah yeah i should have opened this
before i got started because this would
have been probably beautiful like right
over top of the foundation
do you think yeah i did blend it out and
i think that it looks cute and it is now
time to go on to the next step which i
am
so excited for and that is of course
going to be blush as you guys saw in the
beginning i got an unexpected facetime
call from my good friend and now
neighbor miss selena gomez she
recommended that i try the rare beauty
liquid blush in the shade bliss which
i'm going to do
right now but i'm honestly so excited to
try out the rest of the products as well
and selena and i have been talking about
doing a collab in person once the world
is a little bit more
back to normal that would be literally
so much fun so definitely let us know if
you guys want to see that okay now
selena did tell me that these blushes
are super super pigmented so i'm just
going to do a tiny few dots on my face
and start blending it out
oh my god wow that actually oh that
color is so pretty
are you literally kidding me i was
definitely a little bit concerned with
putting a liquid blush over top of
my powder that layered on literally so
nicely and it's such a gorgeous
wash of color are you literally kidding
right now i'm actually gonna add a
little bit more
okay i may or may not have went a little
bit overboard with the blush but i've
been
loving vibrant colors recently i think
this looks super super cute selena you
and your team
killed it with this formula i am
obsessed with this blush and honestly
this color and i'm so excited to check
out all the other products as well
our next step is going to be eyebrows
and we did get a response from my good
sis miss
doji cat now at first she suggested that
i should use peanut butter
just so funny and then after prying she
suggested that i use anastasia beverly
hills which is definitely my favorite
go-to brow products as well so i'm just
gonna grab my little angled brush and my
anastasia brow powder in the shade
medium brown
and go to town just like normal all
right you guys the brows are now done
and slayed and it is time to move on to
my favorite part of my makeup routine
you guys know
is the eyeshadow portion and i messaged
cardi b hoping for a crazy look and she
definitely
came through cardi sent me back a few
different voice memos which i actually
cannot play
on video one because they contain
personal information but also two
they hinted at something that i really
was not planning on telling you guys
just yet because i wanted it to be a
surprise but in a universe where there
may or may not be
not confirming or denying anything a
james x party collaboration coming in a
few weeks from now
imagining like if i was planning out
that collab if it was to actually happen
don't really know
i may or may not have sent cardi a few
different look ideas one of them
including a whop makeup look and she may
or not have told me to do that makeup
look for this video
because we're gonna do something if we
were to do something
um even more iconic for that
long story short too long didn't read
cardi told me to do a makeup look
inspired by the [ __ ] music video and i
have the perfect look in mind to do
seven days a week
all right you guys so to start off this
waff inspired look i'm first going to
grab an emma 506 brush and dip right
into the dark brown shade in my palette
called tea and i'm going to start
packing the shade right into my crease
just kind of laying that color in there
and i'm going to draw on in the shape of
a typical
cut crease next i'm going to grab my
m456 brush and dip into a coated james
and i'm going to start buffing out that
dark brown
and then with my m514 brush i'm going to
dip into 508 and use this as my
transition shade
now with another blending brush i'm
going to dip into a little bit of rusted
and a little bit of your kidding as well
just add a little bit more orange depth
into this
crease and now finally i'm just going to
grab a tiny little fluffy brush the m562
and dip into a little bit of
benny and i'm going to use this to
deepen the crease even more with a
little bit of a face on a pencil brush
i'm just going to use this to highlight
my brow bone now that our crease is all
laid down and blended out of course it
is time to cut it so i'm just going to
grab a little bit of
concealer and a flat top brush and i'm
just going to
carve it out then grab a little bit of
canvas on a flat brush i'm just going to
set that concealer in place
okay so i want to go ahead and add a
really cool cheetah print effect to this
eyeshadow look personally i am not
really the biggest fan of animal print
however
i do think both cardi and kylie looked
so so sickening in the music video
and when i showed this look to cardi she
was obsessed with it so i'm gonna
put that on the eyes i'm just gonna grab
a tiny liner brush a little bit of
concealer and then just start making
random little
splotches in the eyeshadow just like
that
i'm just going to lightly dust over
those concealer splotches with the light
orange color on our fluffy brush from
before just to kind of set them in place
then you're going to go ahead and grab
any black liner i happen to pick up the
one from rare beauty just because i want
to try it out
for this look and we're going to start
adding the little like cheetah
spots basically in all those little
spots that you created you're just going
to
honestly messily start adding like
little like circles
around them there we go now using the
same colors from before i'm basically
going to start sketching out a
smoky liner just using a little bit of
10 off to start adding in
the top color and then using a little
bit of tea and no beans to add in a
little bit more
and then finally grabbing benny and just
patting this right onto the lash line to
create that liner
look now for the lower lash line just
repeating the same exact process in the
opposite step so grabbing a little bit
of
spooky and benny and then getting a
little bit of 10 off okay now i am
literally
praying that this does not mess it up
but i think i'm going to grab a little
bit of the electric cake liner from
anasazi beverly hills the norvina
collection
and grab the purple shade inspired by a
megan's look from the video
and add this into the crease and last
but finally not least i'm going to grab
just a little bit of
face and ring light mixed together and
pop that right on the inner corner for
some nice
glow all right you guys that is one eye
of this cardi b wolf inspired look all
complete i think this turned out
super super cute but it was very
challenging so i'm going to cut do the
other eye off camera which is going to
take me quite a while and i'll be right
back to finish off the rest of the look
all right you guys we are back with the
eyeshadow on both eyes all complete i am
literally loving this look
so so so much but it is not done just
quite yet we still have to of course add
on our lashes and we did reach out to a
few different people for mascara and we
got a response from the one and only
kourtney kardashian courtney said that
her top three favorite mascaras are the
item
beauty lash snack lengthening mascara
she said josie maron argan oil black
mascara and also the ilia limitless lash
mascara oh all those are quite the
mouthful but i do actually have
addison's new item beauty mascara right
here that i'm so excited to try out so
let's go ahead and
pop it on oh i love how tiny this wand
is oh my god this mascara is really good
my bottom lashes are you literally
kidding me right now i will definitely
be adding this to my favorites kit
addison you low-key really really
snapped okay now it's time for lashes i
think i'm gonna pop on
these of course we have highlighter next
although the lack of
powder is kind of giving me that look
already but i do want to add a little
bit of extra glow
unfortunately jlo did not respond but we
did get an answer from a supermodel
herself
miss emily radachowski and she said hi
james huge fan and we also share the
best lawyer this is true we do have the
same lawyer funny enough and she said i
love this super random one which is a
highlighting drops from sleek and then
thank god she said also i love the
charlotte tilbury sticks too now
literally i looked
every single place you could possibly
imagine for the sleek drops and i could
not find them and i needed to film this
video today but thank god i could find
the charlotte tilbury highlighting
sticks and these look really really cute
as well so i'm just gonna go ahead and
pop this on all right you guys well
speaking of supermodels we are finally
on the last step which is going to be
the lips to finalize the entire look and
tie it all together we did get a
response from
the number one the only and a new friend
of mine miss naomi campbell she said
favorite lip color at the moment is
boudoir rose 522 by pat mcgrath lab
gives us a hint of pink and a natural
glow
and i need to go ahead and pick up this
very lipstick right here
oh i'm not exactly sure how i feel about
this specific color with this look
but naomi is a queen so we're going to
trust her input and hope for the best
oh it's more like a lip tint okay this
is cute okay you guys this glam process
has lasted forever so last but not least
i'm gonna take my own recommendation and
use the morphe prep and set setting
spray use code james for 10 off to lock
this all in place
and finally that is this makeup look
chosen by my favorite celebrities
all complete sisters i am so in love
with how this makeup look turned out
today oh my god i cannot wait
to take a photo doing these videos is
always so so much fun but also a major
risk as well because you really never
know what anybody is going to pick but
i think that these products all worked
so well together and honestly looking in
front of me today i think that i
actually enjoyed every single product
that was recommended to me which is
super super cool thank you so much to
all the celebrities and
friends who responded to this dm for
today's video i cannot wait to keep
playing with all these products in my
future makeup routines if you guys
enjoyed today's video though please
don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below click that bigger
subscribe button and come join the
sisterhood and finally click that bell
icon so you get notified every time i
upload a brand
new video if you want to follow me on my
makeup journey all my social media
accounts are gonna be linked right here
around the screen
and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number for updates on
videos photos merch and so much more my
number is 310-905-8746
this video shoutout goes costa's sister
leander thank you so much love for
always following and supporting i love
you so so so much and if you would like
to be the next video's
sister shout out don't forget to always
read people links when they go live on
twitter and also to my youtube post
notifications
all right you guys thank you so much for
watching this sister star studded video
for today i love you so much and i will
see you in the next one