hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I'm very excited because
we're doing a trend that has been going
around honestly quite a lot on YouTube
recently and not is the damming a bunch
of celebrities challenge basically
creators are reaching out to different
celebrities and sending the messages
seeing if the respond or asking
questions or in my case for today asking
them to be a part of my makeup routine
now I just want to give a quick shout
out to soft as nails and Sylvia Ghani
because they already did this before me
but I thought it'd be really fun to try
to do it myself and a bunch of different
people who've actually reached out to me
for this challenge which is very very
strange but also very very cool at the
same time I used to make jokes my
friends about being famous clearly they
did not go over too well but for today's
video we're gonna be damming some real
celebrities and seeing if they want to
be a part of my makeup routine
[Music]
alright you guys let's just jump right
into everything I have my Instagram DMS
and open and were just gonna start
setting some messages and see what
happened so the first step of my makeup
routine is obviously going to be a
primer so I feel like I wanted a I'm at
some different celebrities that have a
really really beautiful skin and the
first person that comes to mind is Miss
Bella Hadid so I'm going to send her a
and Sorrenti M little but I lost and her
on July 1st and said did you just hand
the plane to we're actually on a flight
Taylor from New York to LA and we were
both running late for meetings and we
both did our makeup on the plane
it was low-key kind of iconic I mean
obviously how to each other but she did
not see my DM so let's see if she sees
this one
so after primer cross foundation and you
guys know I definitely love a full
covered and makeup look so I definitely
want to reach out to somebody who like
also is always painted every time so the
first one that comes to mind is a sister
cardi B her makeup artist Erica is so
freaking talented so I think she'll have
a good one one day she'll send okay the
last person that I want to jam for
foundation is probably like the longest
shot from happening in this entire video
but there's a slight chance and that is
Queen living legend herself
Rihanna because she does not fancy
beauty she has her own foundation it's a
really really bomb so lost hi Queen
little Queen hope you're doing well I'm
so excited for all of the new pieces
from the affinity collection do you want
to participate and recommend a
foundation or me it's who use winky face
because she's a businesswoman and I know
she'll see this marketing opportunity
other foundation comes concealer so I
shake the perfect person to reach out to
for this as Isis terrorists are a Larson
she is so beautiful and yes we did have
a beef beforehand but we've deemed we've
popped it out and now we are good
sisters and I feel like she will come
through it with a good and fresh
suggestion let's see if sisters are not
replies now after concealer from Mia
come setting powder and obviously the
whole point of powder is to lock your
face in place so it lasts all day long
and when I think a setting powder I
definitely think I want to DM at Camp a
trust because she's literally one my
favorite artist of all time right now
and I have seen her alive and she goes
crazy she is so insanely talented and
that means her makeup artist has to
really lock her face in please so I feel
like she might have a really good
suggestion
I literally obsessed with her and we've
dammed back and forth a few different
times so hopefully she replies next
comes a bronzer and contouring that
obviously means somebody who is chiseled
who was beautiful and in the Sun so I
think we should go ahead and DM Camilla
Kibeho
she's a lime queen it's so crazy because
the first time I ever him back to me
like a pea was outside of an ariana
grande concert weirdly enough I was
going in and she was coming out and I
was like running and she literally was
like oh my god it's not James and I
turned around and I was like and it was
like the crazies interacted my entire
life because I literally was obsessed
with her and her music and her voice and
whole I still remember it like it was
literally yesterday we took a selfie
together and I've loved her ever since
it is so cool to see her blow up so
hopefully she replies and to suggest I
bronzer okay you guys so the next intro
routine is going to be blush and I feel
like blush is a very like innocent cute
youthful timid makeup product so when I
think of that I think of million Bobby
at brown and obviously on stranger
things eleven does not work too much
makeup but when she walks the red carpet
Millie always looks so beautiful so she
might have a great suggestion once I
blush this on I always go ahead and bake
but we already have our sister setting
powder so the next that was going to be
our brows and when I think of like
really beautiful structure at brows one
of the first people that comes to mind
is sister at Madison birra because she
always
literally perfect I don't even
understand how one human being can look
like that but she might have a good
suggestion sent to Madison beer after
eyebrows are slated in place the next
epic waymaker protein is always a shadow
and when I think of iconic red carpet I
said it looks that I've literally
changed industry let's be real the first
person to come to mind is Miss Kim
kardashian-west her makeup artist Mario
and her have created so many iconic
looks together and cameras always buy at
such an amazing friend and role model to
me so let's see what she has to suggest
hi mom hope you're doing well and the
reaction to the new collection has been
amazing you might want smoking like
chronic look so up maybe I can create an
iconic one with your suggestion well
Matt's the beard Santa T okay so the
positive thought to give me more details
what you mean oops I said grow products
[Music]
myself brow products let's do a dessert
than that let's let's let's see what
let's see what she suggests let's see
what let's see what she let's see what
she suggests another person that always
has iconic eyeshadow looks has got to be
Queen and Lady Gaga I don't think she'll
answer I've never gotten to meet her
before but I want to literally so so
badly
Lady Gaga inspired me so much as a kid
and truly was somebody who like made me
feel like it was a paid to be myself I
love her hopefully one day I will be
able to give her a hug and to say thank
you for everything she has done also she
just announced her new makeup line a
house laboratories I already pre-ordered
the entire thing so if you guys want to
review when that comes out definitely
let me know but let's see she has an
eyeshadow recommendation after I said it
always comes mascara and the person that
I absolutely 100% want to damn for this
is Queen Paris Hilton
because I feel like she always has a
beautiful stunning lash on so I think
she definitely has to have it
good at recommendation hi Queen hold
your wow I'm gonna imagine a video of me
in Paris Hilton like that be everything
to me just like oh oh give anything to
film with her I feel like it would be
it's so iconic imagine like I become
Paris Hilton sugar baby for a day oh
that's a good one that is a good one you
guys if you want to see me in Paris glam
together love me now that would be so
hot autumn eyeshadow and lashes are all
on the next step of my makeup routine is
always high later when I think of a
highlighter the absolute first person
that comes to mind is JLo she literally
revolutionized highlighter and just
going from within I've met her a person
before she is literally the most perfect
looking human being you could ever
imagine in your entire life she and
a-rod told me that their daughters were
in fact sisters so hello you guys if
you're watching the video and love me
the most cannot wait to meet you
sometime very very soon oh I hope she
replies now just in case JLo doesn't see
it because she's obviously busy with her
show right now I want to do one other
person for highlighter and I think we
need a boy and this here's somewhere
hello I've avoided makeup and I have not
damned a single boy yet oh my god let's
do Troye Sivan he's literally killing it
in the musical right now and he started
on YouTube so hopefully he will
appreciate the effort going into this
video and will definitely reply let me
write to him after her that her next
voice comes my lips and of course we
have the perfect person to Diana for a
lip suggested that as Queen Kylie Jenner
herself and venture of the Kylie lip kit
she thought it has every shade you could
possibly imagine so I know still have a
good suggestion and last but finally not
least we have Settings ready to walk my
face in place all day long and for this
step I wanted am probably the most
famous person on the entire planet right
now and that is a lil nos ex who better
to suggest the settings pray and then
him it because if he's taking his horses
to the old town road I feel like horse
riding is like a very or rigorous sports
so he's got her know how to keep the
makeup on all day long I feel like I
want to do one last person for Settings
bright and I think I need to do someone
that like knows Beauty at least a little
bit Oh
Oh shame it all hiya sister say
congratulations your pregnancy first of
all that baby is literally going to be
the most beautiful child probably ever
in the entire world
y'all better watch out she's coming oh
my god I could not even believe that I
would forget this but we need to do our
king Shawn Mendes hello Shawn and I have
Dan back and forth on Twitter and we
also Matt the mikela for the first time
and he was literally the nicest ever I
was so nervous to be there like you guys
have no idea but he gave me such an
amazing pep talk it was just really a
really dope and down to earth we took a
selfie together but we've never talked
to her Instagram DM so I'm hoping that
he sees this and will reply it later on
all right you guys that I think that is
pretty much every single step of a
makeup routine obviously we have to wait
for people to reply a few people have
already started answering which is so so
cool but I'm gonna go ahead and head to
a few meetings right now and get dinner
later on and then we'll check back in
with you guys later on tonight and we
will get glamp hopefully with
everybody's suggestions all right you
guys hello a good morning we were back
in the sister studio I just got back
super super late last night from a long
weekend with the family over the long
weekend long this party up in Lake
Havasu we got quite a lot of responses
first today's video probably through my
fear of celebrities and I'm so excited
so let's just dive right in all right
you guys so obviously you know what the
first seven every makeup routine is
always going to be a primer and we
reached out to quite a few different
people that have hash tag skin goals for
primer and after five days unfortunately
none of them replied so this video is
off to a really really good start but I
will say obviously they're all very very
busy and out of all the makeup steps
this is the only one that didn't get a
response and I didn't even used to use
primer beforehand so I feel like we can
definitely go ahead and skip it and move
right on to foundation and this step was
actually not looking too promising in
the whole response
department either and Tolle I was in the
shower singing and performing my concert
as usual line anyway business you don't
get his sister squeaky clean and ready
for this video today until they heard my
phone ding and it was it Ben Sarah
notification and I opened the shower
door dripping wet and I glanced over at
my phone and you know who's came almost
Rihanna bad girl RiRi CEO affinity
beauty and the most paid
entertainer in the world sent me a
message and I literally had never found
gold harder and my entire life I'm sure
you guys can already guess what she
recommended but to steer employed and
she said I'm so honored and grateful but
you already know you got to use the pro
filter foundation that started all off
right thank you
you guys heard it right here for the
Queen herself and if you guys know if
you've had a long time sister subscriber
when I first tried the Fendi foundation
I really really did not like it but
after trying a few more times I fell in
love with the formula I have a few
different shades that matched me very
very well but since I got tan at the
lake I did go ahead and pick up a few at
different shape to try out 190 185 and
210 it's let's go ahead and get our base
on and find this is that oh my god this
is too late for me I never thought this
day would come where I actually got tan
and my foundation is too light this is a
plot twist y'all didn't expect we're
just gonna blend our pro filter all over
and get some good full coverage as usual
a but quite a lot of like a sunburn and
a sunspots that I need to cover up so
this be the perfect foundation and base
to do so okay you guys so for concealer
IDM does zara larsson and she actually
replied so quickly that I didn't even
need it three times to anybody else
which I love we love a girl who's on top
of her social media and she said hi babe
that's so fine the for sure easy
question it's definitely make up reverse
full cover extreme at camouflage haha
what flaws okay we love a full coverage
Queen work I have a lot of red marks
from acne singing and I get black
readers under my eyes because I never
sleep this one is magic okay great we
picked it up today and I cannot wait to
see how this one works
I'm just gonna put some on the back of
my hand Wow
this is very very thick then it's gonna
put it in using my morphe sponge as
usual oh my god Zara was not kidding
when she said this concealer was full
coverage literally holy crap okay
low-key high key middle key is a
concealer combo looks so good right now
it is not even finding
I'm like obsessed with all the slugs
this is the most full coverage I think
I've ever been but I'm really not mad
about it before I go in and get Creasy
let's move on to our next step which is
going to be setting powder and the one
person that replied right away was my
queen
Kemp HS oh my god I literally love her
and I'm obsessed with her music Kim said
sister of course I'm sister you the
[ __ ] with the sauce definitely put the
Benji Beauty loose powder and butter
love you whoaaah and pass it on I
literally had to apply and say oh my god
I love you so much because of that is
such a classic akin what type of
response and we have this right here a
lot of that Fendi beauties already
getting two plugs in those videos today
let's go ahead and do as she says and
pack it on okay if this is not packed on
I don't even know what packed on who
could possibly be my face feels so set
and locked in place they all gotta go
ahead and brush the access away and then
we'll be ready for the next step
so this age does the game our makeup is
nice and said please but we're looking
at very very flat so we're going to go
into our next step which is a bronzer I
originally D ended my friend and good
says Iggy Azalea about a primer she did
reply and she said that she does the new
primary she doesn't care because her
makeup routine is trash direct quote
from her would I totally disagree good
because the rank-up always looks
literally perfect but regardless it
doesn't matter
she recommended a bronzer and said it so
for today we're gonna be using her
suggestion which is too late on de
Chanel I've seen literally every single
Beauty your ever in history uses bronzer
but I never actually have so I was aided
to try it out like step one into the
skin oh yeah that looks pretty okay
oh I now see why everyone's obsessed
with this this looks so pretty
next thing when I add just a little bit
more color using a little bit of a blush
and for this I reached out to one person
and one person only and that is because
this person literally wrote back within
minutes the first time which is so so
cool and that is Billy Bobby Brown also
known as 11 and changer things literally
is such an incredible child actress I
obviously love her and really recommend
it at the Charlotte Tilbury blush and I
asked her any specific seed and she said
no any one you want
you look beautiful which is so so sweet
I went to the Sun picked up the
Charlotte Tilbury
cheek to cheek now if you've been around
for a while you guys would know that
blush is kind of a newer step to a
makeup routine now I will say I was a
little nervous at the charlotte tilbury
counter because their blush range is a
little questionable
I'm not gonna lie the color that I
picked up tag is this this combination
was the only one that I thought I could
maybe make work so I'm just gonna go in
and apply it very very lightly you know
I feel like when you're somebody like
Billy Bobby Brown who's like actually
perfect already at age 15 it's really
hard to make her look bad right but me
on the other hand it's not hard so I'm
gonna apply a very tiny little bit of
this and hope to god that it doesn't
ruin my entire makeup look okay that's
not bad at all I was a little scared
there first I kind of not gonna lie but
I like how this looks before I move on
to the next time I'm just gonna really
quickly got a little bit more of that
Pentium Beauty loose powder and butter
and it like my girl Kim Pedro said I'm
really pack it on and just do a little
bit of baking all right you guys well my
face is basically in place I'm gonna
move on to the next step which is going
to be eyebrows and I want to reach out
to somebody who I know always has
perfect eyebrows and that is Madison
beer and my good says came through with
the recommendation she said hi sister I
would love to but give me more details
haha what do you mean grow products and
in this moment I realized I spelled a
brow as growl instead so what a correct
way so she said anastacio always a brow
pencil and medium brown which is
actually the literal exact color that i
even used so this is obviously perfect
thank you so much Madison I love it the
absolute most you guys aren't gonna
gonna do my brows on camera quickly and
I'll be right back
to show off my eyes already you guys we
are both eyebrows are slain and ready to
go thank you once again it's about us
and beer if the recommendation on
estancia literally it never lets us down
and now it is time to play with some
eyeshadow I have a few different people
that have never been afraid to rock a
crazy look on the red carpet obviously
you guys know I love a
outside-of-the-box makeup look we don't
exactly do a neutral glam very often on
this YouTube channel and the first
person to reply it was none other than
the living legend my own mother Kim
kardashian-west
literally within at 4 minutes actually
be sending her to Yama icon and she said
for sure so fun
did you see the tutorial opening I
posted on Instagram
was annoying me trying to take over so I
started tutorial and said hi sister hey
sister I said I know I tweeted saying
that you're coming from my brand I love
you guys so much let me know what
palette to use and she said one of your
palettes and I said no literally any pal
and she said oh then duh one of mine it
expect nothing less the Kardashians are
obviously at marketing Queens and she
says let's do this so my era palette
which I was so stated for because I just
got the PR package in the mail literally
yesterday and I think this packaging is
so cool i actually texted him about a
few days prior because if we open up
this PR package we have the so fired
palette which we're going to use in the
studio in a second beautiful glosses
some liner but we also have these big
matches which are actually included I
just got a splinter hi I'd like to file
a lawsuit against Kim Kardashian well
which are actually included because the
side of the Pierre box can light a match
is that not literally the craziest
packaging you've ever seen this is so
friggin cool hopefully the sisters to do
does not burn down but kudos to camp
because that is innovation alright you
guys this is pretty much the Sapphire
palette color scheme up right here it
isn't so pretty kind of simple I'm gonna
zoom you guys and I already have a look
at mine that I want to do so I'm just
going to it throw that to kind of go a
little bit fast because we still have a
lot of other steps to do I'm first just
taking this dark maroonish brown color
and stamping it into my outer-v
using a marquee I'm about four five six
so with it I'm four three three of
grabbing the Terracotta shade from the
palette and buffing right over top of
that edge driving at em 5:13 and dipping
into that light brown kind of
transitional color I'm just going to
very lightly buff out that top edge I'm
gonna do a soft cut crease using the
gold shade in the bottom corner I'm
gonna add a little bit of Y by using an
angled brush and the dark moon shade it
from the palette once again
alright you guys that it's already one
eye using the Soulfire palette all
complete I think it looks so setting in
definitely reminds me of the campfire
I'm gonna go and do the other one off
camera quickly and I'll be right back to
do it the next step alright you guys
know that eyes are all done it is time
for our next step which is going to be
it lashes now in the beginning of this
video when I was jamming people I said
that I really wanted someone who was
always super super painted the house
down so I could actually get like a good
last recommendation because there's a
good lash and there's like God lashes a
lot could really really
break a look so I went ahead and DM the
first ever influencer the iconic woman
who started it all and that has Paris
Hilton and let me tell you she did not
dissipate at all
Paris robot can set me at this video
first magic must be able to be like I'll
give my favorite Laster by me
I heard mascaras also by me literal
goals hello I need that to be me you one
day like it's gonna happen putting out
into the universe right now anyway like
I said it she did not disappoint
I don't home yesterday and expected a
small little package on my front porch
of lashes and mascara but no it's pure
self that who's literally the queen of
extra and this is what I got literally
every single product you could ever
imagine I'm not even gonna lie I didn't
even know Paris Houston how to makeup
line but I'm not mad about it and cannot
wait to literally try all of this I'm
gonna go ahead and grab the lashes and
mascara and pop them on and try all this
for later so this actually comes with
three different mascaras to choose from
we have lengthening volumizing and
curling mascara for this I think I'm
gonna grab the lengthening mascara since
we are gonna be applying a pair of a
falsies overtalk it's gonna apply a call
to this to what my lashes i just relized
this box literally says lashes that
speak louder than words honestly can't
write you a thought that's hot
that was good that was good it is time
for the next step which is of course
going to be highlighter it is time to
get our glow on and be a sister shiny to
face is looking at very very much you
know so I'm super excited to try our
next product one of my favorite
musicians who is not afraid of a little
bit of glam here and there did reply and
that is a Troye Sivan I'm super pumped
as well because he actually recommended
the glossy a nice shine highlighter and
I've never actually tried any glossy
products before I've been wanting to for
a very very long time so I'm super
pumped to test this out
thank you trying for the recommendation
I picked up this like really really
pretty of rose gold e-type color it is a
cream so I'm just going to oh wow
oh my god that is so bright looks so
pretty
did you see my ring finger for a nice
light touch ten little bit on the nose
we are almost the end of this look you
guys we've sought to tie the entire look
together by adding one last thing and
that is the D lipid e doodahs and who
better to ask for her lips suggest and
then the queen of lips herself literally
revolutionized lips in the makeup
industry and that is a kylie jenner
kylie replied and said ah yes are you
feeling a crazy color or totally up to
me and i said it literally pick whatever
color you want and she simply said i'm
sending you stuff now no I literally got
that damn from Kylie as I was leaving my
house on the way to vacation so I spent
the entire weekend having absolutely no
idea what I was gonna end up with on my
lips but when I got home uh surely
enough there was a bag on my front porch
labeled James Charles with some Kylie
products in it and hopefully this look
combo will match this look perfectly we
have a snow way bae kylie jenner matte
liquid lipstick and lip liner we also
have a Kylie lip liner in the shade
coconut and a lipstick in the shade it
snatched let's see what we got oh I
think coconut is gonna be a really good
color with this yes okay
let's hope snatch is a good lip to go on
top well it's literally like she knew
what the look was gonna be before it
even happened and last but finally not
least the ultimate step of the makeup
routine is going to be our a setting
spray for the step I did reach out to
kind of a lot of different people idea
Shawn Mendes i DM little moss acts that
I also damnit a Shay Mitchell because I
wasn't really sure who was going to
reply and this depth was actually the
only step of the routine that we had two
different people reply for little lost
acts did not respond he must have been
busy writing has a 57th
Ulta the rotary works and getting ready
to release it by the way its treatment
now even though he didn't reply or soul
sister supporting but Shawn Mendes
actually responded I was honestly 100%
not even expecting Shawn to see the
message let alone respond so when his
name popped up in my phone I was shocked
and also very very excited
I clicked him the message he said he
wanted to think about it and thank you
so much for the kind words
I'm personally they'll hate to knock it
back to me and
for holding this video which sucks but
you know who did it was Shay Mitchell
and sister came through with the
settings my recommendation chase that Oh
fun a setting spray hmm I'd say go for
the more if you wanna good choice
Farrell and she said don't forget to use
Co - a bottle and I said Oh Mufti you're
so cute does that could actually work
and she said no and I said you know what
code does work
use code James for 10% off perfect way
to adopt today's video all right sisters
and I think that is today's makeup look
chosen completely by my favorite
celebrities all complete looki Lemire
I'm honestly very pleasantly surprised
as to how this luck turned out today
this could've gone really bad really
fast if either nobody responded or if
people recommended products that just
didn't really work well together but I
am so grateful for everybody who took
the time out of their very busy
schedules - right back at ya thank you
guys so so so much and also thank you
for recommending good products because I
love a makeup look today and I really
hope you sisters love it as well if you
did enjoy this video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
and show your love and support it really
does help me out quite a lot and also if
you have not already make sure to click
that big red subscribe button down below
and come join the sisterhood I would
love to have you and the family and also
click that Bell icon so you get a
notification every time I upload a brand
new video if you like to follow me on my
makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both
substantive stars my snapshot for more
behind the scenes and stuff is jane
austen extra s after Charles and my
twitch for live streaming and gaming
content is Jay Charles Beauty this
videos to search out it goes to Chloe
thank you so much look for always
falling in supporting you I love you so
so so much and if you like to be the
next videos sisters have out don't
forget to always reach me piteous and I
go live on Twitter and turn on my
youtube post notifications also if you'd
like to check out or shop for any
merchandise don't forget to check out
sisters apparel calm that is not your
first today's video thank you guys so so
so much for watching I love you and I
will see you in the next one bye
[Music]