hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so as
you can see once again I have a very
very special guest joining me here today
my little brother
Ian you guys absolutely smashed the
freaking lights on our my little brother
does eye makeup video it was definitely
an interesting look to say the least
how did you feel about doing makeup for
the first time it's very difficult in
the last video I did make you guys a
promise and I said if we got 50,000
likes I would sit little Ian down once
again and we would do another video
where I did his makeup I think it is
time Ian to get a full glam makeover
because lord knows my look was not too
full glam or a quality makeover so we're
gonna give it on Ian today how do you
feel about this I'm not very excited
have you ever worn makeup before on my
hickeys yeah okay alright so we have our
pink kitty drink ADIZ and we are ready
to get glam let's do this so I'm first
gonna start by priming it sister Ian
Stacy's in the benefit Porefessional
primer so units obviously a teenager he
is 15 years old which is one question
that we didn't answer in the last video
so Ian definitely has a teenager skin
right now and he does get breakouts
relatively often but that's okay
everybody does so pore freshner is
definitely gonna help to like fill in
his pores and make his skin nice and
smooth so for foundation sonography use
in the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD
foundation stick in the shader why three
six five now you guys know I'm usually
between Y 315 and Y 335 eNOS definitely
blessed a little bit more of a tan than
I am I had to have a fake one but he is
all natural so we're gonna be using this
one today which is hopefully gonna be a
good match and oh boy yeah it looks like
it is how are you feeling about this so
far she was like peanut butter Oh
a Sofer concealer today we're using the
tarte tape tape concealer in the shade
light/medium honey now ironically enough
this is actually one of the products
that you picked up for our video
together already those you know this is
one of my all-time favorites so we're
gonna use this on him as well today I
know I had to do the white in the dark
but I don't think I did that right yeah
exactly
I'm really really excited to contour and
snow study because like out of his
entire face that is the one feature that
he got from either my mom or my dad I
don't even know who has this nose but I
wish I had this nose because of this no
sister right up in here it's a [ __ ] to
contour and we all know that for sure
then I'm gonna stay in space quickly
using the laura mercier translucent
setting powder and my Beauty Blender and
just Pat that right under the eyes nope
don't raise your eyebrows look up there
you go perfect
the to contour and space today I'm going
to use my morphe M 570 brush and might
come on D shade and light palette as
always and I won't dip into the medium
shade so we're looking at questions on
my phone from you guys on Twitter while
we do ends makeup to answer some of your
guys's questions once again similar to
the last video because we got so many
cool and funny ones
and so yes this question is free and
have you had any weird experiences with
fans oh yeah honey my fans been really
weird to you at the meet up in New York
City they asked for my snapchat and
stuff snapchat
happy asked what's it like being so
[ __ ] annoying looks like being so
[ __ ] rude [ __ ] you cat son drooler
asked which one he was better at singing
oh you've literally turned off where do
you match her to me
[ __ ] do it no jacqueline asked can
you all impersonate each other oh god I
sisters has got my pink kitty drink it
II do I really sound like that yeah
basically hey guys it's good today we're
gonna go all right so while Ian's face
is baking in the oven at 350 degrees I
have my benefit precising eyebrow pencil
in the shade number 6 and we're gonna
slightly in Sprouse own AV to their
celebrity crush do you think you could
name on the vine boy boy Shawn Mendes
yeah I'm gonna set the brows and please
do my benefit gimme brow in the shade at
number 5 Daryl last who is straighter
gosh so friends look today he asked me
not to do any eyeshadow and since I did
force him to sit down and do this video
with me and the first place I figured
fine sister I'll honor his wishes so
we're gonna go right on to lashes and
mascara
somebody's the benefit roller lash today
you know it's really really long laughs
his but he also has super hooded eyelids
so this is extremely difficult to like
actually get in there not oh get mascara
everywhere just like I just did
you [ __ ] up I did so for lashes today
I'm actually gonna pop on the Lily
lashes in the style miami's you guys
know that these are some of my all-time
faves and these obviously happen to be
the lashes that you use on me as well
use code Jade for 10% off
yeah no no looking down stay looking
down open how do they feel
do they feel heavy yes uncomfortable and
they're ticklish yeah no no never again
so for her later on sister Eve's today
of course I'm using the anasazi I saw
Hollywood illuminator you guys know this
is my all-time babe oh look at that nose
contour she is not for the gods hunty
yeah no no so the next up for ian's face
is obviously gonna be the Liberty
doodahs and for our first video together
he did me real dirty and put me in a
plum lipstick with green eyeliner
he was shaking trembling dead actually
so from my looking and I'm gonna be a
whole lot nicer because I'm an amazing
brother I'm gonna give him a nice nude
lip so he doesn't look ugly and are
gonna whom the Oprah liquid lipstick in
the shade so Paolo and you can use
Cochise with 30% off all over products
your lips are so chapped I'm definitely
gonna over line Ian's upper lip as well
because he has literally no lip at all
so thanks man you're so welcome our last
and final step today is gonna be to lock
sister Ian's face in place all day long
using our Urban Decay all nighter
setting spray are you ready all right
guys so this is the completed glam look
on sister Ian how do you feel different
I feel uncomfortable and it hurts my
lashes burning but at the end of the day
it's just makeup and it wipes off so T
major thank you to my little brother
invested in the entire world Ian for
doing this video with me obviously it is
not like society's saying for straight
guys to wear makeup that came out weird
you know what I mean and it was really
really cool for him to be able to sit
down or do this with me and just be
comfortable in front of the camera this
athlete took a lot of warming up to do
but I'm really really glad that he was
able to do it with me today so thanks
yeah if you guys sit into this video
today please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and if you have
not already as well make sure to click
that big red subscribe button with the
notification about next to it I post
three videos a week on Mondays
Wednesdays and Fridays that I'd love to
have you join the sisterhood if you'd
like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram or
Twitter they both just James Charles and
my snapchat from over behind the scenes
I sell is James Charleston extra ass
after Charles if you want to follow me
on instagram my instagram is Ian JD 12
you heard the man
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching much love from the Charles
family and we will see you next time bye
[Music]
okay I'm taking this [ __ ] off