hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so I
just got out of a meeting in Santa
Monica which if you know la is probably
on the west side and I currently have to
go to a fitting and then a red carpet
tonight and then a dinner and then a
movie so today's going to be an
absolutely crazy night and the one
problem is that is currently for 1/2
p.m. and that means there is LA traffic
and if you live in LA you know that la
traffic is no joke and is like our long
ventures no matter where you go and I
currently have to go to Hollywood which
isn't gonna be in the car for at least
an hour which is not the best so I have
sister Anthony with me and I packed all
eye makeup goodies in here because I
knew this is gonna happen and I planned
accordingly like the good sister I am I
have all my makeup ready and I just
called an uber frost bear currently at a
gas station and I'm gonna be filming a
get ready in the end and uber video
today I'm a little spooked I don't know
how this is gonna go
hopefully the ride isn't bumpy hopefully
my face looks beats by the end of it but
this is gonna be a major time crunch so
if you guys wanna see to get ready in an
uber keep watching we walk to a gas
station with a because both of us
sisters have to pee and we're gonna get
our uber from here but I have only
makeup goodies right here all pumped up
and I have my Beauty Blender which we
need to of course wet and get nice
good symphony winkeny here that we're
just gonna get her nice and moist city
boys today
Harper James let's go
how's the lighting there it's good
really yeah okay so I have all my stop
sign out here in the back seat I'm gonna
keep it nice and clean not trying to
mess up this car I'm gonna start off
with my beauty blender foundation and
I'm not realizing that I didn't bring
them here either so I guess I only have
money here which is very musty in my
shade and light palette so I'm sorry
anybody who has motion sickness I've
recently been using a new combination of
foundation which I'm starting off in my
Giorgio Armani luminous silk and I like
to add like a few like one pump of my
ball in this way by Too Faced which you
guys know I stand by and then also a
tiny bit of the anasazi liquid glow and
I've been using the shade of pearl I
just like a really really dewy skin base
I don't know why I also know I'm doing
all these liquids cuz ya'll know but I
love my HD stick and a stuff Li new free
but okay so like I said I just had a
very very exciting meeting about
something that I've been working on for
a very long time to hear all about and I
promise you'll be hearing soon so keep
your ears and your eyes peeled for a
very very fun movie premiere that way
managers brother is actually working on
so I'm going to walk the red carpet and
looking lamp but y'all know me I were
the same damn alpha every time I walk
about carpet so I'm going to get silent
tonight which I'm super excited for
because I never really get to get styled
and how they believe like professional
outfit so that should be fun and we're
currently head
over there right now but like I said
Pelle traffic a little bit spooky
especially this time of the day and we
are how long to stay we are away about
20 minutes okay sir about 20 months wait
for the stylist and then from there we
have to go to the carpet so I need to
get glam fast my base is all Ottoman of
course she's my heart shaped ape
consumer and this is in the shade
light/medium and I'm gonna put this
between my pants carefully and try not
to spill as anywhere and then of course
on here so far not as hard to do makeup
in a moving vehicle as I thought it
would be but then again we haven't
really gotten to anything serious I
anticipate the brows being challenges
this is funny I feel like we're filming
a documentary eight oh my god speaking
of this week I actually went to Demi
Lovato's document April or snapchat to
literally follow me everything in this
body but if you guys want me you know
that I went and it was literally one of
the most fun nights of my entire life
I was actually [ __ ] personally invited
by WGME on Instagram as a girl you need
to go and I was like sister I'm there so
it was just a magical experience I got
to meet her she was just so nice
I generally look up to Demi it's so much
because she's been through so much in
this cut out so strong and also she just
has literally like the best voice in all
three so just an amazing experience you
guys have to check out her new movie
when it comes out on October 17th this
is not sponsored we are in traffic hour
as well like I said so the sauna is
looking really weird right now so I
apologize the lighting I'm dealing with
that barely I'm gonna grab my Laura
Mercier translucent setting powder -
really careful this because everywhere
should I be like filming you dipping
into your crimes I mean if you want to
there's not much to see that anywhere
itself look at my hoodie hoodie and
black which is not available in citizens
- appear home because it's sold out but
all the other sisters merch is available
on sisters - apparel calm which you
should totally check out and shop if
you're a true sister also speaking of
10% off we are in a car right now and
y'all know sister James always customer
with a coupon code so if you'd like the
five dollars off of your first ride use
code James D 1 5 4 3 2 ue we couldn't
get even more annoying
I brought my brushes in this like little
carrying case I think it's from Japan
desk to bronze my face brush you guys
when it comes to frosting but I recently
had this one for the first time a few
days ago and I really really love it
there's just a lot software lets you get
like applications wait are we here yeah
yeah this is the address here oh god ok
so just is running a little way I'm
gonna have to speed this process up but
let's go get fitted
okay so she's a baking 350 degrees let's
try not so close well you definitely
look interesting right now it's
Valentine's Day nonexistent boyfriends
it looks better on honestly don't hate
it
Anthony this is just like speaking to me
maybe you should hang up there's a
voicemail I mean honestly for what we're
working with back there it looks good
Anthony you're so good I literally never
walk carpets or go to events and I'm
actually confident happy with what I'm
wearing I love this okay so we just got
the often and now the event currently
service and I think that's away so we're
going to get back in the zubur and we're
gonna clap because this is not red
carpet ready
and I'm doing my eyebrows now this is
not the most easy thing to do it and
it's black okay it's so weird seeing you
from the side but not your highlight
I mean it's usually facetune on anybody
sound okay the fact that there's traffic
right now is actually playing at my
favorite because we keep stopping
[Music]
yeah clean you're keeping it back there
yeah unlike your reputation um good luck
just my face using my skin to navy out
and makeup finishing spray oh my god so
guys so not only that I get to go to a
really fun it will be prepared sleep but
the Demi Lovato thing like I said
earlier flashback was also in the studio
almost all week long working on a few
new songs that'll be coming out soon for
your eyes and let me just so excited
because like working on the script is
doing such a nice breath of fresh air
for me it's what some of my best friends
and obviously you guys know that music
is a huge part of my life and a huge
passion of mine so just like having this
is like a nice break from the makeup
growth because y'all know going crazy
has been really really fun working a lot
of your songs
you guys so check them so keep your ears
peeled can I have to tell you right now
which I'm a little spooked about because
once again nose contouring in a moving
vehicle I would not wish on my worst
enemy
thank you so much oh don't ever again
please I hope you take a really sharp
turn so that you just have like a line
of lipstick across your face why would
you ever
okay so we're all done and we are
running a little bit late but we did
manage to get our entire face done over
the course of the last few hours and a
moving vehicle this is not easy but we
accomplished this and I'm proud of us
even though this look is the most basic
as it can possibly get I'm really
surprised
and I'm gonna give myself a quick spritz
of the Marc Jacobs decadence for a few
just have a so good
can I think we're ready to go
[Music]
alright guys so that was so much fun the
red carpet wasn't slate I felt so good
and my luck and then the movie Buddhist
Cobra as well it was so good
I'm not gonna come too close I had such
a fun time but this big of inspiron for
far far too long we're looking a little
bit crusty a little bit dusty sister
Brittany brought me some makeup boys on
about us youth this space ah
but all that being said thank you guys
so much for watching today's get ready
with me in an uber video this was an
interesting experience at least it was
done a lot harder than expected but I
think I didn't do that out of a job for
the time I was given what was going on
in the car at the bunks and also the
lighting at the end because they quickly
became at nighttime which was about the
easiest thing in the world if you guys
enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and scram if you have not already
I post videos sometimes and you should
also look that little belly cut as well
so you can be notified every time I
upload a new video if you'd like to
follow me other makeup journey to follow
me an image but are they able to stream
Charles and my sister but you ask after
Charles if you're already in the system
I love you so much and if you'd like to
check out any of the official sister
emerge like this use coach James for 10%
equity which was officially sold out but
go to sister Shasha pound come pick up
or hoodies and hats and pops like as all
the stuff is so cute and there's a ton
of new stuff coming soon for holiday as
well so stay tuned the successors how
that goes to my husband Marcus thinks oh
my babe wake and ready for baby this
breakup layers because I didn't take it
so bad
thank you guys so much for watching I
love you so much today I'll see you in
the next one bye
[Music]