hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I
feel like it has been literally as so
long since I've lost in you guys I am so
sorry for the lack of videos that have
been coming out I've been so incredibly
busy with a lot of stuff of my personal
life but we're back we're ready to go
it has also been a long time since I've
worn a black leather baseball hat in the
video but you know what this is what
we're dealing with today
you're welcome for the Hat first today's
video I actually have a super fun at
challenge playing that I've never tried
before and I'm honestly absolutely
horrified to test out but you know what
it's probably gonna be really funny for
you guys to watch fun thing that is
super super vital to both beauty videos
and just makeup in general is light when
you guys watch my videos at home you get
to watch a very very nice and beautiful
pretty setup but I shoot with two huge
huge huge lights that are hanging right
above my head they're very very
expensive as well and they do a very
nice job of lighting this whole room and
making me look very very pretty so for
today's video what we're gonna do is
lose them and I'm gonna do my entire
face and makeup in the dark despite the
fact that I thought my videos the two
very very expensive lights I also film
it with a very very expensive camera
which upon further research I learned
does not have a nighttime mode of course
so to fix this problem I went to Best
Buy today and picked up this also very
very expensive camera that I'll probably
never use again that looks like it's
from 1984 but apparently it has a really
good at night mission mode so fingers
crossed that this video goes well I
thought of this challenge earlier on
today I thought it would be such a funny
video to do I've never seen it done
before but I looked it up and apparently
buzz we did it a few years ago so credit
to them do not attack me for stealing
and their video idea and without further
ado if you like to see me doing makeup
in complete darkness keep on watching
hello
[Music]
so here that would be absolute pitch
block I've turned every single laid-off
in my apartment and closed all my
curtains all I can see is just like
basic shapes and outlines and I have a
mirror right here okay know how because
I put it there and I'm looking in it and
I can see absolutely nothing so this
should be really great so not only can I
not see what I'm doing but for once in
my life today coincidentally I decided
to be organized and put everything back
in storage so I'm gonna pick up all my
makeup product support this video not
being able to see it what they are lord
please help me get to this without
another scandal let's go okay so first
we need a primer so I know that my
skincare drawer is right here I think I
know this is to touch a water cream okay
next is foundation which is English
right here Oh God
okay I know this is a makeup forever
sick but I have way too many shades of
that that is what are you too risky of a
game to be playing today oh I know
exactly what that is
that's cancelled okay I think this is
tuefel this way because I know the TF
logo is right on top and like engraved
letters but I have no idea what shade
this is and I just bought four new
shades so this might go really bad
really fast
next is a concealer which I know is over
this is definitely thar shape tape this
feels very empty wait that's a good
thing that means I use it right welcome
to contour
definitely yeah so next set your blush
comes highlighter
why am I forgetting my makeup routine
discuss I'm in the dark okay that's
gonna be here okay this is the new
Anasazi I'm really a highlighter I think
I hope the next after hand later comes
brows which i think is right above my oh
there's benefical brown eye shadow so
let's head back down to the pallet or no
I want to do they get a worm tone kafka
crease I obviously do those a lot so I
think I know the technique behind that
and I think that'll be relatively okay
leader try to replicate tonight I have
no ideas or that or that
this feels dirty really really dirty
okay this is definitely multi palette oh
I think this might be the John help out
oh this is definitely the 39a this is
too big to be a regular palette hello so
I'm gonna go ahead and pick this palette
I know that this one is a 39a but I
actually don't have the shades like
memorized so I'm too scared of doing
something very ugly with that and I
think that this might be the John help
out so this one that looks like it'd be
a good contender hopefully so next I
need an eyeliner which I know is right
above the eyebrow drawer so that would
be here
I think yeah right here
Oh what did I just do uh-oh I doesn't
want to attempt to do a full on it
so I'm looking for a black liquid liner
I have no idea how ever gonna find oh
just kidding this is the Kat Von D
tattoo liner thing though Oh what is all
these drawers not closing what is my eye
oh setting spray I definitely need ah oh
let's grab yes that's is lips oh god
this to go really wrong let's call this
one oh my god not sad I say and I'm
gonna start by priming my face that I
used in what I hope is my top shot water
cream moisturizer I really really love
this and it is really really great
that's low buddy feels so gross because
I'm so it's taking addressed right now
like this is not what I want to be doing
but this is either born this way or it
could also be luminous silk thank you
guys so I hate that foundation I'm gonna
do three pumps there it is on the back
of my hand
Oh yup there's defecation there uh-huh
uh-huh
I think this is very similar to the no
mirror makeup challenge being that I
obviously cannot see what I'm doing
except for the fact that there is a
mirror right there I just still can't
see myself definitely needs for me to
blend on the neck because if this is the
wrong foundation shade that's gonna be
our only saving grace that might
disguise it a little bit okay so next up
is going to be our concealer which no
definitely not concealer is right here
okay oh this is definitely shaved table
uh-huh I'd done the nose bridge bring it
em out same thing on the other side oh
that's my eyeball the key to this house
definitely gonna be to blend blend blend
blend blend because clearly I cannot see
anything that's going on I know there's
a mirror right there but I won't
then comes Beautyblender dip it right in
oh gosh
[Music]
next comes contour which i know i have
my cup Mundi Oh shade light palette for
but I need to find my contouring brush
and I know that all my brushes are
organized from smallest so I have my
like detail brushes that I have letting
brushes that I have face brushes right
here so this been it's gonna be where
I'm gonna want to choose this one from
this might be actually this is a fan
brush no that should not even be in
there imagine I put it on and there's
like blue eye shadow on it holy crap I'm
going to go right in on my cheek bone
which is right about here how do you
just oh how do you just sit there
whether you're annoying a scar and just
let it hunk like that for like an hour
it's in just going and going and going
collect your car this has been a PSI I
need to move now next we're gonna do
some highlighter quickly and we're gonna
use what I hope is the Anasazi rocks are
easy new highlighter oh you see that
glow me either okay also gonna go put it
right above the brow bone like always
okay that should be good
I'm gonna get my Beauty Blender again
and dip it into oh shoot I'm gonna judge
by the noise of all the snot and right
now is that I'm definitely hitting the
right place okay so now it is eyebrows
heavy time horrified for but let's do
this I'm gonna start off in the front
and bring it up towards the tail which i
think is over here
I hope bring it out then back up I'm
scared now just lean up underneath my
eyebrows which I know I need my Mac I
like to cover up for so I'm gonna put
this on
the back of my hand a little squirt and
I also need a flattop concealer brush
which should be amazing try to find in
this it says my eyebrow bone yeah oh my
god my eyelids feel why this is gross
okay so next is the part that I'm
absolutely dreading and that I'm sure
you're all upset for the eyeshadow like
I said I have no idea what problems even
as dangerous cross said it's a Jocelyn
Hill palette I have a strong inkling
that it may be but I could be very very
wrong so if this is about that I think
it is I do use this palette quite a lot
so I think I have a pretty good idea of
where the colors are and I think that
the third shade from the top is a light
transition shade wait is it the one
below it I can really cannot tell where
my actual creases this is not good I
usually do one eye at a time but I don't
trust myself to remember the colors that
I use and I also definitely did not
trust myself to be able to find the
brushes again in a few minutes so I
guess we're gonna do both eyes at the
same time oh god just keep blending just
keep blending blending blending oh love
that sister voice crack here next gonna
grab another fluffy brush and try to
deepen up the this feels like an m4 33
okay well the right chalk I'm gonna
place this right on my outer area
[Music]
imagine I think I'm doing like a warm
tone half cut crease and by the end of
the video I turn the lights on and I
have a blue smokey eye on with my luck I
wouldn't even be surprised okay so now
that we have the crease colors all in
place I'm gonna take the Stila liquid
metals in whatever shade this is and I'm
going to carve out my crease aha oh I
think that was to go to crease cutting I
felt that one even in the dark you're
still gonna have our little fan
okay and next I'm just going to be
winged liner which is oh right here Oh
if this look turned out any sort of good
by some miracle this is where this is
where we lose it sisters
oh hey that could be good I think this I
might be a lot easier this is always my
better eye for eyeliner oh I forgot to
fill it in no I'm gonna leave it at that
okay we're almost done
thank God it is getting so dark I'm
literally falling asleep while doing
this next up we have lashes God let's
undo the pasta oh god I forgot about the
whole tweezer situation wait I have to
cut these two scissors in the dark
sounds like the worst idea ever in the
entire world though that's my finger
okay oh that does not feel right she's
on there
[Music]
I think oh hello
okay I feel like that could be
relatively correct this whole area feels
very very sticky which is telling me
that I probably got glue in an area that
should not contain glue and now I'm
concerned
okay now that lashes are all are we have
mascara and for this I think I picked
out my benefit roller lash if I am
correct so I'm going to oh god oh god
I'm actually horrified of this between
West carrot with lights on is literally
already scary enough and I'm somehow me
editing to do this in complete darkness
you know what if I poked myself I'm
already pretty much blind at this point
I might as well finish it off oh just
like that oh and last but certainly not
least we have lipstick which i think is
an overlook of lipstick I really it
could not see or smell much but with a
little amount of nasal passageway I have
left Oh nope this is shave tape we have
lipstick which i think is Oprah yeah
definitely over a house that very like
cupcake e-type smell uh-huh uh-huh got a
over line just a little bit oh that was
a lot a bit okay I think we're done
oh we have to set our face in place okay
okay I think I'm ready for the reveal
I'm honestly horrified but let's her
night vision off one two three oh my god
oh that was a lot okay hello oh oh oh
god I'm scared
this is interesting it just at least
lets go back through it step by step we
started off with touch of water cream I
was right it frickin love this thing
then to phrase boils my foundation I was
right once again it warm nude this
happens to be my shade thank God next
was tart shaped tape this is in the
shade light/medium laura mercier that
was correct looks like I forgot to wipe
off my bake apparently that is just fine
and dandy not surprised we use candy
shade and light palette they'll be
pretty hard to freakin it miss this one
in my palette or considering it is
broken and open and barely existing
anymore for highlighter we did grab the
Anasazi I'm lazy highlighter it is
definitely looking blinding to say the
least really love this super flattering
placement of all over my cheek that I
went with today okay let me know why
this eyebrow is low-key like kind of
good
this sister over here she's struggling
let's be real but this one over here
like she's doing it okay so next is
eyeshadow and we did end up with the
Johnson help Allah thank God I was right
I'm not I ended up picking okay yeah the
transition shade which is right here and
then this shade right here I think if I
remember correctly which is the shades
that I wanted to go with definitely not
the half cut crease that we were going
for but doesn't look that bad next was
eyeliner which turned out and trusting
to say the least she comes to a nice
little point definitely is a little bit
wonky in this region it definitely could
be a little bit sharper like ready to
cut somebody but you know why she's
she's a struggle Wang she's like
flopping in the wind she's like not like
airborne yet but like she's trying she's
like the chicken of the wagons lying on
her that was a horrible joke also loved
that I completely forgot to do with
lower lashline eye shadow good job James
I think the best result out of the
entire face though is the lips like
Hello look at these they look so good I
thought at one point my lipstick slipped
and I Overland way too much but
apparently I overlay my lips a lot on a
regular makeup basis because these look
pretty good I'm proud of myself for that
one not just for sure not gonna lie I
really did not have high hopes for this
challenge at all I think this is kind of
like the no mirror makeup challenge and
that you can't see what you're doing at
all but also I did not pick up the
makeup products prior either so picking
all of these could have really easily
been a huge disaster but that just tells
me that I am way too addicted to makeup
and know way too much about all the
products that I use on an everyday basis
because I feel like I did a very very
good job of picking out products that I
would normally use so I guess good job
to myself for that I definitely want you
guys leave me a comment down below
though tell me how you think I did do
you think you could do this challenge
how well do you really know your makeup
collection apparently I know mine very
very well this challenge was so much fun
to film but I will never be doing this
again if you think I would ever walk out
of the house looking like this you're on
something else girl Jaime in my lights
if you did into this video today please
don't forget to give a big thumbs up
down below if you have not already cuz
that little belly icon so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video come during the sisterhood we were
still hosted 3 million subscribers and I
would love to have you join the family
if you'd like to follow me and my make
up journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both does
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes I'm stuff it's James
Charles and extra s after Charles this
video sister shout out goes to sister
Mila thank you so much for your always
falling in supporting you know I love
you so so so much and if you'd like to
be the next video sister shut up make
sure it always we treat a video links
let it go live on it Twitter all right
sisters thank you so much for watching I
love you so much and I will see you in
the next one
[Music]