hi sisters jean-charles here and welcome
back to a youtube channel for today's
that I have a very very special guest my
beautiful mother sister Christie B I'm
okay I'm just located to have her here
for today's video if you guys missed the
last video my entire family is currently
out here visiting me in LA right now it
is so amazing and so much fun in our
last video we filmed together my mom and
my dad actually competed against each
other in an episode of Beauty battles it
was so crazy and so much fun if you guys
missed that video you have to look like
right up here right above my mom's face
and go watch it thank you guys for all
the love and support on the video and so
many of the comments were asking me to
put my mother and full glam and I am so
excited because I've only done her
makeup a few times and every single time
she's complained because it is too much
to put covered but she's gonna suck it
up and her today's video we're gonna
give it sister Christy B s sister full
glam makeover I watched James glam
himself or his friends all the time and
I'm very excited to watch him glam me
his mom with more mature skin let's get
started
[Music]
I'm gonna stalk my bubble States today
by moisturizing her skin using the top
water cream if you guys have my makeup
tips and tricks today from a few weeks
ago I talked about the importance of
using a moisturizer before at your
makeup routine my mom does have more
mature skin but we are obviously gonna
be putting on a whole lotta makeups
today so we really want to make sure
that all the makeup goes on nice and
smoothly and does it look like cakey and
textured because that's never the goal
for Friday's you say I'm gonna go into
the Too Faced Born This Way Foundation
you guys know this is my all-time
favorite and my mom does have a holy
skin it like me as well so this will
work really really well with her skin
type and like we were saying she does
have more mature skin so this is gonna
be a full coverage foundation which I
would normally not do but sister
Christie does love a really good a full
coverage base right yes and that is
because she has it oh sorry
did a lot yeah well don't tell the
sisters a little bit more about what
vitiligo is and how it is kind of like
affected you vitiligo is an autoimmune
disease and there isn't any cure doesn't
hurt and it's not contagious but it is
waste spots that continue to increase as
years go on but I've learned to embrace
my spots and love my skin no matter what
her putting on a foundation on top of
that's what I write I also feel more
confident when it's covered up oh do you
know that I just started using a Beauty
Blender like two weeks ago what I used
to until two weeks ago just use my
finger to put in scared of uh-oh part of
you for making the transition I actually
do like it took me a while to get used
to it you're so brave
thank you very much sorry I successors
are sending questions while me and my
mom are doing our makeup today it's so
we can like talk about stories and me as
a child and all sorts of fun and
embarrassing things so let's do that
I guess scissored you and asks do you
think James is more like his mom or his
dad and in what ways do you think he is
like you James has a very strong
personality he always has his dad has a
strong person
okay so I like you you're kind sometimes
excuse me I remember when you were
younger you'd go to school and the
teachers thought you were the best thing
since sliced bread and I'm like are you
talking about the same James because you
always gave us a run for our money when
you were younger
yep you're very sassy uh-huh nothing is
saying but never two teachers uh-huh and
you're brilliant like your father daddy
it's very very smart just like you are
now definitely did not get the hey smart
genes from sister Christie I got all the
good personality genes that matter and
you got your looks for me too right good
answer
okay so you're just like I was a very
very spirited child as you always like
to say so speaking of sister ELISA asks
can you tell one story of James when he
was younger that you just knew who was
gonna be me just one story because I
have lots of stories oh you did not
sleep through the night until you were
two and a half years old your
pediatrician recommended the Ferber
method which you let him cry for a few
minutes and go in and continue to
increase the time so they realize
they're not gonna get anything from
crying and they'll eventually soothe
themselves back to sleep on their own
you were so determined that you
continued to scream and I would leave
the house in my car because I couldn't
stand listening to you for I would come
back an hour two later and you were
still crying and it didn't work for you
so daddy and I took you to the
pediatrician and asked what was going on
and she said most kids would have given
up she said James is not gonna be an
easy child to parent but he's going to
do great things in life oh she said that
really she did Wow and she asked what is
your favorite memory together with you
and James spending time on Cape Cod
every summer we would rent a house on
the Cape and hang out on a beach well
that's not true I couldn't sit on the
beach I had a chased after you because
you literally would go to the different
people and start chatting with them
nearly - now you're contouring my nose
meaning to make it look more snatched
it's not to notice here on the Jim Shaw
YouTube channel you have a look at good
in tiny nose and you definitely give en
your nose so rude because I did not get
that whose nose do you think you have I
don't know yeah Paloma sleeves is making
a place I am so excited because now it
is finally time for the eyebrows and
such as I love my beautiful mother her
eyebrows need help
oddly she has like three eyebrow hairs
the ones that are there are like 70
miles apart
I just I'm very very excited about this
today we're gonna give her some advice
and Slade and snatched sister brows I
can't wait I can't wait I think I put
them on nicely when I do I'm not usually
taking a brow pencil and draw one line
I'm not used to having a full brow so
clearly I've never had a lot of eyebrow
hairs and I never even penciled them in
until probably a few years ago ever
Billy yeah and what a difference
eyebrows make yeah they change your face
they really do I definitely learned that
from you
we have my eyebrows are definitely under
wet intense transformation for the
better on this YouTube makeup journey so
my mom does really have a lot of eyebrow
houses artists Lee helps us a lot
because we have a lot to work with them
you can kind of put them wherever we
want which is great so I'm starting off
this eyebrow by kind of mapping it out
so I'm really extending it the front of
her brow like a good probably half an
inch in your basic eyebrow should start
like right outside of the bridge of your
nose we're gonna send out a little bit
Anna making a little bit longer then I'm
just calling her natural brow shape and
thickness to fill in the rest of the
and I'm just riding really really light
strokes because she does have a blonde
hair and we obviously don't want them to
look like really really dark brown
butter just look wonky when I get to the
end of the road I'm just extending that
brow outwards continuing with that art
and drawing in a tail at the end to
really finish up her brow sheep and to
make a complete and full brow yesterday
when I did your brows I had like a gel
would you recommend me using a gel on
James or not the point of Bronto is
really to set the brow hairs in place
and kind of push them in the direction
that you want them to go once you
already have your brows filled add so
Brown gel is really gonna be more for
people like me who have a lot of brow
hairs and if you do fill them in you
want them to all light and like the
right direction but for someone like you
who doesn't really have as many brow
hairs brow gel is definitely not
necessary okay now the trick is to make
the other one look the same way yeah cuz
browser they are how does it feel to
have two eyebrows they look good
actually I'm good wow what a difference
some eyebrows make huh yeah really does
and when I see you next time they're
gonna be there okay I can do it a lot of
faith trust and some trans powder dust
for my mom's eye so today I'm gonna use
the brand new Anasazi a soft glam
eyeshadow palette just like the name I
do want to go with a soft glam look
today definitely not gonna get my mom a
black smoky eye that is for sure we're
just gonna keep it light and natural I'm
gonna start with my morphe Emma for part
one brush and dip into the shade and
burnt orange and it's gonna place this
all over her lid for a light wash of
color
my mom does have more wrinkly eyelids
which is hopefully okay it just comes
with having more mature skin I'm just a
very very gentle when using these
windshield wiper motions making sure not
to really tug at her eyelid at all
because we don't want to create any more
wrinkles we just want to get a light
wash of color on there very very nicely
and make sure it is evenly distributed
and blend it out next time I got my
morphe the ab 4-3-3 brush is my all-time
favorite crease brush and packing brush
and I mixed together the shades that see
ya
and rustic and his places on the outer
corner
[Music]
then I'm just gonna go back into my
blending brush and go over those edges
make sure everything gets nice and
blended and buffed out using a flat
pocket brush this is Miami two to four
I'm gonna dip into the shade it
glistening right here and I'm gonna give
it a just quick spritz of mac fix+ and
pop that right on the lid that was a
third different brush for eyeshadow yeah
because I'd still use the sponge type
thing yes no and don't be saying
anything well yeah I mean you still look
amazing but you can do your makeup
routine in five minutes and I take two
hours for my I don't have two hours no
yeah most people don't but what a
difference the bright products and the
right brushes right but you also have to
have a technique James you're an artist
I am NOT an artist no my applicator
works just fine huh
next I'm just gonna go this Mac two to
one ass brush it's just a tiny little
blender brush and dip it to the
slightest bit of Cypress umber and I do
mean the slightest bit and just put this
right on the outer corner just to create
a little tiny bit of dimension I'm then
just gonna go with a Mac Brown a pencil
in the shade at chestnut and by my mom's
upper waterline she usually uses a black
eyeliner but I'm really not a fan of
using black when it comes to a softer
clamp look and I think that's just using
a light brown will create a more softer
more natural look well just what we want
I'm gonna pull my mom's eyelid up just
to make sure I'm really getting into the
root and base of the lash that is
obviously where we want the most color
and most dimension to make the lashes
look more defined and give them more
volume and then I'm just going to
lightly sketch in a line when we get to
the outer corner I'm pulling that liner
up a little bit not really a fall on
away just to give her more dimension and
to kind of lift her eyes up I'm next to
take the tiny pocket brush that actually
comes aware that the southland palette
and all the anasazi palettes and dip
into the shade rustic and just lightly
buff this right alongside her lower
lashline no matter what I shadow look
I'm going for I think it is really
really important to balance out the top
lid to the bottom lid my mom does
however have
small eyes so I'm just using a really
really light wash the color to add a
little bit of dimension but to not close
them up because that is obviously not we
want I'm next indigo to the pretty
vulgar nude liner pencil
I love the formulation of this and like
I said my mom does have smaller eyes so
using a white earned nude in the
Waterland is gonna really open them up
and just make them a pop she also has
beautiful bluish green eyes thanks for
passing that on to me love my Shea Brown
I thought I have going on but it's
really gonna make him cough okay so that
is actually I've said a look I'll
complete like my mom was saying her
normal makeup takes her five minutes
this is just a little bit more of a
spicy situation to just brighten up her
makeup routine a little bit we literally
did this eye look and I think three or
four eyeshadow brushes but definitely
could have been achieved with a lot less
if you're just an everyday eye makeup
wear and I think this look is beautiful
and just makes her eyes very much pop so
our next step to make our eyes pop even
more it's gonna be lashing our necks to
have my mom curl her own eyelashes how
using just a regular what are you doing
if you're like my mom and you don't
really have a lot of lashes thanks dad
for giving me these ones it's really
important to curl your lashes and use a
really good mascara to provide a volume
and more dimension and attention to the
eyes for mascara today I'm gonna use the
brand new benefit bad gal bang mascara
this one is really really good and I
like the formula a lot and is double
luminizing mascara we're just gonna be
perfect for people like my mom if you
have small eyelashes I'm once again
holding my mom's eyelid up to get
maximum access to her lashes and I'm
starting right at the base of the lash
and then just wiggling it upwards make
sure all the lashes are nice and coated
and black I'm gonna pop on a pair of
false lashes today have you ever
actually worn fake lashes before never
oh my god are they comfortable to wear
it depends on as you move on correctly
they definitely are and I'm gonna be
really careful to glue them on and
definitely trim them to your lashes I
really like the style because they are
definitely wispy so they're not gonna be
too dramatic and they get longer on the
outer edge so it's gonna provide a nice
shape to my mom's eye before actually
gluing this on I'm going to go ahead and
I'm going to place it on my mom's eyelid
it just with the sticky material that
comes in the
look down for me I'm going to kind of
measure it to her I like I say my mom
does have a very very small eyelids oh
yes we have to cut a lot off today it's
important to cut your lashes so they
flatter your eye shape and the best way
possible and also don't poke you and
come off all day long
Wow look so pretty it's beautiful how
does it feel
I think maybe I could get used to it
it's gonna be a while it feels heavy
heavy yeah yeah I can see like there's
something welcome to my world I blink a
lot to begin with so is that where I get
my blinking from everybody always come
inside videos saying you blink way too
much why do you always blanket I'm like
I have no idea yeah sorry I do it blink
I didn't okay sir so you can stop
complaining and now go comment on her
Instagram and go harass her for the
blinking it's all your involved thank
you I gave you some good things too but
alright sister so that is one eye all
complete we're gonna go and do the other
off-camera just to say sometime probably
doing a whole lot of blinking while her
at it and we'll be right back to finish
off the rest of the look alright guys
we're back with both eyes all complete
let's go ahead and finish up the rest of
this sister Chrystie clam and makeover
today the first thing we have to do is
wipe away this bake because it has been
sitting here for quite a long time now
and we definitely do not want it to get
too baked she's gonna be burnt to the
crust from the oven very very shortly
don't forget to brush off my thanks for
this Team 5 head up in here after
brushing out the powder I'm gonna
lightly gave her a spritz of the mac
fix+
just to kind of melt everything into her
skin so nothing looks really really
cakey and textured and of course we have
our sister fan we're gonna give her a
nice dry off okay we have one question
from sister char and C says what is mama
Charles as a proudest moment of James
would have to be when you graduated high
school early you were working part-time
and taking very hard classes still doing
YouTube videos and makeup looks till
1:00 2:00 in the morning and getting up
and going to school and taking driver's
ed and you graduated with an ear
perfect average on top of all that on
your plate yeah so that was that was a
pretty proud moment thanks mom
I remember having so many arguments with
our family about me graduating early and
wanting to move out to California and
you guys are just like no it's not
happening like this is just a hobby
you're gonna get over this which I don't
blame them for because when I was
younger I would always do something do
it for like a month
and then get bored and move on so I
honestly I'm still surprised to the say
that I still am like loving makeup and
I'm so so passionate about it but I knew
I wanted to do this and it literally
took me going to the guidance
counselor's office without my parents
knowing and setting up like my credits
to graduate early and then me going home
once it was all finalized and saying hey
I'm graduating know the story I'm
graduating next week yeah yes but I knew
I needed to get it done and there was so
many arguments about it and nothing was
moving and so I took initiative into my
own hands
imagine but it paid off it worked out
the way it was supposed to but most
people who want to be quote-unquote rich
and famous it doesn't happen it's a
dream which is great to have dreams but
you have to have option B because it
doesn't usually happen for most people
and you had an almost perfect average so
I assumed you were gonna go to college
yeah I know and it worked out again the
way it was supposed to but I had a hard
time next we're gonna be went to sister
Christie lepida doodahs what she
definitely needs to have it to find but
they are a little naked aren't they
usually wear any kind of lip color
really never you know I said when I go
out maybe if mom and dad have a date or
something date night but on a daily on a
daily basis no I
okay so it's a special occasion my
lashes going I gotta have something okay
sort of start by over lighting them
using the Mac Baldy Barrett lip pencil I
definitely want to overlay them a little
bit to give them a little bit more
volume a little bit more so you over
line them with the pencil yeah okay
I'm gonna finish them off by filing the
remove the Oprah look and lipstick in
the shade of the sow hallo this is my
all-time favorite and you can use Coe
James for 10 percent 30 Coe James for 30
percent off there you go get that
bargain sisters so the last of our
makeup routine today is gonna be our
setting spray so this makeup can last
all day long and so Christie can have
all the boys shaking at Hollywood
Boulevard while she is here here in LA
so I'm gonna give her a good spritz and
we have one final question as well from
sister Kingsley and way to end off the
video and that is how has James of
change on life wow I've learned from
James with all this going on to for
myself to be more confident I'm 51 and
I'm I don't think I'm as confident as
you are and you're only 18 so I'm trying
to learn from you that it's okay to be
yourself and be proud of who you are and
what you are and what you look like and
your flaws and everything that comes
along with it and the mistakes people
make everybody makes them and just
embrace them learn from them
so I'm actually becoming a better person
because of you Oh sounds small well
thank you for the past all right sisters
and this is the gland formation on my
amazing mother all complete how do you
feel I feel beautiful
I feel 20 years younger really I do oh
so now you just have to move back home
so you can grab me no not happening
sorry I'll be the most fun not going
back hey if you guys enjoyed this video
today please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below how many do you
think we should try to get for this
video 200,000 okay so sure isn't you
heard the woman where you can do it I
know you guys got this also if you have
not already missions with that big red
subscribe button down below
conquer the sisterhood we would love to
have you in the family if you'd like to
follow me on my makeup dirty you could
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes type
stuff is James Charles no extra ask
after Charles if you like to follow my
mom on Instagram you can follow her at
Christie B BAE 19 alpha her links down
below
she literally coming back
two sisters all the time so you ever
want to talk to anybody in the trials
family and I up miss your comment go
comment on her Instagram because she'll
probably write back to them like 30
seconds that's all she does all day long
that's not yeah and if you enjoyed
learning a little bit more about James
when he was a kid my sister and I my
real sister who teamed up and we've
worked on a little project James Charles
born to break boundaries hashtag not
sponsored check it out on amazon.com
there's some cute stories and adorable
pics this sick sister shot it goes to
sister Ariana thank you so much JT for
always followed a good supporter you
know I love you so so so much and if you
would like to do the next video since
your shout out makes it always retweet a
video link so they go live on Twitter
alright guys thank you so much for
watching this video today a much love
from me and my amazing mother and we
will see you in the next one
[Music]