hi sister James Charles here welcome
back to my youtube channel as you guys
can see I have a very very special and
iconic guest with me with column attic
legends of YouTube are finally sitting
down together for a video good Lord here
we go we have filmed this video this
collab this makeup look three times like
so many times this is number three we
finally got it done the microphone is
finally on and connected the SD card is
finally there and not full we're finally
together the wings are finally
unemployed the eye shadow is looking
good it is a little bit of a miracle
because we literally I kid you not
almost kill each other during this video
you guys are literally going to witness
me antara live like a genuine like the
way you fight with your best friend we
like how do not fight like mid filming
this video it was so much my footage not
like dad ass about so I need to know
your guys like best friends if you can
fight their collab and still like any
new YouTube friendship whatever like
literally the first time James and I
film together we're like oh my god hi
babe like you're so cute like I'm so
excited to film and buy like this
clobber like okay [ __ ] like do the
weighing like stop talking it's not
moving if you move over cause like I'm
gonna stab you with this like it's been
a quiet a long ride but I have a great
time filming with my best friends in the
entire world if you guys ever seen how
to created this bronzy Chloe look over
on sister Tana made her makeup look good
for once because lord knows she could
not do it herself
make sure you keep on watching I'm gonna
start with our priming it sister Candace
a season to benefit Trevor I'm gonna
complain for Janus foundation today I'm
gonna use the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD
foundation check in the shader y 225 I
just love a good hard stick on my face
don't we all it's not a pale legend
Casper's angry not hit me hit me yeah
hit me do like that hit me you're
beating the [ __ ] out of me Zane you
deserve a courteous
sanitary legends as he beats me with his
double
we started going to fix the lack of
sleep the tena gets on a daily basis
because she goes to bed at 4 a.m. every
single morning and affects the mascara
stains that are also still on her eyes
I'm going to use the tarp shape tape in
the shade of light what are you doing
yeah his forehead wrinkles when I'm only
18 and look like I'm 30 come through my
god I'm so sorry guys James and I kissed
at Coachella why the group I asked
myself listen every reason the shade and
light palette to contort anaphase okay
when all the drama channel shade us but
then we bring lights
[Music]
tannaz cheekbones using my morphe am 405
brush a contour so those of you guys who
don't know this is me antennas third
time sitting down to film a video
together we fail every number three
literally the third time but I'm so
happy we didn't upload our first video
together you know it was literally like
a tragic like tinder date when we just
met like oh my god honestly yeah it
wasn't like a bad video but now we're
like now we hate each other so I think
it's just way better just a 17 year old
with some blending brushes 18 now did
you really just change it to like 18
yeah well why don't why don't you just
change your whole bio there's like a new
sentence I like that Wow so we're gonna
go to her second rhinoplasty losing the
shade of my palate once again I'm s
the 207 bras I was clock my favorite
sentence James Charles has ever said to
me and our entire friendship is my
facetune is normally unlockable oh yeah
almost I got my selfie that everybody
called World War I feel like everybody
it like some time in their career has I
feel like baking the nose contour is
like a absolutely necessary style even
what I don't like big my face like I
still will be aware those contour I
don't convert my nose we can tell huh
don't that's it you're gonna take it off
god forbid I have a bodily function I'm
gonna use my Anasazi eyebrows in the
shade medium brown to do tennis bras
tell me what I do wrong with my makeup
on a day-to-day basis roast myself your
eyelashes always look awful the fact is
I can pull that out of him and he said
it was it close like you knew what's
coming if you could ship me with one
person during social media who would you
should be with I didn't really can't
think of anybody like funny enough that
I like compliment you as well and be
like do your share not a brow eyebrow
we're gonna clean her up using some more
apparent tape tape concealer yeah this
is not ow there's nothing to pop up your
balls that hurt three like how do you
feel where's the milk telling a video
how do you feel oh look a phase Tara
it's so red now because of all these
pimples that you just pop that did not
even exist in the first no we're done
little sister oh that you weren't LA at
all that I was an LA like every time we
meet something like a youtuber you go to
flower with a millionaire
we can't buddy just post me to my earth
just got some green Tebow about I'll put
your shoes on the carpet unless they're
Fendi okay sit down to film my
videographer will be here in time and I
walk in and James Charles is just like
eating like dominoes on the couch like
being like a normal human being you
don't get me in that about [ __ ] with
it that's why your friends when I first
met you I was annoyed because you are
like three hours late for filming
nothing no nothing has changed I mean
but I must have redeemable qualities
because here we are being friends no boo
social-climbing oh oh oh my god every
time we hang out everyone always says
we're social-climbing
literally how stena haha literally
neither one of us are socially both of
us are perfectly fine I mean you're the
last four means me hands down so you
give me are you high that boring know
speaking of memes oh my god
I made a grinder count and my count
loaded not deleted because they thought
I was being a catfish little like it was
and some guy like literally message mean
you know I could also block me he said
wow I've always wanted to [ __ ] a medium
whose the messiest person we know you do
you can't like lately like just like
robbed all higher knows font or yeah you
know I didn't look at where right there
[Music]
really we're sisters that's a really
rich anise acid ever using the morphe
35o palette you can use code James about
10% off your purchase we're going to do
something very very good Tana bird what
are you doing doing great Anna person a
like orange and very bronzy and like
metallicky i think for like a pop on the
ladder jackal is shaking their Jack ridl
is actually just line she just lit a
candle and is taking a bubble bath
something gross that we both do pop
pimples yeah religiously burp and blow
it into each other's mouths will Tana
ever show up at James house at a decent
time no how many times can we say sister
at the same exact time we're not gonna
do that
will this video even happen great
question so that's the funny isn't a
little we've got together but I can't
honestly we can't even save on camera
you're not thinking of the same moment
I'm thinking oh you're talking about
I'm gonna use the new Elliot Smosh
architect slam liner to do the tennis
liner I just got this in the mail today
I'm tired for the first time and this is
it
so good you can lick it the literally it
most precise point ever so I'm gonna try
it out today going in a half that's a
good way Buffalo Wild Wings is on a
stretcher for the bottom laughs I don't
going back into the original orange
shade at my r39 breast of I'm just gonna
have to start to smoke it out a little
bit this is so much better than the
first time makeup wise yeah that's crazy
dogs are ever in our favor Tara not a
lily lash money Emmy Tampa Florida is
angry for long just a note and I'm gonna
use the Lilly logis Miami's tennis loss
or a literally like the worst thing stop
copying everything I'm saying I'll only
be worsening in the entire world and
recently lost somewhere together I
entered
- these lashes and hopefully they have
changed her life before the better they
really did the difference is though is
that I'm a cheap easily accessible [ __ ]
and these are like some order online
excuse coach James ass lashes and I need
some like Ulta in five minutes yeah for
Tudor that's true a lot cuter cold yep
now we're gonna be using Too Faced
better than sex mascara you've come
Ching that check out Hannah mojo not
dramatic why don't we get a lot of hurt
until we sit down kind of a cute
together it's literally so annoying like
in real life we're like so happy and
every time he's it doesn't go the job
really it's straight hostility instant
instead yeah that's great that is what I
all complete thank God for hours later
we're gonna do the other one off-camera
now before we literally kill each other
he'll be right back now that we are all
done with the eyes thank God it's only
been eight years eight years even who
was the Oprah highlighter in the shade
up Rodeo Drive
so I just got the last 10 minutes
literally searching through a drawer of
hundreds of mac lipsticks to find this
and the entire time James using you
don't gonna find it we're gonna play the
MacBook Philip second shade honey love
to tannaz lips to finish off this look
and video once and for all
oh my god and our last final step is
gonna be to spritz Tanis face uses me
more feed prep and sat setting spray
code James alright guys and this is the
completed look over on sister Tana we've
been filming for far too long now we
bought in like three actual fights mid
filming like yelling at each other like
done but we continued through it and
that's when you know you're that's right
oh my god the messiest thing I'm so
happy this is done and we can go back to
being friends and like each other so I
don't know why we get along so well
we're like just a you know as soon as
they sit in front of the camera we
literally go so hostile like so awesome
he's like stop moving I'm not moving
James like it's so bad enjoyed us
together
you have better this has been the third
attempt yet please give this video a big
thumbs up please hit that subscribe
button down below if you have not
already I most two videos a week on
Mondays and products that I'd love to
have you join the sisterhood if you like
to follow me on makeup journey can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter they
are both just James Charles and my
snapchat and you never were behind scene
size-up our James Charles the doctor
asked dr. Charles and I'm basically just
chopped liver don't check me out it's so
that was coming next if you put a bowl
Ted on anything Ted I mojo on everything
go check out our collab that we just
filmed below I don't know what it's
gonna be yet but if I already have no
idea what we're doing yeah that's tough
a pocket my that's amazing that the
neighbor honestly I think at this point
probably I know you guys think you saw
watching every we'll see you in the next
one
good
[Music]