hi sisters jr. and welcome back to our
YouTube channel as you can see today
I've run into very special guests
my boyfriend's the dog twins we're
finally here this club has been so long
awaited after all my thirsty and serum
common side of Ethan a graceless wake up
for Halloween I was so excited they
turned out amazing if you guys saw on
our Instagram but now they invited me
back over by some miracle and today hey
I did Ethan in Grayson's makeup they'd
ever been cleaned up before get glammed
down but we loved it we did we loved a
Glen make a true sister twin Mako one of
those so thank you so much you do that
you're - yeah I'm gonna do the year okay
so I have all my favorite products my
everyday makeup routine in front of both
Ethan and Grayson I have duplicates of
all of them except for a few items which
are in the middle and you guys will have
to share I'm gonna give even this had my
face and Grayson this side of my face
and they're gonna do their back wheel of
a race we do love a right side they're
gonna do the best to glam me up the
closest to what they think I normally
look like this is a competition - so at
the end you guys we love the competition
love one comment who you think did the
better half of the face yeah so so just
kind of an earring down iron at the
bottom I'm coming my name is I think I
need it I think I need a sister hoodie
I'm not gonna perform as well in this
black shirt okay true well luckily I
can't prepare we love that sister honey
we do little good promo okay ready go I
got go yeah okay so I start with this is
called foundation oh my god we love a
smart man we love a smart man Tony
you're must like low sorry I just
started go well I'm actually doing this
is way better than I thought I would
again on your lips but I think you just
cover that up yeah I'll be fine
out of the two of you guys if you were
taking us right now being completely
unbiased and putting your egos aside
like what I do you think it's gonna look
right even has no idea what he's doing
with or no chill Kristin isn't even a
working camera and as we learned in our
video that is true he got him there and
he also can't read yes when I read the
products I'll know where they go he's
where they go the lipstick was one of
the last steps I believe I'm confused as
to what to do next
I think this lash oh wait that goes at
last also brow brows next boom pencil up
sure the birds make it look good it does
look good all right that looks like a
good eyebrow and they need to squeeze a
little I do it I do oh don't you oh
let's not move you need to relax James
okay this eyelash is the plan perfectly
I'm gonna be so mad huh all right
Grayson the magic is in the tweezers
we love highlight right sisters have you
ever wants to make up cereal you have
not perfect
choose the street yeah I'm going for
that abstract eyebrow of course you are
I'm gonna bronze the [ __ ] out of you or
not all right now it's time for me to
curl your eyelash
oh my god grace then no straight from
grace head oh wow what if it comes up
better than you so you lose your job
Carver girls gonna call it then and
Grayson instead okay I want to know
since this whole friendship has came out
of me leaving throws comments on her
guy's Instagram page I wanna know and I
want you to both to think long and hard
when was the first time you either heard
of me or saw me commenting something
thirsty on your Instagram or Twitter it
was something with Daddy and yeah I saw
it on Twitter he loves it I love it oh
you actually feel really good we love
Italy reason why are you doing you're
getting dust all over me Grayson you're
coming up to my side gotta get the ear
close this James well you're looking
good all thanks to me James I think
you're gonna add me to your makeup from
now on I think I probably show it
honestly I'm actually proud of myself
this is the best I've ever done with any
type of makeup Oh what's the oh wow that
is highlight can you sing you the whole
thing oh and do some lip liner you're
gonna fill it in or no okay it's just
some drawing action here if you're
drawing a deck I swear to god no no no
no stop no look II suddenly I regret all
the Instagram comment
this is easier than I thought oh yeah
I'm gonna take over your channel I think
you're saying honestly do little hombre
action Oh we'd love a girl bright dewy
me jo
that is a great hombre not even a good
one a great one a great one
I'm so bad at makeup well if you look at
without it I'm actually I'm great I'm a
great abstract makeup artist I'm gonna
chisel this job that's what I'm going
for
Picasso is shaking I need the Dolan
jawline - you use them I can't feel that
you flew my eyelid together today really
yeah oh that's what you want right big
lips yeah okay cool oh there's colors in
it okay Kristen's are really going to
monarch come on it feels good it kind of
done find a point and I'm gonna do a
winged eyelash because that eyelash dang
I murdered that up setting spray wait no
this is not I'm setting it this is the
fight part I'm setting it first no no I
need a center it might seem to mess up
you wait oh my boyfriend's are fighting
over there actually is a little bit more
room for blending
oh my we're done we're finished three
two one
okay go oh my god I did it good wait
both of you look like the lashes
literally perfectly
really yes we love a beauty guru I
really wanted to exaggerate the
natural-born facial features that you
had huh so I took your cheekbone and I
put some highlighter on it
so you let me get a little shave tape
concealer on your highlighter today what
is this concealer usually goes under
your eyes uh but when I was standing
okay so yeah makeup is definitely very
expensive so you're going for the budget
options maybe I was yeah one tonic for
many definitely how much I got done with
eyeliner I contoured your nose with some
eyeliner hi
we're going for the snaps look today yes
I wanted to make you look like a very
handsome you look beautiful get out of
here oh if he knows the ear I also
wanted to define a little bit more dark
don't be an era stop throwing at me and
then the little guy there's a guy on
your face yeah oh my god I didn't see
him there what's his name he just goes
by sister okay perfect I love that about
him uh-huh the lips I just try to do lip
liner I think you mess it up all right
enough of the [ __ ] the moment you've
all been waiting for
let's hop over to the left side this is
glam makeup at its best finest and
here's the rundown you know with the
highlighter I kind of took it all over
the face and I added it to the little
ear flap over here too because he needs
to look it doesn't look great
those fries I mean yours don't yeah my
contoured here big lips they're cool
yeah James likes big lips I knew that
about him they look big because I you
know took the lipstick and I went
outside his lips that is a key what is
that called lip plumping yeah sure
hey look at my eye shadow compared to
Ethan's this is full season collective
eyeshadow - you there - just you know
yours is like lettuce vibrant it is
bringing and it is amazing and I beg to
disown Ingres know you think I'm a bit
of makeup artist I beg today no no I
like me yeah please I'm attacking
I killed that wing and I love that about
me I just really got being TT I mean oh
so how do you vote who do you think did
better
I mean I just love both you guys so much
I think that they'll be it's not about
it's about the makeup well let's put it
this way if inside I would feel more
confident walking out with but I started
makeup before they are and you have to
appreciate the art you I feel like grace
inside your art sucks no that's rude
this is my soul
and James's face yeah toda TECA
I killed it regardless definitely leave
I love that about me gently leave us a
comment don't tell me which makeup sign
you guys think was better sister Ethan
my name is Ethan ETH eight and that's
how you spell a why so yeah it's kind of
a longer name that's probably lose
anything will win cuz you only get two
legs more followers oh don't go there
hey bigger interest in this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below
lots even gets to do to a hundred
thousand thumbs up and now your sisters
you can do it you can do it and
subscribe down below click the post
notifications I'm doing something so
crazy because of these two I'm every
single day this week make sure to stay
tuned for tomorrow's video and the next
phase of the MX's video and the next
day's video go check out the back land
that's not very sorry check out through
to the Ethan Christian channel or I did
Derek Lam makeover he does our makeup
glam style games and games
go get'em us and we look we're gonna
wait wait
they'll have to see if you guys like to
follow me on your makeup turned you can
follow me on instagram and twitter
they're both the same charles my
snapchat for behind see size up is same
shoulder charles down yeah you do mine
leave it if you like to follow Chris and
Dolan on is social media turn you could
vote on Instagram and Twitter there miss
Grayson Dolan and his sash is also
Graceland oh my holy you sound like one
of those guys who does the things I did
hey going was going to an archer tobacco
you with the sister sweater to the
background Ethan Dolan on his social
media journey home in signature bones
just Ethan Dolan ended I saw Sasha from
behind see if this happens Ethan Dolan
becsher oh alright sisters thank you so
much for watching we love you so much
and we will see you in next one
[Music]