hi sisters James Charles here welcome
back to my youtube channel today I'm
here with a very very special guest a
legend a queen of season 9 of RuPaul's
Drag Race
so hurry I'm going to learn a bit longer
to live for a very long time it's around
it's not a minute a hot minute for sure
the rest here a long time ago this seems
like those season line speculations were
coming out and I was like hi season I
was not going to get any hints but I did
I knew that this [ __ ] was gonna be here
and she's gonna kill it and now that's
right here we want to sit down so I had
thought my translations for you guys I
am sober and excited Farrah's let me put
in her face on to lie are you guys ready
to see James Charles fair arrived and
you want to see the completed look make
sure you would keep on watching so you
just went ahead and be covered by a
brows and sideburns off camera a very
very lengthy process for like all drag
queens mascara whereas her shaved off so
first things first we're actually gonna
color correct the brows and the
sideburns is it actually the cover FX in
the color brick it's amazing I've gone
through like five of these I wanted to
shave this morning I might be right back
I think to always see where I hate
before it when I wake up all because
mine is notorious for run straight
through makeup will wear - since we're
covering its brows were actually don't
want to really like high coverage
foundation stick this is the prime on TV
paint stick
[Music]
so right now America's using a Beauty
Blender and blending out this crazy and
awesome
brown and cyber color we have AIT's a
really light foundation for this just
because it's the only penalty it means
that I have we needed that full coverage
to cover up everything because sister
got a lot of hair up in here
perfect okay so now that the song
Foundation and today we're he's the
information that I have never used
before the Giorgio Armani luminous so
much I'm so excited to watch so before
we get any comments as well I did get a
spray tan because I'm going on a very
exciting a beach vacation in a few days
you guys watching this now will have
already seen it because the city will
not be enough for a few weeks by spray
tan and we have this Melanie Mills of
Hollywood Colima body stuff oh my god my
mind is very vague like radiating from
my family it's so beautiful it's like a
bronze guys so that is why my foundation
is a little bit darker to say these days
open up my face so I don't any comments
about it about take the face to the neck
like you're supposed to there anything
there so X are what we're going to go
into another foundation we're so crazy
you know there's some people that mix
like three or four foundations like good
luck I've never made some Asia this is
the Marc Jacobs remarkable it's no more
what if it covers a function like no
one's business I think that's actually
enough to cover the whole entire face if
your games I made it in the light
coverage like up straight is a model of
the brows well yeah
[Music]
everybody actually mixed a little
mixture of like midnight powers
my treat banana powder and then some
Laura Mercier powder a little bit of
like white powder and a little bit of
chestnut powers to kind of like a little
bit some colors yeah that's a trick that
I picked up early on my drag career
so tell me what was like to have a short
race it was so weird
honestly like yeah I'm love me too so
when we when I walk to the workroom I
was like I had I was going to say like
hi mom or something funny like that but
all I could think was like oh my god
like this is what it looks like it felt
like I jumped into my TV screaming can
you imagine James for every season
season to be on the show okay guys now
I'm gonna go on my next step and I told
James I was gonna do this he like
freaked out he was like what the heck
that's so against the world I'm very
very nervous so basically a baritone
that she's going to be putting my
concealer on even though she already
powder with other eyes yeah if you are a
fan our beauty gurus and youtuber people
you know this is like rule number one
that you never ever apply well they
never said not to I think they
definitely have said that I've never
seen someone say that's a cool number
one you don't put up the codes are
creative schoolboy but we do it all the
time we glue our brows down oh well I
guess so this is the tarte maracuja
maracuja never when I will say that I've
been using this for years
maracuja creaseless concealer I swear by
it I know they have a new concealer out
that everyone's raving about I have a
try
I'm sure all of it if I love this one so
much but here we go
so how long have you been in Jaguar I've
been doing drag for five years now yeah
I didn't say Gaston until last year
January 1st Oh God originally from Texas
one race in Houston Texas girl I'm gonna
take steroids were Texas born and raised
you know about that but I got my track
started in Austin Texas when I was 18 I
had a fake ID this can clean up scamming
you're gonna shock right now
whoa do you sketch out your creases
before you put on your shot or anything
all that I was sketching Outrigger
eyebrows gonna go brow highlight where
every well yeah yeah that's so cool I
would do across person that's it
everyone is like I um browser like never
liked twins they're always like sisters
okay we here on the day of trial Channel
we love sister heaven itself I'm gonna
make a little mixture again where I'm
gonna actually do a little bit of our
original mixture but then put more of
the laura mercier and a queen of mixing
I like to start with little tiny amounts
the powder first and then obviously
build cuz I feel like if you put too
much on too fast it'll crack and be
campion like ruin your day
so pharoah's you do a little sugar pill
talk about my bra
you have girls are still very good job
and very very hairy because a lot girls
up in here a lot of rails we want like
the best coverage possible so this
shadow is doing a fantastic job of
adding a little bit extra white hasn't
there truly well how they end up using
this one here I led to because I love a
white car crazy
[Music]
this is in the color pinch of peach I
just love a pink blush honestly truly I
don't like orange questions I don't like
dark Brook I just pink blush it all I
wear
see I never wash period ever so now
we're going to go onto my honest I'll
see where pills locate and glean we're
gonna highlight him before we bake so
Ferris heli is obviously like while
she's no curtains are pictures Oh every
single [ __ ] time but I wanted to oh
good thing I'll have to talk to my
hospital because I just lost my vision
so we went in a starburst first and now
we're gonna go in with crushed okay okay
guys we're gonna go to XML we're going
to my favorite eyeshadow of all time if
you are actually a follower of mine you
know that this is like my favorite
eyeshadow I just give it a shot up all
the time it's sugar pill dolly pop
you're so strong I admire you so much
for being strong through it thank you I
had some paid during the myspace days
and like almost killed me but we're
leaving your back dude I have a very
very thick skin I just try to think like
stay positive and something and Chennai
[ __ ] out may be a stupid mistake that
people get mad or I like to sit back and
just take a look at the situation in see
like Heineken or ever thought of myself
as a person I know that's the only thing
you come to kind of see I approach it
there's no time machines yet and you
can't take things back so at that point
like it was can you do besides to learn
it just better yourself in the situation
you know well yeah and a lot of people
that want to criticize you right now
honestly if they people dug up what they
said on Twitter they're 12 years old
everyone is problematic looking like
everybody has that things
they would not publicize it's just my
rock your type
yeah like I wasn't on the hot end
tonight because I said it and they were
stupid they were literally ignorant but
I think nobody should really be like
judged on what on things that they said
so long like anything can happen they
can change somebody like so they can
have an ATAR oh that could be you know
what I'm mostly a different person here
last night circulate nobody should be
judged on what they selling even like a
year ago alone four years ago the fact
that anything was that at four years ago
is not an excuse because it doesn't make
it okay but I feel like nobody should be
judged for what they said so longer
because people change and trust me a lot
of people agree with you on that know
that we finished the liner let's go in
and cut that crease a little bit of the
black eyeshadow yeah we had to move
positions because I could not get over
there and do it at the same all it was
really hard cut ready to cut and we're
going to continue on a limited audience
hopefully with just to get supplies
other girls makeup
I mean honestly that's why I did it no
rightly I would assume so we're gonna
actually go into some jeffree star drug
lord I like to do this with like the
little white liner right there I've
never actually tried this on the lip but
I love it as a liner
I got this time for brows guy I feel
like so nervous because you're like the
king of promise
give me parables that's what you're
talking about on Twitter all the time
like I wish that maybe just one time in
my life that's symmetrical eyebrow I
feel like I do Drive I can like to slay
the face and the conjurer eyes
I think that's harsh muted brows really
I don't like it because my brows I'm so
used to like the very very straight like
you know arch type of shape like so it's
very very hard don't care if I did this
off camera because it's like they can't
answer your sister I know but they they
can make it rhetorically answer and you
watch it because it okay we're gonna
we're gonna do the other about
off-camera also at 17 hours the other
brow like I said my brows are never
symmetrical they're never even give me a
break I'm not like missing just be
laughs okay they might look a little
better after I clean it up of this so
this next step I do I take a kind of
like a taupe color eyeshadow by Thomas
Aussie Beverly Hills this is a ash brown
I always like to take this and this is
kind of what I put the hairs in where I
think that it's like first I like to
line the bottom okay we're going in with
this um benefit roller lash that's
what's so cool about these particular
hairs is the thing
everybody like doll like a little or
like a little deer or something you know
like oh yeah
so when I always like to be afraid that
the lashes on is like go over one last
time with the liquid liner because
especially with like a white eyeshadow
it'll always fall and if I'm feeling
really extra I'll bring the liquid liner
to the club you're like crazy I'm so so
well I like why would they make them all
bring so much with me I always have my
Beauty Blender at much looser stylish
royal so it wouldn't be a pheromone look
without the little individual bottom
lashes so we see we go back in with that
amazing industrial house of lashes
lashes and I'm really obsessed with and
we're gonna put the little rhinestones
as well with this oh my god hang on it
has my favorite part so today I did up
tutorial few minutes ago using the
crystals under the eyes a pretty little
detail they have to be Swarovski so good
it's a really nice distraction from the
leg up uneven brow is that you and I go
to Brian huh
look that looks nice oh just cuts the
light so nicely are you ready for your
lip stains I'm sorry this is my favorite
lip liner grandma huh
they just sent me a huge pocket so
anyway
so how to all my kitchen table over
there are your lessons like we need to
use this tonight sadly there's this work
it's called edge to edge it's like a
pinky
kind of nude now that we've mined the
lips of s dad for him and I are going to
go on with him actually went favorite
pink nude it is I'm Geoffrey starved all
parts
[Music]
or her
alright guys this is the makeup off
complete we're going to have them some
earrings and awake and then an outfit as
well and it'll be right back
[Music]
[ __ ] that walk
all right I guess we just thrown it
these earrings and this wedding I'm
living through this like old Hollywood
at the Maryland I'm gonna hug style look
me up going on
Thank You girlfriend [ __ ] ass laying
my face I just look at everything
yourself up come on you've been
additionally fair yes okay guys if
you're though this video don't forget to
give them a thumbs up down below and
scribe if you have not already I post
videos every singly I would love to have
you join it The Sisterhood if you'd like
to follow me on my makeup journey we
follow my instagram and twitter they
both just change Charles and my snap for
more behind the scenes saves up is James
Charleston extra path dr. Charles if you
want to call Farah moment Legendre Queen
have season not beautiful aren't
everything my username is theorized on
Instagram and Twitter and I should have
my youtube channel up by the time that
this holiday that is so exciting I'm
kind of like get her to enjoy music but
really there's a huge lack of amazing
Queens and the YouTube community I would
love to learn a ton from her I already
have learned some through today so I'm
sure you guys will definitely check out
her channel as well so please don't
click the link down below and subscribe
tell her sister James aside you know
thank you so much for having me today
thank you so daughter are not wait to
see you slay every single episode yeah
make sure you guys check out RuPaul's
Drag Race every single Friday on vh1
thank you girl alright guys thank you so
freakin much for watching I will see you
next week with a new video bye sisters
[Music]
[Applause]