hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I have something not gonna
lie a little bit less like implant I had
a concept for today's video all ready to
go ready to film I sat down and after a
further thought quickly realized it was
not the best idea since I'm an awful
youtuber and could not think of any
better ideas I'm gonna be reading this
makeup book that I did almost two years
ago now to date it is still when my
all-time favorite makeup books that I've
ever done but I feel like my skill level
has grown so much and I think I could
really improve this and make this a
really really awesome look not only mine
awful youtuber but I'm also unoriginal
and since last week's video was
recreating your guys's makeup looks and
today's videos recreate mine I can't use
recreating and my title twice in a row
that'll be really really stupid so I'm
gonna make this video also a Q&A so I
can make the tomato something different
love that I've always been K I've been
wanting to recreate this look for a
super super long time now but creative
looks don't really do that well on my
channel so this is the perfect excuse
for me to do a creative makeup look and
you guys have to watch got you good
without further ado I already have my
base already on let's go ahead and get
started with some questions and some
cool lightning bolt makeups I'm gonna
start this book off by popping off my
eyelashes clearly I'm going to be doing
a lot of work on my face and eyes today
so cannot have any of Miami's
distracting me from that process oh my
god I just lost that no we're gonna be
founder so shut off this lips today I'm
gonna lay down just a light base coat
using my morphe at 35 P palette and
using the blue shade or right in this
corner the first question today comes
from sister Alessandra and she says
pineapple on pizza yes or no absolutely
not I literally think pineapple pizza is
one of the grossest
combinations ever like who wants their
pizza to be sweet I know I certainly
know I personally am a pepperoni type
sister I love me some good pepperoni
pineapple absolutely not I'm your ask do
you want to stay in LA or do you plan to
move somewhere else in the future that's
actually a really good question that I
personally ask myself all the time
thinking in terms of right now I
definitely do plan on staying in LA for
quite a long time I really really like
it here I definitely like love the Sun
the warm weather all my really close
friends are here aside from my
family of course so I really like being
here and my job is here as well I feel
like I'm always getting a lot of work
done as for downtown LA definitely not
I plan on renewing my lease here for one
more year but after this year I'm gonna
save all my money and hopefully be able
to build my own house which is gonna be
such an amazing accomplishment at only
19 years old so fingers crossed that
that works out because that is something
that I'm really really looking forward
to but I guess I really never know what
the future holds like I said for right
now I'm happy but I definitely want to
explore a whole lot more and kind of see
my options and who knows where I'll be
five ten years from now so right now I'm
happy as a Nellie sister but maybe I'm
being and I don't recall one day
couldn't tell ya speaking of traveling
and exploring a new places sister ray
asked would you ever go on tour cuz I
want to meet you so bad that's a great
question sister right I don't know well
I can't believe my nose contour looked
so good today and Here I am packing dark
blue eyeshadow right over top of it and
ruining all the hard work I don't know
what I was gonna say that
katelyn ass if you gotta marry the last
person that you kissed how would you
feel who died Oh awful oh no actually I
think I feel pretty good about that one
yeah I think I'd be okay with that
actually on second thought wrong person
sister Julia oz explain your love life
in one word intense my ass if you could
tell your younger self one thing what
would it be
shut up I really love this natural
everyday glam look that we have going on
right now
ah Briana asked who was telling that you
look up to I think that my answer would
actually be to people and that would be
Jacqueline Hale and nikkietutorials I
remember watching joseline Halen wanting
to literally buy every single product
she ever put on her face because she
looked at that perfect and I were
watching Nicki and it's just really
bringing my true artist out in me I feel
like her looks were always so original
and so creative and I just really love
that about YouTube because do you guys
know that's really what got my start in
the makeup industry to begin with so I
really had to say Jacqueline her nathie
because they've been around for so long
and I think have generally worked so
hard for the platforms that they have
and truly do deserve it and use their
platforms for the best they possibly can
which makes me it really really hot
and makes me happy to call them role
models and also really close friends I'm
just gonna take the darker blue shade
and the darker blush lead to kind of
create some clouds and some more
dimension in the sky
I guess hello Sam asks if you could
change one thing about yourself what
would it be and why and I'd probably
have to say my hairline that's always
the first thing that I change on
facetune I wish it was just like a
little bit lower because sister always
has a lot on his mind he asked if you
could know one thing about your future
right now what would it be and why
good question probably what social media
point that I leave Thursday comments on
is finally gonna give in and marry me
yeah Kaitlyn asked if you were stranded
on a deserted island and you could
choose one youtuber to be sharing it
with you who would you pick and why I
think calling back to a few questions
ago I have to say it's sister Nikki once
again I feel like we'd be able to put
our creative minds together and figure
out some way of like living and
surviving also she's like super tall so
she could probably just reach for all
the coconuts in the tree that looks
pretty what is going on here hello
let me forgot how much I hate it working
a blue eyeshadow and look what I'm doing
cover my entire face with blue eyeshadow
makes me a face tune John asked what do
you think about any drama in the beauty
community I try not to think about the
beauty community Tommy asked what is one
thing you really want to accomplish by
the end of 2018
now in search of this might be a little
bit cliche and it's kind of like a more
vague type of situation rather than like
once is the next thing but I want
everybody at the end of just at 18 to be
able to look back on my year including
myself and just think oh my god how did
he do all of that that is what I want
for my year and I know that sounds
really really cliche but I just want to
get so much time to be working all year
round on so many different projects so
many cool opportunities meeting you guys
working on new works launches working on
new videos like literally everything you
can possibly imagine
I just want to do it I'm gonna do it all
sisters are gonna take over the world
Kayla asked if there was gonna be a
movie made about your life who would you
want to play you oh this is actually a
really really good question
oh you know why I would pick I would
pick sister Jake snatched by Jake on
Instagram who runs on my fan page just
he is literally so cute and I feel like
he's literally like that meaning me we
look alike and he does makeup so he
would definitely be a good sister James
I think I would trust him to play me
even though these are pretty big shoes
to fill
Bibby asked what is your biggest fear
hmm probably a red socialblade just
kidding I am deathly afraid of heights
and snakes
oh and bees and dying yeah all those
things Adrian said quick first all that
comes to mind sing it Oh baby don't say
the Turk with you between my arms
barefoot on the grass listening to our
favorite song when you said you love
dumbest and cheering sweetie I am so
sorry Stephanie asked what's one piece
of advice you have for someone looking
to start a career in the makeup industry
this is a question NTM that I get from
you guys literally all the time and I
think that the best answer I have for
you it would be to do something that
nobody else is doing don't do brown
smokey eyes don't do warm half-cut
creases and if you're gonna do those
favorite looks and that's what you love
that's fine but just find some way to
make your own put your own spin on it
make videos with your personalities
shining through it just do something
that's gonna set yourself apart because
there's a million one people trying to
do the same exact thing and nobody's
gonna make it with the same definitely
all seen a million times trust me on
that it looks like I can barely breathe
Christina asked if you could design your
own escape room what would the theme be
and how intense would you make it if you
guys are part of the sister a snapchat
fan which if you are not go add me right
up here and as a lent time there all
sorts of rants fun activities singing
and of course sister escape rooms you
guys know I do them all the time it is
literally my favorite pastime in the
entire world like if I find an escape
room one day that kills me I'll be dying
very happy as crazy as that sounds but I
do think about this quite often as
bursting as that may seem one thing that
I would love to see in an escape from
would be like a log cabin type of
situation like in the snowy hills or
something and you only have an hour to
escape or else like the abominable
snowman or something comes to get you we
can work on that part of the concept
have really thoughtfully through but you
guys know I definitely have a really
really intense once I think it'd be so
cool to have all different sorts of
rooms but I think the one really cool
aspect of it sense would be in the snow
would be really cool if the room got
colder as the hour progressed and by the
time like the last few minutes are going
and be like freezing cold I don't think
that'd be such a cool out of concept to
add it to the already challenging escape
room let me know what you guys think if
you were to design an escape room what
would it be
leave a comment down below am i bleeding
oh that's a mole I'm gonna try to bring
up some of the darkness and his I up to
the contouring areas and kind of connect
and blend them together to distract from
the poor blending going on in this
region oh that's so pretty
Alex asked Coke or Pepsi Pepsi
hands-down Pepsi is so much better even
though they've had quite the problematic
past so by let me tell you nothing makes
me happier in the entire world than when
I am at a restaurant and someone says
nobody wants a drink and I'm like oh I
want a coke
I let me say coke is still really good -
at at this point it served at most
locations so I just gotten used to
saying coke but nothing makes me happier
than when someone says always Pepsi ok
yes girl yes
Pepsi is more than okay god bless you
thank you so much for that if you like
coke that is okay if you like Pepsi
that's okay as long as you acknowledge
that there is a difference between them
because if you think that they are the
same thing we have a problem Anna said
who was one non beauty youtuber that you
would really love to collab with this
question I think is really really easy I
think my answer hands down would either
be Shane Dawson or jenna Marbles their
content is so funny and they both been
around for so long but continue to make
me laugh every single time they upload a
video I just like they are so creative
and just really like killing the game
I've looked up to them forever I've met
both of them so
yeah definitely love to do a video with
all of them Kay asked when we get more
of the sisters merge I really want to
get the sisters Barbour talking uh yeah
yeah thank you k for always supporting
that means of the world to me I've
actually been getting a lot of questions
about system paralleled in the past a
few days and for those of you guys who
haven't noticed don't really know why
you would this is to prepare website
husband down for the past few weeks this
is apparel was a first-ever polling line
that I've done obviously I have no
experience in that field whatsoever and
I will be open and honest and saying
that it was definitely not the smoothest
processes there were definitely a lot of
problems when I came to like production
and shipping and obviously that's not
something I want to put my name on to so
we just ended the process of switching
companies and just making sure our
production techniques are the best they
can possibly be in order to get you guys
looking at the cutest you possibly can
way way smoother Jen said if for some
reason you couldn't do makeup anymore
what career would you choose oh and
since I know you'd probably say singer
you can't choose that either I mean like
normal nine to five job damn she got me
there I feel like if I wasn't able to do
makeup or sing I probably doing
something involving like numbers and
technology in high school my favorite
subject was actually math which I feel
like it's like breaking the internet kid
law because I feel like every social
media influencers like I hate math I was
so bad at it but I really could probably
be in accounting because that mixes
together like numbers and technology and
math and money which I love or also
stocks because that combines all those
things at plus strategy which you guys
know that I love
probably socks I feel like that'd be fun
Phoenix are us will this be the last
question of the video yes we're done our
sisters and that is this lightning a
recreation look a complete I am so happy
to have this turned on I just feel like
it looks so electric and bright and
beautiful comparing this one to the
original look this one is way way way
better like I said the original photo
was posted in 2016 it's one of the first
looks that I ever did it was right at
the beginning of my makeup career and
you could definitely see how much my
skills have improved since then
obviously they are very very similar
concepts but the contours are definitely
intensified a lot more oh thank god
there's a lot more dimension a lot more
glow a lot more highlights and I'd like
my line work is just a lot cleaner we
added an eye shadow look we have some
lashes on I'm just really really happy
with this turn
and I really hope you guys enjoyed it as
well I also hope you guys enjoyed
learning a little bit more about me and
this Q&A like I said this was definitely
an excuse to do this makeup book today
and I needed something to fill home over
top of that I feel like you guys know
literally everything about me because
I'm so open on snapchat and Twitter but
I'm always happy to answer your guys's
questions if you guys didn't do this
videos today please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below so you
have not already put that little belt
icon so you can notified every time I
upload a brand new video and come join
this sisterhood if you like to follow me
on a makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes I himself its James
Charles the next your ass after Charles
distich sister shadow goes to sister
Morgan thank you so much for always
following in supporting I love you so
much and if you'd like to be the next
video sister shout out make sure Lori's
retweet video link so they go live on
Twitter all right sisters thank you so
much for watching I love you and I will
see you in the next one
[Music]