hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 channel I am literally
so beyond excited to be sitting down to
throwing today's a brand new video I'm
sure you've seen the title we were doing
something that I've wanted to do for the
longest time and something that you guys
have been requesting from me as well for
a very very long time it's gonna be so
much fun but Before we jump into that I
do want to say I do have a few things to
go over in today's video intro before we
actually get started so I'll try to keep
it short and sweet and brief and try to
spice it up with a little bit of editing
so hi sisters first and probably most
importantly I want to say a major major
thank you to guys because a few days ago
this YouTube channel just hit 7 million
its sister subscribers looking back on a
calendar from one year ago today we have
gained 5 million four hundred and
seventy thousand five hundred and sixty
five sisters 7.1 billion I cannot even
begin to explain to you guys how much
you've changed my life in the past two
years I am so grateful for all of you
guys I am so thankful that I get to do
this job every single day and make
people happy and make people laugh and
inspire people all around the world with
my true passion which is makeup and I
cannot even begin it to say thank you
for everything that you guys have done
for me I worst the Rose way that I could
personally say thank you and hug every
single one of you seven million sisters
out there and hopefully one day I'll be
able to meet you guys in person but and
honor of hitting it's such a huge
milestone and an honor of back-to-school
season I do have a very very very
special contest and giveaway coming to
you guys in this video today I want to
give you guys too many details just yet
because it's interest programmed to be
very very long but please watch through
it the entire video and don't forget to
stay tuned until the end to see how you
can enter my at 7 million sister
subscriber giveaway and see how you can
win one of these babies a brand new
MacBook Air and a ton of other cool
prizes I will say that this game boy is
quite a big and beefy one so I do want
to say a major thank you to this video
sponsor for making it possible and that
is quick match quick match is a new
social platform that allows you to
challenge your friends to super fun mini
games you can connect to their current
best friends or meet new friends at
their texting at video chatting or
playing games with them directly my
favorite view on the app by far is
corners if you would like to connect and
challenge with me my game code is a 1 1
4 6 3 7 but good luck I am really really
good no offense
quick matches available to download for
free on both Android and iOS and you can
get it using my link in the description
box down below okay
literally 86 years later now that that
is all on the table and we are ready to
go I'm so pumped tell you guys about
today's app for a new video a few weeks
ago on my youtube channel I uploaded a
video called a makeup artist tries dry
if you have not yet checked it out make
sure to click right up here but
basically I shared with you guys the one
art form that actually got me started
into makeup in the first place which was
not makeup and was drying with charcoal
and one of the top comments that I saw a
lot over and over again on the video is
that instead of drawing with charcoal I
should actually try drawing with makeup
what a lot of you guys may not know is
that that artwork actually already
exists and they're called face charts I
wasn't exactly able to find information
on the origin or invention of face
charts but I do know that they are
popularized by one of the biggest beauty
brands in the entire world known for
their artistry not cosmetics based
charts are basically outlines of faces
printed on a very very special type of
paper for makeup artists are able to
play with different makeup books that
before they actually put them on a model
for the runway because of the fact that
these charts are flat and are basically
a blank canvas there are endless
possibilities of different looks and
designs that people can make and whether
it be for a runway or for Instagram a
lot of Devore artists had actually taken
face sharding to the next level and I've
been able to make careers out of them
milk 14:22 and cons the MUA are two
different artists that come to mind that
had built majority of their following
off the beautiful face charts and a lot
of different influencers like myself
have recreated on they're very different
YouTube channels and Instagram feeds
y'all know me I always got to be a
little bit extra so I got made custom
printed sister Jeff Skiles face hurts
I've never done this before by do you
think it'll be very very fun so without
further ado I have Ollie makeup laid out
here in front of me I'm so excited to
jump into this don't forget to watch
until the very end for a very special
contest of regarding these patients and
let's get glam on paper
[Music]
all right you guys we were all set up
and ready to go we have the regular
camera angle that you guys are used to
seeing and we also have this good and
fun and fresh camera angle right down
here I think I want to do the papers
make up in the same order that I would
do with my makeup starting off with this
skin so obviously I can't use foundation
I can only use powder so how's the
Anasazi a contour book which is little
been sitting on my shelf for the longest
time looks like a display item has dust
on it sorry but I think this would be a
really good to use it for today's video
being that it is literally a book of a
million different color powders hello
okay so sorry y'all I'm just gonna grab
my I guess I'm just gonna like put it on
there I don't really even know I'm so
excited okay
I woulda got my Mac a regular powder
foundation and just put this on there I
think I'm just gonna lay down a light
layer of skin because I think I want to
make my skin tone slightly darker than
what it normally is
no scandals please it's also been this
weird thing where if you rub it in too
hard the paper leak starts to get
splotchy oh my god this is challenging
hello okay I guess this looks
interesting
[Music]
this is hard okay I'm gonna start
contouring hmm I'm gonna take the change
fawn which is like a very famous Anasazi
a contour color it is a cool tone brown
shade and start shading the sides
well my cheekbone is like here oh that
kinda looks good tea okay same thing on
the other side just need to make myself
look at the sisters smashed how do
people do this and like make it look
real that's what I'm like what hello
that's a harsh Oh mmm kind of looks
pretty though I mean I guess it's kind
of looks good you did with some contour
underneath the lamp because I have lots
of filler I wonder how they get us feel
like don't go outside of the lines
what's a good third grade question but
it applies we need to control the nose
ohh oh my god fun I'm gonna grab my tiny
little nose contouring brush and really
you know just snatch it good do you see
how pants that is hello gonna bring it
up here into the brow region cuz there's
gonna be contours there later on with
eyeshadow then I'm gonna blend that out
oh my god guys this is a kind of turn
about low-key good so far oh my god I'm
excited I love being artists we're gonna
have to actually like sketch out my nose
this is hard how do I do that ask Ohio
oh that's the scariest nose contour ever
seen in my entire life okay I'm Cupid
small all right this looks like okay did
I get say
well that rhymes haha I wonder if using
a Beauty Blender and like dipping into
the actual powder and placing about that
way will actually like make a difference
no well actually yeah kind of
no definitely okay oh wow Imogene s
literally using a white eyeshadow
currently to highlight my face so that's
good oh my god this is the tea this
looks so good oh my god that is so
pretty
I'm literally okay yeah all excited I
figured it out
I've cracked the code oh my god now this
is a person ah Wow I snapped okay great
I'm kind of like happy with this so far
low key the lowest of keys we're gonna
start on the eyebrows so for the eye
region of the brown region I'm gonna be
using the morphia 39a palette this is
the palette that I level before last
year for holiday season and in its back
in stock don't forget to use coach jeans
for 10% off of course I'm gonna grab the
Mac brow marker and the shame that
spiked and you got to kind of sketch out
the outline of the brow first okay there
we go that looks done to you
oh my god t-this actually looks kind of
good okay literally I had a guide to
work with on paper and somehow eyebrows
are still and not even how did that even
happen
I don't deserve this okay so I'm gonna
start this auction looking I think I
wanted to like a sunset smokey eye a
moment with a pop of blue which is
perfect for the 38 palette so I'm first
gonna start by grabbing an orange shade
and my m4 33 usko chance for 10% off and
I guess let's just like put it on there
okay faint blending it out for real one
oh my god I literally love this next
tune to grab a red shade oh so pretty
Hello why did that one go on so easy and
the other ones didn't what
oh my god this looks so pretty hello
this is literally so fun I'm obsessed
with this oh good this looks oh so now
I'm gonna add in a little pop of blue on
the eyelid what should actually be
pretty easy I'm just gonna start by
carving the kind of Navy show you know
from the palette and give me a little
bit of a sister spread since it is a
metallic shade and popping that kind of
right
that looks bad that looks gross oh it
sounds better
thank God I was sister spooped for a
second there now we're gonna go into the
eyes and lashes and not even gonna lie I
am a little bit kind of really nervous
for this just because of the fact that
I'm really really not good at drawing
lashes I struggle with this and a
portraits and obviously I'm going to
struggle with it here so I'm first gonna
start by just shading in the eyeball
with a light brown color I guess I'm
just gonna use my regular liner to try
to draw in eyelashes and pray that it
looks somewhat okay that's an ugly loss
no oh okay I'm going to join the bottom
lashes
that's like okay it could be worse but
it's like not bad and add in the
highlights of the eye
oh my god that actually made it look
real tea
all right you guys I think that is I
number one all done I'm not gonna go
touch up but I have another eye to do
off-camera and that took me quite a long
time so I'm gonna go ahead and try as
hard as I possibly can to get them
symmetrical and I'll be right back to
finish off the rest of the look all
right you guys we are back in both eyes
are all complete and actually loving how
this is turning out so far this is
definitely hard like I expected it to be
but I don't like getting the hang of
things a little bit more this is
definitely art form that takes a lot of
practice and a whole lot of
concentration and Charl and error as
well now that we have both eyes all
complete we are actually pretty close to
done
I accidentally may have done majority of
the nose off camera because I forgot
that I was not recording oops so that
only leaves us with kind of like the
cheeks and the lips left to go so I'm
gonna grab the Mac blush and the shaded
peaches you guys know that's my all-time
favorite I'm just gonna use like a flap
Hocking foundation brush and really step
on there pretty uh oh my god this is so
pretty yeah
James Shaw was getting excited over a
piece of paper heard 30 minutes straight
I really snapped north on her lips I'm
gonna go ahead and apply the shade at
Kylie liquid lipstick in the shade of
one wish I really hope that you can like
put this on there
oh my god why is my bottle left in this
photo so big she's a beefy car all too
much stupider is this me having a
revelation no it's very normal-sized so
I'm gonna outline the inside now and you
just kept saying that my little teeth
that always show through okay now I'm
gonna use the Anasazi look with lipstick
in the shade and milkshake and use this
to kind of highlight the like center
portion of the lips to like make it look
actually 3d or not stupid okay so I'm
pretty much on at this point but the one
thing that I'm like not loving how it
looks is the nose contour because it's
hard um so I'm gonna add some fake
freckles to distract from my lack of
contouring ability and then I'm just
gonna use that Mac brow pencil or brown
marker thing and drawing some freckles I
[Music]
think it's time to show your sisters
that the finish I faced her please take
it easy on me this is only my first try
and probably my last for a while but
okay T on camera doc she looks really
good
hello whoa it looks the best
wait I'm so proud of this okay let's
spell the team overall I'm really proud
of how this turned out that I'm actually
really really happy with it too but
starting off I was really not thinking
too positively because this isn't really
really hard I definitely picked up on
the fact that with this paper you
definitely need to scan in at the actual
product that you're using specifically
the foundation powders that I was using
to kind of lay down the base early on it
because blending really is not the tea
and it actually just ends up picking up
the powder from the paper I really
really love how the brows and eyes
turned out I feel like this is very very
similar to how my face would look if I
had this look on which of course was the
goal with this I do wish the lashes were
a little bit better I said in the
beginning going into it that I didn't
think they were gonna be that good and
if they definitely could look a whole
lot more realistic I probably should
have used a little bit of a lighter
lighter and lighter pressure because
they look a little bit chunky not gonna
lie but the eyes definitely happy with
that's where the nose and fake freckles
definitely not my strong that part of
this t-shirt I will say that the
freckles did end up looking a little bit
better once I kind of layered over a
face powder and a little bit
more kind of blush color to make the
ferals look sunkissed like I normally do
on my makeup but they do look a little
bit more intense and shading and nose no
matter what medium you're using whether
it be a makeup or charcoal like you guys
saw in the last video is really really
hard and it's definitely not my strong
suit
Oh laughs probably not least the lips
are not good all that being said though
that is my face hair all complete
I love how it turned out but this video
is not yet complete because like I told
you guys in the beginning I have a very
very special contest that I am so pumped
to tell you guys about I had so much fun
playing with all this makeup and these
face shirts today and I know so many of
you guys out there as well are also
aspiring makeup artist so I thought it
would be so much fun for this
competition
to do a face chart challenge in the
description box down below there's the
link to download this exact face chart
it is just a blank outline of my face
and ask for your Instagram and says
sister right down here well you guys to
either print out the face on a piece of
paper or import it into a computer
editing software like Photoshop and I
want you guys to go crazy using whatever
medium you would like and create a
beautiful stunning it's sister makeup
look on me once you're finished with
your masterpiece upload it to instagram
with the hashtag sister face chart i'll
be looking through all the entries you
guys need to get your entries in it by
Wednesday evening and I'll be announcing
the winner in next Friday's video there
are actually two different prizes the
first and not our back-to-school season
you guys are getting a full ready to go
kits for all your classes starting off
with of course a brand new MacBook Air
which is great for note-taking putting
together presentations or washing sister
James YouTube videos if you hit for it
in class also it's coming with a brand
new backpack filled with a bunch of cute
back-to-school supplies a $250 Target
gift card for any of your back-to-school
necessities just in case you need
anything else and also a ton of small
Starbucks gift cards so you guys can get
a pinky drink a tea every single morning
before a class to get you through the
day now for the second prize and next
Friday's video and not only will I be
announcing the winner of course I'll
also be recreating the winners paste her
right here on my very own face so into
it get dry get painting at get glamming
or get photoshopping I am literally so
excited to see what you guys come up
with I'm definitely gonna be looking for
lots of creative entries lots of color
things that make it pop I think this is
gonna be so cool and so much fun I
cannot wait to see all of your guys's
entries and if this is the least that I
can do to say thank you for everything
that you have done for me don't forget
to check the description box down below
for the finished face chart and also all
details on how to enter the con
all right sisters Dante's slowing up for
this video today I really really hope
you enjoyed this little faced heart
challenge video and I hope you're
excited for this competition if you did
enjoy it please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below and
definitely leave me a comment and tell
me if you want to do more drawing videos
in the future I love these so much and
it is truly one of my other passions
aside from makeup so it means a lot that
you guys support them as well if you
have not already don't forget to click
that big red subscribe button down below
and come join this sisterhood we are
already 7 million strong and I would
love to have you joining the family and
also click that Mouse icon see if we
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram or Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
but at the same time stuff it's genius
Charles that extra ass after Charles
this video sister show that goes to
sister Jackie thank you so much for your
always falling in supporting or I love
you literally it's so so so much and if
you'd like to be the next videos a
sister shadow don't forget to always a
retweet of it and links when they go
live on a Twitter all right sisters
thank you so much for watching thank you
once again to quick match for partnered
with me on today's brand new video I
love you and I will see you at the next
one
you