my sister's James Turrell is here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see that I've done today a
very very special guest I was so excited
to finally be building a video together
you guys have been requesting it
literally non-stop Haunter a took me and
Charlie out of something I have posted
lots and lots of things together in that
way you've been hanging out non-stop we
went to playlist together go to Disney
together so much finally we're sitting
down today to film a YouTube video for
you guys because I wasn't asking for me
to glam up honest and that she just
posted her very first makeup tutorial
no actually it's my second it was
question of all look we are here today
because I want to tickle a lot Addison I
have a really fun idea for a look that I
want to do if I also have so many things
that I want to talk to you about your
eyes if you on tik-tok
everything around out of the world with
the hype house and just Addison right
in general everyone's favorite person
right now sells have you guys if you
guys watch us get glam and hang out keep
on watching
before we ever let's make up Tyrell
Addison first I'm gonna tweet some of
your brow hairs because you have a
beautiful thick brows but there's some
strays okay don't get my do like why
just tweezing your brows what are you
talking about oh gosh now I'm gonna
first of all by moisturizing your skin
now that the brows are all done so we
have a beautiful base to work on okay I
said for the people who might not know
who you are give us a basic little
rundown so I am Addison right right I
guess you could call me a social-media
influencer buck talker okay thank you
answer but yeah yeah so like obviously
like I've started off on tick tock eye
down into the app in July of 2019 a lot
of younger people that I was around had
the app and I was just kind of like
always in their videos but like never
like did my own stuff you know and then
I downloaded it and I was like you know
what I'm gonna post my own stuff so I
posted it I did too and so one of them
like did really wanna got like 93
thousand likes which was like a lot for
me I posted it and then the next day it
started doing really good
that's over does that yeah I know and so
I was like this is so weird like how do
I handle this so I started getting like
a little bit of followers and everyone
was like oh my gosh who is this girl
like I saw her on my for you page link
and then October 27th I hit 1 million
hello do you remember that day that's
killed yeah I remember it exactly and
now a few months later you're at 30
million yeah just never thought this day
would come
so you were up in Louisiana it's Baton
Rouge right well I was born in Lafayette
you did go to college for a little bit
yes okay so talk about like your
schooling experience in the cow
everything basically comment okay LSU at
LSU that's where I went we started
school in August and how many followers
we got at that time I'm gonna say
probably like 300k oh wow yeah I would
assume do what about like a few million
no no so when did you ultimately make
the decision to drop out then
we used the river sign okay I so okay
boy I my first trip to LA after all this
sort of happening was the end of
September
so before I hit a million famous
birthdays reached out to me and they
were like we would love to have you in
the office like do you live close and I
was like sure I live close yeah so I
flew out here I was only here for four
days because it was over the weekend and
I obviously had to college went a was
birthdays did my little interview thing
the Sunday that I was leaving I ended up
meeting like Taylor and Brice and
randomly and chase chase was the one who
texted me me my mom and chase went eat
and he kind of just want you yeah
went to we went to eat we went to eat he
was talking to me about like what I what
I want to do and like where I want to
take this and I was kind of like what
the heck what do you mean where do I
want to take this you know no mean like
I didn't think that that was a
possibility to make it anything more
than what it was at the moment and so
ended up going back and like meeting
everyone and then they ended up being
like hey you should totally come back
next weekend and like just hang out with
us and like we want to just get to know
you better and I was like um I'm in
college but like my birthday's next week
ends like maybe that's like an excuse
yeah so I was like you know what fine I
will
I got an Airbnb and I came back the next
weekend did you really yeah it was just
like I just was like you know what yeah
so it was just like literally just
happening so fast
and so I kept coming back and forth and
then finally December comes around and
I'm like you know what I think I want to
move here so I ended up moving in till
Tycho's know oh speaking of the height
house I met Thomas at Taylor's house and
like it was one day we were just all
hanging out randomly and I met Thomas
and he was like hey I have this idea
about like a house and we all would live
in it and like collab and I was like
yeah totally I was like what the heck is
this guy talking about and and so he
kept talking about it and finally they
buy the house and we're like you know
what let's just like I'm just gonna go
see you
time goes by and the first hype house
photoshoot happens and Thomas called me
and said hey Bryan is shooting our
photoshoot and I had just shot with
Bryant for my first time ever I love
this full story time and he was like
Bryan shooting it and Bryan called me it
was like a dicin if you want to come you
can you know you're I'm willing to shoot
you too and I was like sure so I went
and Thomas was like bringing jeans and a
white top just in case and I was like
okay and he was like if you decide we
want to be in some photos with the hype
house you can and I was like okay like
maybe you know so I got there and I
ended up being like you know what yeah
I'm gonna be in the pictures I wasn't
even like sure that I was committing to
being in the hype house but it's kind of
just like okay yeah you know I'm gonna
just go for it and it kind of like stuck
my ground and like you know being a part
of the hype house just by being in that
first photo
it was establish a moment exactly still
like it just happened like it didn't
even mean it wasn't even like on
intentionally or anything I was just
like I was in the photos and then that's
when the hype house began it's like you
know what when you what was the word you
used or is I presume that any resides
and I'm resigned and decided to pursue
other dreams you know that's so cool
mm-hmm I think I really appreciate that
details okay so one thing that you
mentioned about your mom being
supportive I think is really cool what
is it like having your parents like
involved with the whole tik-tok
situation like active on it yeah cuz
your parents are both tech talk stars as
well yeah so my mom she started it
because I was making videos with her so
like my first videos to actually blow up
were with my mom
ya know the really big blow up ones so
she ended up making a tick-tock account
because everyone was like oh my gosh
your mom should have her own so she made
her own and like now she has I think
like three million over three million
fires I think she has 3.5 million
dollars so she like kind of established
her own little you know thing on
tick-tock right I always like love and
respect to someone comparin SAR involved
with like their kids dreams and stuff
like I was very grateful and blessed as
well to have super super supportive
parents yeah I'm very very very grateful
for that already okay so the base is all
done we literally just talked for like
an hour so sorry I didn't really
walkthrough pick up but we're gonna go
ahead get started Addison's of brows
right now what's gonna grab the anasazi
brown powder and the shades of soft
brown by the way okay so now that you're
out here in LA officially and you're
also with the hypose to Effie week so
you guys did a big like Entertainment
Tonight
interview and like it was like the first
time like the height most ever did like
something as a group which was super
interesting to watch but there was a lot
of criticism in the comments and adjust
ages from people in general but like
think tick tock errs do nothing so like
what does the day-to-day schedule of
Addison rate look like and just like
walk us to it because even from like
hanging out you guys it's definitely not
nothing like that's for sure yeah so
like being on tick tock I feel like
people do have like the idea that it is
a bunch of nothing and like we're just
saying our rims and like making videos
and it's super easy but I feel like on
YouTube you have to make good content or
like people aren't gonna watch it it's
like the same thing so like yeah it may
be a 15-second video but it's like you
want to make it the best 15 seconds that
anyone's ever watched you know so like
it goes with like a lot of time and
learning the dances coming up with the
dances coming up with skin and yeah tick
tock maybe a 15-second video but it's
like when we're working on other
platforms as well like I've been doing
YouTube videos and then like doing
instagrams and like really active on
like Twitter and snapchat it's like it's
all a big job even from me try to learn
like dances and stuff it takes you like
at least 30 minutes to an hour every
time but I want to do well because I can
never figure them out useful yeah okay
you guys both brows are all done I think
their looks are you like I love them
okay before this eye shadow look today I
have a fun idea and I hope that you are
done for this before we're rolling the
camera today honest and I were talking a
lot about how like obviously it's really
important for both of us to be a good
role model in front of our audiences
good morning sisters but like one of my
biggest things for this year has been
like being a little bit more
unapologetically myself yeah the last
four years I've treated my job super
professionally which obviously it should
be but this year I've been carrying a
little bit less and trying to have more
fun and being more out there like
censoring myself a little bit less and
you're gonna say oh you want to do the
same thing right yeah cuz you're
twinning exactly I have been doing a lot
of colorful looks on people lately and I
of course love doing it colorful makeup
hello it is literally like my entire
brand for this video would it be okay I
really want to give you like a super
super mature like red carpet glam I love
it oh yeah okay I think I got a little
bit of senore let's jump right in okay
as usual you guys were gonna do one eye
on a camera then we'll do the other
camera so I'm just gonna get started
offer so using some hoola bronzer
actually before I even jump into any
eyeshadow just to connect the nose
contour into the crease Serenity's
mentioning how like a lot of people
don't obviously understand like what
goes on behind the scenes and I think
it's a lot more work but one thing that
I really really really really really
commend you for and I've talked to do
all the subtyping before him I'm gonna
say it on camera you are such a positive
person I started hanging out with like
the whole high pals like Tech Talk or a
few months ago when I first joined into
the app and everybody there was so
welcoming and so kind to me which I
appreciate it a lot and after everything
that I went through last year yeah I
obviously lost a lot of friends but I
feel like honestly like me meaning you
guys it's actually you honest and in
general was like it was like literally
like a sign from the universe of like
here's the good people coming here and
like I deserve that
and like I resent you touched the second
time we hire I was just like I
definitely have it here it is oh okay so
I just want to tech so I'm gonna read it
you said dude I just wanna text you and
say I'm genuinely so happy I met you I
hope this doesn't sound effing weird and
cheesy but it's been a really tough past
few months and I felt so happy recently
around everyone and I just wanted to say
thank you for being so kind and sweet
like I truly get the best energy from
you and I'm really grateful for you
that's true it's true how would you say
that you say positive even when you're
dealing with like personal stuff or like
stressful stuff like we were talking
about how bubbly person we have I've
always been like very bubbly very
outgoing and I guess um like you said
you're you know a very social person
I've always been that way as well they
always love to be around people and like
have relationships like personal
relationships with everyone you know
right I feel like that in itself just
translated to my personality on the
internet and like being very welcoming
and being very positive and like keeping
that side of me alive for me it's just
staying surrounded by the people that
make me feel like a better person and
then that kind of just makes everything
fall into place that's why I love being
around you oh because you're always
positive I'm sure we're gonna round you
and you were like negative yet no I
would I really have it like I haven't
you ever just like in a really bad mood
that's like stuck with you well I feel
like a golden goddess we're gonna cut
carrots for a little bit into the other
off-camera that'll be right back to
finish off the rest of this love all
right you guys we are back and both eyes
are now complete I am literally obsessed
- and look oh this is exactly what I was
envisioning
I had Addison pop on her mascara off
camera because she is literally the pro
I wish I had your lashes and it's so
annoying
they're not gonna pop on a parenthesis
on top these aren't the lily lofts in
the style of Miami Flair's you guys know
these are my all-time favorite right now
and you can use Coe James for a 15% off
if you guys want to talk about myself
with falsies on in literally forever so
noticed him for highlighter and I have a
fun question for you yeah so I don't
earlier usually my obviously how are you
going to LSU and setting to be a sports
broadcaster just super super cool
obviously tick tock has you know taken
over a little bit of that career path
first of all without every sentiments I
want to do in the future or like what to
you you know like what do you want to
use your platform to do in the future I
honestly think that I'm gonna take this
and bring it to like hosting yeah no I
would love to do that I would love to do
hosting things I really want to get more
active on YouTube and like really just
trying to establish myself on YouTube
with you guys I've been up trying to
force her to do YouTube videos okay I
did one last week for sure alright you
guys so the look is almost complete all
we have left is going to be the labs for
this look we were deciding between a rad
and a nude and I think I might be
looking so it's so stunning but for some
reason I think this is like pulling us
up like a glossy nude and high fashion
direction so gonna do a lip by if you
guys want to see it with a red lip let
us know because we could always do
another video in the future
so we're just gonna go and I'm gonna use
the matte lip liner in the shade of
spice to line her lips first and then on
top of that look later I'm gonna grab
the k'kaw Beauty at number two nude
lipstick and then I'm just gonna finish
it off with a little pop of gloss in the
middle already guys in the last step
we're just going to lock it in place so
it lasts all day long Bernie go off
camera quickly get out of some chains do
her hair then we'll be right back to
tell you guys the finished love all
right you guys we are dark and this is
the final look on it since you're honest
and
Oh complete I love it so much
[Music]
I'm so glad that we finally got to do
this time look at Mitch I am obsessed
this looks I'm so perfect like I said it
earlier and my tux a few months ago and
still to this day thank you for
constantly making me smile you were such
a light in my life and thank you for
being a light in the life of so many
other people as well all your fans and
my fans I know are obsessed with you and
if they weren't before it they
definitely will be now
well speaking with obsessed you guys if
you enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below enter your lovin supporter helps
us how so so so much and also if you've
not ready make sure you click that big
red subscribe button and come join at
this sisterhood we're 17 million sisters
to have you in the family and also click
that Bell icon so you can use every time
I upload a brand new video
also we filled a video over on Addison's
channel we did a chick-fil-a move on so
if you want to see us eat and answer
some questions check that out I think
sure you guys subscribe to Addison as
well if you like to follow me on I
makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter Facebook and
ticked-off are all just James Charles
play stops are from or behind-the-scenes
time stop is change Carl's the next your
ass after Charles and my phone number if
you want to text me for exclusive
updates and information on everything in
the world of me it is three one oh nine
oh five eight seven four six what can
they find you um Instagram Addison
easterly snapchat asks and underscore II
take talk Addison are e and Twitter who
is Addison this video is sister shot
echoes sister Courtney thank you so much
love for always following and supporting
I love you so so so much and if you
would like to the next videos sister
shut up don't forget to always reach
meet my videos and they go live on
Twitter and also to my youtube at post
notifications already you guys thank you
so much watching this to do today I love
you and I will see you in the next one
[Music]