hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
as you guys can see it's that I am today
a very very special guest so excited we
are finally getting to film a video
together because we've been hanging out
for literally weeks now but we've been
saving at this moment no videos no
videos together no cut no tick-tocks
no snaps everybody's ready to go and
reduces you a superfund that video for
you guys today in case you do not know
who charlie D'Amelio
is kevin like the 30 seconds feel so I'm
a dancer I've been a competitive dancer
since I was 5 I new app takes what came
out where you could learn these
15-second dance videos so I started
doing them with my friends over the
summer and I gained a lot of popularity
on it and I went from zero followers to
36 million in about six months literally
insane so yeah also you're 15 years old
correct yes 15 years old superstar 36
million followers about to be the
biggest person on at the entire upper
tik-tok whoa after James Wright totally
I am the better dancer as well so yeah
this video I know you guys wanted make
up but this is actually my makeup but
I'm obviously a lot better yeah so
Charlie didn't teach me a lot about
makeup and today I'm gonna teach her how
to dance because she's not really that
good like at all honestly and I'm like
obviously really good yeah so stop when
you glue your fingers together all right
charlie so before we even get into this
makeup tutorial today I want to know
from you like what is your makeup
routine and look like and what table
looked you want me to put on you okay so
my no makeup routine is concealer from
breaking out blush okay bronzer mascara
highlight I'm feelin pizza
okay so you're a very very light
coverage paper person I think it's
really cool too because we're so used to
seeing some of the biggest like stars on
different social media platforms hopping
a couple face the makeup which obviously
I have no problem with hello I think
it's really cool that you are in front
of millions of people with like barely
any makeup on for this videos today
though what people look do you want to
do you want both lay out oh we can
definitely do it folds over you're on
the right place for that okay well I
have a lot of questions that I want to
ask you so I get to know you a little
better so the viewers get to know you a
little better so why don't we just go
ahead and jump right in
[Music]
let's go ahead and get started with
moisturizer first I'm going to use it
the touch out water cream you already
have a really really beautiful skin but
I want to make sure it is nice and
supple and hydrated supple I just have
supple plump and like nice like smooth
okay full okay so the one question
Charlie that I want to ask while I'm
putting on your foundation is obviously
going from 0 to 36 million followers in
the course of a few months is insane
congratulations from annoying you behind
the scenes I know that you're a really
really nice person so it's really
awesome to like see that you were the
one who know what has not been like what
is if I like to just go from like a
normal girl and Connecticut to one of
the biggest influences on the entire
planet
um it's weird seeing at how things
changed you know people like some people
will try and go live and try and like
talk bad about me trying to make me look
like a person that I'm not in a bad way
so that's just weird seeing how people
switch up or like people will say like
you cut me off or like you're talking to
me and I was like you haven't been
friends for like four years
yeah or like they'll make us seem a lot
closer than we were in real life that's
weird
but for the most part like I know who I
can trust and like I have my best friend
Gemma back home like nothing has changed
yes what about the positives the
positives are I'm getting to experience
things that I wouldn't have been able to
do if I didn't have this opportunity one
of my friends from school who went after
college was talking to me about how I
had said a year and a half ago I want to
start youtube I really want to start
YouTube but I'm nervous kind of people
are gonna say
and they're just like I'm so proud of
you sorry I'm so proud of you because
like you got to do it and yeah this
isn't I hit like 1.5 million subscribers
on YouTube they're like that's so crazy
yeah we're so scared to do it I got to
meet all the people that I've been
watching for years yeah do you switch me
yeah really well I have like my Apple TV
in my room where like I'd have YouTube
yeah I'd like watching videos like
before I went to sleep
what yeah I used to I love like makeup
like okay I wish I was better at it I
used to do like all these my gear
palette that's so cool so that's super
cool you kinda just like I did grew up
like watching YouTube yeah would you say
that like YouTube is kind of what got
you like into social media in the first
place like how did the whole like Tech
Talk situation like Star um all my
friends are doing it that's honestly how
I got into a to do whatever everyone's
making fun of tick-tock yeah like and I
was too but it was like that's because
like dancing wasn't as big on there like
it was a lot more like it was the comedy
like lip-syncing yeah oh I name is like
musically and then all my friends are
doing it they're like Charlie letting
these dancing okay they would have me
learn the dances so I could teach it to
them so they could do take time and then
I was like I'm gonna get one like so
much fun I want to do it and then it
blew up very quickly which was weird and
it was like a pie like 15 videos in
which is like nothing yeah
what I love about the poeple is that
everybody has the opportunity to go
viral yeah and I think it like that's
why I was talking about this earlier
today it's hard it took like girl
following on a lot of social media
platforms like Instagram algorithms
broken and a million different reasons
YouTube very very talented because
everyone wants to be a youtuber Twitter
people go viral all the time but like
just a viral post yeah once and a viral
post does not translate to like a viral
Twitter account but tick tock everyone
has like an equal opportunity to go
viral and I want to hear your input on
this because of that I feel like there's
a far more people that are on checked
off that are producing really really
good contact because in their heads like
okay maybe I'll do this angle
yeah and I mean I get asked that
question all the time did you want to be
famous I was like well yeah of course I
was thought it was cool to like be a
youtuber right do that stuff but I I had
started tick tock like making funny
videos with like my friends like it was
really never meant to be something right
it's like I'm gonna do this to get
famous and then like figure my life out
from there like it was such an accident
though because all my friends are like
we're gonna get famous was like okay how
are you gonna face off tick-tock right
like a lock or just blending in your
concealer and we're only to stuff then I
think my own competition because I'm
actually not as bad as you think so how
long have you been even dancing since
you were five you said I'm dancing since
I was three been competing since I was
five so I obviously didn't have any with
Abby Lee Miller this past year I love
dance halls I love this like the world
of dance I'm not like super
knowledgeable in it but I've always
found it very very fascinating and I
have an immense row to respect for
dancers because I suck on it like ah I
know my dances are really really bad but
I think like that's one of the reasons
why talk it's fun too because you don't
have to be like great at it to like have
fun you just have fun and that's all
that matters but I'm assuming you being
a competitive dancer helped a lot in
terms like just tick tock and stuff I
mean probably I got to pick up the
dances really quickly which helped I
literally watched you watch somebody
dance watch it like once and then sit
there and record and do it right on the
first try which makes me want to like
literally strangle you because it takes
me at least like at least fifty loops so
if you are still doing a competitive
dance obviously right now like tick tock
is just by thought you have 36 million
followers a new thing for you do you
think that like competitive dance would
be something that you would like want to
do is a cup full time job or what do you
want to do for like a career right now
like where's your hot girl right now
it's very difficult because I have so
many opportunities represented to me
that I'm just trying to like try
everything I just did something for
voice acting or a movie oh my god that's
so cool and I actually really enjoyed it
they give us something that I didn't
I was going to like yeah I had a lot of
fun with it I would love to do something
like that because I tried that a couple
days gone and loved it
okay there's just so much fun um dance I
obviously want to keep up with dance and
continue doing that in training and
taking classes in which I can
I don't know I'm down to try everything
but this is how do you do that with one
nostril because I broke my nose are they
this year no really I've been waiting to
surgery for like since August I'm just
you know I shouldn't be able to breathe
so speaking of you getting a bunch of us
opportunities you've been everywhere the
past few weeks to spend it really fun to
watch but like what was the what we're
like okay I've made it okay so
definitely JLo saying she like knows who
I am and like her kids watch me all the
time I'm like oh her daughter she like
just came off performing at the Super
Bowl and she was like so excited to meet
me and I was like a joking that's so
cool that's crazy
Jalen was like your biggest role model
right are you talking about that James
Charles supposed to be honest that's
really true this did happen oh he's a
big one when I met him he was really
worried over it to be honest yes he
dropped he checks me I play lies this
particular almost the entire makeup that
is such a lie I kept getting walls well
that was her personal never been like a
big a bat as well right yeah and I was
only there for one day cuz I my flight
got delayed great how did you enjoy your
experience of that like it's terrifying
it was like going oh there's so many
people and then I was like no it's fine
they're not gonna come up to me like no
one cares about me
most I've ever heard I walked out and
then there was like a bunch of people
there does it go then I felt super cool
do you do well with the crowds and
suffer do you like meeting a lot of
people I love meeting people I like
meeting them in smaller groups yeah some
reason because sometimes I'll feel
overwhelmed so I try to keep my college
which I can but I also get a lot of
anxiety when I'm around a lot of people
yeah and I come here really scary and
you know what I've kind of noticed over
the past a few years especially with me
cuz I used to be the same way like I was
always so concerned about whatever
people would think but I've like fans
and just like people like viewers in
general have gotten way better about
respecting that stuff so I own it uh
there's like a growing crowd of people
that are
starting to understand like okay these
like a lot of these influencers I have
like a huge following like this is not
like this is dangerous
yeah I mean there's of course the people
like that it's mostly the parents that
are like yeah straight up with rude like
I had a mommy yell at me once I was in
the middle of eating dinner and I was
with all my friends and she like called
me out specifically and I was like with
all my friends and I had a really really
just horrible day and of course no one
knows that I'm not gonna post like me
just being upset there's a lot of stuff
going on right and my friend's mom was
like hey we're just going to eat dinner
right now do you think you could just we
just to come a minute so they can like
eat and are like well she's not gonna
die she doesn't eat right now is she you
know one I was like I'm sorry like I can
take it and she's like you know what
this is making you look really bad and I
literally crying she was like I have a
little girl here and I said you know
what girl you just made me cry good good
what I didn't mean to it was like well
you did good and then she was like I'm
following and I was like just mean
because I wasn't even like I literally
said I was gonna do it after and like it
was gonna take five obviously I was so
hungry I hadn't eaten all day great and
you have a right to eat that's the one
like I love meeting people I will always
say pictures people the one time I will
always say no is it what I mean a or not
always just say we'll come in the back
there oh yeah yeah hey I'm so sorry like
I'm to the bathroom and they can see the
page so like maybe right now I'm always
okay I'm always late to meetings and
that's like they want to ask me take
talk something I'm so sorry
I literally have to go right now yeah
I'm really sorry that obviously not
everybody can be a respectful of you
it's really it's like one of the worst
part about being an influencer
I see other things like people post
things and then like everyone colonies
to like wherever I am sometimes that'll
let go - those are my cousin's wedding
you told me about this I can't even
believe this actually happened yeah
that was like a group of like four girls
who got ready and pretended that they
were cousins with my cousin and that I
think that is literal psychopath
behavior there's no other most of this
right back to him and he was like hi
guys who are you nice to meet you and
you they can do I do they work I was
like oh that's so crazy
that's annoying kids are some things
where I want my like privacy and it was
like my cousin's wedding with my family
not the appropriate time at all so that
was like really really weird
okay so aside from obviously privacy
problems what would you say has been the
biggest change from your life beforehand
to now just like the day-to-day stuff I
can't go out looking like trash if
there's people there and then look like
trash I'll say it yeah and then it just
like makes the picture I'm comfortable
because I know I look bad you don't look
bad it's usually when I'm getting coffee
to which is my safe do you feel like
pressure to always look good you know
can I sleep with this one I wouldn't
recommend bad but no ever no never
I'm taking like an hour-long nap like in
the middle of the day if I'm like in
between days and never something upon
ever no do about that it's for your skin
do you know how much energy you need to
take your makeup off agreed are you done
with the base I think so yeah I haven't
done did James Charles export a pallet
what color is that we want to use you
you pick you have for creative I know
but I wanted to I want you to like it
maybe we should have matched the hoodie
I thought could be like a cute little
pastel moment yeah
as we start with this one is gonna be
dipping into some different colors
matching the hoodie I said when I keep
talking cause I have a lot more
questions for you and I have a little
bit more like a serious I share that
what you don't hope you answer if you
don't want to but I know that you've
talked a lot about unlike different
socials and stuff but or anybody isn't
also like your private SAS Affairs like
my favorite era world I know you're
dealing with like a lot I'm doing a lot
right now do you feel like you're being
pulled and like a million different
directions and how was that like
affecting you
so you even want to talk about it
ya know I've actually never talked about
this and the slightest before I have to
beginning when this all started I was
very very overwhelmed yeah and I was
still going to school and full-time like
going to a middle school right like I
was in public school yeah I was
traveling a lot I always had something
to do and I felt like I just had no free
time and then as time started going on I
started doing online school which was
great I loved it so much I mean I was
struggling because there were so many
things I felt like I had to do and I
felt like I didn't have I really well
put together schedule back then and I
just felt like everything I felt like
everyone was yelling at me to like get
stuff done yeah and I was like I don't
know how to do it all cuz I think
there's I just feel like there's so many
things that I have to do you were my my
excuse for most things was like I just
did I had no idea right I had stuff to
do that I would know about but I'm still
obviously a teenager and I would just
forget or take a nap or get tired like I
was really struggling with that but now
associate my family we're a lot better
on making sure like oh I have something
this day like let's not unpack I just
was getting so so so tired we're even
for a little bit I realize like my
videos were not good because I just are
like it wasn't having fun yeah and then
took a little bit of a break from
everything and stopped so I can focus on
myself and then now I'm getting back
into the meetings and still doing work
stuff but also being able to do all the
fun things and like really getting to
sit and enjoy them everything just like
worked out in the best way I'm really
glad to say that you're like handling it
better and all of it like when I first
saw your story I think I was horrified
for you and like I remember I said
you're really like long message and
stuff just like because I won't do the
same thing obviously you grew way fast
knighted and I think just tick tock is
just a different pop from an environment
in general but like I have somebody
who's like very very business minded I
love being overworked and stuff but at
times like it was so because if you
don't enjoy that it's obviously like a
recipe for disaster and even for me as
someone who did enjoy being over it
there was days where I would go home and
just crime
to see precisely I just feel like I'm
like so overwhelmed it can't handle all
this I my entire life like especially
growing up a competition inter and like
having to have not a lot of free time on
my schedule I've been used to like
working hard from the second I wake up
to the second I go to bed make sure I
get all of my stuff done it was just
this was so different than anything I've
ever done before on a more positive note
now that you are managing your time
better what do you like to do for fun
aside from making tic TOCs and dancing
well I always in really enjoyed painting
I mean really I was like mom can you get
me like some canvases in PE and so is
her painting and I had a lot of fun with
it I wasn't that good but it was just
something to do
mm-hmm when I was like just doing
nothing right I got into doing makeup
because I was really into art in the
first place so I don't get to do that
much anymore either but I also I love a
good procreate oh man now what it's time
for it lashes now we're having a little
bit of a dilemma because I really wanted
to do like a natural lash on Charley and
after checking the collection we
realized that we don't have ones that's
really good I'm clearly a really good
beauty girl but like I said obviously
I'm a dancer so this is just like a side
job yeah so honestly as the makeup
artist you should been prepared yeah I
know so that's really bad I'll be
leaving you a bad review but that looks
good do you like your dress fired yeah
yeah okay the eyes are done I love how
they turned out it's a cute little
pastel moment snapped in the hoodie
available soon as sisters apparel calm
now it's time to go on to highlighter
well my favorite part about your face is
you aren't freckles that you have
naturally we cover that with some
foundation so I'm going to go ahead and
draw your ass back on period cute looks
just like normal me yeah okay wow I wish
you wish what little bit is your face
right now
okay so we're pretty much almost done
and last not least we're going to have
the lips
yeah okay now alas not least let's do a
cute little gloss I think all right miss
Charlie D'Amelio I think that is this
makeup look Oh
[Music]
do you like it yeah it's like so
different than anything that I've
literally ever done ever well you can
come over for glam literally any time I
am so glad that you were able to finally
join us on the channel today we've been
talking about it for so long I have
talked about getting to glam you and I
also talked on it getting to know you
and I really hope that you guys enjoyed
it as well if you did please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and share your love and support
and really does help us how so much
where do you go check out Charlie's
handout while you're still over here
make sure you click that big sky button
down below and come join this sisterhood
we are 17 million strong and I would
love to have you in the family
it also makes you click that balamani so
you get notifications every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me on my big return you can check
me on instagram on twitter facebook in
tik-tok or contests James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes I
have to see your Charles with an extra s
after Charles and also if you had a fall
of me if you want to follow me on all my
social medias it is actually D'Amelio
and if you want to see the home scenes
from this video you can look on my
youtube channel for some extra footage
of James and I also if you guys want to
text me for any exclusive updates on it
videos photos and new merch which by the
way Charlie is wearing right now make
sure you guys are following us on
Instagram and sisters apparel for all
updates coming soon there's going to be
a huge huge relaunch of assistance
apparel with some very very exciting
news so fellas over there boys chocolate
sisters Esther Perel calm and you can
text me like I said at three one oh nine
oh five eight seven four six
this videos sisters how that goes to
sister Nile thank you so much love for
always following in supporting I love
you so so so much and if you'd like to
the next videos a sister shout out make
sure you only it's reaching with a nice
label retweet videos they go live on
Twitter and also turn to my YouTube
posts publications
alright you guys thank you so much
watching this videos today thank you so
much Charlie for joining us and that we
will see you in the next one bye
[Music]