hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see today i'm joined with a
very very social guest
[Music]
i am like your number one biggest fan
this is the collab that i have been
wanting to happen so badly and we have
been trying to make it work for quite a
while now
yes i met you at coachella which is
don't even go into that yet because that
is the whole thing that i want to talk
about later on in this video
like i was shy and now i'm like you know
what i mean
we're going to talk about that don't
worry it's crazy what do you want to
achieve with this look for this video
today because we're going to give you a
full-on makeover um
i want to do whatever you want to do
honestly like you're the artiste
okay i'm just an artist but sure just
the artist listen
paint me down okay because i need it i
want it
okay so if you guys want to see me glam
up dojika and talk all about
music how we met for the first time her
rise to fame and literally everything in
between
keep on watching
[Music]
so we're gonna get started we're going
to prime your face which i never do
really honestly i for the longest time
thought primer was a hoax i still
occasionally do i do feel like there are
a few that do just like a little
something i'm just gonna copy
perfect literally just taking mental
notes of what i see in front of me well
okay before we even get into any other
questions
i remember watching an interview with
you where you said that when you were
like 14 you wanted to be a beauty guru i
did
okay let's talk about i really did so i
went to my mom's room i brought my whole
desktop computer
i brought it into my mom's room and i
would sit it down at the perfect angle
for there to be a toilet in the
background
what so i'd be on the floor and then i'd
be i tried to do a vampire look
okay it was one of my first looks okay i
think i did
i think i did all right i did try and
honestly i was like this is not for me
okay but you like you guys i wanted that
i wanted to do it i love
makeup i like painting and drawing and
stuff okay yeah maybe the video thing
didn't really
i didn't click with that didn't become a
youtuber yeah when you started the
beauty stuff
yeah like videos like well technically
13. oh my god there was an
old channel that was like comedy okay
it's not funny
okay like i started this whole situation
when i was like just about to turn 17.
oh wow yeah well okay so one thing that
i want to talk about
we need to talk about the first head
that we met yes
well i'm gonna start with it started at
coachella
and the first time i performed at
coachella what yes
but it wasn't like a full thing i showed
up to do
tia tamara with rico nasty gotta gotta
go
so i did my verse and then i got to walk
around and do whatever yeah
so i got there and i was you know in the
back whatever
and we weren't really doing anything
like we were kind of just standing
around
taking pictures whatever it was cute i
saw you and then i was like oh my god i
know who that is i know that hair
i know that face so then i was like to
my manager
yes look oh my gosh she's like you want
to say hi
and of course me like i'm not like i'm
not good at that i'm not good at like
coming up to somebody and saying hi
i really wish i was she was like [ __ ]
just say hi
like come with me and she yanked me over
thank god
and then we said hi to each other i
remember you were like oh do you know
the song like [ __ ] i'm a cow
yeah and i said yes i do because it was
it had been going really viral all the
time and you're like hi my name is
dojika nice to meet you and i was like
oh my god like you're so cute
um and you were like oh my god i love
your videos and it's so
insane to me that now a year later
you're one of the biggest artists on the
planet and now i'm a fan of you
like that's so it's that is so cool it's
so cool it's so cool all right so we're
going to move on to concealer i'm going
to use a little bit of the
nars radiant creamy fun little
highlighted face
one thing that i definitely want to ask
you about if we're on the topic of
growing up in the social media world
tick tock obviously has become massive
and
you were already starting to like blow
up i feel like but there's no denying
that you are like the queen of the tick
tock
i hope so that would be nice i feel like
everyone's on there
yeah i made my mom i didn't make my take
talk
i had to make a change i feel like i had
to because one
haley really blew it yodeling haley for
those of you guys who don't know
yodeling haley is the girl who did that
the dance is cute as hell say so there
have been 20
million videos made with that sound oh
my god
and each one of those videos also has
videos that's insane yeah
the song is a bop it's really changed my
life
as far as like you know i just i'll make
a song
and people even in the youtube comments
will be like oh let's hope tick tock
doesn't ruin this one
so i feel like my whole career has
become based around it
on tech talk yeah like that might be a
possibility but i mean there's no
denying that the app has the power to
make any song
yeah because you can do anything to a
song you can like do your nails and put
the song in the background whatever you
know what i mean but on youtube it's
different
because you have to like get rights and
stuff you can't you can't use any music
yeah you can't use it
just i think it's so stupid i'm tired of
that like royalty free
like what is the music oh how's it go
the awkward sound that little like ding
ding ding ding like when she was like
awkward oh
my god i really do appreciate tick-tock
and i mean even like the dumb tick tocks
i make
double jointed [ __ ] be like
girl you need to stop it
just stop at first honestly like i would
watch tick tock cringe compilations
sure before i got into tic tac i'd watch
the cringe comps i'd be like oh my god
i'm not part of this
and then i started watching the ones
that aren't cringe ones and i'm like oh
this is literally
vine yeah i was like all right fine i
guess there's some funny people on tick
tock and you know what
almost everybody on tik tok is funny
it's such a funny place
i grabbed a banana powder speaking of
tick tock making songs huge
my i have to tell you favorite song
right now is [ __ ] talk
it's literally one of them it is so
catchy it's not even funny i was working
with the city girls because they're just
the coolest
super easy super cute they're so cute
they are
yeah they're like characters they're
really really cute they're really chill
and yeah we just had a blast i i feel
like you could tell that from just like
the video and the vibes it's such a good
song
all we really wanted to do was just
twerk in the dark yeah
i love that i want to know well speaking
of collaborations who is like your dream
collaborator on the song you stay
pharrell all the time i still feel that
way
i want to work with everybody yeah i
feel that i want to work with like
everybody like i don't know who my
number one really is other than pharaoh
we actually seriously off camera listen
to the [ __ ] song at least 20 times a
day oh my god
when they sent that to me i was like oh
my god this hook because when she's like
spanish so it makes you feel so
it's so catchy but we didn't know she
was saying french we thought it was
english
[Music]
he was like speak for yourself ass
currently just contouring
your nose
[Music]
i feel like you're the king of nose
contour
it's literally sorry about this angle
but i literally
it's like my favorite stuff with any
makeup routine you got to do a whole hop
skip and a jump and a cartwheel and
all types of stuff to get them when i do
my makeup don't judge me
judge me free i do it on the floor but
if you walk into my house
it's like there is just makeup all over
the floor i've seen that whenever you
facetime me yeah i haven't said anything
about it because it's not my place to
judge
i just have like a long mirror that just
leans up against a wall and
i sit on the floor and the makeup gets
spread out so i
end up being like 20 feet away from the
mirror and i have to like sleep all my
makeup into the mirror and then
sit in the pile of makeup you really do
do your makeup often huh
yeah when i don't need to people where
are you going people ask me that i'm
like um instagram screens go what you
mean
i'm going to sleep these are pajama
lashes i've seen you do your makeup
before on instagram live huh
your instagram lives are something else
before we even get into really that i
feel like one of the reasons why i
really
like just like you in general is
obviously your music is good but like
you have
such a fun personality like if you don't
take anything too seriously like you
always just trying to have a good time
and like
if there's any place where i feel like
that shows i just always think back to
your one instagram live where you
started reading your song lyrics with
chain mail and medieval music in the
background magician with the titties
told him pick a copy knowing just when
i'm on
i love doing stuff like that why it's
just like honestly
quarantine will do that to you i don't
know i just felt inspired
so that's yeah that's what came out of
that hmm
okay i feel like we should do brows now
while we let this sit in place for a
brief moment yes
ooh i like to do my own brows usually oh
but she's a
she's an mua now i'd like to see you try
to do the spark brow on me
like that was like a that was like a
threat almost a little bit
excuse me but like i kind of want to see
you do it because i feel like you would
kill that
i would it's my job let me pull up a
reference folder so i can make sure that
these are really accurate and up to your
standards because clearly they're high
okay well one other question that i want
to ask you kind of going back to a
little bit what we were talking about
earlier
um your first i feel like was move like
your first like viral
that was the first thing that ever
really popped off yeah i remember that's
why i first heard about you you wrote
that i think in like 12 hours and it was
inspired by a shirt that you're wearing
it was a satire it was a joke yeah like
it was really like i was on live
and everybody was giving me their input
i had just started i just set up
we didn't have anything ready to like we
didn't have any ideas
prior like i was just like what do i do
today and i'm wearing cow print and my
hair literally has little horns
yeah and i'm sitting there and i'm like
i'm not about to write about a boy and i
just start singing like [ __ ] i'm a cow
[ __ ] i'm a cow right i
made that song in the middle of my
career really
right i had been making music maybe six
years before
yes for like for six years straight i
was putting stuff out nobody
really got into it and i guess it was
one of those moments because it's
something that i would do
i would make like goofy stuff right it
was one of the moments where i was like
i'm gonna make a video to this and i
didn't have a lot of videos
and i think people really appreciate
videos yeah let me put on this
just don't talk for one second you know
what does talking chris [ __ ] there's
[ __ ] talks
oh english spanish how does your
songwriting process work and like how do
you go from writing joke songs like that
so then all of a sudden writing number
one hits
um well so i had been already making
serious music but i i really just like
like to make music i can make like an
if you give me seven days i can make
seven songs
really yeah i mean like i can sit there
and do it all you know
all week if i don't have anything to do
but i just i like to do it so much that
it's like
it's gonna happen regardless you know
like some people think
maybe i'm like i don't really take music
seriously but i
kind of do yeah like i kind of to an
extent like i just like to do that i
mean
i don't really because i could play
video games all day but that
you know if i'm not doing that i'm you
are a gamer huh yes yes
okay well that is one brow looking
fabulous i completed this challenge and
never
questioned me again i'm never washing my
face again
we're going to do this one off camera
quickly just make sure that they are
even and we'll be right back you guys to
go on to
the eyes all right you guys so both
brows are now done look forward for me
here we go those are good i'm grabbing
this blush from
patrick todd have this on your
cheekbones this is looking
so good so i'm gonna give you a little
bit of a
spritzes setting spray which i could not
locate just to add some hydration back
into the skin because we had a lot of
powder obviously
okay so i feel like when you do makeup
stuff especially like whether it's on
instagram live or whether it's you
facetiming me at three in the morning
i feel like you always try to do new eye
locks which i really like
yes i want to work with color and it's
really hard i feel like i get scared
because i know that
once i put that shade down it's not
coming off so i get scared of that
that's why i don't color a lot oh and i
use this palette
i use that palette and i use that one
pink i'm first going to start by
grabbing
oh my god what is this color i'm just
going to start by grabbing it
which is the dark brown shade in the top
right hand corner and i'm going to start
applying it to jojo's crease because
i want to go for a nice cut crease look
today right now i know you're getting
prepared to perform at the vmas which
was just announced congratulations i'm
so excited for you
obviously you're supposed to perform at
coachella this year which would have
been the second day i was going to be
front row at your side
and now it is not happening but there's
always of course next year and i will
still be front row
are you excited like for the performance
just tell me like tell me everything
extremely excited the only thing it's
very different this year obviously
because of what's going on
you can't you know what i mean it's not
like there's gonna be a bunch of people
it's not cla
it's not the classic experience of like
the vmas you know
but it's a blessing to be able to you
know do a full production like what
we're doing i wish i could say what
we're doing
it's so it's gonna be really really
really cool
i'm not gonna get a little bit of oh my
god
i feel like i need to get a room for you
in the camera i'm going to cut the
crease and i need you to focus
okay yes yes i understand two seconds
later
[Music]
literally stand up lewis can you angle
the camera upwards just for a free phone
oh it's crazy how much that oh my god
that's the most i ever
do
[Music]
stop that let's get back down that was a
lot okay now that the eye is looking
so perfect we're going to cut and we're
going to do the one off camera and try
our best and hope and pray
that we can get them even and we'll be
right back to finish off the rest of the
lock
brb all right you guys we are back and
both eyes are now complete
what is this reveal going on here
you're feeling yourself i always like to
edit my videos on a positive note and
we've talked a lot about how you're part
of this new and upcoming rap generation
what will be one piece of advice that
you have
to other girls or other little boys out
there that want to follow in your
footsteps
in terms of music one day don't worry
about being perfect
just do what you like to do yeah do not
spend time trying to impress people
because there's always going to be
somebody out there who's going to hate
on you
and that's just the climate of today i
don't know if it'll change later but
please just enjoy what you do and do
whatever you want don't let anybody tell
you what to do i love that
all right you guys in a few hours lots
of fun and lots of makeup
later i think this is the finished
transformation on dojika oh
oh my god my foot is so numb what do you
think about this lock
i love it it's so good i am obsessed
with the best i've gotten my makeup done
you're kidding i wasn't gonna say it
it's very good really
it's very good i'll just take that to
the video i'm really happy with how this
turned out as well i think you look
absolutely stunning
but you your music your story everything
about you like i said looking at this
video i am such a huge fan and i am so
lucky to have you as a friend as well so
thank you so much for joining us here on
my channel today
i really hope that you guys enjoyed this
video as well if you did don't forget to
give it a big
thumbs up down below if you haven't
already as well make sure you click that
bigger subscribe button and come join
the sisterhood i would love to have you
in the family and also click that bell
icon so you get notified every time
i upload a brand new video if you like
to follow me on my makeup journey all my
social media accounts will be linked
right here around the screen and also if
you want to text me on my
personal phone number for new updates on
photos videos merch and so much more
it is 310-905-8746 if you guys want to
check out dojika
find me on twitter at dojicat
d-o-j-a-c-a-t
instagram doja cat d-o-j-c this video is
just a shout-out goes to sister misha
thank you so much love for always
following and supporting i love you so
so so much and if you would like to be
the next videos sister shout out don't
forget to always read twitter links they
go live on twitter and also to my
youtube post notifications
all right you guys well that is all we
have for today's video thank you so much
for watching thank you again
for coming i love her so so much and i
will see you guys in
the next one
my way