hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see today I'm doing today a
very iconic and legendary special guest
first of all ok we are going to be doing
a very fun Beauty video today because
you are launching at your own makeup
line yes it is iconic ok this PR package
the packaging it's literally everything
it's so orange you know it's gorgeous
this palette is so cute the clothes
right here is literally everything a
beautiful
oh you look incredible and we haven't
even started yet so this is gonna be a
very fun at makeover for today thank you
for being on my channel thank you for
having me this is I'm very very excited
I literally grew up listening to you and
your music and your new stuff is just so
exciting I'm so excited to see the
revamp to you and everything that you
were working on right now I am very
grateful for you for having me in your
home been doing this and doing my makeup
and I very much feel like a little baby
hamster in the makeup on we love a
little baby concern I mean they're cute
but little I can go into a colorful
beautiful adult hamster yes yes all
right you guys so if you want to see it
me transform Akasha into a beautiful
rainbow adult hamster and her music
everything that she's working on and
just do a fun at Beauty makeover keep on
watching
I want you to tell me about like what
you like most in terms of like your
makeup so we can get an idea of what we
want to do for this transformation today
okay so earlier in my career I just had
so many people cover my freckles it's
always like cover them with vinca or
brush them away not in magazines and
this week so happy literally my
followers know I draw them on all the
time I wish that my face look like
there's naturally oh it's so unfair
so I wanted to do like a very like light
base I knew but I want to go crazy on
the eyes oh my please go crazy okay I'm
like a fan of crazy so you can go crazy
wherever you want okay I'm into it okay
good I love let's just jump right in to
save so many things I want to ask you
about so he thinks I don't talk about it
so yeah let's just go hi I'm gonna match
together two different shades of the
Anasazi Beverly Hills luminous
foundation and try my hardest to call
them out to you you can do it thank you
you're the magic color-matching moment
miss kasha Rose thank you for coming
today I am so excited I want to talk to
you but literally everything first of
all I just want to say like I get
excited about the people that I clad
with all the time but I literally grew
up listening to music like you shaped my
2010 so crazy
I was literally either 9 or 10 years old
when animal and cannibal came out are
you 19 2012 I'm so excited to see that
after such a long time they're not going
back with a completely new style and
just like revamped I'm so excited for
the new record to come out it's coming
out in January and it's like a mix of
all the things like all the kinds of
music I like which I like a lot of
different kinds yeah it's a celebration
of not having to be one genre yeah
they're stuck in any box right
obviously animal in Campbell were very
like party crazy
and that's why was that so would you say
that your albums are definitely like an
accurate presentation of like where you
are in life yeah it's like a snapshot
into what my life is like yeah that was
it like 22 for me mm-hmm
so it was a bit of an animal and with
a cannibal and I wrote that song
cannibal about eating man I wrote with
my mom no way ok that's fun one thing
that I know about you that people might
not is it you write a lot of your own
sauce right for other people as well
ok do you want to talk about that a
little bit because I'm back ok so you
never end for I'm so curious you help
right till the world ends for me yeah ok
you wrote for Miley Cyrus veronica's I
wrote a song for them ages ago I've
written like collaborated with I mean a
bunch of people like pitbull and
Macklemore and most recently Big Freedia
yes / raising hell I really want to get
into music which I would talk to you
about later on but yourselves like
singing you're gonna have to sing on
this channel well I have so I'm ready to
be a solo process because it's so hard
to do another thing on makeup to me is
so impressive well this is good then
then we can be beneficial how does the
songwriting process work for you because
you know had a lot of box let's be real
a lot of box music I don't like love it
and this new record I have just embraced
the fact that I like really like pop
music yeah and I can just be an
unapologetic cheesy [ __ ] sometimes
yeah so I liked it I thought I want to
put on a little bit of concealer just to
cover up a nice condor i dark Ness but I
also want to keep the freckles there cuz
that's where most of them are so it's a
little bit of this I'm gonna use the
morphe contour stack and this is number
13 okay to relate cheslow kisses at
cheekbones here and give her a nice good
uplift and snotch love your dog oh I
will give you the best so you've done a
lot of collabs as well as one thing that
I've noticed about your albums which I
live for everybody from a pitbull 3:03
real friends
that's old cut yeah yeah I told you a
benefit Macklemore maybe pop like
everybody okay so you wanna hear a funny
story about that he pops on shore home
dirty love that song I started
a co-write or Arianna and then like it
started just getting like a little
nastier and nastier and this was a while
ago and I was like I think I might just
be like two two branches Roger and then
I found out that dirty love in England
means that's very familiar then I and
then I collaborated Iggy Pop on it was
like my all-time favorite really I was
in the house career favorite Club is
been what egg you pop you the answer I
mean Iggy Pop's like a god to me yeah
but like so is Beyonce so it's like my
musical taste is right if you can come
up with anybody who would you pick and
why mm-hmm in the world yeah well I
would have like multiple answers Dead or
Alive
sure okay so I probably do Bowie oh yeah
in the pop world I would yeah I'll be
everything on your new album you have a
song that is featuring yourself but with
the money sign yeah in the name you know
a little bit throwback but also just
reclaiming the part of my waist it goes
integral in greeting yeah TED talk we
are who we are like those songs are like
literally how everybody like fell in
love with you so I always really excited
to see that it was like making a little
comeback for me yeah the song you're
talking about it's called kinky oh okay
that one's it's like a celebration of
having like obviously rainbow was a
major depart from what your first two
albums were yeah but it was just such a
beautiful story so I think it's really
cool to kind of come back and might be
full circle which is like everything
well I think that rainbow and I do
address obviously some like more serious
things that I had quite frankly with
sick of hearing people be like oh you
can't say you can't say when we're
using autotune is like a very obvious
yes we weren't trying to hide any of
that so I'm rainbows I just really
wanted it to be like there's no effects
there's no kind of gimmicky stuff
happening it's just my voice my
songwriting and little more serious on
this album I just wanted to like you're
allowed to be happy we're all allowed to
be happy and we all should be happy and
doesn't matter if you go through
something that's terrible and you may
never get over it but you can try to
move on milik present and happy and
joyful in here in the fact that we're
alive today that's something that
personally I'm struggling with a lot
right now from just things that have
happened this past year as well so I'm
really excited personally to listen and
kind of go on that journey with you yeah
one thing that I definitely ask you
about because you're mentioning that you
were tired of hearing people say that
you couldn't sing one my favorite songs
from you ever is praying and it's just
such a beautiful song with a beautiful
message behind it but beautiful message
aside did you know that it went viral on
tik-tok and there was a challenger on
that okay okay
tick tock and nice hot dog but uh there
was a whole entire challenge dedicated
to people turn the head man it's an app
right it's it's just I use know I can
hit in my vocal range can you edit like
huh that's so I'm not even trying to do
it I don't know how you doing it's so
hard but he hates your voice into like a
other plant and yo I can't believe you
just have that note yeah babies our God
is the beanie on your music career right
here right now oh if that's what they're
anyway music right I think it just ended
right here right now as well okay I'm
gonna add something nice blast you as
well I really want to I like a nice
peachy pink moment I want to clean up
the side of your nose a little bit
please do when I don't up contour my
nose versus when I knew and
that was done right yeah you have a
really good shaped nose to do a insane
nose contour on if you'd like look
forward just like look at this side of
here now it was like little like can you
even breathe right now I'm so sorry
you're having breathing problems
currently Herod tried that not in about
three months okay I'm gonna grab a
little bit of a face how about my mini
palette we're just gonna pop them on cuz
just cheekbones for a really good do we
look I really want her skin to just
literally look like it's going from
within that is pretty much our Bates all
done so we're gonna move on to the eyes
now okay let me get to use the brand new
casseroles palette so let's get ready in
the Sun well makeup okay yeah let's go
what are we getting ready for our party
I don't know
oh you ain't not quite although you know
I don't party oh yeah but she never were
in my shot I may be tempted to say yes
to be quite oh yes we're gonna drink
water and we are gonna paint my face
okay well I don't need to really do
anything to your brows to be right on
those yeah I think it looks really good
okay so first of all love the clothes
right at the top I love that you did not
just release a palette of neutral colors
like I couldn't know right and that's my
heart
there are a lot of people that are
releasing make appliance which i think
is amazing because it's always fun to
add new things to the market but at the
same time I think that there's also
something would really make apply
instead it doesn't quite make sense I
think this makes perfect sense for you I
mean yeah so I really had to understand
what people would want from me right
when I think of Tessa I think of a party
crazy colorful glitter because very
grateful you put a few glitter yeah they
can go like on top of whatever a daytime
look you have going on or
intensify or whatever my feelings makes
a lot of sense for you and your brand so
I was very excited to see that because
it just like feels very genuine okay
and I wonder singly beautiful today I
thought it'd be really fun to do a
matching outlook tool that I have on now
but do a pop of blue because this is
literally one of the most stunning
shadows that I've ever seen on the lower
person instead of the green and maybe on
some glitter in there too beautiful and
like fun fact any of the matte ones if
you had water to them they become way
more pigmented really oh just don't have
a fun track for all that and then the
shimmer you know they're super shimmery
but play and see what we can come up
with you have a little bit of concealer
for her base let's do one eye on camera
and then we can I was about to go in you
want the CMAs alien skin flap
yeah literally I've never had some what
would even be the husband alien yeah oh
my god mother cross and you can hit the
notes for this little flap of skin makes
doing makeup sometimes very very
difficult we both an alien skin yeah
this what I call mine oh hey mom another
lovingly yeah no I love like we're from
another planet okay that's a good thing
to calm it I have literally never seen
anybody else would that flap of skin
there but yeah we like utilize it and
put shimmer on it and just like play
with it yeah a little buffing brush and
dip into backstabber
love the shade names in this they're all
named after songs right there are songs
that are old school if you know the deep
cuts and some are on the new record and
one of them is unreleased Oh will it be
released
oh it's a secret plan okay I'm just
gonna pop this into your outer V little
area right in here and we're going to
blend at that in a second
I want to know what made you want to
create I'm making one in the first place
so I feel like I've had so many kinds of
makeup on my face for it's been like 10
years yeah I've always loved makeup and
I love color and I love playing and I
love ironically a lot of my influences
are actually men that use makeup just
totally like incorrectly mm-hmm but I'm
really inspired by people that utilize
what they want how they want just so
many different ways to use makeup that
doesn't have to be about looking like
this perfect super femicide all approved
thing it's more about expressing what I
like and like what color I feel today I
just use a little bit of cannibal which
is the bright red shade which by the way
is so beautiful I love about that and
then I'm now gonna grab a little bit of
a buggy feet on a fluffy brush and I'm
squinted buff out to the edges how did
you choose the different shades for the
palate so I wanted to think about what I
wear
yeah well my friends we're all different
skin tones like just what everybody
likes right then I'm also looking for
this chartreuse color which is my
favorite color in the entire world
dinosaur which I have all of my lower
lash line right now and I love that and
I've just never been able to find like
the perfect chartreuse I'm like obsessed
with that color okay and then also like
I have to have a glitter I remember a
few months ago I was playing Minecraft I
was live streaming on Twitch and the ego
popped up was like collaboration with
Kasia and I literally screamed and I I
was live and I was like what is going on
what happened I was like oh I just got a
really cool video opportunity so if
anybody was watching this you guys will
know now was the first thing that I said
was if she doesn't have a glitter I'm
not doing this they're lovely you have
multiple shades of glitter and jammers
and then some matte just but yeah I
wanted to give people a variety so I
wanted to have it really colorful but
also have like the basics like a black
you can always just slap on a smoky eye
and sleep in it and wake up and just
kind of look cool I mean some days or
just like really hungover a little bit
of honey right on to the lid
oh that's really really perfect
like on my leg Cupid's bow oh we should
try that on the cheekbone it's gonna cut
the edge okay I want to test out this
whole little water theory yeah so what
you do is divot just lightly okay and
then which color are you going for it
knocks over okay so get a little wet
make it kind of pasty great Nick it's a
little darker one more tense I'm gonna
use this to lie your upper lash line and
create almost a wing but definitely okay
so I'm gonna grab my little pencil brush
and that sound below love this color
literally it's so something I love the
shape in as well I'm gonna give this a
quick little spritz as well of some
setting spray it's really intensify okay
I'm going to yes thank you
[Music]
you like a lot on your lower lash line
like yeah I do I feel like it smells a
little bit of pageantry and below just
to kind of blend it out a little bit so
it like has something to kind of anchor
into the lower lash abundant than just
being a shimmering blue what is that
well this is a glitter oh my god that's
oh really okay we're gonna put this
below your eye just to really make it
fine you know your entire makeup line is
beginning cruelty for it yeah and you
are the face of any international
ambassador for the Humane Society okay
that's amazing
so obviously animals are very very very
yeah and you have like very cute John
but just on the way in because I have
four cats my mom has nine dogs
I saved a pigeon that's a little like
not pigeon heaven but like a pigeon
sanctuary so okay and then like a stray
cat and there's turkeys running around
in front yard that's in Tennessee so
okay but like long-term goal would be to
open like an animal sanctuary
really yeah oh my god that is so cool I
know you post pictures of cats all the
time Oh
such a crazy cat lady oh love I think it
brings you back to the roots yeah it
says it's like my roots but like a
refreshed adult mother woman version
okay well it's like that is one I all
complete so I think we will now go to
the other eye off-camera have a little
bit more chitchat though everything and
then we will come right back to you
sisters to finish off throws the look
I'm so happy that you have made me feel
like so myself and we just met today and
like funky and beautiful and fun and
cool like all the yes and like a very
unique son of yeah sorry guys when we
were back a bowl I looks are not
complete we decided to do a fun little
asymmetrical movement and we literally
just notice that her nails at the same
time that was not even on purpose so
that's kind of fun yeah obviously is the
change that Godzilla and also spaceship
to align the bottom and then threw on
some glitter as well catch up with a
dollar sign meets it catch it without a
dollar sign yes it's a little bit about
little bit of oh now we're gonna grab
the brand-new Kesha Rose eyeliner I'm
gonna grab the black side we are gonna
be helping on a lot so adding a little
bit here will just really help the lash
anchor now with a little bit more of a
backstabber I'm just going to buff out
the liner and it's used honey as a
highlighter how look at home buttons
that looks it's not showing as much like
era but it looks bright like beautiful
pink in person paint there this is
looking so beautiful I want to add back
a few your freckles yeah we try to do a
light covered face and I feel like we
didn't exactly succeed good times and
it's so hi baby and I just feel like I'm
really ready to go do something very fun
but I want to bring the funk let's talk
a little bit so this is your first of
all YouTube club right yeah okay I kind
of live for that yeah what an honor
you're like popping the cherry soccer
tutorial virginity okay love that have
you like watch a bunch of beauty beaters
and stuff like how did you find out
about the YouTube community I'm like
I know about you and I mainly know about
you
once I started like having the desire to
make makeup yeah so I was watching your
YouTube and like watching you put on
makeup and obviously like I'm so
impressed with what you do with it's
like a work of art face it's amazing
and I like can't quite do it to myself
yeah mm-hmm that's what you're doing it
but I'm learning and I have a had my
face be the canvas for a lot of makeups
murder what like make a break out with
me what really shows up what glistens on
camera what really covers out so things
like that I just feel like I've been
like a test subject for every kind of
makeup and yeah okay well I think we
have one last night which will be the
lips I know your lips are amazing thanks
girl I think we should do it like a
matching color please and it's gonna pop
on a later nude right in the center
are we Donna I think we're done okay
thank you for me I think we are I'm
gonna give you your last alibi at all
spreads of somewhat studies ready to
really lock it all in place and to make
you look dewy engorge
[Music]
sister this is literally and so much fun
I know this look it's so good you know
so much enjoyment of course oh my god I
feel like it turned out really really
beautiful a little asymmetrical just
worm toe and a half cut crease with a
little pop of color on the bottom we're
a little bit of glitter like really
feeling really you look gorgeous but I
had a mazing base to work on to the good
note so thank you thank you so much for
trying to get all this videos today I
really had the best time thank you for
inspiring me alter at my childhood true
to herself come to any shows and scary
movies die also congratulations on at
you're brand new at beauty lime
launching on December 30 sorry yes
Hiep dot-com cachorros beauty it's
beautiful de palette is it literally so
gorgeous and as you guys can tell we
both created Sun looks of it and you
guys are definitely going to check
everything else on the line all right
you guys I think that was everything
that we hoped with this video today
thank you so much for watching and thank
you so much for listening to us just get
glam together talk about all things
music I am so excited for everything
that you're working on and that's going
to be it's so incredible make sure you
guys stay tuned if we write a song
together who knows and if you did don't
forget to go to make a thumbs up down
below your love and support it really
means so much to both of us also if
you're not reading be sure to click that
big red subscribe button down below
come join this sisterhood I would love
to have you in the family and also click
that belt like on so you notification
every time I upload a brand new video if
you like to follow me on I make them
turn you can follow me on instagram
twitter and ticked off they're all to
st. charles and myself more behind the
scenes I thought this J tells the next
rise after Charles world if you want to
find me I am is who is on Instagram and
Kesha rose on Twitter this video is so
special that gusta sister Jada thank you
so much love for always falling in
supporting I love you so so so much and
it's not even funny and if you'll read
the next videos a sister shout out don't
forget to always reach Ava does they
will live on Twitter and also to my
youtube at post notifications
alright sisters thank you so much force
in this videos today I love you and we
will see you in the next
[Music]
[Applause]