hi sisters jean-charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel today i
entered with a very iconic and spooky a
sister special class ally tenor no we're
here today it to film a collaboration
that i am so beyond excited I did sweet
you I was on a trip board and that's
when I came across your use well it's
new of you but I never really watched
any videos and while I was watching
I might have watch like 15 videos and I
was laughing out loud DMD and I was like
we need to do a video together yeah I
was like we probably do I am so excited
to you guys because Kylie wanted me to
do her makeup and I was so down I think
you were notorious for it just beautiful
and light glam and part it's Halloween
you guys know this is like my time to
play when it comes to Halloween letting
you do whatever you want to do I'm your
model so whatever Kylie just launched a
beautiful new entire Halloween
collection we like Kylie cosmetics so
for today's video I don't have to give
her still a beautiful Kylie glam but
with the James Charles Halloween twist
I'm so excited
do you know we're doing that today no I
don't all I know is how you're gonna use
the palette yeah and I'm gonna be
skeleton yeah okay we're gonna start
into his sister's Callison I am so
excited
well my Halloween collection launches on
the twelve okay cause my next step
yeah 3 p.m. est so I wanted to do this
with you I thought it'd be fun to
celebrate the launch and also work
together I wasn't done like I don't do
much YouTube videos have you ever heard
of the collaboration before happens a
collab video Oh only me and Jordan but
lovey though not so true but I love
being the first the first exclusivity
contract yeah six months
um you made me you make it gold so oh
good I'm really glad about that we've
already been together for a while this
video thanks to be honest probably you
shouldn't definitely be honest with that
we lost yeah so uh spoiler alert and
sister surprise there's another video
coming later on in a few all the videos
sitting here for like hours but it's
cool we're just gonna have a positive
outlook because we really want to do
this for you guys and give you this
so yes where I can like we're coming
this first but this is the total while
this is the second video
[Music]
so so anyway now you can feel our change
that's unfortunate y'all really sad
that's the course of Halloween though we
were really positive about it we were we
caught we caught it I'm sure you can
feel how annoyed we are about this the
whole situation was very spooky but what
better way to do with the spooky
situation than to create a spooky
Halloween look on my favorite sister
Kylie so now we're going to start
filming this video before we both cry
more let's jump into the video let's get
started so first we around the palette
interpreted the shade Halloween love a
bunny sister we're gonna place this in
the crease I really haven't decided what
look I want to go for you but that's the
beauty of makeup you can kind of decide
as you go I want some level like an
orange moment on the top
I think I want to bring it really really
smokey onto the bottom lashline and wing
it out because I want to do at the
bottom have a highly space into a skull
a sister skull obviously the entire
makeup community always those following
all of your launches and I'm definitely
excited about all of them I saw you
tweeting about this Halloween collection
and you were like really really pumped
about it yeah you want to talk about it
I mean as everybody knows I do all my
own like reveal it's like my snapchats
because at a certain point someone asked
me to like why don't you just have
someone take the videos for you and then
program but I'm like I like to do it
myself because I know how I want my
makeup to look and I know I can get the
best lighting driver so after I showed
people I just felt the love and the
response and I made me remember why I do
what I do yeah so it was a pretty cool
feeling and it kind of reminded me what
I used to feel like when I first started
I get really excited about things I work
for a very long time I work really hard
on and I put like so much love into
everything right and I'm super I'm like
a hundred percent involved in creating
the packaging if I want this little
thing spot gloss or I want this metallic
material what kind of like cardboards
used I have someone who helps them with
renderings but I don't have anyone that
comes and shows me designs and say like
you should do this and I'm like okay
approved approved approved I tell my
designer what I want you on the
rendering so yeah I'm just like really
involved so then when I finally show
people and they get excited about it it
makes me very excited oh that's like
really everything yeah how long has
Kylie girls would have been around this
is you're about to be three how is like
starting a makeup line and change your
life because it I mean that
single-handedly change the beauty
community Thanks it changed my life
because it gave me purpose and it
allowed me to express myself it's really
my passion it's like makeup so to be
able to live out my passion every day
and like have fun while I work is
probably the best part doesn't want to
play with me called a quintessentially
enough very themes for this video I
started on a Halloween actually almost
three years ago as well so buy for your
anniversary is coming up oh my god am I
did a skeleton luck - yeah this is
simple circle love that I was just
playing around with some makeup but I
had to save from being a few different
clients before and I
but myself for the first time in our
yeah I was kind of fun and I actually
left a decent - so I just encounter
practicing it the first time I ever did
makeup is documented on Instagram so
literally every single time sighs
selling one day and like 10 years
they'll be able to literally pull yeah a
single time that I never wore makeup
it's like so crazy so it's just like a
really amazing journey from literally
just doing in my basement - no else and
having it as a real job think sister if
you're not watching YouTube because
literally when I'm not working I'm
probably watching YouTube videos what is
like a typical day of sister Kylie Kylie
cosmetics pretty much takes up most of
my days and work on the weekends are
usually just me and stormy I try to
spend as much time with her as possible
and then when I'm not spending time with
her I'm just working you know how
sisters for me sisters for me so good
she's a twit sold but she's just
changing every day she really is
becoming like a little person she
reminds me a lot of Kendall oh love that
personality sister Kendall oh my god I'm
sure like being a mother has obviously
changed your life the most ever in the
world I love that I really feel like
this is what I've always was meant to do
I used to have dreams even though like
as a young at a young age of like having
kids really like actual dreams mm-hmm
like it was just a part of my life that
I was crazy I don't feel like a
different person I just look at life a
little differently yeah do you wanna
have more I do want to have more when is
the question right I'd want to give Sur
me a brother or a sister sisters only of
course like I want seven girls and then
like maybe I'll consider a boy mm-hmm do
you have anyway because you have yes I
love bananas for me how I thought of
stormy Travis thinks that he thought of
stormy but it was you it was me I
remember the whole thing but he swears
he made her name up I was just looking
on
nature names like weather like earth
inspired willow was on there and then
that's already tail oh you need a willow
Jenner you think I'm probably taking I
know a willow it's man she is a great
willow I close with her so you know when
you you know someone will join you you
can't really do that any time
yeah that's taken anyways normals on
there yeah just storm like me oh yeah I
did stormy ie okay yeah and then it was
always stormy with an IE I mean I bought
custom things for her that's in her name
mommy
yeah but her the blog stormy ie and then
I didn't fully choose her name I wanted
to like have a week of just me and her
to see if I wanted to change it was that
one other name in mind but stormy always
felt like her name right when she was in
the womb it's almost like she chose her
name so then when they called me from
the birth certificate office and I was
finalizing the name they were like honey
I want to spell it I was like st o RM I
and they're like you sure and I'm like
yeah just an eye you just changed it
right there right then in there I taste
changes eyes and then they were like
okay and I hung up the phone I was like
damn I guess it's her name and then I
called Travis and I was like I didn't
put an e I just found it with an eye he
was like that's cool this looks gorgeous
oh my god interpret reading this here
big story trick-or-treating I'm gonna
take her to one house whose Christmas
ever and we live on a new street oh and
there's no houses on that that's
probably good for you though just me and
my neighbor I swear it's most quiet so
remember when on I'm gonna grab the
shade Hawks on my axe
love that name I record this on the
lower lashline I wanted to look a little
bit of a smoky purple moment really just
to dramatis eyes it and also like to tie
end the whole skeleton with it's about
to go on a very interesting Forbes
article was just posted they had crossed
paths with the article some think it was
everywhere anything congratulations
billionaire status kind of
destroy the club one day here is cause
are you the most excited in the entire
world you could put that in school I'm
so excited it's definitely been such a
blessing to do what I love every day I
worked so hard I'm starting only a few
years ago crazy we're very close yeah
you're only two years older than me it's
just really inspirational to see that
someone so young working so hard and
just like doing that you better major
source of inspiration to me and I'm sure
a ton of other kids out there as well we
really want to work hard and just do
something for themselves I've obviously
done a few reviews on you and like on
Kim's collections dozen people always as
I'm sure you know are always commenting
stupid stuff like they don't do anything
they have no talent
you can business Abby is a talent it's
definitely a talent the comment is it's
so old at this point like everybody's
talents are different and in my opinion
being able to use your own name and
likeness in order to build a brand is
one of the best homes in the entire
world and like I will stand by that
until the end of time people do the same
thing to me they're like oh my god James
like you've literally gotten famous over
scandals and like stupid viral photos
like I don't like okay look it works you
guys are all still here yeah hello well
I can see how hard you work and I know I
work so hard I could have been in the
same position and done it completely
differently and so could you right now
on top of that purple I want to layer a
little something over top we're gonna
grab the hell out gorgeous a glitter
eyes and just a little bit of a
concealer brush and just pop that right
on top of the cut crease that we've
already made just to intensify to make
it look a little bit more Matala
were you like an artist before makeup
yeah that was 2016 alright so that's
pretty much the eyes all complete but
we're not that with this look yeah
because I'm gonna turn you into a sister
skeleton let's do it I just want to take
it like to the next level copper go home
write down because honestly I never
really get crazy with my eyes like this
but I'm really serious like this is like
crazy for your eyes yeah
what's crazy for your eyes mmm a lot
more the mess but no I love it I think
it looks super mom I would actually go
out like this but let's do it
so another skeleton today I need to
sketch out like the highlights first
okay so then I can focus on the shadows
okay so I'm gonna use a white eyeliner
pencil and I start right up above you're
over here what is the craziest making
we've ever had on really probably
speaking of a crazy makeup looks what
has been your worst red-carpet moments
[Music]
just changed so much I see photos of me
all day that's just like nah girl like
whatever but I don't care I'm also not
the type of person that a lot of people
probably think I am except my true fans
have seen me like looking like super
crazy out I don't really care like I
leave the house every day not thinking
I'm Kylie really hmm
like I I don't really feel like I have
to leave the house in full like put
together outfit and glam and I'm just
like I hope no one catches me they
usually do I'm always crazy on the
streets but I can't think of one
specifically all I know is that my
change I wanted to catch out the teeth
on your lips did you have like a paper
makeup look that you've ever worn to a
red carpet or twin event before my
favorite makeup look was when I wore
teal hair long teal hair Arielle did my
makeup that's my favorite not because I
think it's the best we've ever done but
I think that started like how I like my
makeup done like we figured out my look
and then we perfected it alright we are
back and the highlights are all done I
was getting a little hot and steamy
we're gonna go to the shadows now just
because it comes to everything kind of
like backwards order because adding
weight over top a block is a lot harder
and the other way around
I'm actually just gonna lightly like
inner line I guess the black parts as
well because I'm actually gonna use the
purple shade hacks on my axe to blend
everything and it's like a midnight
skull instead of just like luck makes it
more fun on some dimension
what sister would use here the closest
whether I know definitely the growing up
throw the closest in age yeah right now
I talk to them all for like different
things daily probably Chloe Kim since
we're both like just have three babies
together pretty much they up ladies all
day your mom in Chicago we're taking a
bath last night together in my house
blah blah they're just all like really
are so now those lines are all lined out
thank God I'm you get to move on to the
actual pump part which is going to be
once again the eyeshadow so I'm gonna go
to the shade hacks on my axe and I'm
gonna start using this a little bit of
settings Brian how does it like growing
up in the public eye in spotlight it has
like I mean I definitely think that it's
not for everybody and I was chosen to be
in this position cuz I feel like God
knows that I'm strong mm-hmm because a
lot of people just come even times I'm
like
really but I feel like it's just my life
like I don't know anything I don't know
normal is also I have like the best
family ever we're all in it together and
the second one of us like gets out of
line or like right but if way back to
like if I didn't have my family
especially I feel like I would just I
mean they keep me grounded too right
it's important mm-hmm
gotta stay on ball to finish off the
school I'm just gonna grab a little
purple duo crow highly a moment and just
places on some of the kind of center
areas just to give a nice little blue
purple highlight Oh everything that's
fun so the skull is basically all
complete and to finish off Kylie's look
today I'm gonna grab the brand new
highlighter and the shade go ghost this
color is so cool it's like it kind of
looks a little green minty yeah but it
comes off on the skin pretty gold oh my
god it's like oh wow that is cool
that was pretty fast like I'm amazed at
how fast you do this I told you I could
do special [ __ ] this is like very very
cool you think means a lot
perhaps I'll have to try it out give you
one last spritz just everything together
[Music]
I think it's like really everyday
wearable no this is the most glam
gorgeous school definitely I've ever
seen and I'm very impressed so much fun
with you today but yeah but here all day
cause we're here for two hours it's been
eight lots of Huffman's bad it was worth
it and I have fun I don't think I do you
good thank you so much for coming on my
channel this is so much fun
of course I want to do so many large
yeah definitely down cuz since I have
money six month exclusivity yes we
better we better really use it up yeah
we got a lot more coming for you guys we
have a few other ideas and the
pipeline's that me and sister Kylie
definitely want to work on together and
you can enjoy this video today and you
like Kylie's little spooky Halloween
glam please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and come
subscribe if you have not already come
join the sisterhood we were eight
million sisters talking about to have
you join the family and also click the
belt icon so you can get a notification
every time I upload a brand new video if
you like to follow me on our makeup turn
you can follow me on Instagram or
Twitter they're both says shames her on
my snapchat from world but it seems like
top is seeing stars with an extra ask
dr. Charles
Wow a Kylie Jenner yeah this video is
that sister shout out goes to sister
Hales thank you so much lo for always
following its supporting oil every
little you so so so much and if you like
to be the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to always a retweet my
video links when they go live on a
Twitter we really do all right you guys
thank you so much for watching this
videos today we love you and we will see
you in the next one
[Music]