hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel you
guys I am very very excited for today's
video because we're doing a challenge
that I really never thought I'd be doing
now you guys know as an artist I'm
always looking for new people and it
comes to follow to keep me inspired and
wanting to create now to my all-time
favorite pages to follow on Instagram
are by the usernames shine and shadows
and Gabrielle with access now their work
are both so beyond incredible I've
gotten so much inspiration from them and
have recreated many looks on my page but
there's just something a little bit
different about both of their makeup
looks and that is that most of them are
on their arms now I'm not gonna lie when
I first saw these arm looks I was a
little bit confused and the first
thought that went through my head was oh
my god what youtuber is really
struggling for ideas now but when I
thought about a little bit further if
the exact same thing is doing a face
chart which is basically practicing a
makeup book on a piece of paper before
doing on your face but this name is just
on your arm it's done I honestly have no
idea how I'm going to do in this
challenge today as many of you guys know
when I was younger I used to draw and
paint portraits all the time so I'm
pretty familiar with being able to
recreate the human face and I also do
makeup pretty much every single day as
well and I like to think that I'm
relatively good at it so combining the
two could be easy but these artists are
also insanely insanely talented and
create the most beautiful colorful
glittery or blended makeup looks so this
could be a major major fail but
regardless I am so excited it's your
head the sound today and without further
ado let's get started
[Music]
all right you guys let's just jump right
into this challenge today as you can see
my full face of makeup is already on and
fully complete and that is because we're
gonna be focusing on my arm today
hello second camera angle now the first
step of my arm
makeup routine is going to be to apply a
coat of foundation all the way around my
arm up just to even out all the skin and
for today's video I am very very excited
to tell you guys I have partnered with
wrap on to show you at their brand new a
photo ready candidate foundation now in
today's look I am actually wearing this
on my face as well and the shade is 320
and before I even tell you guys that the
find that things about this I will go
ahead and say it and this is not even
part of the sponsorship if this is the
only one of the best color matches I've
ever had regardless of the sponsorship
I'm gonna be reaching for this a whole
lot more so y'all stop drawing me but
let me tell you because actually is a
really mom foundation to the brand new
Revlon Photoready canon foundation comes
in 31 different shades of a medium
buildable coverage natural finish
formula it includes antioxidants and
anti blue light ingredients infuses
vitamin E and also is anti pollutant as
well which means it basically keeps out
all the disgusting crusted bus and stuff
that's floating around in the air kind
of good wearing it on my face and blend
it out so easily and I will say feels
extremely late on the skin as well and
it also provides coverage while still
letting your natural beauty like my
freckles shine it through and best thing
of all it only retails for 1099 so good
so crushed you guys don't have to check
it out and thank you once again to
Revlon for working me on today's video
alright so since this is the first time
of me literally ever try this out I
think for my first look I want to start
off with something easy know if it goes
well I will definitely do another one a
but I want to do this look from my a
paint-by-numbers
photo obviously not the whole numbers
and white part but like the actual glam
that I had on and this one I is really
really pretty and I think I could kind
of do an okay job of putting that on my
arm maybe let's try it so I think I want
to start doing my eyes in the same order
that I would doing normal I look sad
which is starting off with my eyebrows
this could be a major major mistake
because if the eyebrows aren't looking
good the entire look is already
cancelled but that's good because it
means we get to keep doing the challenge
until it works that's not good
looks like my literal worst nightmare
I'm gonna grab my Anasazi at number 12
brushing my Anasazi at dipbrow pomade so
looking at this photo of my eyebrows
definitely like the biggest thing
shocker
my eyebrow and inner corner pretty much
ended the same place but the tail and
that eyeball do not let me turn off like
up here my eyebrows go up at a pretty
soft angle and then it kind of goes
straight out I'm going to incorporate
this freckle and two into my brow so it
doesn't show at the end
okay eyebrows are pretty thick as well
let's be real like I said this is the
first try it's okay if it's not perfect
if I pull this this way I can they kind
of blend out the dipbrow my brother
definitely thick all the way through but
they do have like a somewhat bit of
ombre from like very very filled in and
the tail to a little bit more sparse and
like hairy and airy in the front of the
brow so I want to try to recreate that
same look today I'm just setting that
different place using tea from my
palette then it's blending that shade in
towards the front a little ombre moment
I guess like another angle brush now and
another dark brown shade I'll grab Benny
and T from my palette I'll use this to
like sketch in actual hairs I'm not
gonna go outside of my brow lines as
well because I definitely took rush my
brow hairs upwards so they're nice and
textured kind of good okay okay now I
need to do that again I think mine are
much thicker than what I made this we're
just gonna do it in my head my brows
look like which is a lot thinner and
prettier than what they really are okay
more dip brow mmm okay this needs to be
art or whatever more straight words so
I'm actually going to interrupt this
freckle right here who loved that I
think my freckles knew I was filming
this video I just wanted to really align
themselves so I could draw my eyebrows
in the right place so thank you for that
try just filling this and now saying is
nothing that I did beforehand except now
we're doing it backwards blending in
some of those hairs using a tea from the
pallet once again just to fit a more
like ombre shadow brow color and then
using a tea and Benny
we already the sounds that this is our
practice so I'm going to not worry about
the shape too much wow this looks so
awful I'm scared so grabbing a little
bit of concealer on why you same angle
brush leaves to cut my brows I'm just
going to cut my brows just going in very
very carefully with the excess concealer
then just patting it into a place so we
can use it as an eyeshadow base no doing
the other brow as well these are
definitely not even I already know that
for a fact I'm thinking maybe I should
like add in my nose contour now just
gonna got my regular anastacio contour
kit and my angled brush from Maya James
Charles brush set and then just contour
it and this looks awful for some reason
this contour powder it's creating like a
grey tone over top of my concealer which
has literally never happened before
considering I use this combination all
the time which is really annoying that
this is not happening on my arm where
I'm trying to create a look but to work
just going to ignore it for now and
hopefully it fixes itself later I think
I need to put in my like I liked lash
line first so I know where everything
else is supposed to go and it's pretty
much just a straight line all the way
across so if that's my lash line
okay now same thing on the other arm oh
god what's this eyeballs looking wonky
we're gonna leave it at that for right
now I think I just do when I said on the
normal order yeah okay so I'm gonna grab
an hour 39 brush and start off with a
little bit of code James and put that in
the crease actually packing it on there
and then blending it out just like we do
it on normal or so techniques and just
furthering out the edges onto that
concealer so it looks nice and even yeah
gorgeous bring it into the inner corner
as well but kind of fading it out
because we have that glitter going on
there later of course feeding it into
the nose contour a little bit just like
I always do same thing on the other side
as well
I hate you my cardio bracelets are in
the way of me being able to blend I
absolutely hated that Louis cut that out
now with an anima for fights to Express
I'm gonna dip into 10% off which is the
darker brown and uses to add some like
contour into the crease that doesn't
even exist in these before bringing it
in
and blending it up and just like before
pulling the shade it pretty far out as
well other side to match he's a little
bit of no beans to add even more depth
with that same em four five six brush
and just keeping those kind of more on
the outer third or the outer two-thirds
rather of the crease now I am going to
start sketching out my block winged
liner using a little brush and some
spooky from the palette and once you
buff this into the lash line that we
drew in earlier starting off thin and
then going right upwards and pulling it
right up and then buffing this block
into the crease for some out of
dimension just using this Stila liquid
metals to cut my crease to a nice little
round shape Oh still bad yes oh hello oh
there's one right here
well what do we do now let me add in
some more black because they can really
fix a lot of problems this is not
staying block as I wanted it to be
that's decent looking okay yeah okay I
know it's not grabbing a little bit of a
face and ring light with a little spritz
of some setting spray mama I'm going to
pump it in the inner corner a little bit
on the brow bone too
now I'm going to create my little lower
lash line well it's gonna get covered
off but I need to put it there anyway
okay so we're gonna put some same cards
we use below the lash line and then
using a little bit of both coaches and
10% off to blend those shades out oh not
awful bad but not awful now have it on
that eyelashes which is where this could
get really bad really really fast oh my
god okay
okay hey I'm going to do this again the
other I forgot about the other idea no
no don't go sin no no there's only one
eye for me how are we on this level
delusion and we're only 30 minutes into
filming those the skin not happening
today we're just gonna speed through the
second eye
[Music]
I think I'm done I'm scared to look at
it
this is my first time ever doing this at
least I gave the precursor am I already
planning on doing a second look at this
one fails so let's give the Green
revealed see what we got going on Oh
oh my god why how did the eyeballs end
up like that so looking at both eyes and
both brows
they both look actually really really
good but they're just not even like it's
like a like this and pull the skin down
already looks a lot oh this is so hard
oh you know what I want to do Oh scary
see well imagine this is a thumbnail I
[Applause]
[Music]
have to photoshop that all right you
guys let's be honest with each other
here our first attempt at our arm Fisher
is definitely a major fail I think is
actually the first time we've done a
makeup challenge on this channel and
it's been like a major major major awful
failure but we do not take no for an
answer we don't like to fail and we
never back down from a challenge so I
really want to try this again and take
what I learned this one runs in the
Pyatt next time which is of course that
my arm is round so I need to try really
hard to make these like even I doesn't
want to pay attention to the fact that
one closer to my wrist should be up and
the one closer to my elbow should be a
little bit more down just to offset the
like scan it movement I'm gonna go ahead
and wipe this off and I'll be right back
to try it look number two
so for this next look I am deciding to
challenge myself which is a brave
decision considering the first one was
already challenged and did not go well
but you know what I looked at some of
the videos that Gabrielle and shine
shadows had posted on their Instagram
accounts and I noticed on all of their
videos they started off with the
eyebrows and like eyeballs already kind
of like pre sketched out so they had
like a rough idea of where to put things
which hello like I don't know why I
didn't think about to begin with so for
this second look I picked out this photo
that I posted on my Instagram literally
over a year ago I actually did a look on
this I think this is in my coming-out
story video this is literally what my
favorite looks I've ever created in my
like entire makeup career I think it is
so stunning
so I want to try to recreate like this
exact like eye area on my arm including
the eyes at the different angle and the
eyes being open so this might mess me up
even more than the first time around
but at least I can say that I tried and
if I get this it'll be really cool and
fun in front of so let's just jump right
in again let me grab my Nastasia brow
pencil in the shade soft brow which is a
nice erasable color I'm gonna draw my
eyeball right here actually me to put in
my eyebrows for our still that is a good
brow okay I'm happy with that eyebrow
that means my eyeball would be right
about here to draw and buckles and
beauty marks are literally landing and
they're perfect places and then okay so
if my brows here I have to imagine like
my nose bridge is coming down right here
so like my contour is gonna be I'm gonna
put my contour here I know that actually
Bulger's is gonna be like here oh my
body is meant for this so this means
this line goes right up about here and
the curves end and there's the shadow in
here you actually got lost but way too
close when those we're just gonna be
here the shadow going this way that
means the brow is gonna go right here at
the same angle and is gonna stop right
there cuz she's thick but she gets cut
off so then my eyeball goes down right
here so I will number two
is here and goes this okay like that and
then my left eyebrow does tend to droop
down a little bit in photos which is
she's drooping here about us for sure
now that I hope the rough draft kind of
sketched out it's looking okay not gonna
lie I'm going to fill in the eyes first
which is what Gabrielle did on all of
her videos so I'm going to grab the
Jeffrey Stehr armor druglord liquid
lipstick and use this to fill them in
set this down with some flash back from
the palette let's draw in some nice
eyeballs okay now I'm gonna shade this
in a little bit okay that is a good
eyeball if I ever did see one truly
adding in tiny little lines for our
details that is a good eyeball look at
that that is so professional and famous
I mean so this one is going like right
here now it's time to fill in the
eyebrow oh okay I'm just using team from
the palette and putting in same thing
like the day brought before but into the
tail and I'm just going to use the
excess and blend it forward at this time
not being at so intense and softer and
less scary okay how did that still get
dark that's a good that's good that's a
good eye brow I'm really happy with that
now I'm going to card out the brow what
some concealer underneath that eyeball
tail just because we will push out of
there in a little bit this is already
turning out way better than the first
time I am first going to grab a pencil
brush that is stained with a little bit
of purple and dip in to escape from the
palette and I'm going to use this to
build our outer V of the eye and that's
too big I'm not this whole life I'm
gonna grab this Sigma e 21 brush instead
boosting I run it to about here and then
really brought it up nicely to about
right there it almost think I had some
more escape right into here this is
actually before the palette was even a
things I don't even know why using this
original video probably the 35 be
alright pecan but forgotten the purple
also Wow
below my lash line so I'm gonna bring
that
well leaving a tiny little gap for that
light blue liner that we'll put in later
in this vision oh look I also do
remember that I did a purple liner so
I'm going to throw that on now before
the rest of the look comes on just so I
can kind of keep it in place
ninety to blend that out with a little
bit but love that with a pencil brush
and blend over the edges carefully then
I'm gonna use a little bit of it you're
cutting the bright red and that same
brush I guess we're just sticking with
this one honestly love that letting it
together no need to bring it a little
bit more single because it got a little
bit lost in the blending process now we
go a little bit of an M four five six
and dip into five one eight and blend
out this top edge I wanna clean just the
ads up with concealer just to come on
the original luck it is a little bit
more like pointed so but I kind of like
just loosely hold a thin it might kind
of shape it a little bit more - oh yes
that looks so good and also
simultaneously fresh okay great I'm
really happy right now okay so now I'm
going to Rob hello-hello from my palette
and a little pocket rush and we're going
to use this shade to cut my crease I'm
going to overlay this right over top of
the purple oops oh I don't want to get
on there just like when I did the
original look I'm going to make sure to
bring out this color all the way into
that inner corner and this cut crease
actually went far above the crease which
is really really cool this is more of
like a messy stuff a crease and I got
really love how it turned out so it's
going to bring that into there to grab a
little bit of acappella with that same
brush and use this to kind of blend
together the blue in the purple we use
this to lightly blend oh the edge can
also have a little bit of this hello
right on that inner corner and bring it
onto the lash line
but it gonna be a little bit of Betty on
a tiny little brush this is the M of 515
like hell out look at this and I'm gonna
use this to add some black very little
bit of block just that steady a little
bit to the army I've been here my
jeffree star cosmetics liquid lipstick
in the shade a jawbreaker and this is
from the brand new blue blood collection
well it's not actually this one's been
around for a while but it just realized
with the blue bonnet collection which I
was so excited about and proud enough
sister Jeffrey I believe it's sold out
by the time of this video is up so I
mean go get it but like good luck I'm
going to use this a tiny little liner
brush to lie to my lower waterline and
then adding in a tiny little bit of drug
lord in there just to look make it look
like it's like kind of wet then I'm
gonna grab a little bit of the Mac
reflex teal and add this on top then
just using a tiny little bit of glitter
adhesive I'm going to pop on a few
little chunky glitters gonna use a
little bit more of a ring lay on a tiny
little brush once again and highlight
the brow bone now I think it's time to
draw on the lashes so now I hope to draw
in my eyeliner thank God that was
literally this bullseye night ever I've
ever diddly done did ja know what's got
you in the lashes going very very slowly
toward them look a little close at first
for the bottom lash line did add a
little individual so I'm gonna add in a
little spiky right here and some more
little Spanky's that is literally so
good oh my gosh you guys okay I think
that is officially one out of my two
eyes complete which was the far harder
one I am going to now do the other one
quickly and the challenge will finally
be complete
[Music]
oh my gosh you guys literally five hours
later I was so convinced this is going
to be an easy video to film and I of
course was wrong but finally my second
eye look is complete and I'm actually
very very happy with it
beautiful Wow look at that artistry I
went into the shell ecstatic not really
knowing what to expect and this was way
way harder than anticipated oh my god I
really thought this is gonna be a quick
little one-and-done video no absolutely
not but that is of course because you
guys know I never like to give up on
anything I will probably openly and
honestly say this is like the worst
we've done a challenge so far I really
get a lot of our challenge videos I
usually start off really really scared
and then it somehow it turns out pretty
good at the end it's okay I mean looking
at this like it's okay it definitely
could be a whole lot worse I think we
definitely learned a lot today this is
great practice but I think ever wanna be
on a level even close to Gabrielle or
shine shadows I'm gonna probably have to
do this on my arm a million more times
so it seems like for now I'm just gonna
stick to my normal I shadow on my actual
eyelids if you guys enjoyed this makeup
challenge today please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
show your sister love and support it
really does help me out and mean the
opposite world to me and also if you
have not ready make sure to click that
Baker it subscribe button and come join
these sisterhood we are 15 million
sisters Tong and I would absolutely love
to have you join the family and also do
not forget to click that Bell icon so
you can notify each and every time I
upload a brand new video if you'd like
to follow me other makeup journey can
follow me on instagram twitter they're
both so same charles myself we're behind
the scene itself is janetrose the
texture has after charles this video
censor shadow goes to sister Adam thank
you so much slope for always appalling
in supporting I love you so so so much
and if you look to the next videos a
sister shadows don't forget to always
retweet my videos when they go live on
Twitter all rights this is that eyes
only efforts today's video thank you so
much for watching it thank you once
again to Revlon for sponsoring this
video you guys at the photo ready candid
foundation is it we've been building for
almost six hours now and it still looks
absolutely perfect and yes I am being
sponsored to say so but like the proof
is right here
I'm obsessed and definitely plan on
wearing this a whole lot more I think I
just found a new Holy Grail foundation
although they said
love you guys so much I will see you at
the next one
[Music]