is what you say that's what you say it's
gonna take us eight hours to use
Charleston welcome back to our YouTube
channel as you can see if we were trying
to once again with the sister squad is
that what we're is no it's not I cannot
wait for your video to go off at all the
comments when you [ __ ] that's what you
named it doesn't go baby
everyone knows that yeah only we can
escape it yeah it's haunting me every
day you're welcome saying so we're about
together because that is sister's movie
season and we are celebrating Halloween
as the sister squad it's gonna be fine
and go to infraction if he's not we
already do collabs on to the twins and
Emma's channel and now we have to do one
here so we're gonna be filming probably
for the next roughly fourteen hours
which easily I mean hopefully a week
fourteen hours a day in the Halloween
spirit
interrupting me [ __ ] ass there's a
sister secret if you pay close attention
to this video there's a trick-or-treat
in this yeah this how much one's the
trick and which ones that show you
that's a tree turn me into a pumpkin so
you wanna your pumpkin - bet yeah I do
never really been a pumpkin before so we
figured it'll be fine and good and funky
and fresh - all do like half face
tutorials mostly guys are gonna be here
for 12 hours and I don't want to do a
whole place I'm a commander Freddy but
he's almost cooler doing so Facebook as
well we're picking one way to like
incorporate the real face into the half
a story then we figured it'd be fun to
do my sister's stapler first this
awesome sister staples is scarce it's
just tables so not fit me so special
attacks that I don't know how to do but
we're gonna figure it out together
you just staple gun my face true so I
continue to use this stuff this is nose
and scar wax so it's basically like
moldable skin a second along the line
good I think I'm just gonna like make a
big worm yeah and then you put the
staples in it Japanese spooky ghost
stories do I actually really do do you
yeah apparently like I saw a ghost when
I was a baby
what so my dad told me and he doesn't
believe in ghosts at all like my dad has
a complete like disbeliever and then he
like ghosts or anything like that
and what thinks he saw one when I was
little after like we took badness or
whatever we came downstairs and we
always used to watch TV like feel a
little bit before into bed and then we
had like a little couch so we're really
indication of my dad where are you guys
on your couch watching TV really we
don't want to go there tonight
why not really cuz the mean weight is
sitting there like straight up what and
he goes oh what meaning you know okay
didn't want to freak us out or anything
so he's like okay are you guys saying
just go to bed or whatever we'll do
something else
imagine being my dad alone oh I think
freaking out he said he like felt so
you're that night I'm really rightfully
so and then he like the next day Leaburg
like see dude's nothing
you know you think I really why doctor
like all the horror things that I like
watching okay now that's all on there
it's all weird ugh I guess we just like
flatten it out now gonna use my fingers
and I'm going to kind of blend out the I
think I know I'll be there to support
you
thank you you're doing a great job
sweetie thinks we do something you like
put on your finger to like make it blend
easier geez
don't spit no no I'm not letting you
spit on my face he was literally just
gonna spit on his hand yeah what might
work no we're gonna glue down Ethan's
bra what is your favorite halloween
costume you've ever worn
I like this skeleton thing I did two
years ago it's pretty cool we're like
the class the eyes outfit with a
skeleton oh man that picture that wasn't
the first time I wore makeup for
Halloween what's really we've heard in
the intro that this is our one year from
diverse er II will you take now this is
our one year freshman your anniversary
first time we ever met was like right
between really easily you put this up on
your face before no how do you know that
this is proving to be already too much
more difficult than I ever thought it
was gonna be really yeah it's okay you
got this okay I think it's time not to
make like the gosh now I'm gonna take
this and like cut you open
okay
okay now that all the sky rocks is on
there I think I'm just going to have
some liquid latex and pour into a
plastic cap and I'm going to use this to
go over top of the scar wax to lock it
in place and to like blend the edges and
I'm just gonna use a beauty blender for
this it's kind of ruin this beauty
blender
I'm basically just going over all the
edges with the liquid latex and I'm
gonna do this a few times in a few
different layers hopefully one together
the skin and the scar wax Gracie please
get his gum so now this car would sell
on and set in place you see liquid latex
I'm gonna grab with just some air spot
powder I don't want to be a fluffy brush
those are the good basic stuff no this
is the primo stuff so I don't want to
set this face okay so I need to like put
a little bit of foundation on your like
normal side let's really blend this
together so I'm gonna try to grab some
form this way I'm gonna be your shade
probably not
I did kind of matches better than you
okay I'm gonna stipple this on for a
real one
oh this is actually looking okay yeah
yay I think so the camera cut out at
some point are we surprised no but now
we're gonna paint Ethan orange and we
just did that by mixing together they
read on the yellow change from the
makeover flash palette from the fresh
patch palette just love the orange red
sheets and measurements palette
[Music]
Isis or something I'm gonna like go
through with yellow and put highlights
in like stripes oh my god kind of sister
spooky and good kind of yeah getting
really good I was that layer over top a
quick layer of translucent powder to
Sephora balloon with any eyeshadows just
to make sure it's locked in place
because they don't wanna ruin all my
brushes oh wow look at that maybe did
that yellow eyes won't you give a
shout-out to this palette grid oh no I
have to keep it to keep it on the DL for
now - good good you can give your seat
it's too good I can't get the sisters
taken away maybe later maybe oh my god
TT he did he did okay so now I need to
make the pumpkin dance what are those
called that the crevasses the Cree says
the pumpkin dibbles yeah cue the pumpkin
there falls just gonna have an M 4-3-3
brush and dip into a like burnt orange
color props a nice and rusted color
thank you oh my god this is so good this
was very good
oh my god now gonna take a little fluffy
but I don't know if this a thumbs brush
I'm gonna use a dark cool toned brown
shade and I'm gonna use this like sketch
don't burn this Mason okay just sketch
out the little pumpkin lines for Holly
this way kind of right in the center and
like make them like nice and rounded
[Music]
[Applause]
so good Wow oh my gosh Tee tee hey I'm
just gonna set that in place using a
black shadow time for mouth time yeah I
have to like think about it inverted
okay so that's pretty much the painting
and the makeup all complete its don't
smile at Rufus sorry dad so I'm actually
really happy with how this turned out I
was really nervous at first low-key not
even why but it came together so we do
have a few of my steps for the finishing
touches and one of those is going to be
obviously Ethan had them it's hard gosh
through his face we need to add some
special effects and some spooky a sister
a blood sister blood when it's gonna
take this is whoa oh my god second to
last time we got some sister staples
from Staples ha ha I'm going to put
these in eat them but and at the scar
wax so doesn't actually stop him that's
how he did that but I probably end up
stabbed him you probably well a little
bit but it's okay we should do it in
blood - yeah this isn't so crazy oh my
gosh oh my god last touch I have this
contact it is black out so it's gonna be
my whole entire eyelid black I'm just
gonna put it on the pumpkin side cuz it
was pretty anticlimactic because like my
eyes are already dark
that's so so crazy
are we done I think so are they next
you're sticking to the whole like part
face things great - gonna have the same
thing and Grayson's the fact we'll be a
mummy yes but like peeling off oh yeah
like a mummy but the wraps are falling
off this I dunno how to do stuff good
you do yeah I do not know do Ethan's
imma end up working you figured it out
yes okay so we're gonna sketch your face
first okay
we're how much we want to be like
mummified even though just at this
time for you to the other to the other
side mm-hmm sure why not
I hate you if I want the ROPS to really
underneath the peeling up do I need to
do the wraps are coming off and
underneath it just like beat up like my
skin is peeling kind of how do you not
company what I'm so what all right so
picture of a mummy underneath my face
will be all gray like decane you know
what I mean
and then the wraps are on top of that
yeah what's underneath your cat's me
yeah yeah yes you are good good good
you're good God or something
now what's underneath your thanks medium
a wrap on your face your face yes
exactly
okay so basically my face is underneath
it into the wraps are falling off wait
so what you want me to do to your face
that because zombie look it's dead like
my face is dead on this side like gray
its it's like old like decaying oh I'm
gonna do that then we're back to where
we started well you see it was the face
of green yes so I think we're just gonna
use liquid latex and a lot of toilet
paper to do this okay was gonna be
putting on lots of layers of it Grayson
what's your favorite Halloween memory I
think when I was little my mom used to
get really creative she's an artist of
russia she does hair day you know I mean
she's a really crafty she was also like
really painting enjoying myself like
that we would always make like all our
Halloween time like homemade Halloween
costumes like we would never buy all the
custom from the store just wasn't like
the thing we did her family I remember
going into a Halloween store when I was
little and I was like wait they sell
costumes here like I was like everyone
was supposed to make them I would always
help my mom like bake my costume Ethan
wouldn't he would just sit there kind of
do the same thing
funny I remember that stachy treats in
my pillowcase because I also didn't ever
have yeah you can run what the real ones
are a pillowcase and because your
parents are cheap
I remember asked my mom we can get a
little pumpkin head no she's a cute
pillowcase no no use water I don't want
to spit well that's right it's gonna set
in place once again using somewhat
translucent powder to lock all the late
nights in place just like you said we're
gonna do a quick coat of light
foundation on at the normal skin side
and it's gonna use a more Fiji one rose
just stipple it on now we're gonna take
this and just peel it off I'm gonna peel
up the one side that the mummy is going
to be layered underneath the mummies
within me Oh kind of fun oh okay I feel
really Melvindale okay now I'm gonna
grab a pair of scissors that I'm going
to go and just I'm just going to trim
off any excess that's like really doing
that kind of fish mm-hmm should you be
careful no and I'm not gonna go really
fast but I am I'm gonna kind of do this
carelessly not to cut crazy no but what
I care what sleaze the word I think I'm
gonna okay just just say no gonna go
carefully because I want the edges to be
messy so it like looks real
well don't cut your friends this is
better Halloween psi from me and Grayson
to you
we should probably paint your eye and
mouth black before we put on the texture
yeah yes so I'm gonna do that
[Music]
Suncoast once did you thanks for asking
yeah I woke up little boy little cowboy
at the bottom of my bed really literally
just staring at me
it was in fact bright out but my shades
were just closed and he was just looking
at me I didn't pay attention to his face
but I saw his whole outfit
he had the boots of the Spurs he had did
and he had a bottom I'm skinny he had
like just like suspenders and like was
wearing a cowboy hat a little a little
badge i sat up rub my eyes open them
again it was still there and we're just
going through was just rocking back and
forth forgive me like this Oh God
Oh was it young either I was like I was
like ten
and I was like Ethan I knew it wasn't
heated Bunnykins room was across the
hall from me so I screamed like you know
my door was open a little bit of cracked
ice cream Ethan the thing is still there
I'm moving around like rubbing my eyes
like what he viewed part of my face it's
still just there and ice cream eating
the ice cream eat that ice cream Ethan
he doesn't wake up coz he never wakes up
and then I think my mom said like what
my mom's dancers already like what are
we getting ready for the day I look at
my door to like talk to her through the
coz she's down the hall which I just
hang with my voice down like out the
door and I looked back and it was gone
that's so crazy
I believe in ghosts but I don't believe
like oh like someone tells me they saw a
ghost when did you really write you
don't even have always been like that
but it wasn't scared I wasn't scared to
go to sleep at night and like usually it
would be like I'm a [ __ ] like when I
watch scary movies
uh I'm too afraid to sleep alone like
the sinister the ghoul ugly hate him
he's so scared dude don't be predictive
of all I always imagined him just
staring at me when I was like
asleep were you actually said uh yeah
very during the movie I was watching it
and even probably I think it was with
the girl yeah and I had my eyes closed
the whole time didn't care
didn't try to be a tough guy except for
the fact that I was very scared of the
movie and I kept my eyes closed I don't
really get scared by things that easily
I don't know why everyone thinks not
like free usually yeah well I do look
kind of look at mommy if you look
head-on okay what's up guys I just rose
from my tomb and hey just going to set
that liquid latex in place now I'm gonna
take a pair of tweezers and I'm gonna
start picking out grace and skin pick it
the texture looks good huh it's
disgusting it looks like it got dug up
from a tube you know but there we go and
of good I'm gonna grab now I guess I
foundation call her but like mixed it
with like white and like green but the
level is really great like yellow what's
that for dad oh here we go no that's
like on there's a face I want to go over
with white and gray to like make it not
look like that now I'm gonna use lots of
black and spooking it up a little bit
I'm gonna paint black underneath the
lifted the skin areas as well to show
through the fact that there's like
lifting and dimension even if you kinda
look like a spook money yeah I do kind
of good kind of fresh kind of spooky
kinda fun
so once again I got out a little bit of
a black shadow just to set some of that
black paint in place did he do the
shadow from oh she's really pigmented
how that I've been using a lot recently
white it's literally the brightest worst
is a good thing yeah well that is really
rude hmm
so mrs. brightest flashback Mary he's
got some blood blood well I was like
crusted ride by myself okay now do we do
the cause we have to yeah okay how do we
do that
I think just have it hanging yeah yeah
thanks Grayson thank you three
innovative Halloween ideas are we done
yeah so he's treating me just go - lets
go - you should be like I feel like
everyone's a skeleton but it's a James
Charles skeleton do you know what I'm
saying
it's our v of filming now are you sick
yeah I think so same the makeup looks
are doing well they're mean I on the
other hand are not so what is beauty
hashtag name so that means you're doing
something racist forever look today we
decided let's do something kind of easy
so I don't die and also say like I don't
want to die either because like sitting
for me oh you're so brave I know I think
you can app really are so we're gonna do
a a sister skeleton and you're probably
thinking whoa it was so loosely install
tutorials and I'm thinking the mesial
but you know what it's gonna be fine and
it's gonna be fresh and we're gonna make
it something unique we're gonna make it
different because instead of being on
someone else's head now it's on mine you
okay no okay none of us actually go to
Halloween party still none of us are
gonna get to use them for absolutely
anything cuz we're too busy working
no we're literally gonna finish this two
three the more and then I'll wipe it off
my makeup for the next party and have to
do work yes I am yam not get anything
yes yep so hopefully you enjoy this
video or else we're gonna be really sad
it's gonna start my sketching out I've
never had like a good Halloween costume
before like I swear to god they've
always been lazy so like this is the
first time I'm gonna post something on
Instagram it's like actually putting
effort into Halloween maybe I'll get
some nice sister likes it's a really
endearing to see James actually like
exhausted by something because like I've
never seen him like tired or like
whatever feel like he's always bald oh
he gets tired but I feel like he's
always just going and then like feeling
like it's like okay that's it so he's
like actually tired by this video and I
think it's really good for his
personality development
[Music]
let's return for movie oh my god do you
like it
absolutely I've always loved scary
movies my favorites
Coraline and The Shining the best you
like The Shining it's so good
do you just eat it yeah you like it no
you hated it was it scary or just you
didn't like I wasn't scary it's not
scary
I know iesous smooth oh oh no it's not
like a horror movie it's more just like
I liked it for the aesthetic and the
like part of it more but I could sell
more movies so I consider at that do you
like or like I actually have never seen
Coraline but I want to so about you
would love it I think I know what you
would really love it it's so that it
feels like a movie for like forever it's
just so good it's for like it's for us
angsty kids who can't like to get scared
and [ __ ] now I'm gonna fill it in with
black right now literally delusional oh
it's so delusional what this effort okay
oh that's amazing focus turns to the
tunes
okay you're at a Halloween party okay
well I think we're getting somewhere
with this you show up you're dressed up
as a woman Bromley and you're looking
around and you're trying to find a man
to date right cuz this is like the only
time that you go out but I won't see you
yeah that's true mood for me as well no
one can get mad at me for saying that
about James because I don't I haven't
gone out in my entire life basically you
are finding a man what's he dressed up
as at the Halloween party like what
would be like the guy for you maybe they
go werewolf Oh Twitter was last year
daddy vampire I was thinking that till I
could be relieved really good daddy
warlock
like a Dobby that'll cover my daddy sent
harp oh you would love that James
so James yeah kitty what palette are
using oh you know just this like um
really good one Oh what I was expecting
to come up with a word
now I'm gonna outline your teeth I need
you to be silent mmm sounds very hard
for you
[Music]
crazy oh my god it's so good now we have
to have the block yes I'm trying to move
too much so if I look like I'm like
[ __ ] like this is because I don't
know it was so good
this eye looks sick oh you didn't know
[Music]
and use a white liner and add in some
more details that yes James
you know you the makeup punch have to
like be on brand with the person like
this is your least favorite look I'm
your least favorite foundation on you
know hey we can I wipe this off first
before you get angry at me cuz I'm wet
now we're gonna make it your color we
can make it my go sorry it's not my
fault I'm pale oh my god I'm scared it's
not gonna like trip right this is blank
canvas all over right now it's really
good
are we done Jesus mascara and then done
I need a live like kind of like a woman
you know what I mean
do like yeah I do completely and I'm so
excited for a picture of it to you I'm
gonna say you're right listen please are
you gonna go to Moscow okay where's a
mirror how are you like really yeah
gonna do something else here before tell
me to review it overall I give it a 2
out of 10 I'm just gonna you know it's
good I definitely get 5 out of 6 out of
10 7 on top don't ask me to review
things I can't decide like it's good
like I don't know
I just want to give a warning to you
what you're doing your Halloween makeup
this year do not attempt more than three
looks because I say don't do more than
one we had to make a disclaimer come on
G so I've hurt my back and forth between
many different ideas that is had what
look I wanted to do I ultimately decided
that I have no ideas so I'm going to be
recreating the look that I did on the
twins last year what was a werewolf
makeup and I did this in literally 30
minutes east so it was very very rushed
and very fast but ended up looking at a
really really dope actually and so many
of you guys requested a tutorial that
was my first time actually ever meeting
the twins
I am very annoying to them right now
because this day has been a nightmare
but I am so blessed to have them in my
life seriously it's been an amazing year
and I cannot wait for many more together
I feel like it's just gonna be like a
combination of lots of different like
strokes
grab some black really put that in there
start some fur what IV hot with a beard
T basically I think I put block like all
the way around the face okay and the
brow makeup nice and bushy good
reminiscence of James Charles at 2016
blaack eyebrows we love her gonna throw
some Brown in the mix let's see what she
has to bring to the table I'm gonna buy
some white mix with Greg and like right
here a little bit on the cheekbone for a
little werewolf glow okay I think I need
to make the eyeball like blah that's
what I did last year that I just took
this no gonna feather this black liner
out as if it's like a little furs things
gonna take some little white furs step
- perhaps some brow that's looking okay
I'm going to pop some white in this
little inner corner that I just created
to open up the werewolf eye I'm gonna
draw the nose now exercise I have not
talked in the Buddy 20 minutes sorry
about that so that's pretty much the
face makeup all complete am I happy with
this debatable and I'm gonna keep moving
absolutely because it is 3:00 in the
morning
so what I'm going to do now is add the
gash on my neck that I gave the twins
last year which I actually think and
really pull the entire look together so
who knows maybe this will be a whole lot
better what I'm gonna do is more liquid
latex or to end this entire area and
then it got me uneven shards of toilet
paper we're just going to stick it on
there or liquid latex more paper and now
I'm gonna let this dry okay I'm just
gonna layer over top of this with
somewhat foundation to blend it into my
natural skin tone the worst thing I've
ever done it's gonna cut three good and
fresh gashes using the block from the
makeup firmer but I'm just going to fill
in those three gashes just looks like
they were deep cuts with my thick blood
I'm going to grab a little palette and
I'm going to shove this in there hey Don
I'm still alive but I'm barely breathing
literally
[Music]
it's 4:00 in the morning yeah I'm the
itchy as I've ever been all year
probably my looks so good
I think the liquid uh looking at latex
really like held up I was the last one
to get my makeup done before James and
mine is still the most ruined Oh what
did you do what did you do I don't know
I'm crazy with those contacts I'm sorry
but I I don't know what I did I just
like I look around and I doing a little
circle of like foundation I'm like
someone's shirt like oh my god that's
where it came from with my hoodie we're
going to take these looks off and go to
bed but first we wanted to say thank you
so much for watching this videos today
we were ambitious and playing this and I
cannot believe that we actually finished
it all I can't believe guys we did it
I am really proud of how all four of
these lips came out and even though mine
is very very last second and it's a
favorite it was a nice reminiscent of
last year's makeup look for one holy
that's that's whole year it feels like
way longer it yeah it feels like it's a
look at four or five feels like it's
been in them I'm ready
this video today please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up and down below
and if you have not already
come join the system and show your
support we are almost had a million
sister strongly jamya them about the
film about their project oh the secret
you probably should should I tell them
you guys know why not no wait hey dude
you should tell him Friday for this yeah
oh yeah that sounds really good fries
okay don't brush how about the biggest
outside of my entire career is coming
this Friday on this YouTube channel the
best part of the entire video if you
like to follow me on my makeup turn you
can follow me and see what's what oh
they're both to shave Charlotte's my
snapchat
more or have the same thing stuff in
more delirious for I have a snapchat
stories you can follow me at Dame
Charles the next guys after Charles we
also made a video we went to a
looky Asylum and we were yeah we might
do a spooky haunted house and what did
it we went in them yeah my channel we
dress up as each other it's super fun
maybe it's funny maybe it's not I don't
know I didn't edit again I'm surprised
no no this videos sister shot it goes to
sister Rama thank you so much lo froy's
falling and supporting we all love you
so so so much whether you're ready
Beulah to the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to always a retweet by
Middle East they go live on Twitter oh
my sister's thank you so much charge
those videos today good night
[Music]