hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to toy-u channel
usually for my videos I felt my intro
first and then film the actual video
content but for today's video
I'm doing something a little bit
different my editor I just finished the
final edit version of today's video that
you guys are about to watch and I really
just wanted to cut out the intro that we
already felt and hop on camera now
instead and give you guys a little
preface to today's video and say that
this is literally one of my favorite
videos that I have ever filmed I am so
proud of how this turned out what I know
that you guys are absolutely going to
love it I have been trying to film a
video like this for over two years now
and it's never been possible up until
today now if you are a true sister you'd
know that aside from doing makeup of
course my favorite pastime in the entire
world is doing escape rooms in case
you've never done it at Skate even
before or don't even know what it is
first of all I'm so sorry for you but
second of all escape rooms are immersive
interactive puzzle rooms where you're
basically locked into space for 60
minutes with your family co-workers
friends or sometimes even strangers and
you have to work together to solve
puzzles riddles find clues open locks
and the goal is of course to escape now
I personally love escape rooms for a few
different reasons mostly because I
really really thrive and enjoy high
pressure and high-stress situations I
absolutely love puzzle and riddle
solving and also you get to put your
phone away for an hour and just focus on
something other than like those social
media road which I definitely get caught
up in up quite a lot and they just make
me very very happy most rooms start with
60 minutes on the clock which may seem
like a really long time but when you're
in there time absolutely flies but as
I've done at more and more rooms my
times have gotten faster and faster and
faster and for today's video I want to
challenge myself and combine my two
biggest passions and I'm gonna see if I
can do my full face of makeup while
beating an escape room
[Music]
all right sisters we are here at a 60
out escape rooms in Los Angeles and this
is literally my favorite place to go for
escape rooms because they have so many
different locations and I've actually
almost finished every single one of the
rooms so I'm so grateful and excited
that we got to put this video together
in time before I finished literally all
of them I have not seen the room yet
because I want this to be a surprise I
wanna be able to solve it just like
normal but my videographer Luis who's
behind the camera right now already went
through the room up with the 60 out team
and placed my makeup products like in
the right order so as I go through and I
complete the room I'll be getting my
products like one by one so do my full
face of makeup and a full escape room in
under an hour not really sure how this
is gonna go but regardless it's going to
be so much fun and I'm so excited to
show you guys all my biggest passions so
that further ado let's jump right in
abracadabra so Rene cloak Asian pixel
sir
escape rooms to be exact because you are
here to whisky absolutely alright so
welcome to the DJ's Academy thank you
today you're gonna be basically up to us
chocolates you see if you're good enough
to join uh-huh
are you pretty good at escaping I will
say I'm pretty good at escaping lots of
things specifically you know escape room
scandal
okay so you're gonna sit down on this
move because you have tons of chains oh
okay oh wow are you starting okay
this is this is nice and kinky you've
never done this before adding a new
bracelet to the collection I see this
one isn't as pretty okay to fight for
your right to apply for the Houdini
Academy I suggest you try and get out of
this dungeon best of luck this is
already too much more
[Music]
so I thirty Mikey I think if you miss it
more personal
okay you guys we're off to a good start
look at this little Tama we have going
on here I'm a beauty guru oh can I start
off my first step of the planning to the
pho water cream limiter
this will be such a good table
throughout the entire video well look at
that moisturizers are done okay let's
move on to the next step oh this is a
small a very small space okay wait what
oh your products foundation is it gonna
match don't know don't care can't even
see in this lighting so we're good I'm
going literally so fast okay I'm
blending so this is like gonna be a
five-minute makeup routine
concealer time
okay okay I'm done ready to go okay so
there's this is this a switch that's
looks like what they would use them the
Disney moves in are they beyond it Oh Oh
what's this wait a second oh oh all
right another room okay we have another
one of these holy well this is a letter
on it
okay the sharp oh there's a gun here oh
okay
oh my powder er oh good thank God okay
okay let me somebody's in the place
before I get I don't even have time to
blend again it if we're crazy I'm so
sorry
oh how much time do we have left
okay that's not bad actually we're
making good time okay mm maybe we're
making bad what are we having river suit
[Music]
I did not watch anything we do not
promote gun violence on this channel
maybe we have to shoot this door open oh
my god
I don't think I want to reach and I
think you should return thank you okay
conference so fast I look bad yeah I'm
gonna pull a Harry Houdini and make this
double chin disappear
no laughs Colin that was funny see do I
really that looks like a good match does
it not it looks good in the mirror does
it not on camera this is why my manager
does an odd something is it would the
camera is a good invention
I'm lost following at least nose contour
oh okay another makeup stuff we have
highlighter and blush let's get this Oh
[Music]
I'm trapped in here okay highlight are
gonna pop this on oh maybe if I feel
like Harry Houdini will see this
highlighter and say wow you're still
hired a little bit on the Breville a
little bit um they're a little on the
chin want the cheekbones to be blinding
a little bit on the nose oh gosh
oh I can't believe I just did that a
little bit of Judy's ready to go ready
okay there's like a ball here with like
lots of symbols
oh can I let you in the one room Kitty
girl welcome welcome to them
and now my dears you were about to
recreate one of my greatest stunts I
have been presenting it to a respectable
audiences all around the world for 30
years
oh it's called the box of dead choose a
volunteer and put him inside that box
okay so I think okay there's a symbol
that looks like a W on top of it an
upside down W and the left like prong of
the W has a circle on it and the top
right has a cross on it now it's a
triangle with a cross on top and a cross
on the bottom I put on my mirror huh no
I can't do arrows not a mirror they are
not enough to begin with I wish she
wouldn't get me my eyebrows stop oh wait
hold it down hold it down yes perfect
bring it closer
ha ha closer angle it you're not angling
it right down lower yep perfect
oh look at this look look at this thank
God I have bushy eyebrows on don't
really need to a lot of work to this yes
there now there's no light again Alvin
did you get the line with the spot the
spiral with the line Alan I knew my
eyebrows Lois hello I'm running out of
oxygen oh oh I know what I need a mirror
you going to floor excuse me we're
running out of time
okay I'd like go back to the dungeon so
I guess we're just where's the dungeon
is this the donkey's way back to the
first room okay look wait okay okay so
now we need to flip the lever you're
kidding me wasn't it here well wrecking
ball
[Music]
oh this is okay this is the last room
I'm not even better than Baker oh here's
eyelashes okay eyelashes we're so close
oh thank you okay Mira Mira Mira the
music is getting louder and we're done
oh don't mind me just applying for Lily
washes me I also actually Miami while
we're literally about to die okay let's
let that get top you for a second oh my
god we're running out of time okay you
have five minutes remaining
[Music]
yeah what we do okay
okay another oh wait hold on there are
you ready okay ready
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh what let's finish it off right oh
good okay ready oh thank you this is
professional assistant service right
here we just killed Bob are you serious
does not look whoa you tell me how does
I make a block no you're a liar all
right sisters and I think that is this
makeup escape rope challenge all
complete this is probably the only outro
everywhere you can see me using my hands
oh my gosh you guys doing this video
today was literally so much fun I cannot
even begin to explain it I am so glad
that I finally got to show you guys like
my love for escape room so hopefully you
guys are intrigued and want to check
them out literally like nothing makes me
happier in the entire world is it
possible to do your makeup while
escaping an escape rule ops are fricken
lutely I cannot believe that we did it
and beat the clock but what I recommend
doing it that is up to you guys
definitely leave me a big thumbs up down
below if you enjoyed this video and
leave me a comment let me know how my
makeup actually looks I haven't even
gotten a chance to look in the mirror
yet I do want to give a major major
channel and say a quick thank you to
sixty our escape rooms for letting us
come in here and actually do this escape
room I'm not even saying it for the
camera this is literally one of the best
escape rooms I have ever done the
puzzles the challenges that that design
was so beyond incredible and I could
totally see why this is gonna be ranked
one of the best escape routes literally
ever if you guys are ever in the LA area
make sure you check out sixty out and
say it sister James sent you if you guys
know this video and if you have not
already it make sure you click that big
red subscribe button down below and come
join these sisterhood we're almost
sixteen million a sister so I would love
to have you join the family and also
click that Bell icon see you can get
notification every time I have a brand
new video if you like to follow me on my
makeup Jernigan follow me and segredo
twitter and twitch or I'll just change
calls and my snapchat for more behind
the things I said that James Charles the
next s after Charles this video is
sister sow that go sister Carla thank
you so much love for watching I love you
so so so much and if you like to the
next videos sister set up don't forget
to always reach me only
when they go live on Twitter and ultra
turn on my YouTube posts under the
kishin's alright sisters thank you so
much for watching and for escaping with
us today I love you and I will see you
in the next one bye Lois absolutely not
Lois
[Applause]
[Music]