hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 Channel okay you guys I
am so beyond excited for today's brand
new video as you can see we are not in
the normal YouTube studio setting I am
outside in front of my garage because
for today's video in case you did not
know I recently bought a car for my
first time ever here in Los Angeles I
have been driving for the past few weeks
and is pretty fun and good and fresh so
far I have not died yet
which is surprising to me and I'm really
happy about that
aside from the car there's been a lot of
other amazing things going on and if you
guys did not know we recently just had
10 million sisters here on this YouTube
channel there are so many new sisters
here in the family and I apparently have
not done a Q&A video in literally over a
year now I don't know how that happened
but for today I thought I'd be so much
fun to show you guys my brand new car
hop in the Tesla and go for a little bit
of a ride while talking about all things
in my life
boys drama makeup my palette and a whole
lot more so without further ado let's go
dry with me I don't we not die
[Music]
ready for a got a trivial yeah so slow
this is the brand-new 2018 a Tesla Model
X set seven people for myself and all my
family whenever we are whipping it
around here in California together the
car can block would actually just got it
painted my sticker City here in
California there and literally the bus
and the entire will be finished this so
quickly and it looks literally
incredible just got new black rims thank
God because they were very very
prescient and gross before and I
literally and love with this car you
guys I don't want to get the windows
tinted for a little bit more privacy but
I thought we should be better driving
before I do that and then I died so
without further ado the Sun is going
down which is so incredibly rude at
daylight savings time it just happens we
only have a little bit of suddenly left
first and I sound let's help any go for
a ride all right so three seconds and we
weren't recording but we just missed a
stop sign so it's off to a really good
start by the way my best friend drew was
behind the camera the questions that I
just so you know you can ask yourself
the question so that is very true oh I
thought it'd be fun tuned for a cute I
actually did not pick out these
questions for today's video I asked you
guys to tweet me on Twitter by the way
if you don't follow me on Twitter
probably should actually ask drew to go
out there and pick out the most like
liked questions that you guys all want
on house little kind of like a sister
surprise
the class excuse me ma'am I'm gonna need
you to wait your turn
thank you very much as you'll notice we
have GoPros on the windshield and Druce
only I refuse to text and drive use my
phone while driving to do anything while
driving I think it is so stupid so don't
do that please
literally Everett and the first question
is from Emily are you ever going to be
getting a dog if so what would you name
it love you sister
definitely okay so now that I have a
house which is literally the best thing
in the entire movement they were unable
to come over all the time in my manager
and assistant work out of the house
every single day and obviously sister
Ian listen me now too which is a pizza
bass so it's always a full house I've
always wanted a dog since I moved to
California but I never wanted to get a
dollar when I was living downtown
because I was not home not often and it
was only me so as such as I loved a dog
literally like animal cruelty to leave a
dog in that girl's apartment all day
long and not be able to walk in in
downtown so now absolutely I'm doing a
lot of traveling in the next few months
but as soon as everything settles down I
will definitely be a top date and I am
so got excited as for the name I'm going
to see the dog first away yeah leave
comments below with me mate yes oh yeah
definitely
I really want to get something with a
husky Matt it's like really really badly
consenting Huskies are the cutest butt
both Grayson and my dad and a lot of
other my close friends are really really
allergic to dogs so I think I need to
get a hypoallergenic one so if you have
any really great breed suggestions let
Kitty go now here we're gonna use our
phone on one side since the camera
literally already died one seconds of
the videos you love how good at
youtubing I am honestly like never use a
vlog camera though no because all my
videos are in a professional studio yeah
good time okay next question is from
Audrey how what is your favorite beauty
guru palette other than your own there
are a lot of really really good ones one
of my favorite you can't makeup artist a
see Marie I'm you I actually just
collaborated with I think be perfect
created a beautiful rainbow palette so
other than mine I would have to say hers
basically because it's a very similar
Drive hello where are you going we are
going to die a hundred percent hopefully
just be perfect to implement a question
Vegas driving pet peeve by Becca let me
tell you okay people in California suck
at driving including me but everyone is
so okay so first of all biggest thing
nobody uses their turn signals you're
not a single person so you have
literally no idea what anybody's going
to move relocate themselves speed up
slow down or get off an accent so I've
already witnessed like eighty six car
crashes almost happened and like the
front of my eyes like several as much
I've always been apart from people not
putting on their signal it's like is it
really that hard to answer your question
no it's not watch ready watch that's
ready right click it okay look at
everybody who's behind me which is
nobody but if they were behind me
they're gonna know that I'm currently
making a right-hand turn so that's a
major issue that I have really been
finding difficult also like I'm a pretty
fast driver I'm very impatient I have
places to go things to see money to make
people to talk and if the speed limit is
35 I'm going at least 40 okay I did not
want to be going down a road that is 35
and I think at 32 miles per hour
why the speed limit is a suggestion not
11 and okay the next question is from
two obsessed with Conan and it says what
was the most difficult makeup look for
you to make or recreate I'm not really
sure off the top of my head probably
honestly the hardest talk about of so
much of the velocity videos but putting
like the white in the right areas and
trying to make it actually look like the
foundation was painted on top of the
white canvas for some reason was very
very challenging on the day of the shoot
but I love how Edna turning out
you know I think we need to do both yeah
yeah we already want to go to the
McDonald's yep I think it's pretty close
to you so I'll just whip it over there
forever like someone's gonna crash into
forums okay hello hi can I do
a 10-piece chicken nuggets I'm at a
large fry are sleek we do 20 nuggets and
two large fries on lots of barbeque
songs please and and also Buffalo a
large coke at a large sprite oh yes we
make chicken she said now we have to
whip it around this curb
this is such a big vehicle and such a
small driver like for why I'm the queen
of driving oh my gosh okay this is a
funny one I found
so Johanna asks just curious did you
ever have a girlfriend yeah I had two
girlfriends actually when I was in
middle school her son's name was tasked
and the other one's name was Katie and
they were both best friends
for like three days total both until you
realize that you liked male features
yeah this is a casual one honey Nass
what's your favorite pop tart flavor
s'mores or brown sugar cinnamon for sure
like it's a tie between the tail yeah
this one's you always have yeah curves
aren't straight and neither am i asks I
mean that's proving any tips for being
more comfortable as yourself tea
honestly I like really really bad when
it comes to advice on those type of
questions because of the fact that like
oh good hurry oh let's video is not
sponsored but I should be so the
tunnel's please to be completely honest
I am really really bad at adviced
questions when it comes to me being
myself and being more confident because
the fact that I have become Who I am
through dealing with bullying and
dealing with a lot of things working
against me my entire life I've always
just had a very very thick skin and have
been very very unapologetic and I think
for me you guys really know this but I'm
definitely a like self-proclaimed
workaholic doing the job that I do every
single day and working as much as I do
it does happen on the occasion but I
actually like taking time to get
offended over stop until I let that
stuff get to me for me personally I find
very very challenging because it's not
giving literally just so busy I guess my
biggest piece of advice is like you are
you and you were born that way and
you're in literally the best in the
entire world and we all have our talents
and everybody has their flaws - its
abroad to really focus on like what
makes you happy what makes you feel
confident so that you're not like
hopefully focusing on the negative
because it can turn into a really really
bad
and once you get stuck in that it's
really hard to come out of it that was
like a really crappy entire month and
surround yourself with good people and
so on
oh yeah that's a really good thing to
like sir I understand with really good
people who have similar work ethics and
morals like when I first moved to LA and
I became like a social-media influencer
I tried really hard to fit in with like
everybody and I was hanging out with
everybody and I was pointing to parties
it was a really really toxic mindset for
me to always want a fan and always go to
those house parties and be at those
events and stuff once I really stopped
trying and mostly because I was working
all the time and couldn't even have time
to try to begin with but I really
realized there was a small cork of a
friend's if I'm going to be there for me
no matter what and now I think of them
literally all the time and I've
literally had the same about spine group
since I first started to make it a three
years ago like they were the first ones
I ever had and we've stayed close ever
since so very very blessed to have them
in my life and you guys will be meeting
them very soon if you are be important
there okay so Leah asked who / how many
people are usually behind the camera
while you're filming your videos that's
a good question for those you guys who
do not know when I first started YouTube
it was only just me doing everything and
now through three years of working on
production I do have a full team that
works around me every single day which
is so incredibly amazing and I'm so
grateful for all that I never really
talked about that one before my channel
because I feel like there's a very very
weird mindset when it comes to youtubers
that like if you aren't doing everything
yourself that you're not like
anymore which is so weird I guess my
contact like speaks for itself hopefully
what I have something I usually have my
manager Jake in the room just because he
works at my house every single day so he
usually will just do his work upstairs
I'm filming my assistant Quinn it
usually that's where the camera as well
just make sure all my camera angles are
good and just have got me any products
they have it's already on the table and
I also have a writer named arrows who
will also sit behind the camera with me
on the occasional video if it's really
cabinet to take your face video or every
review I always credit my team in all my
videos and I definitely had a few
questions about him and becoming like a
writer I know I call him my writer but I
guess he's more like a coordinator my
videos are definitely not scripted but
you guys know that I definitely have a
major issue when it comes to stuttering
and having to redo takes so haven't I
always said together before every single
video and kind of concept playing it all
out so I have notes and bullet points of
things that I want to say in the video
topics that I want to touch on or
sometimes even jokes that I want to make
if I it really depends on the video or
the day but there's usually around two
people in the room with me while I'm
filming okay next question comes from
Mari and she asks would you ever come
out with sister swimwear I am really
really excited for a lot of the stuff
that is coming up soon on sisses apparel
so if you guys are kind of keeping up
with it for those you who do not know I
have a clothing line called sisters
apparel it is very fun very fresh very
cute what am i doing what what are we
doing I'm gonna turn around because this
Sun is going down but it's very very
bright so I want to have you on my left
hand side to get my gold oh okay sisters
apparel for me started off as a merch
line which was really fun of course I
did like my repeating sisters hoodies
and the sister sayings but my goal for
sisters abuela is not for it to be
merged but rather like an actual
clothing line so I really want to work
on it I have so many amazing plans for
really really dope pieces that are a lot
more than just like screen printing on a
regular merch ID like I have a lot of
custom stuff that's already in the works
the downtown clash that was done last
month
all custom pieces which I absolutely
love I'm gonna have a lot more custom
stuff coming very very soon including
some Eric up coming this summer so I'm
just really really excited I have a lot
of big fans for and I really genuinely
hope that it keeps going well the
support and sales recently have been
like through the roof like I'd never
expected it to do this well so I'm very
very grateful for all of you guys who
want to support and want to get the
pieces it's been so cool like seeing you
guys rocking them and your alpha and
just integrating them into your everyday
fashion so I'm really really happy I
can't wait to see what the future holds
no you cannot make a left-hand turn here
lilia asks can you do a giveaway for all
the broke sisters that can't afford your
merchant pallet so in this video no but
Titus tell them yeah how we should just
tell them hmm should I tell them no you
could definitely tell them don't offer a
giveaway in this video because at the
end of November but for every single oh
my gosh I tell them yeah sure for every
single video that is being uploaded in
December I will be doing a huge giveaway
it just to say thank you can take it
back to cards oh my god I am so beyond
excited because last year I did a huge
holiday give us ladies and I have so
much fun doing it but I was like I think
I have like two million followers at the
time and I was still saving all my money
to like get a house and get a car so I
was not like doing well now we're at 10
million we're doing pretty good and
fresh thanks to all of you guys so I'm
so excited because for the past several
months I've been saving up a lot of
money to put towards each holiday gameis
lights for you guys is here I want to
give back I want to give you guys some
but really really nice and beefy gifts
just to say thank you everything that
you've done for me so stay tuned for all
my December videos because the giveaways
are going to be let
I'm scared about that I'm just kind of
scared on the slate it'll be good
contact okay
Frances asks can you come to the UK soon
so I can be blessed and meet you please
so I'm not really sure what I can and
can't say so I'm gonna be vade to avoid
getting in trouble because I don't like
getting in trouble but I will not say
that there are definitely lots of travel
plans coming out very very soon for me
which is really good and fun and I'm so
excited because I'm gonna be bringing a
lot of my friends with me as well I do
not like travelling because being away
from home and not being able to work
every single day gives me a lot of
anxiety especially time zone changes but
having my close friends around me it
makes it so much better having you guys
around the wake wing as well make
everything a lot better so make sure you
have a post notifications on because
there definitely lots of announcements
coming very very soon
breezy cakes asks what do you want in a
boyfriend and why
with Apollo sucks number one I want a
boy who is strange
lot that for you that's easy it's you
it's easier than you infect true
somebody who has not involved whatsoever
with the makeup world and any way shape
or form because I need diversity and
variation in my life I would like
someone who is taller than me it's like
a little spoon if you haven't met me
person you know that I'm kind of tall
I'm 510 which is so annoying I wish I
was a little bit shorter like five eight
you would be so cute for me I feel like
so it's hard to find guys that are like
really tall and then somebody was funny
definitely I need a boy who was really
really funny because my life can be so
frustrating sometimes I definitely have
trust I'm super super easily so I need
someone who can make me laugh and make
me smile even only for some days you're
tall just email me and I'll filter them
to Texas yeah I'll filter them for him
okay on to the next question
amber asks what you've ever considered
doing pop-up shops for sisters apparel
let me the most says she says Aaron asks
do you ever find it overwhelming trying
to create content that accommodates to
everybody
oh yeah that is probably literally like
the only downside to my job is trying to
produce content that everybody is going
to enjoy like I talked about before I
definitely have a very very thick skin I
don't really get offended by many things
but something that I do definitely get
hurt by a lot and I can admit this
openly is when people don't like things
that I don't want to work into
really the big production videos or my
palate for examples like no I'm
obviously very very sensitive about
because I said this long to the poor but
like my pal was obviously my biggest
project in my entire career had
obviously my videos are all of equal
scale but I think of each individual
video as kind of like a mini production
and a mini project as well so a lot of
the work goes into a lot of the videos
whether it be in a production level or a
company that I'm working with or the
things that I'm actually doing for my
editing team is working really hard to
actually like make it really really
funny if I was having an off day so
everything one of the videos I like to
think of us like a mini project so it
definitely is really really hard to come
up with concepts that you know everybody
is going to enjoy it the reality that
I've had it got a bigger over time
everybody isn't going like every single
video
there's always gonna be people who don't
like it or who won't laugh as are things
for who aren't gonna understand turn
makeup techniques or products the lexer
and Lux and it's definitely been saying
that spark for me to kind of come to
terms with but I definitely chose I'm
getting better and better at it as I
keep going as a content creator and as I
get older as well so I definitely does
talk but at this point I'm just making
content that I'm really really proud of
and for the most part most of you guys
enjoy as well so I'm just gonna keep
doing that
whoever once said watch can watch it
hopefully stay with us for a while
okay so Masha asks what's something that
makes you want a sister snap every time
someone says it why don't you answer
that question what are something you see
happen a lot in my life that makes you a
no-entry so eating at a restaurant and
like James done a table and whatever
like when we went to Chili's great
kidding waitress okay so the waitress in
Arizona knew James or it was like
someone can go through you give me to
rent alone we're in Arizona for
fourth-of-july trip that might like
parents took us on and then we went to
Chili's one night and like that someone
in the restaurant basically knew who
James was so it was in the middle of
nowhere nowhere it was like we don't
even know where it was still and we were
in those chilies and then the girl
texted all her friends who texted their
friends detectives their friends who
texted their friends who talked to their
parents and their grandmas and their
grandpas in their sisters and those
boyfriends and their children to all
come to this chilies and Stampede of the
chili is really just mom it up for a row
on at 10:00 p.m. at night so there was
we literally to start seeing people come
up to the windows and they're like hi at
the windows of Chili's and basically it
ended up with like a hundred people
showing up at this Chili's all asking
James for pictures well he literally
walked outside of Chili's and there were
a hundred people outside I was like
where did you all even come from like I
don't even know this many people lived
in they have dinner area the thing that
annoyed me kind of not the house had
people like they waited for you whatever
like okay that's nice
um but the people they were people just
come inside and ask for photos while you
were eating like just like come in and
be like hey do you think that'd be like
grab a photo really quick as I have my
20 dollar dinner for two chicken pasta
in it so that's probably what it is okay
Tori Walker asks are you thinking of
going on tour any time soon yes how's it
looking this is another quickie Bianca
asks would you rather vacation on the
beach or in mountains also have a really
cool interruption
Oh magic if we got pulled over that will
be good for the video really would be we
should try to break the law uh-huh wait
would rather go vacation the beach or
the mountains cover the mountains I'm
not really a beach person I hate the
sand I hate the water mm-hmm yeah like a
good beach photo I like being in the
warm so it was like if it was like the
Hawaiian now and it's down but I really
don't like the beach I hate sand if
Sandra really gives me a gal and I don't
like being in cold water so okay so live
us what's your absolute favorite shade
from the palette and why that is such a
hard question because I literally love
someone who close in there I would
probably have to say you're kidding just
because I've wanted a true Matt writer
for so long in my collection that I have
never been able to find one that I
really really like and I also really
like the defense my mom's shade so has a
very special place in my heart and the
yellow sheet is really really bombed too
and scampered for my dad and brother for
DN and plenty for the twins you forgot
about me and boutique for Laura and me
and artistry portrayal yeah and
playground for Anthony I'm not artistry
I'm Mary Mary oh okay there's a couple
more questions kidding Ava asks fine is
your full house to are coming as in
decorator
oh definitely stay on the lookout for
the house obviously I want to be fully
decorated frame post the video and it's
going actually pretty well somewhere I
will say I'm definitely making far
better progress timing wise on this
house decoration and then like my
apartment but it's still not even close
to being done I have a few of videos
coming soon
perhaps a collab
wink wink but I really do want to get
the house work on it as soon as possible
oh and should we give it a good
demonstration yeah but probably going to
like the middle I think right do you
think like over one more so you know
there are 8,000 cars right here on
course all he doesn't this is not good
or fresh for us let's try it okay that's
going how was it doing that my car is
literally moving and staying in the way
my favorite is when it lands did you see
that I saw it it's gonna stop for this
ready this is the craziest car in the
world this is so good for me to like
literally when you're a bad driver you
need this car like ten out of ten would
recommend okay I guess we can ask you
some questions while you're on autopilot
yeah you can maybe use some hand
gestures if needed
yeah Miriam asked is there anyone in
specific who has changed the way they
are towards you because of the fame and
money like I said earlier on in the
video
my Cora Cora friends have done the exact
same sets literally starting making up
for the first time so I feel like my
close friends know and I'm so come to
cable for it but so many people from my
hometown have tried to come back and be
like oh my god
I've said you're home and I'm like
absolutely not you can sit on my face
every single time that I ever so many
other straight boys to that used to
bully me every single day in high school
now sound chat me all the time usually
flirting with me so I guess it's not the
worst thing sending some Piketty wickety
booze oh this is a good one to finish
off the Q&A since I'm here I picked this
one because um it really talked to me
son Aria ask if you can honestly live
with one person for the rest room
I thought you'd answer that I decided to
literally will not move into the edit so
partially because really and we're
already together every single day I mean
really come to my house every single day
okay but okay so I'm like I have a
friend
I come over every single day because I
like working out James says too because
I work from home as well but no but we
need her a little bit of separation too
because sometimes when people move and
together it gets bad can people please
agree with me on that like why don't we
ever we've never gone in a fight yeah
but there's potential to get in a fight
I mean if we live together and something
bothered us I am at James's house six
out of seven days a week from morning to
night time so like just let me sleep at
my house no I'm looking for new houses
right now Andrew will be worried yeah we
thought that we
at least triad yeah I will if I already
told you yes okay so it's kind of
getting darker out this is so annoying
daylight savings time it's actually
cancelled but you heard it here folks
you've heard it here you heard it first
you heard it here folks
hello you heard it here first folks
daily savings I'm literally Benjamin
Franklin says what are you doing like
Hello it is literally 4:45 p.m. like in
the afternoon and the Sun is about to
set is gonna be dark like I don't I why
I don't it is literally so stupid first
of all and also consider a month to go
before daily second was happening the
Sun is way down at literally like 8:30
p.m. and after daylight savings time we
moved apart about one hour and now the
Sun Goes Down at 4:45 p.m. something is
not hunting a hunted one hour turned
into three mandala I just don't
understand the point
oh hey Dean's house all the questions
for today really yeah everything this
driving buddy was like low-key kind of
thought like the way just I get the card
weapon for a real one in the Tesla hello
if you guys like that's definitely gonna
do it again if you wanted to drive
somewhere fun trash if you want me to
drive with someone carpool karaoke lots
of opportunities now that I'm a real
adult and don't over everywhere thank
you so much sisters for watching Jays
videos if you would like to follow me on
my makeup journey please follow me at
James Charles and perfect this new
sister shut up goes to gonna put the
thing right here I don't want to check
my phone while I'm driving because
that's really really unsafe and they
forgot to pick one earlier so lovely the
absolute most thank you for calling in
the morning and if you at home late we
the next video is sister shadow don't
forget to always reach me a bit at least
where you live on Twitter
alright you guys I think that's all you
have for today's a brand new video I'm
gonna have home right now and have
dinner with my family and friends but I
love you so much thank you for watching
and I will see you in the next one
[Music]