sister come here girls up you have a lot
of mica yeah I mean I have a beauty guru
and it's my job what would about the
camera it's rolling we ship them a video
you oh you want to film a YouTube video
kill me from a video um you know
honestly I thought you could use a
makeover
don't be really messy ah I knew it like
a cute one just like a cute little fun
little glam Rosa makeover you think yeah
you down I'm down
look at me let's do it hi sister Charles
here and welcome back to my youtube
channel as you guys can see today I'm
done are they a legendary a special
guest Adam ray okay also known as holy
crap I have so to be filming this video
with you today oh you guys obviously
this is Adam he is one of my favorite
tech stalkers of all times he is behind
the rows of videos do community do look
come here and although he is in
character right now we are gonna be
you're taking ahahaha
this Rosa Klebb and we were going to be
doing it you really thought up makeup
transformation of for today because you
actually really like makeup hot I do yes
so I'm a little excited in it there's so
much makeup in the table guys so you're
taking all of it home with you guys want
to watch me at transform a rock into a
beautiful glam Burson of Adam and
learned all about Tessa Tecton career
his life and everything else which you
keep on watching
[Music]
my hair looks disgusting all right Anna
welcome to the channel officially it is
nice to see you here with you no no
busted contours highly I am so I'm
sitting for this transformation tonight
and before we even get started and now
that you have nothing on tell the
sisters a little bit about you what got
you into tip-top and just like the basic
like short story I'm gonna start with
you my talks
so my name is Adam a lot of people think
my actual name is Elissa 20 years old it
was um December I posted my first video
I was at home had ordered a lash from
some lash company on Instagram and they
were so huge so I was like what can I do
with these like I was like I said I love
makeup so I was gonna use them in a
creative way
uh-huh um but for the video I had put
them on there were a little my stuff so
I was like hmm I came on my first video
I didn't have a name for her wait the
first for the first roast the video
wasn't even actually roasted I know oh
yeah my second video I had sat there and
I was like I have to give her a name you
know she's kind of iconic she needs a
title she was the name right i sat there
and I was like what is the good name you
know I need like something that's like
not too basic but basic yeah I was I
came to life and she changed my life
yeah she really did yeah it's like you
said you were 20 and before that you
were working a regular job right so
where are we even working before so I
was working at a cost in there oh and
like sometimes I don't have to bring
that all side of me and like she is like
very like my alter ego so she's just
like kind of built inside me so you're
from Texas San Antonio San Antonio Texas
okay I've never been to Texas before him
but I want to go so bad I love Texas so
much since I could be lit there mm-hmm
ready for some fun see you later mm-hmm
okay so autumn I know we first started
talking a few what we can see oh you
tell me that you had just ended up
leaving at the call center job yes so I
hated that job it wasn't like my career
anything I wasn't gonna
I didn't pan I'm saying they're right
but yeah I kind of just took a leap of
faith and was like we just Joe so how
has doing tic toc then change your life
because obviously it's way different
than what it wasn't assuming a few
months ago yeah so I think the craziest
part is getting recognized in public the
craziest and like the best part I feel
yeah I go to like my local store and I
get recognized and I'm like what like it
still hasn't sunk in and I have millions
of followers on that platform right cuz
I I don't know I still I feel the same
exact same it's just I don't know I feel
like people expect me to like change in
some weird way I felt the exact same
well that's good it's good that like you
don't feel like anything is changing
because that means that you're a good
person on the inside and now this is
your first time in LA
huh yeah so I had never even been out of
Texas before what I've never been on a
plane never been down to Texas I'm
telling you oh my gosh I was so like
boring yeah I had never been out of
Texas my first time on a plane so yeah
it's like being in LA has been so crazy
and there's just so many opportunities
ok so I want to know if you are a fan of
makeup what has been like your
experience with it in the past cuz you
only helped I think you only have like
one tick tock or Instagram photo op with
makeup on it's like green and pink
eyeshadow I'm using it in like my head
for some reason I haven't been doing
makeup for long I recently got into it I
believe 2019 oh ok so only well sure
yeah
and so I had I was obviously inspired by
a lot of male makeup artists like you
Manny I'm so many yeah and so I had
remember I had gotten paid one day and I
was like you know what I have no bills
like this cheque let me go and go to
Alta and I spent almost $400 on like a
full face oh my god because I was like I
have to get enough stuff for like a full
face so I spent $400 and I went home and
I hated all of it like no I applied
everything and I looked crazy so I was
like what did you do I spent $400 and
now I hate it all but then I just kept
trying I was again YouTube videos I
ended up I wanted to get perfect my eyes
for sure I underestimated the face part
of the makeup process I think everyone
does yeah everyone does it seems like
it'd be so much easier but it's not
it takes a long time but like really get
happy with your babies yeah let's go
ahead and start some contour and this
time we're gonna be a little bit less
harsh okay how do think roses makeup
aside from the eyelashes even from about
um so the way it did it I pretty much
took into consideration all the girls at
the high school in shade no and it's so
it's kind of like so unreal but it's
real because like you're not gonna walk
out in public and see some girl with
that much fun while yo you may walk out
and be like girl do you have that much
contour on you know anything yeah so
it's kind of like that exaggerated look
that I wanted to give her yeah she's
just that girl who just does the most
with everything okay so then what was
like the first moment that you knew you
had like something good going on it was
at one specific video that blew up yeah
so my slushie video was everywhere I
think you got a dollar yeah you got a
dollar so I can go get a slushie that
one for me kind of just it definitely
put us on the map she was on Twitter on
Facebook on Instagram she was everywhere
and that's what I was like I have to
continue to think like I'm sitting here
I know and you're like you're here doing
my face it's insane oh yeah like I don't
know I mean I have watched you for so
long why don't you know how you have
that moment when you're like oh like
this is like kind of crazy yeah I've had
like well I'm gonna day I've had a
couple of those but this one right now
is kind of like so surreal oh that is so
sweet thank you for saying that you have
a really good nose for makeup really
yeah those two tiny look forward okay
Adam one of course what I have for you
was you mentioned earlier how obviously
did not like the call center job and
you're really excited to just get out
and do all the stuff with Rossa what do
you want to do with her in the future or
like with you in the future I would love
to just kind of expand on tik-tok since
I was like my first platform that I kind
of grew on yeah I'm so thankful for it
so I want to definitely grow on there
maybe I want to bring in my closest
family members her boyfriend oh yeah
just to grow on see my nose is gone can
you even breathe let's do some
highlighting using of course the change
house expert Fiat mini palette we're
gonna use the shade of face to the side
yes alright you guys so that is pretty
much our base all complete we're gonna
go do the brows off-camera and I'll be
right back to start off the eye shadow
luck all right you guys we are back and
both brows are now complete and it is
now time we went to our eyes shadow so
Adam what type of look do you want to do
today okay so I'm inspired by your shirt
I want a blue bottle okay I found like a
blue black smokey eye my definitely okay
yeah okay okay let's do it let's grab
that Junior chose Exmoor pig mini
palette let's go some color alright you
guys are gonna start off with an M four
five six and dipping into coma notice
that's like a really popular on
tick-tock is a lot of craters posts like
literally like a few times a day whereas
on your page you don't post nearly as
often as that but all of your videos go
viral
so what is your thought process behind
like one you both your videos are not
yeah so I kind of just film I try and
post the one in video every week it's
just cuz I feel I don't want people to
think I'm kind of like trying to push
out a Content that's not even good
anymore so that's kind of why I don't
post like so consistently just because I
feel like I want quality over quantity
and yeah always like said that since the
beginning do you think that make up
stuff it's like something that you want
to get more into especially on your
social media channels like coming up cuz
of which I would love to see some videos
I would love to see some rum so makeup
videos to my sisters Otis a year you got
a dollar
for sure I kind of wanna incorporate
both of me myself like Adam yeah I know
so like I don't know I just feel like I
can create something so good with both
of them yeah I had seen some comment
that said you should do a contour and
highlight duo like Pat oh yeah I was
like that's so iconic
Oh alrighty nice that is pretty much the
ice not a person all complete we
literally just use the blue tones and it
the palate it looks so good
do you like it it's so good
monochromatic moment alright you guys so
we're gonna go ahead and mirror that I
said onto the other eye and then we'll
be right back to do the mascara and
lashes is that because I think Rosa he's
a little bit of a lesson alright you
guys so we're about the bolt eyes done
and it is now lashes time which I am a
so got excited more okay so I thought
it'd be kind of fun because Adam loves a
dramatic lash to actually use the lashes
that we had on earlier put them on
correctly I won't know where the heck
did the whole wonky laugh situation even
start from like cuz it was kind of like
that dramatic look like the [ __ ] she
doesn't know what she's doing my kinda
like just getting out of the house ready
to go she puts an eyelash upside down
you know okay I noticed time for lip
liner starts gonna go in with a classic
nude lip oh my god it hey you alright
Adam the last question that I want to
ask you while I'm about to set your face
in place is how does it feel for you
when you see other people making roasted
videos or like impersonating you because
I feel like it's become such a huge part
of like the tic-tock culture at this
point yeah so I feel like the most joy
that I gather this is seeing everybody
is so many people all around the world
create like their own version of it oh
sorry I just feel like it's so dope that
I'm able to represent my community in
this way like yeah it's literally gone
worldwide and it's so dope everyone is
calling us I love it and that like I
said this is the most joy that I get out
of making my videos it's so the whole
I'm so happy for you and literally thank
you for hours and hours and hours
oh my god this looks really good I'm so
happy
do I know thank you sister for coming on
the table I had literally it's so much
fun blaming you and getting to know you
you are literally one of the funniest
people that I've ever met
thank you for hours and hours a lot and
an amazing a character that we have all
fall in love with all right you guys
well if you enjoyed this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and show your love
and support helps me out so much
and also make sure you click that big
red subscribe button as well and
conjoint this sisterhood we're 17 a
million at sister Sean about to have you
join the family and also click that
balance on so you don't use every time I
upload a brand new video you'd like to
follow me on my makeup Turner you can
follow me on Instagram Twitter to talk
and face with all just recharge my
snapshot from where behind the seat
sites have a savior on my chest after
Charles and if you wanna text me for all
updates on Burt videos and photos and
everything else in the world of me my
number is three oh nine oh five eight
seven four six if you guys want to check
out out of it I knew his social media
accounts you can follow me at Madame
Marie okay ah social media platform this
video sister sad echoes the sister and
II thank you so much love for always
falling in supporting I love you so so
so much and if you look to the next
videos the sister set up don't forget to
always reach me through links when they
go live on Twitter and also to my
YouTube up post notifications also just
as a quick side note obviously the world
that we're living in right now is very
very scary please make sure you guys
taking care of yourselves
isolate yourselves wash your hands stay
safe stay healthy stay home make sure
that you guys are just taking care of
yourselves because that is really what
matters at the end of the day all right
I love you so much thank you Park to
this videos today I don't think you once
together for joining guys having me
yeah I love you guys so you'll see you
in the next one bye
[Music]