hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel today
you can see I've done today a very very
special guest and one of the og sisters
my best friend in the entire world
sister Laura since it is the beginning
of math that means prom season is here I
am so excited to see all my beautiful
friends going to prom
I remember last year for me prom was one
of the most magical experiences of my
entire life and I know it's like a dream
for everybody so for today's video I
teamed up with sister Laura of course
but also with Ava hair NYC those are you
guys who don't know before I actually
did makeup or ever even try and make up
in the first place I didn't used to do
hair styling and that was my big passion
and job forget like two or three years
before I ever picked up a foundation or
blending marks or anything of the sort I
was holding hairspray curling wands and
lots of coltan of bobby pins it has been
a good two or three years since I've
actually picked up a hair styling tool
so it was so fun and crazy to think this
look I am honestly so shocked that I
still have this in me
I created this like braided updo
situation on sister Laura I'm really
really proud of how it turned out we
even have her extensions hidden which is
a very very very hard thing to do
when it comes to hair styling so we were
super one anothers it turned out and I
also created this makeup look - it's
very very light airy duty with just a
simple Papa glitter on the leg perfect
for prom I would say if I makeup it's
fun to be super super glam but just like
it's the best version of yourself
because it even want to be photographing
well no flashback Mary's situation and
just a whole lot of like beautiful fun
pictures with all of your good friends
on this very special high magical night
that being said this is going to be a
crazy combination at tutorial all in one
so I'm going to show you guys how to
think this hairstyle first then we're
gonna go right into the super easy
makeup look so if you wanted to see how
you created at both of these looks make
sure you keep on watching alright guys
so we're starting off with Laura's hair
already pre-washed off Cameron's in the
clean it up shampoo and a soften up
conditioner we then went to the therapy
session hair masks which are all
scientifically proven to strengthen hair
we did this off-camera or let it be
sitting here for like 54 hours and then
we went on with the main magic time in
wanna primer we're gonna be using a
whole lot of product today
I'm just gonna spread says all over the
air to make sure it was really locked in
place and ready to go for styling of all
of that sorts of stuff I they don't live
it with the steerer but just to prep the
tips and middle of the hair to protect
from heat because obviously very amusing
lots of tools like will gyro
straightening iron curling wands we want
to make sure if Laura's hair is very
very safe and protected because yeah we
don't want it to die and fry off and
we're going to go into this hair dryer
and just dry Laura's hair because it is
still wet we did just wash it up few
minutes ago and obviously if the hair
needs to be drying for it to be silent
so I'm just using this hair dryer and a
flat brush just to a bun boot brush
through the hair on the hair dryer so it
straightens at the same time and then
we're going to go with the straightening
iron as well just to go over all of
Laura's care to make sure it is
SuperDuper straight and prepped for
asylum
I'm just going to take small little
sections as always and just straighten
the hair all the way around including
like these for these parts in the front
because Lord does have extensions in her
hair so for the most part the extensions
are straight for her normal hair is not
straight so we need to make sure they
are really really blending together to
begin the curling process I'm going to
section off Lois hair and split it right
in half down the town of behind that was
enough for some reason and then I went
to the IVA NYC at texturizing spray this
is really going to help to style the
hair and make sure it is super super
locked in place and ready to go and also
provides a lot of volume I'm then going
to this color one and look like to just
begin curling all of Lauren's hair I'm
going to just wrap the hair around in
small sections and then once that coat
is done I'm gonna hold it in my hand
just to make sure it is really really
locked in place before I let it down
just like that I'm gonna go around and
crawl all of those hairs is done we're
gonna take a little bit of time but I
would have had my sped up the process
and cut a ton of out rolls do you guys
have to be sitting here for 16 hours
only crawl for her but yeah I'm just
gonna curl it all in to loose sections
I'm also switching up the direction as
well so they all don't look very very
unifying we do not want them to be like
all super tight bringing that curls but
they are gonna start off a little type
of we're just gonna brush them through
later on and they're going to loosen up
and look much more better
a lot more like natural and kind of
warned that is the look we were going
for today and that'll be perfect for
styling the updo coming in a few seconds
I'm going ahead and I took down the top
of Laura's hair which as you can see is
very very frizzy and maybe my dad was
saying before she does have extensions
so I'm not just going to go ahead and
I'm going to curl the top sections as
well making sure they blend well
together with the bottom portions and
then I'm just going to brush everything
together next I want to start doing this
tiny little braid on Laura's hair she
does have a side part not a middle part
so I'm starting this on the lower of the
two parts if that makes any sense at all
I'm just starting by up doing a normal
braid with three strands then I'm adding
hair as I go over the middle strand I
think this is pretty hard to explain
I've never actually done a hair video
before so if you guys want me to do more
I can definitely try to like get better
at angles or like explaining these type
of things I've been doing this for years
now so it just kind of comes firsthand
to me but I am just doing a normal braid
and adding sections in very very tiny so
it creates a smaller ablated effect and
like I said lower does have extensions
Illinois are these tiny sections and
pull this braid up to the head I'm being
very very strategic in line place then
just make sure those extension tapes are
very very well hidden
once that brings all done I'm just
finishing off and braiding off the rest
of the hair and then I'm going to go in
I'm going to a pancake the braid this is
a technique I learned from a cute girls
hairstyles here on YouTube they are an
amazing channel but I'm just taking the
hair and I'm lightly pulling out the
sides of the Strand just make the bring
up a lot more volume and kind of make it
look like effortless and kind of like
lived and now I'm gonna fake this little
like poop on at the top this is often in
a lot of wedding hairstyles and I'm
gonna add it for this hairstyle today
but I didn't really don't want to do a
lot of TV because Laura's extensions
make that very very far so I'm taking
this section from the crown boy's head
and tying it off into a high pony and
then I'm gonna just grab some bobby pins
and I'm going to push that ponytail
upwards creating a little pouf in the
back and it's gonna pin that in place I
use like 4 or 5 bobby pins make sure
it's really really locked in there but
by having this hair tie there it does
allow us to push that ponytail up
creating that focu without having to use
like 54 million pounds of hairspray and
bobby pins I'm a-goin and leaving out
small sections on the left
the hair but seeing a large chunk of
curls from the middle and I'm going to
tie these together this is one of my
favorite tricks to do it very very super
quick updos I can pull the updos
together in like 30 or 40 minutes when
sometimes it takes up like an hour or
two hours depending on little curls in
place so all I did with scraps together
the big chunk of curls into a ponytail
and I'm just pinning the little sections
to the back of Laura's head this is kind
of hard to explain but just watch as I
go and now I'm taking the sections from
the left and right sides as well just
forming them and little curls little
ringlets and just pin them to the sides
of the head this creates the effect as
if I literally sat there and each curl
to the head when in reality we just
created them into a big little like big
curly fun but I think the same effect
than it looks equally as beautiful and
it saves you so much time like I said
before I'm just playing around with
different areas different places kind of
just playing around with the hair thing
where I would say sure that kind of be I
decided to take these left and right
sections and pin them underneath the
hair just to kind of give it the bond a
little bit more shape and volume just
ratio that nothing was I really flying
around and just kind of locks it in
place I know that excess hair I was
gonna pin it I think right up to the
slide yeah I just pinned it right up
again then it finished all I was gonna
grab the braid and pin it right over the
top of the bun and just lock it in place
beep in the excess and light as well and
that is the completed updo and I'm just
gonna finish off by spraying it with
some dry shampoo to lock it Anna please
now we're gonna talk with Lois to make
up for today for her foundation I went
into the Urban Decay all nighter this is
Laura's pret favorite foundation that
she absolutely loves it and it just like
the name says this is for prom obviously
so we do want to be wearing it all night
long and you want to last through all
the dancing and getting tough on the day
before and hopefully
Conde so yeah it's a great foundation or
concealer tonight little using the apart
shape concealer as I said this is my
all-time favorite and it is more as well
I definitely got her hooked on this so
we're just putting this in the high
points of the face and then it's gonna
blend it out really really quickly using
my Beauty Blender I know I'm going
through this super super fast but
there's a lot going on in this tutorial
it is two parts like I said before so if
it was like a normal time it would
really be here for 54 hours so I really
hope you guys are like understanding
what's going on and then I'm going to
set Loris face in place using the RCM a
no color powder I've never actually
tried this powder this is my first time
using it today but Laura loves and
recommended it to me and I love it as
well now so I definitely will be a buy
myself a bottle and trying it out for
sure I just went ahead in my bronze
alloys face using hoola bronzer this is
both of our all-time favorite balancers
and it works very very well for both of
our skin tones so I'm just really
broadening at my face lightly I don't
want to really be doing a lot of a
contouring and then it's going in with a
Beauty Blender once again and one that
RC made no flower powder just to lightly
baked lower space underneath those
highlighted area so just lock everything
in place for brows today I'm using the
benefit from system eyebrow pencil in
the shade number 4 I apologize this is
out of focus
I'm not really sure why for some reason
to call down to my face which is
obviously not the purpose of this video
so I'm sorry but I'm just lightly
filling in her eyebrows and then of
course with an angle brush and some more
shape to concealer just to clean them up
and shake them like they're all good and
so I started I'm using a modern
undisclosed palette and I'm working with
this burnt orange shade on my morphe m4
23 brush and this we're doing a really
really light halo eye I just picked up
this orange shade on the one thing and
that same brush and I'm going to be
doing that in the outer and inner
corners and just lightly blending that
out then I'm gonna go into the shade of
the mirror on this light fluffy brush
and just pop this in at the very very
center of it
this color is so beautiful I absolutely
love it and it just creates a very very
open and beautiful effect I'm then going
to over line it with the Urban Decay
glitter liner in the shaded Midnight
Cowboy just create a pop of bitter on
and then going to the bottom I shied
away with you or about four orange
eyeshadow her mascara I'm using the
benefit roller lash mascara this is both
me boys all-time favorite heaven for
having me a highlighter which is
actually so balm I really do buy the
inner created a beautiful blonde for
Laura and finally for the lips I'm using
the jewel a clock and skinny dip and
that create chestnut Bagon I can breathe
again and this is the completed problem
Laura she's in her promise I know it
looks like she's naked but if we sit up
a little bit you can tell there she has
a black or strapless custom not getting
flagged today - don't try us I had it so
much fun teaming up with Ava and my C to
create this hair look it's honestly been
like three or four years since I've done
a hairstyle on somebody else so I'm
still like really completely in shock
that I still have it and we and very
very excited to because I used to have
so much but I'm doing all these crazy
updos and hairstyles so this is like
really this is a lot of nostalgia and I
had a lot of fun also this problem
makeup look was super easy and super fun
to create as well it's just very very
light dewy glowy perfect for literally
anybody going to prom this year so
definitely try to rock this and if you
do rock it either one of these Styles a
problem please make sure to come same
time yeah Instagram also major thank you
to my best friend in the entire world
sister Lauper begin this video with me
if she worked Tigers don't and I was 15
again we probably would be playing a
prom together she would definitely be
that friend would be like let me give
you a hot date so you don't look stupid
thank you
if you guys enjoyed this video please
give it a big thumbs up down below let's
say we get this to 30,000 thumbs up for
hair by James like I said it's been a
long time I really shocked
hope you guys are talked to and I hope
you guys really really loved this video
if you like to follow me on my social
media adjourn you can follow me on
Instagram Twitter they both just became
Charl and my snapchat more behind
James Charles the venture s and after
Charles mister talking I'm so surprised
that have turnover yet if you like to
fall sister Laura you can follow her on
more out my model and Samaritan bore us
on Twitter and if you'd like someone
don't flow they can go follow Moore's
booty huh Instagram that is her boutique
I'm not like all my clothes marrying
this wondering and new page if you'd
like to look at all of the sisters being
really really ugly we just made a public
fence
palace even come on set a flashback Mary
you know please go fall so I that over
time it would recommend there were some
amazing pictures on there definitely go
fall but yeah thank you guys so much for
watching this video I still can't
believe that I have not sort of this
outro over yeah I'm sorry I love you
guys so much and we will see you in the
next one good