I'm gonna sweat so much during this okay
so for the intro we all gotta say hi
sisters together James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel so
[Music]
as you can see that I have been with two
very very special guests are we supposed
to say her name
yeah Elijah Daniel I'm Christine have
you be her sisters sister sister Elijah
and Christine here these comedic legends
and today so today I have a lot and
Christine on either side of me and I'm
in the middle and they're gonna be both
doing my makeup because neither one of
them do makeup or wear makeup I've seen
Elijah wish I were a little bit I do I
wear a little bit of concealer when I
have bad acting that's my extent of
that's okay sisters she does have
perfect skin breaking gender norms oh my
god every day so basically in front of
my wife and Christine I gave them both
my everyday go to products they have of
course the makeup ever stick shaped a
Pula than both some versions of
amorphous everything this is all on your
face sorry
I just I've been wanting to do that but
that's not it's fine okay like at any
given moment this is just on your face a
lot of any Carolla only was it bored
with it on but if you make every day
like june wear makeup every day oh okay
he's relatable folks are you ready to go
I'm ready to go ready what are we doing
a look you're both gonna do one half my
face okay
is it a compilation no yeah yeah it's
like a competition see who's better at
makeup
you should be kindly remind you before
we start the everything that place in
front of you you have to use all right I
think I just look up sweetie
are you gonna correct us or do we just
do what we do just do you oh all right
what are you the Porefessional look at
her she's a working girl on the go
I feel like that looks fine I'd love to
see you at her side looks like but I
also do not okay
please no Christine that's currently
blending in my is this a needle yeah
wait your eye out it's a risk I'm
willing to take I do have a good lawyer
oh that's incorrect
that's incorrect Oh Christine Oh
Christine oh I thought you were I
thought you were talking about me I was
doing something wrong no no sir you're
fine oh okay
all right I got it I don't know what
that was did you just put a
Beautyblender and hula bra
sorry I'm sorry I don't know what they
do I'm sorry lifetime supply of
Anastasia Beverly Hills where what is
this this is more concealer yeah what do
you mean more concealer you put on
concealer no hey I'm giving you wings
will not look for oh you do it oh I
don't know I just we're just gonna do
this guy's winged eyelashes eyelashes I
mean I we're offending the entire makeup
community here's our shaking they really
are okay that's disgusting what it says
this is a look is what this is you look
like Natalie Portman at Star Wars
there's that makeup and that like that
like crown and the Cornucopia on her
head sister Natalie sweetie I'm so sorry
she wants a Harvard thank you skin
that is fantastic that in your eyeballs
shaking I'm so sorry I'm so so sorry I'm
just gonna drive how do I transfer this
oh my god we're going very black swan'
sharpie it's very large selection of
brushes over here I need a fix whatever
anyways oh all right what's why don't
you do a selection on camera okay so the
girlies at home alright so the girlies
at home know I'm using this thing that's
a bunch of colors morphe 35o palette use
coach I guess I'm not giving them promo
guys I have the Jaclyn help allen peel
it um it's a bunch of circles with
colors this is for your eyelids right it
looks like a fun dip it's just so
pigmented oh so this is supposed to go
on your lips for the lips yeah so why
don't we pretend it's can go switch it
and this is your concealer you look like
Harley Quinn yeah Lindsey I like to blow
unibrow fooling around okay right you
know like not like full unibrow just
like kind of you didn't shave it for two
days unibrow you know yeah that's good
it's all over your shirt it sounds like
Grandma yeah it smells like a grandma's
closet like when you have mothballs in
it every makeup video I've watched
they've done that in and I've wanted to
do it but we have to go in eyelashes oh
god I dropped it
look good okay so four lashes they have
the lily lodges in the style Miami's use
ko James we're trying to percent off I'm
gonna give one lash to sister Elisha and
one loss to sister Christine I'm gonna
do you put it on the eyelash or do you
put it on your eyelid I'm gonna cheat
and tell you definitely on Iowa because
you don't want yeah yeah you did want me
to be wrong cuz I was gonna go that's
okay you know what nope does it feel
correct
no no it's cuz it's not oh my god that
eyelash is so pigmented what does that
even mean you look like a terrifying
clown let's let's do a little review
shall we
let's do a little reveal here we go oh
okay Elijah your lash it's like kind of
on there
what is this my favorite person yes
sister if the concealer labs the conceal
it's definitely a good a good touch I
also love that you both want for wing
though I was gonna say wing but take a
little Jenner mines that's a generous
it's like it's like you know like this
that's a ruddy 7 got the long it's no
it's always in crop duster yeah this is
a good look I think yeah so normally I
would start with the benefit
Porefessional what's Christine Dan
Elijah I just not at all I did not use
that at all next to be that Make Up For
Ever foundation stick which Eliza did I
did use that all over the thing is
Christine did not do so next I would do
next I would do concealer and I'd put it
underneath the eyes and then the
forehead and on the chin so I knew that
I did that right but just with the wrong
product next I would usually set my face
using a powder the entire face need the
one of you did this
next I do is the benefit hoola bronzer
to go on like my cheek area to and
forehead to like bronze me up like that
my summer glow right no disappeared but
is we're still probably really hot Coast
us from our utility room on the
Traveling Pants
okay so because him sister
pants and then he was saying bronze and
it made me think of like getting a tan
and then it made me think of going to
Greece and how Alexis Modell's character
goes to Greece of meets kosis and
Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants and
that's why it wasn't random
next I would do the eyeshadow so it
going with the palette palette palette
correct both sisters here definitely
succeeded in well let's get the Chi
whose is better and then I would do
eyeliner normally so both wings are
definitely an adventure an adventure I
would call them an adventure I think
there's better I would say Christine's
it's probably a little bit more thin so
that's two point and it has a little bit
more shape to her whereas Elijah's is
more freeform right it's very it's very
spirit like it's free spirit kind of it
does what it wants to then I would do
mascara on the lashes edge Christine
decided that it'd be good for her to
start with that it makes no difference
I I would disagree so I think overall
should we like pick a winner
yeah both flaws no I think the losers
you know I think the loser is definitely
me never being honest here I feel like
allies are probably mess no look at his
cheek obviously you didn't win well it
was the blush moment she wanted to do a
little okay pizza lips was the lips also
a blush romantic the lips tanked the
lips pertain to your whole genuinely
embarrassed about the lip thing you
really thought that's where I what I
thought you would be I thought you were
doing a bit no I thought you were trying
to be funny oh that's funny it's ghetto
you just
elbows are all complete the Traveling
Pants go to Greece find your love a
moped if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup Turner you can follow me on
Instagram or Twitter at their bullets
just James Charles and my stop shop for
more behind the scenes myself is James
Charles that actually
if you like to call either one of these
beautiful wonderful the big come on up
in here you can check out Christina see
Sadako or Elijah Elijah Daniel is trash
this week's shout-out goes to his sister
Taylor thank you so much girl for always
following and supporting you know I love
you so much and if you'd like to be at
next week's sister shut up don't really
enjoy all right sisters thank you so
much for watching I love you so much and
I will see you in the next video we've
had to say bye sisters seven times