[Music]
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
lately I've been travelling so much
doing so many fun and crazy things but
because of that I have not have time to
sit down and do a crazy makeup look in a
long time I've gotten really great at
this point doing my everyday makeup
routine and this is a look right here
that I always go for it's very very
similar to my normal glam just less of
each product and it's a lot more
simplistic I went with dewy skin fluffy
brows light on the eyes simple liner and
lashes and of course a nude lip I also
popped on my clear aviators which I've
been rocking a ton lately and you guys
have been loving them they're certainly
my favorite accessory right now if you
guys like to see how I created this look
right here make sure you keep on
watching some first gotta sort of as
always cry my face use my benefit
Porefessional primer I'm going into the
Laura primer tonight I just got back
from a long time being away from home
I was in Punta Cana with Rachel you guys
saw the vlog that I was in California
for a few weeks then I went to Maui or
Tottie's wedding it was so much fun now
I'm back home for just one week to
finish up high school then I'm finally
done thank God and I get to move and
let's start my career up in LA I am so
freaking excited but my skin is not
enjoying being back in the New York
weather I think I'm just like really
stressed out but I'm getting a pretty
bad break out and I'm really not too
happy about it
we're gonna conceal don't feel don't let
them know not today at least so glad to
be home as always I'm gonna probably
nose using my morphe r32 brush and my
mac studio finish concealer you guys
should know why I do this by now my nose
contour tends to do is slip and slide
around because my nose is super oily so
putting the extra layer on there
even on my everyday makeup routine
really helps everything to stay in place
the foundation I'm gonna grab my Make Up
For Ever Ultra HD stick in the shade at
Y at 315 and I'm just gonna start trying
that on my face I've been getting a lot
of comments lately saying like James you
use all the same products so you just
switch up and at first I was like [ __ ]
this is my channel and then I was like
you're kind of right though and I
thought about it some more and I was
like you know what I am NOT someone who
does reviews I'm not someone who test
out new products very often I kind of do
a lot of crazy makeup books as you guys
know and I
hazily do simple glam like this I've
been traveling so much lately which is
why you guys have been seeing so much
simple super easy kind of boring on my
uncertain future because they haven't
had time release it then I do crazy
looks but I really like the products
that I work with and I tend to not
switch them up just because that's what
really works for me occasionally new
things always do make it into my routine
like brushes I shut up health and stuff
like that but for the most part my
babies remains the same because this is
what really works for my skin type I
have a pretty complicated skin I know
it'll look good every single time so I
tend to not switch it up very much sorry
there are plenty of other YouTube
channels out there in the world if you
want to look at some new products but I
get to find shape type concealer from
Tarte I'm going to highlight my face
anyways moving on I'm just blending this
in with my damp Beauty Blender then I'm
going to drive just a tiny bit of the
Kat Von D while concealer and just make
a few dots under my eyes and in the side
of my forehead same place I put the
concealers obviously not using as much
as this because we don't want to look
too pale but I'm pretty pasty already so
I like to add as much contrast to my
face as possible if you are new
subscriber coming from a Tati channel
hello I hope you enjoyed our wedding
makeup video together I just came back
from Maui and I got to go to her wedding
which was so much fun literally one of
the most beautiful and fun experiences
of my entire life
it was just so crazy because I've been
watching talk to you for like probably
three years now almost and three years
ago I called myself one of her biggest
fans and now after doing makeup for only
a year and a half I got to go to her
wedding and do her makeup for her
wedding what you thought is so crazy so
it's so cool how the internet like
brings people together I don't know if
they keep story okay it's going to
quickly blend out the creases underneath
my eyes then going with the Laura
Mercier translucent setting powder
I have not uses in a long long time I'm
next I got my Mac Studio Fix foundation
powder and my morphe 48 and put that in
the same place I put my concealer
basically my like super easy a rare-book
lay on that makeup routine is the exact
same as my like full-on glam crazy
makeup routine I'll just use a whole lot
less of the same products - Bronson face
today I'm gonna using the comedy show
you the light kit shocking and I'm gonna
use this new brush from the more via
copper collection these brushes are so
freakin pretty I actually have yet to
use them I just got home
I said so I just got a chance to open up
all my PR packages oh my god I've been
in love with copper lately you guys have
no idea how excited I am to move out and
decorate my own place literally walking
it's my house it's gonna be like walking
into a Pinterest board and I literally
cannot wait this brush is actually so
good for contouring and bronzy I'm kind
of shook right now it's much more dense
than I'm used to but it puts in the
color like really really nicely what is
the name of this oh it doesn't have a
name okay maybe you actually have to buy
the entire set together either I
remember you can always use code James
for 10% of all products at morphe y'all
know that they are one of my favorites
I'm really lightly gonna use mine at JD
maybe 180 brush to contour my nose I'm
still gonna sum it down using the middle
shade off the pallet like always but I'm
not gonna go as heavy as normal just
because this is everyday makeup and not
something so intense and drive be yeah
next to make my face I'm gonna take more
of my out Laura Mercier translucent
powder and this brush from the morphia
copper collection and dip it in and then
tap on the powder so while my face
thanks for a few minutes I'm gonna go
ahead and go and can it start an up my
brows now my eyebrows are one set that
actually does drastically change for my
life super glam routines my everyday
makeup routine usually you guys know I
would go into my Anasazi on dipbrow but
today I'm using my benefit processing my
brow pencil in the shade number five to
slay these brows I'm gonna start off by
just lightly a combing through the hairs
and brushing them upwards in the
direction that I want them to go as you
guys can see I already have a super
thick natural brow so I'm just gonna
start off by kind of sketching in the
tail because my brow kind of stops
abruptly here and I want to make sure
there's at least some divine
and that's kind of the only thing I
really like to find so after that I'm
just going to go through and I'm going
to create a little hair like strokes
just to kind of build up that shape a
little bit in any areas that are more
sparse then if there's ever area where I
like to heavier made a mistake I'll just
go on with the spoolie on the other end
and I'll kind of just brush through that
to kind of erase and blend it in a
little bit as you guys can see this is
much later than my normal pretty heavy
brows and it also is a lot quicker so
this is just a routine you like to do
I'm next enter grab just a little bit of
my ape tape concealer on my morphe 49m
begin to its sketch out underneath that
brow I left a little bit of a sparse
area right up in here so I'm just gonna
add a few more little alliance with that
benefit pencil and then to finish off
the brows I'm gonna go to the Maya
benefit gimme brow gel in the shade
number five and just brush those hairs
upwards to kind of create that bushy but
still natural brow effect now you guys
could totally stop here if you wanted to
pop on your favorite mascara highlighter
and some chapstick and just walk out the
door but you guys know me even for my
everyday glam I still got to be a little
bit extra so for my eyes today I'm using
the brand new limited edition of morphia
bronze mocha Paola
I'm her - of this did already sell out
unfortunately but a lot of you guys have
been messaging me asked me to do a
tutorial on this so I'm going to use it
today if you don't have this the 35k
also from morphe is a wonderful
alternative with similar shades first
I'm gonna have this neutral toned orange
shade on my m4 for one and use that in
my crease as a transition shade and then
on an m4 33 I'm going to grab this cool
toned brown shade to it below the orange
we use before and I'm going to deepen up
the outer V and then if I am 514 I'm
going to go out this dark brown shade or
right in the bottom row and I'm going to
deepen out a little bit more
[Music]
and I'm not gonna grab my m4 for one
that I started off with and just go over
these shades make sure they are nice and
blended out I'm gonna add a quick way
using my la girl line our matte liquid
liner oh my god I have a huge pimple
over the top of my wings usually end so
this is making things very very
challenging today and this la girl liner
is sucking for me I don't even know how
I'm going to address this situation
anyway essentially not that deep I need
to go to bed soon because I have school
tomorrow so I'm just gonna move on with
lower lashline I wonder got my m4 33 and
the same orange shade from before insert
that lower transition shade and grab me
the medium brown once again on my m5 14
I'm gonna blend and darken the outer
corner and then with my two 13 and they
dark brown shade that I use from before
I'm going to really lightly hug the
lower lash line and the last I'm gonna
use my OCC pencil in the shade of
feather to open up my eyes to make them
look super bright you know those days
are you like doing your makeup and
literally everything is going wrong
that's what's happening to me right now
my liner got messed up then I try to
line my upper waterline and my contact
got black on it and then I had to take
it out then I was crying then I had to
wait my foundation off it has been a
night to say the least
but I pulled everything back together
wiped my tears put on some translucent
powder and we're gonna keep moving on
because I don't have the energy to
refill this video or mascara today I'm
gonna be using my benefit roller lash
last today I'm gonna pop on my new phase
the house of lashes ikonics
if you would stop earlier on and didn't
do eyeshadow or liner but still want a
little bit of drama with your lashes I
would totally recommend the Lily lashes
in the style of Miami there another one
of my absolute fave shocking would have
an issue an inner corner wants to fly up
can one thing go right today one thing
that's all I ask
one thing god oh my god oh my god oh my
god the lash is freaking on the fact
that I am this excited about an eyelash
go out on the first try I should just
put you into your perspective how crappy
this makeup day has been so far so line
the upper waterline again since I
already cried it all off I'm going to
use the NYX jumbo eye pencil in a black
bean I'll write my next up is gonna be
to add some fake freckles just in the
nose and cheek region you guys know me
and you know that this is what my
favorite things to add to an everyday
makeup look and then my Beauty Blender
I'm just going to go over those freckles
to it literally blend them into at the
skin since this is everyday glam I feel
like we need to make up what we were
lacking in eyeshadow lips all the fancy
fun stuff with highlighter to get the
glow on today I'm going to use my morphe
501 as usual and the Oprah highlighter
in the shade blissful remember you can
use Kota James for 30% off all over
products girl oh wow
suddenly I'm blind I'm just probably
this on the top of my cheeks as always
and I also like to pop it right above my
brow bone when I do more unnatural glowy
looks welcome back I know it's been only
a second for you guys but it's been an
hour for me because my camera just died
literally at this point what else can go
wrong just throw it at me because at
this point I'm ready anyways to finish
off this look finally I'm gonna go to my
Kat Von D a bow and arrow liquid
lipstick this is my all-time favorite
nude shade I always wear it when I do
like light makeup looks and you guys
always ask it stays on all day I would
definitely recommend
[Music]
holy crap I think that was the fastest
I've ever done my lips in my entire life
and we're gonna finish this look with
the Urban Decay all nighter setting
spray after all the mistakes we made
today I never ever at once makeup to
leave my face and this is the completed
every day at glam I just popped out my
denim hat and Maya clear aviators both
floors boutique and I'm looking like a
glam grandpa as I said this look and
totally be customized in any way or any
products you'd like this is what I
choose to do when I want some a quick
makeup that I know will look good every
single time you know for the amount of
things that went wrong while filming
this video this looked really do not
turn out that bad
and kind of show sneaking up being a
shook by the way you may want to check
out the Instagram page sisters apparel
if you get a second what could it be
hmm you have to wait and see what it is
if you guys get into this video don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and subscribe if you have not
already I post videos every single week
I would love to have you at join the
family if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup dirty you can follow me and serve
me on Twitter they are both just James
Charles and my snapchat more behind the
scenes type stuff is James Charles and
extra ass after Charles alright guys
thank you so much for watching and I
will see you next time bye
[Applause]