hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
you're probably thinking wow James you
look really bad and trust me okay I can
see the mirror and I agree now as you
guys know I lived in city of Los Angeles
California and obviously because of a
Cove in nineteen we are all under stay
at home orders and for LA in particular
today the day that I'm filming this
marks our 60th day in quarantine two
official ones now at this point okay I'm
starting to get a little bit anxious my
motivation to do literally anything at
this point has pretty much plummeted
I've been so lazy I've been going to bed
at ungodly hours watching Netflix until
like 4:00 in the morning I've been
putting on outfits I've been in sisters
apparel sweatpants non-stop which it's
not the worst thing in the world because
they're extremely comfortable and you
should shop now sister Joseph Harold
calm my hair is like 18 inches overgrown
I haven't put makeup on in weeks my
beard is growing man I am a man in case
anybody was not aware before here so for
today's YouTube video I thought it would
be kind of fun there try to do like a
quarantine at home full makeover I'm
talking my own haircut trying to do my
own nails okay waxing the beard and the
facial hair giving myself a spray tan
grab your snacks whoo let's get start
[Music]
other what what yeah okay you guys oh
good morning I am very very excited for
today's bow on translation and I just
look up I could look like that I got and
that is because I have a very specific
order of which I want to do my tasks of
this makeover today the first one being
a spray tan because I need to make sure
that my body is fully paralyzed oh
absolutely
oh my god oh my god oh my god no I'm
purposely not going down to the bud that
smell peeling the worst part of my
facial hair is boys right here on my
channel so the shuttle is here and see
if it'll really rip the roots out yeah
literally not a single hair look at
those hair still there I'm so glad we
can't still they're like covered in wax
okay cut the video I'm gonna hop in the
shower
alright so I am pressing the shower but
we simply could and my hair somehow
looks even worse than before but you
know what we got
a little bit later on but I want our cut
godly without but anyway for right now
it's time to do my own intent looking a
little bit hey I'm actually gonna tell
you guys this maze ado is in partnership
with a bomb knights and they are in
Australia tenant gran they actually
learned about them I think it was like
two or three years now the first thing
that I was there when Australia for a
really good friend of Bercow and I
linked our products a lot because
obviously they're self tearing which is
important but I like be a color on your
tones that the public see this house
because it's more like all until where
is a lot of other tanning products or
orange which is not the move so yeah I'm
just going to squirt a nice amount onto
my little tanning glove and the design
used to be color light / medium by the
way they do have a dark as well first
going to rub it on my leg and I just
going to do even strokes all over you
know even show up sir even folks okay so
I really am self tanning in general
especially if you guys are going for
what I do know that I used to get spray
tans all the time okay I'm not going to
pretend like that wasn't like okay but I
like self-tanning a lot better one
because it's a lot less expensive okay
although they look great we're very very
pricey and I got to get them touched on
all time whereas this usually this rub
on and then just wait a few hours but
obviously we're putting this during the
day as well but usually let's do this
before bed and then I'll sleep in it
Alex really makes them bronzed alright
so how do pretty much look like over my
entire body now and I'm just going to
use the access attending the stuff on
the mat and just do what my face so I'm
not gonna do like a full score on here
just because I don't want to be crazy
alright eBay so the second I'm going to
cut in winter Tana
a nice butt cheeks put some clothes back
on and we're going to let this chance at
my body for about six hours
oops six hours in order to get the best
result so I can have that beautiful
Australian aglow if you want to take a
warm shower and wipe everything off and
it'll be beautiful
so in the meantime I have all the other
quarantine and big over steps to get
started
any on the ball nice and that's how it
works by nice and calm and you guys can
use no James first 20% off enjoy your
tan okay so before we head on to the
harder parts of the transformation that
like doing my own nails and cutting my
own hair I want to show you guys one
super easy and really really cute way to
get fake freckles using actual henna in
case you guys don't know what henna is
and is basically a natural type of a
temporary tattoo used in Indian culture
to do it literally the most stunning a
beautiful body art ever and you guys
know that I love fake freckles and live
and put them on all the time and I was
looking into how to like actually
achieve them a few months ago and a lot
of people were using actual natural
henna to do them so I ordered a bunch on
Etsy if you guys decide to do this by
the way make sure that you don't just
get like a stupid store-bought henna get
it on either Amazon or Etsy and make
sure you're searching for natural stop
or else it's gonna look so bad and I try
the same as before so don't worry but
I'm just gonna use my henna cold it and
give myself some phone calls so
basically all I'm gonna do is just start
putting little dots all over my face and
I know this is gonna look absolutely
crazy okay we're gonna leave this on it
for pretty much as long as the spray tan
so we'll take it off at the same time
but when we take this off it's gonna
leave a really really natural-looking
super super light orgy reddish-brown
stain on your skin for a few days that
looks exactly like real freckles
like I said they look crazy yeah yeah
trust me okay it's gonna look so so good
and a lot less particular nation around
this all right you guys so the next step
of our quarantine
glow up is going to be doing my own
nails now this I am so scared for okay
I've never done that my own nails before
work with a lot of really amazing nail
tags here no I I got the set up few
weeks ago as you can see they are very
very grown out so I guess I'm gonna try
to get myself a build today so I've
gotten my nails done enough times out to
kind of know the basic like techniques
of what needs to happen and I know that
I need to start off by getting rid of
the topcoat and gel polish that was on
there already
oh you know they just realized what I
said wait my feet are in the water
oh no fundacion sweetie I'm so sorry
that's my own fault that is not the
brand salt okay please don't kiss my
sponsorship okay put a nice bead on
there
look how Papa sloths it looks milky
that's one that's a notch attend for
sure okay I guess that is one nail all
completes and I have nine other ones
that frankly I don't want to do and
probably I'm not gonna do if we're being
honest so yeah this is gonna be bad and
let's just move on with the maple all
right you guys we're back upstairs in
the bathroom of my chemistry book a
little bit dark right now don't worry
we're gonna wash it off but not this
time for the haircut now this is a body
part the part that I both scared about
about with quarantine all the
barbershops your clothes sort of Trance
ourselves I overheard a nice set of
razors and guards online I'm here
oh really let's go from 1 to 10 how do
you think it is shorter to fix it
situation it started off with the faux
freckles I'm very excited to show you
guys how this actually works so first
I'm going to start picking off my little
spots ready nothing nothing is going on
maybe maybe be hot
stained through the fan and once I
shower you know the Tamil a little bit
and the freckles will actually be there
I wish that's a big brain scientifical
thinking that's dilution this particular
angle for this near selfie and the ray
of light coming in is very very
reminiscent of a certain photo that
befall the Sun - so you guys can see how
we're just unnatural do these henna
sparkles look like I'm so obsessed with
my skin look like this all the time and
you can their makeup over top of them
just like always and they just naturally
fade away so if you guys want a good
easy way to do a football to check out
getting a natural cut up and now all
that we have left is a makeup tutorial
so I'll see you guys in a little bit and
okay you guys it has been a very very
long and personable roller coaster up a
day of these transformation but we are
finally here in the studio for the very
last step of this quarantine law and
that is going to be the makeup routine
now I have not been doing focal Anna but
there are a few steps that I've been
taking every single morning just to get
myself up and just like I'm feeling
ready for the day so I'm just going to
grab me a little bit upsetting mist
first just to give a nice hydrating you
know like boost to it and then what I'm
gonna do is grab the Too Faced Born This
Way Foundation and this is in the shade
at warm beige which happens to be at my
spray tan of color and I'm literally
just going to use like the tiniest bit
of foundation only on a problem spot so
like right here on my jawline and I have
a few pimples I'm literally just gonna
pop this right into place
see you there we go it looks like my
natural skin and that is the base
routine already done and complete I'm
just gonna grab a cream bronzer just to
add a little bit of dimension that's
gonna move right along to a highlighter
and I'm gonna grab it the morphe
highlighting stick in the shade at
zerozero I'm just gonna rub my finger on
the top of it just like this and I'm
going to add it on to the high point of
my face just add more dimension I'm
gonna grab the brand-new at Patrick
table beauty of brow wax these just
launched and look literally so so cool
all you have to do is activate this do
you think a little bit of it setting
spray sunless winter grab the morphe
wand and then I'm just gonna
any its Puli I'm going to rub it right
along in there I'm just going to lose
this product and I'm going to run it
through the Harris oh that is such a
chic brow Patrick and then whatever
access is left on my spoolie I'm just
going to run this through my eyelashes
then I'm gonna grab my lash curler and
I'm just going to give these a nice pin
the very last step which is going to be
a little pop of fenty gloss just the
lips are popping I hate that I just said
that and that finally completes our
quarantine glow ah oh my gosh it feels
so good to finally be done with all of
my itself care steps for today's
quarantine glow up it is currently 931
p.m. and we started this this morning at
10:00 a.m. at this point I don't even
know if it was worth it because of how
challenging today was I definitely
learned my lesson to leave it to the
professionals obviously the guys do not
need to do this entire globe routine but
I think these are super fine and easy
ways just to care for yourself during
quarantine and to keep yourself
motivated and confident if you guys
enjoyed today's video and you like the
finished result please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below into
your love and support it really does
help me out so so so much if you're not
ready make sure you click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join at this sisterhood we're 19 million
sister strong and I would love to have
you in the family and also if like that
belt like home so you can notify every
time I upload a brand new video if you
like to follow me on I make up journey
you can follow me on Instagram Twitter
tick-tocking pays for all to see Charles
my snapchat for more up behind the
scenes tank top shames Charleston extra
ass after Charles and if you want to
text me on my personal phone number for
updates on new videos mert photos and
exclusive information my number is three
one oh nine oh five eight seven four six
this video sisters how that goes the
sister of me Rena thank you so much love
for always falling in supporting I love
you so so so much and if you walk take
would like to be the next videos sister
so don't forget to always read to be
module each leg alive on Twitter and
also turn on my YouTube a posted
vacations
alright you guys thank you so much
watching this video today thank you once
again to Bob my sense of her be with me
I love you and I'll see you in at the
next one bye
[Music]