hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back 22 panel as you guys know
Halloween is right around the corner I'm
posting this on a Tuesday and I think
Halloween is on Thursday this year so
pretty soon I am very very excited you
guys know this is literally my all-time
favorite time of the year I love love
love spooky season I don't know that so
many of you guys do as well so today I
am back with another Halloween themed
video and for today we're going to doing
with my favorite things in the entire
world a drag transformation now
personally a drag has influenced me it's
so so so much growing up I obviously
have transformed a few times I bought my
youtube channel out of my Instagram into
a drag me but I've never actually got
any real chance to perform or probably
for the better you guys are all covered
that but also I've learned so did for
makeup techniques from drag queens and
it pretty much my entire vocabulary at
this point is from RuPaul's Drag Race my
favorite show in the entire world so I
love drag I have so much respect for and
also Halloween is kind of like the
birthday of so many drag queens it is an
amazing time to obviously express
yourself I'll play with makeup and go in
costumes and this end of the year is a
lot of times that drag queens realize
that they have a true love for
performing and makeup artistry so for
today's video I thought it'd be so much
fun to sit down do a drag transformation
I have not done one in quite a long time
and obviously you guys know we just
released the morphe x change cause mini
palette so we're gonna go from this to
this if you guys want to see how I
created this look from head to toe keep
on watching
[Music]
how are you guys let's jump right into
this because it's going to be quite the
long video today and I'm gonna try to go
in-depth as possible so our first step
is always going to be to glue down our
eyebrows obviously I'm very very manly
square eyebrows that I want to lift them
up make them snatched for the gods and
we need to cover them in order to do so
I normally put moisturizer on my face
first but I not put anything on today so
it's completely dry which means people
will be able to stick to it and I'm just
gonna grab a normal Elmer's washable
glue stick make sure it is the purple
one that tries it clear just like this
and I'm going to just go right into the
brow now for this first layer I
definitely like to be a very very messy
with my glue application because we are
going to clean it up after and we really
wanna make sure every single hair is
extremely extremely coated and there is
a thick with two fees layer on the brow
notice I'm going against the grain of
the hair as well now I'm just gonna grab
any old angle brush my brush collection
and I'm going to push very very hard
into my forehead and brush all the hairs
upwards in the direction that they grow
in it so we are flattening it to the
face and now with that glue again I'm
going to press that right down and I
just covering it white white before that
glue dries I'm going to take this and
I'm going to go around the edge of the
glue and just wipe off any excess just
because the glue does get kind of
textured on the edges if you're not
super careful and we want this to look
as smooth as possible
I think that's all cleaned up I'm just
gonna grab my hairdryer on my face this
is the necessary by the way I'm just
extremely impatient so this really helps
gonna add a second layer of glue at this
time just going in the direction of the
hairs try it again more glue or clean up
or blow drying and then one final layer
just for safety
another eyebrows pretty much all glued
down if you touch is to be completely
dry and flat to your face you should
feel no texture whatsoever it is very
weird and strange feeling and it looks
strange but it's about to be completely
covered now I used to use a translucent
powder as the next step but I recently
learned otherwise
so instead I'm going to grab a
foundation powder this one happens to be
the makeup forever I don't even know I
just found this in my set and it's kind
of a powder puff and I'm going to use
this to cover over this brow first you
can use the translucent powder here and
set it just like I did for a very very
long time but by setting with a
foundation powder first you're basically
just adding one more layer of coverage
which why not now I'm gonna grab some of
the dragon Beauty color correcting a
skin fire something at Makita nobody has
time for these names okay and I'm going
to use it this orange color corrector
and paint this over top of the brow
because my brow hairs are dark brown
which have a blue undertone and orange
color corrects blue so this will help
make it disappear even more well right
I'm also going to color correct my five
o'clock shadow region because this area
is also gray because believe it or not I
am a man but it's going to very gently
tap out to this color corrector
so this is pretty much one brow I'll
complete while this one is drying I'm
gonna do the other one off camera and
I'll be right back
alright you guys said that the brows are
all covered it is time for Foundation
and brows now donations pretty easy but
the brows are by far the hardest part of
dog makeup and it seems like they'd be
so simple but if you put them in the
wrong place or if they're not even after
we're in the wrong direction it's game
what we're supposed to be super super
careful
today I'm first gonna have my Kryolan
that TV a paint stick and the shade and
be honestly this color doesn't even
notch me at that well if foundation
stick is just so incredibly pigmented
though so I'm going to use this to cover
over up my brows and then I'm going to
use another foundation that later on for
the rest of my face so I'm just going to
place on here mine's also ridiculously
dry for some stupid reason so instead of
scrubbing this over the top of my brow I
don't want to disrupt anything I'm just
going to top this on like an idiot that
is the obstacles carrying state every
single time I'm gonna use this to go
over my beard region as well now we're
just going to blend
oh and that's I'm just using a attends
foundation brushes at the morphe adam up
for 395 some Yuko James for generous
enough and it's also in the James
Charles original brush that I normally
use a Beauty Blender for foundation and
I definitely will in a few minutes but
when it comes to it this particular
foundation or just kind of any stick
foundations and don't know I like to do
any general half they brushed first just
to really like scrub it in there okay so
now while the solution is still wet I'm
gonna grab an angled powder and just
like any brown cream and this happens to
be a contour stick and I'm gonna use
this to start sketching out the brows
now you guys know beforehand I used to
say everything first and then just draw
out the browser powder and then conceal
them after but doing it beforehand is so
much better because if you put it in the
wrong place you can easily fix the
foundation while it's still wet and it
won't get very very messy so I much
prefer doing it this way and I'm just
gonna pull this tail straight outwards I
feel like the one mistake that really
gets people all the time when it comes
to it drag brows is just putting them
too high unless you're doing a paint
like check see mattel or kimchi where
you're literally trying to give yourself
a new phase which I'm all here for it's
good to start your broth on the same
place that it normally does and just
lift it higher because that's gonna give
it that more feminine type of effect
rather than like a weird character
character alright that is a really good
base I'm gonna do the same thing on the
other side now try to make them even as
you can now that we have the general
shape I'm gonna grab the TV paint stick
in 0-0 this is just the white one
actually I think it's technically
off-white and just a flat concealer
brush this is the m4 ten and I'm going
to clean up the bottom of the brow and
give us that shape alright so this is
why doing your eyebrows a first is so
much better because I've literally been
doing my brows now for 45 minutes and I
still am really not happy with the way
they're looking I cannot get them even
but this will do because we can always
fix them a little bit later on I'm just
gonna move on I'm next gonna grab my tv
foundation stick once again in white and
I'm going to use this and put this right
here in the center of my face down here
for highlights and the sides my nose on
the chin and then just right here no
it's kind of on that end I'm just
letting this white into my skin it just
like my normal beauty routine as if it
were a concealer this is going to really
help bring attention to the center
points of our face but that same clothes
that I used to draw in my brows I'm just
going to sketch in mine
contours and I'm just going to blend
this out using a fluffy brush last step
before we get to set this face in place
I'm gonna grab my nose country marks the
e62 which is available and
the original in mini James Charles brush
sets I'm going to use this to Sketch up
my nose contour and make myself super
super pinched finally 18 million years
later we're done with our face now you
get to set it in place and then
basically redo it again with more powder
so this should be fairly fine up but now
it's pretty much smooth sailing from
here on I like to think that only God
but also Jesus on this fine day
I'm gonna go to the RCM a no color
powder and basically just tap the sauce
on my bench grab the powder puff and
start packing this in now it's time to
bring some color back that we literally
just covered up using this powder this
is where the drying process takes so
many hours but it's so worth it in the
end I'm gonna grab my dragon a beauty at
face palette and I'm gonna start just
recontouring up my face first using the
shade at femme and I am for oh I brush
just following literally the same exact
shape that I had made beforehand
actually gonna go and have a 5 to 7
instead I don't have time for this gonna
grab a little bit of Serge and uses to
really hollow out the lower portion of
the cheekbone up being very very gentle
without shaking because it is extremely
pigmented now for blush let's put I have
an 8 for brush and into the shade be be
a girl in the face pact and use this
color video my face a quick spreads of
some settings right is because there's
like 18,000 layers of powder at this
point
alright so I'm gonna grab an angled
brush at once again and dipping into at
the dark brown shade in the top right
corner of the palette which is an T I'm
gonna use this to start filling in
details my brows and then same thing on
the other side next to the govern Anna
508 which also comes in the mini brush
that I'm gonna grab the shade punched me
which is the kind of neutral tone and
brown shade in the palette and I'm going
to use this color to blend out the t
inward because Joey it looks actually
really good on camera mommy
mom leave us alone here Charlotte Oh
or just three women obvious did not
stand for the Isetta portion where we
get to actually have a fun of course I'm
using the at James house explore the
mini palette available on Murphy calm
and a tall Murphy stores use Co James
for 10% off only $23 and also in all
uLTA Beauty locations also I'm just
going to doing a simple rainbow look you
guys have seen me do these paper looks a
lot of times before but it is a rainbow
Trog a concept it'll make sense later on
so we're kind of kind of like brushed
through this it's just real overall the
concepts and shapes I'm gonna first grab
be in the bright yellow shade and put it
right in my little inner region we're
just gonna start blending it upwards in
a circular shape but I'm gonna have an M
for 33 and dip into five one eight and
I'm going to blend that right next to be
a little bit of a rusted adjust to add
some dimension in there I'm modeling my
makeup by the way off of Raven at
legendary dark cream from season two it
should have been the winner but we're
not gonna talk about that today she is
like by far the most iconic makeup
legend ever and I'm trying to follow
like her general I she with a little
pencil brush I'm just going to grab a
little bit about 10% off and use this to
shade the very bottom part of this
orange like I said we are going to cut
this so you won't even see this in a few
seconds but just add a little bit of a
dimension I'm next gonna grab another
fluffier brush that I'm four three three
and dip into it skip the bright pink
shade and I'm going to use this and I'm
going to blend this pink right in here
I'm going to pull this color downward
but just saying that I normally don't do
but I'm gonna kind of actually close off
this eye shape a little bit now with an
outlet 506 I'm gonna dip into a little
bit love that I'm gonna use that to
shade at the bottom portion shade of
this now is just a white liner and some
concealer brush I'm going to carve out
my crease starting off in this inner
corner okay then I'm gonna set this
liner in place using some more up
flashback
now I'm gonna sketch in my winged liner
this is actually going in a good
direction
I am happy I'm gonna use anasazi a black
liquid liner just to catch out a nice
juicy wing okay so basically I'm gonna
do this with my eye open which is not
really how you're supposed to do with
liner ever but I want the winged liner
to be above my actual eye lid so
therefore basically my entire eyelid
it's gonna be black and then it'll look
like a normal wing with my eyes open
that made sense right now that that
liner join I'm just gonna grab a little
bit of a spooky from the palette top off
the access and
make sure that that black eyeliner is
set in place and very very blocked
because we don't want it to transfer
anywhere on the lower lash line we are
first going to grab a little bit more of
that white liner and I'm using just a
flat brush and I'm going to fill in my
waterline I'm basically just imagining
that there's a straight line like if I
look forward from like the corner of my
eye ball just like outwards so I'm gonna
throw all that end with white and this
is definitely gonna take me looking
closely in the mirror because this is it
an illusion since my face is not
straight across my mini palette mirror
Lois it's great for glamming on the go
now with another Emma five-foot-eight
brush I'm going to draw a little bit of
Cola first and then I'm gonna put coal
up right in the middle of my lash line
right up against the actual
lash line and then like I said I'm
agitating there's a straight line at so
I'm pulling that forward just like this
okay then with that same exact brush
down finally I'm gonna grab a little bit
of a single and escape and I'm just
going to pull this purple color out just
like this so see how that creates out
like a straight line shape that's what
we want and then with that same brush
again just covering a little bit of
social blade and a completing dot line
in the front now I'm just blending out
the line with a fluffier brush this one
is the e30 is six a little bit of a
playground okay you guys I have done
Drive makeup literally so many turns out
and is not even funny and I've been
trying to emulate Ravens like aura and
just shapes of makeup since I literally
started doing it in fact my first choice
look ever three years ago was a raven
luck it was the worst I makeup I've ever
done in my entire life
but I think this is the first thing that
I've ever actually successfully gotten
at the shape
I feel like this looks so bomb I am so
excited right now
and it wasn't that hard either but what
made me hard is getting even on the
other side at which I'm gonna go do off
camera right now and then I'll be right
back
to pop on the wash and finish up the
rest of the look we're back the bolt
eyes are now complete and somehow very
symmetrical it is a blast day here the
sister studio and I'm about to apply
some lash as a person was gonna play a
late coat of mascara today I'm gonna use
the Lily lashes of triple x mascara
because it has been up my favorite
recently okay and then I'm gonna
carefully also apply out some mascara on
my lower lashes but I'm going to skip
out on the lashes
my inner corners and also losses on my
outer corners because I want those to
remain in a white to keep that lytic
spatial illusion going for lashes I'm
just gonna pop on a typical 301 that
drag lash but for once I'm not gonna
stack it I just want to do it one lash
I'm not sure why this is like brave of
me to even attempt this bats be good
alright you guys so those are both of
the eyes all complete and it is now the
home strats are gonna move on to the
rest of the face and the next step we
have is going to be of course
highlighting so I'm moving my face a
nice spritz of the more people have been
set setting spray to Sprint's them at
Moisture about and I'm gonna grab hey
I'm at 5:04 under a little bit of a face
from the palette maybe a little bit of
ring light to honestly why not I just
put this right on the cheekbone a little
bit on the forehead for a little bit of
an extra blow that some right down the
tip of the nose next under grab a little
bit of literally it which is my a peachy
blush shade from the palette I'm gonna
use this to blend together my highlight
and my blush now I'm going to clean up
my lips and oh my God we're like
cruising along thank God and we're gonna
fill in a nude lip like always
[Music]
okay you guys this look is pretty much
about complete at this point I'm going
to give these a nice sprint of the Urban
Decay all nighter setting spray to lock
everything in and then the mini palette
also serves as a fan because I cannot
find my sister's been anywhere so all
right you guys night is the makeup
portion of this look all complete I am
so happy how this turned out I think
this is the first time that I really got
in like my drive face and all the shapes
and angles really really good and I am
super super proud of myself and I hope
that you guys learned a little bit as
well I guess this is definitely a good
first time for me to even get everything
somebody correct if this is like a first
time for all of you guys watching this
video this registration is definitely
not yet complete done because of course
we have a wig jewelry at a full gown as
well before we head out to tonight's
Halloween festivities so let's head out
of the studio and get dressed up as you
guys and that is this rainbow @drive
look inspired by the mini palette all
complete
I am literally obsessive how this turned
out this is gonna be one my favorite
looks than I have ever ever done a shout
out to my stylist Joey Tao for selling
me in this gown and Michelle Herbert for
creating it she literally made the
entire bodice one by one with broken
pieces of mirror which is so so
beautiful and the bottom is all hand
painted she literally killed it and also
thank you to my good friend James for
making this custom little paint dripped
wig I think this looks so so so cute and
I really hope that you guys enjoyed this
video and picked up a few new tips and
tricks I'm running so late for my
Halloween party right now so I really
gotta go but thank you guys so much for
watching hello you guys a good morning I
look like hit by a bus currently we did
not be at home last night and talking
about 6:00 in the morning Halloween it's
like the one time of the year that I
will actually go out and party and it
was lit not gonna lie
just watching back the footage from
filming last night and I still a home
look turned out but I was running an
hour and a half late for my party and I
realized that I did not really explain
my look what I know if the mini palette
pretty much every drag queen friend that
I've ever met texted me so that they
needed it immediately because it would
make getting ready in the backstage area
so much easier that is why the dress is
black in both the dress and the wig are
splutter painted with different colors
from the palette and that is why the top
of the bodice is made completely out of
broken shards of mirror and honor of the
palette not having a mirror at first
glance I'm not realizing it may not be
at that obvious but I'm really proud of
have the look turned out and I'm really
grateful to the designers who work super
hard I think it looked so beautiful so
that is what the concept was and I hope
you guys enjoyed this transformation if
you did enjoy please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up and down below
if you've not ready make sure
that bigger subscribe button down below
and come join this sisterhood I would
love to have you guys and the family and
also click that Bell icon so you can
over use every time I upload a brand new
it video if they do follow me on my
makeup journey you can follow me
Instagram or Twitter twitch and tik-tok
are all dis James Charles and myself
more thy self is James Charles
that extra asked after Charles this
video sisters how that goes to sister
Brenda thank you so much love for always
following and supporting you know I love
you so so so much and if you like to the
next videos sister shadows don't forget
to always reach me twenty links and they
go live on Twitter all right you guys
thank you so much for watching a happy
Halloween and I will see you on the next
one
[Music]
[Applause]