hi sisters team Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel first today's
video we're gonna be doing something so
crazy that no beauty guru has ever done
before and that none of us really like
to talk about and that is face tuning
you guys know I'm definitely the
self-proclaimed queen of face to it
let's be real I am very very very good
at it and if you guys see me on
Instagram you would know that a sister
loves a good tune I just really really
love a photo editing and in my opinion
as long as you're not editing a makeup
actually on a photo editing and
retouching is just as much of an art as
actual makeup itself I've literally
become so known for facesitting at this
point that not only do i edit my own
photos but so many different Instagram
celebrities and youtubers that you guys
all know and love I will not release any
names but also some of their photos to
edit to so half the time that you guys
are seeing are really bomb photo on
Instagram especially if it involves
makeup probably went through me first as
well though I also always get a ton of
questions from you guys about different
editing tips tricks and techniques and a
few descried tweeted on Twitter asking
what if I did a video where I edited
your guys's southies and it got like a
40,000 likes or something absolutely
crazy so for today's video I tweeted
asking you babes to tell me your
unedited and makeup selfies something
that you want fixed and call me crazy
but I'm gonna facetune your guys's
selfies just a quick little just simmer
before we get really into this video if
you're someone who does not believe or
enjoy a photo editing um please do me a
favor and click the little X button
right up here we do not need you here
and I definitely do not want any
annoying comments this video is just for
fun I want to make it very clear that
like I said beforehand I view photo
editing is this as much of an art form
as actual makeup itself but I will never
actually edit makeup on when you're
taking selfies there's a lot of
different variables that can really
affect the final photo such as lighting
the environment that you're in the angle
that the photo was taken it and the
actual camera you're using so what I'm
editing pictures I only like to make
this selfie that already exists a little
bit better using photo editing
techniques but I never will actually add
makeup and I never change my face to
where I'm not recognizable anymore for
me personally you guys know I love a
good face to moment and I am very very
open and honest about the fact that my
photos are all very very edited but at
the same time you guys see me on YouTube
every single week unedited and raw and
also on snapchat and Instagram stories
all day long and a lot of you met me in
person too so it's not like I'm really
trying to hide anything there is nothing
wrong with fixing any insecurities and
making your highlight really pop in a
photo or making your eyeshadow colors a
little bit more vibrant as long as
you're not crossing any lines and as
long as you're open and honest about it
so without further adieu all that is out
of the way let's jump into the video all
right guys let's jump right in the first
response we have to this tweet is a
sister Katie Bruce Lamora another fellow
Beauty influencer and he said can you
fix my flashback oh no unfortunately if
this were fixable I wouldn't have this
candle in the first place okay so
seriously now for the first time sister
Zoe said fix my nose please and thanks
and she said and this selfie right here
Wow a sister looks beautiful and snot
that's good and Sasha snows up just a
little bit more alright so let's go
ahead and open the photo and face tune
and we're first gonna stock with sister
reshape skinnier than Mariah so first
what I want to do is go ahead and take
this smooth tool and I want to go over
all of a sister Zoe skin to kind of
create an even base all throughout
especially when it comes to it the nose
region usually you guys know I like to
just have everything in because if it
looks too smooth that looks very very
fake and cross it and bust it and
they're gonna get clocked a real fast
first sister to date and even though I
like to edit my photos the house down
boots I like to look them as real as
possible next I want to do is grab the
tones tool and then grab Hicker and I
want to pick the lightest tan color
right on the center of her cheek and I'm
gonna go back to tones and then I'm
going to lightly tap on this light tan
color all around her cheek area and on
to the side of Zoe's nose bridge so next
I want to do is go back into tones I've
got the picker and then I'm gonna take a
dark kind of brown shade and I'm gonna
pick it right from Zoe's contour over
here and I'm gonna use this color - now
sketch in a new nose bridge if that
makes sense so basically you guys know
what I like to contour my nose because I
definitely have a very very large
sister schnoz that I like to just snatch
that was a lot whoa and the closer you
draw the two lines together this smaller
your nose it's going to look I'm gonna
go back and as always nose with this
dark brown color and I'm gonna sketch in
to nose contour lines and obviously this
is gonna look very very intense but
we're gonna blend them out so now that
they turn into poor so we do an anteater
here I'm gonna grab the eraser tool and
I'm gonna lightly tap over those two
lines to soften everything
make it not look absolutely crazy and
then it once again a smooth tool to kind
of blend everything out so now that we
have the contours and the brightness
built in we definitely need to add some
highlights to really provide a contrast
and finish off this sister nose snot
what I want to do is grab the tones tool
once again as you can see this is a very
very similar theme throughout I don't
gonna go to palette right over here and
what I want to grab for Zoe's skin tone
is a shade right in between a yellow and
orange barely Goldy Sheen and then or
right up at the top I want to drag this
color picker to like an off-white type
of color then I'm gonna go right in and
top right on at the tip of the nose and
then kind of right down the bridge
focusing it mostly right in between the
eyebrows all right guys are we ready for
the iconic before and after here we go
before and after ooh
literally so good it looks like she can
barely even breathe do you guys know
that it's always my goal when it comes
to editing my nose contour and as well
nose contour is one of those things that
is very much affected by lighting
sometimes it can look really really bomb
and the right lighting and sometimes if
you're in a very shadowed lighting it
can look literally at the worst I just
fixed up Zoe's nose nice and good it
made its sister snatch and I think she
will definitely love this and for all of
you guys out there if you're like me and
you're on a budget saving for a sister
house that is how you get a rhinoplasty
with facetune let's move on to the next
sister selfie so we obviously want to
work with her nose done hello a little
reason girl so good we went to somebody
else who wants a different feature fixed
oh okay this baby is from a sister Emily
and she says I wear my makeup for an
hour when this photo was taken the
foundation was a little bit splotchy but
the vibrancy and the eye shadow isn't as
much as I want it also do anything to
make it look less wrong let me move
every selfie ever and she attached this
photo of herself oh my god hello girl
you look so beautiful your eyeshadow
looks amazing it looks like this is
actually a recreation of my coachella
look so definitely down to help a sister
out with this let's pull this into
facetune and see what we can do so in
this photo Emily said that her
foundation was a little bit splotchy but
in my opinion I think it looks really
really beautiful and bright
natural-looking I definitely want to
focus in on the eyes for this because
she said that she wishes the eyeshadow
was a little bit brighter and more
pigmented so I'm just gonna zoom right
in and when it comes to working with the
eyes the first thing that I always like
to do is do it the details tool I'll
just tap a little triangle right down
here and then I'm gonna go in and
lightly tap over both of the eyes this
really brings up the saturation it makes
the block of the eyeliners definitely
darker
makes the eyes pop a little bit and just
makes the eyes in general more
eye-catching if that makes sense
whatever I'm editing an eye shadow
especially colorful look on based it I
would like to do it in the same exact
order that I would apply and so for this
I'm assuming because I did this as well
that she started off with the colors in
the crease and so what I want to do is
grab the tones to it right down here and
I'm gonna start off with the right eye
or I guess her left eye hello and I'm
gonna grab a yellow tone first and I'm
gonna grab it right over here and I'm
just gonna start off by lightly tapping
right in it dot regen then I'm gonna go
right in with orange topping right next
door
same thing with the red right next door
as well and then already it's looking so
much brighter but let's be real definite
looks a little bit fake right now so I'm
assuming she was going for a half cut
crease so what I'm gonna do is grab the
eraser tool and zoom way in and I'm
gonna lightly scrub over that crease
region to make sure that it still looks
nice and cut and then I'm gonna zoom out
and lightly tap over that entire eye to
keep the shadow that we've blended in it
but only make it like 50% there that
makes sense so it's just a little bit of
a boost but not to the point where it's
like fake and looks like a literal
rainbow on the eye so before I go into
the eraser tool just like I did in the
other eye if there's one a really
important thing that I want to note that
I can't I self personally doing all the
time and is a major major major major
face to know that it's gonna give away
the fact that it's edited real quick so
whatever you're taking a selfie at like
sister Emily or like me have you turned
your head to the side and you take a
selfie of course we get that good
jawline we got that good highlight but
whatever eye is facing away from the
camera is never going to be as bright as
the other eye because there is it light
heading in so you can help it out a
little bit but definitely be careful and
use it at your own risk so as you can
see before and after before and after
definitely hoping out the pigmentation a
little bit without going insane like
we've done the other eye
I think I'm popular that so next in this
makeup tutorial if I'm remembering
correctly I cut the crease using
concealer and then glitter and I was
doing Emily did the same exact thing so
I want to make that glitter on her lid a
little bit brighter if you zoom in as
you can see it right here on the lid you
can see that she has some specks of
light which tells me she did put a
glitter there but I'm losing the
lighting she was and
didn't exactly pick it up so let's bring
it back a little bit I'm first gonna
grab the tones tool once again
when to palette and a light yellowy kind
of born shade and go all the way over to
the left and an off-white and then I'm
gonna sketch that right in between the
lashes a really important technique
winter face tuning is always the top
things and as opposed to scrubbing it on
especially when it comes to eye shadow
stuff because if you're wearing lashes
the last thing that you want to do is
cover up those losses with whatever fake
glow you're putting on because it's
gonna look really really fake and really
really bad I think I'm definitely happy
with that animate the lid much nicer
brighter definitely the glitter looks
like it's actually there now and while
we're still on that kind of a light
yellow white shade does like I did on
sister Zoe with the nose snatching I
want to add a little bit of that shade
or right here into the inner corner to
make her inner corner highlight a little
bit brighter and then same thing right
up here on the brow bone to really
intensify that highly and add a little
bit more contrast and attention to the
eye once again eraser tool just lightly
tapping over that and that looks so
snatched similar to rely shadow at the
last some of editing is what's going to
be at the blacks or the dark shades and
you always do this to make sure that
nothing gets really really money kind of
gob tones one last time and grab a black
and zoom all the way in and I'm just
gonna start lightly packing this right
into the crease to kind of add a little
bit more dimension onto the outer corner
and then as well right underneath that
eye region because as you can see
there's a little bit of lightness and
her crease that she probably did not
want there and then tapping in included
that looks a little bit crazy and
ridiculous so once again dropping the
eraser tool and just lightly tapping
over everything to keep a little bit of
that dimension but just erasing it so it
still looks a little bit natural and
last I finally not at least when it
comes to editing the eyes at this step
is totally optional I personally love to
do this in all my photos it's really
what gives me that doll like look that a
lot of you guys love it's going to be to
brighten the actual eye so in this photo
emily has beautiful bright blue eyes but
clearly she's wearing a pretty big
lashes and black eyeliner so they did
get a little bit lost inside what I want
to do is grab the tones to all once
again and I'm going to dip into a kind
of like an aqua shade then zoom into the
pupils and I'm just gonna kind of place
that color right in the bottom and a
little bit of a rounded u-shape there it
is girl so good hello she thought it
staring it's my soul loved ah and then
of course erasers will top over it so
it's not too intense and too scary
alright I think we're ready for before
and after numero dos let's go and take a
look at what we were able to do -
Emily's rainbow eyeshadow look we have
the before and the
- literally so cute as you can see we do
not actually edit any makeup on just
edited what was already there to make it
a little bit more intense more vibrant
more eye-catching and I think this looks
so beautiful and so stunning and this is
actually like the same exact I think
that I used to edit my Coachella rainbow
makeup look photo so if any of you guys
recreate the look try this out and try
any of these techniques with your
eyeshadow looks I guarantee it'll make
your makeup look so much more beautiful
and so much more pop in it for your
sister selfies alright guys so let's see
who our next victim is that we already
did nose contour and also the our region
so I think I next want to focus on skin
you're kidding hello Britney J said give
me a snatch dose and a blinding highly
also this was a recreation of one of
your looks you guys are all so pretty
and talented what the huh oh here's this
Ginty okay Leah said can you fix my skin
please sister make it look snap so let's
see hello
it literally already is - okay I'm not
gonna help her but this does bring up a
really good point that I actually want
to mention when it comes to editing skin
and once again it this is saying that I
catch myself doing a lot what are the
biggest no-nose of face to ever is over
editing the skin there's this smooth
tool and there's a super smooth tool
moving can only go so far obviously it
always like to start out with the smooth
tool just lightly tap over everything to
kind of even out the base I personally
love the look of a little bit of skin
texture even if there's a few
imperfections in there because I think
it makes the photos look a lot more raw
and a lot more real and if you're
editing a lot more believable okay let's
see who we can actually help out here
hello okay this is a selfie from a
sister Anarky and I love her I follow
her on Twitter hey girl
what's up and she sent me this beautiful
host makeup selfie with this beautiful
pink weight on it hey girl
love that and she actually gave us a no
comment so I wouldn't think this healthy
version focus on the skin because
there's a few things that I want to
change to make this photo just a little
bit better alright so we have this photo
up and ready to go and the first step is
always going to be the smooth tool she
literally has almost perfect skin but
she does have a few blemishes right here
on the cheek that we can definitely get
rid of super easily so I'm gonna grab it
the patch tool like duct go right over
the pimple area and then bring it to an
area right next door in the contour just
to get rid of it and click the checkmark
and bam gone wow so easy is so beautiful
gonna go right over this same exact
thing click the little check mark wow
blemishes never heard of them
for me personally when I'm editing
photos if I have a really bad pimple
that's always the absolute first thing
to go I'm very very insecure about my
acne and I know
a lot of you guys out there are as well
but if you're able to rock your acne and
feel beautiful and confident with it go
you major props
unfortunately for myself cannot say the
same but if any you guys wonder how to
edit it out patch tool that's how so now
we go back into our normal regular
routine of styling the sister smooth
tool just to kind of blend everything
together and just give you a nice and
even base as you can see here if I click
the before and after it still keeps a
lot of that skin texture and a lot of
the dimensions of her face but it does
blend out some of those harsher areas
and contours making everything look
really really beautiful and more smooth
so much of the eye shadow I now when I
grab the details tool and I want to just
detail over any features such as the
eyes the eyebrows and the lips because
of course we did a smooth out the skin
and I don't want to lose any of that
dimension and I was time for the tones
tool and this is literally like my
all-time secret to getting a perfect
skin and freeze to it can't believe I'm
about to give you guys this full-on
secret but turn welcome I love doing
charity work I'm gonna grab the tones
tool and I just want to even out
anarchies skin tone and then a recontour
it so it looks literally so incredibly
statue all about to be so shot gonna
grab the picker tool and I'm gonna grab
this kind of light ish yellow shade or
right here underneath her eye and I'm
gonna use that and tones and I'm gonna
kind of brush that over this entire
region do not change the color I'm gonna
grab that same exact shade of yellow and
I'm gonna pop that right in the center
of her forehead right over her upper lip
region as well if you're like me and
you're a man you probably have a 5
o'clock shadow and if you're like
anarchy and you have beautiful big lips
usually your lip tends to flip up which
gives a natural shadow in this region so
sometimes it's really good to put a
highlighter there to kind of counteract
that so it doesn't look like a really
weird and gross by the clock shadow that
most of us probably do not want I'm also
gonna pop a little bit of this yellow
right here right kind of on the jaw line
region or right in between like this
contour area and then similar to every
other process so far I'm gonna grab the
eraser tool and I'm gonna lightly tap
over that entire region to keep the code
that I just added but make it a little
bit less intense so it's not like the
most and like literally bright yellow
okay so we just highlighted and our key
space by adding a lot of yellow all
around but she is a woman of color and
the last thing that I want to do is
lighten her skin tone or give her a
flash marry moment that is so not the
mood for today a so now I want to kinda
rock those highlights by a contouring a
little bit better grab the tones tool
once again and I'm gonna grab a shade
kind of on the outer perimeter of her
face right up in here by her hair
and I want to use that brown shade with
the tones tool to kind of add in and
intensify a little bit of those contours
to really bring a lot more dimension
back so I'm gonna place that right in
the hollows of her cheekbones kind of
right along her nose bridge similar to
sister Zoe from before hand and also
right up in that hairline region to make
the forehead look nice and snatched when
you're editing - before you go ahead and
save or erase anything it's really
important to check the little blue
button down here and select your before
and afters to see where your color
actually is as you can see right here I
accidentally put a little bit of brown
it and our he's hair and I definitely
did not want that there so I'm gonna be
eraser tool and just go right over at
that region because if that looks a
crusted busted and I actually have some
brown up here as well this contour looks
absolutely beautiful once again like I
said I'm gonna take the eraser tool
though and kind of soften it a little
bit because let's be real it's looking a
little bit harsh and I don't want her to
look crusted just a little bit more
chiseled alright guys I think we are
ready for our before and after sister
Anarky ready here we go we have the
before and BAM the after oh my god
literally so it's not as you can see it
by using the tones - and the details -
and the smooth tool you're able to
really even out that skin tone and make
it look so much more smooth while still
keeping all of the different highlights
and contours and looking beautiful and
defined these are the techniques that I
use in all of my photos to get beautiful
skin so hopefully you guys were able to
follow that and it was a little bit
complicated but I think anarchy is going
to absolutely love this alright sisters
so those are three photos of you guys
all completely edited if we started off
with this is your nose contour eye
shadow and then also skin off through
and I feel like that had all of the
different points that really go into my
face tuning Rutina but this video would
only be fair if now I have to face soon
myself until you guys what am i before
actors I done this a few times before
but let's be real I definitely face tune
a lot so I thought it'd be fun to kind
of look through some of the photos that
I've been taking recently and show you
guys what it takes to go from regular
photo to Instagram ready let's go
through a camera roll and find a good
and fresh
sister Instagram a selfie so that's you
can see of 8201 photos I definitely need
to go through and clean those up soon a
lot of them are a selfie he's okay I
have these always from a Shake Shack a
few days ago I took them while I was
eating fries I've been in fresh photo
shoot let's see other words you have to
pick up the one that I want first and
there's
a lot of them oh my god the lighting and
Shake Shack is literally the worst hello
wait that's not hey shake sucker I love
you please sponsor me okay I just go
through all these and the bad lighting
and the bad outfit choice not exactly my
favorite not even gonna lie but I think
that I finally decided on this photo to
possibly be grabbed don't even know
might be doing this editing all for
nothing but I'm gonna pull this one
right in to face soon and I'm gonna show
you guys the full-on process I'll be SP
through this because it's actually gonna
be a lengthy process but you guys get to
watch enjoy
[Music]
you
literally 20 minutes later that was ugly
a long visioning process but this photo
had a lot of saving to do let's be real
and I probably will even go back into
this later on and I think I'm ready to
show you guys this iconic sister James
Charles Instagram ready before and after
ready we have of course the before that
you guys all saw and one two three BAM
the after hello there was definitely a
lot that I wanted to do if we look at
the before and afters as if idli on the
base yeah sister needed a little bit of
work there was this really weird and
very very dark line going down the
entire side of my face I have no idea
what that was I'm assuming it was a
shadow from either like a windowpane or
something lord knows that's not usually
there at least I hope not I did do a
little bit of reshaping and you guys
know I'm very very insecure about the
size of my forehead so brought her down
just a little bit and then for the most
part I just evened out my skin tone
using the same techniques that we used
on sister anarchy slim down the nose
bridge is a little bit using the same
technique she used on sister Zoe and
then detailed the eyes like we did on
sister Emily that was super simple then
I finished it off using a not so simple
filter it does add a really really cool
effect and I think that that is it the
finished photo and I really like how
this turned out I was a little bit
spooked at first not gonna lie but I
think this might be Instagram ready
maybe
alright sisters that is only half for
this videos today and not even gonna lie
I just had so much fun for the past few
hours editing all these pictures base
hitting is of my all-time favorite
pastime so hopefully you guys all watch
us to learn some helpful and do it tips
and tricks that you can use next time
you're editing your Instagram pictures I
want to say a major thank you - Zoe
Emily and anarchy for all sending in
their unedited photos today it sounds
kind of cheesy to say but honestly post
an unedited photo online these days is
very very very brave you guys know like
I was talking about earlier literally
everybody edits their photos at this
point and it's something that I really
really love to do hopefully learn some
helpful tips and techniques and you guys
get to see that I never really like to
edit on makeup but really change myself
much I just like to edit and enhance
what's already there to take your photo
so I'm pretty good and really really
beautiful too like literally the best
ever have everybody shaking and having
wigs snatched left and right also side
note that I've been thinking about this
entire video like I just think
beforehand it is obviously okay to edit
to fix any insecurities that you may
have or just to make your photos look
really
Bob but it is so important that you guys
love yourselves love your bodies and
love the person that you are and of
course if you want to change that that
it's a very very personal decision but
you should definitely not rely on face
tune to be someone that you were
absolutely not as I was looking through
all the pictures that you guys sent in
today I was continuously stuff like
every few seconds of how beautiful you
all are of how talented you all are and
I just want to say if cheesy moment that
I do love you and you guys are all so
incredibly beautiful and this video was
100% strictly all for fun please do not
go crazy with these tips and techniques
I just want to show you guys a little
bit more about what I do but it is
important to love yourself I love myself
with or without face to reshape the
tones to all the details tool to smooth
tool and everything in between
and I really hope you guys do as well
all that being said if you guys enjoyed
today's a brand new video and if you
learn something new give me a thumbs up
down below and show your support it
really does mean a lot and also leave me
a comment and tell me what your favorite
technique that I taught you guys was
today if you have not already make sure
to click that big red subscribe button
down below come join the sisterhood it
is a pretty pretty lit time they'd also
click that belt like on so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup journey convolve me on instagram
on twitter they're both the same Charles
and my snapshot from work or how the
same time stuff it's Jana Charlotte that
extra asks after Charles this video is
sister Zelda cosa sister Biggs
thank you so much for always telling the
supporting you I love you so so so much
and I know this videos coming out a week
later but when I posted this it was your
birthday so have you birthday girl love
you the most and if you like to be the
next videos sister shout out my stories
or retweet via links whoa retweet my
video links but they go high on twitter
I need to go too bad alright sisters
thank you so much watching this video I
love you so much I'll see you in the
next one
[Music]