hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys know it is October meeting it
is my favorite time of the entire year I
love fall season is so so so so so much
I'll like the falling leaves and the hot
cocoa and the pumpkin spice lattes and
the cute decorations and
trick-or-treating at Halloween oh my god
I literally love it so much and I am so
excited as well to get back into all the
fun makeup looks like cranberries dark
Browns oh I am so so so here for it
obviously I'm fortunate I live in LA
well not really unfortunately I love it
here but in LA it is still very very hot
so I'm literally dying in this
turtleneck and denim jacket but I had to
get into the fall mood for you guys
sacrifices last night well my fighters
over I was editing a video and my friend
decided to unbox all my PR boxes on
snapchat which by the way if you don't
have me Ida you should definitely go
check me out over there I post on there
all the time and do lots of fun unboxing
rants story times etc but yeah my firmus
over here is unboxed everything and I
literally realized how much freaking
makeup I've been sent in the past few
weeks I was a little bit shook because I
had like literally 30 boxes to open but
I was so excited to try a ton of view
products for today's video I grabbed a
bunch of products that are new releases
or products that I have not yet tried
out and did a full face of fall first
impressions makeup and I absolutely love
how this look turned out spoiler alert
almost all the products that they use
today are really really really great so
without further ado if you'd like to see
how I created this look today using all
brand new products that are actually new
to my regular routine because I know
sister James is not switch it up very
often gyri picady junkies and let's get
started alright guys so I'm first gonna
start off by priming my face using the
no horrible um primer from touch and
soul this is a smooth and pore covering
a top-secret for perfect makeup primer
and I'm very very excited to try this
out I know a sister Jeffrey twice about
this all the time on his channel and
absolutely stands by it
I for one haven't actually never tried
it before so I'm very pumped you guys
know that my skin has actually been a
pretty good recently because I've been
moisturizing a lot but I definitely
still have a lot of pores unfortunately
oh wow this feels really good so three
seconds in and I already like this
primer it feels so incredibly like
smooth and the poreless but that being
said I absolutely have no product on my
face right now so let's go to some
foundation and see how it actually holds
up
for foundations today are gonna be going
into the milk makeup blur liquid
foundation and this isn't the shade of
golden light I hope this is the right
shade for me
these released a few weeks ago on a milk
makeup but I actually have not gotten a
chance to try them out but many of my
friends really really like this so I'm
gonna try it out for myself
I definitely like a good full coverage
foundation and you guys know that I am a
hardcore stand of the make up ever ultra
oh that's a good match think on of the
Make Up For Ever Ultra HD stick so it's
pretty hard at this point to ever beat
that one but let's go ahead and apply
this and see what we think so this is a
liquid foundation that is set to dry
down in a natural matte formula meaning
it it's like pretty matte but still has
like a little bit of do to it which is
definitely the styler foundation that I
like you guys know that I am really not
digging like the full baked full matte
look anymore and I do like a little bit
of a natural glow so holding this
foundation if it does what it says will
be a really really great one for me okay
so the foundation was all applied and
blend out and I don't love it but I also
don't hate it at all the match of color
is really really good free and I'm
definitely like a fan of this it matches
my scanner pretty well which is a very
rare occasion on the channels YouTube
channel I know you guys always drive me
for it my skin texture it looks decent
I've had foundations I think my skin
look better and it's definitely hot ones
that made it look worse I noticed that
it is deadly so I'm pretty a little bit
on my nose which I hate you guys know
that's like my biggest pet peeve when it
comes to nose contour not being able to
have like a perfect one so not loving
that the coverage is really really good
though because I skin look very very
even all that being said I'm gonna go
ahead and apply the rest of my routine
now and I will come back to the
foundation later on and see how it wears
that everything else later on top
obviously I don't have any dupe
concealers to try out today so I'm just
gonna use my handy dandy shave tape in
the shade of light okay so actually
after Lang shaped tape over top of the
foundation I like how this looks a lot
more and layered over top especially in
like the poor region really really
nicely I love my under eyes look right
now as well as my nose was fixed by the
same tape thank God we're not about to
have a walking nose contour today those
days are long gone
I'm gonna go ahead and set my face in
the normal place he's using the brand
new two-faced peach perfect modifying
setting powder
I know Jackie ina said she loved this
I've been super looking forward to
trying oh and yeah hopefully we won't
get any flash like marriage today I'm
just gonna make sure any creases that I
have under there
gone and then just pack on the setting
powder oh my god actually smells like
peaches ah that sounds the best ever oh
my god
okay whoa talk about a mattifying sign
encoder my face looks like as dry as the
Sahara Desert but not like a bad way I'm
honestly really taking it but I'm
definitely gonna have to apply a lot of
highlighter later on ask for the actual
powder first of all it smells literally
the best like this is really really good
I don't think I've ever had a setting
powder that actually smelled like good
and not like actual death or like
Grandma which is my so I like this a lot
and looking up close my pores are like
gone like literally they look so covered
and filled in this honestly may very
well be a brand new favorite I know I
don't really like baking any more but
I'm gonna go ahead and use this powder
to lightly baked just to see if it does
bring any intensity and brightness back
to the face especially I like the nose
contour region underneath the contour
like I always do
but before I do that I'm gonna go ahead
and stretch my face a few times using
some mac fix+ just because I'm looking
extremely dry right now and I need some
of that hydration bra back at my Vegas
now let's get up nose as usual using my
Beauty Blender and pack it on to the
areas that I want to be a little bit
brighter before I actually go to my
brows I'm gonna add a little bit of
blush using the brand new Anasazi a
blush kit and the shade radiant I would
normally do this before I actually make
my face but it completely slipped my
mind I'm gonna use this shade in the top
right hand corner called coastline it is
so pretty under mine see a little bit of
the amok in the shade peaches which you
guys always my multi-faith and I'm just
gonna apply this using my more pe4 brush
well that is really pigmented okay so we
all know Anastacio does not play around
when it comes to pigment but I deftly
put on a little bit too much I'm gonna
grab my ours your brush from morphe and
just my face powder and go over that a
little bit to kind of make it a little
bit more subtle so now that my face is
all done and baking the oven at 350
degrees we have a little bit of a
cooking malfunction there but we're
gonna go ahead and move on and next is
going to be the brows today I don't have
any new brow products to try out for you
guys so I'm just gonna go in with my
normal benefit brow products I'm gonna
first go in with the benefit car brow
gel in the shade number 4 and start to
to find out the tail as you guys know
there was actually a really good long
while where I stopped using pomade
products on my brows altogether and just
went over to a pencil
I feel like the old James Charles block
IRA was so so bad and a very touchy and
dark subject we should talk about I
think what cause that was way too much
brow pomade so I just stopped using it
altogether but recently I've kind of
been getting it back into it just to
like really define it the brows and get
super super sharp lines and honestly I'm
actually kind of living for it we just
have to make sure that we don't get back
into that original Brown style again as
always I'm just gonna grab a little bit
of concealer on my morphe e43 brush and
clean up that bottom edge once eyebrow
is all cleaned up and defined I'm gonna
grab the 24-hour brow setter and use
this to brush all the hair Stinton place
I've actually been using this a lot more
than the Gimme brow gel and I still love
gimme brow don't get me wrong but this
one is clear it just does a really good
job of brushing the hair is like into
place but also keeping them like
literally glued down it's almost like a
liquid version of hairspray and it's I
like this law so now that the brows are
all slayed and locked in place we're
gonna move on to the eye shadow and for
today I do have a new first impressions
that I am literally so excited to try
out and that is the Laura Lee Los
Angeles cat's pajamas eyes shadow
palette I cannot wait so this is the
actual palette it is absolutely stunning
it comes with ten shades for $40 which
is only $4 a shadow which is not bad at
all I will say I have not put this on my
eyes but I definitely haven't done a few
swatches and this is so incredibly good
let's just do like let's just do one
just to show you guys I'm gonna go ahead
and grab the shade of redonkulous on my
middle finger we're just gonna do like
like you're kidding
it is so pigmented as Manny would say my
first girl the shade okie-dokie on my
m/45 brush and just uses to stuff the
eyelid in place to prepare for shadow so
first good our way I'm four for one and
dip into the shade bomb-diggity and uses
of the transition ok whoa those that
feel a little bit a kickback on the
shadow but I really don't like that oh
that just means it's really pigmented so
hopefully this isn't like the Anasazi of
self culture point but let's put an
apply and see how it blends in oh yeah
okay whoa the shade of Lee blends out
not as vibrant as you see in the palette
but that is definitely not a negative
for me at all this shade looks
absolutely beautiful as a transition
shade in the eyelid crease and it is
blending like butter like that looks
really really good oh my god
yes sister Laura I'm next going to grab
a clean m4a3 three brush and dip into
the shade of cray-cray and deepen up the
crease a little bit you guys a little
could knock it over how well these
shades are blending together like Deezer
really really good shadows that looks so
good oh my god I'm next to me I have
another m4a3 three brush and dip into
the shade it kooky and use that once
again to deepen up the crease a little
bit and prepare for the eyelid shadow
I'm honestly so shocked right now like I
was expecting this to be good but like
this eye look is literally blending it
sounds like you guys are watching this
all go down I'm like whoa if you guys
haven't noticed it's actually really
really rare for makeup brands to include
reds or Maroons in their palettes
because a red formula is really really
hard to perfect and make it pigment in
it to blend enough on the eyes and the
fact that Laura included it in her first
palette and it's actually like really
good is major major points in my buck I
can't even tell you I am so so sick of
having palettes that are full of
beautiful beautiful oranges and there is
not a single red shade on my girl
I need the Maroons I need the Reds I
need the cranberries and this palette is
honestly giving it to me so I'm living
for this for my little gonna grab a flat
Packer brush and get into the shade in
one year in fact that on the lid and I'm
actually gonna grab some Mac fix
actually you know what let's go ahead
and apply on the lid a dry person see
how that applies then use some fix glass
you're literally kidding this is already
so pretty and I haven't even wet it yet
I'll Linder grab more on that same brush
with my mac fix+ and really pack that on
there to make it super metallic you her
kidding that looks absolutely stunning
just out of curiosity I'm also gonna go
a little bit of that on my finger and
try to play it that way I might let just
see how it looks
Wow
this shade is absolutely beautiful just
add a little bit more dimension I'm
gonna grab a tiny fluffy brush this is
my M 506 and dip into out the other oh
my god get it in one ear and out the
other
so freakin clever and I'm gonna use this
to it deepen up the outer corner a
little bit for the news in that stay
brush I'm gonna grab the littlest bit of
the shade oddball and really deep it out
just that or a V just to add some more
down and then to finish off the upper
lid I'm gonna grab my on 5/13 at one
last time and dip right back to cry cry
and then I'm just going to buff out
those edges I love how this is turning
out oh my god for the lower lash then
I'm first gonna go my own for a 3:3
brush and the shade of Craig right and
just put in a light transition shade and
I always like to make sure especially in
this outer corner here that the lower
lashline and upper lashline shadow are
connected what my biggest have peace
ever some people have like a nice sharp
defined line right here to cut that like
powder shadow wing and then all it's on
the bottom lash line shadow starts but
they're not connected like there's
literally like a I just I really hate
how that looks so next thing I grab my
m1 tube for our brush and dip into the
shade at Kuki and use this to hug my
upper or my lower lash line next to my
gram I am a five five nine and didn't
took the shade it Corky and use that to
deep it up right up at the lash line and
then finally describing a little tiny
bit more of oddball
just to deepen up that very outer corner
to highlight the brow bone I'm gonna
grab the shade a scatterbrain on just a
flat packing brush and it'll brought
that on there oh wow I'm also gonna play
a little bit of that on the inner corner
as well okay I was gonna save all my
thoughts until the end of the video but
I'll just go ahead and say it right now
because I feel confident and my answer
that this palette from Laura Lee Los
Angeles the cat's pajamas palette is so
so good I honestly was not expecting
anything less than really great from
lore but this how it like really it's
just beyond great as you can see the
shadows blend so well together they are
incredibly
when said if there would be one negative
thing about it that I would want to
mention is that some of the shadows do
have a lot of Fallout which I don't see
a personal problem with it that just
means a really pigmented if anything
just make sure you tap your brush before
you actually put it on or just make your
face you can wave everything away at the
end but like I said this palette 10 out
of 10 definitely sister James recommend
do it alright so I just went ahead I did
the other eye off-camera super quickly
and that the eyes are both done I'm
gonna apply some lashes today as always
but I do have a new first impressions
today and those are the more feet
eyelashes I am obviously a morphe
affiliate you guys know that you can use
Koji's or 10% off or over your products
I literally say all the time and even
have a hoodie with the setting on it
also check out section parallel comm for
all your sisters merch anyway all that
being said I was up the morphe office a
few weeks ago and i was like looking
through all their products and I was
like wait a second are those lashes and
one we hold Murphy has lashes which I
literally did not even know about they
were not announced I just kind of came
to the store but they look beautiful
then I'm gonna be applying in style i
traction which look very very similar to
the house lashes like onyx and they are
stunning
so while I clean all these launches I
guess I will give you guys the rundown I
absolutely love how the style looks
especially with the shape of the eye
shadow that I went with today the one
thing that I will say about these lashes
that I don't love is the actual band on
them the style of lash is beautiful but
the band is really really thin and
flimsy now some people may like that
because it's really easy to like kind of
manipulate it but I personally prefer a
much thicker and more durable band
because I kind of feel like when you
come to glue it on it's a lot harder to
work with but I feel like that works and
the fact that it won't come off as easy
whereas like now that we have a thin
band it's kind of just like flipping
around and I really had to make sure I
like how's it on their wall gluing it on
at the end of the day it's really up to
personal preference I don't love this
lash band like I said but these lashes
are only retailing for $10 and with an
influencer code they are nine dollars so
it is much better than like a lily lash
or a New Balance and watch I just I love
them so you guys could totally make your
own decision on that but yeah these
lashes are beautiful just don't love the
band so those are both eyes all complete
I honestly love how the suck is turning
oh so far and then the eyes are done are
next up is going to be the glow and once
again for the glow I do have a first
impressions product and that is the
brand new Anasazi sugar
glow can I
Gazi basically chose all the favorite
highlighters from the individual
highlighter palettes before and put them
all together into one palette what to
think is absolutely genius it's like a
favorites palette within the actual
brand so that is super super dope and I
think if we're actually going to go
ahead and apply and mix it the shape of
butterscotch and starburst today for
this look as always I'm gonna play using
Miami
501 brush I mean this really should come
to no surprises you guys we all know
that anastacio always kill that their
highlighters I've been using so
Hollywood in literally every single
video for the past like almost two years
now but wow I'm sure these are so good
now that my highlight is all on I'm
gonna grab my blush brush one more time
which is my e4 and dip into the shade at
terracotta and breeze and this put a
little bit of this more on the
cheekbones just to kind of blend
together the highlight because I feel
like it is a little bit too pigmented
and it's not yeah a lot better there we
go I just completely didn't finish my
sentence it's a little bit too pigmented
and it's not blending together for that
one for the lips today I'm gonna play
the ofra liquid lipstick in the shade
Hannah Lulu as a base this was literally
the perfect lip color to use for this
look oh my god I think I'm actually
gonna take my packing brush and dip it
back into the laurel leaf I grab a
little bit of porky and in one ear
together and make this lip metallic okey
whoa adding that shadow was like
literally the pounce idea opera this
looks so so pretty and was literally the
easiest way to make a DIY metallic
liquid lipstick protip simple DIY if you
ever have a lipstick that drives down
matte but you want it to be metallic
just put it on let it dry it out
completely and then just layer over top
with a similar shade of metallic
eyeshadow and there you go super easy
and looks so so good and all that being
said this look is all complete so let's
go ahead and finish off with a little
spritz of Urban Decay all nighter
setting spray
alright guys and that is this fall first
impressions makeup look all complete I
absolutely love how this look turned out
and honestly I think I pretty much liked
almost every sync one of the products
we've tried today which is so exciting
starting over from the beginning the no
horrible um primer there we go that's a
mouthful from a touchin sole was
absolutely wonderful it made my skin
feel so so good and super smooth
definitely did like a blurring effect
which I love next up we use the milk
makeup foundation and I was in the shade
golden light it was a really really good
match for my skin as you can see which
normally does not happen on the future
channel so that is great it wasn't my
favorite product in the world but it
also was my least favorite it looks
really really beautiful all the skin and
is honestly holding up really really
well till at least I have a little bit
of a problem start with us on my nose
which is like honestly a breaking point
for any foundation for me my nose
contour is super super important to me
and vital to my makeup routine so as
soon as a foundation it doesn't sit well
on my nose that is instantly out for me
but I feel like the pros of this
foundation are outweighing the cons so I
like it definitely try that for yourself
and let me know what you guys think next
up we use the Laura Lee Los Angeles
cat's pajamas eyes shadow palette and I
already told you guys what I think of
this this is so incredibly bomb it
launches on October 13 you guys have to
check this out one that comes out these
shadows girl Laura Lee Kelton let me
forget it once again but we also use the
Anastacio radiant blush palette and I
use the shade coastline and terrace and
breeze all together so literally three
out of the four shades of the palette I
really really like the firm of these
they blended beautifully the only thing
I will say is that they are super super
pigmented so if you check these out just
using a very very light hand because you
might be looking a little bit crazy we
also went in with the new honest cons
you have sugar lo can't which as you
guys know Anasazi always kills the
cloaca came and I use the shades of
butterscotch and starbursts today and I
love how the skull looks I mean
come on girl it's like so blinding
alright guys most of all the new product
she tried out today definitely leave me
a comment down below and tell me which
out of everything I just talked about
that you want to try the most they were
honestly also good and I would totally
recommend them so I can't wait for you
guys to get your hands on them and let
me know what you think if you guys
enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below if you have not already I posted
three videos a week and I'd love to have
you join to the sisterhood if you'd like
to follow me on my makeup journey you
can follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both dis James Charles and my
snapchat for world well had the seed
plates up is James Charles that extra
ass after Charles if you're already a
sister or if you're new to the
sisterhood don't forget to check out
sisters apparel calm which is my
clothing line for all your official
sisters merch and Kia alright guys thank
you so much for watching I love you so
much and I will see you in the next one
bye
[Music]