hi sisters James Harold's here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel as
you can see we're not in the normal
white ball background makeup studio
because today I am here in Coachella
Valley in California because it is
Coachella this weekend and I am
literally so excited I mean all my
friends got sisters VIP passes it's
hashtag lit anyway I wish I did not just
say that but for today's video I wanted
to do a fun festival inspired makeup
tutorial I want to do a rainbow look
it's been a hot minute since I've
actually played with color and a few
weeks ago I posted a rainbow eye picture
on my Instagram and it's out of my
all-time at most like photos so thank
you and sisters for always killing of
the game and then also I did maybe go
and buff and beyond with my Coachella
Alpha it's like your guys's wigs are
about to be snatched at this point when
seeing this video you guys have already
probably seen them over on my Instagram
but at the end of the video as well I
want to do a little fun at Coachella
lookbook so I hope you guys are excited
and let's get on the video I'm first
gonna talk with using a good sunscreen
this is the touch-up pore perfecting
silk'n sunscreen hello SPF 35 we are
obviously in the middle of the desert
and it is really ridiculously hot here
and the Sun is intense so it's really
important that you protect your skin
even when you're putting a full face of
makeup on it can definitely penetrate
all the way through and I rather be safe
than sorry I'm also gonna use my
all-time babe the touch out water cream
moisturizer I love this thing it's
literally so good like Hello it just
makes my skin it's so soft and smooth
and the air out here is ridiculously dry
like I said we're in the middle of a
desert so I really want to make sure
that my skin is hydrated and doesn't get
the air sucked out of it and last but
not least first skin prep I'm gonna go
to the touch-ups cell canvas you guys
know I'm really not a big fan of primers
but this one for some reason it's just
really really bomb it fills in the pores
and honestly makes my skin so so so
smooth and with the amount of dust
that's gonna be flying around in the air
at this festival I really want to make
sure for once my pores are filled so
they can't get clogged and other stuff
if that makes sense
skincare 101 with sister James /
foundation said I'm gonna go to the Too
Faced Born This Way Foundation you guys
know this is my all-time a favor and a
fun fact actually last year at Coachella
was the first time I ever tried this
foundation and I literally have fall in
love with it and used it ever since
and thank you doing friend hay-zu's for
showing it to me it's actually so cool
because a lot of my friends have changed
a lot this past year but my best friends
have all remained exactly this
and last year Coachella it was me and
Laura and Victor and Marcos and his
girlfriend Brittany and then hay-zu's
and we just got crunk and partied the
entire time sober of course but now
we're all back here together and it's
just such an amazing amazing group of
friends that I am so blessed to have in
my life
I'm literally pray that this foundation
color is going to match me when I take
photos later on today I did just get
spray tans literally the darkest I've
ever been and I was hoping that it was
gonna wash off a lot in my shower this
morning and it did it but you know what
we're just going for that bronzy
Coachella type of look I'm really really
hoping that this foundation matches it's
kind of hard to tell because we are an
outside lighting which I'm definitely
not used to but we're gonna make it work
it's actually so crazy to think about
because I'm pretty sure when I went to
Coachella last year with Laura and all
the sisters that my Instagram was just
over 1 million followers like you're
literally kidding me and we just hit 4
million a few days ago like that is so
beyond insane to me I was looking
through all the photos from last year
and just reminiscing and I'm just so
excited to be here again I really really
do love music festivals and obviously
you guys know music plays a huge part in
my life and I'm just so excited to just
listen to some really really dope music
have some really amazing outfits and
just see a ton of friends and a bunch of
you guys as well I think there's gonna
be a full-on
sister be angry I like taking over
Coachella but I am so beyond ready for
it
the air here is literally so dry
concealers already drying down oh my god
I'm scared but you took one this so fast
oh there's B there's a B there's B oh
it's a fly I don't know I've never
actually talked about this on camera
before but I am like literally deathly
afraid of bees for some reason I've
never been stung don't even know if I'm
allergic I just hate that with all my
heart I'm gonna blend out this concealer
underneath my eyes and then literally
hover my setting powder like right at
the ready I'm so scared at how dry this
weather is and how fast everything is
drying down which means if we don't set
this fast enough we're gonna get sister
creases and all the wrong places all day
long for the remainder my face I'm gonna
grab a really dense powder puff and
really pack it into the powder and Pat
this on it has been a hot minute since
I've like really a baked and powdered my
faith but I am gonna be really really
hot and sweaty today the Sun is like
beaming down yeah I know the Alpha that
you guys are gonna see it later on in
today's lookbook video I am gonna be
wearing a face Mac so I really wanna
make sure that my face is very very set
and pleased to get as little foundation
transfer on it as possible because it's
a sister Louie Vuitton bandana and that
was way too expensive to have a
foundation encrusted and dusted all over
it before I go in and really contour my
face I'm gonna grab the brand new k'kaw
highlighting
brightening powder oh my god if you guys
thought my video over on nikkietutorials
channel reviewed this this powder is so
bomb like literally and sane I have an
absolutely lovingness to pack on right
in the high points of my face to give it
a really really bright end and contoured
look I'm also gonna pop this right up
here in the corners of my eyes right
down onto the middle of my face and onto
the sides of the nose to help further
that snatched illusion coming in a
second next make sure we have that
bronzy summery glow I'm gonna grab my
morphe am 5 to 7 brush and my Anasazi a
contouring kit and dip into the right
two shades right up in here and use this
to really chisel on my face today hey
sister oh we got sister Laura coming
tail I mostly make sure to really
contour out and snatch that jawline as
well you guys know we gotta be as as
little as possible at all times always I
definitely need to chisel out my nose
and make her good and snatch this
lighting is a little bit spooky so it's
probably looking the worst oh that's a
little harsh oh I'm actually really
happy with how the base is looking right
now or at least I think I am before I'm
gonna really bake everything out I am
gonna give myself a light spritz of the
skins a navy eye makeup finishing spray
before we put on a more powder this to
do is it sponsored by Scandinavia so
thank you so much to them for sending me
and my friends to Coachella you guys
know I don't really work as a whole lot
of brands here on my channel but I just
really really love skins a navy and
they're by far one of the best brands I
have ever worked and they're just so
nice they trust me as an influencer I
loved in the most so makeup finishing
spray so bomb obviously were gonna use
it just our face but just to give it a
little sister hydration because we're
looking a little bit dry right now I
guess we're gonna use our ticket box to
fan our piece today because I forgot my
dad at home I got a good question I'm
really really looking forward to
obviously sister Beyonce and sister
cardi B I'm sister says oh there's
knowing about her once
yeah rollerskating she was literally so
sweet she was with her two nieces and
they were sisters so hey it says his
nieces if you guys are watching and she
was just so nice literally the entire
time she was like interacting with
different people at the roller skating
rink
this acting like a normal person which
was just like really really dope to see
because she's one of the biggest people
in the world right now she's so talented
like hello I'm a sister says a stand to
see her perform today I'm gonna bake
myself in the oven for a few minutes I
guess just by standing out on the Sun
because literally thought is like the
heat temperature we're dealing with
right now at home do my brows off-camera
quickly I'll be right back to start off
the eye makeup
let's go ahead and jump right into this
rainbow I look and of course that i'll
be using the morphe at 35 be Pella this
is my all-time favorite I already went
ahead and started up writing my eyelids
and instead of using a translucent
powder I actually use the white
eyeshadow here so hopefully that'll make
all the colors a little bit brighter I'm
gonna grab a fluffy brush and dip into
the yellow shade first and pop that
right in the inner corners normally you
guys know I'd like to start off kind of
light and then blend in it but for these
type of looks I'm really gonna pack the
colors in there and then blend them in
after because I really want the colors
to be as pegmatite as possible next
gonna grab a fluffy blending brush into
the orange shade impact that right in
the center on the crease well take kind
of placing that color on there and then
blending it out I think you should have
really focuses pigment right in the
crease because I am going to cut it
today and then just use the excess
shadow left on the brush to blend it
upwards into this region and also
slightly into the color next to it after
I finished each color I'm gonna go back
into the previous color with the same
exact brush and make sure that they're
evenly blended together right in that
transitional region next under grab one
last faulty blending brush in the bright
red shade in the palette and I'm going
to finish off that I look and I'm
actually gonna pull the shadow white out
into the classic v-shape that you guys
know I live before wasn't owl hooting
right now it's like 2:00 p.m. all right
I was nocturnal they're awake and let
ready to go I'm also gonna pop the same
exact colors in the same order on my
lower lashline as well what I did this
look originally I went with a very very
bright look but for today's look that I
have planned I'm doing a very very like
ninja inspired type of dark and smoky
looks like I'm gonna using a whole lot
of black to really smoke this out and
make the colors really really intense
I'm gonna go ahead and line my lower and
upper water lines that I using the
Maybelline lasting drama waterproof
pencil I just picked this one up super
quickly at a store I forgot mine at home
love that of course sister James is
forgetting everything are we surprised
we really shouldn't be you guys know I
absolutely hate doing this but I feel
like it is very very vital for the type
of look that we're going forward today
oh well that's dark and it's gonna
really highlight my eyes if you guys
notice as well it has been a hot minute
since I've worn my grey contacts in a
video but I feel like they're
appropriate for today's look I'm gonna
grab a small flat pocket brush this is
the Sigma e 20s and very very carefully
at up off the excess and then blend this
right into the lower lash line
okay need way more than that or the
outer V region to actually want the
block to be really really defined this
is a really really good and thick
cardboard so I'm gonna do is actually
rip this and this is a technique that a
lot of different drag queen
and I'm actually going to hold this
cardboard onto my eye I don't know how
to do this here Bob could you friend who
hold your handheld mirror for you that's
a legit sister right there okay I'm
gonna place this card right on the
corner of my eye I'm placing the shade
on here in the shape of kind of like a
winged liner and then I'm of course
going to blend it out by having this
cardboard there and really pressing it
onto the face you're gonna get a really
really clean line when I take this off
we're just gonna make it so much easier
because you guys know if with a little
bit too much black your look can go from
really really beautiful to really really
muddy and spooky real real fast if
you're not careful oh wow I really
thought I had it there I'm scared I'm
gonna have another smaller fluffy brush
and some more black shadow and attempt
to blend out this outer corner it's
looking a little bit spooky totally I
don't know how to take my own advice and
the situation and I'm gonna pull this
really lightly into the crease right
before we get ready to cut it this is
looking spooky I was really confident
this time I'm not as confident that on
this side of the yard there's little old
me filming a rainbow makeup tutorial and
on that side of the yard Laura's husband
and her brother are having a drinking
competition to see who can drink a can
of beer faster
I love Coachella okay I think I'm
actually kind of happy with how this is
turning out maybe it's lightly I'm just
basically going in a back-and-forth with
both black and the different colors that
I'm using to really create the eye shape
that I'm trying to go for today it's
really hard to blend black seamlessly
into other colors especially ones that
are bright like orange and yellow and
create a seamless transition but I feel
like we did a pretty decent job now that
I have the basic eye all complete I'm
gonna take a really really light
concealer this is the k'kaw beauty one
put it on the back of my hand and I'm
going to cut my crease using a mac 242
brush and before that can see that even
dries down I'm gonna go ahead and grab
the in your dreams
iridescent angel cosmetic glitter impact
that right over top of the lid for a
nice pop oh my god that is so pretty
oh you're kidding hello okay now I'm
actually loving how this is looking so
this took a nice turn for the better
for once now that we have the glitter
all place on though I'm gonna grab that
fluffy brush that had a black on it and
kind of blend out this outer V if so
there's an even transition between the
glitter and the black and I'm gonna kind
of pull this into the lash line as well
so it creates like a more rounded cut
crease type of shape I forgot glitter
glue on this shape which is classic me
so I'm gonna grab a little bit of lash
glue and dab it on the back of my hand
and try to like I don't even know how
I'm gonna
that's rude I'm gonna get the Tom Ford
liner as well into a fan up black line
along by a flashlight just for some more
dimension I'm gonna grab that flat
smudging brush that we used on the lower
lash in as well dive into a little bit
of block and then go right over that
liner that we just put on there so it's
kind of a more smudge liner type of love
all right guys and that is one eye off
complete obviously we still have lashes
to do but that took me a hot minute so
I'm gonna call the cameras quickly relax
in the shader for a little bit so I'm
not burning and do the other eye
off-camera of course at the green blue
and then purple and I'll be right back
to finish off the rest of the love all
right case about one hour later now
literally Coachella's gonna be over by
the time I'm done with my makeup today
but I just finished both eyes I deftly
was not loving them at first but I think
they definitely turned out pretty decent
and of course we have sister face soon
to save the day so I'm gonna play a
light coat of the Mac extended play
mascara to prep for lashes I'm gonna
make sure to get those really really
evenly coated as well because you guys
know I don't really do what black smokey
looks very often but when I do to them
it's really important that you get a
good coat of mascara so that there's no
light spots and everything blends really
really well together and then for lashes
today I'm gonna pop on a pair of Lillie
lashes Miami's you guys know these are
my all-time faves and wispy I did not
spend an hour on each eye look today to
get them covered up by a big lashes so
these be the perfect solution I'm gonna
pop this right on the exact center of
the eyelid and really make sure to pull
that ending upwards because we did do a
v-shape with this eye shadow look today
and I want to make sure that the eyelash
follows suit and doesn't look droopy
because you really want the eyes to look
kind of a port and snatched oh yeah
she's looking good this is really good
okay alright so those are both eyes all
done and complete thank the Lord that
took way too long and now it's time for
the glow so I'm gonna grab my Anasazi of
Beverly Hills so Hollywood highlighter
my all-time favorite but before I do
that I'm gonna get myself once again a
quick spritz of the skin to Navia
settings way to get my skin is nice and
damn oh yeah there she is girl oh-ho-ho
wow we truly love a glowing sister
apparently so does that bird I'm gonna
play a little bit of this right onto the
brow bone so they really pop and then
I'm gonna grab the Tarte shimmer clay
pot in the shade up top yeah this is
what my all-time favorite pigments for
in a corner highlighting it is literally
so freakin pretty ready for this
hello so good I got these little gem
sent to me from the brand in your dreams
and they look so cute I think I want to
pop these little teardrop ones right
underneath the eye to really bring
attention to them oh yeah we love her
she's good
wait I want to put little those two
little dots above my eyes - I love these
ideas okay where do they go oh oh you
know why I have an idea
Oh ready for this let's place this one
yeah okay this we're down for okay that
only took 17 years whoa finally moving
on we have a lipid e doodahs I'm just
gonna use a classic glossy nude lip
clearly we have a lot going on the our
region so we definitely want the focus
to be up here and not down here and
laughs but finally not least of course
we have to set it in place and one last
time thank you so much to Scandinavia
purse aren't you in this video I'm gonna
give my face good set with the makeup
finishing spray and this is the oil
control version we know we're gonna be
sweating a whole lot today so I wanna
make sure this is really locked and the
skins nav your settings right is set to
last for 16 hours and it's truly my
favorite settings for in the entire
world this stuff is so so so bomb and
yes obviously this video is sponsored
but I do love them and they're just an
amazing company to work with seriously I
love them they're just absolutely the
best and they trust me as a creator so
please sisters go show them the love
because both me and Scandinavia love you
sisters so much you can now use code
James for 25% off hello quarter off your
sister setting spray go pick it up right
now I promise you will not regret it and
make sure you go thank them for sending
me and all my friends to Coachella so we
could have this amazing content for you
guys and so we can enjoy ourselves and
have a little bit of fun rude all right
sisters and that is this rainbow
festival makeup look all complete I
absolutely love how this turned out it
has been a hot minute since I've been
able to play with a whole lot of color
and I really really love this and I hope
you guys did as well if you wear this
look to any festivals make sure to tweet
me a picture I cannot wait to see all
your beautiful faces but this video is
not over yet
I came to slay this Coachella season so
hold on to your wigs and let's do a
little sister look bow
[Music]
[Applause]
all right sisters I hope you enjoyed
that mini little lookbook and tutorial
this video was so much fun to film and I
really really hope you guys enjoyed it
if you did don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and leave me a
comment as well I love doing love books
I do have a huge passion for fashion I
love being a poet without even knowing
it and if you guys want me to do more of
these I would really really love to do
them I love a good sister styling moment
if you have not already don't forget to
click that big red subscribe button down
below and come and join the sisterhood
we are so close to 4 million so thank
you guys so so so much and as well click
that Bell icon so you can notified every
time I upload a brand new video if you
like to follow me and I make up chard
you can follow me on Instagram Twitter
they're both the same Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes type
stuff is James Charles is an extra s
after Charles don't forget to go
DoubleTap all those Coachella pictures
just in case you guys missed that mystic
sister shout out goes to sister Kelly
who's been behind the camera for the
past four hours burning and also sister
hey-zeus who's incident next to me
helping me do the products holding up my
mirror for me being the true sisters
that they are love you guys both thanks
for the charity works today
alright sisters I love you so much and I
will see you in the next video bye and
happy festival season
[Music]