hi sisters James Turrell turn welcome
back to my youtube channel you guys for
today's video I am a little bit doing
something that I've wanted to do for so
long now this has been on my video ID
list for like a million years I don't
know why I've never gotten to it I think
I've been too scared of the idea but you
know what I love a good sister challenge
and for today's video I went to Hobby
Lobby of Michaels every craft store I
could possibly find and I'm gonna be
getting a fully ready hopefully using
all art supplies at this point I think I
am a little bit a broken record was
saying like oh my god I started doing
makeup for the are we gonna James you
think you're talented who art has always
been a huge huge huge passion of mine
and it's what got me into makeup but
even before doing makeup I was always
drawing always painting always coloring
to a lot of the materials they have here
in front of me such as chalk pastels
paint brushes watercolors face paint and
sponges I am definitely not a stranger
to but they usually do not go on the
face I think this we are really fun and
potentially dangerous challenge
hopefully I don't get a break out from
using this stuff on my face but you know
what that's why it's called a challenge
I got without further ado let's jump
right into the video for foundation
today I got this tempera paint by upon
reading the label that says warning not
safe for consumption can cause cancer
great so this is not happening today I'm
just gonna use my normal foundation and
powder but I did find these natural fine
sponges at the craft store so Beauty
Blender never heard of her
we're gonna use a natural fine sponge
today I just went ahead and dampened and
then wrong on my Beauty sponges in the
sink I'm gonna grab my two-faced for
this way in the shade a warm nude you
guys know this my all-time favorite and
I'm gonna put it on my artiste palette
today when I think of artists why I was
like the first thing to come to mind a
little French man with a beret and a
little mustache painting it a little
easel we wait I am an artiste
okay first foundation brush today I'm
gonna use this one an actual paint brush
and I'm going to get my little palette
and brush it on oh the brush and then
apply it to the canvas oh my god low-key
want to supply really really nicely
hello what's going on - my fellow beauty
gurus out there who may be watching this
video I don't ever want to hear a single
one of y'all ever say
I'm just gonna paint this on until using
an actual paintbrush surprisingly this
is like not that Bob can't forget to
blend down the neck that I'm just gonna
take one of my own natural blending
sponges and dip it into the access
product on at the pallet and use that to
kind of stipple it end oh my god this is
kind of working Picasso is gonna be
trembling in his grave can I say that is
that offensive for a concealer of course
they're gonna grab my tart shave tape
and this is in the shade light neutral
and I'm gonna put it o want my little
pal ain't I need to stop doing about
right now and then to apply I'm gonna
use this filbert 8 brush this literally
looks like a more PM 2 to 4
conspiracy-theory morphe brushes are
just artist brushes repackage whoa
low-key why is this brush like really
good this is doc really staying in my
collection for hot dog creases you've
got to be kidding me okay once again
beauty sponge to blend it all out now
that my face is all set in place I'm
going to set it using another natural
sponge and then it's the Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder this I'm
actually scared about okay I'll sit in
there Oh God so now that we have the
base all down in set in place we can
finally start building on top of it
using our art supplies so for contouring
I think I'm gonna go into this 48 colors
soft chalk pastels kit and hopefully
find a warm tone a contour shade in here
if I can get this open okay so we have
our two sets of pastels right here the
way it was packaged but it looks like
there were more inside and they're not
so our contour options here are very
very limited as you can tell the only
two shades that may help us out are this
a very very bright burnt orange and this
very very dark brown this could be where
it goes back to cause my face today I'm
going to use this masters touch oil and
acrylic
number four thirty round mop brush once
again morphe is there something you're
not telling us okay maybe if I like
scrape off oh my god some of the pigment
oh there we go okay there's my word
bingo we've cracked the code ladies I'm
just gonna scrape off a little bit of
the
burnt orange shade as wells we have like
a blush situation gonna grab my around
mop brush and dip into those two
pigments tap off the excess and
hopefully wow a benefit hoola bronzer
whoo Kat Von D shade and light palette
whoo Anasazi Beverly Hills contour kit
never heard of her
okay clearly we're going for a beachy
sunkissed look today that's what we're
going for yes correct
I obviously love that I'm complaining
about my face being orange when I just
used this to contour oh god I'm gonna
attempt to contour and snatch my nose
instead of using me once again oil
acrylic 425 Obul mop brush once again
this is literally a fluffy crease brush
what is going on say a silent prayer for
me on this one
oh okay not the worst but definitely not
the best I'm gonna grab some more chose
as a setting powder and another natural
sponge and just use this to bake my face
to not only lock everything in place but
also hopefully bring back a little bit
of my natural skin tone because this is
a little spooky mokuba all right so
while we're baking in the oven we're
gonna move on to the next step which of
course is going to be my eyebrows and
you guys know I usually live for a good
eyebrow pencil but what I don't like
using is brow powder so I'm gonna take a
break from the acrylics for a short
circuit and today I think I'm gonna use
these watercolors just gonna grab the
little paintbrush that came in the set
and dip into my little cup of water dip
into the brown shade which is very very
warm
oh god this could be bad I'm also gonna
grab some block two because that sounds
scary okay here we go
this could be good then I'm just gonna
apply it using an angled brush that I
found once again at the earth store oh
oh oh my god I love that I am literally
sliding this challenge what is going on
[Music]
yo why is that brow low key fire oh I
love this so much
oh my god you're literally kidding me
wow I am looking to makeup invented glam
the other gurus could never the other
guy Wow
once again Anasazi Beverly Hills whoo
this challenge surprisingly is going
very very well so far all right so now
that the brows are all done it's time to
move on to the eyeshadow and I'm really
really excited for this obviously this
is the part that I can shine in you guys
know I love a colorful eye shadow looks
and I feel like I literally have the
morphe a35 be here or sitting in front
of me actually you know what more p35
you sweetie I am so sorry
use KO james her tempers up but you know
what this could be a really really great
second alternative so I'm just gonna go
in and so I was like am and see what we
can come up with I guess I'm gonna go
ahead and scrape all my colors in the
beginning to get the pigments ready for
you so I'm first gonna show off with
this yellow shade that I'm gonna use
I think decrease I'm gonna grab this
hole and shade then this red shade then
this cranberry shade that is purple
shade and then finally just a little bit
of the black all right this is what we
got going on let's see what we can come
up with oh there it is despite the fact
that these are literally raw segments
going onto my eyeball I'm actually
surprised at how not pigmented they are
and how much I actually have to layer
them up but I feel like we can
definitely make a some form of really
cute I look work with this I'm just
gonna layer in some red into the crease
oh that's penguin Ted okay we're getting
somewhere we're getting somewhere
I really want to do a sunset halo eye
with these colors it's literally one of
the hardest color combinations to do and
it also uses a lot of different colors
so it's a challenge next I'm gonna grab
this number six round blender watercolor
brush literally pencil brush use Coe
James 10% off morphe something you want
to tell us here I've definitely noticed
that the best way to get color payoff is
to definitely pack the color in first
and then kind of blend it out later if
you go in and try to like layer up like
I would normally do eyeshadow it doesn't
really show up that much and obviously
when it comes to a sunset halo eye we
kind of need that pigmentation there so
definitely pack and then blend if you'd
ever be doing this I don't know why
you'd ever need this technique ever in
your entire life unless you're gonna get
ready using our supplies but I'm just
being the gurus that I am I want to go
ahead and cut out the center of this
crease and plop summit glitter and more
shadows on there so I'm just gonna grab
that rounded concealer brush once again
oh my god I literally love this brush
this is a hundred percent getting added
to my regular collection
[Music]
you
okay the one major downside to using
chalk pastels for your eyeshadow the
fall out who for the lid I picked up
these ultrafine glitters from the cross
short now of course you guys know
glitter unless it is cosmetic grade it
should not be used on the eyes but you
know what most of these products
probably should not be use of on the eye
so don't call this advice but I'm gonna
pop this gold one right on there I'm
literally in love with how this is
looking so far like hello this is
definitely a good sister i luck so I
think I want to add a winged liner I'm
getting a real confident clearly but you
know what this looks good so I'm gonna
grab this ace paint that I got and this
is body safe
thank God so I'm gonna grab the black
shade and do my best to put on a good
and fresh sister wing liner the sirens
my eyeball may or may not be burning a
little bit right now but you know what
that's a wing and it's ready to cut
somebody
I am literally honestly impressing
myself right now I literally feel like
the Christian army I'm gonna try to
adjust away some of this fallout oh
thank god okay wig for the lower lash
line why not let's do a pop of color I'm
gonna describe this a blue talk right
here scrape a little bit of it all and
plop it on there all right sisters that
is one eye all complete I do not plan on
going this intense but I'm literally
loving this so far I'm gonna go to do
the other one off camera quickly and
just really really get in the zone just
be a true artiste and help you right
back to finish off the rest of the LOC
all racism I am back those are both legs
all complete I just wanted to throw it I
really lost with Miami by Allison baver
and then also my Mac extended play on
mascara sorry
love you guys the most and love this
challenge knows that I was not taking a
chance getting a style by using some
wonky products on my eyelashes my de
Grasse
the next step they were set up all on
the routine is going to be the glow and
before we get into this I'm gonna give
these a quick spritz
I'm not fix+ I am NOT gonna chance to
kind
since we're feeling a little bit cakey
right now get it but um baking Joe's
crafts or anyway that was the worst now
if you're not familiar with baking this
is called las Arras and it is basically
a edible shimmery powder that goes on
top of cupcakes to give them a nice
shimmery Sparkle something God just
edible that's gonna be safe with the
skin and I'm going to use this for my
eyelid in our today it's literally the
only shimmery product I can find I hope
that color works for me and I'm just
going to put this on and live my fantasy
just in every other young thirteen year
old gay boy maybe he was gonna be the
next star Oh cake maker oh you have got
to be kidding me oh my god you're
kidding me oh my god honestly Beverly
Hills so Hollywood who I don't only know
sunny side-up bakery lost your toss oh
I'm speechless
Oh God does not
you know what we're going to make it
work okay well I'm not going to why I'm
a little bit disappointed by the
highlighter of course it looks really
really pretty literally is hitting it
like Hello love that but when the light
isn't hitting it it's definitely a way
to tart
this is the only shape they had
available act like you guys were all
sitting at home be like wow how is she
gonna make themself glow from within and
have a blinding highly using our
supplies when I'm sitting here like wow
I have luster dust and was ready to have
you all shaking but slowly with this
fellow especially this nose contour
situation oh you're all doing just fine
Laos is certainly not least the one
thing we're missing as the Liberty Doo
Dah so for this look I feel like I would
do a red lip
I think it's so much very very lazy to
all the clothes we helped coming on so
I'm just going to use the red base paint
from they can't before
all right are you guys I think this is
today's look and the whole face eating
only mark supplies challenge all
complete oh my god I am literally
obsessed with how this turned out holy
crap I'm sure you guys let me know in
the comments but for me personally I
think I absolutely killed this and never
again do I ever want to hear anybody say
make up as an anon if somebody says that
some in this video
perfect went to any of you right if you
guys enjoyed this video today please
don't forget to give a big thumbs up
down below and let me know so much fun
doing this and independence challenge at
home please tweet me a picture also
please be very very very careful most of
our supplies are obviously not for
consumption I'm definitely not
recommending anything please check the
warning labels before you put anything
on your face or your eyes but this is so
much fun to do today and I'd love to see
what you guys can come up with if you're
saying if you've not ready don't forget
to click that big red subscribe button
down below
come to this sisterhood it's a pretty
lit time and also put that Bell icon
sepia but every time I close a brand new
video
if you like to follow me and I make up
32 other crazy own pieces I can produce
don't forget to check me out on Twitter
they're both so st. Charles and my
snapchat war I haven't seen things that
this day of shows the night after
Charles this video sisters narcosis
sister Elora thank you so much pain
points all in its brief here in love you
so so so much and if you at home like we
do next videos sister shut up don't
forget some ways we treat you didn't
listening online on Twitter all right
sisters thank you so much for watching
don't forget to always release your
inner artist and Harper you can I love
you guys I will see you in the next one
bye
[Music]