hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel Happy
New Year everybody I am so glad the 2017
is over thank God it was a roller
coaster every year with a lot of highs
and lows if you'd like to check out my
Year in Review video that I put up last
week I am so proud of it make sure to
click right up here but I am so excited
to move on to bigger and better things
this 2018 although nothing really
happens when it becomes a new year it is
a major opportunity for everybody to
kind of start fresh and just stay
motivated and inspired and of course we
see everybody posting their New Year's
resolutions and goals across all social
media and one thing we see all the time
is new year new me first today's video
we're going to be doing exactly that
becoming a new me when it comes to your
favorite internet personalities there's
usually a really really big fandom
behind that one person which we like to
call stands and stands like to do edits
we get all sorts of amazing fan our
drawings paintings makeup recreations
and one tip at a weekend all the time is
pumpkin I've seen a lot of people on
YouTube but recreate their Punk edits in
real life by like dyeing their hair
getting fake piercings and of course
press on like water tattoos but for
today's video
my job is obviously a makeup artist so
I'm gonna be recreating my punk edits
with makeup one feature I see all the
time in Punk edits is the cat scratch
eyebrow I've worked way too hard on
these have tweeze them to death to get
the perfect shape so I'm definitely not
shaving to scratches in my eyebrows
today so I'm gonna start off with my
Elmer's washable glue stick and glue
down just the second half of my brow you
guys see me do this a million times now
in different drag video so if you really
want to know how to glue down your
eyebrows definitely check one of those
videos I'll link them somewhere up here
on the screen so you can get a more
in-depth tutorial once that brow is all
glued down and dried I'm just gonna take
a powder puff and some translucent
powder and pack it there to really lock
those hairs in place so we can cover
over them
I'm gonna use my Kryolan TV paint stick
in the shade and be to cover over those
hairs oh my
no house a good route cover whoa and
then just applying a really light layer
of the Too Faced Born This Way
Foundation all over the rest of my face
not really for like a glam look just for
like kind of more even a skin tone all
throughout when it comes to the neck I
am actually gonna grab a lot more
foundation than the face and really make
sure to blend that in and pocket kind of
all over because we're gonna be putting
a lot of tattoos here and this we do
really want a full covered even skin
tone so we have a good base for all the
drawings I'm gonna go ahead and do the
rest my base off camera today just to
save some time like I said we are not
going full glam just adding a little bit
of dimension back to my face just make
everything kind of more even edit ready
for a tattoo for my eyebrows today we're
gonna start off by filling in the base
and mica brow gel from Benefit and
number four so how basically my brow
shape all sketched out and like I said I
was gonna make them really really close
to my normal brows I just didn't want to
obviously shape a scratch in them so I'm
gonna take my shape tape concealer on
just the back of my hand and a tiny
liner brush and I'm gonna sketch out my
cats Raj this is definitely like an
interesting look not really sure how I
feel about it so far Wow
Grayson Dolan is shaking so one thing I
see all the time in Punk edits and like
face tattoos is a lot of people get
tears right here and I think that means
the amount of people that you've killed
I mean for me personally I don't know
about any of you guys but killing people
is exactly on my 2018 agenda so instead
of putting a tear right here I'm gonna
put the adidas logo please sponsor me
[Music]
this is already turning out to be so
much harder than I expected oh my god
okay so another trend I see all the time
in face tattoos is a big word and
cursive right above this eyebrow
obviously reading from left to right so
this might be like mirrored on the
camera you're just had to trust me here
I don't really know how this is gonna
work or turn out we're just going with
the flow but since this is like right
near my brain I'm gonna put the word
sisters because you guys are always on
my mind that was so cheesy oh it is
gonna be backwards you're kidding
I can always flip the footage I don't
know why so myself up to do this
so obviously this side of my face is a
little bit intense right now we
definitely need to balance that out on
this side so since we've been using my
Kat Von D tattoo liner I figured I would
add some stars to this sided honor of
Kat Von D but using an X liquid liner I
[Music]
know that milk makeup literally makes a
like star eyeliner stamp that I could
just be putting right all over my face
right now but of course I did not have
that or do i nope I don't one person
that was iconic for their face tattoos
is lil peep rest in peace he's gone away
too soon not only was he an amazing
musician but he was also an openly LGBTQ
person in the rock community which was
so amazing so in honor of him I'm gonna
recreate some of his face tattoos he had
a horseshoe right in between his
eyebrows for a good luck and since his
new year is starting and we had quite a
rough last one we're gonna need it he
also had a broken heart tattoo right
here on his cheek and I'm gonna recreate
that today because lord knows I'd had my
heart broken by a far too many stray
bullets and a lot of punk edits people
usually edit their ears to be Pierce or
like a gauge in their ear with a really
really big earring obviously my ears are
not even pierced so I'm gonna draw one
huntin eye using some more eyeliner oh I
feel like at this point my face is that
pretty much done and honestly I'm not
even gonna lie I kind of like how this
looks I really thought I was gonna be so
spooked by myself but I really don't
even mind this like a punk
sister and chains inversion anyway I'm
gonna go to move on to my neck one
tattoo that I see all the time on bill
people that are covered in tattoos or
they may even just have one or two are
Roman and numerals most people tend to
get a really significant date tattooed
on them such as like the death of a
really close relative or the birth of a
child or an anniversary date but for me
I have none of those things so I'm gonna
do my birthday I love myself
you
[Music]
there we go May 23rd don't forget to
wish me a happy birthday
another tattoo that I see all the time
on different people is a rose this is
gonna be really really challenging and
I'm kind of already regretting this but
I'm gonna try to place a rose right up
in here wish me luck
[Music]
this was literally the one of the worst
cities I think I've ever had once I have
the rough and I do mean very very rough
outline of the roads I'm gonna grab my
morphe e39 brushes just this very very
very tiny little brush and dip it to
some black eyeshadow and try to shade
the Rose a little bit honestly not bad
another thing that I saw a lot of these
edits were a butterflies butterflies are
super intricate and usually their
patterns are very very symmetrical and
beautiful so I'm gonna put this one a
smack dab right in the middle of my
throat so I can actually see it in the
freaking mirror and we can hope they
make it really really good okay honestly
not even gonna lie that butterfly turned
out a lot better than I was expecting
kind of living for this I think the last
like big major tattoo I'm gonna do is
gonna be right over here I'm gonna put a
crown there because I'm the queen of
[Music]
drawing on besides my neck is literally
so hard I can't even begin to explain to
you guys how much pain my eyes are in
right now I feel like they're about to
pop out of their freaking sockets they
should not be looking all the way over
here but we're gonna make this work
[Music]
alright guys those are all the big
tattoos finished my eyes currently feel
like they're going to burst out of my
head so I'm gonna take a quick little
break then I'm gonna come back and do
some tinier ones just in between to kind
of fill the space off-camera and I'll be
right back with the finished Punk at it
in real life with makeup look all right
sisters I am back it has been about two
hours now meeting I've been working on
this for literally four hours but I
think we are finally done with the
finish line before we actually did
makeup I used to draw all the time when
I was honestly really really good at it
I used to practice every single day and
I would draw portraits and all sorts of
intricate really beautifully shaded
drawings so going into this I really
didn't think this is gonna be that much
of a challenge for me in particular
point was I wrong though hence now this
is probably the hardest makeup challenge
I have done today I've talked about this
in a few videos before but I don't
exactly have the most steady hands I
usually will start shaking if I get
really really nervous or if I'm trying
to work on something very very detailed
and intricate so this was a major major
challenge for me I think by far the
hardest part of this entire challenge
was this rose tattoo even if I was
drawing a rose on normal paper I think I
would definitely have some trouble just
because the shape and overall form of
Rose is very very hard to capture on a
2d flat surface but it was even more
difficult because it's on the side of my
neck where I have to literally like turn
my eye all the way over here to even get
a decent glimpse at this area and I
still can barely even see what I'm doing
my eyes literally were in so much pain
by the end of it but I think it turned
out descent I already loved and
respected tattoo artists before I used
to watch tattoo videos all the time on
YouTube and would always want to go with
my friends when they got them done just
to see the artist in progress but I
respect them even more now after trying
it myself because this is so hard
alright sisters and that is all I have
for this video today I really really
hope you guys enjoyed it if you did
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and subscribe if
you have not already join the sisterhood
and click the little bell icon so you
can be notified every time I upload a
brand new video leave me a comment down
below and tell me what you would get if
you were going to get a tattoo I really
really love them and would definitely be
down to get one one day I just have
later
no idea what I would get if you like to
follow me on my makeup journey you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both the same Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes
lights up is James Charles that extra
ass after Charles this week's shout-out
goes to sister yay oh thank you so much
me for always falling in supporting you
know I love you is so so so much and if
you would like to be the next video
sister Charlotte makes it always a
retweet video link so they go live on it
Twitter all right sisters thank you so
much for watching I love you pretend
this is a full heart so much that I will
see you in the next one bye
[Music]