hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I
just want to go ahead and jump right
into the intro for today's video because
I've been wanting to do this for
literally so long now I am so excited
and I do think that this is probably
gonna be one of the longest videos that
I ever upload to this channel so saddle
up get ready because for today's video
we're doing my first ever full on Drive
transformation now you're probably
thinking sister James what are you
talking about we've seen you do Drive so
many times on Instagram and here in
YouTube and yes you're definitely not
wrong what I actually think is really
really cool and almost like a
sentimental part of this video is that I
started to make up three years ago now
and because of the fact that I started
on Instagram all of my looks are
actually documented in photo for you
guys to see including my chart makeup
the first ever time that I did jog was
probably about two years ago now and it
was this photo inspired by Raven a
legendary Queen from season two and
honestly should have been winner of
RuPaul's Drag Race as well as every
other time that I've done drawing after
that I will confidently say that through
a lot of mistakes a lot of misplaced
eyebrows and a lot of practice by drag
makeup abilities have definitely gotten
a whole lot better and of course they've
gotten some pretty nice wigs as well but
that's kind of about it I've been a
major fan of RuPaul's Drag Race and a
supporter of someone including that have
both been on the show and all for a very
very long time now the drag community
has influenced my personality sense of
humor and also makeup skills with
different tips and techniques so so so
much throughout the past three years and
I'm generally so honored to be in the
LGBTQ community with amazing drag queens
that being said though even though
drying and dry Queens have been such a
major source of inspiration to me at a
huge part of my life it is an artform
that I don't really know that much about
as an outsider and as a fan I have even
made the mistake and looking at drag
queens on stage looking beautiful and
fierce as just a man and a wig and a
dress absolutely killing it when in
reality there is so much more that goes
into actually being performance ready
with both the skills and putting the
look together so for today's video I
thought I'd be really really cool to
take a topic that I love and abso
but can be educated on because I'm
ignorant towards and really just take a
full-on deep dive into the world to jog
and see what it actually takes to put
together a go luck in time for a major
special event or performance I thought
it'd be the perfect time to take on this
challenge because I'm actually flying to
New York very very soon to work on some
super-secret sister projects and while
I'm gonna be there coincidentally Drakon
New York City is going to be happening
and what better place to try out being a
dropping for the first time ever then at
Drakon a little convention filled the
dry Queens that I have loved and looked
up to for so long the only issues are
that I'm currently in the process of
moving and then I leave for New York in
less than two weeks so this is gonna be
quite the time crunch we have two weeks
to pull off this full-on Drive
transformation can we do it let's get
started
[Music]
all right so we have two weeks until it
dry condi are actually happens I think
in order to have success in this I need
to split up my focus into four different
categories which I figured out are the
body the outfit the hair and the makeup
and I think I actually need to hit them
in that order as well starting on for
the body because of course like the body
is gonna affect the fitting which look
back to the gown and then I just pick
the hair or based on the gown and then I
need to pick the makeup based on
everything altogether I think I
definitely need to pour most of my
attention into the body first because
that's gonna be by far probably the
hardest part of this entire
transformation I don't exactly have much
to work with you guys know from my
several accidental but picks that I post
it on snapchat there isn't a whole lot
there in order to give myself a little
bit more sister shape I'm really going
for that hourglass figure I need to get
two different things being padding and a
corset I'm not exactly sure how I'm
gonna do my padding yet which has me
very very stressed out but we're gonna
figure it out we always do but I do know
how I'm gonna do it my corset I reached
out to a ton of my drive friends and
conveniently as well the try guys which
are a huge channel here on YouTube just
did a video last week where they got
corset fitted so I reached out to the
same shop they're called what katydid
located in Burbank California and I have
an appointment in about 30 minutes from
now for a corset fitting I'm gonna go in
and get sister snatched so I'm gonna
call it
and let's head over and see how much of
a skinny legend I could be today
[Music]
she's been waist training for about 30
years
whoa hundreds of styles of custom
courses and everything and we've kind of
a drive back to these several different
styles now the extremely high quality
through an everyday few years if you
want to yeah oh yeah we have a lot of
really famous drag performers that use
these as their base for their costumes
as soon as I talk to my designer about
mean of course I he's like um yeah it's
a wonderful place to start out find a
corset that works for you and there are
what really wonderful price okay so the
fitting is like this we take your
natural waist measurement no then we go
four to six inches down and that wall
your versat size of your arm let's do it
we're gonna go through the mortician
we're dog look yeah oh yeah great great
to pad out I would I would try it on an
extreme
this one will work for your your padding
okay I like this one for me because the
regular my tisha pushes on my ribs a lot
and a young breathe as much young I get
anxiety when I can't breathe
but this one it puts all the pressure on
my waist which I like oh yeah so you
have tons of padding room you can pop
them in the butt you compat your hips
out and you have tons of room for that
then you have a teeny little waist yeah
and then once you pad it out it'll look
even teeny
oh my lord this is crazy and so cool
250 186 perfect it was matched alright
so we just turned out of what Katie Did
literally everybody there was so beyond
eyes and so sweet I am ready to be
sisters snatched a little bit of the
flops were sticking out of the science
because they're normally meant for more
curvy people but that is what we have it
padding forward I don't know how we're
gonna do this yet but we're gonna figure
it out alright so now that our body is
off knot and ready to go now we're able
to move on to the way I reach out to
wake the great who is a huge insanely
talented wig stylist she does wig for so
many Queensland drivers including kimchi
and I asked her if she'd be willing to
fit in the end for a last-minute wig for
a jog on she actually did say gasps that
she was going to try to fit in a custom
wig for a jog on which I am so excited
for but we only have the one week of
time to do this which is cutting it very
very close so we just go to the FaceTime
call so you can plan out the style and
figure out what we're going to do so
without further ado let's go meet sister
Gloria how are you are you all so
amazing thank you so much for calling
you today it's so nice to meet you by
the way hello James thank you for taking
on my wigs today for Drakon New York
City I know it's literally in a week but
I feel like if anybody's gonna be able
to I don't like think about things if
anybody's gonna be able to do this it's
definitely you okay I have true true
true faith in you but we get sort of
those little consultation and why do you
tell the sisters a little bit about you
your business and what we're gonna be
doing today
my name is Gloria I'm the Jacob Hall
trains a Twix and grace
yeah weeks ingress is been around for
about five years people knew about us of
kimchi and we've been involved basically
I've seen your weight on so many iconic
Queens are styling it's like insane and
I'm so excited to be working together
for this love obviously this is a very
very quick turnaround so I feel like we
should figure out what type of look we
want to do like now yes my final
planning session with my designer
earlier today it's going to be an old
Hollywood be like super super it's like
a little yellow where we have platinum
which is a cooler tumbler that it's
almost why - I feel like the platinum is
gonna wash me out for Shore because it's
a white gown and I'm already pale and I
think they're great would be better for
a Down moment so I feel like the warm
tone original is definitely the way to
go
perfect I feel like I'm definitely in
such good hands for this look today I am
trusting you definitely looking forward
to seeing the finish was the like thing
I'm gonna look so stunning in an updo
thank you so much for your time and
do this alright alright thank you sister
so much keep me posted
I'm gonna be a curvy sister thank God
for Planet pepper
I call them there Louise and absolutely
need Harold they overnighted me the
potting so now I get to be Sun tea and
really bet
I think sister oh hi mom hi sister I
included it ashore brief as well try
this on over top of your pods and tights
just with everything out how's that I've
got hope to see somebody
[Music]
oh I'm sweating 42 is it good the
difference between here and here it
hurts so bad
three days I was here with the person
you have all these pins this is how to
do it all by hand inside
oh wow so you don't have any any
Christmas maybe LC right okay I just got
a notification from the UPS saying my
weight is here it's arrived oh my god
okay you guys literally it's here okay
okay so I put her on Oh probably yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
okay you guys literally we leave for
dark on in 12 hours tonight and there's
a lot to be done still so now we
officially have to finish wave thank god
alex is coming over for one last final
fitting today he texts me this morning
that the gallery is done of course he's
going to kill it and I'm so committed to
sealing all pulled up together
honestly it was going to be at the last
step the one thing that we're missing
now is the shoes which is not good
I ordered shoes from a really huge
online website and paid for express
overnight shipping that were supposed to
get here approximately at five days ago
now so as soon as we land in New York or
morning we have to go assister shopping
and find me a pair of men's high heels
that's gonna be really great and fun and
probably not easy obviously we're gonna
handle the shoes tomorrow before I
hardly I can actually finally take a
little bit of a breath we did it we are
ready kind of for joke on end I will see
you guys in New York all right we're
officially on at the plane we're ready
to go and sister company we have our
Shake Shack for
we have a six-hour play ahead of us if I
had not been to New York in sick
quite the adventure let's do that we
define here to New York the thorny and
rock on earth now tomorrow and the one
less thing we have not gone yeah our
shoes so I'm currently at Steve Madden
and I'm having it slow because I just
ride on a size 9 which is my normal shoe
size and I could not get my left foot in
and my right foot was slipping so I've
now gone conclusion that if I want to be
a woman I have to wear to two sizes that
are literally a completely different so
I am NOT trying an 8 and a half on my
right foot at a nine and a half on my
left foot
and I'm really gonna buy two different
pairs of shoes that no overwatch
hello it is currently 8:52 p.m. JA Ronn
is now in t-minus 14 hours I have
everything that I need but I am still
really really nervous for tomorrow and
I'm not exactly sure why I think that I
have my look altogether but the one
thing that I'm really missing before
this whole video is like a lesson on how
to like actually be a drag queen and I
think that because I've been planning
all this so quickly and because I just
moved and because now I'm traveling that
it kind of slipped my mind but that was
a really important thing that I should
not have skipped over so I do have a few
friends that I know are in Thai way now
for the actual convention tomorrow so I
think I'm going to do cross my fingers
and send out a few texts and pray that I
can get somebody over here tonight to
talk to me and hope we hope they call me
nerves also talk to you guys it's all
because I think obviously I'm trying
this out for the first time but it'd be
really cool to actually hear the
perspective of somebody that does it for
a living but doesn't every single day
that it's great at this and to maybe
speak on what it's like to be a what
these are grateful to me and to anybody
else out there who is of trying it out
so I'm going to send out a few times and
I'm going to become some makeup
inspiration for tomorrow and I'm going
to walk in the hills a little bit and
I'm going to try to calm myself down
I'll see you guys in a little bit break
you guys it is currently 10 o'clock p.m.
Oh literally on the dock mom Tina
punctuality and I have joined today with
Asha a legendary New York city-based
Charlie from Brooklyn she is so talented
and a good friend might as well so sir
hi I thought it'd be so much fun for us
to kind of like sit down and talk
together about tomorrow because tomorrow
is New York City yeah I am so nervous
and you've always been a really really
great friend and mentor implyin even
I've only done driving a few times I
thought I'd be really great for us to
like sit down together
to talk about like the whole job process
because as I told you I'm doing a penny
where I do like my first name ever in
fall on track and I thought like doing
John Deere extending as I first like
public appearance could have a really
fun and fresh but now I'm like really
nervous about it too like a lot of
different reasons I thought like it'd be
best to get it by someone who's like
working in the fields I'm like doing it
really well too okay see we're gonna
have to like Dean nervousness eyes you
because I ever know if it's a word but
the thing about it is that I think drag
is all about confidence yeah
when you're in that Juche yes you have
to just feel it like you don't know what
insecure dragons
you're gonna shine no matter what right
and you're really good at makeup I saw
you did this one transformation it was
the first transformation you did where
you said that you were going for a very
natural look
yes it was really good and it was it was
just the perfect blend of natural and
like the stereotypical like drag makeup
if it's anything like that that you're
doing I can imagine that everything else
is gonna be just like in order to like
pull this actually off I've been working
with a lot of like the industry
professionals and like the top of the
top to hope I look together
um Casius adventure asks and it wakes
and grace in my hair and then wrinkle
into my jewelry and then I do my makeup
I'm not the best of the best but I have
pretty zit with a blending brush I will
say so it's not really the look that I
am worried about because I know that I'm
actually in good hands I'm more worried
about like the drag community because I
felt like not the best relationship with
the drag community in the past and I'm
really scared because the dry community
people that I look up to a lot like I've
been watching drag race that balding
dark beans on social media literally
like extend season and from way
beforehand
I've got so many that my voice looked up
to so many of them including you out
there Santos that's before and it's kind
of scary because although I love a lot
of people I know for a lot of them the
feeling isn't mutual
which is fun but it's a little bit of a
scary thought because it's a community
that I respect and by doing driving for
the first time I don't want to walk in
there and disrespect anybody we'll be
fine because honestly drag is very
inclusive especially in a safe space
like Drakon you will be respected and
it's just like I think about everybody
does drag technically you've been doing
drag right celebrities you drag all the
time nicki minaj lady gaga like i
there's so many different ways to look
at drag it's not just like assist mail
and address sometimes it's just like
James Charles doing makeup
that's your drag that's your drive
nobody can tell you different but if
people don't support you from the drag
community those are just little pieces
they can really like get over themselves
because you are a person and we're all
people in the community I support you
and I know a lot of other people do
support you there as well so you will be
welcome and you know you're gonna have
fans there as well people who are going
to be like going but nanos when they see
you I hope there will be some sister
service where I haven't actually
announced that I'm coming yet so sister
surprise I don't know who's gonna be
there what is going to be like the
hardest part about being a job tomorrow
the worst three things about being a
drag in my opinion to me are one
blotting you have to touch up your
makeup very frequently especially when
people want to take pictures like it's
very handy to have someone who has a
touch-up near you or even just like for
the girls on the go have a little powder
puff in your paranoids do so that one's
taken care of already girl you don't
want to look like a oil pit in the pigs
and then also the feet walking in heels
all day when you're not used to wearing
heels by this point I have hoes I am
basically a horse
I'm used to it that's what I'm most
scared about I will say number three
would have to be the end of the day
being in drag all day is so different
from being in drag
all night when you're in driving all day
the lighting especially if you're
wearing contacts and lashes it just like
makes your eyes tired and heavy
and then when it's time to get out of
drag it's like you slowly start peeling
at all like a second and third skin and
then you kind of just look at it and
you're just like how am i alive you're
gonna be so tired your feet or the VM
pain and you're gonna be like how am i
alive but while you're doing it the
fantasy is still turned on yeah that it
just doesn't matter like except the
shoes remember
break some flats oh that's gonna be hard
so speaking of getting like your
signature look all together the one
thing that I've noticed throughout doing
this transformation today and obviously
of course I am working with on the top
of the top this is very expensive it
does cost money usually to be beautiful
but drawing on a budget is something as
well I guess my question for you is like
obviously I guess that gets blurred you
onto a bigger platform where anyone to
get tons of pigs but your boys book
dialog like watching before put some on
your stories seems it was so amazing but
beforehand everybody's kind of like a
queen on a budget just like any others
you have to buy materials store on your
mark warm what advice would you give to
smaller creeks that want to start out
doing drugs and how does drive on a
budget really work for me before I was
given the platform of drag race I had to
learn to make everything myself that was
the real way to stay on the budget is
you want to look nice but as nice as you
want to look the also have to like save
the money right you're not getting paid
enough to look the way you look you can
go to the club and even if I did my own
wig I had to pay maybe fifty bucks for
the wig and then it's like the ten
dollars for the hairspray and then the
brush and the column the dress was maybe
a forty dollar dress I got off the block
but I still bought a $20 pack Oh mr.
Oscar Ryan shows 2-digit up yeah you
know the makeup the shoes I'm a size 14
my feet can fit into canoes like little
boat find the way to learn to do
everything yourself yeah that's the hard
thing because showing is not easy doing
hair is annoying unless you really have
the patience and the time girl now when
I get my wig made by Gloria from wigs
and grace like I'm just like thank you
for saving my life and making me look
like a trout like
catfish more like angelfish Oh majestic
I guess my last question for you is if
you kind of already it slightly touched
on this but just to give like an overall
answer for myself and for any other
young kids out there who want to try out
dry what did the best he said overall I
think the best advice for anybody is
really just know the reason you're doing
drag or find the reason through drag
itself because for some people drag is
their art form for some people who are
fond of dragons their medium to show
their talents and for some people it's
to help them find themselves some people
discover their trends to drag some
people discover who they are for me drag
is very therapeutical so I think the
biggest advice is to use drag however
you can to help yourself and help yeah
but like also if you can't help yourself
first you'll never be able to help other
people so I used to be like super insane
with it like I had so much anxiety and
so much depression and you know teenage
angst idea and I started doing drag and
I did slowly like kind of picked myself
up and I didn't have anybody around me
and I just kind of found a person in me
and I learned to love myself and I took
that message and I started to teach it
to other people so when I see like
Queens who you know may not look the
best or like look like they don't have
the funds I never sit there make fun of
them or be like oh wow because you don't
know where people come from right even
if like they don't look their best
instead of saying something like oh look
at her like she looks busted going up to
them and just saying hi introducing
and you know saying like I'm happy
you're doing this because anybody who's
trying to drag deserve some type of
recognition and everyone has to start
somewhere as oh yes like people think
that you wake up overnight and you're
just like the glam squad and you're
decide oh yeah it's like girl that's why
I was like nervous for this video too
because I'm obviously very blessed and
privileged to be able to work with the
team so I really appreciate getting your
acceptance weren't an issue for a very
very long time and it's my problem like
trying out driving a little baby driving
for the first time to like being the
superstar Queen I think people will see
what you're doing and will see that
you're using your platform to also like
further what you learned and they will
learn from that as well so I think that
what you're doing is cool it is risky
because like I know why you're nervous
right but I guarantee people are gonna
look at this and they're gonna think
that you're brave and they're gonna
think that it's cool and they're gonna
want to try it too
well thank you so much to super joining
me today this really has actually helped
me a lot like all my nerves I'm a really
good about this I'm sure by the time I
wake up tomorrow morning the feeling
that's may be bad but I'm gonna just go
into it my office'll all give it my best
and just one absolutely fierce than
fabulous and I'll see you there if you
don't come see me first I'm getting
assess your security to escort you
around I just happened to wake up this
morning and it's currently 10:30 I set
my alarm for 8 o'clock and I woke up and
my alarm is still on somehow but it's
10:30 here in New York my timezone
literally to not stress on my phone and
now I'm 2 hours late good morning
it's 11:00 a.m. this is not good I'm so
mad like I cannot believe I'm gonna
start off with looing dollar of my
eyebrows because I have man eyebrows and
I need to not have those today so flat
that's what we want
so once the glues like on there and
brushed up a little bit I'm actually
gonna take a wet washcloth and just go
over some of those edges really really
lightly just to kind of blend them in it
to my nostrils again so now we need the
glue to dry before we move on to the
next layer what do we do to make them
dry you ass
let me tell you damn coming soon just a
source ass apparel hog so now that my
brows are both glued down and basically
almost I am is gonna take my favorite
loose powder and grab quite a lot of it
and just a powder puff and I'm going to
press that right over top of the brow to
lock them in place and also to put any
remaining powder inside of any little
gaps just make sure they're super super
smooth
approximately three videos ago now you
guys all heard me say color corrector
usually stupid I have never color
corrected in a million years guess that
I'm about to do call it cracked because
I am a man my beard is showing a lot for
some reason today in the last several
weeks I need to get laser hair removal
right now so we're getting starting off
the foundations hey I'm gonna grab my
kryla TV paint stick so this one is in
the shade NB which is not my shade I'm
gonna go over top of this with
Foundation and they're very short a
second but this is the a super intense
full coverage foundation like literally
it's like cement so what I'm gonna do is
go like this
now this looks disgusting so I'm gonna
take my to pay for this a foundation
which you guys know is my all-time
favorite and go over time for that so it
looks less crazy so now I need to
highlight my face and when it comes to
drag makeup obviously drives all of a
high-contrast so instead of grabbing a
concealer what I'm going to do is grab a
white foundation this is the Krell on TV
paint stick once again but this is in
the shade at 0-0 and the stuff is
actually really really bomb I love using
this and I'm just going to curl like
this okay so normally I'm without my
face in place right now but I think I'm
actually gonna do my eyebrows first so I
can powder over top of them to lock them
in I normally would never do this I
don't know why I would take a rest on a
day like this but we're gonna do it all
right
now as for the jawline I'm going to
contour up my jaw as usual just really
chelsa out there because we don't want a
double chin but when it comes to the
corners of my jaw line we're gonna do
something sad then I'm gonna take my big
round fluffy brush this is the m5 27 and
dip into that same middle tone shade a
little bit but mostly into the kind of
left or caramel shade and I'm gonna use
this as like a bronzer to marry together
my natural skin tone and the contour
shade just make everything blend really
seamlessly low-key happy with how I'm
looking so far so now we're gonna move
on to the eye makeup so I'm gonna do
first is grab one of these weird cards
at the hotel has in here and we're to
rip it in half and I'm gonna use these
to actually frame out my winged liner
today it makes this so much easier ten
out of ten would recommend let me tell
you how we're gonna do this I'm first
gonna have a big fluffy brush this is
the a before for one I'm just gonna dip
into a credit like neutral tone brownie
of warm 4G the lip and put that in my
crease as a transition
and I'm gonna use this I'm gonna blend
out right into the nose contour in this
inner corner and I'm gonna pull it up
into the white so I'm now gonna grab
this little business card and my fluffy
brush I'm gonna place this card right on
the corner of my eye just like this
being right below my lower lashline and
kind of right past the end of my eyebrow
I'm gonna press it in there and I'm
gonna go right in my crease and blend
I'm gonna pull all the way out to the
edge with that same color I'm going to
pull it down into that outer corner as
well and onto the lid and really deep
enough that outer crease well that brush
is still there I'm gonna grab the fluffy
one and there's gold where those I just
make sure they're nice and blended out
and then with the slightest bet just
gonna go right in that just to really
create a lot of dementia
I'm gonna grab my m4 33 once again going
over that edge just make sure it's
blended pulling it right off and now
we've right this worked oh yes
bingo so good and fresh now what I'm
gonna do once it is complete I'm gonna
grab a concealer brush this is the a
before 2-1 and more of the white and I'm
going to carve out my crease once again
using white eye shadow in this outer
corner I'm gonna grab my fluffy brush
with that cool toned Brown once again
I'm just gonna go over at this white
edge and just to start kind of blend
again that's okay I all together then in
that little outer corner and just gonna
go back in with my eyes are brown
I'm gonna grab a liquid liner this one
is the wet and wild one I'm going to
draw out my away nominee is that black
puppy brush once again once that way is
loosely drawn on there and I'm just
gonna set what were that with the block
because I'm not sure that this black
wing is blended into the rest of like
the eye look I really cannot stand when
like you can
see the way I think it looks really I'm
gonna grab the wife once again surprise
surprise I'm gonna put this in my lower
waterline this I shape is definitely
very inspired by a farrier she's
obviously on my ultimate favorite queen
but I really having white in this inner
corner right here because it just opens
up the eye and makes it look so much
bigger and very doll like what you guys
know are definitely my all-time favorite
techniques to do during it even like my
regular makeup style I just like make
myself look like a so just let the upper
lash line hits but whenever we go into
the white or just especially the lower
region as well you guys know I
definitely have very very sensitive eyes
and then like contacts and with all the
lashes and on top of being sick the last
thing that I want is my liner like
running around or jumping into this area
then without popping brushing that dark
front from before this question blend
out the lower lash so I end up below the
new lower lash and that we just created
and making sure to carry it right up
into the upper way so we pretty much
have the I started portion of one eye
all comb feeds here is what we have
going on so far
hello really loving this so far I
obviously have the other I have to do
and I'm running a very very late so what
I'm gonna do is go to the other one off
the camera quickly and I'll be right
back to finish off the lashes the lips
the highlight and then everything else
I'll see you guys in a few short minutes
I wasn't finished
Audrey and I also custom cut these
lashes together so pretty so nice so
spiky so now I'm going to try to glue
these on instead of wash glue today I'm
gonna be using we bonding glue to glue
this onto my eyeball okay so my eyes are
now all complete thank god this is
taking me so long I'm running so late
but at this very Lily do not even care
anymore now I have to and it's my look
I'm gonna do some highlighter of course
I'm just gonna start my stressing my
face using the morphe
besides just looks like nice to me
there's something to stick to
not spill I have a lot of powder on and
have not you setting its prey out folk
are scared gonna have an M 504 brush oh
yes I'm gonna lion up my lips using the
colour-pop I loves how to eat lip liner
in the shade of Kirby is my all-time
favorite all right you guys in three
hours later that is this makeup look all
complete I'm going to lock this in place
using some sister setting spray and I
have a lot more to do so first we have a
beautiful body padding currency of
Ostrow booty call it's a corset now
how's that oh yeah it's all the way like
uh-huh you're good you don't want any
tired
like holding this tighten up cuz that's
not the dress little not that I'm still
alive but I'm barely breathing oh my god
I could feel that looking it's so nasty
looking to go somewhere huh
I can't even bend over oh my god makes
you appreciate drag race' like getting a
20 minute quick drag driving like they
put a body on it so it's like how did
you get that body on that quickly I
can't imagine how it like you could make
this process any easier
let's see full service management or a
cure
every time you throw everything pull
these women talk and then I'll get this
looks like Legos my mom puts on my
panties polish into the hair now so now
we have to put on our I would like to go
around the edge of the lace and leave
about maybe like a quarter to a half of
an inch around all sides just so it
doesn't look really really weird on the
hairline obviously this is a way but I
wanted to look as real as possible so I
have to glue it onto my head so now we
have this which is spirit gum and this
stuff is a lot but it's what we have to
do so I'm gonna brush this on to my head
right here customer sideburn is gonna be
and I'm gonna put some right up here in
the center of my forehead I'm not gonna
be putting on too much as you guys I'm
obviously not gonna be like performing
or anything today but I definitely do
want it to still be a pop please such as
I love a good wig flew comment that is
not what I'm coming after today
now we just going to press the wig right
onto those areas
looking good a girl feeling gorgeous Oh
perfect
Thank You Cathy okay so the earrings I
got today are clip-on and once again I
have to use some Spiricom to stick them
on or else they won't fall because
they're super super super heavy it's
just time
Craig they were able to close this Oh
is it tight
we an she look will mana
really yeah we're are the shoes okay I
want to say I have literally just tried
to squeeze your foot into the heel and I
was like oh that's bone like there's no
way it just for the paper or tissue this
is not New York City we're just calm
down definitely a little bit now that I
feel super super confident beautiful I
just hope that I don't fall over at this
point but I've been texting a lot of my
favorite greens this morning I'm gonna
go to
and there should be a really incredible
experience so let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
just hurts too much
this day was insane oh my god okay that
is drunk on day one all complete I
probably look disgusting at this point
my hair is still on my dress is still on
my waist is still singed and still
working the shoes are gone long sleeves
pretty early on but today amazing I'm
gonna head back to the hotel and D Drive
and take all this off because I
literally feel like I'm about to die
today was so much work and I want to
tell you guys all about my experience
the good at the bad and the ugly so
let's call it over and I will see you
guys in a few shots oh my god I've never
been in more pain in my entire life
my okay I'm glad my skin is still alive
you're dying for that corset to come off
now I tied this really tight so just
give me a minute
cuz it's been on your 400 come on
I'm trying room turn around turn around
what does it look like you look like the
predator I don't know that's the only
way I can describe this back my toes
hurt so much
oh my god this has been the longest day
of my entire life I look disgusting like
I'm scared
hello my normal makeup I can keep on
filling a few hours during the day I
like get over that this no I can't today
was insane
like absolutely insane I was so nervous
you know there's like a lot of things
that I was worried about my outfit my
hair my makeup looking good because my
drag makeup has definitely been quite
the roller coaster for me my shoes which
obviously did not exactly end up working
out but you know what it's okay I took
them off there were a lot of other
creams that has their shoes off it's a
little walking around in slippers or
barefoot which I thought was so iconic
so I definitely was not the only one
that wanted to go for the talent but the
thing that I was most nervous about what
we're all was actually meeting so many
these things that have looked up to
forever because of the fact that I don't
exactly have the best reputation in the
chart world it's been a community that
I've loved forever but I've really tried
to stay away from in order to avoid
trauma just because it's something that
happened in our own two years ago with
and me cutting a line and a security
guard very very well that's right that I
don't really need to get into but it was
a complete misunderstanding and
now a lot of the drug fans don't like me
so that's great every single Queen that
I read today was literally you so beyond
nice I'm gonna answer some of the photos
here with the creeps that take photos
with and they were also incredibly
supportive and how does such nice things
that's they have it my first time in
Iraq so many the Queen's actually didn't
recognize me at first until I said my
sister and then they were like oh my god
what just watching that reaction was
actually so incredibly cool so many of
them said the way make up look beautiful
though they did not recognize me which
is definitely a good thing because it
means I did a good job of camouflaging
myself and becoming a sister superstar
at Rockwood I was also able to meet so
many of you sisters as well was just
always so crazy to me I did not notice
that I was going to draw a gun obviously
because they wanted this whole video to
be like a little bit of a sister
surprise so surprise but so many of you
guys have found me right away after I
posted a snapchat my hotel room this
morning and my finished look and we
liberation up the convention time which
is [ __ ] what I thought that I already
had like the absolute highest level of
respect for John Queens before even
going into this video but let me tell
you that bar has been raised
literally like through the roof although
I had so much fun today this is probably
one of the most physically challenging
experiences I have ever had in my entire
life wearing that corset all day long is
so incredibly painful my back literally
looked like it was about to turn purple
and like fall but literally like it was
so hard to breathe in the Walker on the
entire day working with sister Alex for
the gala wasn't so much fun because he's
moving so talented and I think for next
time I do drug I am probably am NOT
Quinn to get a gown as beautiful as I
looked walking around with a train all
day was so hard
spent so much money on that gown and
every penny and that was worth it but
the entire bottom of it is covered with
footprints from people stepping on all
day long so definitely need a body suit
for the next and the shoes let me tell
you about the shoes apparently I learned
through this lesson that my feet are two
very different sizes great did not know
that how I went 19 years without packing
in this now I don't know but apparently
it's not be looking for a pair of white
high heels
so and now we know aside from the
physical pain ups in a little bit this
experience has been so much fun and I am
so beyond glad that I did it it's truly
one my favorite experiences that I've
had to take to sink everybody walk
around and their wigs and makeup and
crazy hair and outfits expressing
themselves like what a beautiful and
amazing thing this has been such an
incredible and eye-opening experience
for me because obviously I've done drag
so many different times on Instagram but
I've never done my full try all right
you guys my skin is thought sooner well
now I'm going to lay down in bed and
probably face my big toes and also get a
huge sisters snack because I have not
need anything I am starving if you guys
enjoy this video today please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below so much work in love went into
this not only from me but so many
amazing people as well so go down and
show your sister support means so much
to us
also if you haven't already don't forget
to click that big red subscribe button
and come join in this sister Ida we're a
point five million sister strong oh my
God we're getting so close to the big
ten million and also click that belt
like on simplification every time I
upload a brand new video if you'd like
to follow me on my makeup journey and
see my drug transformations and also a
whole lot more normal a complex as well
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both does James Charles
and when it's nap time for more behind
the scenes and stuff is James Charles
and extra ass after Charles this video
is sister shadow goes to sister Mary
perfect name for this video today thank
you so much luck for my styling in
supporting Roy let me little yes so so
so much and if you at home willing to
the next videos that sister shout out
don't forget to always reach me quitting
something go live on Twitter alright
sisters thank you so much for watching
this videos today I really really hope
you enjoyed it so much fun I love you
then I was seeing
[Music]