hi sisters James Charles - and welcome
back 22 Channel oh my god you guys I am
so beyond excited for today's a
brand-new video I just want to jump
right into it today's video has been
literally the most highly requested
video probably ever from you guys and
something that I've wanted to do for a
very long time as well
ever since I announced the palette and
that is well it's gonna be the fastest
intro ever full face of makeup using
only my palette if you sisters know me
you would know that I love a good at
competition that I never ever backed
down from a challenge I always go above
and beyond sand I really really do not
like losing so not even gonna lie when I
first read this comment I was a little
bit nervous about doing this challenge
but after kind of looking at the full
palette and planning everything out in
my head I do think that I actually will
be able to slay this challenge of course
there will be a few complications along
the way when it comes like a foundation
and other things like that but we're
gonna get through them together all that
being said I am so excited to dive in
and so without further ado let's unleash
our inner artist and do a full face of
makeup using only my palette
[Music]
all right you guys so to make sure that
I sisters slay this challenge today I
think I'm gonna go in the same order
it's my normal makeup routine and just
replace each step along the way so I
don't miss any and of course you guys
know at first I always do my foundation
to lay down a light base now looking at
this palette we have already run into a
little bit of an issue now you and I are
sisters so must be honest with each
other we all know that I'm not exactly
the best when it comes to matching my
foundation there's no need to talk about
it thanks so if I was to use one of the
change in the palette my options are
either bright white bright yellow orange
which happens a lot regardless and super
super pale none of which really seemed
to be viable options so I posted a poll
on my Instagram story and I asked you
guys I said should I start off on my
base already on camera and just do every
other step after using only the pounds
or should I not cheat and literally just
scam foundation and I literally a two
percent vote don't she know Foundation
won with 51% so I guess we're doing a no
foundation makeup look today I'm not
exactly sure how that is gonna work out
I am having a pretty good skin day today
thank God but I am definitely very red
so hopefully this like it calms down
during the process of the video
regardless I guess we're gonna move on
to the next step already okay so after
foundation we have concealer which I
cannot do and then after a concealer we
have powder which I can do but there's
no point if I'm not actually setting
anything in please
so after powder I guess were already on
to contouring so we definitely have a
lot of options when it comes to a
bronzing but that is going to be at the
next step so to contour I'm gonna get
Miami 405 brush this is that my brush
set and dip into the shade I think hunch
me might be a pretty good at contouring
color it is one of the only cool tone
Browns
in the palette so let's try that kind of
good okay a little more just a slight
chisel okay down down for this I think I
want to keep it pretty light when it
comes to the face makeup just because a
lot of contour and blush and highlight
might look a little bit strange over top
of my normal skin when there's no base
underneath to even everything out oh my
god you guys my face actually might
match my
for once okay this is already not
looking the best because at this shade
is very very cool tone but my face is
very very red and they were kind of
mending together to already make orange
don't even want a bronze oh maybe we'll
just go light lastly before I go to the
bronze I'm just gonna grab the e at 62
this does come with my bracelet and it's
the custom brush that I made and I use
this one for and nose contouring I'm
just gonna grab a little bit more punch
me and just go right down the side of
the bridge
oh god that does not look good I guess
the good thing about a hobby foundation
was that I can literally just drop it
off if it looks stupid
what are those oh it's my glasses marks
you're literally kidding me people who
wear glasses to truly know the struggle
like these red marks are permanently
embedded into my skin forever and I've
been wearing these contacts all day long
like how rude that looks not good it's
okay we're gonna make it work so bronze
gonna grab me five to seven brush that
dip into the shade code James now this
shade is very very pigmented so what
we're not going to do is make me look
orange Oh too late okay oh my god you
guys really got me covered this whole no
foundation thing Jesus maybe if I just
like really blended out it won't be oh
that's bad oh my god no it is good about
this though washed out I'm gonna grab my
makeup plate if I go like this all nice
and chiseled doesn't look good for blush
I'm gonna grab my efore brush and dip
into the shade literally which is this
metallic pinky peach shade this is what
my all-time favorite shades in the
palette and I feel like this one is
getting overlooked a little bit at some
of the reviews that I'm seeing so I want
to show her some love the shade is so
what beyond beautiful and I added it to
the palette to be a perfect kind of
blush shade to mix together your bronzer
and your highlighter it is like oh my
how obsessed she's looking up a little
of time I think I'm gonna lay down like
a light coat of highlighter to just to
kind of get the face going so I make my
face a quick spritz of the crepiness at
settings prior they were saying
literally and the entire world you guys
need this in your lives and I'm gonna
grab the shade face on Miami 501 this
comes in the brush that a little bit
above the brow bone as always love a
good glow here like can you imagine what
it would be like to actually have like
good even skin and to be able to do this
and it looked like not disgusting then a
little bit right down the tip of the
nose as well this pilot or is really
intense when you don't have the base
underneath it oh my god I'm gonna come
back to the base later on and see if
there's anything that we can do to kind
of fix it so next time is going to be
the brows and I'm already a little bit
concerned about this step I'm not even
going to lie my Anasazi umbrellas is my
favorite pencil in the entire world and
whenever I get Austin interviews if you
could bring three big upon us that are
deserted island what would they be in
that it's always the first one that I
say because I literally had quite the
broad transformation and using any other
products triggers me including brow
powders which I absolutely hate so an
eye shadow is really not any different
for the brows I'm gonna grab my m15
eight brush this also comes in the brush
set and dip into the shade T in the top
right hand corner this is a cold tone
dark brown shade and I'm going to fill
the brows go start ways to catching the
tail and then drawing the bottom line
I'm trying to keep it very very light
hand because I definitely do not have a
lot of cool tone Brown options in the
palette and I want to be able to like
actually layer it up and add dimension
so I don't have Sharpie brows so to do
that I think I pretty much only want to
define the tail this is actually a
pretty good color for my brows just
gonna use the end of that brush to kind
of blend anything in the front of the
brow okay come on that's not that bad
I'm gonna try it on the other brow as
well so are you guys I'm literally being
so quiet I just know that I don't really
have many options when it comes to
making this look good so I'm trying to
actually focus clearly makeup has no
rules but this is why I will never
understand how people do their eyebrows
at first before anything else because
this books literally crazy Oh ready to
move on so moving on we have the next
step which is going to be of course the
eye shadow which is my favorite part of
the entire routine or we get to use the
palette for what it's actually intended
for it to look really good and fresh
I decided not to cheat and do no
foundation in honor of you guys but when
it comes to this I am going to cheat and
I am going to use just a little bit of
an eyeshadow base this one is the P
Louise basis is literally one of the
best bases in the entire world I learned
about this product from a lot of my
favorite international artists such as a
mum of Mitchell and say Siri MUA and
Kaleigh they're also incredibly tells it
and it works really well for all them I
have had nothing but amazing results
with this as well
and I know a lot of you guys we're
concerned about the fact that I
recommended an eye primer or like a Mac
Paint Pot this product right here is a
super super great alternative as well
gonna use a little bit of this to clean
up the eyebrow using the Amba 410 brush
this one it does come in at my breast
and then with one of the flat concealer
brushes from the brush set this is the
m22 for I'm just gonna grab a little bit
more of that from the back of my hand
and I'm going to tap on any excess and
use this it would just little patting
motions all across the eyelid just to
lay down a light base with a look that
I'm going to do so since we're keeping
it pretty neutral on the shades that
we're using when it comes to my face
clearly I do want to go in and play with
a few different colors when it comes to
the Oxbow my shadow why not let's
unleash my inner artist together I think
I want to do like a sunset smokey eye no
with a blue and purple on the lid mmm
yeah guys we're just gonna do that I'd
hope they don't look alright so just go
ahead and zoom do you guys get a little
bit more so we can focus on the eye look
together and make sure we get all the
details I'm first gonna go to Miami 4 or
5 6 brush and dip into a little bit of a
mix of the shades and cola and escape
and just pack this literally right on
that outer B I'm not gonna put too much
on here because I have a lot of colors
that I need to fit in this eye look
today and the last thing that I want is
for it to get really really messy
and that's better take another M 4 5 6
brush and dip into the shade it's single
which is the bright purple and I'm going
to use this shade to diffuse out that
edge making sure to keep this once again
at very very low to the eyelid because
we have a lot of colors I'm basically
laying this purple right over top of
those two dark shades just to how to
diffuse the edges going back into the
other brush and just adding in some of
the darkness again next we're gonna have
4 3 3 to continue this sunset I'm gonna
grab the shade you're kidding
literally my favorite red in the entire
world and I'm just going to buff out
once again that line I'm trying to go in
with a little bit of a light hand
because this red is insanely pigmented
and I still have a few more colors that
I need to add overtop of it so I don't
want it to get too high up just once
again using those stamping and patting
motions to get the pigment on there
first and then just lightly going over
to blend it out going back in with a
single to make sure we don't lose that
purple in that blend next better gonna
be another M four five six and dip into
the shade and five one eight and this is
the bright neon orange and I'm going to
diffuse out the red and I'm definitely
taking my sweet time especially since we
were getting close to it the eyebrow I
do not want all the colors to get muddy
and then finally just a little bit more
of single lastly I'm gonna go a little
bit of beyond an M of 514 brush and just
use this to buff out that final orange
edge so now that the eye situation is
finally figured out oh my god not
wearing foundation literally not the
move I think I want to do a pop of blue
on the actual eyelid so oh I shouldn't
be cut the crease first I'm first gonna
dip into the shade acappella Miami one
to four and give it a quick spread of my
a setting spray and I'm going to first
pop this right on it the outer area of
the lid just kind of patting and
wiggling that shade right on there I'm
gonna put in probably about two halfway
on the lid as well and bringing that
right up to that crease line and then
with whatever's left I'm gonna go in and
lightly wiggle that brush and between
the transition area just to kind of get
these two to blend together I'm gonna go
back with my original brush that I use
literally first and a little bit of Cola
just to Pat over that transition just
make sure it's nice and smooth and then
without same brush I'm gonna dip into
the shade how low which is the right
metallic teal shade a little bit more of
the settings right and I'm gonna tuck
this shade on the inner half of the
eyelid event of lemon together I'm just
gonna start topping over at that border
with whatever is left of Hello Lassa
finally not least because why not i was
gonna dip into a little bit of artistry
on my finger and i'm just gonna top this
right over top of my lid for the laurel
are the way to show off a little bit of
you're kidding just right up against the
lash and then just a little bit of beet
to blend that right out
the little Cuban e15 to browse just who
these come with a brush set I'm gonna
grab a tiny little bit of ASCII and use
this finally last but not least just to
tuck this right up against that lash
line up for a little bit of dimension
and to connect it in it to that outer
little wing that we created to complete
this eye look I'm just gonna grab it why
not last pencil brush and dab into the
shade of B and I'm gonna place this kind
of really heavily into the inner corner
and then with a tiny little detail brush
this one is not even in the brush spot I
don't know where I even found this I'm
gonna dip into a mix of the shade and
ringly and so good give it a quick
little spritz and I'm going to tuck this
shade right on top of that yellow loving
my shadows are too pigmented it's gonna
grab a little bit of B and go right over
that just to kind of dull it down a
little bit never thought I would say
that when it comes to the inner corner
highly gonna use that same exact mixture
and pop a little bit onto the brow bone
and I think finally that is what I all
complete oh my god you guys I don't know
why it that took me so long I still
struggle with sunset smokey eyes every
single time I do them I generally just
don't understand how some people can fit
so many colors in such a short amount of
space like literally this tiny little
space has to have eyebrow highlight and
yellow and orange and red and magenta
and purple and dark apart wall
look how how do you do that I don't know
clearly but this is looking like okay is
it my best no is it my worst definitely
not so in that case I am happy and ready
to move on to the other eye which I'm
now going to do off camera so you guys
don't have to stay here and watch me for
another two hours be right back all
right hello I am back and those are both
eyes all done and complete and now I am
definitely ready to move on there really
isn't a whole lot left of this look that
I'm able to do with the palette but
we're going to try so I think the one
thing that I really want to address is
my splotchy skin as I put more add more
and more makeup on to my actual eyes it
became very apparent that I was not
wearing any base makeup like I said I am
very much not used to this I wish I had
even skin because this look is so beyond
beautiful and I wish that I could rock
this and feel confident while doing
but I really just don't so I do want to
do a little bit of like covering if I
possibly Canada what I'm gonna do is
grab a beauty blender that I went in the
sink but completely wrung out like there
is a little easier moisture in this and
different to the shade in canvas it is
like the pale kind of eyelid a setting
shade and I'm gonna put this on here and
see if this does a neat good job Oh
we'll be doing a lot of fast oh my god
here we go
Oh oh my god I literally should have
covered my entire face with this I
cannot believe that I did not try this
out earlier I think that I probably
assumed that canvas was too light for my
skin tone but clearly it is not and of
course we can always address it with
bronzer I don't know where my mind was
doing this I really should've thought of
this as well because I've been watching
a few reviews and what was so cold
how did I actually saw a few different
girls using the kind of tube which is
the kind of peachy banana shade as an
under eye setting powder for darker skin
tones so genius it is literally so cool
watching so many different people test
out different techniques so if you are
of a similar skin tone to me and you
happen to be doing the full face using
only one eyeshadow palette challenge
canvas is a great foundation color I
think just for funsies I want to add
some fake freckles so this look one
because they're really really cute and
two because they're gonna distract from
my other skin that's going on so I'm
gonna grab a tiny little lighter brush
this is the e30 7 and in two teeth does
they'd be a little bit dark let's see
not too well you know what maybe I'll do
a few of them entities like for the
darker ones let's see just placing on
little tiny dots everywhere to add a
little bit of like a sunburn effect I'm
gonna go over a little bit of a punch me
and dipping into the tiniest little bit
of 10% off and I'm just
pop that right over top and it's kind of
like okay so that is the face pretty
much all complete and I guess the last
if at all staff is going to be at the
lips which I'm not exactly sure how this
is gonna work but we're gonna try I'm
gonna grab an animal one two four brush
once again and dip into the shade Mary
which is probably like the best nude lip
shade in this palette and see how oh my
god you're kidding I will say this is
very hard to get a precise line this lip
color is gross but it's a lip color
maybe if I do okay I'm gonna put a
little bit of flash back maybe in the
middle kind of a flash like everywhere
or rather this is little bit only
working because my lips are so dry right
no maybe a little shimmer will make it
look kind of glossy
[Music]
is this full face using only my palette
all complete like I said in the
beginning of this video going into this
challenge today I was a little bit
nervous because you guys know I go
bigger go home and everything and I do
not like to lose but once actually kind
of examined the entire palette and
figured out what I wanted to do I was a
lot more confident and ready to go
that being said I am very very pleased
and proud of the finish result today I
think this looks so credibly beautiful
and it's honestly hard to tell that I
did this with no other products but
getting here was definitely not easy I
feel like I would have flown through
this challenge and not how to literally
any issue had I just done a campus all
over the face first I don't know why but
I just didn't think of it and my brain
literally cannot work on makeup
backwards I just have to have a base on
which is what I feel like really really
threw me off the contour finally and
blush could be a little bit better a
little bit sisters thought she but like
I said if I had a base on it probably
won't be having that issue same thing
with the eyebrows it didn't really have
anything to stick to so they look like
okay not the worst pearls definitely not
the best process I've ever done on a
Saskia sweetie I'm so sorry that I ever
tried you for this video as for the
actual eyeshadow I don't know why I was
sister struggling to do a sunset off cut
crease I do these types of looks all the
time but for some reason I just could
not blend its today that being said the
finish is all I think is so it'll be
beautiful I am in love with this eye
look and I think it highlights both the
blue shades and the warm tones on the
palette so incredibly beautifully I
definitely think that adding the frame
freckles were a really really great
touch I cannot believe that using a dark
brown shade like Tia literally worked
for this but I use it for any brain
lately and I definitely do think it
distracted from some of these splotchy
skin so really really glad I added that
and for the lips I cannot believe that
this even stock period definitely does
not look amazing would not walk out of
the house with these lips on but that
being said for literally begin I shadow
palette not bad
regardless of how this finished look
turned out though I had so much fun
doing this challenge oh my god you guys
know I love pushing myself so thank you
so much to everybody who suggested this
I definitely wanna do this again in the
future and if you guys decide to do this
challenge please tweet me photos I would
love to see it what kind of looks do you
guys come up with literally using just
the palette if you enjoyed this video
today please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and subscribe
if you haven't already come during the
sisterhood we are over 10 million a
sister so I'm gonna love to have you and
join the family and also click that Bell
icon so you can get on vacation every
time I upload a brand new video
if you like to follow me on my makeup
journey and see more colorful looks like
this and lots more makeup challenges you
can follow me on Instagram my Twitter
they're both so James turn off my
snapchat for work but I have seen that
stuff is James Charles of extra ass
after Charles
this videos sister shadow goes to sister
Tatiana thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting or loving
literally it's so so so much and if
you'd like to be the next videos sister
shadow don't forget to always retweet by
meddling so they go live on Twitter
alright you guys I think that is all I
have for today's video thank you so so
much for watching don't forget to check
out both morphe calm and Ulta calm as
well and make sure you sign up for the
mailing list to be able to grab the
palette whatever comes back in stock it
is literally flying off the shelves oh
my god I cannot thank you guys enough
for all your support make sure to grab
us so you can unleash your inner artist
alright you guys I think that's all I
have for today is a brand new video
thank you so much for watching I love
you and I will see you in at the next
one
[Music]