hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys all know last Friday was the
world premiere of Maya Brandon reality
competition show instant influencer and
I just wanted to take a few minutes in
the beginning of today's video to say a
major major thank you I'm filming this
on a Saturday which means the show
actually came out yesterday and I was
literally crying all day long I was such
a huge mess because of the reaction and
the comments that literally could not
have been more positive and I am so
incredibly grateful and I cannot wait
for you guys to see the rest of the
episodes in a season because honestly
they just keep getting better and better
and better just like last week's
premiere episode two will be uploaded
once again this upcoming Friday on my
youtube channel right here at 12 p.m.
EST streaming for free that I am look at
that make sure you click the
notification bellow and down below so
you don't miss the notification when I
upload episode 2 about being said
welcome to today's video obviously it is
Tuesday so unfortunately there is not a
new instant influencer episode today but
I thought I'd be really cool for our
videos in between the episodes on
Tuesdays to do something in relation to
the last week's episode I thought it'd
be fun to discuss some comments and some
constructive criticism from you guys
about the show also discussing the
elimination so warning right now there
will be spoilers ahead if you have not
yet watched the episode make sure you
click right up here and go watch it now
before watching today's video and just
overall spilling some tea about the show
and more information that you guys
didn't get to see from behind the scenes
in episode 1 all the contestants were
challenged with making a marketing
campaign video around a makeup product
that already exists in the industry a
lot of the videos were really really
cool up one of them that stuck out the
most me it was Palin's and she had a
beauty sponge as her item how to do your
full face with one tool in one tool only
the Real Techniques Beauty sponge of
course we all have a million Beauty
sponges we even used them every single
day when we're getting ready but I
really liked Kalin's video because she
interviewed her personality she really
made me want to buy the product and she
also had a theme for the video which was
using a Beauty Blender for your full
face of makeup
now obviously I'm pretty sure and
kaylynn's commercial she was only
talking about her base but when I was
watching her on the judging panel my
gear start attorney and I was like oh my
god this would kind of be a fun
challenge but I hadn't at least seen
many people do so for today's video
inspired by a Miss Kailyn of brown at
the show I let a guy my Duty's funds
that I use on an everyday basis
and see if I can do my full face of
makeup using only a beauty blender while
filling some tea about the show let's
get started
[Music]
all right you guys say one thing the
comments section on the first episode
and when threw in screenshotted a ton of
different things that I want to talk
about in today's video but obviously we
do have a challenge to do in Kayla's
video she used the Real Techniques
sponge so in mine I'm gonna grab my
personal favorite which is from a Juna
1ko it's a microfiber one so it's really
kind of like fluffy and just applies
everything really really beautifully I'm
gonna grab my touch out water cream
which is my oyster Iser and start off
with some skincare using my sponge I've
actually never done this before but you
definitely can so we're just gonna I
guess grab some on there and to start
you know applying it to the face also
I'm aware that my face looks a little
bit crazy right now I promise as much as
it looks like it I did not go crazy with
the blush unfortunately I fell asleep in
the Sun a few days ago and I forgot to
put on sunblock which is a major lesson
to you guys always wear sunscreen and I
got very burnt Oh Lois look at how that
looks on camera I have never had a sign
that hurts as much it literally was
painful just to put on their shirt today
were filming this YouTube video so
please do not comment about my
foundation matching okay I'm gonna try
my best
I've been applying my Olivera just let
me be and wear your sunscreen always the
first comment that I want to address
while I'm doing up my foundation of my
yet beauty sponge is this one from Zee
mystery and they said I really
appreciate that it's free especially
during these times
now this comet makes me a berry oh I
forgot to call it cracked well too late
now
now this comet makes me very very happy
to hear because it was super important
to us that everybody was able to you
know watch the show and enjoy it for
free what's actually crazy though is
that we filmed the entire show in
January when Corona was not even a thing
here in America yet so our decision to
make the show free literally nothing to
do with the parents out there it was
actually a goal of ours from day one and
when we were talking to our production
company and our partners for the show
which obviously ended up being a youtube
originals it was like literally a thing
that we negotiated inside we are not
doing this if it's not gonna be free so
we're very grateful that we were able to
make that happen so everybody could
access it and we're even more grateful
that it is free during these really
really hard times because everyone stuck
at home it's fun enjoyable content and I
know you all have really important
things to spend your money on right now
like bills and staying alive during this
awful awful awful time so I will say
that I really really
want to continue to do more high
production content for free in the
future as well so fingers crossed they
were able to continue to make that
happen
the base is looking at gorgeous so far
is that cheating's I just cheap fix plus
I just bring down my face I wasn't
thinking about it so the basis a lot and
now I'm going to go in and start to
cream contouring and I'm going to use
the Tarte shape Cape in the shade D I'm
just going to put this on the back of my
hand and ones in a little bit with the
foundation this next comment that I want
to very quickly talk about is from
Lorelei la Fran boys la Fram boys a loss
and she says is someone gonna tell James
that he was meant to be a host this
comment literally oh that is not the
color that I want to be using right now
ah that's a skin oh my god oh my god are
you serious oh come on
well okay this is gonna be a bronzer I
saw this comment so many times on
yesterday's video and I'm not gonna go
super in-depth on this because the whole
point of this video is not to compliment
me but I want to say a major major thank
you to the people who noticed this and
comment to this because it means so much
to me you guys know that I wanted to be
some like this for a very very long time
and as excited as I was to get started
on set I was very very nervous
episode 1 and I don't really get nervous
really for anything I kind of go into
everything like ready to go but
obviously this was such a new experience
for me and I was surrounded by industry
professionals that were working on the
shelves the last thing that I wanted to
do was you know get on set and embarrass
myself and how big to redo takes a
million times and of course we still had
every do quite a lot of things and get
you know good audio clips and video
clips of everything but as we really
started getting into filming even on
like day one I just felt so confident in
it and really felt like this is what I'm
meant to be doing and if you guys
thought I was good in episode 1 it
literally got way way way better by the
time of the finale so this means a lot
thank you for saying this thank you for
noticing this and I definitely want to
and have plans to host so other things
this week is from Aisha and she said cry
I love them hashtag instant influencer
with a screen shot of indigo and Kailyn
in the workroom after
elimination I just want to put this in
there because first of all I told you
all that you were going to love the
contestant and so what so glad that like
literally everybody was obsessed with
everybody on the show all six of them
were so much fun it's such a pleasure to
work with and be on that way that an all
of us are still in a group chat to this
day and we talk all the time and have
been so excited about the show and I
have just been really really itching for
all of you guys to get to watch them and
to fall in love with your favorite and
DePalo and support them everybody has
been like any a ridiculous amount of
followers on social media since
yesterday's premiere which is so so cool
obviously that's the point of the show
but at the end of the day though you
guys as the viewers get to really make
the final decision of who you know you
want to follow and support so keep
loving that I'm so glad you guys do
great and last but not least before we
jump into a powder I'm gonna grab the
covergirl clean fresh clean the
covergirl clean fresh cream blush I
don't really love cream blushes or cream
highlighters or liquid highlighters worn
liquid blushes or really liquid anything
why would you say that like you boo me
it's such a like this duck summit comes
from Oliver and he says this is a great
show thank you so much for someone who
is personally not really into makeup I
enjoyed it so much it wasn't too long it
was exciting and the contestants are so
talented true I wish we could see the
contestants talking while the judges
deliberate thank you for leaving a
constructive criticism in a really
really cool way I love reading a start
to criticism and seeing what you guys
want to see in the show it was actually
kind of weird because we didn't plan on
filming anything of the contestants
while they were in that like holding
room before going back to their video
mobs mostly because we didn't really
plan for that like to be a full set so
that room literally looked awful on
camera but once we got the footage back
that the contestants like talking to
each other and like gossiping and
talking about the judging and the
challenges we were like oh this is gold
like we have to include this in the show
which is why I love being there despite
the fact that it looks you know not the
best and we definitely longer do this
for season two and who knows it might
even end up being something that we post
like on an insta influence or separate
Channel because that's like a lot of
really good side contact but I think you
guys would love to see as well so
definitely us know and definitely keep
us posted with more cultural criticism
and feedback we'd love to see it and we
obviously want to make the show the best
that it possibly
Hanabi so wednesday ina Thank You Oliver
for the suggestion okay there's hardly
time to set this base in place god bless
I don't want any more creases so I'm
just gonna grab my beauty sponge at once
again and dip right into my translucent
setting powder and we're going to lock
it in all right you guys that's pretty
much the base for now all completes and
of course the next step is going to be a
brows an eye shadow I'm gonna be
skipping my brows because I think they
look okay and there's just no way that
anything is gonna happen with the brows
I do want to try to do eyeshadow I'm
going to quickly go to the bathroom and
give at both of these Beauty blenders a
quick little cleaning because they're
very very dirty but I'll be right back
zoomed in to try to create a look okay
so for eyeshadow today I do have some
cream shadows that I found in my
collection I have never actually used
these before I've never even used a
cream eyeshadow if I'm gonna be honest I
don't have high hopes for this but I'm
just gonna try it out and see where
things go
okay so Long's really got this eye
shadow I wanted to talk a little bit
about the judges in the episode and what
you guys have thought about that this
card from abuse s says Paris is well
Abdul James is Randy Jackson and or
veena is Simon Cowell this comment
definitely gave me a cute little giggle
yesterday because if you're an original
American Idol fan you know oh geez Paris
obviously came in and was super super
nice to the contestants which made sense
because usually when you're a guest
judge on the show that's like the role
that that person fills and then I
obviously as the host was kind of like I
wouldn't say like neutral because I
definitely gave quite a lot of criticism
so I tried to match like all of my
criticism with a positive as well so
that way the contestants are able to you
know use that information to their
advantage if they make it on to the next
challenge
and then obviously at noir veena is
there and she gave quite a lot of you
know more serious critiques and there
was quite a lot of comments about it
glossy fox said it the face of novena
makes are killing me
Ariana Guzman said I love nor Venus
Christian show criticism she really
knows what she's doing yes I would 1000%
have to agree nor veena is one of you
know my closest friends in the industry
but she's also you know the creative
director and a leader of a
billion-dollar makeup brand that all of
us know and love so honestly for me it
was like a no-brainer to ask taormina to
be on the show nor Vina brings so many
really really strong critiques and
knowledge to these contestants from what
she's learned from working the industry
for the past several
and it's really really good I love her
because she's so brutally honest but
sometimes later in this industry you
really need to hear that because it's
those cupboards that can really take you
to the next level if you take in that
information and use it to your advantage
instead of taking it to heart this looks
terrible oh this is a bad choice okay
you guys I'm just gonna stop here on the
eyeshadow and move on to the rest of the
face to finish off this challenge I knew
this is a bad idea okay I called it
there's the footage exists I never even
used a cream eyeshadow if I'm gonna be
honest I don't have high hopes for this
and it definitely was I don't think it
looks awful but yeah I definitely prefer
my morphe brushes heyday of the week to
Beauty Blender all right you guys so
while we work on finishing up this look
and finishing up this challenge I want
to talk about probably the thing that
has been most controversial or comments
about since episode one and that is the
elimination also once again if you have
not seen the episode please like right
up here because spoiler alerts are
coming right now and I don't wanna ruin
it if you guys want to watch it Academy
does mess I'm a huge fan of how the
elimination is set up it's not made to
embarrass the person that is being sent
home James tells you personally it you
two are alone and he encourages you to
keep doing YouTube videos James have you
read this you're doing a great great job
thank you so much Ekaterina Richard why
he just says the ending is a bit weird
and the girl is so emotional but
suddenly having to draw her YouTube
channel wall she's about to cry Leah
says everyone's like no Paris but James
was so nice to Britney when she was
eliminated I cried oMG alright so I'm
going to highlight using my morphe cream
highlighting second the number Effect
one no matter what reality show you're
watching the eliminations are always a
little bit controversial because of
course everybody has you know they're
different favorites everybody has
different beliefs as to you know who did
best in what challenges who should have
what home who should have stayed etc etc
originally we did actually have it
planned to do the eliminations kind of
in like the typical reality style format
where we just tell you know the winner
and the loser in the judging room but
since this is like a influencer slash
like content creation based show we
thought it would be kind of cool to tie
and elimination with that whole theme
and we came up with the idea of doing
the video lab elimination I personally
really really liked how they turned out
because obviously it's good
entertainment and that is the point of
creating a show also further points the
account arena brought up which is one
it's much more personal just send
somebody home
because you actually get to sit down and
talk to them face-to-face to hold her
hand to hug them to make sure that
they're good but also to give them a
constructive criticism and feedback for
one last time of what they can do to you
know better themselves in their career
moving forward nothing it's like
embarrassing but I would prefer to be
eliminated in private and not in front
of all my cast mates who happen to do
better I guess it's just because like I
don't like that type of confrontation um
so I really do it worked out
obviously yes Brittany was very very
emotional being sent home and yeah sure
I guess it's fair to say that it may
have been a little bit awkward to launch
Brittany you know cry and have to prohm
or herself on camera but first of all
it's better to promo yourself all crying
that I'm probably herself at all and
that's the whole point of the show is to
give it smaller artist platforms that I
think really really deserve it and we
almost wanted to bring it like a full
circle and tie it back to being an
actual influencer and filming a YouTube
video obviously it's an episode of a
show which is not exactly the same thing
but you guys are used to seeing me at
the end of all my videos sign-off and
you know do my little promo and get you
guys to follow the other socials and
that's the last thing that you guys get
to see of me on all my content so we
thought it'd be really cool to give it
the artists who do get sent home one
last opportunity to shine to plug
themselves and to you know make the last
impression before going home I'll write
you guys the only thing I'm missing left
in this look is going to be at the lips
so I'm gonna grab that crema covergirl
blush once again that I use on my cheeks
and just a little bit of that on the
back to my hand and I'm going to use my
mini Beauty Blender to finish off the
slock I just applied some mascara off
camera because let's be real this look
was looking a little bit busted without
it and I thought the lips are data that
is this full face using only a Beauty
Blender all complete you guys I had up
so much fun at doing this challenge
tonight and also addressing some
comments and questions that you guys had
about the show I hope I answered some
questions and further clarify it at some
things as much as putting this look
together was a little bit of a mess I
honestly don't really think it came out
that bad and I am obsessed I think this
looks so beautiful especially using the
cream blush and cream highlighter to I
was on the biggest fan of them but
honestly I might want to use them a
little bit more often at the eyes on the
other hand I wanted to try it out okay
it was definitely a fail but and then a
you guys try out this challenge and do
get a successful loss
let me know how it goes at tweet me a
photo I would love to see it your guys
his work if you want to see it more
entertaining and fun makeup content
please check out my brand new shell
instant influencer airing right here on
my channel for free episode
is live now in episode 2 will be out
this Friday only a few days away of turn
on your own vacation bill set your
alarms put something in your calendar
you guys are not gonna lot of mess at
this one if you guys enjoyed today's
video please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and show your
love and support also please make sure
your thumbs hang up the show episodes as
well it really does help out a lot and
we really want a season two it also
click that subscribe button down below
and come join up this is your head we're
18 million sister song I don't to have
you join the family and also type that
bow-tie phone so you can own fit every
time I upload a brand new video if you
like to follow me on my makeup table you
can follow me on Instagram Twitter to
take stock and Facebook to ultra steam
Charles my snapchat for but have the
same time self-esteem showers the next
rest after Charles in if you want to
text me up right here on my personal
phone number for any exclusive updates
on amort videos photos and everything
else new episodes as well my phone
number is three one oh nine oh five
eight seven four six this video sister
shadow goes to sister Delana thank you
so much love for always logging in
supporting I love you so so so much I
feel at home late to be the next videos
a sister shout out don't forget to
always reach me a video links when they
go live on Twitter thank you so much
watching today's video don't forget to
tune into influencer this Friday I love
you so much and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]