hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel and
it's currently a rainy day here in a
California while we were on quarantine
and for today today I just wanted to sit
down and play with makeup and we're
going to do this thing that we actually
have not done in quite a long time now
and that is a makeup challenge now a few
weeks ago I was scrolling through Tech
Talk and I saw a really a really cool
video of this moment applying her makeup
using an airbrush machine now if you
don't know what an airbrush machine is
it is this baby right here basically you
pouring little drops right into the top
then you turn it on and then you spray
your makeup out on to at the face so
airbrush makeup is actually not
something that is really new to the
beauty world it is most commonly used on
movie sets and special effects makeup
horror film but it is really not a
technique that has made its way into
like the typical mainstream Beauty
universe and that is because if you
don't know what you're doing it is very
very hard so although it's not new to
the makeup world it is new to me and for
today's video I wanted to try out doing
a full face of makeup using only
airbrush machines now I wanna be honest
of you guys and tell you that today is
my fourth time trying to film this video
so usually I do my makeup challenges and
you know it's a little bit of a bumpy
road but in the end it usually comes
together for this particular video
however it was not doing that it was
literally melting all over my face it
was spotty I could not get it to look
good and I just did not understand why I
was getting it so ridiculously angry but
then I realized okay this is the makeup
challenge obviously I cannot be good at
everything and instead of just giving up
and moving on I want to get this video
one last shot so I did some research
watch some videos and called in some
backup and we're gonna try this one last
time so if you guys want to watch me
into a full face of airbrush makeup keep
on watching
[Music]
okay guys before we jump in I want to
give it to super quick shout outs the
first one being to the brand attempt to
you what they are an airbrush company
and they heard that I was doing this
video so they sent me over a full
package of goodies since all the makeup
stores are closed and during a
quarantine that the to do is not
sponsored okay I'm not being paid to say
anything I do have some products with
other brands as well but I do want to
say a major thank you to them and the
second channel is to a channel here on
YouTube but by the name of an airbrush
MUA by Z G is so incredible and she does
the full videos on her channel at using
airbrush makeup when I was failing so
many times I left a comment on her video
not like if she was gonna see it or not
and she literally saw on FaceTime with
me for hours the TV at the proper
techniques in showing me what I was
doing wrong she even sent over some of
her personal colors and machines for me
to youth to try out for today's video so
she is literally an angel she saved this
video okay you guys I want you to go
check out her channel look for their do
okay let's get started
so nobody you guys knows my makeup
routine I start off with my foundation
first and then go on to eyebrows eyes
and the whole shebang for airbrush
makeup we're actually gonna do in the
opposite order starting with brows and
eyes first because if I mess it up which
I very well might it'll be easier to
clean up instead of how I would be like
the entire base over about being said
let's go ahead and grab our first color
which is going to be you know dark brown
for our brows we're gonna do three drops
okay so no see if we could go like this
there it is with the airbrush you can
obviously just like go in and spray it
which we'll get you later on but for
more specific details it comes with a
lot of these really cool stencils which
help you get like more accurate lines
and shapes and stuff so I'm gonna grab
this fun little brow stencil we're just
gonna go right in okay there we go
okay yes that looks great okay great now
I'm gonna have to do any arch okay now
I'm gonna do my tail and this gonna
oh okay well I'd like to think that only
God but also Jesus shoot chefs are over
starting over
attempt number three oh this is so hard
perfect oh my god perfect perfect for my
boobs that looks cute she's chic she's
here she's ready to party you know we're
gonna clean off first sense all cuz now
it's all dirty and we're gonna do what's
wrong number two okay so I want to make
sure that these are even obviously
tonight it's not okay
I'm happy with them they could of course
be a little bit better but after trying
this for different time I am very happy
with these these are by far the best
that I have done and I just want to move
on that while we have that so we're
gonna go ahead and move on to the iris
of a portion already kind of followed me
right okay I really stated for the I've
set of courses because the last few
times that I've tried this it wasn't the
skin that I was messing up on I actually
really enjoyed it it was the eye shadow
portions because I literally could not
get the colors too later on and they are
melting they were getting in my eyeballs
and my contacts it was not good but I
picked up a lot of different techniques
from Ziya that I'm gonna try out today
so hopefully this will work a whole lot
better so I'm gonna hold my stencil back
up to my skin at once again because I
don't want to get any of this color on
my actual brow that we just you know
we're so hard on but I was gonna go
ahead and spray this nice vanilla color
on my brow bone to brighten it up oh
this excitement probably seems so lame
but you guys after trying this so many
times on the other eye of all perfect
two layers a little bit on my actual
eyelids as well
I really Bane the eyelids at almost like
dark areas right in this inner corner
for some reason so putting on a light
wash will just kind of neutralize that
so for my look today I want to do
something a pretty it but nothing too
colorful because if that takes a lot of
practice I'm actually gonna grab this
nice little shimmery bronze shade first
to go my lid very weird I'm gonna use
stencil just to avoid getting it on my
face well they're pretty okay there we
go you guys know that I always do while
I'm Cara then while I off you can't work
that way with every bus either you have
to do both eyes at the same time to keep
your colors consistent to not have to
clean the gada a million times so you're
in for a treat today same thing on this
I wall so for our next color we're now
going to grab a burnt orange shade so
we're gonna do our crease color now this
order so strange and this we're gonna be
very careful with because we need to
layer this up it's gonna start layering
this in the outer corner and then just
pulling this shade up into the crease
pretty good like even so far this is
looking good okay then I want to darken
up my upper corner a little bit so I'm
gonna grab it summit dark brown and I'm
gonna add in a few drops into the
machine and then I'm just going to
what's called a back bubbling press it
in there and then mix the colors
together some nice bubbling happening in
there okay layer this into the outer V
this is a million times more fun than
regular eyeshadow are you kidding
so now I'm gonna go back in with a
little bit more of my orange color just
to bring something with that well this
is really giving it to me right now wer
this is like everything that I needed
anymore she on the other hand is that's
how my feelings I want to add back a
little bit of that shimmery color since
it got lost in the blending this is
what's good about airbrushed shoes that
you can layer everything together
that's pretty oh wow that's so excited
alright you guys so now we get to the
part of this look that could very well
ruin act or title together and that is
going to be the eyeliner now if you are
like me you're probably thinking how are
you gonna do
with everybody and you know I'm gonna
show you I thought that this would have
never been possible but then I saw
everybody's video where she just you
know went right in surprisingly you can
actually get a Barry do you tell mine
with this we're still gonna use our
since all this out and pray that this is
not what takes us down because we do so
good so farms are in the middle of the
lid oh my god and then for this area
we're going to continue with the same
shape that we've been doing and we're
going to use this to darken up very
lightly oh my god I light up with
airbrush who would have thought it would
be possible not me I'll take that right
now let's try this again on the other
eye perfect I think I'm happy without I
don't think I want to go any further
okay great so that is converse the eye
shadow portion of this look all complete
of course we can add on the brow bone
highlight and lashes a little bit later
on to look just because I don't want to
mess anything up but before we go on to
the foundation I'm gonna quickly take
just a makeup wipe and we're gonna clean
up this bottom edge that looks gorgeous
okay same thing on the side I know that
I was getting so excited and literally
screaming throughout this entire portion
but after so when he tries okay it feels
really good to just get something that
actually looks presentable on the eyes I
feel like I'm finally succeeding at this
makeup challenge and now it is time to
move on to our next step which is going
to be a foundation and so it should be a
little bit of smoother sailing from here
on all right so now it is time for our
foundation and I have two colors here
that I'm going to mix together
Foundation is definitely what I'm most
excited about and also like what
airbrush makeup is kind of most commonly
used for especially with like weddings
because obviously your toes to look like
airbrush and it's just like looks
flawless all blended together so I'm
really pumped for this stop I'm gonna
grab one of my straight edge stencils so
I can do this portion if I have a shoe
that actually messing up any of the work
that we just did well I really really am
obsessed with how this covered look it's
very much like your skin but better type
of on deal you can still see my freckles
and beauty marks poking through which
personally I
love like 23 foundation with airbrush
all the time are you kidding
okay let's doing that too okay I think
it's done
not as time to contour I'm gonna grab a
few drops of this clock called hazelnuts
zis a way to hold this really a really
far away what I'm going to do that's a
little bit dark oh okay why is wow this
is my bad type and this one's coming out
so much better today
okay okay little harsh oh god this bout
looks bad we're gonna layer some
foundation back over top of that it's
just looks gray now what I do
should I just wipe off this area though
okay that definitely helped oh wow
well no way liners gray though once
again I'm gonna cut cameras for a minute
get back to where I was then we're gonna
recontour I'll be back okay hello when
you're back i touched up the foundation
got the eyeliner back to where it wise
we're just how to contour it once again
and this time we're gonna literally hold
this 8,000 miles away okay that's not
that bad I think with bronzer and blush
over top of a no look it'll like come
together now decide for blush I'm really
hoping that this will like pull together
at the contour a little bit I'm gonna
start on my right hand side which
apparently today is a better side that
looks yellow now to this side oh forgot
your nose contour that's scary
my big ass nose okay I'm just coming I
can't even listen that okay no nose
contour
on the highlight let's go this is the
final stretch you guys we're doing good
let me out a little bit on the brow
bones should I try to do my inner
corners or is that like risking it
that's good okay oh my god oh my god you
guys well I think at this point we can
turn off our airbrush machine because
we're dying but we do have two long
steps to do which is going to be it just
of course the eyelashes and then
all right you guys we'll finally after
three attempts it looks like four times
is the charm four wines because that is
a fullface using only airbrush makeup
all complete I am incredibly happy and
proud with how this look turned out
today it is not perfect in any way shape
or form okay I'm not claiming it to me
but in comparison to the other three
times that I film is okay this looks
amazing and I am so so happy with it I
want to say it once again a major major
thank you to airbrush Mui a by Z she
literally saved this video hey this
would not happen if it would offer oh my
god don't want a face I've never and
show her this look does it look good you
could be honest
[Music]
thank you for your videos and thank you
for being such a good teacher I
appreciate it so much
thank you talk to you soon Arisa guys
well looks like we have officially been
airbrushed approved by the pro I
definitely want to practice so much more
because I feel like this could be such a
fun way to apply makeup I'm definitely
looking forward to hearing what you guys
have to say about this let me know your
thoughts in the comments down below
would you ever try our airbrush makeup
let me know if you enjoyed this video
today please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and show your
love and support and helps me out a lot
and also make sure you click that big
red subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood we were almost 18
million sister strong and I would love
to have you in the family and also click
that Bell icon so you can over kitchen
every time I upload a brand new video if
you like to follow me on my makeup turn
you can follow me Instagram Twitter
TechTalk and Facebook all just James
Charles a snapshot for more behind the
scenes nights out she hugs that extra
ass after Charles and my phone number if
you want to text me for any fun updates
on videos merch and so much more my
number is 3 100 905 8 7 4 6 this video
sister shout out goes the sister of
Mikayla thank you so much lo for always
following and supporting I love you so
so so much and if you like to be the
next videos a sister shadow don't forget
to always reach me with a link something
alive on Twitter all right you guys that
a thought for today's video thank you so
much for watching it remember that my
new show instant influence are we
streaming free starting April 24th right
here on my
some nice a quarantine content I love
you stay safe stay home wash your hands
and I will see you in the next one
[Music]