hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so if
you saw in last week's video which if
you have not you should definitely click
somewhere up here and check it out I did
an unboxing a free makeup that beauty
gurus game video and I opened all sorts
of wonky products all the new releases
seemed so good and I was absolutely
dying to try them out and of course
today just two days after filming that
last video I opened my door this morning
and there are about 50 new PR packages
waiting for me
they couldn't have came two days earlier
to be in the free PR video but you know
I would regarding to what we've got for
today today I wanted to sit down I've
got a new makeup that is all fresh off
the shelves we have a new primer a new
foundation a new highlighter and a new
eyeshadow palette so a ton of great new
products that I am so excited to try and
honestly all turned out really really
good spoiler alert so I did this warm
tone a pop of color crease that you guys
have all been asking me to film a
tutorial on I posted a pic on my answer
a few days ago and y'all went crazy and
I did do this look using the new Anasazi
a subculture eye palette and it turned
out so freakin good
so if you want to see how I created this
makeup look right here using all new
products and first impressions make sure
you keep on watching alright so before I
go into the actual foundation I'm gonna
first go into my benefit Porefessional
new pore minimizing makeup now in the
last video if you guys have not checked
it out yet definitely go watch it it is
a PR unboxing video but I got three of
these and I thought that this was like a
three-step process but my dumbass failed
to realize that there's actually three
different shades not three different
steps so I grabbed shade number two and
I'm going to put this on and see how it
works hopefully we'll be minimizing my
pores because I could use it alright so
I guess this product is not technically
a foundation it just as its pore
minimizing makeup I'm not really sure
what that technically makes it as but if
I look close up in the mirror my pores
honestly do look really really good they
don't look like completely cover
obviously there's gonna be nothing that
I can put on my face that's kind of
completely go into my pores
unfortunately for me and for everybody
else out there but definitely they do
look pretty pretty balm and looking at
the monitor as well my skin definitely
has like a blurred effect so I think I
actually really really like this product
but let's see how actually layer
underneath foundation okay so Furcal and
ations they were actually using a brand
new at first impressions product and
that is the Smashbox to do skin is
shaping foundation it is a dual ended
foundation stick with one end being
Foundation's and wanted being a contour
stick so
I am super super excited to try these
out I've heard really really good things
about them and I did actually get to
test use this a very very very long time
ago with matchbox and I was in love with
it then so this is not really a first
impressions for like a second
impressions but I think it'll be good
hopefully I grab the shade of 1.2 which
looking at it on my face is definitely a
little bit too yellow and I know people
love to comments like my foundation it
doesn't match my neck thank you I am
well aware of the fact that I like to
use a more tan foundation than my
skintone I think I get so many comments
about it and it is definitely something
that I am aware of and do on purpose so
thank you so much for your concern but
I'm gonna be using this shade today and
it is definitely yellow and I'm
recognizing that right now so please
don't comment about it aside for the
fact that this foundation stick is
nowhere near the right color for me I
actually really really like how it looks
on my face it is definitely way too
yellow but I'm gonna even it out with
some concealer so far so good
before I go into any concealer I'm gonna
quickly cream contour my face using the
other end of the foundation stick this
is saying that I definitely don't like
doing very often I definitely before
contouring with powders however for the
sake of this video obviously I want to
give the product a fair shot and a full
on review so I'm going to cream contour
just the slightest bit alright so this
is definitely blending out really really
well as you can see it does not take a
lot of effort at all and it runs really
really nice the end of the skin
obviously no one wants to sit there
pouncing a Beauty Blender into their
freaking cheek for 30 minutes trying to
blend out a cream product so it looks
good and this is definitely going out in
a pretty little effort which is awesome
and I do like the color of this as well
it's definitely like a contour and
bronzing at the same time which is a
great and definitely a time saver as
well that's kind of how I like to do my
contour slash bronzer in the first place
I really don't do them separately
they're kind of like one baking process
free and that's how I really do like it
so I definitely I'm liking this
foundation stick a lot I'm gonna try to
fix up my skin tone a little bit using
the Tarte shape tape and light I do not
get any new concealers in my PR packages
although color pop I know just came out
with new concealers and I'm dying to try
those so definitely let me know if you
guys nothing to do a video review on
those once I get them in the mail with
my luck they'll probably come in like 20
minutes
as I'm felling this video after I
already had my shape tape on but
whatever it will make it work another
time the actual color of the foundation
definitely looks a lot better now that
I've lined it up my concealer and I'm of
course it's gonna set it really lightly
in place using my Laura Mercier
translucent setting powder all right so
it's called my face today I'm gonna
using the brand new makeup forever
artist face color
single little thing and this is in the
shade asked one one two and as I talked
about in last week's video this has a
very very special place in my heart
because sister caste want my best
friends in the entire world
did actually work with makeup forever on
creating these shadows and bringing them
all together to create a little bit of a
trio so I'm gonna be using her three
shades today to sculpt and make my face
look beautiful this contour sheet is
definitely very very cool tool because
sister Cassie is more on the pale side
and she has a more like pink undertone
but this honestly looks really really
good on my skin it doesn't look grey or
like Ashley in any way shape or form it
got fleas like a very very good like
cheek bone or like bone shadow type of
color it looks like very very natural
and chiseled out I really like this for
blush today I'm gonna grab the maker
Forever artists face color blush in the
shade of B 402 now as you can see this
is bright ass orange so I'm only gonna
use a very very little bit of this but
you guys do know that I love orange
blush a lot and oh my god this is very
very very pigmented which is a good
thing but also a scary thing oh my god
I'm just gonna really really lightly
table something that's a lot of blush
this is not what I want this is not what
I planned and I just gotta say I do not
understand something is really something
is orange something is really wrong
someone is literally playing music
outside my window so loud right now for
no reason at all I'm getting so annoyed
and now their sirens of course what else
could go wrong I just did my brows
off-camera you guys to see me do it so
many times now no point in trying the
same exact process and now for the eye
shadow we have the star of the show
don't do the on assad's you get
subculture eyeshadow palette I am so
excited for this this is actually not
featured in my last video and I did
feature the anasazi liquid glow
highlighters which we will be using in a
little while as well I just got this in
the mail a few minutes ago before I
started filming and I tweeted and so
many of you guys wanted to see this now
for the actual I look I was planning on
doing this cut crease the pop of color
left a few days ago on my Instagram
everybody was freaking out they loved it
everybody asked for a tutorial so I was
gonna film not to me but this
like I said just got here a few minutes
ago everyone's like oh my god you have
to use subculture so I am warning you
now I'm gonna be using the more classic
colors from this palette not the boring
ones at all because I feel like this is
gonna be so beautiful but there's
obviously like this teal tone the green
at the bronze II shade and the electric
chartreuse as well so I will not be
using those shades so please let me know
if you want to actually see a more
in-depth advanced tutorial using this
palette but for today's that I'm going
to use any more classic warm tone shades
I apologize for that but you guys asked
for this I first gotta grab my Anasazi
angled brush number seven and dip into
the shade of fudge and start sketching
out my crease
oh wow that is what we like to call it
ladies and gentlemen pigmented so cut
crease is releasing that I've done a lot
on my channel and they are by far my
favorite makeup look to do I just love
the look of a good cut snatched crease
and this is the technique that I used to
do them I always get questions about it
because it is only a unique technique
but I always start off by drawing at the
bottom of the crease line with an angle
brush just to define it in and then
blend upwards afterwards I'm gonna
centigram eye makeup Shakti 63 brush and
dipped into a little bit more fudge and
I'm just gonna buff out that line a
little bit now normally when it comes to
these eye looks beauty guru is never
even touch the brushes that actually
come in the palette but I am gonna grab
this one today on the fluffier and and
different edition new wave which is this
like very mac and cheese orange e yellow
shade it's so beautiful and I'm just
gonna use this to blend that out oh my
god these shadows are so beyond
pigmented
oh my god it is no secret to anybody
that Anasazi always kills it with the
pigmentation in their shadows but oh my
god these are real good nice carving my
morphe r43 brush i'm gonna dip into the
shade all-star and I'm gonna use that to
to find out that crease again I'm gonna
grab my makeup Shakti 63 brush once
again and dip into the shade of Roxy and
I'm gonna use that to blend together the
fudge transition shade and the all-star
pinky shade if that makes sense
this is looking so messy for some reason
there's definite looking a little bit
more wonky than my normal crease and I
really don't know why exactly but you
know what we're just gonna keep going
and hope that it looks good by the end
of this to finish off the shadow portion
of this crease I'm going to grab my
angled brush once again and dip it to
the tiniest little bit of the shade
rowdy and they're just going to carve it
out one last time
for some reason that was one of the
hardest cut creases I've ever had to do
I don't know why normally I can fly
through them so easily but today I'm
having an off day I guess whatever it
looks pretty decent now so I guess
they're gonna go ahead and move on and
for the pop of color liner today I'm
gonna be using the lime cryin liquid
liner in the shade sit truth you
definitely ought to be super super
careful at this step as well because
especially when it comes to colored
liner they're usually very very drying
so if you do mess up its gonna be a very
very very hard to fix your mistakes like
I have made several times throughout
doing this type of look so just be
careful please to do my Wayne Leonard
today I'm gonna use my tried-and-true
and that is the Kat Von D tattoo liner
in the shade it trooper
this is definitely a much bigger waiting
that I wanted to go forward today but I
guess it's just one of those days oh my
god I forgot to blend out their cream
contour underneath my lab for my lower
lash and I first gonna grab my fudge on
my morphe r43 brush and just buff that
into the lower lash line then I'm gonna
grab the other end of the Anasazi brush
that comes in the palette and I'm gonna
grab the show you a new wave and just
buff out that color to line my water
then I'm gonna use the NYX wonder pencil
in the shade light actually helps to
open your eyes up and make your eyes
look huge in fact almost every single
time I wear a cut crease with a white
liner in my waterline I always get so
many comments feeling wide you facing
your eyes to be bigger and I'm like girl
about everything else on my entire face
is too soon except my eye shape why is
that even a concern so wonky and for the
last day I'm gonna pop on the house
luscious iconic lashes I know that in my
last video I did get a package from Lily
lashes and I use the miami's but I feel
like iconic lashes like the absolute
necessity last when it comes to a cut
crease they just look so beautiful and
so stunning and I did just get a new
package of these like 20 minutes ago
once again I was totally so annoyed for
some reason of course every single PR
package in the world decides to come
like three days after I film an unboxing
free PR video huh that's just my luck
while I'm gluing this lost I do want to
talk about something that I addressed in
the last video as well and that is the
illegal drugs that I received in my pure
package and I do want to give a major
major apology to a cloud9 syrup the
brand that did send me those products
they are not illegal and they are not
drugs either and I felt so bad because
like after reading your guys's comments
and doing some more research I was like
so shocked and I felt so ignorant dumb
so CBD and hemp oil are not illegal
contrary to what I thought in the video
and they're also in marijuana like I did
think they're actually unlike the
medical side of marijuana the part of it
that like actually helps you and doesn't
get you high
not gonna lie as soon as I recognize the
word hemp which I knew was in weed I was
so turned off because you guys know that
I'm very very anti drug and I am very
very ignorant to the topic it's
definitely not something that I've ever
wanted to learn about or wanted to
educate myself about just because I do
know that a lot of people in the social
media world and in the entertainment
industry do go into very very bad path
a lot of like drugs and addiction and
stuff so that's just saying that I've
tried it very very hard to stay away
from and I do pride myself in you can do
whatever you want but like I said I'm
very very ignorant to it so as soon as I
saw that I was like oh nope nope nope
nope not happening but after learning
about it more I did realize that it was
part of the medical side and I saw so
many comments from you guys being like
oh my god this is so disrespectful like
I used hemp oil and CBD every single
night because I have really bad anxiety
and I was like oh my god
obviously mental health is so important
that I would never want to purposely
degrade anxieties or mental health
issues at all and I really do sincerely
apologize if my comments in the last
video I offended you in any way shape or
form like I said I was ignorant to the
topic but now I've educated myself on it
and it's so amazing that products like
this do exist on the market to help
people out with those type of issues
because I know they are very very
serious thing like I said that is very
very much not my world and instead of
educating myself I just made a very very
ignorant comment for a clickbait title
which was definitely wrong so I do
apologize and it is still not for me but
if you guys want to check out their
products please do check them out they
are an awesome brand and the brand has
reached out to me cents and like gave me
a ton of information so yes
sorry to cloud9 syrup and if you guys
want to check it out I will link this up
down below alright and they're both
creases all cut and ready to go and now
it's time for what we've all been
waiting for the glow for my highlighter
today I'm using the brand new Anasazi
liquid glow and I'm gonna be using the
shade Perla today so in the last video I
swatch for you guys to shade peach phase
which if you actually look at the two
labels on the boxes the colors if it'll
focus look pretty relatively similar and
I did use peach phase but apparently
that is actually a darker shade than
Perla which is why I was giving that
dark reflect which I was worried about
so for today we're growing the shade
pearl and hopefully that'll be light
enough for my skin tone oh my god you're
kidding this is gonna be so good I can
already tell
so you can definitely apply a lot of it
in one area if you want to super
pigmented highlight and you also see
that you can apply a little bit of it
and really blend it out to get a more
subtle glow and it definitely like looks
beautiful either way guys sister
Trevor's here comes my sister sister
ain't that mr. mister on the radio so
you know you're gonna look good thanks
alright I'm also gonna got my Anasazi at
number 8 14 brush and dab a little tiny
bit of this to highlight my nose oh my
god
literary satellites from space are
crashing as we speak this note are you
kidding me this is so beautiful
and I'm also gonna play a little bit
this on my brow bone as always I've been
loving highlighting up here recently for
that summer natural dewy glow and oh my
god this highlighter is literally GG
gorged it is everything so the anasazi
liquid highlighters are definitely a win
from me as you can see on my face right
now they look so beyond sunny I am so
shocked and these are definitely a new
step to my regular makeup routine so
Hollywood can move over I mean this
sister would definitely still be here
but this is definitely a new contender
for sure and I definitely try these out
in my everyday makeup routine as well
but when I do like a more dewy no powder
looks I will definitely let you guys
know how it works on there - especially
unlike the body and the collarbones oh
my god I'm just picturing how frickin
stunning that would look alright so now
that this look is all complete the last
step is going to be the lips of course
and for today I'm using the ofra liquid
lipstick in the shade so Paulo this is
not a first impressions obviously I love
Oprah and you guys know you can use
coach azar 30% off all oprah products
they are so bomb i actually did not
receive any new lip products in any PR
packages recently so yeah and then of
course to finish off this look we're
going to use our Urban Decay all nighter
setting spray to lock our face in place
all night long
alright guys and that is this burnt
orange with a pop of a chartreuse liner
cut crease all complete damn that was a
mouth ball I really hope you guys
enjoyed this video with me going over
all these new products and first
impressions and honestly I think every
single one of them that I tried today is
a major major win definitely leave a
comment down below and tell me out of
all the new products I tried out today
what was your fave to hear at your
sisters feedback if
enjoy today's video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
subscribe if you haven't already I post
three videos a week on Mondays
Wednesdays and Fridays and I'd love to
have you join the sisterhood if you'd
like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both just James Charles
and my snapchat for more behind the
scenes life stuff is James Charles that
extra asked after Charles this week
shadow goes to sister Becca thank you so
much girl for always falling good
supporting you know you mean so much to
me if you would like to be at next video
sister shout out don't forget to always
bring my video links and they go live on
Twitter all right sisters thank you so
much for watching and I will see you in
the next one
[Music]