hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so as
you guys know I did recently switch over
to doing three videos a week which is
such a fun challenge for me it is truly
so much more work than I was
anticipating but I'm absolutely loving
making all these videos for you guys and
I really hope you are enjoying them as
well speaking of making a lot of videos
for the past week videos they've all
been a super super makeup and glam
oriented I mean I even jumped in a
freaking pool with the full face of
makeup on to show you guys that
waterproof makeup is possible definitely
check that video out if you have not
already but for today's video I wanted
to just sit down throw on some likely
I'm adjusting a little bit more personal
with you guys a few videos ago I did a
more personal Q&A where I insert a lot
of questions that you guys wanted to
know about being an influencer or being
a beauty guru and just kind of questions
in general that nobody really really
likes to answer or give the honest truth
to I don't actually think I answer any
other questions in the actual video
oopsies
but I know I did get a ton of questions
about PR packages getting free makeup
for brands what that entails is that
sponsored yada yada yada so for today's
video I thought I would unbox a bunch of
PR package that I've been saving for the
last few weeks it's been like three
weeks since I've actually unboxed any
new products I've been dying to get my
hands on these and do some swatches so
without further ado let's show you guys
some of the free makeup that I get on a
daily basis
[Music]
the first Tiger to open is for my babes
over at Benefit Cosmetics and I'm so
frickin excited to open this because I
just love benefits so much and they're
PR packages are literally always so
adorable if you guys follow me on SAP
I've done a few unboxings over there and
they're always so well thought out and
put together they have by far one of the
strongest PR teams of any brand I know
so definitely a major left to benefit
and you didn't hear this from me but you
may want to keep your eyes peeled for
something with James and benefit coming
through so in the box comes a little
curl that says sister James enjoy the
new goodies xoxo a sister Stephanie and
any year we have a [ __ ] official makeup
so I guess this might be their new
Porefessional line I think there are
three of them and they come in one two
and three if you can see that on the top
I guess one three two in this case but
these are the pore fessional pore
minimizing makeup and I guess this is a
3-step system so the back it says makeup
to minimize the appearance of pores you
all know sister James could definitely
use some help in that area and it says
covers imperfections without calling in
pores and that is step one step two
smooth and reduces the look of pore
and step three instantly modifies and
controls access service for eight hours
okay that's a big claim I'm so confused
Oh press Oh okay so number three is
obviously a liquid I have no idea what
numbers 1 & 2 are but I definitely want
to find out because like I said it's
sister James definite need some help in
the pour department that is for sure so
if you guys want to see me try these out
soon definitely let me know all right so
our next talk is just from sister Lilly
ghalichi over at Lilly lashes I'm so
excited for this hopefully there are
some Miami's in here because my sister
is running a real low okay we have a
little card that says James on it and
then oh they're all Miami's oh my god
that is really what I needed the card
says hi my gorgeous sister James these
brands are really not on top we wanted
to top you off with some of your
favorite letters and of course it's a
Miami steak lamb XXL Lilly and the lily
lashes team true sisters thank you so
much to the Lilly lashes team I was
definitely running low and Miami's and
Lord knows at this point I am probably
gonna be buried wearing a pair of these
so definitely needed to restock all so I
reached out to Lily because I wear these
lashes all the time as you guys know and
I get so many questions every time I
wear them as well so the other Lee
lashes in the style mink Miami and as
well you can now use Cochise for 10% off
your purchase of all lashes it lately
lashes so definitely check these out
they're by far my favorite pair already
since this next package is definitely a
pretty pretty big one and this one is
from toe
so inside comes this beautiful box which
my dumb ass accidentally just ripped but
it was beautiful about 30 seconds ago
all right so this is actually my first
ever PR package from Tasha you guys know
I'd like to be very very unbiased when
it comes to this stuff but I will say I
am very very very excited to open this
I've heard that their skin care stuff is
so good and you guys know that I don't
really do skincare and I definitely been
wanting to start it so this is a perfect
excuse to do so and let's open this up
and it comes as Cardon it says oh my
gosh sisters
I love that all these brands know me so
well that says oh my gosh sister's brand
new face drops for our fave rise and
glow James Charles oh my god
also in the Box comes this really really
beautiful container which looks like it
is a mask yes it is the violet sea or
radiance mask and by the name of us
doing it as a brightening mask for sure
this looks so good I'm gonna open up
because I wonder if it's actually a
violet oh it is oh wow that is so pretty
definitely we try this out
very very student thank you so much
hotcha for the package and yoli glow you
better hit me up soon sister all right
so this next package is once again a
pretty pretty big one and it's also very
very heavy too I don't recognize the
name on this box so I have no idea what
this is or how they got my address in
the first place let's go ahead and open
this up what is this the first thing I
see is this pamphlet that has a
marijuana leaf on it and now I'm
horrified is this literally a PR package
of drugs telling this doesn't look like
the most illegal medicine that has ever
been sent in the mail are you kidding
this has CBD syrup all natural hemp wait
a second you guys know sister James does
not do drugs or drink I'm a good boy but
if I'm remembering correctly from last
year's science class I'm pretty sure
that hemp is like in weed is this
literally a package of marijuana okay at
this point I am convinced and also
horrified that I may have just received
a package of illegal substances to my
apartment so I'm going to read this
pamphlet now all the way through and see
what the tea is because this is not what
I want
this cloud9 syrup is the number one
selling hemp ocf infused with pure hemp
CBD and nine all-natural herbs
it's legal and okay that's what I needed
to hear it's legal and safe to use with
positive health benefits that support
increase in happiness temporary relief
as well as many ailments extreme
relaxation as well as amazing flavors
that you mix with your favorite drinks
that you'll love our kid of an idol that
sounds like cannabis we're back to the
weed thing okay so what I'm gathering
here is that these substances are legal
which is wonderful that means I won't be
doing my makeup from the jail cell thank
God I'm still not exactly hundred
percent sure what these actually are I'm
just gonna go ahead and put this box
away you guys think whatever services
you want in your body but Swisher James
gonna stay clean all right so this next
package is from our sisters over Anasazi
at Beverly Hills and I think I know what
this is and I'm so excited to open this
up all right so this is the box that
comes inside of the box and their
packaging is always so beautiful so
sleek and just super super modern and
simplistic and I love that yes oh my god
it is what I thought and is they're
brand new
Anasazi liquid glow illuminators I am so
excited for these so it looks like these
liquid glow illuminators come in four
different shades being called Perla
oyster bronze and peach phase and I have
been waiting for these for so long
following the Anasazi snaps an Instagram
page they looked a little reso Bob on
all the promo pictures and you guys know
that their illuminator in so Hollywood
is by far my favorite highlighter ever
I'm wearing it today as always so honest
all day it definitely does not play
right when it comes to that glow let's
go ahead and test one of these out
looking at the little color things on
the top it's looking like peach face
would probably be the best match for a
James Charles skin tone highlight so
let's pop her out of the box oh my god
this is actually huge too for a liquid
highlighter it's 0.628 fluid ounces
which is literally almost the same size
as most foundations that's really crazy
I'm gonna squeeze a little bit of peach
fuzz onto like my hand oh wow oh wow you
can literally see just me moving my hand
I'm looking at the monitor right now
against the light these are so metallic
and beautiful I am
shook to the core this is like blinding
next-level highway right now the formula
feels really really nice it's definitely
like a very very creamy consistency and
not too liquidy as well which is
wonderful that means it's not going to
move around on the face I mean I love a
good highlighter but we're not trying to
do the full face of Highlander challenge
every day so I definitely am a little
bit concerned though being that this is
one of the lighter shades of the
collection and as you can see when the
light isn't hitting it it definitely
leaves a pretty pretty dark reflection
so I'm very curious to see how that'll
actually look on my skin I will
definitely try those out very very soon
so let me know if you guys want to see a
video with those alright so last but
certainly not least we have this package
from our sisters over at makeup forever
and just like with benefit makeup
forever it is one of those companies
that truly does have such an amazing PR
team they really do care about their
customers and their influencers which is
so amazing and is like the best quality
a brand can have but all personal bias
aside let's get to the makeup oh my god
if this is what I think it is this is
something very very very special so
there's a little card inside that says
we asked six of our friends to make the
perfect artist face color palette so
here's how they made their show us how
you make yours probably makeup forever
oh my god so not only do we have sister
Kim who created her little trio but we
also have sister Cassie so if I'm
reading this correctly all six
influences created a trio of a bronzer a
blush and a high
and Cassie says I love about the
versatility of my artists face color
trio palette can be applied with a
subtle touch for a super soft flame or
kicked up a notch for a little more
intensity love that all three shades
conveniently fit in a small compact
pallet perfect for a vanity fave or
chucked in a small makeup bag for
on-the-go I'm obsessed with H 102 highly
asked one one six sculpt and beep 208
blush and I hope you love them just as
much as I do
major hard core cheesy moment right here
by him soul beyond pronto sister Cassie
she's by far one of the most talented
makeup artists that I know if you guys
don't already follow her you need to go
check her out and I cannot believe I'm
looking at her beautiful face on this PR
package and just let you know I may or
might not have taken this photo so the
package came with the nine different
products being three highlighters three
contours and three blushes and these are
the three that sister Cassie paired
together but I'm not actually gonna open
them up because I definitely do want to
use them soon but these colors are
beautiful and I cannot wait to put them
on my face all right sisters so that has
all the PR packages we have to open
today I really really hope you enjoyed
this little unboxing video we saw all
sorts of funky products from
pore-minimizing makeup face masks drugs
and even makeup for more my best friends
in the entire world so this was so much
fun to open up and see all these new
products if you guys get into this video
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below it really helps me
out and as well if you would like to see
me actually use all these products and
test them out do some live swatches on
the face definitely give this video a
thumbs up and if we get it to 50,000 I
will do that for a Monday's video if you
haven't already also make sure to hit
that red subscribe button and the
notification about next to it so you can
notify when I upload I post three videos
a week on Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays
and I'd love to have you join the
sisterhood
this week shout it goes to sister chase
thank you so much boo for always bawling
and supporting you and know I love you
so much and if you would like to be it
next week sister shadow make sure to
follow me on Twitter and ways for you to
my video links when they go live all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching have a wonderful weekend and I
will see you on Monday bye
[Music]