hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you can see so they have a very very
special guest today this is Hannah a
living legend and she's actually the
winner of my fan I hate the word fan my
sister makeover giveaway she's here we
have our paint rings and we were ready
to get clam today I am so excited that
you are here you came all the way from
where Pennsylvania in the middle of
nowhere huh I'm so excited we are here
in California together we are at my
friends warehouse where we filming it
this makeup transformation and then also
a little wardrobe transformation as well
this is gonna be a full day a full glam
makeover and I am so beyond excited how
are you feeling I know I texted her
earlier today and I was like what kind
of look do you want and you basically
just told me really really light
beautiful glam huh that's the third
makeup usually like tell me about like
your normal everyday makeup routine blow
though a very extra but at the same time
not too much yes love that oh my god I
seen her in certain like you're always
rocking like that fierce winged liner
like your brows with your foundation so
buy a beautiful sky thank you seriously
unfortunately but we're gonna like you
look so freaking bomb tonight it's so
pumped so let's simplify it having your
face you think the benefit Porefessional
primer my relation like a thousand maybe
whoa yeah that's so crazy
that's the big city around where we
lived my time growing up was like very
very small but I still had like the
smallest consider 30,000 people
oh so for foundation obviously a reason
the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD foundation
stick not on the shade why 315 today
because anna is a pale beauty she's
coming for slim again so I have a for
chasing me I have y 2o 5 to 15 at 225
and 245 ever test them and see which one
matches the best which is 225 and the
Make Up For Ever Ultra HD foundation
stick so you can use this one all over
your face
what's on there really I love that
you're like so not afraid to like rock
luckily I'm full of freaking coverage
love I think there are so many people
especially nowadays that are like I
can't believe never serious on that one
well especially like in like
Pennsylvania if you're wearing a lot of
makeup that immediately makes you like
like if you went to school like that and
everything yeah you'd get called so many
names because that's just not normal in
C when I was actually in high school I
think I only wore makeup to school twice
I I mean either I never cared that yeah
oh I was I literally didn't wear because
I was too lazy to yeah like when you
don't have any hair it's not like I can
do my hair up all night oh my god
speaking of it looks like on the
original video because obviously so
inspire them um I wrote I suffer from a
location just lost all my hair to the
condition I cried for hours because I
felt like my long hair to find my beauty
I felt embarrassed to leave the house
without a wig makeup helps me walk out
the door every day and still feel like a
queen without my hair it is a huge
stress relief doing my makeup in the
morning and feeling confident enough to
go out with my friends and be myself I
honestly would be hiding in my house if
it weren't for makeup and amazing people
like you to make me feel beautiful I
love you James oh yeah I love that
confidence because like most people like
obviously that gets a very very heart
disease for a lot of people to do and
like truly does show like certain like
body parts or accessories like aren't
needed or that's what we're to put it
but certain things are needed for video
yeah that's like staring septic you
don't need long flowy curly locks to be
beautiful like you don't need like a
beef AC beautiful either like I love it
you're oh that's just in terms me so
much I'm so so freakin happy that you're
here when if you don't be asking when
were you diagnosed
alopecia is like yeah tell me about it
cuz I love it I'm just to be honest I
really I'm not familiar with it I never
really went to get diagnosed per se
because I was kind of like
Barriss at the time especially when I
first got it but I mean especially I
mean I've been told by my just family
doctor there's nothing else that it
could be right so I mean obviously
that's what it is but um alopecia areata
is the type that I have which is just
the way that it falls out is the second
part areata means it falls out in
circles or out your head okay about five
months ago now that is I was was when
the first patch fell out so this was
recent though yeah okay and about three
months after that I decided to
completely shave my head for the first
time
lava yeah because I most of my hair had
already fallen out and I believe that
there was just no point in keeping it
for the rest of it because I mean I
thought I looked more like a goofball
with like just three patches of hair and
no hair at all no I rather just had no
hair at all yeah I was looking your
entry of the pictures when you were like
fully ball we're so funny I feel like it
was just so cool it almost like we were
talking about drag earlier how like me I
reminded very much like I'm gyre like
something yeah yeah just like and like
soft so that just like you know looking
you know hair oh my god I felt that are
just like it was so cool and it's so
confident you like just a young girl
like rocking blue know you don't hear at
all that's so awesome
oh my god her bronzer today I brought my
benefit hoola lights antenna is more
fair skin I don't want to use regular
glue because if I make you look really
really orange so they just released
their do a light version which I
actually have been loving I used it on
myself cast a for the first time woman
back in the day I feel like contouring
like wasn't a thing like I was
definitely like I started doing makeup
right when all this started coming out
that like you can set your face with
setting spray because like a new
freaking revelation there's so many like
makeup advances and trends if I don't
know where it all came at the exact same
time yeah well like I even remember it
like there is no such thing as primer
when eyes are doing makeup Oh
like I remember starting in like they're
only being like professionals around
even back you know and like I think 2015
I want to say don't call me the Smashbox
ones and I was like the only popular one
I was like every brand it's definitely
true when you see the look on Instagram
got everybody we had to go through the
uh the ugly stages and now all these
kids are not going to do this it's not
fair at least everybody's gift that I'm
doubly friends while like musically kids
mm-hmm and they're all like 12 and
they're all yeah
like top models look you ready to walk a
runway like what is in your baby formula
I like they all are so beautiful and
southern I'm like like this really so I
heard you got a very interesting a prom
alpha oh yes tell about oh I wore a
Cinderella dress and a giant bedazzled
headband love with my completely shaved
down bald head Wow well insert picture
right kind of everything can't relate
unfortunately I took that my best
friends the province she was the girl I
love
okay so now you have a braver like
distinct brown style look I'm looking at
your like they always look very good and
like they never change
thank you which like makes me nervous oh
[Laughter]
okay so I used to shave my eyebrows off
completely for like two years
Geoffrey start is shaking hello
oh my god okay yeah yeah I'll let her
know he's doing just fine
oh poor hands I said I'm using the brand
new Urban Decay Naked heat i palette
this is enough what I have on my eyes
right now I use this for the person
that's wearing and I'm loving how my
look turned out so we're gonna give him
a very similar look she asked for a
light glam
just like very very pretty but not too
much which love easy peasy I first met
my morphe m57 3 much used to go ginger
10% off and dip into this unit saw
straight up in here just for a light
transition
so I don't say that you're not walking
nails huh no but usually you have like
claws on normally I get as long as they
possibly can make them we just have like
the little salons that like in Walmart
that will dip your nails oh no
yeah it's we're gonna take you to a good
I'll be good I'll be good
so I'm next to the road my Murphy I'm
one five one brush and dip into the
shade and wiggle and ashes and mix them
together this Mela is honestly it's so
stunning I saw a lot of mixed reviews on
it I personally really really loved it
and I love this total blotting brush as
well I feel like it's just so good to do
like little detail work but still
blending at the same time one of my
faves I'm gonna go into this steel up
magnificent Mel's in the shade kin Karma
these things are so pretty and you're
just a why'd you just tell me and like
we only have one Sephora near me and
it's like two hours away and I went in
to get these and at like we went in like
three different times to go get these
and they were also about every single
time and for one final of glitter and
the Department of the urban decay at
Midnight Cowboy liner and just layer
over top of the Stila thing that's at
the Opera shadows all done were going to
give Hannah a twin letter because she's
always rocking a fierce a swing so I was
gonna try to recreate this the best I
can today and do her some justice I'm so
reason the acav on D at tattoo ink liner
a letter come on be sister is literally
drying out as I did their wing I've had
this one for a long time now so I my
tried and true it's time to buy a
restock anyway I find I'm gonna need her
to last for one more I got this side so
girl let's pray she pulls through okay
let's do this lower lash now I just have
to lower lash then I'm gonna go back in
with sauce on my 233 brush and just give
it a light wash the color on Hanah lower
lashline then just a find the outer
lower corner I'm gonna use my morphe r43
brush and dip into n Fuego and ashes
similar to the upper lash line and just
define it just the outer edge I'm just
gonna press this into Hannah's lash line
to make her lower lashes look really
really smoked up and defined Hannah
already has huge beautiful eye so when
my look I put on a white liner on the
waterline for Hannah's I'm actually
gonna leave her water light blank now
the Hannah shadows all complete I'm
gonna go ahead and do some lashes and of
course when were using the Lily lashes
in the South Miami these are my all-time
faves and I were in there right now so I
want to make her how long has it been
since you were called suju's you just
wear like mascara curl them yeah
no I don't curl them either my girl so
you dis referred to destiny don't like a
new song right did you like just here
recently like how we should have
something like did you just hear justice
if you're like yeah and that's just
getting on the radio how much how old is
that we've had it for like a good like
it's like it's like it already like how
does like peak time and I was like kind
of fading out that's hilarious because I
just heard it for the first time on the
way here in Italy the song was spreading
ad Esposito so that is one eye all
completely uncertain out we're gonna go
ahead and do the other one off-camera
just save some time that'll we'll be
right back to finish off the rest of the
video now that we have you both of
Hannah's eyes all done and snatch for
the gods we're now gonna go in with the
highlighter and tannerite using the
Oprah Beverly Hills illuminator and my
morphe M 501 brush I'm just going to top
into this light champagne shade up in
here and a little bit of the white as
well just because Canada is later skin
so you wanna make sure it's not too dark
girls will get that gray cast which is
the worst thing in the world
so you're saying earlier like you are
known for your like
good glow huh oh yes I love a good
yellow toned blinding Himes like yes
what are like your favorite highlighters
the eyeliner have been obsessed with I
don't even know the name of it I bought
it in Ireland when I went there on
vacation a while ago and it like doesn't
even have a company name on it or
anything
but I'm obsessed with it I don't even
care so our next up is going to be the
lipid e du das to finish off this look
and I'm gonna first start off by
lighting that using the ILS not any
colour-pop collection I freaking love
this lip pencil is all my all-time
favorite shades
and then in the center and over top
arena layer the colour-pop ultra satin
lip in the shade likey like likely just
kidding
all right so now the Hana things are
beautiful and done we have to set her in
place using our Urban Decay all nighter
setting spray of course since Hannah's
from Pennsylvania she is definitely not
used to this crazy California heat and
humidity we need here to not melt off
today because we have a lot more fun
stuff to do so without further ado let's
replace all right guys and this is the
finished look over on sister Hannah
honey
oh wait we need to give you a me oh you
may be the get ready for that's ready
for the grand reveal bronze to the gods
today oh my god
now that you have to makeup on we have a
few more fun things to do with it since
our hands today so she looks slim make
sure you thumbs up this video if you
like her makeup but let's go ahead and
get moving and we will be you guys in a
few seconds alright guys we have a
sister Hannah here in a very very
special location and we are at so we'll
see you guys know what this summer here
is my best one in the entire world but
some of you may not know is that she's
also the proud owner of three Dementors
boutique locations and we're currently
at I'll be one in a winner California
she figured since were already giving
him an amazing makeup makeover we should
also get four she already looks adorable
there's no issues show us the glam so
far and this later
so obviously had a party looks amazing
but we figured why not give her clothing
makeover as well just a full-on
then makeover so we were lb-1 and we're
gonna do some shopping hands gonna pick
up some new clothes and show you guys
how to strut are you ready she's like
she was born right
[Music]
alright guys so we were back and has
been several hours I'm getting a little
bit crusty or done with this - at least
sister Hannah still looks beautiful
baths the focus of this video and she's
who matters today so much fun with you I
am so glad you got to come I just like
I'm just so inspired about you and your
journey and how far you've Kaitlyn right
well thank you for sharing like
everything with me and you guys didn't
do this amazing video today with sister
Hannah please don't forget to give it a
Bega thumbs up down below and subscribe
if you have not already I post two
videos we got Mondays and Fridays that
I'd love to have you join the sisterhood
I would also love to do more of these
fan hate that word' like I said a
million times the makeover sister
makeovers later on in the future of my
channel maybe this could become a
serious I love meeting all because as
I've always said
and it's weaseling that I would do all
the time and I hope had an amazing
experience and I'd love to do this but
more of you guys so definitely give me a
thumbs up on this video if you want me
to do that because so sure James will
consider it if you haven't already make
sure to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow me on Instagram and
Twitter they're both just James Charles
and my snapchat for more
behind-the-scenes life stuff is Jane of
Charles and the texture ask after
Charles if you'd like to follow sister
Hannah and watch her makeup turning her
journey through her beautiful amazing
life where can they find you at
everything is yes go get her follow tell
her sister James sent you guys also this
week sisters shadow goes to Sebastian
thank you so much your voice following
and supporting you know I love you boo
if you guys don't already make sure you
retweet my video links will they go live
so you can be next week sister shout out
alright guys that is all we have for
this video today I really really hope
you enjoyed watching this I truly had an
amazing and iconic day filming this that
I hope sister handed to it was truly
such an amazing time like I said I
really hope you guys enjoyed watching
and I will see you in the next one bye
[Music]