hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
cutting right to the point for today's
video I wanted to sit down and just do
some type of glam look I feel like for
the past several several videos I've
been wearing a super super light glam I
mean it has honestly been a week since I
put on eye shadow which is absolutely
horrifying considering my job is
literally a makeup artist I put together
this winged out bronzy half cut crease I
look that I absolutely am in love with
and then I added these gold little star
freckles which you will see later on in
the video which is such a cute little
touch that I am so in love with and then
I just paired it with this nude lip and
this is the look that I came up with I'm
getting like very very summery festival
vibes
I know summer is like basically over
with and that means back-to-school
season is coming whoo check out last
week's video after needed tutorial on it
but I figured I would do this little
festival kind of inspired look just to
bring us back to the good old days all
that being said if you guys would like
to see how I created this look make sure
you keep on watching so to start off I
already went ahead and I primed my face
using my moisturizer and then I'm gonna
go in with my Make Up For Ever Ultra HD
stick in the shade of y 365 for a base
it's actually been so long since I've
done a full coverage glam I feel like
I've only been doing a light building
natural glam for a very long time now so
I'm super excited to actually be doing a
real look today and this is gonna be a
super super fun one as well I'm also
gonna grab a little bit of Too Faced
spores and Sohee foundation in the shade
and natural beige and just put a little
bit on the back of my hand and I'm going
to dip into my Beauty Blender and kind
of use this foundation to blend out the
make up front row Ultra HD stick these
are both my favorite foundations for
very different reasons so I'm gonna get
the best of both worlds today oh my god
I can't believe actually never tried
mixing these two foundations together I
guess I've never really thought about it
because the makeup everyone is a stick
and then the two based one is a liquid
but my skin looks so good right now oh
my god chicken seal today I'm gonna grab
my ATAR shape tube concealer in the
shade light/medium honey and just
highlight the high points of my face
I don't know if it's all that studio
light that we added but I think if my
eyes are not deceiving me that we were
having a super super good skin day today
which makes me so happy thank you for
once in my life to lock our face in
place that are gonna be using of course
the laura mercier translucent setting
powder during the summer time I really
like only setting up my nose area and
then under my eyes because those are the
two areas that definitely wear out the
fastest and get the most creases so I
really just like setting hair to lock
the face but then as for the rest my
face
I literally just add the lightest layer
a powder possible if even powdering at
all because I really like the summer and
dewy foundation look as you guys know I
feel like it just looks so beautiful and
so natural and I am going to a party
slash event tonight that I'm literally
so excited for it is the desi and Katy
dose of colors launched I am so proud of
them and so skater to try the products
but I definitely need this foundation
and makeup look to last a very very long
time because it is early in the morning
today and I have to wear this at like 7
p.m. tonight so definitely want to keep
this in place
I don't think want this look to be super
super golden and bronzy today so of
course we have to pack on the bronzer
and for this I'm gonna use my benefit
hoola bronzer as always as I Murphy M
for a fire brush and you guys know you
can use code J's for 10% off all morphe
brushes since I didn't pack on the
setting powder today I'm being very very
light when I'm applying this bronzer
because if I dig it into my face too
hard it's definitely gonna lead the
powder looking super super patchy and I
definitely want it to cling on to the
still kind of wet foundation so I'm just
being super super light and letting that
color get on there naturally
alright so listen to you guys I
literally just did exactly what I said
not to do and I was bronzing to hard
enough you can see right here on camera
my foundation is coming up a little bit
and starting to separate so I'm just
gonna lightly go over that with some
more studying powder just make sure that
area is really really locked in place
because I don't my foundation to wear oh
next thing to grab my Kat Von D shade in
late huh and my Anasazi a 22 brush and
we dip into this light yellow shade
right up in here I just used that a
little bit to reinforce the highlights
on my face it's good to reinforce those
highlights that we originally put on
with the concealer just because after
bronzer and contour that brightness can
sometimes get lost amongst the blending
and everything so it's always good to
reinforce and make sure we are snatched
and fully chiseled I'm going to grab my
Luxy 180 nose contouring brush and dip
into it the middle shade and the left
shade of the shade of my palette and
then lightly
my nose I'm gonna grab a little bit more
Laura Mercier powder and just lightly
baked besides my nose just to make sure
it's really really locked in a place I
guess might as well go really full-time
bake the rest night phase to it has
definitely been a hot minute why not I
just went ahead and did my eyebrows
off-camera you guys to be doing them
literally a million times so I figured
might as well just skip out on it today
as well I kind of want to cry right now
because I literally just hid my entire
eye on camera and explained everything
only just realized I wasn't actually
recording so normally my videos don't go
in this order normally I do one on
camera then off I guess what is already
done so now we're gonna do the other one
on camera again but this time we better
be recording I'm gonna start off with my
um 4-3-3 brush and dipping into the
joseline help palette I'm gonna grab
this kind of mac and cheese type shade
and it's gonna put that all up in the
crease I'm literally so annoyed right
now because doing eye looks on camera
and having to explain everything
literally takes me forever but I can
literally recreate the same eye look off
camera and like ten minutes no matter
what I look it is so I know I'm gonna be
late to my event now and this is not
what I wanted to happen I'm not swearing
another M 4 3 3 brush and I'm gonna dip
into this orange shade right up in here
and put that in the crease once again to
deepen it up when I get to this outer
corner I'm going to wing out the shadow
quite a bit because we want that like
blended out festival type makeup look
next I'm going to dip into this warm Tom
Brown shape it up in here and start to
deepen out the outer corner and blend
that up a little bit into the crease
then with my m56 - I'm just gonna blend
out those edges
using my M 509 brush I'm just gonna grab
the slightest bit of the black shape on
the bottom corner and just eeping out
the very very very outer V I'm gonna be
super super careful with this color
because adding too much block can really
ruin this look very very very quickly
and this black in this palette is super
super pigmented as well so I'm just
going to add a light amount and then
blend it out like I said I'm being super
super careful and letting this out I
definitely am NOT going for a block
smokey eye look today maybe that's next
video but for now I just want to deepen
up that outer corner so adding block is
really really risky but can definitely
look great if you do it right I'm gonna
add some little on top of the lid but at
the base I'm gonna go to the my morphe
35o palette and my makeup shock t6 brush
and I'm gonna dip into this orange shade
in the bottom right corner and just use
this to carve out the crease
oh the shadow is literally so pretty oh
my god one slash taught us on there I'm
just gonna grab a clean a blending brush
and go right over those edges to make
sure everything is really really
diffused and blended out except for the
crease obviously but that's kind of the
whole point to add a little bit of
glitter and more pop to this eye look
I'm gonna grab these steal at liquid
glitters stuff and rose gold retro you
guys know these are so bomb I'm gonna
lightly Pat this over top of that shadow
oh yeah wow that is over looking for
that looks so pretty for the lower lash
that I'm gonna go in with my M 4-3-3 and
dip into that burnt orange shade at once
again and just put a little bit of it
down right after I destroy this glitter
fallout oh my I'm definitely gonna hug
the shadow very very close to the lash
line when I get to this outer corner I'm
also gonna blend it up into this dark
out our wing portion it being a very
very careful to not really take it on
into this area just think I kind of just
did because that's when things start
getting really really muddy like right
here but no worries we're gonna fix it
next intagram I am 509 brush and dip
into the soft brown shade right here and
define at the very very upper lash line
lower lash line then if I am 149 and a
little bit of burnt orange and just come
up on that out because once again we
definitely don't want a black smoky eye
one check that I love to do is driving
my Beauty Blender and a little bit more
of that translucent powder that I use it
doesn't matter which one and I'm just
going to put a little bit of powder
right underneath that shadow to kind of
bake it and lighten it back up to skin
tone and this will actually really do a
good job of cleaning everything up and
then finally I'm gonna grab my NYX
wonder pencil in the lightest shade and
use this to a line at my waterline
census look at super super intense and
dark on those outer corners I definitely
wanna use a lighter color in the
waterline to open my eyes back up we're
all still gonna look super super small
and tiny for mascara today I'm gonna do
a light coat of benefit roller lash two
bears no this is my all-time favorite
lashes so got a pop of my house lashes
iconic light it has been so long since
I've used these lashes and I'm honestly
so excited I'm getting like so much
nostalgia I think everything using Lily
lashes miami's for the past like sixty
four years straight so it's time for a
little bit of a sweat job
for that classic golden glow of course
you guys know we're gonna be using the
Anasazi Oh sell Hollywood illuminator I
use this all the time like literally in
every single video but it truly is so
good and it works really perfectly for
my skin tone as well I find that
oftentimes a lot of highlighters can
leave a gray cast on my skin because I
do have a pretty light skin or it'll
just look really walking in general so
definitely would recommend it so
Hollywood of course gonna put this on my
brow bone as well you guys know the
drill by now I'm also gonna highlight my
nose easy way I'm a 4:3 one brush all
right so that is the glow all complete
and before we actually move on to the
lips
I do introducing a little bit fun for
this look if you guys follow me on
snapchat you know that this whole are
you doing my setup process has been
quite the process yes a few weeks ago
mr. Kay came over and actually helped me
rearrange its entire Beauty room and now
I've actually rearranged again but
regardless they've always been one of my
favorite channels I love their videos so
freakin much and they have been a major
source of inspiration for all my
apartment decorating stuff and when
Caine was over she did give me her
little mr. Kay a beauty mark stickers
and I didn't test these out earlier on
but I'm gonna be putting these like
little gold stars up in here on my Halle
area because why not
I'm just gonna take my little pair of
eyelash tweezers and I'm going to cut
out my stars I just remove the plastic
throw from the top as well and then I'm
just going to place it on my skin where
I want it and I think we're gonna put
this right over here on my highlight
region and then I'm just gonna hold it
in place and I have a damp towel here
and I'm just going to press this right
into the skin I tested this out earlier
as well before I actually did this whole
look to make sure that this one mess up
my entire face the foundation and it did
not it looked super super great so I am
not worried I am just being really
really careful because obviously we
don't want our entire face to get wet
just the part that has the little
sticker on it as we learned in my video
from a few weeks ago most makeup is
definitely waterproof this is literally
exactly like all the temporary tattoos
that we all did we were like 8 years old
but just a whole lot prettier
alright and once it's been on for 30
seconds I'm just going to give it a good
little pat and then oh yes I love all
these gold records without they're loose
frickin cute if you guys want to check
out mr. Kate please I'll leave her stuff
down below her channel is so amazing and
so is her shop as well and by the way
speaking of it down below
from now on all products that I use in
all my tutorials will be listed in the
description so if you see something that
I'm using or you want to shop anything
that I'm using always check down below
first obviously the eyes on the face are
very very bold so for the lips today I
definitely wanna keep a light nude so
I'm first gonna start off by lighting my
lips using the Mac lip pencil in the
shade whirl alright and last but finally
not least I'm gonna set my face in place
using my morphe crepin set setting spray
all right scissors and that is this a
bronzy gold festival style makeup look I
don't know what the hell to call this
I'll complete I really really love how
this turned out especially the gold
freckles today's video is absolutely
chaos by it turned out pretty in the end
and I guess that's all that matters
you guys like this look and enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below ever
you have not ready I post three videos a
week on Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays
and I'd love to have you join the
sisterhood if you'd like to follow me on
a makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for mobile
haven't seen myself is James Charles the
next your ass after Charles this week's
shout-out goes to his sister Haneen
thank you so much girl for always
following and supporting you know I love
you so much
and if you would like to be at next
week's sister shout out make sure to
always reach me my video links and they
go live on Twitter sisters thank you so
much for watching this video I love you
so much and I will see you in the next
one bye
[Music]