hi sisters skip here and welcome back to
James Charles YouTube channel for those
of you who don't know I'm James's dad
last night James Charles brought us into
his world with the tick-tock dances
[Music]
today I'm going to take James into my
world I'm a general contractor my day
involves everything from framing taping
painting bathroom surveys here anything
and everything I'm used to getting dirty
from the time I get on site to the time
I leave we're gonna see how James
Charles handles the situation we're
gonna work on a little project we're
gonna demo a bathroom some things never
change so as usual we're waiting on
James James come on bud God go to work
that's what you're gonna wear to work
today
yeah you said boots work boots well I
don't know what's wrong with these
you're gonna break your ankle I'll get
you a pair of boots to wear okay I'm
ready to know you were gonna wear this
this is what you're gonna wear be us
okay this is a working a workman's
jumpsuit okay let's go get your boots
changed and we got to get out of here
we're running late of course we are
don't be later bye
[Music]
okay god I want to ask you a few
questions about your job so the viewers
at home know about like how I grew up
with you and I was like what their job
entails so you are a contractor and
you're self-employed business and how
like to be a hard worker why do you work
for yourself why do you think I like
trickle down to people I like working
for myself because it you're gonna work
that hard and as as much as I do it's
far more beneficial for me
do you think because
that way and they cut yourself and
played still do you think that had a lot
to do with why you and mom or so lenient
let me do what I do was frightening to
be honest with you my mom and dad really
had no idea as to what when you were
doing it and more importantly how you
could actually turn it into a job but
you were always a hard worker but there
are always multi tasking you always say
all right you to do it little cribs
hopefully going to take this up I'm
thinking like MTV Cribs tour hey yo MTV
and I'm gonna give you a nice space so
where does the bathroom are gonna be
demolish a as you can see low few leaks
so good thing I have a good they have a
hard time as I was just saying yes a
nice popcorn feature on the ceiling that
we may or not be removing eventually
some blue walls all throughout so we
have a vanity sink a navy blue cab what
do you call them the bottom portion of
the bottom version of the sink has some
nice navy blue cabinets we have a mirror
and then this light that looks like it's
from 1854 on the mirror so we're going
to get rid of that over here we have a
shower as well that's about their tour
this is what it's like now so get ready
to see it not look like this
first thing you had to do is turn off
the water use a valve back there it goes
yeah yeah yeah righty-tighty now you
want to pick up the seat flush the
toilet this comes off and any residual
water in the tank you got to drop that
old sponge in there soaked up as much
water as you can out of the tank
happy t10 what is this thing that's the
plunger you can break that just pull it
up and snap it off because it's going
out it's garbage now lift up the seat in
your hand lift up the seat oh now that
water has to come out of there and go
into the bucket don't pull over the top
of your glass it's clean water it's just
in the toilet bowl
[Music]
all right don't you dad we're gonna need
that now take this this is one or
absorbing crystals so any residual water
that's left in there it's the same same
product that is they treat the inside of
diapers pampers with an income walk-down
itself all right now we gotta take two
bulbs which are these down here we even
open up your tool pouch oh yeah I have
tools for you it should spin free now we
can pull the toilet bowl okay this piece
of cardboard because there's a wax ring
underneath and the wax ring is what
directly comes in contact with all the
human waste bodily waste okay okay
pick up multiple flanges on there that's
why I'm going to sit flat that's the
first put a lot of wax on the bottom
there's a lot of wax around there and
all of this just remove the toilet bowl
your first tour lever normally I would
just carry that down in one piece but
you're not gonna be able to do that
probably so you want to just knock it
apart yeah
[Music]
can you hand me my screw gun start at
the very top you see yeah one take those
out and we'll be able to take the door
right
[Music]
this is got to come off that side that's
clean waters that chip just pull right
off it might just be stuck to the
ceiling okay that trim plate comes on it
keeps it from shattering and pieces
falling down on top of my hands the
sheetrock want the backside of that bowl
so just to get it with this sledgehammer
at the wall the wall is coming down
[Music]
I'm gonna get a garbage bag so I can get
all this out of there put it into a
garbage bag okay okay and hold that one
tight go ahead
[Music]
come on did you just say new weeks alert
he wasn't on film it doesn't count
I mean basically we're talking to Howard
and have to cut the bottom of this and
we even ignorant obviously said well why
can't we just pull it up anything well
the drain is attached I said we should
just try like baby Yoda yeah so gotta
clean up I'm just trying to save your
ears ever stayed in that position he
looked like a birthing English Bulldog
okay glasses off oh ah all right you
guys well I think that is all we have
for today's demolition right down that's
about it but you knocked it out you did
a great job I'm very proud good saying
that no no I'm I'm impressed
was it fun having me with you
so that absolutely I enjoyed it did you
enjoy this more than the check top
dances last night
absolutely I enjoyed it this I know how
to do well thank you welcome back today
like I said I learned all my hard work
for me I'm so grateful to have you in my
life any renovations anytime soon yeah
thank you for joining me today it was a
lot of fun all right you guys so thank
you so much watching today's video and
thank you Dad hurt let me warn you I
love you and I love it you guys so much
if you enjoyed it please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
show your love and support really does
help us out so much and also make sure
you click that big red subscribe button
and come join this sisterhood I would
love to have you in the family and click
the Pelican so you get notifications
every time I upload a brand new video if
you like to follow me on my makeup
journey component it's your twitter
facebook a tip talk on to st. charles by
snapchat school Brian that seems obvious
it smells like shot after Charles and if
you want to text me at one-on-one for
any new videos new photos merch shops
and all other exclusive information my
personal phone number is three one oh
nine oh five eight seven four six don't
look for him anywhere because he is not
alive this video sister shadow goes to
sister Erin thank you so much nut for
always following it's a party Olivia so
so so much and if you'd like you the
next videos of sister shadow don't
forget to always reach me political live
on Twitter and also open to my youtube
with post on vacations all right you
guys thank you so much nice video today
I love you and we will see you in the
next one
[Music]