hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so it
is officially fall season it is the end
of November and you know what that means
it's Thanksgiving I personally love
Thanksgiving it is one of my all-time
favorite holidays I have not been home
in over six months now since my senior
graduation so I am literally so pumped
for once to hop on a plane and fly all
the way back home to regular old open in
New York and see my family I literally
missed them so so much I cannot wait to
give momma Charles and sister Ian and
daddy Charles a oh whoa
no oooh and father Charles that was
almost really really bad I'm associated
to get them all really really big hugs
the point of Thanksgiving is obviously
to spend time with your family and
friends and be thankful and of course
eat a lot of really really great food
I've been getting so many treats from
you guys telling me that you guys are
going to different family Thanksgiving
parties with a bunch of relatives that
you have not seen in so so long so for
today's look I put together this funky
little cut crease moment perfect for the
Thanksgiving feast and it's like the
smokey winged out bronzy little fall
moment we have bronze glitter on the lid
and some very very intense fluffy lashes
I just wanted to go very very extra
today so everybody at the dinner table
knows I am that [ __ ] we're really going
for the grandma Charles to be like Oh
sister you look so good why don't you
get in line for the Thanksgiving feast
first and I'll be like oh don't mind if
I do all that being said if you guys
like to see how I created this final
little Thanksgiving makeup tutorial keep
on watching
[Music]
alright guys let's go ahead and jump
right and this eye look is simply gonna
be pretty complicated and definitely a
lot going on today just like our
Thanksgiving dinner plates we got the
stuffing at the mashed potatoes the
gravy the turkey and the whole shebang
so I'm gonna be using the brand new
Morpheus 39a dare to create palette I
absolutely love this palette I can't
with the holiday collection that I
modeled for if you guys have not yet
seen my full-on review definitely click
somewhere up here I think if this is the
right side fingers crossed
to check that video out I first got my
m4 for one brush and dip into this
middle transition shade I actually lost
a little sheet with the names on it so
you're just gonna have to bear with me
today I'm just popping the shade right
up in the crease and blending it out
using windshield wiper motions and I'm
actually not topping off the brush
before I find this color we definitely
want this to be a very very vibrant and
pigmented and when we get to the outer
corner I am doing my all-time
favorite trick upholding that shadow out
a little bit for the next color we're
gonna grab at our 39 brush and dip into
this burnt orange shade right up in here
I'm topping the shade right up in the
crease and normally what I would do
crease shade I would always hold the
brush like this completely parallel or
horizontal there we go to my face but
for this I'm actually kind of holding
the brush downwards to really get it up
in that crease and make sure it doesn't
blend any higher we are gonna be cutting
out the crease today so it's okay for
everything gets on the lid because we're
gonna clean it up later and then same
thing with that outer corner I'm gonna
pull it out and like a nice little cut
v-shape we are gonna be going from
really really light orange obviously in
our transition to really really deep
black in the crease area which you'll
see in a few seconds but I am gonna be
blending in between every snap to make
sure that none of the colors get muddied
it together I'm Mexican I grab another
clean r39 brush this brush is basically
the exact same was the M 4-3-3 so if you
have that one
feel free to dip into that one too or
literally any blending brush it's really
not that deep to this and burnt darker
orange shade right up in here but we are
just gonna want make sure every color we
go and we're using a smaller brush or
just a more defined motion to really
make sure that those colors are getting
more and more dark and defined with each
time and once again not getting to money
on next thing I got was smaller more
defined brush this is the M 507 and I'm
gonna dip into this like ready tone
brown shade up in here and I'm gonna use
this to deepen up once again the crease
and the outer V as you guys can see when
doing these style of looks it's really
really important to start off light and
build your way up darker and darker
using a smaller and smaller brush and
smaller motions each time because if you
start off with a dark color and just go
right in everything it's gonna look
really really wonky and unblended like
really really quickly so I know it may
seem like a lot of extremis I mean we've
already literally use for eyeshadow
colors and this doesn't even look like
much it yet but if you just take your
time and be patient this is really gonna
like help you with your makeup in
general just starting off really really
slow and having patience will help you
make those iconic beautiful blend it out
smokey eyes so this is where things are
going to start to get more complicated
more dark and more intense I'm gonna
grab my m14 9 brush which is this very
very tiny pencil brush and dip into the
black shade in the bottom corner and
uses to deepen out crease
or the outer V not the crease oh my god
I just brought my mirror a little bit
closer obviously you guys know my
eyesight is not the pest I really want
to make sure that this is very very
defined and precise cuz you guys know
adding a little bit too much block and
make an eye look go from real good to
real bad real fast so excuse the mirror
in the video I'm gonna move it in a
second so with the block on the pencil
brush I'm gonna take this and I'm gonna
top it right into the outer of V we're
gonna cut this entire area out using a
shimmer shadow in a second but I do want
to get all the color on there in the
right shape just like that so we can
blend it out at how the pigment still be
there because like I said we don't want
to add too much block but where there is
the block we want it to be black if that
makes sense
to blend that black out I'm gonna grab
Miami five up seven brush once again and
dip into this cool tone a brown shade up
in here and just lightly go over those
edges like I was saying adding a little
bit of black and quickly get too intense
and I think this definitely just did so
I'm gonna go to my r39 brush and dip
into that light orange shade from before
and just go over those edges to
hopefully make everything a little bit
less dark alright so that is the lid all
complete like I said it did get a little
bit darker than I originally wanted it
to but oh well I guess that's just what
we're gonna have to deal with today now
we're gonna go ahead and cut out the
crease I'm gonna grab my morphe cream
shadow in the shade copper today which
is this beautiful orange shade as the
base of course and then my makeup shock
t57 brush it's just this tiny really
flat definer brush we are gonna be doing
a lot more of like a detailed crease
today than the classic average half cut
crease where you just kind of blur out
the edges so I do want to make sure it's
really really light and defined I know
some people really like to do a
concealer first when they're cutting out
creases but if you're using a pigmented
cream shadow I feel like it's really not
that deep because you're just gonna
cover over top of it anyway and it does
the same job so like why do you more
work if you don't have to you feel once
again talk about the mir but I'm gonna
lean in close early make sure I get this
exactly where I want it I'm just going
to carve out this crease I'm just
wanting to send like normal but then
once I get to the outer corner instead
of just fading out the edges I'm
actually gonna pull this shout out once
again
when that defined brush and I'm gonna
make kind of a loop back around to the
lower lash line this more rounded define
cut crease is a look that I've been
seeing a ton of people rock on Instagram
lately but I've never actually tried so
I just wanted to test that out today and
honestly I think it looks so stunning
and really really cool and definitely
adds a more like avant-garde twist
to the door euler half cut crease just
for an extra little pop on top I'm gonna
grab the Stila liquid metals and the
shade of bronze bell and just Pat a
little bit of this over top of that
morphe cream eyeshadow I really want to
make sure this is dried down before I go
in with any more shadow or anything else
obviously we don't any of that shadow to
transfer so the last and final step of
my upper lash line today is actually
gonna be to grab the Kat Von D tattoo
liner in the shade of trooper and I'm
gonna really lightly outline at that
outer curve for lashes today I'm gonna
pop out a pair of how's the lashes
ikonics
then I'm just gonna blend together my
real lashes with the fake ones of course
using my benefit roller lash mascara
once the lashes are blended together I'm
gonna grab a black liner pencil and you
guys know I hate doing this but for
today's look I filet it as necessary I
really want this to be very very sexy
and sultry
I want everybody other things doing
doing our table to know that I am that
[ __ ] that gets the turkey first I
really wanna be nice and intense
it's been a long time since I've done
that whoa
for the lower last I'm gonna grab an
hour 30 and I'm brush and dip into the
bright orange shade and just run that
all around the lower lash and then of
course I can sort of connect it at that
outer corner I'm gonna take my Beauty
Blender and dip into a little bit of my
chances at setting powder and I'm going
to bake right underneath that shadow
because I think it's getting a little
bit too low there and like I said we do
want to keep this very very defined just
like that I'm just gonna grab any flat
top brush and I'm gonna dip into the
already brown shade and I'm gonna run
that along the lower lash
Wow finally I'm just gonna grab a flat
top rounded brush and use this to
highlight my brow bone using of course
what other than my Anasazi illuminator
and so Hollywood then same thing on a
pencil brush in that inner corner
alright guys Metis one eye all complete
I'm gonna go ahead and do the other one
off-camera quickly and I'll be right
back to finish off the rest of the lock
alright guys and those are both eyes all
complete I actually ended up taking off
the electronics and switching them out
for the Lily lashes in the style Sydney
these are much more intense and
voluminous not gonna lie my eyes are a
little bit on code right now you guys
know I always do have to cut off a lot
of lash to make them work my eyes are
very very tiny but I feel like the
dramatic Ness and the size of these just
really fits at this look so sister it's
gonna suck it up I already added a
little bit of highlighter earlier but I
feel like we are definitely not blending
enough I mean I'm trying to be on the
level of like aunt josephine is grabbing
for the stuffing and we're like BAM and
she is literally so shocked that she
forgets about what she was doing and
then we get to snatch it up first I'm
gonna go in and lightly spritz my face
using the tatcha dewy skin mist just to
give the highlight or something to stick
to and then I'm gonna grab of course
you've gassed in my honest Asya so
Hollywood illuminator Oh
aunt Josephine is literally shaking she
just fell over alright guys and to
finish off this look today I'm gonna go
into the anasazi liquid lipstick in the
shade its sepia I'm not used as lip
color and so long but I felt like you
would pair perfectly with this look I
use it a few days ago for a chocolate
and I literally fell back in love with
it it is the kind of a brownie mouth
tone but it definitely does have some
purpley undertones which matched
perfectly with the reds in the eye look
today and I just like it pairs perfectly
for this fall look and finally to finish
this off I'm just gonna give my face a
good spritz using the Scandinavia makeup
finishing spray
alright guys and this is this little fun
Thanksgiving cut crease look all
complete it has been a very long time
since I've done a tutorial so I really
really hope you guys enjoyed this video
today like I said I normally do not go
this extra but it is Thanksgiving and we
really want to be that [ __ ]
at the dinner table we want the family
to know we are right there and we are
trying to get served that Thanksgiving
feast first if you guys did enjoy this
video today please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and
subscribe if you have not already click
that little notification bell so you can
be notified every time that I upload a
new video so I know Happy Thanksgiving
you guys you truly do mean so much to me
and I am so beyond thankful from all of
you guys and my career I would not be
here if it was not for you guys and you
do mean so much to me especially
considering you've been through
literally so much together I mean
literally everything has been thrown at
the sisterhood but we are still going so
strong and we're growing more and more
every day so thank you guys so so much
definitely make a comment down below and
tell me what you guys are thankful for I
will be reading comments while everybody
else is taking their nap after the
Thanksgiving feast if you'd like to
follow me on a makeup chair you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat Ferber head scenes I self is
James Charles an extra ask after Charles
this picture sir shadow goes to sister
Lancia thank you so much baby for always
following good supporting you know I
love you so so much and if you'd like to
be next week sister shadow make sure to
always retweet my video links when they
go live on Twitter all right sisters
thank you so much for watching I love
you so much Happy Thanksgiving and I
will see you in the next one
[Music]