hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so it
has been a hot moment since I've
uploaded on my youtube channel I am so
sorry if you guys can follow me on
Instagram and snapchat you would know
that I just actually finally after a
million years graduated once and for all
I did technically graduate early a few
months back but I just went home back to
New York for the first time into four or
five months since actually moving to
California and I walk to the rest of my
class for my graduation and it was kind
of iconic normally what I know I'm gonna
travel I agree film videos for you guys
but this time I had a lot of really
exciting meetings and stuff going on
beforehand for products that'll be
coming out soon so I didn't get a chance
to pre film but I promise when you find
out what I've been doing on the DL it'll
be worth that well it was an amazing
trip I was definitely ready for it to be
over with by at the end of it and I
definitely missed being on my la a grind
working every single day so I'm finally
back home and I decided to sit down and
film a video for you guys today I
tweeted asking you guys what you wanted
to see because I wasn't really feeling
any makeup inspiration at the current
moment and so many of you guys had to do
a a Q&A now you guys know I'm pretty
much an open book
I am so open and honest with everything
that goes on in my life y'all basically
know every single aspect of it
especially if you are a loyal snap fan
follower so I kind of was do something a
little bit different so for today's Q&A
I thought I would do a Q&A based on what
it's like being a social-media
influencer in questions that nobody
really wants to answer I tweeted asking
you guys to send me harsh honest and
hard questions to answer and I actually
got so many cool ones so I'm super
excited for this and we're gonna talk
about everything from how much money I
make to I like meeting fans weirdest
experiences and everything under the Sun
of what it's like to be a social-media
influencer so if you want to hear what I
have to say on this and answer some
really really honest question make sure
you keep on watching Laci asked are most
beauty gurus / social media influencers
a lot different in real life than they
present themselves on a camera okay so
yes and no for the most part beauty
gurus everybody is like the exact same
as they are on camera in real life if
anything we just make a lot more jokes
and can be a lot more ourselves because
we kind of understand what goes on
within the actual industry but for other
social media areas of like the spectrum
in different careers and stuff I
say more no I've met a lot of people
that are in the beauty industry that are
so completely different as they are on
camera in real life but never in like a
way that I've been it disappointed or
upset it's just mostly in a way to like
protect their image and to like keep
their audience satisfied if that makes
sense
Loie asked are you ever cautious about
surrounding yourself with people from
the industry like seeing the beef / dawa
24/7 online it doesn't make you guarded
abso-fucking-lutely they're like maybe
three people total this industry that I
actually trust I have a lot of super
super close friends but it's so sad to
say that you can never really really
trust anybody so I am super careful of
who I really trust and talk to I think
finding that group of people that you
can really really trust is super super
important in this industry as many of
you guys know watching from an outside
perspective this industry is crazy and
has so much horrifying drama so it's
really really important to find their
cup of people that you know you could
love and trust and always look to when
times get tough because trust me they do
we can ask when people are sponsored and
they say it's their honest opinion of
the product is it actually no obviously
it's gonna depend on the person you're
watching I can only speak for myself
here but in my case yes it is always
honest if you guys look through my email
and saw the amount of money and offers
that is given on a daily basis you would
probably be freaking shook to the core
so many brands reach out to social media
influencers about campaigns but I reject
actually like 90% of them I'm very very
blessed and thankful to have you guys
and have a lot of different sources of
income from all across nine platforms so
for me and many other influencers brand
deals are not saying that it's like
super vital to me to be waiting for the
next paycheck however the ones that I do
do are the ones that I actually really
do care about so if I do like the
product I will definitely do the brand
deal take the money for and give an open
and honest review so if somebody's
reviewing a product is usually because
they genuinely do like it I definitely
did get twisted sometimes between some
people but like I said I could only
really speak for myself here so if you
guys are seeing your review product and
say that I like it and if I'm being paid
obviously I do like it because I'm like
it what Dan asked has dating changed a
lot for you since you've gotten so big
and two boys treat you differently you
guys know that boys and dating a tunnel
has never really been a strong suit of
mine or like a
I'm pretty bad at it so it hasn't really
changed in the fact that I'm still
single as [ __ ] however I have noticed a
lot more guy type of social-climbing me
which is so sad and so like gross to
even think about but I've just learned
to be really really careful with who I
trust and try to date guys that are like
on the same type of like social spectrum
as me I know that sounds so [ __ ]
shitty to say but you have to think of
it from my perspective it's really scary
to like really trust somebody and let
somebody in if they have a lower amount
of followers it's because you really
don't know what their true intentions
are so it's much easier to talk to
people that are on like the same
wavelength or at least like in the
social media realm I really hope that
doesn't come across really pretentious
and shitty follower count at the end
that he means nothing to me my future
husband might have zero followers who
freakin cares I'm just saying from a
trust and weight it's a lot easier to
talk to and trust people that have a
little bit more of a social following
just so you are a little bit more sure
that there's nothing going on on the DL
Maya asked what is it like to go from
nobody caring about your mistakes to
everyone pointed them out and
criticizing you if you guys have been
following me for a while especially on
Twitter you know that I have definitely
I've gotten myself in a lot of a pretty
pretty awful and offensive scandals to
answer your question it's halfway really
[ __ ] annoying but to also I'm very
very thankful for it and let me tell you
why the part that I absolutely hate is
really really old content a lot of the
scandals that I've gotten involved in
people love to freaking dig up the past
and old tweets and old stuff and just
use them against me now for me
personally the tweets that were pulled
up were from a 2013 they were gross and
they were really really offensive and I
have since apologized for them I am not
making any excuses for them because they
should not happen said or I came out of
my mouth and I definitely should have
known better however that being said
there is literally no human being in the
entire world that has the same person
they were five years ago or was the same
person that they were when they were 13
years old five years ago I was just an
average everyday middle schooler with
like a hundred followers on Twitter they
were all for my school I didn't know
what it's like to have a social
following I didn't have anybody watching
me I didn't have anybody looking up to
me so it was a very very different world
I said a lot of really really gross
things that I shouldn't have said and
also a lot of things that I didn't
really understand the true impact or
underlying meaning of and that's just
because they didn't grow up with a lot
of diversity around me but now I know
that those things are shitty and wrong
which is why I have apologized and why
I'm addressing them
but it definitely does suck to have
things keep getting pulled up constantly
when you've already tried to move on
educate yourself and just be a better
person in general
I definitely will always like reread it
my tweets and snapchats before I post
daily because I have so many of you guys
watch me I'm looking up to me which is a
really really huge weight on my
shoulders but it's something that I am
so thankful for and something that I am
so proud of to be leading such an
amazing community I would never want to
degrade and disappoint or I find anybody
on purpose I am I'm so thankful that I
now have you guys to call me out when I
[ __ ] up so I can further educate myself
and just be a better person in general
Christian asks if all of your followers
disappeared overnight and you lost all
your influence would you still continue
to do what you love without a platform I
definitely think so yes but maybe not as
frequently have you guys been following
me for a while on Instagram you know
that I kind of started doing a lot of
more creative and avant-garde style
looks and that's really where my heart
lies I talked about this before on my
channel but I really don't like doing
glam that much and I usually only do
actual like glam when it comes to events
and filming YouTube videos just because
that's what really performs well and
that's what looks pretty for like photos
and red carpet and stuff so I probably
wouldn't do it as frequently and I'd
probably only be doing makeup when it
came to like the creative artsy a crazy
type looks but I definitely still be
doing makeup for sure because I love it
and this is like my hobby and well now
my job but if it wasn't my job I would
still love it if that makes sense
Jayla asked how much money do you get
for brand sponsorships no this is the
question that nobody ever answers but I
know everybody wants to know but I'll
tell you why they don't answer and
that's because it's actually illegal
when we do branded or sponsorship videos
we always have to sign contracts that
say we're not gonna discuss how much
money we're being paid or what's going
on behind the scenes aside from the
actual content that you guys are seeing
on our Instagram pages now I've worked
on campaigns and products before that I
absolutely cannot discuss the financials
of it is illegal I'm not trying to get
sued in any way shape or form but I will
tell you without giving any further
detail that the most I've ever been paid
when it came to his sponsored YouTube
video was in the six-figure digits
Leo asked how much money have companies
offered you to post about them on your
social media at the end of the day
yograj Trust is a lot more important to
me than any amount of money I will say
that I have declined several over
$1,000,000 offers because it wasn't
saying that would fit my brand cemet
asked be real how many of the people
you've collabed with are you actually
friends with Slash come to earth outside
of
every single one of them Ryan asked how
many times have you cried because of
hate zero nikki asked do you actually
like to meet your fans or does it get
annoying sometimes if you guys have any
person you know that I freaking love me
too you guys so so so so so so so much
it just makes me so happy to be able to
put a name to the face of all the people
that have been supporting me since day
one and it truly does warm my heart and
make my day I love me too you guys I
love taking pictures but I will say that
the 1% of the time I [ __ ] hate it is
when I'm eating nothing bothers me more
than when I'm about to stick my fork
into like a nice juicy steak her he's
some delicious french fries and ketchup
and my coke then when I see somebody
from the other side of the restaurant
kind of take a slight picture like this
because if I'm not gonna see yeah that
really really bothers me I just feel
like eating it's like a time of having a
good time with your friends and family
and just like it's just very very
disrespectful in general so if you see
me in public please ask me to take a
picture I would love to freakin meet you
I will give you the biggest hug people
take an amazing selfie just please if
I'm eating wait until I'm done and the
last question for today at Kalyan asked
do you love your job to end this video
on a positive note
abso-fucking-lutely I am so thankful to
be living my dreams and living this
amazing life at only 18 years old so
many people can't even say when they're
older that they do their dream job and
Here I am being very very young freshly
out of high school and just having an
amazing time and having all of you guys
watch and support me it really does mean
so much to all you guys are there on the
other side of the camera and even though
there are hard days I wouldn't trade
this for the world
if you guys are like a loyal beauty
community fan you know there's a lot of
really shitty and annoying and awful
stuff that goes down in this industry it
definitely is a very very cutthroat and
hard place to survive but I would not
still be here if I didn't love what I
did trust me on that one alright guys
and that is all I have for this video
today my phone just died sorry I'm all
out of questions like I said before I am
very much an open and honest book being
a social-media influencer definitely has
its pros and it's cons there's some
amazing days there is good pay good
friends and cool opportunities but at
the same time there's a lot of heat and
really really shitty situations that we
all get ourselves into so it's
definitely a crazy world that I live in
but I'm very very thankful to be where I
am thanks to you guys I really hope you
enjoyed this video and you learned a
little bit more about me and my weird
ass job if you did it please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below that lets me know that you
love this video and I'd definitely love
to do more of these Q&A social media
influence or videos in the future so
definitely make a comment let me know if
you liked it if you haven't already make
sure to hit that big red subscribe
button down below and join the
sisterhood also click that Bell icon
next to it so you can be notified every
time I upload a video so you can be a
1st of the page major shout out to
sister Jayla for sharing last week's
video on twitter love you girl thank you
so much for always following and
supporting our rankings thank you so
much for watching stay shook and I will
see you in the next one
[Music]