hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel first
of all if my voice sounds even more
annoying that it normally does please do
not comment about it I'm well aware I'm
currently getting over food poisoning
from a very suspicious ravioli that I
ate a few years ago I've been a very bit
under the weather but we will never let
that stop my YouTube video production
first today today I am very very excited
because we're doing a challenge is
probably a good friend Jackie
if he doesn't follow me for a long time
you probably caught on to the fact that
I definitely have my ride-or-die
products and I don't really such a my
makeup routine that often oh really
honestly at all it's been things that
I've gotten caught out for quite a lot
but I'm not a review channel I'm not
really a tutorial channel either and
what I find thing that I love I
definitely like to stick to it because
it works every once in a while though I
do find that brand new at
diamond-in-the-rough product that I like
to just slip right that was quite a
sound effect but I like to just come in
late to just doesn't like to just slide
that was a good wide that was the fun
side of that then I like to just slide
right into the makeup routine and it
quickly becomes one of my all-time holy
ground favorites to be used and hundreds
of videos have to the fact and for today
I thought it'll be so much fun to put my
makeup knowledge to the test and ask how
well do I really know my own a beauty
routine for the show today I sent my
team on a very difficult mission they
set out with all my favorite products
right every day at beauty routine and
they found it too very similar if not
little exact dupe products they
unpackaged all three and then repackaged
all three into the exact same packaging
so it looks like it's the same product
but it's not and I'm going to have to
use my touch the application the smell
and my eyesight obviously to try and
figure out if I actually know which out
of the three products is my actual
favorite that I use all the time I'm not
going into this I am pretty confident
considering I literally use these
products almost every single day I'm not
even sure I made it this far this a
beauty guru but who knows I could get
literally all of them wrong and I also
may find some really amazing products
that I would like to add to my routine
so that further ado oh not without
further ado but one last thing to tell
you guys
we get started you probably noticed by
now but if not I'm wearing a brand new
assistants apparel hoodie
it is in the color lavender which I am
so pumped for you guys I am obsessed
with this color it is literally so
beyond acute I've been getting so many
compliments on it all day long I am very
very pump to tell you guys about our
brand new pastel collection it is
launching this Friday April 12th at 11
a.m. PST on sisters - apparel calm we
have four new colors being at this
little lavender while we had a banana a
yellow one this is a much like more
muted version of our other yellow we
also have this like very very cute
orange creamsicle color
I lost the finally not least we also
have this super cute teal color I know a
lot of you guys been asking for mint I
was convinced that this was mint and I
have since been informed that this is in
fact not mint its spearmint I guess if
you want to call it we can definitely do
a mint one in the future but regardless
I think this color is still so beyond
cute if you guys want to check out any
of the four brand new hoodies make sure
you set your loans for Friday April 12
at 11 a.m. at PST they are limited
edition so once they sell out they're
gone for a very very long time
don't miss out the pastel collection is
so beyond cute and I cannot wait to see
you guys all I also forgot to mention
clearly then we also have foam phases
launching as well and at both of
lavender and teal and matching your
honey colors I thought it'd be so much
fun to start releasing a phone cases
every time we have a new colored hoodies
launching it just so you guys can kind
of collect them and start matching kind
of fun kind of funky kind of fresh as
always they're available in a bunch of
different iPhone models they'll also be
launching at the same times everything
else okay that is all I have without
further ado now let's see how I know I
make up routine
[Music]
so you're all primed and ready to go
yes the first step of your makeup
routine is foundation so here we have
NARS two-phase and is that the order
that they're in okay okay okay I'm
already noticing that this one's a
little bit more chunky
like not like chunky for like a little
it's like a little bit thicker whereas
opposed like this one is definitely like
a little bit more watery but I also
don't know when you put these in this
bowl so I'm noticing that these two
colors on the right hand are definitely
a little bit more like neutral toned
which is good for me and this was a
little bit more peachy orange color so I
think I actually know exactly what the
order of these is okay and I do know it
okay that smells like paint that is
literal that is paint is this acrylic
paint that's not a funny joke if you did
that to me is really okay I mean it's
all like good paint like I would sniff
that paint again okay okay this one's
much like stickier and I feels cold
while going on that's not a familiar
feeling I do know what the three of
these are I'm a genius
oh okay I know per thought that this one
is the Too Faced one I'm confident in
that
this is born this way for sure okay so I
know the goal this challenge is just to
pick out my favorite of the three and
then apply it but just for my ego sake I
said I want to try to label all three
just refine it so a final answer we have
to boots but on this way
NARS and then derive elimination
am i right well the sisters know but we
don't want to build your ego so we're
going
see if I can drop me to the end I'm
gonna go ahead and wipe my three fingers
off that and I'm going to dip into my
amazing a to face for the safe
foundation that I know and love and use
every single day is this am I wrong oh I
think I'm right this is definitely born
this way yeah cutter percent it's the
smell it smells very clean I know
[Music]
so now that your foundation is on yes to
the next step yes
so concealer here we lovely in front of
you we have tarp shake
okay Matt oh pro longwear yes oh okay
this I am NOT covenant because I use the
tarp tape tape all the time I don't
think I've ever actually once used the
bond Pro Longwear concealer except for
as an eye base and I just started using
this away at coverage concealer recently
but I don't think I'd like use it enough
to know it's smell and texture yeah well
I already see this one is a little bit
darker for sure and a little bit more
like peaches honed this one is super
super light and this one is like a very
like middle-of-the-road a type of
concealer that is quite the strong scent
I don't know why but I think that's not
prolong wear this there's a shame shame
I hardly ever said sure there's a shame
it smells just like it shape team hasn't
very like clean almost like floral smell
I have not a good with fragrance I have
a person but this got on the hotter was
that shard is a shave tape and that
means this smells like peanut butter
okay this is easy final answers you a
shape tape knock Pro Longwear okay so
I'm gonna put my is you a full coverage
concealer and my Mac Pro Longwear
concealer I know so don't play with me
now I'm going to grab my guitar shave
tape
then I use every single time and I'm
very familiar with the smell of miss
Lewis I did my beautiful endure right
into it oh my god okay who sees so we've
gone through foundation and concealer
yes
next step is power yes please
so in front of you today yes you have
the Too Faced peaches these all look
exactly the same
you have the airspun and you have
already off the bat I noticed in the
powder in the middle has it some chunks
than that this is no shade I know that
the first batch of matcha powder that I
thought was a bad one but I know it's
all my collection so I think that this
is it the powder powder is phenomenal by
the way that's definitely that's the
powder powder that's a respond the smell
alone is enough to literally distinguish
when this is literal grandma in a bowl
and that smells amazing this is okay
easy the Christmas game final answer
heiress pot pot check and the two-faced
sweet peach powder this stuff literally
smells so good
like it's insane I'm gonna use the sweet
peach powder for today and I'm gonna put
miss Patrick airspun off to the side
thank you guys for playing I hunt
reverse that positive on this one you
cannot even for me oh my god smells
literally so good it tastes so good
James gesina yes because you're very
confident right now yeah yeah I want to
bring you down yeah you have not gotten
everything correct yes I have okay Louis
do you like your dog I do really I don't
believe oh is this contour did you guys
like literally take the stuff out of the
pans and like read pan them oh that's
dedication so professional you guys are
team
morphia bronzer Anasazi eye contour cat
and hoola bronzer from benefit like
anything like anything either there does
that oh god I don't even know if I can
get my finger in here okay so definite
little bit more orange a tone so this is
definitely a bronzer this middle one is
a little bit more cool tone which leads
me to believe that it maybe the Anasazi
won just because I know that this one is
from a contour kit and this last one is
definitely a little bit more of a deeper
bronzy color that is benefit hoola
bronzer I have a very strong inkling
morphe anastacio betterment and for
today's video I'm gonna use the
Anastacio contour color gonna grab my a
map 405 and just step right into this
beautiful little pan we have going on
right here okay doc just voyage puzzling
out the cheekbone this is definitely
Anasazi oh I'm gonna dip my morphe e62
this is my angled fluffy brush that I
created for my brush set into this
honest hacia hopefully contour color and
use this to also just love my nose also
get this ready for this ready for this
ready for this ready for this and they
grabbed Miami
five to seven brush and grab my cool
bronzer I'm gonna Brown the face a
little bit after I contoured easily
honest
bronzer yes I'm sure it was those concha
once again I'm gonna grab my sweet
Pete's powder I'm gonna use it to bake a
little bit before we move on to the next
step we do yes brows oh so we decide to
give you a break and let you do it like
you okay great great okay I'm gonna do a
where I was quickly off care of that and
I will be right back with you guys for
the next step our resistance we are back
in my eyebrows are looking nice and good
and for us and snaps using actually my
Anasazi eyebrow products as always and I
moving on to our next step which is I
think going to be if I don't get this
right I'm literally gonna be cancelled
Oh which one has colors colors from each
so we can match up the color okay I
[Music]
honestly think that I know already but
if I am wrong this is literally to be
the most embarrassing thing that's ever
happened to me in a challenge before but
okay so here's here's where my brain is
going okay
the left hand a pink shade has a little
bit of shimmer reflect in it which my
pink skip 100% does not have so I think
this is from the new Anasazi Riviera
palette I think the middle row is mine
because out of these three like magenta
shades in the middle the one in the
middle is the most like burgundy whereas
these two or more pink and I think that
this left-hand column is Jeffrey's
because this tone of pink is a little
bit more peachy which i think would be a
very Jeffrey type of pink and this fella
needs a little bit more purple the black
I have nothing so I'm just noting you
put them in the right order
Jeffrey saw her husband James
Charlesworth a palette in the middle and
okay I'm gonna put my two very dear
friends off to the side I will not be
using them today about I love people
this is definitely skipped like I know
for a fact this pink is just like too
bright to be somebody else's that's
definitely my baby oh my god I didn't do
a swatch test before well that's better
I think I'm gonna do a halo I look
inspired by the one that I did in my
campaign the bubble gum moment cuz I
literally could not think of another
look that I would want to use pink
burgundy and black for gonna dip with
Miami four five six brush into skip it
skip
I know it's skip and it's literally you
cannot tell me otherwise you see that
staining mama oh you know that is
definitely staining that's skip then
with an amplifier most excited if into
what I believe is boutique from my
palette I hope is boutique for my palate
I know is boutique for my palate and
then finally with that same brush to
stepping into a little bit of a spooky
the black color and using this to deepen
out just the internal corners
[Music]
all right you guys that is one hallo aya
using what I think is the James house
and it's Murphy palette all complete I'm
gonna do the one off-camera quickly and
I'll be right back to move on to the
next step and quiz
alright sister through her back I just
popped on some mascara and Lily lashes
in this aisle so I strap Miami's my team
apparently could not find dupes up
either of that yeah you got bored if
either suit god of course you guys can
use coatings for 50% off your chest but
the look is pretty much all complete we
only have a few it stops left the next
one being a highlighter I believe there
is a lot on the line as well
because we got face from your oh no we
have they all look exactly the same
oh yeah from the balm
okay so literally when I created face I
went into the morphe studio with like
all of my favorite highlighters those
like I want to mix up all these and so
Hollywood was like my biggest source of
inspiration for face
considering I always wore it they're
very similar colors I will let you know
right now that's all hey what doesn't
exist anymore but it does today mama
okay let me do a little swatch I'm gonna
do a swatch test beautiful
awesome beautiful I am almost positive
that the this one on the left here is
mary-lou manizer from the balm because
out of the three swatches it is the
lightest and also the like least not
reflective but it's a very like flat
shape whereas both these two definitely
have like later pearls and darker pearls
in it mary lou manizer is very flat and
i remember that from always using it
beforehand so I'm pretty confident that
this one is Miss Mary Lu we can
eliminate her okay so now between these
two I think I do now this top one is
slightly more gold tone than the one
below it this one is a little bit more
peachy which leads me to believe that
the top one is honest Asya so Hollywood
and the middle one is faced from the
James Charles exploring palette and the
bottom one would be mary lou manizer
from the balm Mary Lu James Charles X
Murphy
Anasazi so Hollywood oh that is
definitely my highlighter
[Music]
so games yes Louis
god bless my quiz is over okay lipstick
Sao Paulo my family yes okay what are
your first thoughts the middle one is
dark I'm Augustus Melhem is what I'm
actually going to do this is over a
hundred percent over lipsticks smell
like cupcakes 100 percent old from Sao
Paulo and positive this is Kylie I know
this is Kylie because I've used her lips
like so many times definitely Kylie okay
uh-huh house passive-aggressive she's
gonna dip into my lovely sau Paula look
a lipstick that I do love which you can
use ko James for 30% off off by the way
mmm tastes like cupcakes okay how did I
do I don't know okay my face looks very
normal like this looks like I created a
normal look using a normal product so
I'm gonna hope that I got pretty close
to a hundred percent right so you
definitely get a point if you guess the
one you usually use yeah but it's bonus
if you guess the others
okay so for foundation we had NARS yes
two things
yes and Brent oh yes you did guess Too
Faced correct thank God
okay you did not guess those two really
[Music]
okay and trusting concealer yeah oh
thanks something this great some
heart-shaped a powder bronzer yeah this
is very well okay in my defense I try to
change this and you will not let me
Wow you guess that the one on the right
was morphe yeah that is correct
okay you guessed the one in the middle
was on Saskia yeah upon that I used as
incorrect
the one in the middle that you use was
hoola bronzer for your contour really
mm-hmm okay I'm trusting Asha
Oh God you guess the darkest one was on
Sascha that's incorrect the darkest our
weight the darkest on when you meet the
darkest one oh yeah when you use honest
hacia charles x morphe palette oh my god
you have got to be just wild crazy I
mean I'm not mad about it because like
Anasazi shadows are literally fantastic
like there's another best on the market
so least if I like thought it was good
which it is I mean hello this look
turned out beautiful it was Anasazi a
shadow
same thing with Jeffrey too like it
would not have been a this is
embarrassing so for highlighter you have
face yeah right thank God okay great
yeah
I mean we can tell looks amazing yeah
yeah I know those are all cracked those
are all correct and Wow
I am a professional clothes taker the so
the only one I thought of percent realm
was literally my own palette that's
really embarrassing that is really
really a very
all right sisters we'll definitely have
her this makeup quits today I had so
much fun filming this video I feel like
I should be very very proud of my
results because I'm Loki killed this but
I failed where it literally mattered the
most regardless and you're through this
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and definitely
leave me a comment let me know if you
guys whatever try this quiz out if you
do let me know your results I would love
to hear how well you guys know your
makeup routine if you've not ready make
sure to click that big red subscribe
button down below and come join these
sisterhood we are 15 million sisters
y'all gonna love to have you and join
the family and also click the belt like
Khan said you'd a replication every time
I upload a brand new video if you lead
follow me and I make up to her you can
follow me on Instagram Twitter they're
both ashamed Charlotte's my subject more
behind the scenes I hop is James Thomson
that extra ass after Charles death
videos sister shadow Louis's sister
Haley thank you so much love for always
falling and supporting you know I love
you and your username oh so so much and
if you look to the right videos a sister
shout-out don't forget to always retweet
my video and they go live on Twitter and
also trigger my youtube and post
notifications and last and finally not
least and don't forget about our sisters
to pair up pastel collection launching
this Friday April 12th at 11 a.m. at PST
we have all our pasta hoodies and also
the teal and lavender phone cases I hope
you guys are excited set your alarms
that's what I brew the studio's today I
love you guys so so so much thank you
for watching and I will see you in the
next one
[Music]