hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
today i'm up bright and early because i
am filming a video that i
truly never imagined would be happening
uh today i'm gonna be adopting a child
i love kids i think they're the cutest i
think they're the funniest i know i have
a lot of young fans out there as well
and i love you guys
so so so much but i have only talked
about
at least right now in my life the fact
that i do not want kids i just don't
think that i'd be responsible enough to
actually have a child and i would never
want to bring a kid into this world and
not be able to take a good care of it
and i just referred to a child as it
this is why
every time that i talk about not wanting
to have kids though every single adult
around me always yells at me and it's
like okay you never know until you try
so i guess that is the point of today's
video i'm going to be adopting a child
hi guys hi elia
hi we're going to film a video today
elliott where i
do whatever i say oh that was not what
we
had agreed upon your mommy dropped you
off earlier today and i'm going to be
taking care of you all day long today i
have a little bit of work to do but it
shouldn't be too much and we're just
going to make sure that we have a fun
day together
are you down yeah okay do you want to
tell them how you know me first yeah
because me and mommy are best friends
right
yeah and then i may when i got big well
no i've known you since you were a very
little baby
yeah well it sounds like you're telling
a contradicting story here
yeah elliot your birthday's coming up
this weekend huh
how old are you turning five you're
turning five years old
yeah are you excited no why not i don't
wanna be
big oh you wanna stay a little forever
yeah i guess today's video is gonna be
really fun for you then because we're
gonna make sure that you have an
absolute blast all day long
yeah let's get started
it's okay girl
okay why don't we stop this for just one
brief moment
so i want to know what do you usually do
during the day we go to starbucks first
i get a pink drink oh do you really
yeah period oh you're such a good sister
because that's usually the first one
okay okay so you want to go to starbucks
then yeah okay
ready yeah let's go now
okay
you need a car seat huh i have a
presentation
is do you know what animal he is yeah
what animal good
why is he gray because grass are great
why is he grey though did you get him
dirty no
i think that's why do you have your
phone
yeah okay oh i need my car i think
being a parent is too hard you kind of
got out of players
autopilot yeah i can't believe you even
know what autopilot is
[Music]
okay so not really sure what to do here
yeah we do we'll get you a phone charger
don't worry you know why i make a mess
my question
because i can do it
[Music]
whoa that's the spaceship
okay ready elliot to go to starbucks
yeah of course tingle with me
ellie why do you have to finish your
background do you love finn
is her favorite i love that can it
just stay in here in here yes you want
them to come with us
oh he wants to stay in the car oh you
don't want to come with me
oh why not do this it's a target
yeah well maybe we'll see let's go to
starbucks first then we'll talk about
target later okay okay
well you have to shut it then run away
okay hit the bottom button
ready to go yeah okay
good job what flavor cake talk to you on
um
okay can we do a strawberry pig thank
you
ready kitty girl now we gotta wait for
our drinks to be done okay
hey what's going on
[Music]
at this point if you're somehow a
subscriber and you don't know who elliot
is i would be a little bit concerned um
basically you guys know like elliot said
the beginning of the video
my best friend laura is elliot's mommy
and i've known elliot since he was a
baby and i've known laura for almost
five years now which is awesome and her
and her family owned a clothing boutique
down in whittier california called
laura's boutique
um
oh look who's there to greet you finn
hey get your drink
[Music]
okay do you want to start with my makeup
yes okay do you know what to do
to start off with um yes this okay and
then what's going to be your first
product do you know what this is called
no it's called foundation yeah okay
do you put it on here or do you put it
on my hand the hand oh good
and then put it in my dip this yeah so
you use the butt end
this end right here just like this then
you put it on my face
i'll help you out okay i got it okay
i'm gonna put it all around here
okay do you want to rub that on my face
yeah
my hand feels soft so as long as you get
another pattern
so ellie i want to ask you how do you
feel about auntie james wearing makeup
yeah i think it's cool you think it's
cool
do you like the looks that i create yes
like charlie
i like that one oh when i did charlie's
makeup yeah really
i practice all the time that's my job
just how like mommy and daddy work at
the warehouse to sell the clothes
i work here in the studio to do makeup
when every time my mom's doing pictures
do you do this
yeah she always does that she always
blends it out can i get can you get one
of those
the yellow one are you ready to start
off with your the eyeshadow already yeah
okay i i like red so i'm gonna do the
red
oh for some nice staining oh we're just
gonna right in
and i'm gonna do a one up okay what's
your favorite makeup look that i've done
on myself
um the one you did with charlie okay oh
you look good like right here
do you like it yeah okay i love that
i didn't do black oh no we didn't do any
black we can though
it looks good looking thick in there
does it look like my normal makeup to us
yeah
sure that's a nice blue thank you i made
it myself
blue yeah oh i made all the colors in
this palette
now i think i'm i want to do this one
the contour
yeah okay do you know where that color
goes where do you know what contour
usually does
yeah what put that on your face and put
it on your shirt okay well
do you know what it's for yeah what face
well yes but
so we put our contour like right here to
make our cheekbones look nice and
snatched
you want to do some lipstick maybe yeah
tell me any color do you want a red
a blue you want oh a red yeah oh that
was a pretty instant answer let me get
you a good red hold on
i like your shoes oh i plan on stock
chocolate
[Laughter]
it sounds loudies okay
i'm more skinnier more scary
yeah beard
i don't i know i do thank you for
reminding me you forgot how honest
peter left you should put some water
right here
some water why because it's on
here and here well that's because you
you put it there i know
you covered that beard
that's the beard that's a flap here
look at this skinny that's a fat one no
that's a skinny one
okay she's thick she's thick thick
i have blue in here oh if i needed to
cover my eyebrows
you should cut my eyebrows i don't think
we need to do that today
can you i think we're done okay i think
we can be done yeah
so we're done with the video and then
i'm buying it bye
[Music]
ellie requested that we download heart
rate on the xbox is it
downloaded oh yeah i think we need to
have lunch first
you're not hungry yet no never hungry
you wanna go to taco bell yeah you just
said you weren't hungry
[Music]
what do you call that one elliott um
bart
yeah i don't know bart and d minor
all right you guys we're back from taco
bell we both got our twinning baja blast
elliot's clearly already eating his
nice taco what'd you get in yours and
salad you like to watch youtube videos
while you eat huh
who are you watching a man a few words
later kitty girl now that we're done
with lunch i think we should go
take some photos together yes does that
sound fun
oh we have it off it all packed out for
you ready to go want to go yeah let's go
okay i got 20 outfits for us
so ellia we got these like these
sweatpants for you and then we got this
really cute jacket too okay
okay and we got you little shoes too so
we can be matching
can we get them yeah all right elliot
show us your fit
[Music]
are you kidding me
you're gonna show finn you're out
[Music]
okay should we take some photos yeah
let's go okay let's go where do you
think will be a good location
why don't you create a directos
finn look look at me look at me finn
look at me all right that's it did we
get it
oh those are so cute
oh my god look at that and finn too
that's perfect
okay that was easy great good work you
guys um let's film some tick tocks tell
the sisters what dances you know for a
tech talk
sure okay what other ones you know
[Music]
a movie i thought you wanted to go
swimming and play fortnite and do my
makeup who's a little bit confused you
keep changing your mind of what you want
to do
stretch ready
yeah you can ready it's the being four
years old for me it's a bad dance for
family
it's playing fortnite all day and not
even going to school for me it's almost
fake freckles from me
it's the tiny teeth for me it's a rough
thing for me
it's a wrong foundation for me it's a
boyfriend every week for me
oh yes i do know how to fly
you know have a lot of kills yes see
those
taxis yeah i'm gonna want a little drive
you're gonna go on a little drive
[Music]
this is me driving
let's get it get up get up let's get out
of me elliott
[Music]
oh my god elliot you're a savage
yeah do you want to tie them okay okay
ellie i have a little bit of a surprise
for you okay all right you guys so
elliot mentioned earlier that his
favorite tip talk in the entire book is
charlie
and charlie's are my best friends she
was on a photo shoot all day today very
i wanted special do something really
exciting for him to finish off this day
with his auntie james
all right sit there okay okay just sit
like that
have you had a fun day so far pal you
have okay
close your eyes give a special surprise
for you are your eyes closed
are they closed open your eyes
open your eyes open your eyes
oh we have somebody here hey
look who it is you want to see you know
okay i'll close my eyes oh that'll help
good good
yeah you're famous
[Music]
oh yeah you're so famous you have to
remember that okay anyone else is saying
this
come on you're famous hi oh my god
[Music]
oh my gosh elliott why don't you show
charlie your iron man
thing okay are you the worst parent ever
come on you're famous let's go oh
yay okay let's have a check my house
again
[Music]
okay so you started me and charlie will
come in
oh now we're getting serious
okay elliott now that mom and dad are
here to pick you up and you got to see
charlie i want to know how was your date
today with auntie james good
you liked it did you have fun yeah
what was your favorite thing that we did
today
makeup do everything like that so you
loved everything yeah do you think that
i'd be a good parent one day
yeah you really why would i be a good
mom or dog
and i really want to go in there right
now
because i have a big pool and you want
to go in it yes so that's why i'd be a
good dad one day
yeah okay all right you guys well
elliott thank you so much for coming on
this journey with me today i love you so
much well i had so much fun filming
today's video and adopting elliott for
the day and i'm so glad that he had fun
as well
if you guys enjoyed today's video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
thumbs up down below and subscribe and
come join at this sisterhood and finally
click that bell icon so you get notified
every time i upload a brand new video if
you want to follow me on my makeup
journey all my social media accounts
will be linked right here on the screen
and if you want to text me for updates
on new videos promos merch and so much
more it's 310-905-8746
make sure you guys follow elliott
everywhere as well he has a lit
instagram and a tick tock
hey why don't you you scroll through
here and you pick the sister shout out
her sister bella yeah okay this video is
sister soda chris's sister bella thank
you so much love for always following
and supporting i love you so so much and
if you liked it in the next video sister
shadow don't forget to always retweet
building single live on twitter and also
to my youtube post notifications all
right you guys thank you so much for
watching this video today elliot i love
you
[Music]
and i will see you guys in the next one
bye
[Music]