[Music]
hi
sisters james charles here and welcome
to the official
2020 house tour and also
20 million subscriber special oh my god
you guys i cannot believe today is
finally here and we are finally filming
this video i am so beyond excited and i
know so many of you guys have been
waiting for it as well
and here we are a few months ago i
revealed to you guys on my instagram
that i actually purchased
my first ever home which has been my
biggest dream since i was a little kid
and it's been my number one goal since
actually starting in social media and it
is crazy that it became a reality we
actually purchased this home back in
november of 2019 and have been
renovating for the past almost
nine months now and finally after
renovating decorating and getting
settled in i am finally ready to take
you guys inside on the
full sisters house tour last and final
thing that i want to tell you guys
before i let you in
is that this is the 20 million
subscriber giveaway
this home would not be possible if it
were not for you guys and i am so
incredibly grateful you will have to
watch all the way to the end
to find out what the giveaway is but i
will tell you it is the absolute biggest
giveaway we have ever
done and i know that you guys are going
to be super excited
come on in
[Music]
all right you guys come on in i'm so
excited to show you the entire house
obviously upon entering the front door
we are in the nice lovely entryway
and the first room that we have right
here on the left is the formal
living room
[Music]
if you guys remember the last house tour
that we were in the vibe and like the
layout is honestly pretty similar
but this house is like a trillion times
better and bigger so i'm so excited to
show you guys
my favorite part about this entire
formal living room is of course the fin
on the ground
but also this beautiful chandelier that
we have in the ceiling
and also this stunning floor-to-ceiling
fireplace my friends and i are in here
all the time singing together and having
little jam sessions
personally i cannot read music but as
long as you know how to play the
classics that's all that matters
coming out of the formal living room we
are of course back into it the entryway
we just have this cute little circle
mirror and i love this detail that
literally looks like it's like heading
from
a pen obviously it's secure on the wall
because there's a lot of earthquakes
here in california but
it's just perfect to check our face
before we go out of the house and run
any errands
and then right around this way we have
the formal
dining room now i say formal because
honestly the chances of us
using this room are virtually very very
slim if i'm
being real we never use the dining room
or the last house and
already just from moving in here about a
month ago the only purpose of this room
has been either meetings
or dumping packages that we get from the
mailbox we really eat in the kitchen
which you guys will see a lot in a
second
along this one we just have the storage
cabinet and then right above it is this
picture which if you guys have been
following me for a long time you may
have recognized this this is actually a
photo that i took myself on my senior
trip in school to south africa
there's actually a few different photos
from the trip around the house which you
guys will spot throughout the tour
my amazing interior design team which
we'll talk about in a second wanted to
make sure that there were personal
touches
from me all throughout the house which i
just think is so so cool and really
important during interior design okay
now coming out of the
formal dining room if we keep walking
further into the home
this next feature is the wine cellar now
wine cellars are pretty popular in newer
construction builds especially in the
area that i'm in in california
but for somebody like me who doesn't
drink wine it's pretty pointless and if
you guys remember the last house
the wine cellar literally stayed empty
for the entire year and a half that i
was living there so when we moved into
this house i was like okay we have to
put something in there so at least
looks presentable so we decided to fill
it with one of my favorite drinks
coca-cola all right you guys so directly
across from the wine or
i guess coke seller is first of all the
stairs to the basement which will be
later on in the video i'm so excited to
show you and then we also have
the formal office i'm obsessed with
these beautiful glass
french doors that open up into the
formal office
now personally for me i'm not a very
like formal office type person i
honestly would just take my laptop and
work anywhere
which you guys obviously know um but we
didn't want to have a cute little like
office space just for anybody who
doesn't need to use it for anybody on my
team
and we also have my gaming set up here
it has been like months since i've
played any games or streamed online i
low-key honestly missed games with james
so if that's something you guys want to
see come back let me know because it's
all set up and ready to go so all right
now coming out of the office
i am so excited to show you guys the
space that we probably use the absolute
most
in this house it is such a massive
upgrade from the last place
and that is of course the kitchen
honestly you guys when i walked into
this house and saw the kitchen it was
almost like a guarantee in my heart that
i needed to buy this house because the
kitchen
really is the heart of the home there
are two beautiful stunning marble
double islands we have these massive
pendant lights light gray cabinets with
a lot of white features as well and i am
just absolutely in love
with this space it is no secret that i
do not cook
okay i'm not hiding it i postmates
literally every single
meal but despite the fact that i do not
cook my friends and i are in the kitchen
all the time eating sitting at the
island filming mooc bones together
talking gossiping and most importantly
just being with each other if i take you
guys back this way
there's not much back here other than
just like i think this is called the
butler's
area of the house i'm not really sure to
be honest um we just have like the
coffee machine cups back here a little
mini fridge
but i do want to show you the pantry
which is right over
here once again not much cooking but we
do do a
lot of snacking and i really want to
show you guys this because of how
beautiful and organized it is
thanks to reorganize a few weeks from
instagram stories i was talking about
how we're moving into the house
and i got a dm from somebody being like
you need to get your house
professionally organized
and i was like what does that even mean
and i started doing research and
found out that there is literally people
whose job it is
to organize your house and make it look
pretty and i was so excited i posted it
on my stories rhea and her team reached
right out and they came
literally the next day and made the
house look so beautiful
this looks so good all thanks to her you
guys should definitely check her out
because she has saved my life okay so
right across from the kitchen we have
one of my favorite places in the entire
house which is the
living room
this is pretty much like the relaxation
destination
that little rhyme like i mentioned the
kitchen you guys know my friends and
family are here over all the time
and in the living room it was really
important that we had a lot of different
seating spaces so we have these gorgeous
chairs from
craft house we have this massive sofa
we're actually waiting to put another
like
chunk or like star
piece of the sofa and so we have here
before sitting space and then we have
this gorgeous leather shades lounger
look at me being a furniture expert
right below the tv
you know we are in here literally all
the time as a family and friend watching
movies playing xbox sometimes chilling
and honestly watching a lot of music
videos as well
it's just like a full vibe in here while
we're in one of my favorite rooms that i
feel like has really really good
decor i feel like it is only appropriate
to give a shout out to the interior
design company that did
the entire house from day one which is
leclaire decor
now brenda baby's home has been a really
stressful project but also a really
rewarding project
and working with la claire de court was
definitely one of the most like
rewarding partnerships i have ever had
i have nothing but like the absolute
best thing to say about them
um their entire design team sasha mel
and then i worked directly with meredith
was
amazing from beginning to end they were
just on top of everything they were so
organized they actually cared so much i
truly felt like on the last day of the
project when they were placing the final
decor items and really fluffing the
pillows and they're getting ready to
leave i was like losing a piece of
my family like they just took such good
care of me and if any of you guys want
to check them out if you were moving
into a new house
i would one billion percent recommend
leclaire decor for any of your amazing
design services
they did such a good job clearly and
this house would not look as beautiful
as it does
without them all right you guys so
there's only one area left of the main
floor that i want to show you and that
is the guest
bedroom now this is opposite of the
formal living room so
the other way when you come in the front
door as we move past the mud room and
the cute little ensuite bathroom
we have the guest room of the house
there are actually a lot of bedrooms
when i first moved into this home but we
converted most of them into workspaces
but it was definitely important that we
kept at least one being a guest room
and that is this room i love the wood
tones and the blue tones it gives me
very like beachy type fives and since we
have friends and family over all the
time it is the perfect place for any of
our guests to
sleep also it coincidentally happens to
be the room that is furthest from my
bedroom
so this is perfect for when the parents
come to visit nice and far away while
we're on the subject of bedrooms it is
finally time for me to take you guys
up to the next level of the house i'm
gonna take you guys off this beautiful
rounded staircase which coincidentally
when i was first looking at this home
i hated so much this entire wall used to
be all ship flap and the railings were
different and it was
so ugly i actually talked to my
contractor about removing the routed
staircase all together
but once we made a few changes it really
came together and now i
am obsessed it is the most beautiful
stunning focal point of the home and
i just love that it brings your eye
upwards into this gorgeous round
landing area
[Music]
one of my favorite parts about the
entire house is this bookshelf wall
mainly because we have a rolling ladder
i don't know why this is just my biggest
dream
[Music]
it's not perfect we have a cute little
chair just sit down and relax and we
also have this gorgeous
huge mirror for lots of outfit photos i
always take my instagram selfies in here
in
the morning but i have my new looks on
speaking of having looks on the first
room that i want to take you guys to
upstairs
is the fitting room now this is once
again one of those bedrooms that we
converted into
one place but we actually are in here
literally
all the time i hope you guys have
noticed but i've been working a lot on
my style recently trying to just go for
more elevated
high fashion looks thanks my new stylist
lena who you guys met a few videos ago
and this is where her like work space is
we have clothing rocks with different
future outfits
some of these you guys have seen some of
them you have not seen just yet so
hopefully you'll be excited we have a
bunch of really cool pairs of shoes as
well to pair along with the outfits
and then we have this massive
floor-to-ceiling mirror which is either
our fitting room
mirror or also a lot of times we learn
tic tocs in here too
and this is like the dance studio next
door to the fitting room is
lewis's bedroom now you guys obviously
know lewis he's in the background of
almost every single one of my videos and
you've seen him on my instagram as well
i don't want to go too in depth because
obviously this is his space and not mine
um i
had to use adjectives to describe this
room it would be
um straight sure
well what else we want to say there's
artwork of a girl getting changed on the
wall
there's shoes everywhere it is art but
it's
very straight so that's lewis's room
sure right next to lucy's room is the
laundry room there's not much to say
about the laundry room
there's a double washer and dryer
because we have so many clothing items
in this house that need to get washed
all the time
maybe cute little blue pendant and just
some things that are air dry and then
right across the hall from lewis's room
is trevor's room once again this is
trevor space not mine so i don't want to
do the tour for him but
it's very very cute very simple he has
his desk there because trevor is still
in college
which is incredible he balances doing
full-on school work and working with me
full-time which is amazing we love him
and we stand
very kind of like similar vibes to the
guest room downstairs lots of cool
gray blue and like tam tones very like
beachy
decor and i love knocking on trevor's
door every single morning getting him up
and ready for the day now the last
bedroom that i'm going to take you guys
to on the upstairs level is of course
going to be
the master bedroom which is across the
hall now we have these
beautiful double doors and it leads
right into my space
[Music]
we have this beautiful four poster bed
keeping the same theme with the beachy
vibes
tan pillows blue pillows cute little
accents we have this leather bench
we have this gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous
gorgeous chandelier in the middle of the
room
personally i hate chandeliers i don't
know what it is i can never find ones
that i like but this one
and the one downstairs were really
speaking to me so i'm so glad that we
found this one up for the space i think
it is
perfect along the opposite wall we have
another fireplace which is
so beautiful i love this matte stone
i've actually never seen anything like
that before especially with the wood
accents i think it looks
so good we have this tv which i
literally never use
some shelves and then also fun little
added feature there's a mini fridge in
here
this is actually fully filled with water
but i just finished it and have not
restocked it yet so i promise that i'm
not drinking coke before bed
the addiction is bad but not that bad i
have a mini fridge
okay come on into the master bathroom
[Music]
okay you guys i am obsessed with this
massive bathroom because of how big it
is
as you can see there's pretty much two
of everything and i'll explain why
it's because this bathroom and closet
was actually formatted to be his and
hers
but since it's be living here it's just
his and his there's two different things
there's two different toilets as well
one sheared tub and then one massive
massive
marble shower as of right now it's only
been using this in the morning but who
knows what future activities could
you know ensue later on next to the
shower as well i have this heated
towel rack which is so nice to leave
online in the shower so when i get out
of the shower and it's freezing cold
i get to warm up in my nice little towel
i thought that was a fun feature
uh this is always the vanity that i use
for getting ready so i have like my hair
hair stuff over there
and then this vanity is like my personal
care item so i have
my one size patrick star makeup wipes
and of course my soap my moisturizer
um deodorant and then i have my on my
sands and medium light which i'm
literally wearing
right now i always use it for tanning
stuff and then the serene to keep my
breath
fresh right next to the master bathroom
speaking of his and hers we have the
master
closet now this is one of the faces in
the house that actually took the most
time with the renovations because there
was a lot of work to be done in here
like i was mentioning it was a his and
hers type of situation and originally
this closet was the like his closet
used to be gray black very like dark and
dreary
and it actually had a door on it so we
opened up the entire wall we painted it
white
this is the closet where i keep all my
custom dressy or like costume
type pieces if you guys look around
there's a lot of really iconic moments
in here that you guys have seen at
coachella different red carpets
influencer as well
and i'm very much looking forward to
adding more pieces to this closet
as i do more exciting things in my
career and then coming right out of the
extravagant costume closet we have the
more everyday casual closet
and this is like my absolute dream a lot
of the other places that i've lived in
the past okay my downtown apartment then
my last home
did not really have the best closet
space literally in the last house i had
clothes everywhere because it was
overflowing
so it is so nice to finally have a
massive closet where i can put
everything all in this entire wall i
have my different hoodies t-shirts
i have jackets in here different bags in
here my more formal cases
here pants more jackets lots of shoes
jewelry in the middle lots of
accessories
this is the ultimate dream for me as a
wannabe hopefully one day in the future
fashion guru all right you guys now the
last place that i want to show you of
the master bedroom
is the outdoor patio we have these
gorgeous
sliding glass doors which actually open
all the way up
so it's just very much like luxurious
indoor outdoor
space i love these pocket doors and this
is one of my favorite places
of the entire house this patio actually
gets direct sunlight all day long which
is
so nice especially during these hot
months in the summer here in california
there's been so many afternoons where
i've laid out here tanning and like the
day beds which we got from restoration
hardware
and then once the sun goes down we have
these outdoor couches chairs as well
and this massive fireplace in the middle
where my friends and i can roast
marshmallows and then look up with the
stars in the sky
the patio also has the most gorgeous
stunning view of the backyard
actually no no no don't show that just
yet that's gonna be a full reveal for
later on in the video okay now that you
guys have seen the upstairs and the
bedrooms and also the main floor
there's still one floor left of the
house that i have not yet
shown you guys ever since i started
doing youtube about four or five years
ago now
i have been dreaming of what it would be
like to have the perfect
sisters headquarters we've been
renovating for months
and i'm so excited to tell you guys that
those dreams have finally
come true come on in
to sister studios
in honor of hitting 20 million
subscribers we're giving away
100 000 dollars
[Music]
you