hi sisters James Charles here welcome
back IG Channel oh my god it feels
literally so good to be sitting here and
filming it in front of this camera right
now I know you guys have obviously been
seeing videos for me all the time but
they were actually all pre filmed
because I've been to traveling and just
working on a lot of super awesome and
secret things the past few days which
has been so so so exciting you guys are
literally not ready for the things that
are about to come with The Sisterhood
but regardless in case you cannot hear I
am very sister sick right now I just
traveled to a Vegas in Salt Lake City
this past weekend of a good friend at
lips like Nick for her makeup tour but I
got very very sick which is so
inconvenient and so rude and so
homophobic but I've been downing mucinex
and don't stop and awesome and blowing
my nose every 15 seconds Thank You
Kleenex hashtag not sponsored but
hopefully we'll be gone soon
and if you already hated my voice get
ready for this video because this is
about to be intense since I literally
have not had makeup on in over a week
now and knowing that blowing my nose
would take off my nose contour in about
three seconds flat I really just want to
sit down today I play with a little bit
of makeup I have a really pretty look in
mind inspired by a bum of a Mitchell I
saw The Times Instagram page and I was
like wow any this on my face right now
so we're just gonna chill I want to do a
little bit of a sister Q&A as well
because I haven't done one in a while
and for videos that I'm doing these more
colorful creative looks doing a juicy
Q&A during that was literally the only
way that I can guarantee it'll still get
views and you guys will still watch so
love being a bargaining Queen let's jump
into the video all right guys just
something right and this question is
actually a really good one to start off
with that I'm really gonna think about
here but this is from a sister owed Ron
and he said if you couldn't be convicted
of any one type of crime what criminal
charge would you want to be immune to
that is such a good question if I could
be immune to any criminal
oh my god 100% hello Rob the u.s.
national bank right now take all the
money and run and nobody ever knows are
you kidding I finally be able to buy my
sister house without having to worry
about three lines of credit 100% that's
actually such a crazy cool person though
I've never even thought about I want you
guys to all answer that in the comments
down below to actually maybe not I could
get bad real fast
never mind dog dude
I think you're a great hair you're
kidding what is this I do what this is a
joke I have a great hair at age 18 oh my
god wait Kelly give me a zoomin that's a
gray hair I quit
oh my god I'm scared you call Hayes what
the hell that just ruin my day and my
life probably oh my god
sister Nika ass what's one thing wrongly
did in your makeup routine before you're
a professional makeup artist that you
would say to your younger self right now
when you have all this knowledge oh my
god 100 percent will be stop using so
much powder while baking your face
clearly you guys know flash like Mary
happened for a reason and it's because I
used to use literally so much baking
powder it's absolutely insane like I
used to pack it on with a powder puff
not even a beauty blender and it looked
so bad and not only did I look very very
textured but it also created one of my
biggest scandals of all time which thank
God I was able to turn it into a meme
and make it productive for me but oh my
god it was really really embarrassing in
the moment I feel like a lot of people
who watch beauty gurus for makeup
education including myself this is
totally how I learned how to do makeup
in the first place
tend to follow exactly what a lot of us
do and implement those steps into like
their everyday makeup routines literally
once again that's how you learn to do
makeup in the first place obviously you
should support and watch whatever you
want and whoever you find entertaining
duh but when it comes to actually
listening to the tips and advice and
implement take different products and
techniques into your routine I would say
that it's really really important to
find a guru or one or two who have very
very similar features and skin types to
because people like Patrick Starr for
example who use a million pounds of
pressed powder may sit there and say yes
baked your face bake your face bake your
face but for those people who want a
really really dry skin if you do that
you will look like the Sahara frickin
desert and then on the flip side there's
a lot of gurus out there such as icarly
by Bell or Jocelyn Hill who have more
normal to dry skin and they don't really
set their face much at all except for
underneath their eyes and for people who
have oily skin if you did that your face
would be melting off at about thirty
seconds flat after walking outside with
no pressed powder on so it's really a
matter of finding different people that
you not only like and find entertaining
to watch but also are able to give you
accurate techniques that are going to
work for you I definitely say for me I
wish I took my skin type into
consideration more when learning how to
kind of set my face in place we would
have avoided klaustreich mariya but
at least we got a really iconic meme out
of it Mariah asks how did you grow so
fast in the beauty industry
what's your secret / method you use to
get noticed / stay notice this is
actually a really good question that I
get asked all the time I've kind of
briefly touched on this in a few
different videos but you guys know I
love giving business advice and it's
like my favorite thing in the entire
world so I thought I would answer this
one today I think the reason that I did
grow so fast in the beauty industry it's
because of the looks that I started off
doing and I don't want to talk about me
being creative because I literally feel
like I talk about that in every video at
this point I think that originality is
really what grooming to begin with and
is what's kept me relevant up until this
day I'm definitely someone who can take
pride in the fact that I do create a lot
of really really original concepts for
my channel that I've been started a lot
of other people and a lot of other
creators as well and I just worked
really hard to come up with new concepts
the whole time I'd like the makeup
industry its kind of hit a wall in the
sense that we've literally all seen
everything done like a million times are
like every single eyeshadow palette that
comes out I feel like is looking exactly
the same like every single week there's
a new challenge coming out that feels
like one of the other challenges that
we've all seen I think what set me apart
from a lot of different influences that
I was doing something different and
that's always the advice that I give to
up-and-coming artists or people who want
to build a social media page is that you
have to do something different you have
to do thing that's gonna set yourself
apart from everybody else with a little
bit of glam and a little bit of face
tune who's doing the same exact thing
because as blunt as it sounds
nobody's ever gonna make it with some
brown smokey eyes and some nude lips
like it sounds harsh to say that but at
the end of the day there's a million
other people doing it so the only people
who are really succeeding and who are
gaining quickly are the ones who are
really setting themselves apart and
establishing themselves as both an
entertainer and an artist if that makes
sense
I also callate - if you go into the
industry trying to grow and trying to
gain followers and that's your reasoning
behind doing the makeup in the first
place you're never gonna make it because
it's gonna be really really obvious and
apparent to the people that are gonna be
following you whereas if you go into it
really focusing on your art and like I
said putting out a new original content
that nobody's seen before
the followers gonna come no matter what
because it's gonna be something
interesting that they're gonna want to
keep watching so I feel like you really
have to go into it with the different
lenses that everybody else and kind of
think like what can I bring to this
industry that doesn't already exist here
and it's gonna be those people who
really think outside of the box and
think strategically that are gonna make
it to the top a strass where have you
always wanted to go but never been able
to oh that's actually I'm really good
there's actually a lot of places that I
really really really want to travel to
um South Africa was actually like my
number one place that I really wanted to
go to and that trip is now checked off
the bucket list which was literally
amazing and also not so amazing at the
same time you guys all know why
Australia some words that I also am so
excited to go to oh my god literally it
one week from today I'll be in Australia
on tour and I've ever been more excited
for anything in my entire life I am so
pumped I've heard it as such a beautiful
place Australian boys are all so
beautiful so I'm just very very excited
and if you are a sister down under and
you want to come see me don't forget to
check out James house Australian comm
for all your tour information and
tickets I think the sisters VIP packages
have already have completely sold out
for both shows which is so late so thank
you guys for all the support but there
are still VIPs and general admission
tickets available this siren is being so
weird I am just trying to promote my
tour as I was saying before I was rudely
interrupted yes
Australians definitely once on my bucket
list that'll be checked off very very
soon so I'm so excited for that I want
to go to Italy first show you when I go
to Paris I want to go to the UK I want
to go to New Zealand I want to go to
South America I really want to go to
Peru I want to go to Canada I've never
been to Canada before even though it's
literally right up there hey my Canadian
sisters up north I would really love to
go to Japan eventually that sounds so
much fun hello I just want to travel and
just see all of my sisters all around
the world sister Priscilla asked who is
the kind best celebrity you ever met Wow
can't wait to answer this one because I
know it won't get me in twist
accountable but I probably actually have
to say Kim Kardashian hands down she's
been absolutely incredible every single
time that I met her she definitely has a
little bit of a controversial public
figure but she doesn't let that get to
her and she's just really really funny
she's unapologetically herself and she's
a really really smart businesswoman and
she's just really really nice all on top
of that and has always been nothing but
absolutely amazing I would really love
to work with her one day so I definitely
love it sister Kim handsome easy answer
for that one
all right guys I'm currently baking in
the oven I'm gonna go into my brows
off-camera
sorry I literally cannot talk while
doing them I need to focus so hard core
to make sure the eyebrows end up being
sensors and not like distant cousins
twice root because
it happens let's be real so I'll be
right back in a few minutes to start off
the eyes so starting on behinds today
like I said I'm doing a look inspired by
a mobile of Mitchell one of my all-time
favorite artists and he's a UK artist
and UK artist use a lot of very
different techniques than ask American
and us artists and their eye shadow
always looks away a bomber than ours so
I definitely want to try a lot of the
different techniques today so I'm gonna
start off with the P Louise eyeshadow
base this is a kind of similar textures
like the mac prolongwear concealer and
I'm just going to Pat this on using a a
flat concealer brush and then for my eye
shadow today I'm gonna be using the P
Louise I shut up palette apparently
instead of really blending this in
you're supposed to kind of a tap it in
to place and what really is scaring and
worrying me about this is that none of
the UK artists ever set their base they
go right in with the shadows of right on
top and kind of blend it even though
it's still wet so I want to try to do
that today I'm not sure how to nor turn
out but clearly they're doing something
right they're putting something in the
water over there that's always making
the shadow look bomb so you know what
we're gonna take risk so unless I throw
my brush on the ground like I just did
I'm gonna grab my morphe Emma 511 brush
I love this brush that is a really
really big fluffy brush and dip into the
shade P Louise right here in the palette
and I'm going to use this yellow shade
as a transition shade and the outer
portion of the crease this I said look
it's gonna be pretty complicated so I
don't really want to explain what I'm
doing so I'm gonna go back to answering
your guys's questions during the process
and sister Bobbie asked have you ever
unfollowed one of your fan accounts and
why and the answer to that is actually
yes I have one very specific incident in
mind and this was a very very hard
choice for me to make but I did have a
obvious reason for doing so and that
being that this person was being very
very mean to a lot of my other fan
accounts and we actually had an incident
in the sister and a few days ago
regarding a very similar thing actually
but after all the crap that I've been
hit with from BS of stand Twitter and
people online just hating me for no
reason and just being so nasty the
absolute last thing that I want you
sisters to be is mean to anybody even if
somebody's being the worst person in the
world are being rude to you they're
being mean though
to somebody else please I asked you guys
don't address it don't say anything just
be the bigger person and either be nice
about it or just don't say anything at
all if anything you guys know I'm
definitely a firm believer and allowing
people to grow and change from their
mistakes and although the love from you
guys is always a really really intense
and amazing
they hate from the haters is also very
very intense and you guys know that for
sure so if the haters coming into the
sisterhood already having a bad feeling
about us and feeling that we may be
really really dramatic or really really
scandalous or all have god-like kind of
mindset then we all think the same way
prove them wrong let's just all be is so
amazing and so nice to one another that
all the haters come in or like oh oops
these people are actually a really
really dope and James is awesome and all
his fans are really really awesome as
well so like I was saying I haven't
followed a fan account before I'm not
happy about it I it paid me a lot to do
so but at the end of the day this person
was being very very nasty to a lot of my
other friends who I also love and care
deeply about and that is never okay so
be nice share the love no matter what
even if somebody's not sharing the love
back because I guarantee it'll come back
around to both you and the positively
and them in the negative life Karma's a
[ __ ] sister Zoe asked if you could
bring one thing from your house in New
York and bring it to your apartment in
LA what would it be and why literally
the answer this is so easy my dog Benny
oh my god I miss him so much
it is literally insane and for some
reason too I think there has been a very
very strange influx of dogs in my
apartment building recently it's really
just making me so sad and miss him so
much
and you guys know like I've been trying
to buy a house really badly and it's not
exactly working out but the first thing
that I do when I get a house before I
even like my furniture is literally
getting a dog I cannot wait to adopt one
oh my god I am so beyond excited I need
a dog right now in my life I really want
to get like a husky pitbull mix like
that just sounds the best and the entire
world it's been on my agenda trust me
sisters tannaz if you had a launch your
own makeup line what would be the first
product that you would come out with oh
that is totally so easy
definitely a 100% in eyeshadow palette
you guys know eyeshadow is by far my
favorite part of my makeup routine and
so I really feel like I can be super
super creative and always switch things
up and always push the boundaries I just
live for a good colorful moment
I definitely have if you are really
really or really bomb ideas for palates
they've never been done before either so
you guys will have to stay tuned and see
what happens I'm gonna take this
metallic light blue shade if I'm a 35 B
you guys know this is my all-time
favorite palette from morphe with all
the Rainbows she's use go James for 10%
off this palette and all other amazing
morphe goodies and I'm gonna try to pop
this on the lid maybe and this might
give us the similar look I'm scared
sister Katie asks what is your current
favorite clothing brand oh that's
actually a really really good question
and if you had asked me this literally
like six months ago my answer would have
been literally like per for 21 and top
man which is the most boring generic
white boy answers ever but my answers
have now drastically changed and I'm
actually really happy about it because
you guys know I definitely said I'm
getting this year that I want to take
fashion a way more seriously and really
get into it and just be really proud of
the outfits that I wear because a lot of
times my face is looking a real beat but
I'd wear the same hoodie and every
single picture ever which I'm sure it
got really really boring for you guys
were really really fast so right now I'm
really loving a lot of the different
trends that are going on involving like
modern street wear
that's like my all-time favorite style
of fashion I just feel like it's so it's
so so cute for me too I really love that
style because it's really fun to
experiment with it and it's like a very
very kind of more masculine street wear
type of outfit and then just a B ass
face right on top I said F gender
stereotypes it's very very heterogeneous
and it's just really really cool to like
play on that and I just have really
really been loving it so recently I
really been loving the brand jeah the
label they are I think in Australia
Brent and their products are so done
with actually wearing a shirt for them
right now this is like a really really
cute jacket I love Laura's boutique use
coach a store 10% off that is actually
my best friend's brand but they do have
a lot of really really cute stuff that
I've been wearing a lot recently there's
another brand that I've been wearing a
lot recently called Medi cow they are a
German brand and I actually just found
out that there's literally one girl who
runs the entire thing and the clothes
are so cute she means everything from
scratch if you guys want to go check it
out I will leave her stuff down below
she is so talented
actually maybe don't check her out
because then she won't have time to make
all my clothes but she was really good
she definitely deserves the support I've
also been working with a lot of
different designers out here and I like
to get costume
has made such as oh wow Brian horns the
guy who made all my Coachella looks and
literally slayed them is working on so
many cool things for you right now and I
am just so so so excited my bank account
is not because getting custom fashion is
ridiculous expensive but I'm definitely
a firm believer in paying people for
their work especially when it's custom
and really cool stuff like that and it's
just been really fun for me I really
like the world of fashion it's something
that I've been very very interested in
but I've never been very good at so I'm
definitely really excited to be working
on it a lot more and just be having
really cool outfits that I'm really
confident in and feel really proud of
because honestly not gonna lie it's
something that I struggle with a lot so
it's been a fun challenge for me and I'm
definitely looking forward to it a lot
sister Rhea asked does it annoy you
there's so many people on YouTube use
sister all the time now the same that I
get asked all the time and I don't think
I've ever actually addressed it on
camera but no matter what way you really
look at it no I don't mind it at all in
fact I actually really really love it
obviously it started off as like a
personal joke between me and my close
friends but when it came time to pick a
name for my fandom because I literally
hate the word fan more than anything in
the entire world sisters made sense
because it was already what I call my
best friends and I like to think of you
guys as a far more than fans and kind of
like a close family that we all have
together so it made sense and if people
want to call it their fans sisters too
that's super cute it just means we're
all one big happy you to a family I
think it's super super fun and then also
if you look at it from the other side as
well
it's literally a free promotion which
I'm definitely never gonna stray from at
this point we've kind of reinvented the
word sisters I'm gonna say it we read
about - the word sisters and it's how to
become like a meme at this point which I
am so down for now a lot of my being on
social media has literally been like
turning myself into a meme and then
profiting off at the hate so that's
definitely I'd like to do and sisters
has kind of become one of those memes at
this point and now I'm known for being
hi sisters and I live for us so
everybody should say sisters all they
want
I do wanna add a little bit more of a
pop just like how Mitchell did on his
vision to look with some sister glitters
so I'm gonna mix together a few at
different once it's just a white
translucent one this one is like a blue
a green reflex steel type of one then
I'm gonna add in a few of these little
holographic star glitters as well
right on top of the land
[Music]
for a lot of thing I'm gonna use the new
bounds I'm a dragon Lee Lash's
these are definitely much bolder and
bigger than what I usually would wear
for a lily lash Miami but I feel like
these will definitely match the look of
really really well today and they
survived me of the style that all the UK
artists use I have not been more proud
and more excited for an eyeshadow look
in a very very long time so I'm gonna go
ahead and do the other one on camera
quickly and I'll be right back to finish
off the rest of the look and answer a
few more juicy scissor questions whoo
all right sisters we are back that took
me a hot minute to mirror this I
overtook this one but I think we got
them pretty close I am literally in love
with this look and I'm so excited to
finish it I want to take selfies right
now so let's go ahead and move on and
finish up next up is obviously gonna be
the glow but before we do that I think I
want to answer one last question from
you guys so let's go ahead and see this
one is from sister Johan and he said
tells the story of you getting caught
tickling your pickle oh my god do I want
to tell the story right now this they
were before starting the story to my
younger audience out there especially
parents if you're watching with your
children um hi mom and dad by the way
that's awesome that you guys watch with
your kids hello you rock best parents
ever this story is not exactly the most
PG you guys know you have a very very
family-friendly channel I will do my
best to kind of you out certain words
and tell the story in the best way
possible it does however have a very
very important message behind it so
choosing your own well I'm telling you
right now this may be inappropriate but
you already saw most of the makeup look
if you want to click off because you
don't want to hear this I don't blame
you but let's jump into the story if
you've been a longtime subscriber in
mind any watch a lot of my videos I've
alluded to the fact a few times here and
there that I may or may not have been
caught when I was younger doing my
business and if you've also been a
longtime subscriber you would know that
I've never actually told my coming-out
story because I've said that there was
legal problems with it I didn't know if
I could really tell them without getting
in trouble and what people don't know is
that those two stories are actually the
same story
when I was younger I think and around
sixth grade I was 12 years old at the
time I was
hormonal I had just gone through puberty
and just like every other boy I was
going through that stage of life clearly
at this point in my own head I had
figured out that okay I was not exactly
interested in the sisters and was
definitely done for the brothers so here
we go you guys know that I've definitely
always been very very active on social
media and at this time period I was
active on tumblr at the time there was a
lot of really really famous bloggers
that I loved and looked up to and one
website that all these famous bloggers
would always go on to meet their fans
was called omegle which is an online
chatroom
I remember gonna make literally all the
time and sitting there for hours
clicking through different strangers
trying to find at different famous
bloggers that I really really loved and
wanted to meet and just wanted to talk
to you for a few short seconds and
ironically enough I don't think I ever
once met anybody who I was looking for
because there was always a thousands of
thousands and thousands people online
but when they're scrolling through
strangers video cameras on an anonymous
live video cam website I'm sure you can
imagine what I started to come across as
a hormonal twelve-year-old thinking
about this is making me want to die I
quickly realized that although a lot of
people on tumblr we're using the site to
meet their fans and meet new friends
that a lot of people were using omegle
for different purposes and through
realizing this I also started using home
Agel for different purposes if you get
what I'm putting on the table here oh my
god
so me and sister-in are three years
apart and the way the school system was
divided is we had elementary school
middle school and high school so during
middle school when I was in sixth grade
and this is all going on he was still in
elementary school meeting every single
day I would have an extra guarantee one
hour from when I got off the bus at home
to when he would get off the bus at home
since he was coming from a different
school once I kind of figured out the
schedule and how to really finesse the
whole situation the visits to omegle
became more and more frequent until they
were literally a daily occurrence which
thinking about it now is literally so
repulsive but at the time I'm not even
gonna lie I was definitely like addicted
to it it was a fun challenge for me
which is so like psychotic to think
about but I was 12 I was very very
hormonal I was going through puberty and
that's why I'm telling this story now
because obviously it's a very very
serious and scary thing that I don't
want any of you guys to go through so
snob also as well very very important
thing to know I was a minor at the time
I was obviously at 12 years old but I
never once ever ever ever ever ever got
naked on camera and to this day I have
still never sent a Dickey D Piketty
that's for personal reasons but every
single time it would always be a guy who
was above age doing his business and
then when he would ask me to take my
clothes I thought oh he's be like oh my
camera's broken I don't know what's
going on I won't turn on what the heck
this is so where this has never happened
before so I could avoid obviously taking
my clothes off which I did not want to
do and do not want to blind anybody with
and also of course breaking the law so
although this is a horrible idea I did
not break any laws which is great
obviously but once again still please do
not do this literally ever anyways like
I was saying this became a very very
routine I was doing this all the time
and I was getting very very good at it
until one night that will go down in
history forever setting the scene it was
probably about 9:10 p.m. on a school
night one night Ian was already asleep
because he was much younger than I was
and my mom was already asleep as well
because she always was a bad very very
early for some reason so the only people
wake in the house for myself and my dad
and my dad always would chill in his
living room watching football or
watching the news super super late at
night every single night and his living
room was right below my bedroom in our
house I remember very very vividly I was
writing an essay for a history class
that I absolutely hate it and in the
middle of it I took a break to do my
business so I went on to omegle calm
started searching through people
eventually found someone and there we go
things got started and all of a sudden
in the middle of my business
tickling the pickle my door slams open
and there's my father in the doorway
looking at very concerned and there is
me standing right in front of my
computer which is in the same line of
view as my door
butt-naked with the screen lit up right
in front of me and all he said was you
need to turn that off and go to bed
right now
so I said got it sir good night love you
the most and I read my little naked butt
into my bed and shut my eyes and cry
myself to sleep the next morning I woke
up one downstairs for breakfast took a
shower and
nothing happened nothing was different
my dad did not look at me different my
mom did not know what was going on I
said yeah and I was so confused and also
obviously like literally having a panic
attack the entire day of freaking out
wondering what was gonna go on did he
see anything clearly he saw something of
mine but did he see anything on the
computer screen so I was freaking out
all day long said nothing go to school
all day long awesome and periods nothing
no texts nada obviously I know that
something is going to go down and
they're going to say something but I
didn't know when I didn't know what they
were going to do and I I just didn't
know another time I was so freaked out
and I was so nervous than when I got
home from school that day I didn't even
go upstairs I literally Santos's that I
think I was like drawing a picture or
something
you guys don't used to draw all the time
was all my favorite hobbies that was one
of the only things that I could do
before I really had makeup to kind of
escape and to just really focus on my
creativity and love the outside world go
away because at that moment I just
wanted to disappear into a hole and
never come out
well behold when both my parents get
home they say sister James well I was
just changed at the time but James we
need to talk please come with us
upstairs and instantly as soon as I
walked upstairs to them and said that my
bed and started talking I realized oh my
god this entire time I've been so
nervous that I have not touched my
computer since last night when I jumped
from my computer chair 70 feet across my
bedroom straight into my bed butt-naked
meaning I did not clear my internet
history so sitting there talking to them
the entire time I was already freaking
out but now I'm really freaking out
because I'm realizing oh my god if my
dad did not see anything now he's really
gonna see something so of course the
first thing that comes out of their
mouth is we would love to check your
internet history my heart literally sunk
faster than the Titanic and that walk
from my bed over to the computer
turning on typing in my password going
to Google Chrome opening the internet
history and it being right there right
at the top was probably the hardest 10
seconds of my entire life I can
literally see the disappointment in my
parents face and they clicked on omegle
and there was the blog website and what
made it even worse that I literally
forgot about once again on the front
pages you can put an intro
of the different topics that you'd want
to talk about so for example soccer
football webkinz Club Penguin at the
time or the names of 12 and 13 year old
bloggers that I was trying to find but
now instead right there on the front
page was about a ten word list
consisting of gay by men boys and woo
there was the closet door was flung open
and outran me unintentionally I remember
Hensley started balling as any child
would because I was obviously
embarrassed that they caught me doing
this but also now because I was out of
the closet and in this current moment I
was not exactly ready to fly myself out
like that but thinking about it now I'm
actually kind of thankful that this did
happen as crazy as that sounds because
the conversation after is probably one
of the coolest conversation I've ever
had at my parents in my entire life I
love them the most we've always been
very very close with this conversation
meant a lot to me because instead of
freaking out about me being gay and my
dad is very very Catholic as well so
that was something that I was super
super scared about the conversation was
very obviously more tailored towards
please don't do this this is so
dangerous there were predators out there
like you are putting yourself at such a
major risk and we don't want to see you
either get in trouble or get hurt and
I'm so thankful for that because from
that day on I never once did it again
and I've always been so careful about
that I've always been a very very huge
advocate for myself and my friends about
online pornography and chat rooms like
that but whoo that moment of my life is
probably one of these scariest things
that I've ever had a deal with it was so
horrifying it was embarrassing it was
sad it was just a lot of emotions going
on at one time and I'm so thankful to my
parents hilda and the way that they did
but yeah that's how I got caught doing
my business on a chatroom with the
camera off thank God and that is also
how I came out of the closet to my
parents I literally cannot believe I
just said this all in a video I had
never told this story publicly ever once
in my entire life but I think that this
does have a very important message
behind it obviously it was very very
embarrassing at the time and thank God
we my family can laugh about it now
several several years later dad I love
you the most
tell you how to see that but I think
this story does have a very very very
important message behind of Internet
safety parents and kids if you guys are
still watching this through all of it
congratulations
love you
please be careful as to what you do
online please do not send risky pictures
to anybody if you have text via snapchat
via any app that is currently popular
right now it is so incredibly dangerous
you never know what they're doing with
that picture that you get screenshot it
they could scream record they could take
a picture even though their phone so
it's on the deal and you would never
ever ever know until it comes back ten
years later as blackmail and it's just
so dangerous and so so so stupid you
never know who's watching you never know
who's recording you never know what
people's true intentions are there are
some really really really crappy people
out there and please learn from your
mistakes it's dangerous and it's very
very embarrassing if you get caught so
don't do that and story time complete
whoo
and last but finally not least after
filming this for four hours and it's
been a long time since I've been this
obsessed with the makeup look on my face
so I definitely need to set it and lock
it in place for the rest of the night so
I'm gonna grab the screen to Navy eye
makeup finishing spray and get wake up a
hobby spreads all over to make sure I am
locked in and ready just go you guys all
this is my all-time favorite settings
right and you can use code James for
money off your purchase I think it's
like 25% which is pretty low so go check
it out I'll raise this is that is
definitely enough questions for today
and I think that is the finished look as
well oh my god I absolutely love how
this turned out I feel so beautiful I
love the contest between at the bright
blue and the kind of burnt orange ready
shades the glitter I don't ever wear
glitter I don't ever wear big lashes
this just feels really really dope it's
something I haven't done in a while
and I love this thank you once again to
Mitchell for inspiring me today oh I
love this makeup look at economic to
take selfies right now I really hope you
guys enjoyed this makeup look and this
Q&A it's today and you learned a little
bit more about me I mean I think you
definitely did probably a little bit too
much but you know what you guys know I
definitely like to keep you very very
close and now you know a bigger secret
and my most embarrassing moment ever so
you're welcome
you better give this video a big thumbs
up because just give the video a thumbs
up please if you like to follow me on my
makeup trend you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both the
same Charles there i snapchat for more
well hasn't seen sighs I miss James
Charles that extra ass after Charles
this video is sister shadow echo sister
Kayleigh
thank you so much rated froy's falling
at support you know I love you so so so
much and then you like to be the next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
raise to reach a Twitter link so they go
live on it Twitter
also sister shadow goes to my dad for
everything that he went through that
night love you scam alright guys thank
you for watching I love you and I will
see you in the next one five
[Music]