hi sisters James Charlton and welcome
back to my youtube channel I'm gonna
make this intro short and sweet and good
and fresh because I want to jump right
into today's video we're doing something
that I truly never in literally a
billion years could have ever imagined
me doing and judge about the title you
already know what that is I am so beyond
excited and grateful to tell you that we
have been invited to the 2019 Met Gala
in case you're not familiar with the Met
Gala it is pretty much the biggest and
also most important event in the fashion
industry it is held every single year on
the first Monday in May in New York at
the Metropolitan Museum of Art's and it
is a fundraiser for their costume
Institute there's the new theme being
found every single year and all the
major designers all paris celebrities or
influential people to dress them for the
red carpet and create iconic moments in
fashion history and somehow by a miracle
i have been invited as I mentioned
before everyone on the carpet is dressed
by a major designer and this Here I am
beyond excited to tell you that I was
invited by Alexander Wang literally my
favorite designers of all time the MEK
Mela is in less than one month from
today which is not a whole lot of time
to prepare and get myself ready I'm not
gonna lie I am extremely extremely
nervous I've never done anything like
this before I don't even like know
what's gonna happen is the only my first
time experiencing this but I am very
very grateful because I would not be
experiencing this if it were not for you
guys and because of that I would like
all of you to experience it with me in
today's video we're doing something that
has never been done before and that is
documenting the behind-the-scenes
process of what it actually takes to get
Met Gala ready we're about to hop on a
flight in a little bit to head to New
York for our first official meeting with
the Alexander writing team in our first
fitting we're gonna put together our
outfit we're gonna go to our dinner
together we're gonna get dressed we're
gonna get ready in full glam of course
and I'm gonna try to film as much of the
event as I possibly can I am beyond
nervous but most importantly I am so
grateful for this opportunity to not
only attend such an iconic event like
the Met Gala but also learn a whole lot
more and show you guys about an industry
that I am a super passionate about let's
go
I have a phone charger my phone and a
water bottle no bad we're gonna be a
nerd for literally eight hours why him
I better sleep on this plane I swear to
God and then we get in it and relief
this is gonna be the quickest trip over
my entire life I've also be the most
excited
[Music]
all right sisters we are officially here
in New York it's currently 24 right here
- so yeah this is first you're going to
the back alley and I'm not colliding I
am very very nice like mortified I'm
doing this mostly because like YouTube
is such a good new platform in the
digital space and there's not that much
respect especially in Jerusalem media
for youtubers we honestly get like we're
gonna find a lot so the fact that like
you're willing to work with me for the
back gala and invite me is really an
honor so before even like it's right I'm
just gonna say thank you because it gets
really really cool and one thing that I
was working on in my videos is deleting
that boundary and really making effort
to show like youtubers honoring people
who are business people anyone
about the brand I'm always I'd love to
be able to survive yeah it's really kind
of you know just experiment and take
this is my things that other people you
know you got ready for I think that you
know when this opportunity came up and
also you know what Derek and everyone
you know talking about like of course on
youtubes gonna be making it yeah
excitement there was just something
really exciting so I'll be at the table
I probably say the scariest part of the
red carpet oh hey you know once you get
past the red carpet it's just plain good
together was just like a hat playing
like running around the Britain actually
to be honest no one's really even eating
the city after see might've just kind of
like socializing say hi to people so but
the carpet is pretty I mean every year
it's still like I can't like crazy
nerves or anyone I feel like after
they're like just kind of smelling at
you it's a really fun and I'm really
excited for you and I think I get the
nerves to whenever like you know when I
bring new people you know that a lot of
the times my dates have been like the
first time like when I brought a
humorous or first-time are yeah Kristen
Wiig was our first time and so they you
know to kind of have me ignite that kind
of you know energy is just oh that's why
I say it once again thank you
I'm fell beyond excited for that
opportunity and they honestly being able
to solve it is super exciting too
because people don't get to see this
stuff happen
so like they're gonna fall yeah you're
getting the full guidance process what's
we're trying to follow the story so
that's it
[Music]
Oh
[Laughter]
this already
[Music]
like what do you like
you
[Music]
all right you guys we just finished our
dinner hours in front of Derek's house
and I'm just a very very special sister
guests will be here today also Rosie
huntington-whiteley legendary model and
we just found out they were all going
yogurt we just now know what I first of
all I'm so excited because I was already
nervous to begin with but knowing that
I'm going with youtubers defile
understand so much families may feel a
lot better
first of all it's a lot less
nerve-wracking this is our first time I
know
so where the news lives up for Lily and
I you kind of like broke the wall down
last year first youtuber to be at the go
thank you what was like that whole
experience what tell us everything so we
prepare go up the stairs the one at a
time it's not as big as a ton it's very
little this mother like 116 stairs yes
it was like a few steps pendens way to
sort of splat yeah no it looks mad looks
right especially when like Rihanna's
there with like a wide lens you don't
like whoa this is big you aren't there
just to watch you and appreciate you and
empower you you're there because you're
there you don't even baby so you've been
working hard
celebrate yourselves at this moment yeah
thanks well I think that's what's really
exciting - it's like obviously all of us
I feel like on our platforms are really
out of that about like working really
hard trying to take different
opportunities that may be outside of the
YouTube world obviously and I just spent
a competent for YouTube and the business
side of saying that's the million times
so like it's really exciting that that
there you must get to be half okay so
for Lily and Liza I don't know what does
it mean for you guys
I guess Rosa do this we can see here in
respective what does it mean for like us
as youtubers to be in my because this is
a very special moment I think those are
you to the sauce you better go yeah it
was nerve-wracking because I was not
myself but it's Sun comforting to have
like like that's a it's a breaking
moment like for social media like I
think like social media has been so
heavily incorporated into this year
because they realize the value that it
brings you I'm like everybody's talking
about it there's reviews like it's so
fine so to be able to have us there
we're representing a community that has
been like not undermine but has been
undermined just slowly means that
they're getting up yeah
by God is already in existence one of
the things that I am most scared about
because I will about like I am
definitely my comments get to me a lot
and I know and this talk to save I know
the secretary shell public coverage are
there going to be pictures being like
some previous living around with two
hundred thousand by approximately who
like who invited James Charles like who
like each other's on to the carb and I'm
trying to brace myself for it because I
think you have every right to be this so
much so like the theme is so you and I
think like everything that you guys have
built and it's exactly what Billy said
it's about the world Pride weekend you
know you're second there's so much to
embrace about you and so much like every
reason that you guys should be them also
than some of the other people there's a
familiarity philosophically for a second
it's like you know this and I know it's
hard to implement but I know you know
this that the people that are saying who
let them in the carpet also people that
secretly want to be on the carpet
okay so you have to like know that when
you read that tweet you have to know
that this is not about weasel this
person yeah that's you know thanks but
there's nothing to do with you yeah
so one thing bad what you literally has
nothing to do with you and everything
but someone else thinks of you smelly no
business yes how they speak of you is
what speaks of them when it's true
that's who they are I mean this is just
such a special moment for all of us and
I just want to be able to enjoy it and
this was great advice
[Applause]
good morning you guys it is Monday May 6
2019 the first Monday in May today
yessum that gala and we're about to get
ready um I went to bed last night and
literally 4:00 in the morning I could
not fall asleep and I ended up waking up
today at noon noon I'm not done that
since I was already in like eighth grade
so feels good to be well-rested I feel
like I am ready to conquer this day but
I don't have a few hours to get ready
now so we're going to sit down and get
clam as you can see we're already
running into our first dilemma here with
my alpha that you guys clearly saw I
don't really have a shirt on underneath
the chainmail I'm gonna be wearing
meaning my foundation has to match
perfectly to my body and we already know
it's not going to try to get as close as
possible I just went ahead and swatch a
few of the different ones that I brought
with me and none of them are really
matching so don't really know what to do
oh this one from Dior match is really
really really well on the neck like it
almost as like blending in did you are
air flash but on my face looks a little
light like pasty and pay off whereas
this one on my face I feel like it's
looking a little bit more good or just
to face in this a dusty shell but on my
neck it looks a little bit not good
we're just gonna blend it really far
down really far down and hope that it
works or they can like mix the two them
together I'm very nervous as you can
tell I'm really very talking on camera i
ah I cannot believe that today's
actually happening this is so crazy and
so wild this would look good
here's my seashell oh yeah okay so I'm
just gonna blow the sand all over it you
guys have seen me do my base pertain
literally a million times this is not
going to like an in-depth makeup
tutorial I just want to like get glam
and kind of asked you I need to blend it
up into my hair as well so go ahead and
blend this down the neck I'm not really
sure where I want to blend my foundation
to the band and it's gonna come like I'm
doing that but see now this looks way
too dark
why am I facing body eight different
colors oh I have to blend it so far
grandpa phonation it back into here
oh my look at that haha I'm gonna grab
some do your air flash we're just gonna
leave blood mist and how'd it get your
body and face be the same color like
asking for a friend how do you do that
like what precautions do you have to
take because like this is ridic
Oh what about the bat oh and he does
blend it I'm like oh I like upper back
everybody please welcome Louis my
amazing editor and videographer and also
foundation blender I think this is
pretty London
finally it is concealer time okay I'm
pretty happy with how my face is looking
right now honestly think this is kind of
good trash let's go ahead and accept us
in place
I'm powdered and literally everything in
existence because I don't want to sweat
anything off but then again it's like
kind of cold in New York right now it's
not fully summertime yet and also I have
no shirt on underneath the chainmail so
I'm gonna be freezing I'm not gonna grab
my crotch or cat and search literally on
my face I am very nervous for this as
you can tell by me not talking which is
a rare sight for a James Rollins YouTube
video as much as I'm so excited and
blessed and thankful and grateful and
pumped to be there there's still a part
of me that literally feels like I just
started doing all this yesterday and
that I'm still nobody just a random kid
living in the middle of New York with
very little friends and just working
hard in school and it feels so surreal
this is actually like my life and then
I'm getting invited to these favorite
things and then I get to walk red
carpets with like celebrities that I've
looked up to and watched and I was a
little kid so this is really really
weird I was dealing back and forth with
a few celebrities that are friends with
that I know have gone for several years
and of course nobody's getting away the
full details of their outfits but what
I've heard is that everyone is like
going so crazy and like I want to go so
crazy but I'm like so scared
ah I'm usually never my head about
anything like I'd really really don't
get nervous but I feel like this is such
just a crazy thing I'm sister scarran
I'm sister scarran but you know what
it's gonna be fun day I think my talk
last night at dinner was like so
incredible with Liza and lily and Rosie
and Susan and I really feel like they
helped me call my nerves so much about
the whole event like if I was to walk
out of that chair and go right to the
gala
it would've been fine but now I've had
like 12 hours to sleep on it and get
back into my head and continue thinking
it's a harsh
nose contour oh wow all right you guys
I'm gonna go into my brows quickly
off-camera with my Anasazi eyebrow
products as always and I'll be right
back to start off the eye makeup so now
it's time for the eye makeup which like
everything else I'm a little bit
stressed about for a few different
reasons if you guys saw in the first
thing Alexander suggested that he wanted
to see me in a black smokey eye for a
potential makeup look to pair with the
Wardrobe now if you look through my
Instagram you would notice that I don't
really do black smokey eyes really ever
I don't really putting block in my
waterlines because it kind of irritates
them sometimes and I must prefer a nude
or white to really open them up and make
my eyes appear bigger it's just like the
look that I am really used to so this is
gonna be a little bit different for me
last night when I got home from the
party I did a kind of play on some
makeup and I experiment it I did a black
smoky eye on one eye and then kind of
like a rainbow splatter paint look on
the other eye too soon as this year's
theme is camp and it's very extravagant
and outside of the box and I proposed at
Alexander and he said no still on the
black smokey eye and I definitely wanna
respect his wishes and make sure that my
whole look is part of his vision and
also to the whole like theme of camp is
outside of the box and for me as someone
who does extravagant makeup ups all the
time a black smoky eye kind of is
outside of my box in a very very weird
way so it might work fingers crossed
I'm first gonna go ahead and grab a
punch me at the cool tonot brothel is
how it on a fluffy brush and start
running this in the crease just to lay
down a little bit of a transition color
and then I'm just gonna grab a tea with
an AB 514 brush and use us to deepen up
the crease make sure that's nice and
blend it out with a little bit more
punch me using an Emma 508 brush I'm
just going to sketch out a line I'm just
talking some spooky onto my lash line oh
yeah look at this
I like this I'm gonna chuck some block
into the lower waterline and then using
the littlest bit of spooky and tea mixed
together I'm just going to very very
lightly blend out that lower lash line
I'm not evenly putting on lower lash
line shadow it's really just like
setting that liner in place I'm just
gonna highlight the problem using a
little bit of face and ring light mixed
together this is very like a Kim Chi nut
gone last year inspired a good smokey
liner moment not intentional but loved
camera already what happened
maybe a little black salon moment this
is very like sleek sultry this is
outside of my box that is absolutely for
sure I do like this though I think it
was kind of good and fresh and I'm glad
that I with Alexander session okay
flashes time I'm gonna gonna face a
quick sprint of my amore be prepping set
settings right just walk in all odor
don't got me a little bit of face on my
m5 before gonna grab my normal color top
lip liner
lippy I really hope you guys know this
super quick to get ready with me I would
never normally do a lot like this but I
truly feel so beautiful and so sunny
looking to me right now like Hello I
don't think right right now it's just
like this black smokey liner we have
like a little bit of lightness on but
Lin a little bit of more definition in
the crease super sultry kind of ended up
being inspired by Kim and makeup by
Mario unintentionally loved them the
absolute most and love this makeup hook
the obstacles and I hope you guys liked
it too but this video is not yet over
because now I have to go get dressed and
actually go there's I'm running very
late right now so do you like it oh
thank you sir I think this is my invite
look the Costume Institute the
Metropolitan Museum of Art 1000 Fifth
Avenue Oh should I open it the
Metropolitan Museum of Art Costume
Institute benefit co-chairs Lady Gaga
Alessandra Michelle Harry Styles Serena
Williams and Anna Wintour the Queen
herself requests the pleasure of your
company at a preview and dinner to
celebrate the opening of the exhibit
Camp notes on fashion Monday the 6th of
May okay we have a little look from
Derrick as well dear James let's have a
man ball get it but I'm just gonna get
dressed now funny
pants on well that woman so easily
[Music]
already fantasy officially all dressed
from head to toe in full-on Alexander
Wang and I have never felt so glamorous
and so sexy and sultry I'm headed over
to the party with Ellen sander and a few
other guests that you're going with and
it's going to be a wonderful night come
along okay you guys are especially on
the way to the back table right now I
know this is an awful angle I can't
really accept my arm any further without
breaking any safety pins so you don't
have to do with that I'm so nervous
right now
my arm is literally shaking he's right
if this footage is completely unstable
all right I'm stable right now I'm oh my
god I don't really get nervous for these
type of things literally ever but I
don't know why like this is just so
intense to me is the look that I would
never do nails that I would never do an
outfit that I would never do but I feel
really beautiful and I'm just really
excited to see a bunch of amazing people
and hopefully like we talked about last
night this is a really amazing step
forward for youtubers in the community
and they're definitely gonna be hate
comments and some negativity after this
but you know what just like Lily aligns
we're talking about it's about breaking
the boundaries and dealing with that and
making it easier for the future people
to come after we burn this Lily how are
you feeling that your dress is taking up
houses also because this wouldn't fit
into a car but also just like I'm taking
up so much space and everyone's being so
kind
well you look beautiful Susan is a real
sister Susan that is my sister and you
said this dress will not go into puddle
and she bent down she sister Susan as a
queen Alessia how are you feeling feel
good I feel the same way I feel like I'm
also at the second half of this annoying
yeah cloud also not only and how are you
feeling look at maneuvering in different
ways tonight yeah James how are you
feeling I'm still nervous but I feel
like I look as we get closer I really
think I have to do it yeah I know I'm
just be really happy while doing it
beautifly waiter now I have a big very
careful humming so notice your safety
pins come on done they wouldn't hurt
I'll be sister stopped yeah it's part of
the Brown's dinner tonight
of a safety pin bus everybody here is
ever so we're all
and the value
all right you guys either did this vlog
style it is currently 3:00 in the
morning and I have a plan to catch it
about three hours from now and my entire
team is asleep I literally just got back
about to take Liam tablets so much fun
oh my god you guys literally walking up
to the red carpet was one of these
scariest things that I've ever done in
my entire life but as soon as I got to
the top of those stairs and got to shake
the hands of Anna Wintour Lady Gaga
three Styles three Williams and
Alessandro I was like so called and
sodas ready to enjoy the night and that
experience was one that I will literally
never forget oh my god Alessia Cara and
Haley Bieber at my table and they were
so so kind I walked in with Halsey I
can't tell her how much of them I was up
her and but that you guys always comment
saying that I look alike which was so so
so funny I met Sean for the first time
we got a sister selfie together he was
so so sweet and he had some really kind
of words of encouragement for me and
being there because I was really really
nervous
Katy Perry token said hi I was talking
to Kim Kylie kendall and Kris for quite
a while I met my Lee for the first time
ever I got to tell her how much I loved
her and that her concert was the first
one I ever wanted to it was so so so
insane and hopefully we'll be able to do
a video together sometime soon it was
just a very very fun and welcoming
community people and I was scared at
first but they made me feel right at
home
and I'm just very very grateful for this
opportunity I want to say thank you to
all of you guys for subscribing and
following me and watching my videos over
the past few years I never in a million
years thought that I'd ever be invited
to the Met Ball but it's literally
because of you guys and I wanted to
thank you to youtube for inviting me and
Alexander buying it for addressing me
and though an Anna Wintour for approving
me to become below there's definitely
quite the mixed reaction on social media
I was just reading a few comments and
decided to click off they don't want to
read any negativity regardless like
Eliza lily and I were all talking about
we knew this is gonna be a contour
and we knew now Frodo is gonna be happy
about it but I think this is such an
amazing step in the right direction for
influence or representation in media and
I'm so honored and excited to be a
catalyst and be someone who is pushing
for that and can really paved the way
for influencers who come after me I
think that of the way out for the city
you guys thank you so so so much for
watching if you liked it please don't
forget to give a big thumbs up down
below and show your love and war and it
really means so so so much to me and
also click that big red subscribe button
and come join disinter head we're 16 a
million sister saw absolutely love to
have you join the family if you like to
follow me I become truly involved in
circum and Twitter at their voltage to
Charles the way step check for pregnancy
myself it seems Charleston the
picturesque after Charles all the
reuleaux I will finally be going on tour
to 24 different cities all around the
United States if you want to get tickets
oh forget to check out sisters Josh
tor.com all right you guys I'm gonna
want this makeup up and go straight to
bed
thank you so much for watching I love
you and I'll see you in next one
[Music]