hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel oh my
god you guys for today's video I have
actually really really excited and I
just wanted to write in because today's
video is literally one of the most
requested comments from you guys
probably ever in the history of this
channel and I think I know why -
obviously you guys know I'd love to play
with makeup and it's my hobby and now
thanks to all you scissors it is my job
and I get to do it every single day but
I probably never would have fell into my
love for makeup had it not stem from my
love for art a few years ago when I was
younger I would come home from school
every single day and spend hours and
hours of my time trying portrait with
charcoal or pencils sketching in my
school notebooks or on my homework
drawing different painting and
scrapbooking literally you name it and I
was definitely trying to be a creative
in some way shape or form the toilet of
my palette that it's not really so
obviously is unleash your inner artist
which I feel like has definitely
it and my makeup stylist as well at this
point you name it I pretty much painted
every single day on my face at this
point everything from skeletons and 3d
special effects for Halloween time Tori
what is't dripping down my skin - even
at the aurora borealis literally stocked
up right here on my forehead and that
brings me into today's brand new video
my love for art has definitely made a
very large impact on my life and
somebody also has an intense love for
art is Bob Ross if you know who Bob Ross
says he's an icon and a legend or EP
gone way too soon but he truly changed
the art industry because of the fact
that he would go on TV for like 30
minutes segments and create a beautiful
landscape painting but what was
different about it as they who's
actually taking the audience through the
painting step by step almost like a
regular tutorial if you really kind of
think about it Bob Ross was kind of like
the first-ever guru before being a guru
even really existed and he had an
immense love and talent for painting but
to most everyday people painting is very
very challenging and he brought his
knowledge and his skills on a public
platform which at the time was TV and
share that with the world and help
people at home learn how to be better
painters just like I kind of do with
makeup every single day so for today's
video after literally thousands and
thousands of you guys commenting and
asking for this I thought I would
finally give it a go and try following a
raus painting tutorial on my face super
quickly before we jump into the video
don't forget you guys this is one of the
last videos that my December it gave us
lays every single uploader in the month
of December to say thank you to you guys
I am giving away a more px James Charles
PR box including the palette and the
brush set assistance apparel artistry
logo hoodie it sold on everywhere and a
brand new 2018 MacBook Air all you have
to do to enter is make sure you follow
me on all my social media platforms
including my Instagram Twitter and
snapchat all the Millea right up here so
when I do a YouTube channel by clicking
that big red subscribe button down below
and come join The Sisterhood and finally
thumbs up this video as well as all my
other December uploads and leave a
comment down below all the official
rules and regulations will be in the
description box as well so make sure you
read all those for all the correct
information and so I don't get sister
sued good luck you guys
thank you again and without further ado
let's jump into the video all right so
I'm going through the Bob Ross YouTube
channel I really wanted to do something
like very wintry because tis the season
and I found that this wine which is
called a Bob Ross reflections of calm
season 31 episode 1 originally aired on
February at 22nd 1994 literally before I
was even born so let's see what Bob's
gonna have us paint today
[Music]
oh that's so mr. Ross I was in say my
lawyers gonna need to talk to him but
this was filmed over 20 years ago the
whole paintbrush idea hello my intro
uglisha in the artist that entire
campaign Wow
maybe his lawyer though should be
calling mine hello I'm Bob Ross and I'd
like to welcome you to series 31 of the
joy of paint he's so Paul first time
with us allow me to extend a personal
invitation for you dragged out your
crates and your brushes and paint on
with the seats he'll tell you but let's
start right off today they haven't run
all the colors across the screen that
you need titanium white while they're
doing that let me show you what I get
done up here hello blue today I'm using
an 18 by 20 process with this it's pre
strict and double primed and then I've
just covered the entire canvas with a
very thin coat of liquid white okay so
possibly painting on a canvas I'm gonna
be painting on my forehead and equally
as large surface a few months ago off my
Instagram I did an aurora borealis like
where I basically painted like the
entire aurora borealis and like a winter
scene on my forehead and then I didn't I
look inspired by it and I really really
loved how it turned out so I think first
two days did it I want to do it the same
thing to kind of keep the painting up
here and maybe even do an eye look using
the pallet after the sock just like a
little bonus tutorial moment I have my
colors picked out right here on Biddy's
makeup rubber flash palette and my
canvas is already primed with foundation
and lots of powder and concealer tell
you what let's turn up day with a little
two-inch brush okay you think I need a
two-inch brush should I be using like
paint brushes for this I didn't prepare
okay suppose it looks like it's like a
light blue so I'm gonna take that's not
gonna mix together some blues this could
use my hand as a palette because I don't
have a fancy bob ross actual pala that's
like a good phthalo blue right there
criss-cross strokes that easy and easy
all the way across the canvas
and work down by the way the paint is
continually mixing as a liquid white
that's already on the canvas and
automatically your sky will get lighter
and lighter as you work down toward the
horizon oh are you kidding me there let
the canvas work for you how the colors
in the paint he this is an entire sky in
literally one minute is this a prank I'm
using my crisscross techniques and
really just Criss crossing that for a
real one I wish I had a two inch brush I
feel like that really helped me out here
gonna really get this into the hairline
because we got to go all the height to
the top of the canvas he said as you go
down they'll be less and less product I
don't like how do I just crisscross
crisscross crisscross lots of wintertime
sky if I ever did to myself we're just
gonna move on but I suggest more than
the outside unison if everything works
just right it looked like a shrimpy of
lights just freakin right across your
water speaking it works great thank you
it's guy me in the beauty industry I
guess I'm gonna have some more of my
blue color I'm gonna pull it in from the
side like he said to keep your brush
straight but I'm working on a not
exactly flat canvas here so this is a
little boobs I just did what he said not
to do okay I'm already not following the
story I'll pull inwards sorry Bob
there's my eyebrow I think my water is
up too high right now I want a dark in
the corners on this I'm gonna take a
little pressure depression glue is much
much stronger than phthalo blue god it's
a beautiful blue
in the corners I'm just gonna have a
small amount of depression oh I love
okay great we finally get to add some
forehead contour this I have definitely
downpour I'm gonna grab a little bit of
blue and maybe a little bit of black
even two to really deepen that up and
make it look like my forehead is that
eight hundred miles long when the
painting is completely done these dark
corners will help lead the eye toward
the center of the painting come up a
little in the water - we don't want it
left out okay just blend that cover till
it's nice and smooth
I don't understand how he's doing it so
fast and so he's done like three paint
ROK's and there's a there's the entire
ocean like a what hello no it's not no
it's not yeah is it yes is it really
people be like James but back heck you
just did an entire snowflake in one
second on your face this is true I think
if I'd had a campus like this one be as
difficult I feel like it I really set
myself up for failure here doing this on
my own forehead adding some dimension to
the ocean like Bobby said oh my god my
hair why did I let you guys talk me into
that it's like are you serious oh my god
I'm gonna rip all my hair out this looks
he has it literally um like I can see
that the sky in the ocean on his already
and the mine like what is this I think
we should just keep going let's you know
let me be positive everything why
Stern's all gonna be on so this is where
I really had a good time it's cleaning
this little brush shake it off really is
the fun part this whole technique I'm
just gonna clean my brush you think I'm
makeup wipe but I do love beating the
devil out of certain things today let's
take crimson a little bit of black I
want to make up a little mountain in
here I want to make a a dark we'll have
endure like in color that's most
important how you load the knife take
cut across the paint and get a little
rule that lives right over the edge of
the knife okay let's go up in here right
here just decide where you think
little mountain who lives in your world
and drop dead painting is a very
individual effect we all see nature
through different eyes and that's the
way you should paint it all we're
looking for is the nice top edge we
could care less what's happening down
below our brush is good and dry a couple
liquid whites on the canvas you can
literally move color if you were working
on a drag canvas right now you'd be an
agony city that's a mountain you just be
the mountain and literally 30 seconds I
can't put like a knife on my face so I
guess I'm just gonna use like a flat
square brush which is like I mean sort
of as close I'm gonna get it right like
I don't know what else I would use well
no I think my water my oceans too tall I
don't have room to move out in anywhere
well now I have a blue forehead so what
am I gonna do now okay he literally just
like took the brush and like like what
honey he just like a little scrape down
there are you kidding me go back to the
solid dark color and come right up in
here that's Oh No hold on sweetie I'm
gonna need your paws oh my god here we
go another mountain okay so this one he
said he wanted to be more crimson than
blue so I'm gonna take some red and mix
it together here
always remember if you can see the
entire Mountain it's always more
distinct on the top but it is on the
bottom
okay Gus had missed and now we have
wonderful solution lays around a lot
across getting political okay so we okay
so when it comes like the bottom of
these rods he living stinking living
blends it away okay I need to pause it's
not good for this video he takes a dry
brush after that and just like goes in
and just like but lends it away how I
don't really know but we're gonna we
include me to figure it out yeah okay
this is not that bad like it's no Bob
Roth is for sure but it's not bad it's
fun to take and reflect a mountain right
into the water
Oh God now we're just looking for a
basic little recollection here exact we
first start is easier to take the canvas
off your easel and turn it upside down I
just basically repaint them just like we
did Howard's also draw the same mountain
again look I don't even know what I did
the first time
are you kidding me I'm so focused right
now it's not even funny I want to make
this like actually good like I don't I
don't I can't flop okay that's not that
bad oh my god you're kidding yeah now
we're gonna blend it out just like Bob
sad blend it upward so it's like a
little reflection in the water
[Music]
as possible
we'll have thick and firm response the
walls to go take a little white flag
little you know oh my god you had this
has got to be Jose
oh my god Hey look first her is applying
too much pressure like he literally just
like ran the paintbrush over the area
with like with a little bit of white and
they're all sons of mountain range I
think this is so sick though because you
guys know that I always loved art but
what I was really really good at was
drawing portraits with like pencil and
charcoal I still liked painting but I
really wasn't that great at it
so like learning these techniques is and
same because I never in a million years
would have tried this stuff but it's
like not as hard as I would have thought
making some gray on the back of my hand
I don't really know how to do this
exactly I mean not horrible honestly it
could be a lot better but like could be
a lot worse gonna touch up some areas
where I'm like having a little bit of
trouble here so when I do my aurora
borealis like a few months ago I
actually did do winter mountains in the
photo and they were white as opposed to
like a shadow and that one like we're
doing right now if you zoom it on the
photo there's like a lot of dimension in
detail in the mountains and I will say
I'm pretty proud of how they ended up
looking if like it did look pretty real
that's because I spent literally an hour
going in and drawing tiny little black
lines and dots to symbolize like
and shadows and the mountains what all I
had to do was scrape it on there with a
knife we'll just take it's a mountain
killer same amount covering sort of a
lavender would tap a little bit right
into that two-inch brush don't be afraid
of this brush because it's large it'll
do wonderful things
let's to say I don't don't be afraid to
this brush because it's large it'll do
wonderful things that it's my model in
life just not for brushes let's have
some fun some blue and some black put
some brown in it add some green what
yeah basically all your dark colors
there's one number six fan brush little
fan brushes are you kidding just put a
little bit of color right on the brush
it's all there is to it
gross fan versus living - nothing
there's literally no plant fan brushes
they're the dumbest brush little trees
little closer to this but living very
far away suddenly I need a fan brush to
make this little grass he had like a
Gotha we pull this up he had like a
green and like some dark mess okay we're
gonna put that like over here
I'm gonna use like a little liner brush
maybe I got some more dimension oh
that's the shoreline this is crazy like
oh my god are you serious so a little
bit of white and I notice how he when he
was like playing around with the colors
he like kind of like let them be messy
so almost when he puts them on they're
like it kept some of that dimension
maybe that's the technique that I'm
messing up a little bit is that like I'm
trying too hard to make it look perfect
that doesn't exactly work I think it's
totally a lot more than just that
technique that I'm messing up just
cut in a little water line if you put a
little too much liquid white on there
and you think it's a little too strong
just rub it it will just be absorbed
into the color it'll go away he's such a
good teacher that's what I will say too
is like everything that he's doing he
makes it look so easy
but you actually get to watch him and do
the entire thing I suppose that I'm just
like cutting to the finished product
he's a little bit away to sketch in a
water line I mean honestly like not
horrible
like not great but still not horrible we
need to figure out hope we're gonna put
in here so let's take some pression blue
set green crimson brown here's old
two-inch brush we'll take him let's just
block in some areas we're gonna have a
big tree that lives right here this is
sort of your bravery test after you
worked so hard to put in all those
gorgeous things when you come up here
some crazy fuzzy haired guy says we did
a big tree right over the top of air and
I already listed a tree once again he
just painted it an entire tree in 30
seconds so I have my little two-inch
brush I'm gonna put that over here cuz
this is where the tree should go oh so
now we've had a wall because um that's
not a tree and anyways like not even
close to like everything else is like
okay this is like Bob like that's a blob
of paint I don't know how he did that I
doesn't take advantage of what happens
we call those accidents and they can be
your best friend
oh my literal God he isn't because right
going down there those are trees and
those are trees in the reflection
you're kidding huh oh my god this is too
challenging for me I also set myself up
for failure I doing this on my own face
but let's put some freakin trees in here
what are you kidding
how does he do that I mean it could be
worse maybe if I use like a little bit
like more of like a fluffy brush as
opposed like a pencil brush like this
will work cause it
like all that texture no that did not do
anything maybe something like this it's
like a literally like a rough that
actually literally hurts yes this is a
horse right underneath that we need a
reflection is the treatments right here
we'll put some highlight I'm so sure
this one lives a little closer to us so
we can make out a little more oh my god
that's an entire poetry oh my god no
okay so no oh he put a tree like right
here-ish I'm just like stifling this on
for a real one I'm hoping that it looks
good
that looks so dumb are you kidding me
how did he do that no I'm annoyed
because they actually wanted this to
look good and it's not looking a good or
Frosch there's your freaking pine trees
in the forefront Bob what the oh I don't
understand how he does this so quickly
that'll snatch it right up are you
kidding Bob Ross is not a superstar
beauty guru Wow Bob Lois is really
coming from prayin today mixing together
green and yellow on the back of the hand
the little palette here I really thought
I was gonna be okay at this I am not
realizing that these trees are forming a
separate island to overlap the water and
I did not get that memo before oh no
like Bob said you know we get to choose
where we want to put our things in our
world so these trees are going in front
they're loving their grass area right
here taking this into my own hands for a
second you know we're just putting the
grass right here we're dragging that
brush upwards to create the appearance
of grass just like Bob said Bob sweetie
I am so sorry it just looks like he's
like painting maybe Bob Ross has Mother
Nature conspiracy theory he just paints
it in there
well now I feel stupid I messed us all
treat lives okay back to the victory
craze that's the beauty of pain yes you
really don't have to know exactly where
everything's at we Thomas works trust me
I know okay so I'm gonna go back to this
and I'm gonna hide away my mistakes by
using lots of dark colors and making
this tree a little bit more tree like so
let's make this a tree and it goes all
the way down just like Bob said that is
the worst of all time are you kidding me
[Music]
you can put this right on here oh my god
are you love me just okay so I think
before we move on to the next step I
want to pause for a second actually move
away from the tutorial and fix a mistake
that I made early on which was putting
the lighter mountain-like on the edge as
opposed to in the middle so we have this
like kind of entire area on my forehead
a completely blank so I think I want to
try to do another big tree over here
since I butchered this one so badly just
to one fix it a little bit and make it a
more composed to painting but also to it
to get a little more practice then so if
I put it like over here just like
sketching in I was like little thing
with my number two brush that looks
literally already a million times better
than the first one okay love that love
me making progress next we added a
little bit of green landscape so I'm
gonna do that as well over here just
sketching it in not really caring
because it's our world and we get to
place the greenery wherever we want it
to be so I'm just gonna put it right
here kind of right underneath my eyebrow
sucks gonna take a little bit of that
landscape and we're just gonna blend it
downwards oh there's some on this side
too so taking some more yellow and green
for some dimension gonna stipple it
right on here ah slightly too yellow no
worries though
it's gonna take our 2 inch brush and
just dump right over top of that just
blend it away we have the liquid white
underneath so no worries I forgot to add
in my tree trunk with a little bit of
brown and a little bit of titanium white
before adding in the details let's do
that now
can't blame us let my mind know maybe a
little bit of white perhaps it's a birch
tree we get to choose it's our world
never gonna go back in and add some more
dimension discovering our little bit of
green and a little bit of yellow mixing
it together on the palate just stifling
it right on there
oh my god that's a tree I feel ready to
add some more like dimension into my
grass I feel like my grass is looking
slightly flat so I'm gonna grab some
yellow and some green just like the
trees and just go in and just like
slightly sniffle just like he said and
then lift it right up words just right
now that creates the illusion of grass
and that in the foreground of the
painting I'm acting like I know exactly
what I know but really they have no idea
great part of the tutorial I want to
show you an easy way of making a
fantastic effect one side only I'll put
in the light color so you get dark light
now watch it watch a little stone biz
right there and wherever you want these
are you just drop them in several little
stones put some little grass seed things
it brings it all together he makes it
look so easy oh my gosh it would put
just the indication of a little water
line here they're sort of bring it all
together
[Music]
I really hope you've enjoyed this I hope
you'll join us for no television series
from all of us here I'd like to wish you
happy painting
god bless my friend oh I guess we're
done
it was literally almost as if he was
like throwing the paint on the canvas
and it was just like working what's the
same that I've talked about my videos a
lot of times that like you shouldn't do
as an artist because it doesn't work
that way but like Bob Ross like is
magical and it is working totally for me
it isn't so much just happened I mean we
literally painted an entire mountain end
of like forest landscape on my freaking
forehead my hands palette as you can
tell it's covered with every color you
could possibly imagine and I really hope
you help us look turned out just as fun
I thought I'd clean up this palette
super quickly and take out my palette
and do a super quick and easy Bob Ross
inspired I look just to kind of pull the
whole face together let's get started
again I'm gonna prime my eyelids as
always using my morphe tab but one seven
three brush on my Mac painterly
paint-pot
grabby gonna add about four five six I'm
gonna dip into the shade of the dark
matte green and pack this in an outer V
shape and then with any excess I'm just
bringing that shade right into the
crease and then having a 10.33 are gonna
dip into a social blade in the bottom
left hand corner and use that to buff
out the edges first pocket light color
on there and then just using light
circular motions to diffuse not that
edge I pack a little bit of Daddy into
that outer corner mixing together a tiny
little bit of dotty and a little bit of
tea on a tan 506 as well I'm just gonna
use this to deepen off the outer V
grabbing a little bit of concealer and
an m12 four brush I'm going to quickly
cut the crease now on another I want to
for brush I'm gonna dip into the shader
wah I'm gonna give it a quick spritz of
some setting spray and I'm gonna pop
this shade right in the middle of the
crease and then just like always with
that either access shadow that's left on
the brush I'm just going to blend in
that edge so there's no harsh line on
that concrete with that same brush I'm
gonna grab a little bit of ring light
and give that a sprint up some setting
spray as well and we're gonna pop that
in the inner corner and overlap it right
over top that guac to make kind of like
an ombre metallic shade dipping into a
tiny bit of it be and I'm gonna pal
in the inner corner gotta highlight my
inner corners with the yellow just like
Bob Ross dead with his trees for the
lower lofts I'm gonna grab a little bit
of a cola and pack this right up against
the lash line oh good it's happen to
both the playground and a little bit of
brother to kind of make a more phthalo
blue type of mixture if you will and use
that to buff out a little bit of cola
and finally to finish off the side like
I'm just gonna grab the next vivid
bright light yellow liner and use this
to cut the crease gonna quickly curl my
lashes and pop on a little bit of Mac
extended play mascara and then finally
popping on it Lily lost in the style so
extra Miami I almost forgot lots of
family at least in a girl banana 4 3 1
and dip into a face a highlighter shade
in the palette and use this to highlight
the brow bone
all right scissors and that is how you
guys can create this super simple Bob
Ross and start I add makeup look I
wonder if you guys at home watching out
we're like oh my god how did he even do
that does the guy was at watching Bob's
Israel earlier on I'm gonna go and
finish it all right off camera quickly
and I'll be right back with the final
look and my thoughts oh I thought I
threw the other eye off camera quickly
somehow that I using the chain of face
for my palette of course and a brown
tone of liquid lipstick just took math
with like the whole tree vibe and you
guys I think that is this a Bob Ross
makeup tutorial all complete you guys I
had so much fun from with this video
today oh my god I almost bought myself
that I waited this long to do it but
like I said at the beginning of this
video I've always loved art and had such
a passion for it but painting was never
something that I was really thought
Creina
and for my videos and I am definitely a
perfectionist so I was super nervous
right into this today but following the
Bob Ross tutorial made it so much easier
than I would have expected he was so
calm and so sweet and slow which is
really great for beginners like me and
also I was really only shook at first
because he was doing so many different
little tips and techniques that made the
painting come together so fast I was
like literally watching magic infront of
your very eyes but actually watching him
doing it and explained how the different
techniques work made it easy for me to
try to recreate it as well it is very
obvious to me why so many people loved
and watch bob ross not only were his
paintings literally iconic he is so
credibly talented but also as well he is
generally just such a great teacher he
explained everything so so well and you
can just tell he has a true love for
what he does and is in fact on the art
world I'm bringing painting and all of
its techniques to the everyday consumer
will never be forgotten
I think that is all I for today's video
if you guys did enjoy this as much as I
did please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below income traitors to
support and love it means so so so much
to me and also leave a comment let me
know how you think they did on my Bob
Ross painting I definitely think if this
were on a campus it'd probably be really
really good and fresh I'm definitely
dying to test out more painting
techniques very very soon but I don't
know what they're saying if you have not
already don't forget to click that big
red subscribe button down below as well
come join this sisterhood we were over
11 million sister song I'd love to have
you join the family and also click that
Bell icon so you can get notifications
every time I upload up write a new video
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
and maybe painting journey you can
follow me on NC on Twitter they're both
the same Charles and my snapshots more
up on the seat sent out is genius
chocolate extra ass
dr. charles this videos sister shout out
goes to sister Alana thank you so much
love for always falling and supporting
your little doing it's so so so much and
if you like you the next videos sister
shadow don't forget to always reach with
a video link so they go live on Twitter
really hope you enjoy this and hope you
join us with the rest of this youtube
series and from all of us here happy
painting and god bless my friends
[Music]
[Applause]