hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today today we have a very very very
special announcement that I literally
have been waiting at three years to make
oh my god I could not believe this day
has finally come but I am so pumped it
is not even I don't like this video too
long sword is gonna jump right into
things I'm going to be filming executive
producing and also hosting my very own
beauty competition show and you guys are
going to be a part of it as you guys
know I started in YouTube around four
years ago now and over the last four
years we put out some really amazing
videos together let's be real you guys
do I have such a huge love for
production and just going above and
beyond with every single of my videos
and this what I'm about to talk to you
guys about is definitely not because
we're about to take beauty content I
know okay you take Beauty content and
blow it out to a place that has never
been done before as a kid growing up a
reality competition show so far
literally it's the only thing that I
watch on TV and I find being honest you
guys there still to this day at my
guilty pleasure and when I first started
getting into makeup and social media one
of my biggest goals that I set for
myself was to have my very own a
competition show one day three years ago
when I first moved to LA I remember
spending one morning sitting in my
downtown apartment and creating a full
Notes app document on my phone and
planning out a full concept for a makeup
competition ciao I came up with the name
of the description literally every
single challenge that I wanted these
contestants to go through literally
guest judges as well like I was a fully
ready to go at this point but I had
never produced anything like that before
I barely even knew how to use my camera
and my lights at the time and an ID like
that honestly just felt a little bit
impossible so it just sat in my phone
for literally three years but I had a
really long talk to my team about what I
wanted to do to keep myself inspired and
I brought up the idea of doing it the
reality show and still felt like it was
going to be impossible but a few months
later after a lot of different
brainstorming sessions a lot of
different meetings with a lot of
different people with a lot of different
companies after a lot of different phone
calls and a lot of different sleepless
nights it's becoming a reality and the
impossible it's about to become possible
let's talk about it
[Music]
when we started talking about actually
making the show a reality the most
important part to me by far was that it
was authentic and that it was by
creators for creators and it showed an
accurate depiction of the beauty
community and what it actually takes to
be an influencer and it was very
important to me that I was able to have
a say every single step of the way and
also get my hands dirty too I really
wanted to be involved in the last thing
that I wanted was to have some like
trillion-dollar sad that I just showed
up to every single day with fall and
hair and makeup and glam already done
and to shoot and call it a day that is
not me that has never been me and that
will not be the show either and getting
into that level I was honestly a little
bit scared because that like feels like
a lot to ask for but I am I'm so
grateful that I found the dream team
to make that a reality and to have it
hosted right here on YouTube
we'll be partnering with a Brian Graydon
media for the actual production and I
guess we've got around about the show
because I am so excited to announce that
it is officially been picked up by
YouTube originals as well the show is
set to launch in spring of 2020 so it is
literally only a few months away which
is so crazy to even think about it is a
limited series and it is the first ever
beauty and social media influence our
competition show of its kind ever it is
going to be massive and it is going to
be posted or right here on youtube.com
Asajj James Charles and the reason why
this is so cool too is because there is
so much going for this it is literally
insane but despite all of that it'll be
on my channel right here completely free
for everyone to watch and enjoy it like
I said my creators for creators for the
show we're gonna be finding it the best
of the best of the up-and-coming beauty
influencers from all across the YouTube
world out of everyone who enters only
six will be flown out to sunny Los
Angeles to compete in a real challenges
of course you're planning an artistry it
will be tested it this is a beauty
competition show but I'm not just
talking about bronze smokey eyes and
Rainbow half cut creases L don't do a
clearly love those lot but I'm talking
about crazy intense challenges that will
not only test your artistry but also
your uniqueness your ability to convey
an audience and will truly see if you
have what it takes
become the next beauty superstar six
will compete and will learn a whole lot
about the beauty community a marketing
artistry and about themselves but in the
end only one that can be the grand prize
winner that gets crowned and goes home
with $50,000 and a lot of really other
setting prizes as well that we can't
talk about quite yet all right so I
guess here comes the fun part
if you've been listening so far and
you're thinking to yourself oh my god
I'm a topic on your Beauty influencer
and I think that I bring something
unique to the beauty community and I'm
really talented and I can captivate the
audience and I really want to go to LA
and I really also want to win $30,000
here's how you can enter since this is
not just like me something in my little
studio anymore this is a huge huge
project let me just quickly get some
requirements out of the way first
you must be 18 years old or older to
enter this competition you also must
reside in the United States at least for
season one and also you must have an
octave at YouTube channel in order to
enter you must upload a youtube video to
your channel sending your name age where
you're from and then in five minutes or
less do your best to impress with a
chitchat you're ready with me and I know
what you're thinking oh my god five
minutes is not a long time at all and
you're absolutely right if you have that
star quality we're gonna see it right
away and it should not take more than
five minutes to come across additionally
we really want to see the person behind
the brush and underneath all that makeup
so in those five minutes do your best to
tell us your personal journey and your
story how do you got started and makeup
or on YouTube in the first place what
you think you uniquely bring to the
beauty community and also what this
opportunity would mean to you when you
upload the video to your youtube channel
don't forget to title it James Charles a
casting call and also put this hashtag
in the description net so we can make
sure that we can find the very last step
is to submit your application that we
make it very very clear before we get a
lot of questions about it uploading your
video does not mean that you are
officially entered there is one last
thing to do and the description box down
below there's going to be all the rules
and regulations and all the legal
mumbo-jumbo but there's also going to be
a website link at the bottom of the
screen that is James Charles casting a
calm and you guys will have to go to
that site to submit your final
application on the website applicants
will enter some very basic information
answer a few questions as well as input
your YouTube video link and then when
you
submit you will officially be entered
and our team will be waiting to watch
our videos and pick up the six finalists
after a crazy week of watching a ton of
different submissions and narrowing
everything down my team will contact
these six finalists but until then good
luck if you do not meet the influencer
requirements to enter or if you don't
want to enter because you're not an
influencer and you just love the beauty
community we still need your help
because we want to know who you guys
want to see on the show I can easily
make who I think is gonna be the next
big beauty influencer all day long but
the reality is influencers are not
influencers without their audience and
therefore I want to know who you guys
want to see on the channel now the
casting call is live and people are
gonna be uploading the videos you can go
on YouTube and search James Charles
casting call and all the different
audition tapes and videos are going to
be going off and I want you guys to pick
your favorites thumbs up the videos
share them on Twitter and let your
voices be heard and because it's going
to play a major role and who actually
makes it to the top alright the greatest
boil you think that is pretty much
everything that I have for this
announcement casting call video I don't
think I missed anything but if I did
feel free to leave any questions down in
the comments below or tweet me on
Twitter I cannot believe this day is
finally here
like I said this project has been it's
such a fun idea of mine for such a long
time that I can not believe that it's
finally coming to life thank you once
again to Brian crane and media and
YouTube originals for believing in me
and making this dream a reality but also
thanks to you guys for supporting me
since day one and allowing this to
happen this is such a huge passion
project and I think this is going to be
as such an incredibly positive thing for
the beauty community I love supporting
fellow artists I love it just sharing
any of my knowledge that I've gained
over the past several years and I cannot
wait for all of you guys watching it to
find some amazing new talent to watch as
Wow more information coming soon spring
2020 right here on youtube.com slash
jean-charles for free get ready and good
luck bye sister
[Music]