I'm joined by two very special guests
today insisted Joey Graceffa and sister
Daniel and today we're moving a fun
makeup challenge
yeah we're on Joey Channel I just did
his makeup and turn them into a boy
version of a clan I took it off but we
figured for my channel we do something
super super fun I started a little bit
of series on my channel now where I have
two friends both take one half of my
face and both compete to see who is the
better and you are we really trying or
are we trying to be no I'm all you
topstitch oh oh I have Oliver Edna
products right here in front of me like
always that I use in my everyday makeup
routine and I do have duplicates of only
some of them so joined in they're gonna
have to fight over something I prepared
we're gonna make it work definitely
comment down below tell me what you guys
think I should name this series because
I definitely wanna do this a lot more
often
I'm also give me the names of people
that you think we should do it to it
because big sister wants to do we're
already on to the next collab Hunger
Games began
okay since we don't have a primer to
fill those pores that are not exhausted
I'm just going to go in and with this
this is my man up rubber HD stick oh I
got the beauty well you can use good
answer 10% off for Joey so yes we need
to conceal a cake cake were you know we
need to conceal
I need to see what shades I do have two
opportunities and we can share them as
well do something over here okay okay
what's after a concealer yes figure it
out on your own the powder powder is
what I need to be doing okay next I am
going to pent or marry me Julian stop
getting powder on my side I'm gonna
built in on this forehead [ __ ]
she needs her okay so I got the temples
I got the forehead I'm going in with
this I don't know what it is but he did
it on me so I feel like that's a thing
okay what do I used to snatch your nose
gasp again I don't know if this is right
we're going I don't think that's it well
you know what you like it really pointy
right yeah some weird word port city
when to thee is this not contour what
does that is up you can use oh no Joey
yeah we need a little bit of hula yeah
okay I'm gonna move on to brows because
I love the brow three love it sister bro
okay we love precisely my brow no
where's that frothing that I'll butcher
to LA so I had a bad time you're right
american dragon jake long did you ever
watch that show he was a boy
well so was I what did you shoot I know
who say well we're not really sure I
don't know what to do next
would you have any blush oh my goodness
I almost forgot about her shining
shimmering splendid sister's making his
own tutorial what are you doing though
that's a lot of something it looks good
I know quick love a supportive boyfriend
I don't really know the terminology but
I know we start off with a transitional
shade yeah maybe like a copper lid and a
nude kind of look oh well I have my
packet over here here for you I shove a
factor in a palette well that means I'm
gonna be using these Sela ones because
they're so sickening but we need a base
coat so we're gonna go in with this
spray okay that's a simple base coat all
right close your eyes oh it's sickening
I'm gonna blend right now because I feel
like that's what a lot of people forget
to do this is like a soft champagne
pinky New Year's Eve moment okay over
here
tell me uh all right we're going in with
the other stealing you when you do it
well I think you've been hoarding all
the [ __ ] on it get away get away from my
palace I want some glitters where are
those butters no you can't have those no
I'm allowed to you know that all looks
gonna be too similar are you crazy
oh you know what I'm gonna do that thing
where people smuggle your under eye what
do you think I'm not watch I'm not do I
check for you know oh you're gonna do
exactly what you're doing right now stay
away from her good luck to you as you
lure the thing up morning pop downstairs
something's missing
you suck this is why we don't play board
games you're gonna be so shaken by my
side Am I yeah I'm sure that will be one
actually they come on very similar
reminds better oh they do not look
similar at all rude you want to make
sure the glue is tacky catalina
delivered attacking rocket attack at a
wackadoodle
I'm joining a McMahon anastacio Beverly
Hills lip kit you look like you need a
wobbly now actually I can make this my
own color the first time probably my
sides gorgeously perfect the awesome
instead looks like a bruise lip like
somebody punched him in the mouth
mine is like cute girl going to her
first New Year's Eve partying is like
going to her last I've done it's not
this smiling sister
oh my gosh editing a video so they and I
actually got myself same thing with the
list I was like I'm gonna use it one
second Joey jesus H Christ
I'm nervous the other side there's no
it's not good it's just more subtle 1 2
so let's run sister Joey's huh you did a
lot of bronzing and contouring hangout
but look how good it looks you look warm
you look fresh you look like you just
can use my gosh I was definitely better
at Daniels and tongue I will say that I
love to school it on literally perfectly
yeah that's clue it's like right in my
lashline you guys can see that that's
right yeah well I can't see I know the
glasses on so they're the color I
actually really like I normally would
never choose a little color like this
for myself of us I couldn't do a lot but
I don't like actually like it like the
little black Jetson or sister Daniel
side
foundation concealer powder at once
again you definitely didn't do as much
power as
that's for sure but I think my skin that
does look really really good stop okay
now I shadow is definitely better than
Joey sigh okay and that pay so it's
definitely you picked the red color yeah
but like the darker shade in the crease
of the make a nice little of the way
which is good but I wash on the other
hand looking a little on game for day
those lips the application was pretty
good
okay to your application is also good
for you both over line thank God thank
God the nose contour I think for both
sides as a little bit of a floppity
floppity world okay so I obviously like
both sides everything I can't even pick
a winner because Joey and Daniel both
put in a lot of effort and work which I
really really appreciate that's awesome
I think you guys for becoming a future
MUAC beauty industry oh my god damn them
new blood so even though I've kept it
going that I want you sisters make a lot
down below and tell me which side you
think is better
do you like sister Daniel or sister Joey
let us know down below all right sisters
and then I'm going out for this little
videos today I really hope you enjoyed
our club with my two favorites sisters
if you did it don't forget to give a big
thumbs up down below Instagram if you
have not already since that little boat
vacation posted you be notified every
time I upload a new video and you want
to check out our video we didn't over on
sister Joey's channel like I said we
turn it into a glam boy I'll say it was
so much fun
probably the whoops turned out really
really really sick smash slow second
mate but we're not going to show me you
you have to go check it out over there
subscribe if you haven't already if
there's if I we gotta make up dirty to
follow me on Twitter they're both
disdain Charles at my snapchat before go
ahead see that says janab transmitter
after Charles I love that this week
sisters have a close his sister Spencer
this takes to search other goes to
sister Spencer thank you so much for
supporting you I love you so so so much
and if you like to be in space or sign
up make surprised original video a
something alive on Twitter
alright sisters Ella be so so so much
happy holidays thank you for watching
and I will see you in the next one
[Music]