hi sisters james halter and welcome back
to my youtube channel as you guys know
it is december it is the holiday season
but that also means that New Year is
coming and we are about to be done it
with 2019
once and for all thank God it has been a
good year and 2020 is about to be upon
us when the end of the year comes around
those always all sorts of lists that pop
up documenting big things that happened
that year whether it be a beauty groups
we are products of the Year at the
Billboard top songs of the year we also
of course have our favorite YouTube
rewind which is always an interesting
look back on here and as well Google
also does a year in searches now we all
know that Google is the biggest search
engine in the entire world and we all
use it on a daily basis and you can
pretty much find like literally
everything ever on Google so the Year
interviewer always a really interesting
way to kind of look back at trends and
really see what people are searching for
and this year when I was looking through
the trends I came across a very
interesting discovery and that was the
list of the most searched people in the
entire world number one that was Antonio
Brown number two was Neymar and number
three was James Charles so not
surprising that the list was topped by
three perfect so no no but in all
seriousness somehow yours truly James
Charles was the number three most
searched person worldwide in 2019 now at
first when I saw this it was a very
alarming and very shocking until I
looked at the actual graph of the trend
and suddenly it wasn't so shocking
anymore if you don't know what this
means don't worry about it if there's
that many people actually searching my
name which it's very scary I figured
there must be a lot of questions as well
so for today's video inspired by a wire
I thought it'd be really fun to answer
the web's most searched questions about
me let's go
[Music]
all right you guys we're just gonna jump
right into these questions today I
honestly have no idea what they are Luis
would not let me see them hopefully some
of them will be juicy but nothing it's
how bad Luis did go ahead and prepare
these lovely ripoff tear sheets just
like they have in the actual videos so
let's just go ahead this first prompt
says why is James Charles and if we
uncover the first one says why is James
Charles famous I really don't know this
is your fault you all did this not me
why is James Charles so popular well you
know like I was think in the intro
famous awfully hello the amount of
touchdowns and homeruns that I got for
the Lakers this year was like
groundbreaking so that's probably why
people tend to love me a lot why is
James Charles playing Minecraft
oh okay to be honest I love that this is
actually a search term kind of fun when
I was a younger kid probably 12 13 14
years old minecraft was my absolute
favorite game out of come home school
and play every single day and this past
year minecraft had a major revival in
the YouTube space that thanks to are a
king of PewDiePie and I'd have to play
in a tournament called at minecraft
Monday where we all competing with a
bunch of other youtubers and it was
really fun I never won because I was too
busy being a famous athlete and not a
famous game work it was a really really
good time why is James Charles pallet
not on Murphy that is a great question
it should be on Murphy calm and all
Murphy stores in retail locations on
both of us you can use Co teams return
for some alpha or a scandal happened
that I am not aware of so why is James
pallet so popular once again a lot of
the other athletes on the team really
love spooky the black shade for like
they're under
what does my father there there there
son
walk nope sorry I mean there I black
yeah we were on the field last game and
I think like Tom Brady LeBron James also
Babe Ruth oh all had me apply there i
black so I just like dipped into the
palette and gave it a little bit of
swatch and they were good for the entire
game so that's why
all right this prompt starts with is
James Charles is it James Charles
Mexican is not really the most searched
thing with that no I am NOT Mexican I
think that my parents are polish and
Irish which is Caucasian as hell but my
best friend's family is a full Mexican
so Mexican culture has become a very big
part of my life and I love it so much
and this past year I actually did my
first ever video in Spanish which was
actually the most liked beauty video of
all 2019 so muchas gracias
for that is it James Charles death
that's a dark on the inside yes on the
outside whoever I'm still here is James
Charles miss Coe girl you know I
downloaded tik toks a few weeks ago and
I have honestly been loving it so so so
much and I you but but I've been seeing
these terms like Bisco girl and II boy
and I honestly have no idea what they
are so said I open it up so if you guys
want to let me know what that'll be
really really great but as of right now
so sunny opening up Sun I hope I don't
know is James Charles married you know
actually I am a lot of my fellow
athletes that I love to say we're
married to the game is it James Charles
Hispanic damn okay Caucasian is how it
is honestly really cool that these are
two of the most searched things about me
just from that one video alone it really
does go to show that you two is such a
worldwide thing like I said I love that
video so so so much honestly si quieres
new video that's fine you apart they a
dost die my own like David hodo video
cuz maybe I'll do it is it James Charles
single yeah like I said Mary to the game
but can't talk about this one very
single incredibly single if you will
remarkably say is James Charles
Tran oh I am NOT Tran I am ma'am I'm
assuming that this is supposed to be is
James Charles trans as an transgender
and all jokes aside to answer that
question I am NOT transgender identify
as a man but I do consider myself to be
androgynous which basically means that I
can percent in both feminine and
masculine ways I've been posting a lot
of different photos on Instagram where
the wigs on which I've honestly been
having so much fun doing in saloon and
I've been getting a lot of questions
about this topic which I definitely do
understand no I just like switching my
appearance and trying out new hair cells
and new outfits that's the beauty of
makeup and the beauty of gender
expression is James Charles a Gemini I
am actually M&I my birthday is May 23rd
I've not done a lot of research into
astrology or zodiac signs
I'm just not not into it but I know a
lot of you guys are so that's thing that
you're interested in or think that I
should look into definitely let me know
was that James Charles shot oh no I was
not and I hope not that is concerning to
that as a search let's move on to the
next one please why is it James Charles
hunt no I was not on Dance Moms of butts
I did a video of them at this past year
I know all of y'all saw my choreography
the girls were up struck literally my
skills unmatched and you know I'll be
actually still keep in touch to this day
it she is so nice and I would love to be
on the show so Abby give me a call I
would love to take part in some way or
maybe even adopt a daughter in the
future just so I can go and fight the
other bands was James Charles adopted
speaking of adopting no I don't think so
James II dad dad yeah quick question was
I adopted yeah really we found you in a
mail basket
and my adopted it's for a video thank
you love you bye was James Charles in
Sally Walker yes actually this was one
of the most fun collaborations that I've
ever done I got to be an Iggy azalea's
at music video for Sally Walker and the
next day I actually got to do her makeup
for her up cover and we found that from
like YouTube channel which you can watch
right up here if you guys want to check
that out I definitely would love to do a
very similar type of collaboration with
other artists in the future so it hit me
up if you need a music video appearance
and a really acute problem cover makeup
look was James Charles on the masked
singer no I was not on the masked singer
although I am obsessed of the shower
head like my voice is so annoyingly
distinguishable that the gig would be up
in like three seconds far so probably
not happening anytime soon
Dennis it the gig would be up the jig
would be up does it matter
people's ears will be bleeding and they
would know it's me it's what I'm trying
to say so was James Charles in taste in
taste
oh yes was James Charles mom and haha no
my mom Christy B was not in home alone
although I and she get questions about
it literally all the time the mom went
home alone was played by the actress
named Catherine O'Hara my mom's name is
Christy they're not the same person
although I will say they do look very
very similar what is it James Charles
networth oh that is for me to know and
you to not ever find out what is James
Charles dog's name his name is Finnegan
his insecurity has been Charles and he's
literally an angel sent from above oh
and he is also right no animal testing
we do not agree to the animal testing
here on the ship what is James Charles
oops
real my real name is James Charles
Dickinson
um when I was growing up my parents were
really concerned about Internet safety
as every parent is and should continue
to be so I just sorted going by a James
Charles which is my middle name for just
a little bit more
to online and its stock ever since and I
love it
what is James Charles did is there
something missing on the runner Oh what
is James Charles I would say that I am
10% class 20% sauce and 70% athlete
what is James Charles oh my god
zodiac sign I am a July what is James
Charles sexuality very gay
what is James Charles oh my god
middle name Charles what is James
Charles birthday May 23rd already for
that one too Roxanne Roxanne Dana
James of Charles died oh my god no once
again I did not die and I hate the
people are googling this did James
Charles go to college no I did not go to
college I graduated early from high
school with a 4.0 GPA and Ohio DARS may
I add and for me I was on a career path
that was taking off and I really wanted
to focus on so I moved to LA and started
working full-time did James Charles get
a dog yes did James Charles invent the
pink train technically no because a few
years ago it was still one of those like
secret menu items and you how to order
the a strawberry acai refresher with
coconut milk and water only the true oh
gee sisters will remember having to
order all about it in order to get the
actual drain but when I first moved to
LA I was walking to Starbucks and
ordering that drink every single morning
and I would I just post about it on my
snapchat story and say I got the pink
ring which then turned into the pink
kitty
djenka D which is not the pink shade in
my palette and from talking about it all
the time people started ordering it and
eventually Starbucks actually added it
to the permanent menu and they did tell
me that that was because I mean and you
guys ordering it so kind of cool why
does James Charles
sing I sing because singing it makes me
very very happy I love music so much I
will tell you that
sometimes I listen back to videos of me
singing and I asked myself the same
question so why does James Charles blink
so much that is also a great question I
never even realized that I did this
until I started making YouTube videos
and I got thousands and thousands of hit
comments about it so thank you so much
for making me insecure about a normal
bodily function that literally every
single person does I really have no idea
you tried having awful I say it and not
be able to see anything and having to
our color contacts and eyelashes that
weigh a pound each and having powder
file why does James Charles wear a
safety pin to keep my ear safe and the
last question on the video why does
James Charles say a sister although this
is actually cute when to end things off
on I say sister because it is the name
of my fan base if you do not know that
welcome to the party our little family
is not so little anymore and after three
years we are at 16 million sisters but I
am so grateful for each and every single
one of you no matter how big we get
together being a sister means being a
positive being a creative being a kind
to one another being hard working it but
most importantly loving everyone for who
they truly are no matter what and going
into xx xx none of those values are
changing and I'm holding myself
accountable and I ask that all of you
guys do it the same to keep this
community a a positive one I'm so
grateful to call each and every single
one of you a family member
all right you guys well those are all
the most asked questions about me from
this year's Google searches
once again cool that we're the number
three most searched person if you guys
send into this video please don't forget
to give it a big thumbs up down below
and show your love and support it really
doesn't mean so much to me and also
makes you look that big red subscribe
button and come join this sister and I'd
love to have you in the family and
finally click that battle icon so you
notification every time I upload a brand
new video if you like to follow me on my
makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter and tik-tok are
all just James Charles and my snapchat
for more behind the scenes I staff is
James Charleston extra ass after Charles
this video is sisters how that goes to
sister Lorenzo they give so much love
for Owens following and supporting I
love you so so so much
and if you will it be the next videos
sister shout out don't forget to always
reach people to this when they go live
on Twitter thank you so much for
watching this video today I love you and
I'll see
and if the next wives
[Music]