[Music]
I'm an artist hi sisters James Charles
here and welcome back to my youtube
channel or should I say oh my god you
guys today's video - one EP film for
literally so many months I lied is not
even funny today is the grand reveal of
my sister collection with morphe that
I've been working on for over a year now
and I am so beyond excited to show you
guys everything that we have in store
first off we just talked about that
little commercial you just saw fully
produced by me makeup by me and music by
me and I'm best friends Anthony Brenna
so much fun is so good so fresh so I
guess we should just like so good do it
I figured I should show you guys the
James Charles artistry palette first oh
my god this is the packaging right here
we have this beautiful look right here
that you guys just saw at the end of the
campaign commercial I created this over
six months ago now and you have no idea
I have never wanted to post an Instagram
picture more and I can tire life but
I've had to hold it back and keep it a
secret I am so proud of how this look
turned out it was inspired by my look
from 2017 a blank canvas and we had this
beautiful like Bay packaging and we have
more Fiats James Charles and my iconic
sister signature and just a white glossy
font the packaging is super super
minimalist but I absolutely love it and
think it is just so chic and we turn the
pala to the back we have this cute
little note from me sister David it says
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my palette I love glam
but I also have a huge passion for crazy
colorful outside of the box makeup and I
created this palette with that in mind I
included every beautifully formally to
change necessary to create literally any
look you can possibly imagine we'll get
into that in a second I cannot wait to
see what you come up with when you
unleash your inner artist team Charles
as well as the palette we also have my
brush collection at launching as well
these two together complete did James
Charles likes Morpheus sister collection
I am so beyond excited this is basically
my all-time favorite morphe brushes have
also a few different new brushes that I
made myself
as well I'm gonna be jumping into this a
little bit later on in the video so make
sure you stay tuned but for now let's
jump into this baby if we just pop her
right on open this is a brand new one
comes in a bubble wrap so it stays
protective when it's shipping tada oh my
god so the palette comes in a matte
black soft touch I literally love how
these feels so so so much and the text
on the fries in a shiny box has more
Phoenix James Charles just like the
packaging on the outside and the white
it is just very very sleek minimalistic
very much my overall style oh my god I
have it open this on camera 439
beautiful amazing colors now the top of
the packaging we have this little saying
right up here that you heard at the end
of the campaign commercial in my little
isn't that it unleash your inner artist
now I've had this quote in the Notes app
on my phone for literally two years now
and I knew that I wanted to use it for a
big project and hello what better to use
it for that this eyeshadow palette my
admission as an artist inside of the
community has always been making it fun
creating a new content doing things that
nobody would ever dare to do taking a
step away from tutorials and making
Beauty videos actually entertaining
playing with color playing with
avant-garde looks that most people would
necessarily deem where will a brutal
content and they're doing that I've been
able to express myself and put myself
out there and find all of your sisters
and find such an amazing audience that
also has such a love and appreciation
for art so that is why we are unleashing
our inner artist with this collection
now obviously you'll notice that there
is a plastic knife that comes over all
the shades is obviously protects that
wall traveling but all the stadiums are
also listed on every single one of the
colors there are 39 iconic Shay names
that you guys are definitely going to
recognize from all my sister sayings and
also some things that definitely have a
personal wing to me as well we're going
to get into those in a quick second but
for now I'm just going to take this off
and show you guys
a pallet in all its glory obviously you
guys know the morphe palettes usually
come with 35 but this one comes with 39
with the middle row all hopping Baker
pans this is obviously remodeled after
the 39a which is the palette that
launched last holiday season that I was
actually the model for I'm gonna dive
into each individual shade in a second
but before I do that I want to put the
palette into three sections and kind of
explain how I organized it and why it
looks like what it does and it's gonna
make a lot more sense right now
so unleash your inner artist the whole
point of creating my sister collection
with morphe was that I felt like there
was something missing on the market and
that was one I shadow palette that could
truly create any single look no I know
this palette is obviously very very big
but the whole point in making this was
that you could travel with it take it
anywhere take it on set if you're
working makeup artist have it in your
kit if you're at home beauty guru like
myself and literally be able to create
any single look imaginable so the top
two rows of the palette are for my more
everyday wearable glam Shana type of
people now the middle role you'll notice
are all the bigger shades now more we
did this for the first time in the 39a
palette and they did all the transition
shades because I thought what's so cool
- how much time does to say for each
different skin tone but you definitely
don't need someone transition change so
what did I do
I made these seven middle shades all the
most-used
shades no matter what look you're
creating so we have a matte white and a
matte block perfect for setting your
base or deepening anything up whether it
be a typical everyday glam look or an
artistry or even a try look we have a
highlighting shade this is literally one
of the most beautiful highlighters ever
I will show you in a second and then
these four colors are all four colors
needed to create literally any warm tone
of smoky eyes so you have your
transition shade you have your deepening
shade you have your further deepening
speed and then you have your further
deepening shape now what you've all been
waiting for
last but certainly not least the bottom
two rows of the palette are all of our
rainbow shades now as an artist and
starting off I have always wanted my
perfect rainbow eyeshadow kit but I have
never been able to find it obviously the
morphe 35c as muslin that I've used for
a very very long time but it is gone now
r.i.p it gone and now to be forgotten to
replace by this baby right here there
were definitely a lot of shades in there
that I felt like needed a major major
improvement so when I had this palette I
di
morpheme very very closely to firmly
every single one of these J's to create
literally the most bomb rainbow
eyeshadow colors you will ever see in
your entire life so before we actually
get into the individual swatches I do
want to kind of go over each of the
individual foremost we have going on in
here because there quite a few I did
tell you guys that this is a very very
versatile palette and I was definitely
not lying so we of course have our
beautiful metallic shades all throughout
the palette they're going to be applied
best with your finger or a damp brush
using a Assessor settings bright we do
have one glitter kind of metallic
pigment as well you guys are going to be
shook when you see this and this is kind
of like a layering shade that is best
Pat on lightly we have one a beautiful
blinding highlight shade as well and
then of course majority of this palette
is a beautiful vibrant pigmented or
rainbow matte shades now I do want to
touch on the map shape and some of these
formulas behind them because most of the
math in this palette are considered
pressed pigments and not typical
eyeshadows now what does that mean I
didn't know until very recently when I
was formulating this with Murphy but now
I do is I want to share with you guys
the ingredients and pressed pigments are
just slightly different than iron
shadows and they are actually exactly
what their name says it is literally
just the actual color pigment pressed
right into a pan ready for you to use
whereas the iPhone has a lot of other
stuff mixed in it as well to make it
perform it really beautifully now that
being said by doing press Penguins it
allows you to make the most vibrant true
to color product ever and I am so
incredibly proud of these as an artist I
will say straight up to you guys some of
these pressed pigments are a little bit
harder to work with it just because you
have to use slightly different
techniques but once you figure them out
they are so incredibly beautiful and I
know that you guys are going to fall in
love of them so my advice to you I have
personally found that packing on the
pressed pigments with a flat brush works
the absolute best to get maximum color
payoff and to make sure all the shadows
stay in place and as well I always use
shave tape or my concealer as an eyelid
primer before doing any eyeshadow for
the press pigments I would actually not
recommend this now this may come as a
little bit of a shock to you guys but
have you been describing me for a very
very long time
that I'm definitely a firm believer and
the makeup conspiracy that primer is a
scam now I'll okay still to this day but
when it comes to these press penguins I
swear to god you guys
myself and the morphe team have found
out over the past several months that
using these press payments on an actual
product that is formulated for the
eyelids is going to make the shades
perform so beautifully and it's going to
give you the best result possible now I
really like using the Mac Paint Pot for
this and I also like the morphe eyelid
primer as well and it's only a few
dollars with code James for 10% off your
purchase I've never believed in this
I've never cared enough but through
trying these press 10 minutes I will
100% say confidently that you're going
to want to use a product specifically
formulated for the eyelids for maximum
blunt ability for maximum payoff and for
maximum pigmentation it all about being
said let's jump into the sponges so the
version in the top left corner is called
canvas it is inspired by my iconic blank
canvas look from last year and it's just
a super light and bone color shade and
it's perfect for setting the lid okay
starting off with a blank canvas can
barely see that because it's like my
skin tone color but it's there
next time we have the shade of ring
light which is obviously inspired by my
iconic ear by story that started it all
and this one is just like a metallic
kind of bright gold it's literally
almost metallic white and so pretty
Hello next ring like we have this gold
shade called so good I love this color
so much when creating a gold I really
wanted it to be a light true gold eyes
like so many gold either route to bronzy
or to yellow and this one it's like
right in the middle so good well I'm not
going to swatch as okay oopsies next to
so good we have this bright orange shade
which is called a five one eight
inspired by my hometown area code where
school colors for orange and black so
this is like a little ode to my past
length basically and this one is a
bright vivid orange now this formula
looks matte but it is one of the shades
in the palette that is a pressed pigment
here is five and eight oh so good right
there next to five one eight we have a
little bit more of a vivid orange color
this one is called rusted because I
always say crusted busted dusted
said and it's kind of what this color
reminds me other so pigment on this
shade right here is a metallic bright
orange color and it is called Halloween
inspired by my favorite time of the
entire year and when I officially
started doing makeup for the first time
oh my god all the Potala shades in this
palette are truly unmatched look at that
next to Halloween we have this really
unique brownie gold a type of shade
right here this one is going to be
perfect for placing right on the lid for
a smoky sultry look and this one is
called web gorge and then finally to
complete the top row we have this cool
tone a brown shade called tea because I
love the good sisters type of tea and
this is literally just the perfect whole
tone Brown for deepening up any love and
that is the first row of the glam shades
all done so starting out the second row
right here we have this light cool tone
brown shade called punched me named
number two my best friends in the entire
world
Ethan and Grayson our friendship
literally started from believing throws
comments on their in certain pictures
and that's still how it is today this is
just a super easy basic color for any go
to glam look there is still I said oh my
arm
I'm not good at this next to punchy we
have this peachy a pinky champagne E
metallic color and this one is called
sister I just wanted a super beautiful
soft light color perfect for putting on
the lids of any it glam looks just
because you guys make me soft and kind
of happy a lot and that's what the
shader runs me off so next door to
sister we have this cool tone mauve
shape right here called and Mary know
this is actually not named after a
flashlight Mary this is named after my
best friend drew now Mary used to
actually be a terminus used derogatorily
is that a word directed it was it was a
derogatory term towards gay people a
very very long time ago but the gays
have reclaimed it as we always do and
now I mean all my gay friends but I say
hey Mary whatever we walk in and they
started from me and true
I love this color so next to Mary we
have this shade right here called
literally now this is literally one of
my favorite colors in the entire palette
because it is like this bright pinky
peach color and it is slightly metallic
and when you swatch it it actually gonna
be honest is not even that impressive
but I'm originally why I love it so much
it looks like this when you swatch it
I guess that is so really really pretty
but you could either layer on a lot of
it and get a color just like this which
obviously is very very stunning or you
can use that in little doses which is
how I personally love it so if you take
a brush like this which is like the 501
this isn't my brush that we talked about
this in a little bit you can apply to us
right on the cheekbone and it will give
you a beautiful light pink glow or you
can use it on an e for brush which is my
all-time favorite blush brush also
available in my brush set and you can
pack just a little bit more on and
because it's like a peach color right in
between pink and orange you can blend it
right in between your highlighter and
the bronzer and it will blend it
together so so so beautifully I'm
obsessed with literally this shade right
here is the color that I am the most
proud about releasing in this palette
now this shade right here is called Kerr
kidding and you're gonna see why it's
called that when I swatch it in about
three seconds from now but I have wanted
a true red color in an eyeshadow palette
since I started to do makeup and it does
not exist
literally every single round is either
not pigmented o or it tends to run to
magenta or to orange this is rad are you
ready for this
you're kidding oh my god why have you
ever seen a bag that good we went back
and forth on formulations for the shade
so many times but you guys I cannot wait
for you to have this in your hands and
start playing to them because this is
literally the best red eyeshadow on the
entire market and I can say that so
confidently that's you're kidding next
to it you're kidding we have the shade
shucks and this is a metallic cranberry
red now this is not actually similar to
Halloween and I'll swatch them X to each
other I really wanted to create a
metallic cranberry rabbit because I feel
like a lot of the metallic orange and
metallic red shades tend to look
very similar and they wanted that true
metallic red shade that you can put
right over and you're kidding and have
it look so beautiful look at how good
that looks next to shucks we have this
deep matte red maroon color right here
called a boutique that this is obviously
named after my best friend Laura and her
entire family who owns a Laura's
boutique an amazing clothing business
located right here in Whittier
California Laura is my best friend in
the entire world and our family has sent
us so much for me I actually lived a
Laura and her family for six months
before ever moving to help so good for
what if we're actually ever moving to LA
and I cannot think oh I don't want to
start crying and I could not think her
and her family enough for everything
that they've done for me moving on right
away
Oh knees move on right now and the last
date in the second row is this deep kind
of eggplant to color right here and this
one is called it Benny this is named
after my family puppy from back home I
literally messed him up so so so much I
don't know if you guys have ever
actually met him before but he is it
pretty much a discolor and this is just
going to be a perfect shade for
deepening up any look that was a
disgusting swatch I'm scared try that
again this is the shade Benny and that
is the second row of shadows all
complete so moving on to the third row
all the ones with the bigger pans once
again these are probably gonna be the
ones that you guys are gonna get the
most use out of starting off from at the
far left we have the white shade which
of course is named flush now creating a
matte white shade of something that I've
wanted to do for so long now because I
feel like so many of them are literally
so bad you put them on and it just
disappears this is not that watch this
gonna get my finger out I'm gonna do a
regular swatch yeah very okay looking
right raw gonna get the same thing
you're in
I'm gonna grab more
there's a second layer and there is your
third layer of white I wanted to create
a white eyeshadow that you can actually
layer and build up to a pure white
because I feel like getting this bright
it's like literally not possible with so
many other brands the shade is
especially going to be perfect for all
my drag queen friends I'd like to
highlight their brow bones or use their
creases with a bright white shade
instead of in place
Fache like Mary stuck with me for a very
very long time and I promise to you and
you were definitely gonna want to have
flashbacks sticking with you for a while
next to flash like we have the shade
face and this is just a champagne gold
piloting color I think it is so so so
beautiful I literally took all my
favorite highlighters that I use on an
everyday makeup basis and brought them
in and I was like I want to create this
all together next to face we have this
light ones transition shade right here
called toon get it these two I'm so
funny and this is gonna be the first
shade out of the whole like warm tone
smokey series that we have going on
right here in the middle this shade is
this going to be the perfect wash of
color to put down first just to get your
worm toned look ready to go next right
in the middle the palette we have this
orange shade called code James and the
next to coat James you have this
beautiful burnt orange shade right here
perfect for deepening up your crease of
any warm tone look and of course this
one is going to be called you guessed at
10% off which don't forget to use KO
change for 10% off your sister
collection when this launch is next at
10% off we have this a warm tone brown
color right here perfect for finishing
up your bronze smokey eyes and this one
is called no beans this is obviously
named after one of my all-time favorite
foods in the entire world my Chipotle
breathable in which I get no beans
Lhasa finally not least other no beads
we have the blonde shade in the palette
called spooky I named this up to my love
for all things spooky like horror movies
and Halloween I just love being a sister
spooked my arm is literally raw from
what I think they swatches yeah can you
come here please
Kyleigh a charm to do some swatches
quickly yes
Wow I'm gonna have to put up a fight
okay good so sorting out the rainbow
shades in the bottom of the palette the
first color we have right here is the
bright yellow and this one is called be
a named doctor actually the Indians bomb
Christy of B that is her nickname that's
the best yellow eyeshadow literally in
the entire world look at that don't make
fun of me
so next door to B we have this metallic
green I hated that has kind of gold
reflux and glitters and this one is
called wok also named after Chipotle and
my love for Mexican food
look at that color that's so good
next to clock we have this metallic
bright teal shade right here and this
one is called hello hello hello yeah
every other palette called they want
their pigmentation back yeah you've
laughed at me thank you
next to hello we have this bright teal
shade right here called a playground
now this shade is named after my best
friends in the entire world Anthony card
jhula you guys know him as we've always
are singing covers together
but me Tiffany actually met each other
on a playground in fourth grade I was
following him around I wanted to be his
best friend he did not wanna be mine and
that's where he's a long one this shade
is called a playground and it just means
so much to me to be able to be a machine
after Anthony and the palette he was
also part of creating the music for the
commercial as well which is just so cool
love you Anthony the absolute most next
one looks like we have this shade right
here and this one is called rose ooh hey
popper mister yeah my favorite shade
favorite in the entire palate is just
like a true like blue I don't even know
like it it's just like blue there's no
green in it there's no purple and it's
just like literally true blue and I'm
obsessed that I think it is literally so
pretty
I will say you picked a really a really
hard color to do this is by far one of
the hardest ones to firmly and the
entire palette you gave me use so many
issues but it did turn out really really
beautiful in the end this one I just
like I 1/8 is one of the press payments
you have to work at this and a little
bit of a different way this one's gonna
perform best when you use packing
motions right on the lid to really make
sure that color is locked in place as
opposed to like big blending moments
[Music]
that's brother so pigmented so brother
II next sort of brother we have this
shade right here and this one is called
artistry in honor of the palettes name
and I don't exactly know how to describe
this formula because it's not metallic
it's like glitter the shadow almost has
a little bit like a wet formula it has a
slight blue you can see it on camera you
could never see payments like that on
camera that's exciting that's good no
obviously it does swatch very very
beautifully but we actually created the
shade in mind for layering so whether it
be over a black or a dark purple or even
make it be white shade we created this
color to really just make it pop and
sparkle with blues and purples over top
of a base for maximum payoff next
artists should we have this matte
magenta shade right here and this one is
called love that love that and lost in
this rogue we have the light pink shade
right here and this one is named after
my favorite drink and the entire world
thinkety thinkety now the shade of Lee
does not swatch the most pigmented but
it's actually Wow you can there it is
well I was getting worried there first
like a it does not swatch the most later
content but and it's supposed to be a
light wash of color either on the lid or
as a transition sheet when it comes to
blending in any pink colors later on and
that is the first roll of the rainbow
shades all done starting off the last
roll of the rainbow shades we have the
bright neon green right here in the
bottom left hand corner and this one is
called
socialblade literally best name in the
entire world
major thank you to socialblade for
actually allowing us to use it in this
palette but it's beautiful and green
just like my social blade please to you
guys next to socially we have this
beautiful dark forest green shade right
here and this one is called daddy named
after with Laura's husband and one of my
best friends as Victor you guys have
seen him in all my daddy does eye makeup
and voiceover videos this was
favorite color in the palette just as
beautiful green Shane okay I think my
arm is good now you can go thank you I
know from then congratulations thanks
again bye next to Daddy we have this
metallic aqua shade right here and this
one is called Cape Cod named after the
beaches of Cape Cod Massachusetts now we
did go to Cape Cod Massachusetts every
single year and if we definitely made
the most out of it our memories that we
have there are so incredibly fun I truly
do miss it so much
and I created this color based off all
the memories of the beautiful water and
oceans and Cape Cod next door to Cape
Cod we have this deep blue shade right
here and this one is called Cola named
after Pepsi and my side addiction to
soda that I really need to get over now
don't get me wrong I definitely still do
love a Coca Cola too but I see there's a
good name for the top blue shade and
that's was born a cola next we have this
a deep metallic blue shade right here
this one is called acapella named after
my love for acapella music it is so much
fun for me to sing with all my best
friends and create beautiful parts and
harmonies without any instruments oh
look at how pretty that is
you're literally kidding me so good
acapella next we have this a deep purple
plum shader right here and this one is
called escape you guys know I love
escape routes there's literally nothing
in the entire world that makes me
happier than solving a task a room I
don't know why I just love use my brain
and strategizing and problem-solving and
is it so so so much fun and it was also
so much fun creating this purple as well
just like brother this is one of the
little bit more tricky shades to work
with you do have to definitely pack it
on because it is a pressed time yet but
when you do it right look how beautiful
that color is next door to escape we
have this beautiful bright purple shade
and this one is called single named
after me who needs a boyfriend when you
can have a beautiful purple eye shadow
tell me honestly
and lastly finally not least the bright
neon pink shade in the bottom right hand
corner this shade is called skip and
honor of my father this is the favorite
color and the entire palette and scape
assist nickname that everything one of
his friends call him this pink shade and
the formulation I am so I'm kind of
proud of just like you're kidding in
Tucson my favorite shades in the entire
palette
know that my father is very very proud
of me as well and all the work that I
put in it just means a lot that I was
able to name ashamed after him for this
power and that is the rainbow all
complete sisters those are all 39 shades
and how they swatch what they are called
what they mean to me and how beautiful
they are in my palette that I created
with morphe you guys have no idea how
much love and care and work and
sleepless nights went into the creation
and planning of this palette I've had
this idea in my head for so long now and
I cannot thank the morphe team enough
for working with me and believing in me
and making a vision come to life you
guys I am so incredibly proud of this
palette I have been using it for several
months now on the DL I'm sure you picked
up at this point but I could not wait
for you guys to have this in your hands
so that is all the details with the
palette out of the way but I did say we
were coming out with the sister
collection and that means we also have a
brush set so you might be a little bit
surprised that I've created a brush set
and that is because if you didn't call
me for a very very long time
I've actually publicly said before that
I don't really like brush up and you can
call me I'm not because for the most
part I still stand behind that to this
day but the reason behind that is
because I feel like in so many brush
sets are either too many brushes to the
point where you won't use half done
because there's a stupid brushes that
serve no purpose or the actual set is
too small to where you have to order 20
extra brushes in order to make it a full
useable set this brush set is not that
so I got the opportunity to make a brush
set at first I was like no but then I
was like oh actually yeah I probably
should just make literally the best
brush set at the entire world and that
is this brush set right here this baby
contains 34 brushes and just like the
palette I created it with all artist in
mind that you can literally create any
single look with it so when you open up
the box of the brush set it comes just
like this all 34 brushes and a contour
blending sponge right inside of a custom
James Charles X more feet Taavi case
this isn't so cute I love these for
storing on my makeup table I have so
many of them over here that I keep all
my brushes in and they are perfect for
traveling as well it comes with oh yeah
obviously it comes with the top as well
oh I probably should say that I just
took
so it looks kind of cute for like a good
little displaying moment you feel me but
this is what it looks like I'm gonna go
through the collection kind of quickly
just to show you guys exactly what's in
here if you're a true Ivan morphe fan
you probably might have a lot of these
in your collection already aside from
the new brushes that I created I'll get
into those in a quick short second but
buying this brush kit is definitely not
a necessity and anything I would tell me
back on the palette out of the two of
them but I did want to create this for
all my artists out there as the perfect
brush set because I did it truly feel
like it was missing from the market I'm
gonna go in the same order that I do my
routine in and starting off we have a
foundation brush just the M 439 and my
opinion this is by far the best
foundation brush in the entire world but
if you're like me and you don't actually
like using foundation brushes so they
actually let me include the morphe
contour and highlight blending sponge
which I absolutely love
when you soak them in water they
actually get so large which I love for a
quick foundation application I prefer
this much over a foundation brush but
like I said this that was created for
everyone so they're both here and you
can pick whichever one you want
next resetting my face in place we have
the e 48 brush this is just a taper
powder brush that I like to use right
underneath the eyes to pack on the
powder super cute
next for contour we have the Amma for
all five this is just a fluffy angled
brush I love this for chiseling out the
cheekbones
now we're in the process of contouring I
did tell you guys that I've created a
few different custom brushes for this
brush collection so I want to tell you
about the first one and that is a bit to
eat 62 now this is a tiny angled of
synthetic fluffy brush and this is for
snatching the nose you guys know that I
live for a good sister snatched schnoz
if you go back to my older like photos
my nose contours looking at obviously
horrifying but once I learn how to
contour properly and a little bit of
face to it as well my Instagram gave a
truly shot up and I'm so proud of my
nose contour now it's on my all-time
favorite steps eye makeup routine so
that is why I created this one right
here it is perfect for just laying down
that contour and bronzer shade right up
in there and then tilting it just to
blend it oh and you're gonna snatched
for bronzer we have the big and beefy
and five to seven brush I love this for
going right in to blend together my
contour and my natural skin tone just a
light bronzer shade and its really big
so I can get a lot of area
if you're like me and you have a huge
forehead as well next four plus we have
the e for brush this is just a synthetic
fluffy angled brush I really really love
this for gloss application because you
can either go light and laid out a light
wash a collar or really pack it on there
for a bright kind of drug type look this
brush the thought of my collection since
day one next for brows we have the a
matte one five eight now for me
personally I definitely do prefer a brow
pencil so I will not be getting much use
out of this brush just being straight-up
honest but I know so many sisters out
there do love a good brow pomade I mean
I definitely did it in 2016 the Sabre
brush that I brought Hamid is literally
what led me to James Carlos herbie block
brows but when you know how to use this
correctly and this brush can truly be a
force to be reckoned with and it is just
a tiny little ankle brush on one end and
he's fully on the other end just brush
the hairs all in place and I do love a
good angled brush once the brows are all
filled in I included the Emma 410 brush
just to clean up your brows with
concealer underneath and it's just a
flat concealer brush and then I love
using the abbot 173 with just a little
bit of translucent powder to blend in
and set the concealer in place to prep
for I shall now moving on to what you
guys know is I very part of my entire
makeup routine at the eyeshadow these
brushes are gonna be what you apply the
James Charles X morphe palette where the
[ __ ] there is a little bit of a twist
now we of course have all the iconic
Parsons that you guys have seen me
literally use since day one in all my
tutorials we have the m4 for one I love
this brush it is a big fluffy brush
perfect for layering down a transition
shade into the crease
we have the m4 33 which is my all-time
favorite crease brush I literally have
27 of these in my collection all in the
different color eyeshadow stained in it
I love these for just laying down colors
and packing things into the outer corner
all you the I'm 433 we have the second
brush set created in collaboration with
morphe for this collection and that is
the m45
six now this is literally the most
iconic blending burst of all time
because it is the m4 33s little
now we all know and love this brush like
I was thinking I have 27 of them in my
collection
this brush performs the exact same way
as its older sister being that it lays
down color and also blends it out at the
same time but it is so perfect people
that have smaller eyelids or if you want
to do little detail blending work and
don't want to get that color absolutely
everywhere you literally need this in
your collection and give me like two
weeks and I'll probably have 27 of these
as well we have the m22 for brush this
is just a small concealer brush that I
love for cutting the crease then we have
the a matte one six six I love this
brush for packing on a color after I
actually cut the crease we also had the
eyelet 1 to 4 which is kind of like the
baby sister to the m-16 6 I love this
brush for packing on either a
highlighter on the brow bone or what I'm
doing like sunset smokey eyes and I have
a lot of colors to pack all on the lid
and blend it together I love this for
topping on the shades this brush is
gonna be like your holy grail tool for
packing on those pressed pigments and
the actual palette to really get maximum
payoff we also have the m500 stick which
is like this tiny fluffy pointed a
tapered blending brush I love this are
going in the outer V and deepening up
with the crease region we also have the
tiny little ab 1 v 2 brush this is just
a tiny little fluffy packing brush it
may be very very small but it definitely
has some really important use I love
using this brush to blend in shadows on
the lower lash line we have the Abbott
251 brush this is the smallest liner
brush that morphe makes you can really
get an on fleek winged liner if you love
a good a gel liner
I lost probably not least we have the am
at 4:31 I love this tiny little pencil
brush for highlighting either at the tip
of my nose or my inner corners so those
are all the brushes all complete but
you're probably thinking what the heck
James you said this is the 34 piece
burst collection and it is what makes
this collection so iconic and perfect
for all my artists out there this has
never been done before but every single
one of the eye brushes that I hand
picked out for this collection comes the
duplicate just make it even better - at
the m-44 one at the M 4-3-3 and my new
baby brush the M 4.6 come with three
because why not
once I had the idea to actually create
this brush set for all artists and to
create duplicates as well and morphing
was on board I was so incredibly
grateful and excited to get started I
know so many guys out there are two
artists and work with color all the time
this is literally what my blending brush
table looks like so many colors so many
the same exact faulty brushes that I
know and love and that is why I wanted
to throw duplicates and there's to all
my artists out there can seamlessly
create the books that they want to
without having to stop and clean their
branches in between or they're having to
order a million different brushes all at
different times and that is the morphe
exchange Charles brush set all complete
you made it to the pallet you made it
through the brushes I've been holding
this from you guys for far along enough
I'm sure you want to hear all about the
launch my beautiful artistry palette and
all 39 shades inside now I'm sitting
this networks from swatching this all
day long well we were you telling for
$39 for 39 shades and my 34 piece full
face brushed collection including all
the duplicates a custom tubby and the
contour blending sponge a $218 value
will be retailing for a hundred and
forty nine dollars if you choose to buy
them together the sisters collection
will be retailing for a hundred and
eighty eight dollars but you can and
should use go chains for temper some of
your purchase of course to get yourself
a little bit of a sister Cisco if
there's any time to you say it's gonna
be right now or I guess not right now I
should probably tell you guys when it's
got a long ha the launch date get ready
to mark your calendars and set your
alarms tell your love dogs or hands and
uncle's your family your best friends
and more importantly your sisters
because we're going to be breaking
history on Tuesday November 13th at 8
a.m. Pacific Standard Time I'm gonna
leave all the information regarding the
pallet the brush collection the pricing
and the launch down in the description
box down below so don't forget to check
down there so you guys make sure you
have all the accurate information and
don't forget anything when it comes to
launch you guys I think that it's Holly
Harper today's video oh my god I just
want to say thank you so much all of you
sisters out there for following and
supporting me since day one this would
not be possible if it were not for you
guys and thank you to morphe for
believing in me and making my vision
come to life I am so incredibly proud of
all the products that I created and I
literally need you guys to all have
these new hands right now
I created this collection with every
single person in mind whether you like a
symbol of light glam look all the way to
crazy avant-garde rainbow colorful drug
you can literally create any look you
want with this palette in brush
collection and I cannot wait to see all
of your sisters unleashing your inner
artists oh my god literally almost
forgot hello if you like the idea that
I'm wearing right now that I've been
teasing all over social media for the
past few weeks not only is my sister
question coming out with more feet but
to master my artistry palette we also
have the artistry collection launching
on sisters apparel a few days after the
palette lon it'll be on November 15th
and we have this sisters logo hoodie and
rainbow we also have the repeating of
logo hoodie on the back and as well we
have the one piece that I am most
excited about in the entire world
sister fans literally obsessed these
they produce it's so much air I love
these from when it's hot out but more
importantly you guys know I use a lot of
it sisters setting spray all throughout
my makeup routine and I love giving my
family good work and letting it all dry
in place and lock in without at the
artist collection that super cute super
simple super small and is just going to
be a limited edition launch on scissors
of mail so if you guys want to pick out
any of the regular pieces make sure to
get them while they last because once
they are sold out they are going to be
gone make sure you guys follow me on my
makeup journey my Instagram and Twitter
are both dashain charlotte's and my
snapchat is more and it seems to us out
there's going to be so much palette
related
very very soon and you are definitely
not gonna wanna miss out everything will
be posted there first and thank you so
much watching this video I love you get
ready for Tuesday November 13th and
[Music]
I'm pleased you're an artist