hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so as
you can see we are in a completely new
and different setup I'm actually filming
in my old Beauty room because a few days
ago I decided last second to turn my
film in I grew up into a walk-in closet
literally the most obnoxious first for a
problem ever but I was actually running
out of storage in my closet and I was
thinking oh my god I want to focus more
on clothes because you guys disheartened
to realize that I usually wear the same
five outfits like every single week
which is getting a little bit
embarrassing at this point so sister
wants to step up her fashion again for
sure I decided that I wanted to change
my filming room into a walk-in closet
which I now have installed and you guys
will be singing the apartment tour
coming on very very soon but that left
me with a very rear dilemma of not
having anywhere to film so I actually
just converted my Beauty room into a
beauty and filming room mr. Kay helped
me it is so freakin beautiful so I
really really hope you guys are enjoying
the new setup it's just it's very very
simple background with shells and
paintings and yeah definitely comment
down below and tell me if you like it
let me know if the audio is good let me
know if the Lighting's good this is the
first video I've ever even film sitting
down here so I'm trying my best to make
sure it is all set up but of course as
we go on and things progress I'll get
better and things will be perfect and
the way they were before and back to
normal James Charles quality all that
being said I've heard today's video as
you can see I'm wearing this bronzy very
very simple glam this is actually
kendall Jenner inspired look her makeup
artist hong van gogh i think that's how
you pronounce his name posted a
beautiful freakin picture of Kendall on
his Instagram and I was cooked to the
core and I wanted to recreate this look
so so about me obviously the Jenner and
Kardashian's always have iconic makeup
looks that everybody's always recreating
if you guys want to see how I created
this bronzy glowy winged out shadow
moment inspired by at Kendall J herself
make sure you keep on watching alright
so since this is a super dewy and
moisturized look I'm first gonna start
off by priming my face using my a
benefit total moisture cream I've
recently been loving this cream so
freakin much if you guys know me you
would know that the skincare is not
exactly something that I've learned a
lot about or kind of focused on in the
past but I've been trying to get into it
a little bit more recently because I'm
not trying to be you know chronically
and gross by the time I get to like 21
so I want to have nice and glowy skin
forever so I have been moisturizing a
lot more recently and I've truly but
actually seen like a major change in my
skin
I've been trying to cut out the Pepsi as
such as it hurts and drink a lot more
water too but honestly Ivan seemed like
such a major difference
I had this breakout so going on from my
New York trip but she's heading away
she's on the way out I told her to pack
her bags hopefully we'll be back to
Dewey and beautiful skin within the next
few weeks
fingers crossed in this amazing photo
Kendall's makeup artist hung it gave her
this beautiful dewy moisturize
foundation look as always that we all
strive for but can't really achieve
because it only looks good for about
five seconds but for today's look to
recreate this as closely as possible I'm
gonna use the Giorgio Armani luminous
silk foundation I'm going to be doing a
super super light coat of this
foundation all over my skin I really do
not want to do it like the full coverage
today I just want a very very light
layer just to even everything out but
still give us enough coverage to the
point where like our blemishes and red
spots are covered because Lord knows
thanks New York we have a lot of them
right now next I'm gonna grab the Tarte
shave tape concealer and this is in the
shade light/medium honey and I'm just
gonna use these slightest bit of this
just to go over any areas that have a
little bit more breakouts like right up
in here here here I'm basically just
applying a super light amount of this on
any areas that need a little bit more
coverage did you guys do luminous look
has a beautiful finish but doesn't have
the most coverage in the world so I'm
just gonna use this to just amp up those
areas and really make sure we have that
flawless but still a dewy finish when I
blend this in I'm just blending it in
super super lightly to make sure to just
bounce it in and blend it without
actually taking off I need the product
and then to actually bright and I'm
going to grab a shape tape once again
but this time in the shade a light and
I'm just gonna do a little bit of that
under both of the eyes then I'm just
going to grab the slightest bit of Laura
Mercier powder and I'm just going to
lightly set underneath my eyes and
that's actually about it
for the contour and Bronson a for once
in my life B cap on D shade and light
palette is nowhere to be seen on the
front of my table and sadang abusing the
benefit hoola light bronzer until Pilate
said I'm using my makeup Shack t 28
brush I think I've only used this
bronzer maybe once before because you
guys know sister James loves a good a
bronze a cut contour but for today
second I feel like I just want to keep
it really really light and do we just
like the photo of camel because it was
literally so stunning like my breath was
taken away and I want to recreate it as
closely as possible and Kendall was
really not too a contour she just had
like a nice bronze look going on for
brows that I'm going to quickly define
them using my Anasazi offense on the
shade medium at Brown in the photo that
Kendall's makeup artist shared she had a
super super thin and just really really
arched brows and those things are two
qualities that definitely are not
associated with James Charles brows
that's for sure so I'm just trying my
best to really define them the least
amount possible and just kind of fill
them in and give it a little bit more
shape but still keep them really really
the light and airy
just like kendall ash and lastly to
finish off the brows I'm just gonna go
to the Anasazi a clear brow gel and I'm
just gonna brush those hairs upwards to
create the light and fluffy feathered
brow effect to primary let's for Santa
I'm just gonna add a drop of the shape
tape light/medium honey on the lids and
then I'm just gonna blend that and using
my makeup Shack tee at 59 brush just to
give a light and even base for the
little bit of shadow that we're going to
put on there the hashed out of today
we're gonna be using the morphe 35o
palette and listen i know you guys are
probably so sick of hearing all about
this palette but trusty it is actually a
really really good palette I just feel
like with a lot of celebrity makeup we
all like look at these celebrities at
this beautiful glowing glam and we just
want to recreate them on ourselves but
oftentimes we feel as though because
they're celebrities they're usually
using like million-dollar makeup so
obviously the 3500 was a very very cheap
alternative to very very expensive
palettes it is $22 for 35 shades and you
guys can use code James for tempers and
love your purchase at morphe brushes
calm I
yeah it's gonna be a bomb pilot to serve
this look obviously used it ever a brown
orange home palette you want to but I'm
gonna go with this baby today to lay
down at light base in the crease I'm
gonna go with my makeup Shack t4 brush
and dip into this cool tone orange shade
right here for this actual makeup look
Kendall had her inner corner pretty
light and then it got more and more dark
and defined as we got to the outer
corner when we get to that super
snatched upward V which I am so excited
for but yeah for the starting shades I'm
gonna keep them very very light and just
make sure they are nice and evenly
blended out next I'm gonna grab my
makeup shock t-33 brush and dip into
this warm tone orange right up in here
I'm gonna focus this color on the outer
lid and then jog whatever is left up
into the crease and make sure they are
blended out and then a little bit into
the inner corner next under grab that
same exact brush and dip into this cool
tone Brown right below it and start to
define the outer corner I'm gonna be
very very slow impatient when layering
this color onto that outer third even
though this look is supposed to be like
that effortless glam look those looks
are usually the ones that actually take
the most amount of work ironically
enough so I'm just being super super
careful I'm blending it very very slowly
and lightly to make sure we still have
everything really really blown out and
even once you get to that outer corner
I'm also taking that shadow on the tip
of the brush and I'm going to start
winging outwards dipping into that same
last dark brown shade I'm gonna grab my
morphe r44 basically just use any angled
brush you want and I'm going to try to
sketch out that little wing that kind of
had it going on
then govern my makeup Shakti to brush
I'm just going to lightly blend out that
line and diffuse that darker color
inwards
and then one last time gonna grab that
t4 brush and just blend over those I
just make sure everything is really
really nice and defined but still a
blended well up together now that we had
this line all sketched out it is very
very defined looking and I'm loving how
it looks but I definitely do want to
clean it up the slightest bit but I feel
like using concealers is gonna make it
look too intense so I'm gonna do is grab
the Mac next to nothing studio nope just
kidding' just the next to nothing a
pressed powder and my makeup Shakti 86
brush and I'm gonna dab just the
lightest bit of that and I'm going to
use that powder just to kind of sketch
the bottom just to clean it up
oh yeah that literally looks a million
times better the lower lash line
normally the first thing I would do
would be line it so we can it then smoke
out the shadow below it but I actually
can't find a mile an hour that I was
gonna use I usually love using the NYX
tan liner I brought it out to film and
now I cannot find it anywhere so I'm
just gonna go into the benefit high brow
pencil instead is this eye safe I have
no idea
couldn't tell you but it's a light
off-white shade so it's gonna do the job
anyway
okay Wow I honestly have no idea this is
even safe for the eyes but it goes on
really really nicely and it's super
pigmented as well so sorry next guess
we're using benefit high brow from now
on for the lower lash line it's gonna be
super super simple I'm just gonna start
off with my 82 brush and dip into that
cool tone of brown right below our poor
orange shade that we use on the upper
lash line and I'm just oh there she is
I'm just using this brush and pressing
the shade right up into that lash line
just to create a little bit of a
defining moment and I am gonna bring
that shadow all the way into the inner
corner as well which is saying that I
normally don't do it but Kendall had it
so we're gonna do it today next I'm just
gonna grab my
t-49 brush and dip into the original
light orange shade that we used and just
buff out those edges to highlight my
inner corner and brow bone I'm gonna
grab my ETA t6 brush and dip into the
Laura Geller gilded honey highlighter
and there's going to push my brush a
little bit of a fix plus to make it
super intense and blinding
as we are only doing lashes today Lord
knows that wearing a lot of falsies
continuously it rips them out of my face
all the time which is so so sad so I
don't have very many lashes left to work
with I am gonna go into the lash curler
quickly and just snatch those lashes up
so just to help without defining a
process and then for mascara today I'm
going to be using the Maybelline Big
Shot mascara
all right status when I complete I'm
gonna go and do the other one off-camera
quickly and then I'll be right back with
you finish off the rest of the face
alright and that is both eyes all
complete and the next step of course is
going to be the glow I'm gonna use once
again gilded honey and I'm going to use
my Alexi 560 brush and I'm going to dip
into this and I'm going to put this
right on the highest points of my
cheekbones now I would normally would
never use fan brush when it comes to
highlighting because I don't know I just
have never like learned to use them but
I was watching desi Perkins new video
today where she tell her subscribers on
how to cover up cystic acne and it
looked so beyond Bom I was like so
intrigued the entire video but I noticed
when she got to her highlighter she used
a fan brush and I just looked so
freaking pretty sounds like you know
what if does he looks hot I want to look
hot too so I'm trying this outside and
honestly so far I don't actually hate it
I'm also gonna use this bar so I'm gonna
apply it right on the tops of my brow
bone on my forehead for that healthy and
natural glow okay I'm actually really
liking the way that a fan brush applies
highlighter this could be like a
freaking revelation up in here
oh look so pretty I'm gonna go that say
behind later on a tiny pencil brush and
I'm gonna use this to highlight my nose
now to finish this look off all we have
left is lips I'm first going to the Mac
strip down liner and just over line my
lips the slightest bit to give me a
little bit more dimension
oh my god these sirens are so annoying
[Music]
are we done yet nope
as in for the lips today we're gonna be
using the new dose of colors lipstick in
the shade butterscotch
just as Orca that's up these slightest
bit because we're looking a little bit
concealer here right now I'm gonna go
into the to face new melted latex liquid
gloss stick thing and put it on my lips
no
oh okay so I'm not really sure what you
would call this color now that we have
put on a lip liner a lipstick and then a
gloss over top men wiped off the gloss
because we didn't like it but whatever
is like lapped on the face right now is
exactly what I was going for so I guess
we're going to leave it all right guys
so this is the completed kendall jenner
inspired look I'm honestly at freaking
living for how this turned out I feel so
beautiful and bronze and just snatched
even though we're not even wearing that
much makeup if you guys see them to this
video don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below it subscribe if you
have not already I post two videos a
week on Mondays and Fridays and I'd love
to have you join at the sisterhood also
leave me a comment down below and tell
me if there's any other celebrities or
any other specific looks you'd like to
see me recreate I would love to do more
videos like this in the future I had so
much fun and this photo of Kendall was
just so freakin stunning are you
literally ha to sit down and do it for
you guys because so many people were
talking about and asking about it and it
was really a simple look to create all
together so like I said hope you enjoyed
this video and let me know if you want
me to do any other celebrities in the
future if you'd like to follow me on my
makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they are both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind in CSI stuff is James Charles the
next ask after Charles this week's
shout-out goes to a sister Madison thank
you so much for always following it
supporting girl I love you our
researchers thank you so much for
watching and I will see you in the next
one bye
[Music]