my sister my sister's James Charles here
and welcome back to my youtube channel
[Music]
cutting straight to the point as you can
see from the title down below and that
amazing intro clip today's video is
going to be reviewing the brand new at
k'kaw Kim kardashian-west Beauty line I
have been a huge fan of kim kardashian
for a very very long time now I think
she is so beautiful
so amazing and so talented and yes I do
say talented because of her girls of
what you think about her she turned one
little video into a billion dollar
empire her and her family they are by
far the most famous family in the entire
world and I respect their business
mindset so freaking much they're
absolute geniuses and such as I do love
Kim whoever at that being said she did
just released a beauty line I am a
beauty guru and that means today's video
is going to be a review and it is gonna
be completely and brutally honest no one
is safe not even sister Kim alright I'm
not rambling without further ado let's
go ahead and get on with the video
alright so before we actually hop in and
test out the contour six I do want to
apply a little bit of a base I was just
watching the Beauty tutorials on at
k'kaw calm with Kim and Mario and Kim
was definitely wearing a little bit of a
base when Mario did her makeup just for
a quick light based I'm gonna go ahead
and play the Giorgio Armani luminous sub
foundation in the shade 3.5 you guys
know if you follow me on Santa this is
actually not my favorite foundation I've
not had the best experience of this but
I do know Kim loves this and I want to
do my best to recreate her look as much
as possible
and I'm also just going to quickly
define my brows using my Anasazi
eyebrows in the shade medium brown just
to give a little bit more shape to my
face
all right so now that the base is all on
and I'm looking a little bit less pimply
and red let's go ahead and move on and
test out these contour sticks looking at
the k'kaw beauty website right now there
are four different sets that launched
and they are the cream contour
highlighting kits they're all sold out
so major congrats in camp but when they
were sold they did launch for $45 each
so for $45 you're actually getting two
different shades of contour stick two
different highlighters one being matte
and one being summery and a dual ended
brush one being a kabuki brush and one
being like a little sponge on the end so
honestly from $45 you're getting six
things now I obviously have not with
these on my face yet so I cannot really
tell you if it's worth it
but for the number of things are kidding
and the price definitely a pretty good
deal now the kids do come in four
different shades being light medium dark
and deep dark now four shades may not
seem like a lot but being at the actual
event yesterday and seeing them all in
person it goes from a really really
light to deep dark and trusted the deep
dark was actually pretty dark so that is
so awesome that Kim is not forgetting
about all the dark girls out there
because honestly they exist I have been
deciding between a light and medium but
for today's video I think I'm gonna be
actually using the medium kit y'all know
that I do like being a little bit more
bronzed and we're not trying to have
another flashback Mary moment so I'm
gonna be using the medium camp for today
I'm gonna open up medium in just a
second but that does leave me with light
dark and deep dark to use and less
virile I am definitely not gonna be
using these two so I don't think want to
give them away to you guys because they
did sell out super fast so if anybody
one of these it wasn't able to get their
hands on them make sure you get this
video a big thumbs up down below and
then leave me a comment and I will
definitely be picking a winner on
Monday's video to give these kits away
for you guys alright so let's go ahead
and open up the medium set and honestly
living through this packaging the new to
plastic bag is really really cute to be
honest I really really like it oh oh my
god okay so the products actually come
in an airtight sealed package as well
which is super awesome means they're
going to be fresh and definitely not
like damaged by the mail or anything so
that is amazing love her and don't love
the fact that I forgot to bring a pair
of scissors in okay
so okay so as promised this that comes
with two highlighting in contour six and
then a a brush as well so let's go ahead
and put these into at the test first and
things again the packaging is super cute
this is super cute this is also a lot
smaller than I expected - looking at the
Instagram post I thought this is gonna
be a whole lot bigger like I was
thinking like m-43 nine morphe saw a
kabuki brush but I was definitely wrong
so I'm definitely curious to see how
this is actually gonna work on the face
but I'm not gonna judge until we try
obviously so like I said I already have
a light base to foundation on so the
first thing I want to do is go into the
highlighting stick and I'm gonna open up
this end cracked with the matte
highlighting shade and I'm gonna use
this under the eyes just to brighten up
the high points of my face so I guess
I'm just gonna go right and use like a
normal concealer oh okay this is much
softer than I was expecting
oh my god it was really really good this
form is honestly going on really really
nicely I'm just putting in all the high
points my face when I only put my
concealer and then I'm just gonna try to
blend it in with the actual sponge to
see how it actually it blends together
rather the product is all and I'm just
gonna use the sponge to blend it and but
similar to a Beauty Blender I definitely
want to wet it so I'm just gonna spritz
it using my Tarte
Ready Set radiant skin mist just to get
it a little wet
we're then just gonna go ahead and blend
her in okay woah so let me get this
close up this sponge definitely takes
off a lot of the products like I don't
know if you can see actually on camera
but my skin is definitely showing
thinners I don't know about this but I
think I wanted to have my face using the
sponge on the end of the brush and then
the other half using of my Beauty
Blender oh good idea James so then we
can see how they actually compare
because I want to give the product a
fair chance I just went ahead and I
apply it more matte highlighter to the
other side of my face that I use the
sponge on this is definitely a major
fail for me it's picking up a lot of the
product and it's just not letting out
very very nicely but I haven't used the
Kabuki brush store and I get to this
when we get to the contour but this bomb
is definitely not my favorite I am gonna
go ahead and use my Beauty Blender just
to blend everything else out though
because I want to get the product a fair
chance you haven't even gotten to see
what it looks like yet so let's go ahead
and wonder out all right there we go was
so much better oh my god
when in doubt beauty blend it out
alright so once that is all blended up
it is definitely looking really really
beautiful on the skin I'm thinking that
this was probably like a medium type
cover
it definitely like even everything out
and actually did a pretty good job of
covering my under-eye bags as well but
it definitely is like not full coverage
because I can still see my skin
underneath it but I do like that so this
is definitely a pretty good product so
far definitely does not like being the
sponge but I'm glad we went in with the
Beauty Blender because this is pretty
bomb well get back to the shimmer end of
the highlighting SEC towards the end of
the video but let's move on with the
contour so opening up the stick we have
a light contour end and a darker contour
and this is the medium stick keep in
mind and in the video that Kim posted
she said she likes to use the lighter
end of the stick to do like her nose
contour and sometimes even like
eyeshadow under and lower but she likes
to use the darker stick to contour the
rest of her face so we're gonna do the
exact same thing today I'm first gonna
use the lighter end of the stick to it
snatch my nose I would like to contour
the bottom window so it kind of like
lifts it up and just gives it a little
bit of like a cute doll like a fact and
you guys know that I definitely love a
good at pinch nose I'm putting these
lines pretty close together
okay I'm not just realizing that I
happen to use the darker under the
second way nose contour and not the
lighter atoms imagine if I like actually
paid attention took my time on something
for three seconds okay okay so moving on
looks fun with the contour and I'm first
gonna use the lighter end of the stick
it's almost like a bronzer so just gonna
put this in the hollows that only two
brings pretty far up as well on both
sides and I'm just placing this right
underneath my cheekbone to really lift
it up and chisel it out and I'm also
gonna grab this lighter shaded I'm gonna
put it right on the forehead because
y'all know that I hate my look as short
and small as possible next going back
into the darker and I'm going to use
this to really contour out the deepest
point that liam8 the very outside edge
of the forehead and then the very very
bottom of the cheekbones as well as the
going to really
all right so like I said this sponge was
definitely not my favorite but the
Kabuki end is still here so they only
want to give this a shot and test it out
with the contour
I'm not really sure who in their right
mind would ever contour their nose using
computers but that really did not do
that out of a job of blending it oh I am
gonna completely go back in with that I
definitely dip it a lot of contour as
well so I am gonna go back into once
again with the highlighting stick
underneath just to redefine it a little
bit oh my god yeah when you use the
Beauty Blender this literally blends out
so nice and evenly like this looks so
freakin good okay so once this is all
blended out this honestly does look
really really really pretty similar to
the highlighting stick the contour stick
formula is bomb it blends out so
beautifully and looks really really
natural on the skin which I love
definitely not full coverage but enough
coverage to the point where like you get
the color there and it makes a beautiful
impact Ashley's like a Buki brush it's
not bad I am someone who never ever uses
brushes to blend out creams or
foundations I'm just not the type of
artist I really have never understand
when people do just because I feel like
kabuki brushes do always rub a
foundation it kind of makes things look
uneven that being said this did one out
really really nicely it honestly was not
really rubbing off the foundation it
just went on really really beautifully
it applied nicely but I did have to
really work at it so I kind of like do a
mixture of windshield wiper motions and
topping to make sure I wasn't lifting
anything up but once it was applied it
was definitely applied and looked nice
I'm just really not a brush type of
person but you might be so definitely
check this out it's not bad this on the
other hand it's not great all right so
now that all the countries it's all
complete let's go ahead and get deep
glow on so for this we're gonna use
these shimmery pearl the highlighting
stick obviously let's go ahead and do a
little swatch on the hand
oh it actually looks really really
pretty that was like a very very subtle
not the lion dink low but that's
definitely what Kim was going for when
she was talking about this yesterday
definitely just like a glow from with
Anna but let's see how she applies on
the face I need to let pop her on in the
inner corners on the courts I have been
loving putting a little bit of how
they're up here recently - for that like
to e4 hand block and then also on the
cheekbone and then I'll just with you my
beauty butter and lately a blend this
out okay not bad as you can see it's
definitely pretty it's not blinding by
any means but I actually really really
like this now don't get me wrong you
guys know I love I've got a blinding
highlight all the time but I think this
product is really really good for just
like the everyday person who just wants
to like look really moisturized radiant
like glowing from within but doesn't
wanna look like they have 54 different
pounds of like metallic highlighting
glow pigment all over their face like I
said I haven't fallen camp for a very
very long time and we all know she used
to pack on the makeup like full be full
contour full eye shadow glam highlight
to the gods but more recently she's been
rocking like the very very dewy natural
just moisturize skin look and I think
she looks so beyond beautiful so this
set is definitely like her new makeup
style packed into one set and I really
like that alright so now that all the
products are locked in and we're looking
nice and snatched in the video with kim
mario definitely recommended using a
light coat of setting powder just to set
everything in place and actually so
beyond stuff right now because i
completely forgot about the fact that
there is not an ounce of powder on my
face yet this is literally all liquid
foundation and then cream products
overtop but you guys know that I
definitely love packing on the powder a
lot but there's literally no powder on
my face in this books it's so beautiful
like there's no creasing it just looks
natural I'm honestly living for it oh my
god I'm just gonna do the lightest
dusting
just so if I touch my face it doesn't
like come right off or anything all
right so that is the base all complete
I'm honestly really really liking how
this looks so far and last but finally
not least in the videos Kim said she
does use these for her eye shadow as
well so why not just try something out
let's just take a little bit from there
I don't have anywhere to go might as
well give it a shot
dropping the lighter under the condo SEC
I'm just gonna place this right on the
eyelid now nervous gonna use my fingers
to literally lightly blend this down and
then grabbing the darker and I'm gonna
go in the inner and outer corners to
kind of create a defined halo eye type
of of that and then once again just
having my fingers to it lightly blend it
out and then for a pop I'm gonna grab
the shimmery highlighter and I'm gonna
place it on the center of okay wow we
literally just created a bronzy halo eye
and the matter of like two minutes and
honestly it does not look half bad I'm
gonna go ahead and I'm gonna lock my
face in place using the Urban Decay all
nighter setting spray - the finished
look
all right so let's go ahead and talk
about these products all right so once
again the k'kaw beauty hiding contouring
cream set comes with two dual ended
contour six and another dual ended brush
and sponge contraption thingy as for the
holiday and contouring sticks they
definitely have like a medium level of
coverage they do a good job of like
evening everything out and just giving a
nice little defining moment but they are
overpowering to the point where you're
like full coverage hiding Impuls acne
and stuff like that you can still see
your natural skin underneath which I
personally like if you are a full
coverage type of person you can
definitely layer and build it up but
regardless they're bomb as for this
sister right here this was definitely
more of a Miss for me I'd really didn't
like the sponge it's definitely pretty
dense and I just was like it didn't do
that great of a job of really blending
off the product I felt as though it was
really removing the product rather than
actually blending it and that's
obviously never what we want is was a
kabuki brush and it actually went on a
very braid nicely I definitely was being
really really careful and had to work on
it a little bit more but when I was
doing it this down
did a really great job of just flooding
up the product evenly and smoothly
without ripping off any of the
foundation which is really really great
because I definitely have a personal
vendetta against using brushes for
foundations but this obviously did a
really really great job I definitely
loved using the Beauty Blender to blend
these out it just did so much of a
better job but this definitely is not
bad by any means I just really did like
the sponge and I'm not really a brush
person but it's really not bad and that
even being said obviously it's her first
launch her first collection these
products are brand spanking new so it's
not like everything's gonna be perfect
on the first try let's be real look at
sister Kylie for example so many things
went wrong on the first launch but now
after many many launches and new
products she arguably has some of the
best on the market so I definitely it's
gonna take a lot of launches and stuff
to Kim to get everything perfect but
definitely a really really great star do
I think this collection is worth
checking out for $45 absolutely even if
you exclude the blending tool you're
still getting four different shades of
highlighting and contouring sticks for
only $45 I think that is so Bob
especially being associated with a
celebrity name like Kim Kardashian
you're definitely gonna want to check
these guys out all right guys and that
is all I have for this video I just want
to say a major thank you to all of you
guys watching you all truly do mean so
much to me and I would not be here
without you
if you guys did enjoy this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below subscribe if you have not
already I post two videos we got Mondays
and Fridays and I'd love to have you
join the sisterhood if you'd like to
follow me on I make up turn you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind the scenes type
stuff who knows maybe I'll be here with
sister Kim again soon you definitely
wouldn't want to add me as just James
Charles with an extra ask after Charles
all right guys thank you so much for
watching I love you so much and I will
see you in the next video
[Music]