hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel oh if
you really thought we were done with
just those brushes you were wrong sister
in case you guys been living under a
rock living legend Kylie Jenner just
released a ton of brand-new products to
her makeup line for the holiday season
not only did she released two eyeshadow
palettes but she also sent the beauty
world into flames and she announced her
$360 luxury brush set I just interview
on that in the last video so if you have
not yet checked out my brand new video
on that make sure to click right up here
but she also launched a full line of
concealers just like always that ever
Kylie's name was attached there has been
a ton of controversy on these babies
right up in here so I got my hands on
the full line of all 30 concealers and
today we're gonna put them to the test
you guys know that I am a loyal Stan of
the tape tape concealer I love this and
I use this all the time and almost every
single look but not even gonna lie I am
getting a little bit bored of having the
same exact makeup routine at every
single time I have another point right
now where I just want to be more
creative and try out new products so who
knows maybe this concealers will be
amazing but we're about to find out just
to clarify as usual when it comes to
reviews because you guys know some
people are crazy in that comment section
this video is not sponsored I am NOT
being paid to say anything
I love Kylie but I'm not on her BR list
so this is completely unbiased even
playing field these might be amazing it
these might suck we're gonna find out
together
we're laut further ado let's go ahead
and jump into the review
[Music]
so before we actually go into the our
makeup routine today let's go ahead and
talk about the actual product itself so
the day that I'm filming this is
December 13 I'm not exactly sure when
this video it's gonna go but it should
be up relatively soon after that but the
skin concealers launched today on Kylie
cosmetics and she says they are
lightweight and designed to give a
flawless skin line finish contrary to
Kylie's absolutely ridiculous price tag
on her breasts at these consumers will
be retailing for $20 each on her website
when these lunch which I actually feel
is a very very fair price
looking at Sephora I'm looking at other
concealer prices like the NARS radiant
creamy concealer I think it's $30 Urban
Decay Naked skin I think is 29 the NARS
soft concealer is 30 Kat Von D is 26
makeup forever is 34 and cosmetics is 24
and I believe shape tape is 28 to find
correct so this is definitely honestly
on the lower end of some of the
concealer price tags this is the
component it comes in and based on the
bottom of the package it comes with a
point 22 fluid ounces of product in
comparison to shape tape my shape tape
has point 33 fluid ounces of products so
you get a little bit more in this and
then the very popular color pop no
filter concealer comes with only point
14 fluid ounces so this is probably a
middle of the line when it comes to
actual amount of product that you're
given moving on let's go ahead and talk
about the shade range because that has
also been a very very controversial
subject of this launch
so Kylie's concealers launched with 30
different shades starting with the shade
of pearl in the top left with the
lightest shade and the bottom right
shade being a cocoa which is the darkest
looking at the contrast between the
lightest shade and the darkest shade
together I think that this contrast is
honestly very very impressive there's
obviously a huge lack of diversity and
the makeup industry and I really wish
brands was hard to recognize more people
of color bloggers there are so many
beautiful and talented ones out there
that deserve equally as much cosmetic
recognition I really wish it wasn't the
case for a shade this dark is like
something to applaud over but like I
said the laka diversity and the beauty
industry has caused it to be so honestly
good job sister Kylie for doing this
obviously a few months ago Rihanna
chopped her fmt beauty line which
literally had the entire nation shook
she had 40 different colors in her
foundation which i think was so so
incredible and honestly I think she set
the standard for future launches
literally every time I go into Sephora
at this point most of the middle section
and literally the entire darker section
of the Fanta Beauty line is always sold
out what you think is so
so great but a lot of people are
comparing this launch of Kylie's
concealers to Fenty beauty's foundation
having darker foundation chains has
always been a major issue for a lot of
huge beauty brands and I think fenty
vidi has now really changed the game
when it comes to shade range a lot of
people are very very angry with kylie
and a lot of people are saying that
she's just copying rihanna and my
opinion it feels a little bit weird to
fight in favor of a really really large
shade range which is really really great
but that have Kylie come out with her 30
different shades and then turn around
and say that she's doing it wrong and
get angry with her forehead I don't know
though I am definitely not at a place to
be showing my opinions about this and I
don't want to speak over anybody so I'm
definitely looking forward to watching
hopefully Jackie I know Alyssa Ashley
unnie Batangas video about these
concealers because I really want to hear
what they have to say quickly before we
begin I want to swatch for you guys the
lightest and darkest shades just to show
the contrast first we have the lightest
shade of Kylie's concealer which is the
shade pearl then we have the latest
shade of shape tape which is fair and
then finally we have color pops latest
shade which is in the shade a fair five
out of the three of these Kylie's of the
lightest and then we have the darker
shades and just to clarify these
swatches are not to help anybody find
the right color this is simply just to
show contrast first we have Kylie's
darkest shade which is called cocoa then
we have a Tarte shape tape which is in
the shade mahogany and then finally we
have color pop in the shade of wrench 75
your cars out of all these once again it
Kylie's is the darkest whoa that took a
very very long time and now that we have
all the logistics out of the way and you
guys know all the details let's go ahead
and actually put this concealer to the
test
originally on her snapchat she said that
they were definitely lightweight and
buildable for a very very natural type
look so that's exactly what I'm gonna do
today I am gonna be filming it a little
bit with a very very fun friend so I do
want to do a kind of more like glam look
as opposed to something super intense so
I'm just starting off by priming my skin
using the Mac stroke cream in the shade
like the gold one just for very very do
we look for foundation I'm using my Too
Faced Born This Way Foundation in the
shade nude and I'm gonna doing just a
light layer of this I'm not gonna go
full intense coverage like I normally do
so I brought up my Tarte shave deep in
the shade light which is one that I
always use to my everyday makeup routine
and by looking at the collection I
determined that my best shade is
probably gonna be
gypsum I'm just going to go into this
concealer in place and
my normal location starting off under my
eyes I'm also gonna pull this down my
nose bridge as always because you guys
know that I like to it snatch the nose
in comparison to say page just because I
know that that's what I use in a lot of
you guys use as well it is definitely a
lot more light weight when I put it on
it doesn't feel so like clunky but
hopefully that doesn't mean that the
coverage won't be as good let's go ahead
and blend in oh wow
okay actually blends out really really
easily damn okay Kylie did not come to
play I don't know if you guys can really
tell on camera with all these lights but
obviously you guys know that I talk with
a lot of expression in my face and I
just raised my eyebrows a little bit to
set underneath my eyes and now I have
really really bad creases so hopefully
this consider doesn't get too crazy and
when I set it with powder it'll fix
itself I'm gonna grab a lighter
concealer in the shade stole from the
collection and I'm just gonna put this
right in the inner corners underneath my
eyes just to try to build up the
coverage a little bit and brighten
because I feel like the lash eight I use
which was gypsum was a little bit too
close to my natural skin tone not even
being dramatic this actually blends out
like a dream like this is going on very
very smoothly it's not picking up any of
the foundation underneath and definitely
it's like pretty decent coverage too I
know it says light carpet on it but I
actually feel like this might be more of
a medium coverage and if it is light
it's definitely buildable because as you
guys saw when they out of that second
layer it definitely added a lot more
pigment and my under eye bags are like
literally gone and I got I think three
hours of sleep last night so this is
kind of a pressed that before we start
cruising all over I'm just going to
blend out below my eyes and then grab my
translucent powder and my Beauty Blender
and just underneath there to make sure
it is in place I'm also gonna pack this
on my nose set up the forehead to make
sure I don't get any crusty wrinkles and
then just using access to go over thrust
my face not going in too intense because
I do want it to be kind of doing today
and not too matte but obviously we want
our makeup to say on looking in the
mirror I absolutely love how this works
so far I was able to layer up the cover
so it looks super super nice my under
eye bags are literally gone honestly it
looks really belief flawless I'm so
pleasantly surprised
I didn't think they're gonna be bad but
I was not ready for this shape tape
maybe quaking by the end of this video
but obviously we have a lot more to go
but the one thing that I will say
and with the amount of light going on
and skin Swilly filters there is no way
that you're gonna be able see this on
camera but it is here you're just kind
of trust me on this one I promise if you
are a fellow glasses wearer like me you
know those red circles that we get right
up in here on the nose bridge from other
classes sound your nose there's
literally like permanently embedded into
my face I can kind of see the circles
peeking through on both sides the
concealer does not cover them fully but
then again this does not claim to be a
full coverage concealer so it's
definitely not a deal-breaker
all right guys the other my face is all
set in place and ready to go I'm gonna
go ahead and finish them off my makeup
routine and then I'll be right back to
do a little check it and then I'm gonna
wear this for a few hours and we're
gonna put it to the test it looks really
great right now but who knows and a few
hours that may be creepy and gross and
completely worn off we're gonna have to
find out alright scissors it has been
about one hour now and I just finished
out my makeup like I said I was gonna go
for this light everyday look I added
some fake freckles and no lashes and
just nice and it's later growls I love
how this book turned out I feel
absolutely stunning but the point of
this video is not this look it is the
concealer like I said it has only been
one hour now but it still looks really
really bomb I did cover up my cheek
region obviously with freckles but you
can still tell under the eyes right here
it still looks very very bright it isn't
actually creasing either which is really
really great my forehead looks fine and
my moustache region looks fine and
there's no creases everything looks
really really good and I'm honestly
extremely impressed I have to have out
to see a few different rents right now
but I'm gonna take you guys along with
me and we're going to do some check-ins
every few hours to see if this concealer
stays in place all night long
okay sisters we are doing a talk to
check in and what better person to do
Otaki check in then so I'm wearing a new
product on my face right now I would
love for you to tell me what you think
about my skin right now okay the
foundation looks really nice I like the
highlight I like the whole like brow
highlight inner corner moment you have
going on I dig that the freckle area did
you make it darker yeah I did I put some
bronzer on and some blush on to like
okay to make it look like youthful like
I was sunkissed but thinking more
specifically about like complex it's a
contested the Kylie concealers of course
this is like the hot product shocker
I've seen better okay I don't know it
looks a little powdery were you ladies
loving it I honestly was I was a little
bit shocked because I didn't I didn't
think they're gonna be bad but I wasn't
expecting much and I was actually really
pleasantly surprised and looking at them
compared to what they look like an hour
ago I feel like they still look exactly
the same just an hour mm-hmm your under
eyes don't look bad I think the thing
that I'm noticing is the Sunkist thing
you did is throwing off a little bit of
the brightness well I feel like I met I
felt like after I do that I was like oh
maybe not the best example for handle is
it full coverage or just like it's light
coverage but I felt like when I put it
on it was more medium coverage which I
definitely was not upset about and then
I was able to layer actually really well
so it is buildable for sure I mean I
want to show lack my face life rocks I
process are taught to the entire light
range of the concealers this is pretty
full coverage yeah I feel like this is
this is actually really nice I agree I'm
not breaking the rules you never really
want to put concealer on top of powder
but I'm just gonna see what happens I've
been wearing this makeup all day long
that's actually the way to do it if you
really really need a touch-up with your
concealer like put it on the back of
your hand with a sponge and then you can
kind of just get the tiniest amount I've
never done that before but I'm horrified
really just kind of like touched up the
situation I like it I do too
I was like and it's only 20 dollars to
it which I feel like is honestly it's
way deeper than it's change it's not
it's not 360 it's not I I think it's
good but obviously I need to keep
writing this if they're out tonight and
I will keep you guys posted it's been
two hours now I think it still is going
up pretty strong under eyes may look a
little bit dry but that's just good I'll
keep you guys posted alright sister I
just got back home from it very very fun
night out with friends and it's
currently
11:37 p.m. at night
this means this makeup has been on for
just over eight hours now I definitely
am really ready to take this off and go
to bed but let's do our final check-in
and final thoughts so this is Kelly I
face after eight hours of wearing with
absolutely no touch-ups I mean we can
tell it's getting a little bit crust to
get this point I'm definitely
getting some creases around this area
I'm definitely looking a little bit oily
as well but honestly I don't hate it you
guys know that I've honestly been loving
it the more natural dewy skin rips loose
on kind of living for this like lift and
makeup look but let's discuss the actual
concealer and like the under-eye region
looking in the mirror like I said my
face is a little bit do get oily right
now which I kind of like but if I touch
like right here or in the side of my
forehead it definitely feels a little
bit oily but if I touch underneath my
eyes it is literally bone-dry or like
I'm talking Sahara Desert level you guys
saw that when I asked how do you a my
under eyes she did did if they looked a
little bit dry to me personally
obviously I see myself with makeup on
every single day I do not see that this
might be a little bit weird to say and
definitely may comment down below if you
think otherwise but I actually feel like
my under eyes look a little bit better
than normal I feel like the brightness
is still very much there like you can
not see my under-eye bags
peeking through at all and I feel like
the crease such level on them is a
little bit less than normal as well
aside from the aesthetic self on a
feeling level my under eyes do feel
ridiculously dry I feel like 20 dollars
for the amount of product you're getting
is actually a really really fair price
especially in comparison to some of the
other high-end more popular concealers
on the market right now on Kylie's
Instagram she said that this was a light
coverage but buildable concealer and I
would agree with her on that and
definitely went on a pretty light but I
was able to layer over top of it for a
more full coverage and brightening
effect and I actually really really love
how this looked on my under eyes and on
the rest of my face today I will say
though that this formula is pretty
drying it looked absolutely beautiful on
my skin before I said it with a lot of
powder but you guys know sister James
needs a whole lot of powder I do have a
combination to oily skin so I think that
if you have my skin type this will be
really really perfect for you because
it'll dry down a little bit and just
sent really beautifully into place but I
think that if you have dry skin this may
be a no-go because it might look a
little bit crusty and dusty just like my
under eyes were a little bit close to
getting today I think that the one major
flaw with us that may defer you from
getting to concealer as the fact that
Kylie is an e-commerce brand
I know Kylie has been doing her little
Kylie truck thing that like goes around
all different stops in LA and love
people try out different products what
you think is really really great
obviously she does not have any stores
where you can actually test the products
and and what I find really really great
about these concealers is that Kylie
doesn't do returns so if you order a
shade it's a completely wrong shade
you're stuck with it and you have 20
on the train if this is a product that
you want to check out I would definitely
recommend it doing your research
especially when it comes to your shade
range I would very much recommend
finding another beauty blogger or
influencer who has purchased that
concealers or receive them NPR that has
a similar skin tone to you and trying to
figure out what shade really works so
you can make an educated decision just
our reference for those of you guys out
there who are close to my skin tone my
two favorite foundations are my Too
Faced Born This Way in the shade a nude
and eye makeup forever stick in the
shade why 315 and I usually like my
concealer to be one or two shades
lighter so in shape tape I'm in the
shade of light and therefore in the
Kylie concealer I am in the shade gypsum
overall after testing out this concealer
and my makeup routine and wearing it for
eight hours straight I think that Kylie
has a winner on her hands
alright says it is literally getting so
late and I need to get my beauty rest
tonight I really hope you guys enjoyed
this video testing out the brand new
Kylie cosmetics concealers there has
been so much controversy about these
that I was honestly very very excited to
test them out definitely become a down
below and tell me what you think will
you be purchasing them and you think
they look good on me do you think they
look crusty and dusty and dry definitely
me comment down below I can't wait to
read what all your sisters have to say
if you did enjoy this video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and click that big red subscribe
button come to the sisterhood click that
little bell icon so you can be notified
every time I upload a brand new video
don't forget I'm currently in the middle
of my sister give a slay week I'll be
doing 12 huge huge twos giveaways all
leading up to Christmas with one big a
final giveaway happening on Christmas
Day if you would like to enter just give
this video a big thumbs up down below
you have to be subscribed to my channel
and follow me on my Instagram and then
leave me a comment telling me your name
your age and what you would like for
Christmas don't forget to follow me on
snapchat as well which is James Charles
the next year asked after Charles over
all my stories I'll be posting all the
different giveaway prizes and the
winners one day after they're announced
this week sister shout out goes to
sister Zoe thank you so much for your
always smiling it's a party you know I
literally love you so so so much and if
you would like to meet the next video
sister shut up make sure to always reach
8 video links and then go live on
Twitter all right sisters thank you so
much for watching I love you the most
ever in the entire world and I will see
you in the next one bye
[Music]