hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
cutting straight to the point I'm going
to a very very fun event tonight and I
have a lot that I want to talk to you
guys about I feel like we haven't sat
down and really done the chit chat
already to me for a very very long time
I mean my clothing line lunch and I am
so excited to see all of you guys
rocking all the sisters hoodies and then
my music came out lastly can my acapella
group you guys were so excited about it
and I am so excited about it and there
are so many more fun covers coming soon
I also took a little bit of a break and
had a little bit of a breakdown on
Twitter a few weeks ago as well which I
definitely want to talk about so yeah
one little thing I forgot to mention
before this chitchat with me get started
this video is sponsored by covergirl so
thank you so much to them don't forget
to watch until the very end to see me
try out their brand-new I'm melting pout
lipsticks and yeah without further ado
grab your popcorn Geiger Pinkett Eve
Jenkins because this is going to be a
long one and let's get glam so I'm
obviously starting off with my base
already done I went ahead and did my
foundation at concealer of brows and
contour and powdered everything
off-camera same exact routine that I use
every single time so let's just go in
with the eyes for today's eye shadow
look we're gonna be using two very very
unique palettes that I never use on my
channel being the morphe 35o and the
morphe 35o palette I want to create like
a sunset I look so I'm gonna start off
by guarding my m4 for one brush and dip
into this late transition
oMG shade right here and put it in the
crease while I'm doing my eyes I do
definitely wanna talk about the negative
with you guys before we get into the fun
and positive things for the remainder
and majority of this video but I do just
want to address this and that is kind of
why I took a little bit of a break from
YouTube and social media for a few days
and also why I've been a little bit down
in the dumps when it comes to like
Twitter and filming lately I feel like a
lot of social media influencers just
live their lives and our lives look so
crazy and fun to you guys on the outside
but on the inside there's a lot of stuff
that goes on behind the scenes and a lot
of emotions behind it and I feel like a
lot of people don't like to talk about
that and I definitely happen to talk
about that a lot I'm next intagram IM
433 and dip into this warm tone orange
shade away over here I would definitely
talk to you guys about how I was feeling
and sometimes being a social media
influence or having an online
personality is really really hard
and I'm not talking about on a physical
level because let's be real we literally
sit in front of a camera and make
freakin makeup tutorials in our
underwear for a living so I definitely
am NOT talking about on a physical level
but on an emotional level is where this
job can be sometimes really really
really stressful and super overwhelming
up next we have another clean M for
three three and dip into the Mac blush
in the shade sketch simply because I
don't have a good maroon eyeshadow that
I really like I know when it comes to a
lot of social media influencers
including myself a lot of us like to
pretend that hate comments don't get to
us I mean you always see us doing like
reading hate home videos or posting hate
tweets on Twitter just to give like a
good laugh for you guys but honestly at
the end of the day I don't care what
anybody says one thousands and thousands
and thousands I hate comments are coming
in eventually they're gonna start to get
to you and is sometimes really really
hard to focus on the positive when there
is so much negativity on the internet
let's be real I've definitely made a lot
of mistakes in the past that I am not
proud of but I've apologized and own up
to every single one of them which i
think is really really vital in order to
grow and become a better person but
let's also be real and saying that I
definitely am an easy target for the
internet to pick on in laughi at the end
of the day a lot of people said that
hate comments don't get to them
including myself I really try hard and
not let hate give to me I'm just to
focus on the positivity because there is
so much positivity with you guys but
when you do start to receive thousands
and thousands of hate comments on like a
video or a tweet that you pose it really
can put a lot of pressure on you and
make you start to question your morals
and why are doing what you do and for me
if that happens relatively often have
you been following me on snap or Twitter
for a while you would know that there
was a time about two weeks ago where I
had a little bit of a breakdown on
snapchat video I was filming and I did
actually end up taking a break from
social media completely for a few days
because everything just got really
really overwhelming and I want you guys
to know that it's okay I'm nice tender
grab that same M for three three and dip
into at these two purple shades right
here and use that to deepen up the
crease when I talk about this openly
with you guys I don't want you to think
I'm complaining or ungrateful in any way
shape or form because but isn't the case
at all in fact what I tweeted that I
needed a few days to take a mental break
I got so many amazing messages from all
of you guys that completely understood
where I was coming from which meant the
entire world to me I also got a lot of
tweets and messages saying oh my god
you're 18 years old living in the middle
of LA like I said I am so thankful to be
living a very very kind life thanks to
you guys but at the end of the day there
is no amount of money that can buy
happiness
trust me on this one and unfortunately
with this job often comes a lot of
pressure like I said and a lot of
responsibility and a lot of negativity
as well so sometimes that happiness can
be really really hard to find no matter
how much money is in your bank account
no matter how many cool opportunities
you're having it no matter what car you
drive where you're living
happiness comes from within and
sometimes no matter who you are what
you're doing what your job is you need
to take a mental break because mental
health is so so so so so important and
definitely needs to come before any type
of post on social media I don't want to
sound like I'm complaining or ungrateful
in any way shape or form there are so
many more important and awful things
going on in the world right now that
make my issues literally non-existent
but I do just want to have an open
conversation with you guys about this
because I know it's something that not a
lot of influencers address but I
definitely do and I know a lot of you
guys do look up to me as well not only
for makeup but also for life advice
which means literally the entire world
to me and I do try best to be a good
role model obviously of course we're
gonna fail sometimes but if you were
like me a few weeks ago and you do get
in a rut or you're not feeling creative
or inspired take a few days off do it
every night or do to get your heart back
in the game mental health is so
important so sometimes taking a break is
totally okay and I definitely wanted to
share that message with you guys I know
it's well a lot of people were wondering
whether or not I was gonna quit YouTube
and obviously hello I am here I don't
plan on leaving anytime soon I have a
lot of really really good content coming
out and a lot of products that I'm
working on that I am literally so
excited for you guys to see but like I
said definitely needed a few days off
but sister is back and ready to go so
now that we have up all the negative out
of the way thank God we can focus on the
positive but before we get into that I'm
gonna grab some more shave tape in the
shade lights and and just put a little
bit on the back of my hand and grabbing
my way to go morphe and a four-to-one
brush I'm gonna cut the crease and then
quickly keeping my head tilted back so
it doesn't crease I'm gonna grab my M 4
to 5 brush and dip into my Kodi Ariston
powder and then set that concealer in
place and then without saying M 45 brush
I'm just gonna dip into this light bone
color shade up in here and just set that
in place for once I'm actually gonna
keep this eye look fully matte aside
from the Bravo and Haley of course but I
really it's been a long time since I've
done a matte crease I usually end up
doing some type of a
shimmer on the lid but I'm kind of
getting tired of that right now so why
don't do a little bit of a matte sunset
look okay so onto a more positive note
while I clean up this crease please but
so many fun things have been happening
lately and I'm so excited that you guys
are finally getting to see them if you
saw last week my clothing line sister's
apparel finally dropped and you guys
went crazy I think we literally sold
almost 2,000 hoodies in under 24 hours
which is literally so insane I cannot
wait for you guys to all get your
sister's hoodies so you can take me your
little pictures and your flashback
Mary's oh my god I just cannot wait I've
been working on such as apparel for
literally so long and I'm just so
excited that you guys are equally as
excited as I am and I also have a lot of
fun designs planned for the future as
well and a lot of things that are being
manufactured that are a lot more
complicated than just hoodies and hats
so definitely keep your eyes peeled
because I bake big plans for sister's
apparel also if you guys saw my acapella
group flashback released our first ever
cover this past Friday on my youtube
channel and I cannot even thank you guys
enough for the positive response we got
so many of you guys absolutely love the
song and we were so so so nervous but
also excited to put it out music
obviously is a huge huge aspect of our
life that you guys really do not get to
see much up until recently on my youtube
channel but I'm very very excited that I
get to share that with you guys now and
we have so many exciting covers coming
soon on Pascha that you guys are going
to love this is just very very exciting
for me because I've been singing with my
best friend Anthony who's actually in
the crew many of you guys know him since
literally we were in third grade and
we've been trying to put together an
acapella group for literally like almost
10 years now so we are so excited that
we finally have a really good at group
of solid super super talented kids that
all share the same love for music so
definitely keep your eyes peeled for
future flash projects because it is
definitely a group you were going to
want to watch trust me on that one I
think this look definitely needs a
little bit of a wing so I'm gonna grab
my Kat Von D tattoo liner in the shade
trooper and just sketch out a sharp eye
swing ready to cut somebody that is
definitely a large in the charged wing
but honestly I am kind of living for it
I'm gonna grab my e43 brush from morphe
and then a little bit more shape tape
and just clean up the shadow below the
way
I'm next area by NYX wonder pencil in
the shade of light and just put that in
my waterline same exact thing with the
upper that I'm gonna first off with my
m4 for one and a bright orange shade and
disc all really really lightly
underneath the eye to create a
transition shade I'm also not breaking
the shade fully to the inner corner
either because I do like to when I do
these paper I looks cut out that inner
corner so it makes my eyes look a little
bit bigger and wider I'll show you guys
in a second I'm next I'm gonna have an M
at 213 and dip into that dark purple
shade from the 35b and connect the
winged liner and use this to hug the
lash line when I have this rush my hand
with the purple when I get to the inner
corner I'm going to really really
lightly pull that forward as opposed to
following my natural eye shape and going
up I'm just creating kind of a second
little crease up in here and then I'm
gonna clean that up with concealer in
this area this is very similar to drag
makeup which just makes my eyes look a
little bit bigger then once again we're
gonna grab Miami 151 and dip into the
Mac blush and the shade is sketch to
blend together that orange and purple
alright so that is when I all completed
that was simply a very very lengthy
process and turned out a lot more
intense and I was planning on a but I
really really like this look so far so
I'm gonna go into the other one off
camera quickly and I'll be right back to
finish off the rest of the eyes and the
rest of the face alright so that is the
other eye all complete this is
definitely a lot more intense of a look
than I was originally expecting or going
for but I'm honestly it kind of loving
for it or kind of loving for it oh my
god
four lashes today I'm gonna go to the
Lily lash in the style Alena these
lashes are so so so beautiful they're
like very very good because they're big
on the outside but tiny on the inside
I definitely like these a lot what I'm
doing this I make sure to get super
close up to the root of the lash right
up in that upper waterline just because
I don't ever do it black in the upper
waterline anymore because it always
makes me super uncomfortable where
throughout the day I always find myself
picking at my lashes at my waterline
because it always ends up transferring
and it just makes my eyes feel really
really bad so I stopped doing that and
it's made my life I don't see a million
times easier but now that I do mascara I
have to really make sure it's black up
in that region so it doesn't look really
really dumb when I'm looking forward
like this sensor is a sunset look I
definitely wanna have a very golden
sunkissed highlight going on so of
course I'm gonna grab my Anasazi upsell
Hollywood illuminator and mix it with my
mary-lou manizer from the balm and I
also
gonna include a little bit of this ink
lot pigment in the shade 7 of course got
a highlight above the brow bone as well
this is what my all-time favorite makeup
tricks and they get a lot of questions
about this too and why I do this and it
is because when you take photos from
either the side it gives you that nice
like glow like right there but also I
personally like it because when I take
photos front on it reflects obviously
here and here which makes my face look
wider and I like my face to look really
really wide and chisel because of my jaw
line I do have a very very long face so
I like to kind of slim it down just the
slightest bit and this trick really
really helps and to make sure my
highlight and contour are nice and
blended together I'm gonna grab the Mac
blush in the shade up pinch me and my
morphe morphe my morphe for bronze
alright so for the lipid II doodahs
today I'm going to using a brand new
product for my sistas over at covergirl
and those are the melting pout lipsticks
they come in these cute little squeeze
tubes and there are a ton of different
shades I just picked out for that I
think might match I'm gonna do a little
bit of a swatch just do you want to look
good on the actual lips
I feel like this nude shade number 105
is a little bit too a pinky for this
look umm let's test number 140 this
definitely could be really really pretty
honestly I think number 135 is a little
bit too much of a blue tone shade purple
for this look so that one's gonna be a
now and then number 150 Oh number 150
looks really good I definitely think I
want to go into the shade number 150 but
before I do that I'm gonna grab the
covergirl farewell feathering liner this
is also a new product and it's basically
a lip liner but it's invisible and it
goes on and it stops here at liquid
lipsticks or any lipsticks from moving
around which is so so great then I'm
gonna go ahead and apply shade number
150 oh yeah
okay so I actually really really like
how this lip turned out it went on super
super smooth as you can see it is
obviously a liquid lipstick formula but
it didn't write out an auto percent
matte which I don't mind as well it is a
dark ready cranberry shade which is
usually a red flag when it comes to
lipsticks because they usually are very
very patchy but with this the formula
actually looks really really consistent
so these are definite winds for me as
well the lip liner is great as you can
see my lip line is super smooth and
strong so I love it okay so finally to
finish off this look I'm going to grab
my Urban Decay all nighter setting spray
and give my
they say quick little spritz alright
guys so that is this sunset cranberry
look I'll complete this definitely got a
lot more dark intense and vampy than I
originally anticipated I was going for a
little bit of a lighter eye at first but
I actually really really like how this
came out as well I guess follows like
relatively soon I mean like I'm ready
for spooky times and ready for pumpkins
Halloween you name it so I guess we're
just jumping the gun a little bit but
who cares I like this look as well I
really hope you guys enjoyed just
sitting down and chatting with me I felt
like I had a lot that I wanted to get
off my chest
obviously you guys mean so much to me
and I always want to be open and honest
with you guys so yeah definitely give
this video a big thumbs up if you
enjoyed this little chit check it
righted me and subscribe down below if
you have not already I post some number
of videos a week depending on whenever I
have time if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes stuff is James Charles
and the next your ass after Charles if
you didn't see yet my clothing line
dropped last week so make sure to go
check it out as sisters - apparel comm
I'm actually wearing one of the iconic
sisters hoodies right now and you guys
should definitely check it out at
beginning so many tweets and I can't
wait to release more in the line as well
my acapella group flashback released our
first cover at last Friday where we did
attention by Charlie puth we had so much
fun and you guys loved it as well it is
available for streaming on iTunes and
Spotify and a bunch of other places in
the description so there's check out
that video as well this week's shout-out
goes to a sister Violet thank you so
much girl for always falling in
supporting you know I love you so much
and if you would like to be next video
sister shout out make sure to always
retweet my video links and they go live
on Twitter all right sisters thank you
so much for watching like I said in the
beginning of the video you guys truly do
mean so much to me this industry can get
really really hard sometimes and I
promise if it were not for you guys I
would not be here doing what I love
every single day I am so thankful so
never forget that and I will see you
well that was a lot of talking and I
will see you in the next one bye