I sisters James Charles heard welcome
back to my youtube channel you guys
sister yet is rocking town after 2008 is
probably back in time for the summer
it's been talking the James Watts
apartment together
and since we're currently on a little
hiatus from brother and sister I
definitely want to smell something at
the end because I know you guys have all
miss him a lot
yesterday I anybody in front of and I
walked into my closet and I didn't know
what I wanted to wear and he was helping
me go through things and he was
critiquing a lot of my wardrobe and he
had definitely has a huge interest in
fashion but a little bit different than
your interest a little bit different
yeah but he definitely does like fashion
a lot Ian's outfits and my opinion are
scary it's the same thing yes you never
text season certain pictures before
posting but every time he does I always
look at them and I'm like wow that is
literally the worst since you clearly
have very different fashion senses I
thought it would be such a fun video to
do it in and I tried to buy each other
I'll bet like James did say we
definitely do have different styles of
clothing they like to wear but growing
up together I feel like we both have a
good sense of what we like so I thought
this challenge might be easy okay I
think every time I see you were in a
very very new style you change that your
interest and clothes a lot
whereas I'm feeling - I'm pretty similar
for the past few years so I think of
anything you might have this easier than
me say you like to wear like $1,000
black sweatshirts because they say so
basically to do this job today we're all
gonna head over to the mall and I'm
gonna shop with my best friend drew and
he's gonna take my videographer Kelly
and we're going to sister shop for each
other in secret and we're going to avoid
all cost not show each other what we're
getting and we have to put together a
full-on look so head to toe whatever it
takes to put together like a full
Instagram ready
look oh good question
okay I feel like we actually maybe
should do no budget for this let's just
do no price range I am scared of that I
won't talk to you define you am buying
you an outfit well yeah but I could ugly
one
gonna do that turn it well yeah I guess
you got me there
okay I guess we'll do no price range but
please don't go crazy on my credit card
I got you
do you yeah okay all right I guess um
this is yours
thanks book let's go sister shopping all
right guys we just got to the mall and
I'm ready to pick out sister Anne's
outfits I definitely have a lot of work
to do today his style is very much bad
so I definitely get a little like kind
of just good cohesive luck and I know
he's had a toga that he wants a ring so
I'm gonna try to be a good older sister
and gave him a cue train to make him
super super happy hopefully he'll love
the outfit that we come up all right
guys right now we're in Nordstrom I'm
hopefully gonna find James a full outfit
so pants shirt or sweatshirt shoes
accessories everything
lots of good and fresh brought the
t-shirts that are probably for a white
sweatshirt shopping for yourself about
to be buried this is a tricycle I think
I need this right now
okay I'll be purchasing this for myself
sorry yeah
what doesn't have true looking the woman
who not seen anything over it I'm gonna
try okay I designed this jacket from
champion wears a lot of champion and he
also wears a lot of chocolates like that
this could be a really good in fresh
piece for him oh you know what it makes
a plenty I'll go with the Puma that's
what I'm saying
they're also 770
there's something different $345 all
right we got these are 700 janesville is
adsense you can afford these pretty
easily so these might be enough all
right so in order to really find
anything besides the shoes everything
was Connell Christ those buff never leaf
in James's style let me put the
Valentino's on hold but I'm kind of
scared to spend 700 but we're gonna keep
on looking really like dragon boom pans
and that's the only straight boys that I
really know with my life so that could
be a good option for you this is
definitely James book $350 there's no
matching pants might not be a good idea
once again was wearing tonight
and they monster champion chocolate
we need these this jacket says James
it's only five ninety so those Adsense
BAM
easy it's black so it's gonna match it
anything nonprofit shirt for one look I
need to just get him like a Q relatively
simple plain shirt that doesn't have
alright so we decided to get the
Burberry jacket was 6:46 instant change
after tax hopefully it's gonna like it
it's gonna match everything so let's
keep on jeans are you excited about your
sister purchases I really a look a big
brown bag okay guys we successfully
bought a pair of shoes in a jogger pan
and a jogger for me
our total came to at three hundred and
twenty six dollars this is proving to be
very expensive very quickly and we only
have two items down south
thrust
irenna scribes the whole Valentino shoes
I think we're gonna go with these
because it changes the true indeed a
sister adidas sponsor there we go this
is the hot arrest on slightly low by
right yeah
waiting to knocking on that that is
awfully short of everything it was her
away I really like the shirt business
blind they are to get really cute
conventionally while Achaeans outfit but
he is notorious for wearing oversized
shirts and he's already very tall and
skinny so I don't want to make any more
of a string bean than he already is and
this shirt is very long so I'm gonna
hold this contender but his pants are
usually like just straight fit kits that
are cropped way to hide those ankles
look weird what my biggest have to do is
with the alpha jump a couple be honest
so this one needs like charcoal jeans
that I think it actually really good and
they're definitely not something that he
has so we're actually done at getting
has entire outfit so that's really great
work really professional shopper is but
since manager are done so earlier we're
gonna go get some ice cream
a sister snack while again the finished
stop because he sucks
there were definitely a look at some
kappas folks I know James is a couple
items already so we're gonna find
something he doesn't already back to
Louisville the shoes and pants and
jackets oh my goodness yes those
shopping so I decided to peace out for a
few minutes and take a little bit of a
detour to get Ian a little sister
surprise so we just got double dose we
got some dior glasses and a cap a
t-shirt James Andrew said they were done
with their whole outfit but they said
that we back in 30 minutes so I'm quite
curious to see where they are all 16 9nk
courtesan three-quarter 63 but a little
brother's definitely more of a man
[Music]
I could impress 3,000 to have a
particular tree just do it yeah it's
kind of fun we could be twinning sister
sibling it's for real
that's all I'm paying you today as a man
I love that when you're that far right
to get a free cookie 11 large over here
okay good actually it better be good for
4,000 it's kind of worth that I'm scared
oh I'll be a to go first I'll show
you yours first you think yeah are you
confident that let's do it all right so
weird you like bottom Oh quick shoes at
their time I guess bottoms up
wait is that the lyrics or the bottles
[Music]
tea
oh really love those okay funny the
boffin
15th pair of Adidas joggers okay it sure
do need to always more can't go wrong
with a brand new perfectly let's compare
answer the hardest part really love a
good cup of sir
these are good so far I told you okay
wow that's really gonna prize next to I
don't so like though
oh this is God
it's the brewery talkin sister I told
you I will cost about it why don't you
actually love this yeah this is the
masterpiece yen you're literally kidding
me me and drew walked by these in the
store and we're like we need those right
now we did you the best
I told you this oh my god did I go off
or did I not go you kind of went off not
gonna lie how much did you spend until
it all you thought was the glasses were
700 something dude I ready to see yours
I'm kind of scared I think this'll be
good I don't like that you off the
weirdest clothing taste ever well first
I got this adidas jacket which is mine
let me know over there okay
first awkward okay I want you to know
that I put together this fall cohesive
outfit too so everything will match no
it's not like God not just this thing
okay I think they're pretty civil side
of the shirt you have on now they match
it okay I think they're pretty cute do
you like everything gray right and below
so you can watch as the most outfits
yes okay do you like that yeah really
yeah I feel like when I was in your
pieces I really want to make sure a lot
of the things like went together because
they like one of the main issues you
have with your office is that they never
match there's always like a few really
good elements with and there's always
like that one thing that you add that's
ever like not me you just have no you
just have questionable taste okay ready
I have no idea what pants you got for
those shoes now Matt you're really
scared why only a very few amount of
pair of pants that that's not true we
actually don't really think about oh I
don't really think all these pants
watching my shoes
well the rest go together really nicely
we'll be fine okay okay good I got you a
good pair of dark skinny because they're
not fully blocked because they like you
have a lot of black pants already and
they're like a nice wash and I also
think you don't really have that when
you purchase skinny jeans my most a lot
of pants that you wear are kind of
straight fit and you cut them at the
ankle and it doesn't look good okay Wow
two for two so far Nevers are gonna move
in with the shoes though yeah yeah I
will admit I don't really think about
that together but I think we should be
fine next item is your certain rue de
Mexican dude this shirt I've ever really
cute I feel like you have a lot of like
graphic tees so introducing that was
like simple but I had like some sort of
element to it so it like you would
actually watch we're cool I think it
it's a little bit long the way I have to
crop it depending on looks with the
outfit I don't like not crop but like
just like cut like two inches off like a
crop top
although that is a good approach to you
pick a lot of items that make you look
like a string bean like you're already
very tall and lanky and you wear shirts
that are like eight inches too long and
pans that are straight and no jacket and
like long shoes so you just look like
you're like 87 feet tall about your
knots we need to break it to you ready I
guess lastly we have this last one
now uses last okay we found this one
first and I actually think you're really
gonna like this one
oh god I almost want another one for
myself I think you'll look so good or
not it's a large so it still gives you
like that oversized shape with a bigger
t-shirt and then we got either really
skinny jeans are kind of like taper of
the body give you a little sister shape
instead of being a sister shrimpy yeah
I'm excited if you go put them on what
pull them up more they're skinny jeans
well you're saying those four to twelve
ey those are a medium I can spend an
extra sister in here it's kind of as a
good lock okay they really are a little
big role that's how you do that's what
you do when your pants are too big dude
oh it's too bad you can't see it hello
host the gay is tell it's a hundred
degrees my program you just gave me a
winter jacket you gave me a winter
jacket as well you be kind of killed
that how do you like your like pants
I'm not used to pants like that
everything you guys sister shucks the
mouth I'm just not used to skinny jeans
I actually really love on this look
looks on you I think even though that
seems a little bit uncomfortable they do
look really good it definitely did
exactly what I wanted it to do of giving
you kind of like the larger oversized
pores on the top but the skinnier
portions on the bottom so everything
looks a lot more cohesive and not as
strangely like I do have one last thing
to add to this outfit
Oh God what did you do
I'm so scared probably made our building
bad impulsive Perez I just wanted to
really completely off bad give it a full
sister James look it's beautiful
Wow lucky here all come wait yo how much
did this cost the fall outfit yeah for
$1,750 okay pretty fun though right you
know I spent one point five so that
means we literally spent over six
thousand dollars on this challenge today
that no budget thing really made it no
challenge
[Music]
all right it's like as that completes
his sister shopping spree in this video
today I actually had so much fun doing
this not gonna lie I was a little bit
worried in the beginning because like I
said again cell is ever-changing but I
was very much looking forward to putting
you in something much cuter than the
average sister you've helped and I am
very proud of how this turned out and
I'm glad you like it
I think James's style is very hard to
find in store is actually really true
finding clothes that you would just buy
like looking at was kind of difficult
you're really dead this is so good I
will definitely be wearing this under no
TV probably soon on Instagram if you
guys who doesn't videos today with me
and sister via the room so what I'm
doing those please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below and show
your support it really means so so so
much to speaking of support really hope
you guys can skip that after this
challenge if you have not already as
well don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we just hit six
million sisters oh my god literally like
hello one of the people that my mind is
blown every single day and I feeling
distress or that it's going it's so so
so fast you all mean so much to me and I
promise you when I say there are a lot
of really really amazing things in the
works that you guys are gonna be so
sister took over so thank you guys as
always for all your love and support
and I say in every single video but
truly like I am something will begin
this job I'm so grateful for all you
guys I don't mean us as well so thank
you love you click the subscribe button
also put that belt like those secret
about every time I or we upload a brand
new video if you like to follow me and I
make up turning a puppy on Instagram or
Twitter they're both just shamsher off
and my snapshot for more I haven't seen
sites up the same Charles on some extra
ass after Charles Borromeo my brother
journey all my social media is our teen
JD this video super shadow cosas sister
Emma thank you so much repost all your
ignore I love you literally it's so so
so much and if you like to me the next
videos with sister shadow don't forget
to always a retweet my bitterly so they
go live on a Twitter all right sisters
thank you for watching we love you and I
will see you in the next one hi
you
[Music]