hi sisters Charles here and welcome back
to my youtube channel so as you can see
I have a very very special guest with me
here tonight and my little brother he's
here so my mom and my little brother are
out here visiting California for the
first time ever they have actually never
seen my apartment never been out here
before how do you feel about be in
California for four days it's
interesting I am so glad so like inside
it is definitely better an interesting
week so far we've been having a ton of
fun which is why I do not upload a video
last Wednesday I apologize I was having
good family time because I have not seen
them in a very very large
I have not think they've got a very very
long time so I definitely wanted to see
them and I actually flew Ian and my mom
out here on one condition and that is am
what yes I love being a marketing genius
so for today's video I grab sister Ian
and Marian no sister for today's videos
like I said I grab sister Ian and we sat
down today because it is clearly a
hardcore brow he plays basketball and
football thank you and video games and
all sorts of brawl things and I put on
makeup for a living so that should show
you where we are in our relationship I
wanted to give in a little bit of a
challenge today and we are sat down in
my studio with a whole lot of makeup all
around the walls and Ian is gonna be
challenged with putting a full face of
makeup on me so do you know anything
about makeup at all no I do not hey why
did you answer me have you ever watch
all of my videos no like they always say
family is your number one Supporter so
without further ado if you would like to
see my little brother try to put a full
glam face and makeup on me a
professional makeup artist ready for
this I don't know you really haven't
watched on my video so far your keep on
watching there you go alright so we're
gonna switch into vlog Mon temporarily
I'm on my iPhone because sister Ian
needs a good sister needs to pick out my
wake up that we're gonna wear for this
video I don't have a single product in
front of me but over there we have a
full
all of makeup products let's go
so my makeup room is currently
completely under construction right now
but we do have both of the acrylic
drawers set up a shout out to desi
Perkins for that decoration and
organization inspiration but let's get
pickin in I'll give you a head and say
that basically you're gonna want to
probably Gosling for every single drawer
this is why ya know what foundation is
that born this way to face a good choice
no yeah sure
anti-age Christy yes there's an urban
decay chill I think it says she's a good
one again you're actually doing a pretty
good job so heart-shaped ape blur stick
sounds cool
what kind of look are you going for us
today well I mean I wanted to look good
what is this wrong I don't know
oh highlighting powder what I thought
that was Jeffrey star is he's popular I
think James's favorite oh excuse me
you know Glee caller wait Ian open it up
I have ready you know what that is
yes sister Kane just picked out all of
his makeup products and I swear to god I
actually gave him no help at all
and he actually managed to pick out a
lot of parts that he used on an everyday
basis so I'm thinking he actually may be
a sister of himself a James Charles
video watcher and I think he's lying but
let's go ahead and get started do you
know what you're gonna do first
um no Christy no no no no
it's just oh excuse me it doesn't read
the direction there's something oh that
doesn't have any directions I guess
doesn't work
this yeah perfect
look anymore probably so while eating
uses several several several pumps my
foundation on this beauty blender I
tweeted you guys asking for some
questions but me and Ian can answer
throughout the process of this video so
without further ado let's get started
oh my god you already put foundation on
that area excuse me pimple your face -
and you have 50 pimples all over your
face don't ever disrespect me like that
ever again I don't want to look I want
you to be and Brooks that what were your
first thoughts when Jane started wearing
makeup I was kind of scared uh-huh
then you started making money and going
places so I accepted it okay so what's
next good shape tape let's call it that
what is this oh this is the why should
about this I'm not telling you anything
Oh God
tor michaela said what's James's most
annoying habit always thinking he's
fright no matter what that's because I
am yeah oh oh yeah look at that she
loves a chiseled contour put on your
face
what do you mean everything I'm like I
mean I'm like you're lucky cheeks and
not like your eyes and yeah there's
a few more things here
well brush are using more feet m5 yeah
sister brother sister Taylor asked who's
your mom's favorite daddy
our dog is scientific so much worse
another one because we're not working
with me here I'm so sorry
one this setting but whenever your heart
desires that oh oh my god the
Beautyblender can't fix everything
obviously it really can't but what thing
makes you the proudest of your brother
but then where do you see him in ten
years the fact that he's successful with
his job but he's enjoying it Oh what do
you see me doing in ten years most
likely makeup okay stop Ian oh hey maybe
Maddie asked as you two get along when
you were little
no what about now well this question is
just from you from a sister Jack he said
have you ever been bullied for having a
famous gay brother to people like you
more because of it love you both sisters
it depends like my friends accept it and
like I don't know there's like kids that
it's like say to me about you I
don't say anything back Christian said
is he single yeah Serena said what is
your best memory of each other let's go
with the ugly green if you're admitting
that it's ugly why are you putting it on
as you look ugly with it
Caroline said what's the last thing that
you fought about filming this video Jake
asked who was the worst troublemaker as
you guys know I'm very much like a rule
follower like I know
as you guys know I very much like follow
the rules and try hard to like stay in
line Eaton was very much the opposite so
you definitely got in trouble more often
I just broke your eyeliner yeah you
picked that color of all colors Qasim
plum Kelly oz wasn't like to have a
famous older sibling do you ever feel
like you're living in his shadow
oh I guess sure it's kind of fun but
kind of annoying at the same time why
about 15 I haven't done anything with my
life
you're 18 you're already making do
that again no down yeah oh my god I suck
how did I put blue on you just put it on
on what your eyes from no just the
lashes I wrote I will definitely see you
tell you that how do I put these on my
hand
that's upside down Mary asked what was
it like oh my what was it like when
James moved to LA and beyond us do you
ever miss him no okay I get his room you
don't miss me at all oh my god
Chris how did James tell you that he was
gay I hate kind of tell ya I don't think
I did however we were on the trampoline
one day and you had like called me gay
like trying to like be an [ __ ] and I
just was like so and then I was kind of
like yeah oh yeah sure again it's like
literally perfectly on there what a true
sister on the lips
you tell me look really kinda wonky yeah
I'm wet how do you feel about your job
today on me your lips look a little
strange the wings look a little the
foundation honestly does not look bad
the eyebrows could be better like your
everyday eyebrows no they don't
overall I think I'll give sister Ian a
sister again it's gonna get a C on
today's look overall today what do you
think about like doing makeup it's very
difficult and people that do it like
have a talent and yeah it's basically
okay alright guys so if you enjoyed this
to do with sister Ian at brother in
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below if you have not
already I post three videos a week on
Mondays Wednesdays and Fridays and I'd
love to have you join this sisterhood
all right sisters let's see if you can
do this if we can get this video do
50,000 a thumbs up I know you can do it
go click ow
oh my god make sure you guys go see that
thumbs up fun down below as well I know
you can do this if we get this video to
a 50,000 comes up I'm gonna do a video
doing IANS makeup and later or not yes I
am yes I am 50,000 thumbs up go do it if
you'd like to follow me out eye makeup
journey I promise I usually have much
better makeup on than this I'm sorry
sister you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat for world where
hadn't seen Thai stuff is James Charles
the next row asked after Charles whoa
where's my shadow relax okay so I guess
if you like to call a sister Ian you
could find him on Instagram I am JT 12 I
would not recommend following him though
but you do you this week's shout-out
goes to sister Emily and thank you so
much girl for always falling in
supporting you know I love you so much
and if you would like to be at next
video sister shadow always make sure to
retweet my video links and they go live
on Twitter all right sis just thank you
so much for watching this video I are
actually rather we thumbs up we'll see
you in the next one bye