hi sisters team Charles here and welcome
back 20 YouTube channel you guys I am so
good excited because today we are
finally back in business with a
regularly scheduled and makeup video and
I am so beyond pump but also low-key not
like nervous but I just like don't know
how this video is going to go so like
I'm skeptical right now there is a huge
and I think really really funny trend
going on youtuber basically people are
going to different fast food restaurants
and letting the car in front of them
decide their order you can basically end
up with like a four-piece happy meal
from McDonald's
or like 18 different Doritos Locos Tacos
Grande chicken chalupas talked about and
you have no idea what your actual wheel
is gonna be until you get to the final
window which is literally so crazy I
figured it'd be so much fun to try to
figure out how to kind of it turn this
concept into a makeup video now I do
want to give credit to all my favorite
creators taught right now me up maples
she did someone think a few weeks ago
and her buddy was so much fun to watch I
will leave a link down below if you guys
want to check it out but I want to do
some one thing today so basically we're
going to head to Ulta and let the people
in front of me in line pick my makeup
routine
now obviously Ulta does not have like a
drive-through window where I can just
pull up and be like I'll take whatever
they're having although that is a good
idea to send me an email of how fat and
also most people tend to not go in and
spend like a thousand dollars on a full
Fraser sheen at one time out there on a
sister shopping spree go off girl like
more power to you risk factor 100
percent if that happened to happen today
I was able to get behind them in line
that make this video a whole lot easier
but the chances of that are very very
slim so what I think I want to do is go
into Ulta and I hide away a little bit
and wait until there's a few people in
line in front of me and then hop in and
say I want all of that this might not
work as well as I thought it was going
to know now that I'm saying it out loud
but you know what we're gonna try and
regardless we're gonna come back here
after and we're gonna see if you can put
together a full face to make up using
whatever the people in front of me in
line purchase at the makeup store let's
go sign
[Music]
we just arrived all they're gonna do so
bright I can't even see okay we just got
here
to ol top all right you guys we were
here we must walk it I am praying the
third people night let's go ahead and
see we got okay everybody that's
sticking out right now
try pay for everyone's orders can I get
everyone's makeup okay the only
condition is I need you all to tell it
like they're gonna keep track of what
you got and I'm gonna get the same thing
for myself is that okay
[Music]
when I was in 193 with tonight hmm I
know for $1,000 has to be a full-face
maker between here like there has to be
big beefy one all right you guys we were
thoughtful but I have a whole lot of
makeup here with me oh my god literally
like me picked I feel like the perfect
time to know because there were so many
people in line and they all had lots of
items and bits and bobs which is good
we've already done the part of the
challenge where we go to the triumph
through we have the people online at
pick our order we've paid with a credit
card at window number 2 and now we're at
window number 3 where we normally get
the food but now we're going to look
through art and lives bags and see what
the heck our makeup routine is about to
consist of today so let's just dive
right in and see what we got so into a
bag number one we have okay we have it
CC cream ooh a foundation brush I wonder
if I should use my own brushes or not so
literally only use the things but if
nobody brought other but other brushes
okay then we have an foundation brush I
guess Dermalogica skincare I forgot the
ultra sounds like other things ooh a
little formula 10 2006 keep your cool
skin calming gel mask
this unique gel mask helps reduce the
appearance of nasty breakout Louis you
know what while we're going through nice
as I was saying while we're going
through the other bags let's go ahead
and put this nice mask on our face to
really calm the appearance of breakouts
because my skin has teamed better days
okay we also have chopstick once I'm all
complete let's look at the backs okay in
this bag she's humming oh okay we have
an elf eight tart I delayed more oh my
god yeah yeah we have the morphe palette
okay a morphe 35c palette stunning vibes
office do you guys cannot use coach Ames
at Ulta unfortunately but you can use to
go James for 10% off all your morphe
products at Murphy store oh my god
somebody brought us a tape
okay so you taping the sheet of light
and getting this is literally my shade
light/medium honey Oh Lots
frickin go we have a Kylie Jenner velvet
liquid lipstick in the shade
come and oh okay uh-huh another colored
liquid lipstick in the shade surprised
me this is off to a good start
let's look at this file I wonder whom I
had this in their bag they do not want
to use this in this video today I know
soccer you guys obviously uses a million
a trillion times and I definitely wanna
try out some new brands but I would love
to get this away at the end of the video
and I also have a good and fresh idea
for a big giveaway that I want to do too
so it makes you guys watch to the very
end some texture and body dry shampoo
Louis and we also have some Anasazi at
Beverly Hills not lipstick in the chain
of spice oh yes somebody bought a bar
set thank you okay we have the morbid
Jocelyn Hill brush that we already the
foundation brush but if I have to do my
content of the eyebrows oh my god
somebody bought my is this literally in
Miami
somebody is my Lily lashes in a style by
happy use could use for 50% of your
purchase literally my hair launches on
the entire world thank you Lord uses in
heaven above this was like my crown okay
I don't know these people in line were
like sisters at heart we have okay
whoever had this bag was okay literally
whoever bought this bag was literally a
sister and also in here is the Urban
Decay all nighter setting spray okay we
have to throw we have to face for this
wing in the shade a warm beige
definitely not the color and we also
have the Anasazi Beverly Hills Alyssa
Edwards palette which I have been dying
to play with I love Alyssa Edwards she
is one of my favorite drag queens of all
time that I obviously
as well their shadows are so Bob this is
definitely going to be the palette that
I used to create a look today I am so
excited to use this next bag we have a
better than sex mascara from Too Faced
this is a really good one
ah Nastasia liquid lipstick and the
shade crush this is a good and I love
this color nude great we have another
shape tape but this one is in light
neutral I use this color - we have
Maybelline Dream bourbon cover full
coverage protective makeup sunscreen we
might be able to mix us together with
the board this way though to make this
one a little bit less scandalous and
then another anasazi lipstick in the
shade of kiss okay yeah another morphe
palette the 35 aged hokhmah I really
really like this pile that's what I
think just launched we have next can't
stop won't stop setting powder Oh nobody
got a setting powder yet thank God
I've actually never tried this one
before but hopefully she will come
through because I cannot absolutely not
knots at my face so there we go
some were urban decay all nighter urban
decay D slick oil control setting spray
whoever bought this viagra really needed
to lock their face in place make a
revolution conceal and define full
coverage foundation okay I actually
never played with any makeup revolution
products before but I've heard that
they're really really good this color
does not look like it's even close to a
right match but I really really want to
try this so I'm how could he do his
candle should have gotten spray in this
video we have the Aveeno ultra calming
and daily moisturizer and sunscreen oh
good I'll put this on before my makeup
whole Beauty Blender great Oh any more
of a sponge Wow this Carlin's bag was
Lynn oh we have another shade makeup
revolution considered divine shade after
10 so a little bit later better oh wait
we have two shades to make a revolution
concealer and CA and c9 okay regardless
of the foundation I will definitely find
with these concealers today cuz I heard
they are so Bob so this is really
excited about okay we are on to our last
bag thank God we have the it bye bye
Foundation okay had this one yet either
let's look at the shade for this too
you know I'm just glad to see the fact
that Ulta has lots of different shape
variations at this point so you have an
elf blending brush you have the next
bear with me hydrating a jelly primer
I've never tried some before benefit
roller lash used to be my all-time
favorite mascara Oh champagne mom okay I
don't think we've actually pulled on it
no we've had no highlighter yeah okay
okay this is a perfect another option oh
the rock alter-ego lipstick I Milani lip
stick and elf ultimate foundation brush
okay this is good and that's the not
least you have an Anasazi eyebrow
definer okay I usually use the brow is
but this can work too
in the shade medium brown okay good
that's my color all right you guys well
I feel like this is a very random but
also a very very successful makeup haul
I'm pretty sure we have every single
step of our makeup routine covered in
front of us and definitely paid off to
wait for the store to get really busy
and wait in line I had it so much fun up
meeting everybody in the store today
that they're all so so so sweet and they
also did a really good job picking up
making our products so I'm gonna go and
unbox my favorites and then let's get
started it with a fondant makeup look
all right you guys I'm gonna get started
okay I'm gonna get started to use anyway
Aveeno ultra common daily moisturizer
that includes a sunscreen your skin care
should always have sunscreen in it
that's good okay so for foundation today
I'm not exactly sure let's just try our
options okay so we have the Maybelline
Dream cover see what this color looks
like okay not too bad honestly at all
we haven't born this way my all-time
favorite foundation in the club worm
beige which may already know
unfortunately for me is not my color
definitely not it we have a makeup
revolution in f10 and make a revolution
in F this day is day for the books and I
need everybody to pay attention right
now because my foundation is not going
to match in this video just like every
video but this time it's not my fault so
I think I'm going to mix together the
makeup revolution
shade 10 which is definitely too dark
and some of the Maybelline one and see
if we can get a good mix I like put this
one around like kinda like the edges of
my face and cover up this awful breakout
and then I used two Maybelline why not
more towards like the middle of my face
this isn't that bad like it's it's not a
match but I've had worse let's be real
I've dressed a little bit of the
Maybelline - and to like the lighter
areas we're gonna use our it cosmetics a
full coverage complexion brush to blend
this in okay that color isn't that bad
oh my god yes let's mix together our
darker shade some cream contour let's go
ahead and blend that and it using our at
Beauty Blender now for concealer I'm
gonna grab the shade c9 also from what
makeup revolution I have associated
Travis concealers today I've heard such
great things about it I'm just going to
pop this and all of the same normal
areas I'm just gonna go ahead and blend
that in as well okay I'm kind of liking
how this is looking a lot I definitely
feel like I'm missing a little bit of
coverage I was gonna have a tiny little
bit of the shape taping out this just
right underneath my eyes just for a
little bit more lightness and coverage
but that's that I promise let's grab the
next can't stop won't stop setting
powder and lock this in place this is
actually the only setting powder out of
all of those makeup bags so hopefully
they strokes out because we don't have
another option this powder looks a
little bit dark oh we're just gonna push
this on there and then we're gonna wipe
it off hopefully this comes off
translucent because this is looking a
little bit not correct so squeeze our
other elephant foundation brush to wipe
away the excess it's like shiny a little
bit for some reason which I feel like a
setting powder should not be at all
oh okay I've liked everything that I've
tried so far except for the setting
powder I do not like it at all looks
like I have white foundation there's
stuff but it's completely set down and
dry I did not like that would not use it
guys now we have to contour we don't
really have anything from let's look let
me check out the Adelaide more
importance of a contour suite of that
and has a color called contour I can't
put that on my cheek well I'm gonna grab
a little bit of I feel beautiful which
is deep blush color on that foundation
brush and let's use that at least to
apply a little bit of a blush that's
definitely our very pretty color I guess
I have to literally use a fluffy
eyeshadow brush to contour today I
wonder if there's a color in the actual
Anasazi part let's see yes okay we're
gonna go the shade h OE from the Alyssa
Edwards on a salty palate and we're
gonna use a little bit of this color to
contour I'm gonna be careful because
this is definitely a dark shade and I
don't want to go too intense I'm gonna
grab that alpha blending brush that we
got in one of the bags and grab that
same h OE color and use this too
Torinos I am happy with this so far so
normally right about now I would bake my
face to lock everything and please and
also brighten up the center but consider
that setting powder literally is sucked
I don't really want to put more of it on
so I guess where it's kind of stuck with
this so I'm just gonna go right into it
the brows they God we have the Anasazi
broad to find her I don't use this one
too often but Anasazi illiterate makes
the best brow product so I'm gonna go
ahead and do this quickly off care and
I'll be right back to start off the
ominous already knows we were back in
both eyebrows are now complete I'm not
exactly having the best I brought a at
this one turned out really good at this
one not so much but you know what we
have phase tuned for reason I'm gonna
grab the Anasazi Beverly Hills acts
Alyssa Edwards palette I am so excited
about this one today I already have my
eyes primed with some makeup revolution
concealer what I'm just gonna grab a
little bit more so it's nice and tacky I
really want to use the yellow and the
pink and the blue and the purple and I
could literally just do a yellow pink
purple blue let's try it
president JH 33 brush on the shaded
dreamer I'm gonna pack this on the outer
like the type area oh wow that's pick
attentive love that just gonna lightly
go over the edge of that and kind of
blend the color out next with that same
brush since I really don't have any
other options I'm gonna grab believe
which is the kind of lighter purple
color and put this right over top and
next to dot blue this purple is
definitely blending out really really
well to it not perfect but purple is by
far the hardest shade to formulate when
it comes to eyeshadows I would know
because we literally went through the
800 million different lab samples of a
single and escaped until we got one that
we were happy with that looks good okay
next I'm gonna grab the JH 32 brush and
dip into a Texas made the bright pink
shade and I'm gonna put this right next
to believe same exact techniques just
having the color on there and then
lightly
buffing them together to blend it out
let's grab the JH 42 brush and the color
brick road which is deep bright yellow
I'm gonna pop this on the inner corner
wow that is a bright yellow oh wow
I was literally one dip in the pan too
and it created all of that pigment that
is so crazy I'm gonna try to
do that yellow and pink to create that
orange color that we want I'm just gonna
go ahead and repeat those same steps on
the bottom lash line okay nice nautical
djh of 43 brush and dip into the shade
boost and draw out a little bit of a lip
blocked lighter wow that looks actually
really good I'm super happy with that
and lost the finally not least on my
edge age 39 brush I'm just gonna dip
into a headliner the bright white and
put a little bit of this in the inner
corner just to a little bit already base
that's pretty much the eye shadow of one
eye all complete I am obsessed with
these colors and this ombre pattern it
looks so so good at the blending could
be a little bit better but it's
definitely my own fault
I have not done a colorful makeup look
and literally weeks at this point so I'm
a little bit rusty not being said
practice does make perfect so I'm gonna
go and do the other eye off-camera
quickly and I'll be right back to finish
off the rest of the look already guys
you're back bold eyes are complete I
literally love this look so much I think
it looks so it's very much like a
butterfly ask which I'm so down for
alright now that we have a bolt eyes on
Khurana run oh God I'm angry now that
both eyes are now complete I'm gonna
grab the benefit roller lash color
mascara and apply a light coat of this
to my lashes and then I'd like to think
that only God for giving me my early
lashes my Lily lashes use comb James for
15% off your order
these are my all-time favorite lashes in
the entire world I had no I wear these
every single makeup look but you know
what we're gonna put them on
all right you guys moving right along
the next step of our makeup routine is
going to be of course the highlighter
and for that I'm going to grab that gosh
champagne pop shimmering skin perfecter
it has been a hot minute since I used
this highlighter I remember it not
exactly working that well for my skin
tone so we're gonna find that out I
guess looks so pretty
why don't I think this didn't work for
my skin tone at one point you're
literally going we're gonna grab the JH
39 once again that same clothes that I
used to put the white and my inner
corners and we're gonna grab some more
champagne pop on this and use this for
my nose highlight gonna probably tide a
little bit in the inner corner as well
all right guys we're pretty much already
at the end all we have left now is lips
and we have quite a lot of options we
have the lorac Pro in CEO that will be a
good color with this lock okay
she's definitely a contender anasazi a
spice that is such a pretty color but I
feel like it's a little bit too like
orange II for this particular type of
look Anasazi uh yes I liked its color a
lot but I don't really want to do a
lipstick without a lip liner and I don't
actually think we have one of those we
have Kylie velvet liquid lipstick so not
a full matte in the color surprised me
yeah this would work with this look but
I don't know if I want a bright pink we
have another Kylie that this one is a
velvet in the shade of commando that's
very similar to the Anasazi one though
that I didn't love oh so how about some
in the color Tanya this one is going to
be a no I hate that
that is what my fellow choice actually
I'm gonna do a little combination I'm
gonna start off with the lorac pro one
in the color CEO because it's a little
bit of like a darker mob and then I'm
gonna go to the Anasazi a kiss in the
middle for a nice ombre lip
okay a little bit and last but finally
not least one less print of the Urban
Decay all nighter setting spray just
talked this beautiful makeup looking
place
alright you guys and I think that is the
finished makeup look all complete
decided completely by the people in
front of me in line at the makeup store
I had it so much fun at them in this
challenge today and at more than
anything obviously I love how those look
turned out but this was a such a fun
opportunity to just try out so many
brand-new products that have literally
no sight and what was like coming my way
I think there were so many things here
that I would never have actually picked
up myself but I really really love how
this look turned out and I really hope
you guys did as well I do want to say a
quick thank you to all tough roads being
it literally the best and letting me
film in their stores but I also want to
say a quick thank you to the customers
that were in the stores that were so
kind and so sweet I was able to say
thank you by doing something fun for the
customers in the store but I do want to
do something fun and say thank you to
all of you sisters watching the video at
home as well I said earlier on that I
wanted to do a little giveaway and that
is definitely going to be happening I'm
gonna give you away at one James of
Charles Murphy pallets but not only this
I will also be giving away a to one
$1000 all to give cards so you guys can
go on a little bit of a sister shopping
spree all you have to do is give this
video a big thumbs up down below and
leave me a comment and you must be
following me on my Instagram and YouTube
both of which are just James Charles
I'll be picking all three winners one
week from today and they'll be known
somebody stories all legal details in
mumbo jumbo will be in the description
down below but this is just I found a
little way to say thank you and I love
you guys so so so much so good luck
don't forget you guys as well that these
sisters of hero pride collection is now
live on sisters - apparel calm I am so
excited to be donating a huge chunk of
the proceeds to The Trevor Project it is
going to an amazing cause and you guys
will obviously be wearing a very very
cute regular pieces as well if you think
anything up don't forget to tie us on
Instagram if they do follow me out I
make it up Turner you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter that are both just
James Charles my twitch is jay chou's
foodie for fun at games with James
content and my snapchat for more behind
TJ stuff is Charles an extra ass after
Charles this video is sister psittacosis
sister Anna thank you so much love for
always following it supporting you know
I love you literally is so so so much
and if you'd like to be next
sister shut up don't forget to always
reach it video links when they go live
on a Twitter all right you guys I think
that is all I have for this videos today
I thank you so much for watching I love
you and I will see you in the next one
[Music]