[Music]
um
hi sisters james charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
before we jump into today's video i want
to play a really fun game of spot
the difference ready go
do you see it yet yeah yesterday i broke
a nail and if you were a fellow acrylic
nail wear like i am you would know that
this is already one of the worst
things to ever happen but what's even
worse about breaking a nail
is when you break a nail and you don't
know when it happened and you don't know
how it happened and you don't even have
the rest of it to glue it back
together i called my nail tech and this
morning i have an appointment which
brings me to today's video because
i wanted to do something kind of fun and
also a little bit
uh scary i figured it was time to spice
it up try something new and especially
since i broke the nail yesterday and had
to have my nail tech
come back i'm going to be trying out
living with extremely long nails
for 24 hours so i've been seeing so many
really amazing talented artists like
cardi b
i know sweetie has really long nails in
our top end music video and
nail art and like growth is kind of like
a trend and like a community in itself
so i figured
i would dive in for one day and one day
only because i have a feeling this is
going to be very
very challenging and i'm going to see if
i can survive for 24 hours with
extremely long acrylic
nails let's get started
[Music]
okay right so it's currently 10 11 in
the morning and we're going to walk out
of the studio and into the
sister salon oh my god i cannot wait to
give you guys the house tour my amazing
nail tech
john is already here and set up and
we're ready to go
hey okay so we are obviously doing crazy
long nails today yeah do you do long
nails very often
um he's having a conversation excuse me
how do you feel about the long nose are
you ready for some scratches
do you do super long nose very often i
do have certain clients that prefer
extra extra long yeah part of me yeah
she's like probably
one of the one of my clients that
prefers the longest i wonder how
how long is that going to take okay so
depending how long you want
we're going to be like like
[Applause]
what are some things that he has to like
look forward to with the long nails well
we'll probably have to do like a
kind of tutorial i'm not concerned with
like wiping my butt
typing i'm sure they'll be challenging
but i'll figure it out i'm more
concerned that i'll break one
you um no you can slap people
and be in fights and stuff and you'll be
all right oh sure
so that's nail number one huh that's
number one
god show the camera real quick oh
that's already that's double the length
of my fingers literally so being on your
little pinky
okay let's go
oh my god oh my god put it together
oh the difference in life holy crap
three
hours later
oh my god it's really been quite a while
okay what time is it how long
one one thirty two three hours three
hours three hours
yet okay i was thinking because i
watched my
try to wash my hands for the first time
before the video we're obviously trying
out lots of fun things right
sure said we wanted to drive we said we
wanted to of course eat and we also said
we need to
you know uh yeah private
the bathroom here really good way to you
know
kill three words of one stone would be
to go to chick-fil-a
actually killed three birds finn
well i was thinking obviously we have to
drive to get there and i'll get the
spicy chicken sandwich which will
definitely cause some bowel movements
and then go to the bathroom and then
oh should i pet the puppy oh come here
come here oh my gosh he's terrified
oh ew
okay so what's the next step paula she
said oh yeah
oh really swatch it really swatch it for
me oh give us a swatch
this is apparel butterfly collection
launching very soon
on sisters
but also jesus and also john legend it
is currently
you 2 13. p.m it has been officially
four hours
wow this my hands feel so heavy right
now this is like a pulling on extension
like what is it
i tried hi
okay so like i said earlier it's
currently 2 p.m i am
starving we have not eaten yesterday so
i want to get a pair of socks on and
drive to chick-fil-a
i'm a little bit concerned with the idea
of putting on socks
i was just you know in the bathroom
urinating it took me a good
30 seconds to figure out how to pull my
pants down
um get out of breath not really out of
breath it's just more um
thinking sure i'm not sure how to get
this over oh wait wait look
okay yeah it's looking a little tricky
this is gonna be re-uploaded to like
butt hub or something
that's fine okay that took like four
minutes to get on top
process oh my god
[Music]
i don't want to meet him with these oh
my god i'm looking doors
hi sir hi sir
hi how are you doing good how are you
just chilling oh yeah
hey how you doing with those nails yeah
so i'm going to pull the bag out
wow oh my god there's only
8 500 pairs but 3 500 went to friends
and family so there's only
five thousand oh
my god crazy
you're so good that was a nice i'm
scared to even touch them
scratch them by accident nails oh my god
these are so
sick
hey how you doing really fish in there
and get the nice laces out oh that came
in handy for so long that definitely
worked
one hour later let's really use the nail
to
fish in here shut
up it looks like you literally like
playing with noodles
hey hey 20 minutes later oh
my god these are so sad you guys you
have to go check out breakout la and
they are
the shoe source literally we drove an
hour up here just to drop these off they
look
so sick it's gonna be such a good outfit
photo minus
the nails we'll definitely get rid of
those before oh no
okay so oh well i was gonna say how to
open the door but luckily the tesla
opens it for me
let's put my seatbelt on
that was a good palm thrust
[Music]
okay so when your nails like grow or
obviously in this situation just get
three inches longer your depth
perception gets really messed up because
you're used to
rubbing things reaching for things or
touching things at a specific distance
away from them
i'm like completely off balance of like
where my things are also i just realized
i could be talking with so much emphasis
this entire time
oh that's a lot of emphasis i'm gonna
make that girl on tick tock don't be
content
when you can have better you feel me if
you want to fly high you gotta let go of
what's weighing you down good morning
everybody just wanted to let you all
know that you
are beautiful can i do a uh spicy
chicken sandwich combo please yeah of
course
wait can i get buffalo how are you thank
you love
you yes of course let's do it we're
going to filming a video today where we
live
for 24 hours with the longest nails i
love your nails
do you like them
let's get a photo together
thank you
okay now that we're in the car ourselves
and we are perfectly safe i'm gonna take
the mask off so i can talk to you guys
it's very nice that chris from breakout
said that he loved the nails it was even
cuter as well that the girls that
chick-fil-a noticed them right away and
said that they love them i think that
that's very very cute and honestly i
think that was like the confidence
booster that i needed
to get through the rest of today a
little mukbang
[Music]
just really wedge it in there oh
no not a puncture not a puncture
okay how do i open the sauce i think
just jab a nail in it and then lick it
off
[Music]
oh give her a good grip
oh no well it looks so tiny because your
fingers are so big
don't say that well just because the
nails
is that how you normally hold it no how
do you normally hold it
oh yeah too much overlap now really
intertwined
together oh no
all right you guys we are officially
down here in the makeup studio because i
really wanted to film some tech talks
today
with these nails now i am not looking
forward to
this glam process so this should be
really interesting
i'm gonna grab the milk hydro grip
primer give a nice
squirt onto my hands i literally just
got lasik and fixed my vision and i'm
gonna accidentally poke myself in the
eye and be blind okay so now foundation
i'm gonna do some squirts on the back of
my hand i do like that my nails also
doing the pump as well
i'm not really sure how to hold this can
you hold it with your nails only
[Music]
oh no this can you guys this cannot be
real
well that kind of works okay i'm gonna
do some cream contouring
i'm just gonna do a little bit of a
concealer
this is the ugliest i've ever looked in
my entire life oh my stomach is starting
to really
turn make some questionable noises you
guys are like actually concerned about
my plans
[Music]
no
i have to poop no i have to trevor i
said i could feel it brewing
we i have to go
okay have fun in there oh okay well okay
okay
okay i'm gonna poop and i will uh
talk to you guys in a second okay so
this is
far more personal than i ever thought
i'd be getting on youtube but here goes
nothing it's got some nice strands of
toilet paper
um like wrap my hand in it
oh my gosh okay like this
okay this is the worst thing for my
entire life why am i doing a tutorial on
this
okay i'm holding it up and then just
like placing it in there
and i'm like so like obviously i'll make
this right here but i just move myself
with the last second just really hope it
sticks there
[Music]
all right just in case i missed a little
bit it's disgusting
really getting all the nuts and crannies
we have around here
there's so many fun questions about my
bathroom trip did you pierce the toilet
paper with the nail at any point
no i did not by the amount of times that
i folded it just in case of an emergency
oh it was about 50 for apply i'm just
going to throw on some highlighter and
then
probably call it a day soon because i'm
getting bored
i don't want to do this anymore it's too
hard
this is the way to really peck my nose
ew oh
stop saying it was if you don't pick
your nose everyone picks their nose not
in public
oops oh ew did you just see that that
disgusting fly should try to
snatch it with your nails i just catch
it right in there
yeah really lock it into the cage i
don't want to put on lashes
okay you guys well it is exactly six
o'clock p.m right now which means this
glam process took me almost
two hours on a normal day i could get
this done in probably 30 to 45 minutes
maximum but because of these nails i've
been sitting here for two hours i am
so bored i am so over it i hate just
like not getting things done and i feel
like this is
such a waste of time it's just a
struggle
so now that the makeup is all oh wow
it's right outside luckily i have lots
of surface area to cover the sun with my
nice long nail true we're gonna take an
instagram photo
with the nails this is bob
this is bob
i am holding the phone with the nails
interesting you really probably don't
even need the pop socket anymore with
all that grip
i know he should do you should do a put
a finger down oh my god
put a finger down if you decided that
it'd be really fun to film a youtube
video where you try to live for 24 hours
with extremely long fingernails and you
think that filming this video is gonna
be a piece of cake because you have
nails on it literally all the time
but then you try to start doing your
daily tasks such as tying your shoes and
writing back to business emails and you
literally can't do anything at all
you realize that your stomach is like
kind of grumbling and feels a little bit
weird and you realize that you really
have to go to the bathroom
so you go poop and then you realize that
you actually have to wipe your butt and
you have a full on panic attack because
you realize you can't do it
and you start crying because you're not
technically gonna be there for another
four hours to take them off
james what are you doing
why are you taking your makeup off i'm
over the stage i literally i'm free i'm
like actually starting to
get really anxious with just oh lots of
anger is happening
i have not been able to respond back to
any texts today i have not been able to
send any emails or taking my laptop
which is very much stressing me out
these are gorgeous they're fun to look
at and they were fun to
really tap out or do some nice asmr at
first but now i am very much over there
i'm supposed to come back tomorrow
morning to take these off so it would
like actually be 24 hours
but i like i honestly i can't do it so
thank
god he's on his way back right now
or guys that can so we'll start right
here just in case you want to keep a
little wind
sure oh
my oh lord i need to wear
armor the thickness that took an inch
there
holy crap all right you guys
this has been quite the day as you can
see
just left and we are back to our normal
length of nails on
just want to share some quick thoughts
my overall sentiments my feelings first
of all i just want to say a major shout
out to john for
being here for literally like six hours
in total today working on these nails i
don't know
what was really going on i honestly feel
like the best way to describe the
feeling that i was experiencing was like
claustrophobia
in a way if that makes literally any
sense i have so much respect for the
nail attacks that do
nails like that all the time the girls
that wear nose like that all the time
they are so beautiful they are such an
art form and if you are able to actually
function in your daily life with those
nails
more power to you because i obviously
could not but all that being said this
is quite the experience and i did have a
whole lot of fun
trying this out for the first time ever
so if you guys know this video today
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and share your love
and support it would really mean so much
to me and also if you have not already
make sure you click that big
subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we are 20
million sister sean and i love to have
you in the family and also click the
bell icon so you get notified every time
i upload a brand new video if you like
to follow me on my makeup journey you
can follow me on my social media
accounts i'll be linked right here
around the screen
and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number for new updates on
videos merged photos and so much more
it is 310-905-8746
this video sister shout out goes to
sister evan thank you so much for always
following and supporting i love you so
so so much and if you
would like to be the next video's sister
shout out don't forget to always retweet
me links when they go live on twitter
and also turn on my youtube
post notifications also i know y'all saw
that cute commercial in the beginning of
today's youtube video don't forget to
mark your calendars set your alarms
tell your friends and get ready to check
out and shop the sister's apparel
butterfly collection
launching on august 6 at 12 p.m pst on
sisters apparel dot com
this may be my favorite collection that
we have ever released and i hope that
you guys are excited as
i am all right you guys that's all i
have for today's video i love you and i
will see you in the next
one wow it feels good to wait without
extra weight being added to my hand
[Music]
you