hi sisters team Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel today i'm
done with to a very very special guest
Maddie and Kenzie Ziegler and today
we're being an episode of Beauty battles
just in case you don't know what a
beauty battle is and is a little series
I do here on my channel where we have
two different people both take half of
my face to compete and see who is the
better
MUA I am so beyond excited being better
you've actually collab before we have
and we actually collab like one year ago
like today really which is yeah oh yeah
we didn't even have time for that to
happen it just danced so hello this is
our one-year collab reverse arena and
then this is my first time ever having
Kenz my channel so you're so excited
we're so and this is gonna be a good and
fresh sister Beauty battle what do we
think is gonna win me obviously we've
just like to say with the products yeah
beauty gurus okay what is that - we're
taking the touch of the silk cream this
primer from taja hashtag not sponsored
is incredible yeah like ten out of ten
would recommend now I don't use primer
but I've got the sent to me and
everyone's raving about it I've seen you
rip yeah it's insane and I don't like
primers I think they're so stupid yeah
there's some reason this one it works
for all so uh what do you put it on with
finger finger yeah hands are definitely
clean I would hope so
sister oh my god okay my best friend and
I we always say stuff like that now
because of your videos since this every
time I walk in there like we love a
something sister yes literally always
say oh don't you love my catchphrases
have literally become like an
international sensation for some stupid
reason I'll be like walking on any
street or in any store or in any like
please ever and I'll hear like at least
five to a good big sister across the
room which i think is like so funny to
me it's crazy this is your go-to right
yes this is one of my favorite it's the
boss Oh same how do you point an but
that will match it'll match the spray
tan don't love a flash like Mary's
history
I actually to us yeah I don't I don't
know
right behind that oh my god would you
live under a rock um thank you yeah
Persall Wow comes I'm sorry I'm sorry no
but like seriously were you that white
or it was a bad way say you don't know
this right either like everyone every
photo I look at I'm like there's no way
you were that way I wasn't that white I
was in Boston doing a meet-and-greet and
I took a picture with a bad her name was
Pam I myself are on Twitter today I can
say Pam and she was a far darker skin
that I was so when you take a photo with
contrasting skin tones automatically the
person with later skin tone is already
gonna look way lighter when you take it
with flash because of like the light
balancing on the camera I don't know
really how it works and then she always
puts a filter on her photos that make
them even brighter so I did look like
kind of gray in the photo and I
definitely did have flashback but the
picture that went viral people
completely desaturate it it made me
white so I was not that way but I was
definitely not looking at too hot it was
bad but not like that body right my side
looks better already
you guys hit me credit here okay she's
way better at makeup than me at
foundation Latoya so stop laying
foundation you know I was watching your
videos I sound like a fan why I kind of
am I'll stick to my own service you
don't you don't pull it out all the way
anymore oh wow that was like a recent
video that I have to hide cuz i watch
everything oh my god I love that you
keep up with me it's always really cool
to me when I like people that I actually
consider like close friends yeah talk to
you about my videos because like we're
busy yeah we're crazy busy like today so
far I've already had three meetings this
morning I had to go show my Coachella
outfit I had two business calls and then
I took a shower how to shave my entire
body to get ready for Coachella and I
had a fitting tonight too that I already
forgot about he literally has Nair on
his table that just means a lot that
like people like us are able to like
take out their time and really like
support the project it's so important to
support our friend Prasad you're really
funny as well like your videos are
really funny all things tell me more
well sister Kenzie is speaking of
YouTube you miss the girly thing or in a
new YouTube show I am tall spotted
please so I'm on the show called total
eclipse I'm the main character I get
bullied all
so it's pretty sad it's pretty in the
show yeah I know yeah it's really fun
filming well you obviously started and
dancing but do you really like acting
now - yeah I think my like main thing
that I want to do is singing right now
but well she's a musician she is we need
to do a singer makeup routine featuring
in Kenzie
yeah it's that'd be so much fun I can
feature on it too you know music - I
went into an audition the other day and
they made me sing happy birthday and
then I was like really embarrassed and
they're like you have a great voice can
you sing it for us
yeah right I don't know how to be we're
just gonna um what do you mean you don't
know how to bake I remember we went
through this on when I did your makeup I
really don't know how to do it I'm just
scared for the nose snatch well I think
you have to faith faith trust in a
little bit of powdered us um you see I
don't really know how to do this okay
yeah I'm not gonna help you because I
feel like you know we're at it we're in
a competition
yeah I want to win we used to compete
against each other our whole lives so
it's actually really nice to not have to
compete against one another anymore cuz
like I took more of the acting yeah
she's taking more those are you doing
acting
oh yeah but you know what I mean like if
we go yeah I totally good cuz I have
this singing and he was like you you're
more dancer though my favorite moment of
the show that shall not be named yeah
when Kenzie finally was in the same
column I know what you're gonna say age
category thank you when has he's finally
the same age category and you guys
battled against each other
I lived everyone was like making like
the biggest deal like I was mad and I
wasn't oh well you literally were like
the Queen like everybody knew baddies
there was no right that's why it was a
big deal that's why I was a huge girl
I have voice but like a huge fan of you
but I was like wow I was like I was like
a proud like no way mm oh man it was
awesome it was good because like you
know everyone always used to compare us
have you guys always been ridiculously
competitive oh no me I mean I didn't
really care as much because I I didn't
really like to
as much when I was younger yeah I didn't
really want to do it because it was so
much pressure
yeah like everyone was screaming at me
and I wasn't even in any that a group
dances like in the first 16 so I was
like I don't know why I'm here voodoo is
about doing everything I do okay now I'm
gonna take some blush a tea - tea why I
probably wear believe yeah I fix this I
think you just keep going Wow
I only did one side of the nose so you
have to do the other side no dip Sri
Lanka probably now right now it's the
hot do you think you can come up with a
song for contouring my nose right now
that's for next time that's our daughter
sister colossal sister yeah you guys
should have your own because we had ours
we had our own sand that we need a
sister Jo yeah you're not you're not
invited
well I just volunteered as tribute so
we're Milo Hunger Games honey where you
said babe Kenzie what are you doing I
don't know what I'm doing whatsoever and
I'm we don't know it's not gender sister
it's funny cuz I can say it to you like
my sister there was a video of you it
says James Charles knowing Maddie
Ziegler for one minute straight and I
was like I don't know how they got that
because you did not annoy me one bit
yeah I'll just catch you I like the word
says the worst they really get you guys
I think they're funny but I think what
sucks is that the comment section that
always gets horrible and then it turns
from a joke video to a really serious
thing actually hey situation which is
never fun and is completely unnecessary
right I was luck serious like I
obviously had a lot of work into the
content I create and like I'm very very
blessed to have an active group of
followers or I don't like need to social
time off anybody to have anybody to like
be successful you know so like I pick
and choose who I want on my channel and
I usually pay people that I'm really
close with like me and Maddie said in
our original video like we've been close
friends for a long time we still are
every time somebody comes I was like wow
they're just using each other for
fallers and it's like first of all it's
our job and obviously of course it's a
collaborative effort do you think we'd
want to be sitting here something in
front of a camera if I didn't like I
would we wouldn't know nobody would
filming Beauty video is just an FYI to
you guys out there really suck sometimes
just I got five to six hour process and
it's like really really hot and
lengthy it's tiring you just want to
stretch your back in it let me go to the
chiropractor by the end of it you're
dirty like you just want to wipe
everything off obviously it's fun and I
love my job but trust me when I say like
if somebody didn't want to do this we
would not be here trust me on that
yeah when you didn't mind make of it it
was like three hours it was a long time
yeah but like when you see the video
it's like yeah
a lot goes into it my house it seems
that nobody really sees and knows about
I mean I love that at the end of the day
obviously would not be here like if I
didn't enjoy it but it just sucks that
people always wanna look at the negative
for everything but it's kind of funny
I'm doing those two where's jack sister
Jack oh my god speaking of sister Jack
come here Jack Jack if you don't know
our man is here fun fact
Jacquizz from Australia Australia and
sisters hello I have a fun and special
sister announcement for you I love they
were just popping this race yeah I'm
coming to Australia or stop Australian
sister tour and I want to meet you guys
there's a link in the description down
below or you can go to James Charles
Australia calm and go vote for wherever
you're closest big city is so I can come
meet you all of our Australian fans out
there
go see dreams okay I'm using the Jaclyn
hill house she thinks he's a guru
burn buddy thanks dude do you eat when
people say that the only show I hate is
when I'm on dating apps you think that's
like a basecoat but that's a shimmery
color oh I think this what he thought
about this is that Maddy will literally
like rub on her foundation with like
three fingers and then like put on like
some brow gel and call it a day but
she's like know so much about makeup and
Kenzie's that be like a full glam type
of girl and it has no idea yeah Maddy
have you been watching drag race this
season we talked about okay who's your
favorites right now I'm really loving
miss crock I have a personal bias
towards our query because I am friends
with her and I heard dragons it's
sickening we need the best what miss
Crocker I'm looking she is so funny yes
her comedic timing is amazing I also
love a player st. Claire she is a real
woman really little man he's good I
think she's maybe not shining as bright
as she can but she's still doing really
well
she literally looks like like an angel
yes like she looks like she's like oh I
said it out of heaven look into the
driveway okay I want to do liner but I'm
gonna do this no we both do it I'm most
excited for Beyonce I think that's like
the most typical thing to say but she
just is so talented she's making her
comeback
ah you know I am so excited I also
really said her to see cardi B I did go
to go to LA she for the first time it
was really really fine but you guys know
that I don't like drink or smoke or
anything and that's kind of like really
what yeah the Bible coaching a lot early
it's a little bit overwhelming not gonna
lie but so this year I'm really just
gonna try to focus on the music and the
Instagram photos I am serving looks all
you sisters watching it you guys are
going to get a full on Coachella
tutorial and lookbook and I think the
next thing that goes up after this one
peoples waves are about to be flying off
okay that when delimiting wig on my
account and I'm just like my favorite
thing about that ever was when Kim
Kardashian posted a selfie with her new
blonde Tara everyone was like wow wig
and then she tweeted it was like you
guys it's not a wig on I love her that
was the funniest thing that's holy
okay I'm gonna like go underneath it's
so funny because you know she's known
for being like a social media like
Queens but like but she's also a mom and
like she's like okay I think I'm just
okay
literally there's two sides they're both
black and I just don't get it at all
look at that one's longer I want to do
like a blue under your eye but if not
that's so like I can draw like a little
heart on your gee that's a tiny one like
right there Oh
yeah I'm doing it alright okay so what's
your favorite video you've ever built
that's actually a really really tough
one
I'd probably have to say either my
three-part series of the en or probably
a blank canvas just because they usually
on a club I was really proud of it cause
it was really awesome to look back on
everything that I've done in the past
year because like it has been an
emotional roller coaster with bullying
really highs and also really lows like
even like while editing that like a
little remember I was like snapchatting
I was sobbing crying it was so
embarrassing but I was also just like a
really vulnerable moment for me just
like I just put a lot of heart and soul
into a lot so I think that's definitely
like one of my all-time favorites and I
think it will probably forever be oh
yeah never in a million years would have
ever thought I'd like be here right so
weird we never thought we'd like be on a
reality show and then now we're here you
know a statement suck you really never
know what I thought that's gonna happen
then it just kind of does and you're
like wow I had no clue was going on when
I was like six yeah ladies were
following me around and I was like yeah
sometimes I feel like we didn't really
have a childhood you know like we've
never been like a proper one there was
just cameras on us like all the time a
lot of people think that like being
famous really having a following itself
is all fun and games but it really is
there's like a big dark side to it that
not a lot of people get to see a lot of
people don't think about just because
they think like oh you're on TV you're
making money you would relate these cool
things but in reality like there's a
really huge lack of privacy there and
obviously we get to kind of pick and
choose now what we decide to share with
people but at the same time like it's
sometimes really hard for people to
respect those boundaries and really know
like when to kind of leave you alone or
when to kind of like ah let you do your
own thing and it's sometimes hard to say
only can't make this Joker I can't say
this or talk about this or be seen with
this person or go to this restaurant or
do this activity because it might come
off to the general public in this sort
of way it's like it's just really
strange to have to like constantly be
thinking about that at all times they
can do anything you're not having to
think twice about a situation yeah
but we're like wait if we do this are we
gonna get like no it definitely is the
choice that we chose to live at this
point I'm really thankful for honesty
like it's like a battle that I'm willing
to fight every day but it is really
crazy
something that people really don't think
about ever okay be honest I know you're
like competing too but like does it
really look bad it's like you never
finished the other it's like we're just
like stop it and you just don't connect
the lines the heart was also really my
dear the minute I was watching Dance
Moms and you were at like age seven
walking out with the foulest glam ever
with like yellow glitter on there I
would why I loved it every time it was
so funny to me I was like these girls
will be gonna have you but most busted
crusted dusted busted scanning ever yes
by the time they're like 12 yes
no no surprisingly we never broke out if
we had chewed at competitions we would
sleep in our eyelashes week oh and just
did I was gonna thought we'd have to get
ready in the morning for competition
like 5:30 he used to wake up yeah so
anyway so what she would do is I would
do my makeup and I would roll her over
while she's sleeping in did her full
face while she was sleeping that's a
truce yeah and then waking up with
eyelashes on and everything okay middle
of my eyelid I find the one doing all
the people's makeup a long set of
mascara and lashes the hardest thing
doing there was always lips
I feel like lips are very very specific
thing that can go so wrong
we're just like the slightest change of
shape at the slightest like over liner I
don't know why yeah it's the worst I can
do myself educator yeah shame on
yourself I really trust what I just
suited up I'm doing this like at a weird
a yeah it's really like hard doing it
like this I think we're both done ah now
we need to set your face oh it started
in place make the heart stay for him
wrap right I think if these literally
tried this deal I got some okay you can
do your thing okay oh it's so refreshing
going for the wet look very oh are you
ready for the grand reveal
I'm nervous for you to see it I'm
nervous from retail I'm obviously
nervous oh do you think I'm gonna probe
to 100 this looks so good like you're a
literary kidding me hello
Kenzie yours actually looks a really
good tale yeah it does the skin looks
really really even the highlight is that
all three places love the sister her I
think if anything like you said just the
contrary it's okay for a beginner Mui I
think this is really really good thanks
second time doing this actually first
time doing full glam flashes what yeah
I've never done like oh I'm shocked
like Hello thank you so much the reason
not like mine doesn't look that crazy is
because like all I watch is makeup
videos yeah you know and like I learned
so much from them that's how I learned
how to make them bridges tutorials yeah
Wow we love and educated makeup guru
sister yes so proud of your sister thank
you guys you guys literally you both say
this I think mighty Kenzie both did
amazing
so you sisters do to leave us a comment
down below and tell me who you think won
this challenge sister Maddie or sister
Kenzie hey you're never gonna win I mean
there you go girl you're never gonna
live without us
hey I think you guys know this video so
do please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below if you screw up if
you haven't already we're about to hit
four million sisters here on YouTube
you're a little bit kidding me hello
that is so iconic so thank you guys for
all the love and support click that big
red button hit that Bell icon so you
notified every time I upload a brand new
video that are good and fresh and fun
and you guys will have to see my
Coachella lookbook coming up very very
soon so that'll be fine as well if you
like to follow me on a makeup trade you
can follow me on instagram twitter
they're both just jam show myself work
behind the scenes and shave charles
knives after charles if you'd like to
find these two a beautiful lovely and
talented sisters at work and they find
you guys well my instagram is Kenzie and
my Twitter is Kenzie Ziegler and all of
my social medias are just Maddie Ziegler
love that this video sister shout out
goes to sister Lacey thank you so much
love probably solving and supporting you
I love you so so so much and if you
do the next video sister shadow make
sure to always reach me via video links
and they go live on Twitter all records
that were here for the sitter's today
thank you so much for watching it thank
you to my beautiful sisters and friends
and we will see you in the next one
[Music]