hi sisters James Charles head welcome
back to my youtube channel I know this
whole vibe is a little bit different
than what you're normally used to it has
been a hot minute since I've had a hat
and glasses on on a youtube video but
for today's video actually have
something that I am really really really
excited about and that I've never done
on this channel before and that is a
drawing video in last night's video I
recreated a bunch my followers makeup
looks and literally thank you guys so
much for all the love and support on
that video if you have not yet seen it
click right up here it was so fun to do
but I was actually reading through all
of the positive comments and so many of
them were actually talking about how
amazing the looks were and how they
actually required a lot of artistic
ability and I was getting a lot of
questions at whether or not I was able
to draw I've talked to this a few times
in different YouTube videos but I've
never ever gone fully in depth and
before I ever was picking up a blending
brushes and beauty blenders and
eyeshadow palettes I was actually
drawing for the entire first half of my
life and I was not gonna lie pretty good
at it if I do say so myself my all-time
favorite medium to work with was
charcoal and with charcoal I really
loved drawing portraits I've always
obviously had a very huge interest in
human faces which clearly translated
into my love for makeup getting to do
art on my own face but I would always
creep or just a really really powerful
woman that I've looked up to I've done
cara delevingne at kendall jenner kylie
jenner but it's been at several several
years since I've actually done one today
so for today today I thought I would
just sit down and chill into a little
chitchat art with you guys I've never
done this before I'm super super excited
for today's portrait I really want to do
this picture of Demi Lovato that I
printed out you guys know I literally
love dummy she's one of my biggest role
models and she's also so beautiful so I
think she'll be really fun to create
today I have no makeup on this is just a
very very chill vibe so hopefully you
guys like this video and without further
ado let's get to a sister sketching
[Music]
okay so let's jump right into it this is
probably gonna take me a several several
hours I'm guess I'm just gonna be
switching between like this camera and
then this camera and like time-lapse
hello so let's just get started I have
my notepad here of charcoal paper and I
have a few different charcoal pencils of
different hardness I have these good and
fresh cysts or blending stumps and then
of course I have this reference image of
dummy that I printed out literally hello
she looks the best ever in the entire
world so I'm going to try to recreate
this image today okay so I guess I'm
just gonna first start off by sketching
some of the light outlines of her facial
features using the really really light
pencil I know a lot of people say don't
outline like it's against the rules of
artistry when literally hello how else
are you gonna know where to put your
things so we're outlining today her face
probably goes to about here in the photo
and then her hair is covering it so I'm
just going to sketch in some hairs okay
her lips are probably gonna be about
here on this photo I'm pressing really
lightly my pencil as well because I
don't want to add too much color right
away since this paper is white I
obviously can't go any lighter with it
then white hello
color you can only go a darker so I'm
being really careful as to where I
actually put any pencil because it's
gonna be really hard to lighten things
later on a little bit also this top lip
here Leslie she's a pretty rounded
Cupid's bow actually um let's catch our
her sister schnoz Jeff Lee is a short
brown tail so probably right about there
I guess that's kind of all we need to
start sister shading a little bit so now
that we have two basic kind of layout of
all of dummies and facial features I
guess we get to go in and start shading
now and this is by far my favorite part
of the entire process I love love love
shading it's kind of just like
contouring of the face where you get to
really identity'
and highlights and shadows and just make
everything come to life so let's start
sister shading I want to avoid any
smudging as I possibly can so I guess
we're just gonna start right up here and
I'm just gonna grab my HB pencil from a
faber-castell and kind of lay down just
a really really light wash of color I'm
going in super super light with this
because remember you can always layer on
it's very very very easy to add in any
shadows but it's extremely hard to bring
back any highlights but it's also
important to keep in mind nothing should
ever be white except for the highlights
in somebody's eyes or on the face and
like the lips then I'm just going to
take one of my up blending sums this
one's kind of like a medium sized and
start to blend out that shading to
create smooth transitions
if anything ever becomes too harsh - I
really like to use these gummy erasers
you can get these at any art supply
store and you can kind of use this and
lightly kind of drag over the image to
pick up a little bit of that pigment I
really really love these racers for
doing this they work so much better than
normal pencil erasers would definitely
recommend I'm gonna go to the little bit
of a deeper pen so now this is a a 4b
which lays down color a lot harsher than
a normal to be white or than a normal HB
would I don't even know what these
pencils mean I'm not even gonna lie to
you guys I just know this one's deeper
so we're gonna use that one now I'm
gonna lay down this one right alongside
at dummy's hairline because obviously
we're gonna be drawing and hairs on
later on but there's definitely an
intense shadow going on in this region
and I need to add this to the picture
just gonna grab a blending stump and
blend that out so now that we have like
kind of the base the forehead it laid
out obviously we're going to come back
to this far later on but I want to keep
moving downward so I'm gonna grab a dark
pencil and I'm gonna start off doing it
Demi's eyebrows and I'm just gonna
basically do this by drawing in really
really light hair Ashok's
kind of in the same way that I would
normally do my own eyebrows in makeup I
definitely don't want to start off too
harsh and turn into Sharpie brows
because we all know what that looks like
I'm gonna go to the eraser like pinch it
and take this little dot kind of and use
this to go right in those brows and kind
of erase just some of those areas that
look a little bit more harsh to kind of
bring back some of the original paint
but underneath until it--and everything
up so it looks more natural
so now we get to start off by favorite
part of the entire portrait which is
always at the eyes I'm first gonna start
by shading the area that the eyes are in
so I'm just gonna grab my light pencil
once again and kind of shade this inner
corner I'm at dummies and nose Bridget
just to lay down a light base then same
thing I'm here I'm gonna lay some color
down right above the eyelid fold and we
have to create that kind of rounded
shape right up here with the brow bone
doesn't gonna follow the eye shadow
shape as well and bring some of this
color upwards just kind of like a
transition shade and makeup and then a
little bit below as well making sure to
leave open a white space which is where
the waterline will be later on I'm
actually so excited to be drawing Demi
today you guys know Heike how much of a
huge fan of her I am the rich is like
the only person to actually like Stan
even though I literally hate that word
she's just so talented it's not even
funny I want to do her makeup so bad
although Joe Pell glam does do a pretty
good job but like Demi needs a sister
James snatch she follows her on
Instagram we've dimmed back and forth a
few times about it I'm supposed to do it
all but she's I feel like my dream club
I just oh my god I feel like I could do
so many beautiful things with Demi who
about to me claiming her and then like
singing together actually that's a bad
idea
imagine me clamming her and then her
singing to me and me not opening my
mouth and being silent much better
option okay so now I need to turn
eyelashes which I'm actually kind of
scared for because I do have a tendency
to definitely over draw eyelashes and
then they turn from like eyelashes into
like I fur and that's definitely not the
look we're going for today I definitely
wanna give her like on Miami lash as
opposed to like a fluffy lash if you
know what I mean so we're gonna be
really gentle
that's like four eyelashes okay at the
beauty guru and we needs to calm down a
little bit so this is gonna be a
scenario where I should have done the
left eye first
so my fault but I'm gonna grab a tissue
I'm gonna put this over the eye that I
just did so I can work on this eye
without rubbing the side of my hand
against the entire drawing let's do the
eyebrow first
[Music]
okay so I need to start shading in
dummy's nose which I'm really not
looking forward to being that noses are
by far the hardest part in my opinion in
any portrait because one wrong shading
moment and like literally the entire
nose is gone
we gave Demi a rhinoplasty sorry sister
so I'm gonna try at my absolute best to
follow the shading in this original
picture and cross my fingers and pray to
the Lord and having a bob that we can do
this oh that was all supposed to happen
speaking of things that were not so so
happened
oh great segue James this weekend I just
went to Tanic on well didn't go to
tannic contactually went to the area of
tannic on and then proceeded to not
attend tanyka and it was interesting to
say the least
that's all I want to say on that
probably can't wait for a hashtag sister
cloud 2019 I want to take one of my tiny
blending sums now that already has some
charcoal on it and I'm actually gonna
use this to create some of the freckle
that Demi has on her nose
okay this is like not bad team is Demi
[Music]
she doesn't have a slight butt chin as
well which can relate so I'm just gonna
sketch that in and make sure I leave
like a little bit of a shot a moment
there so I can kind of shape that in
place and it going up on this side of
the jaw she definitely has a much more
intense shadow so I'm gonna grab a much
darker pencil this one is 6b and keeping
in mind who's gonna be here here in a
little bit I'm just going to place in
some of that pencil to blend out in a
second okay so I'm gonna move on to the
lips now and lips have voiced assume
that I've kind of struggled a little bit
just being that similar to kind of like
I was saying in the forehead earlier you
have to really keep in mind the
lightness areas because it's hard to
bring it back once it's gone and when it
comes to the lips you have to make them
look wet looking which includes a lot of
highlight it looks like her makeup
artist use kind of like a gloss over the
entire lip area as opposed to kind of
over lining the actual liberation if
that makes sense do you guys know what
I'm talking about so I'm gonna try to
create this shadow over top of the
actual lip region I'm just using a light
pencil okay so I know that this lip
looks really really weird right now
trust me um hello I see it too but if we
actually compare it to the reference
photo as you can tell all of the kind of
dark shades and medium shades are there
all I really need to add back in is
going to be the highlight shades which I
have to add on with a pen later on so
I'm actually gonna leave this how it is
right now surprisingly
[Music]
well that actually didn't take as long
as I was expecting it's my talk that
I've been doing this for a little really
like six hours now so that's really fine
and brush but now we'll finish up I
guess the neck and the hair which should
be pretty easy so I'm just going through
my darkest pencil and I'm drawing in
hair strokes all around where the edge
of dummy's head is going to be I'm not
realizing that this entire outside area
is gonna be filled with black so instead
of wasting this charcoal pencil I spent
a lot of money on and sitting here
scrubbing the entirety of this canvas I
just found this can of a black paint
which I got when I moved into my
apartment hashtag not sponsored but I'm
gonna actually try to paint the entire
outside edge with block instead
hopefully this isn't the worst idea ever
I can't find my brake paint brush so I
guess I'm literally just gonna use a
morphe 57 brush to paint this entire
thing so usko genes for 10% of your
purchase
I'm gonna grab some white paint also on
a morphe this brush and draw in some
hair highlights okay you guys I'm so
nervous I don't know why what the heck
okay three two one okay on camera low
key looks pretty good in fresh their
sister dummy seven hours later I'm
really really proud of the finish result
let's be real it is definitely not
perfect it could look a little bit more
like dummy I definitely wish I didn't do
the paint on the background I think it
looked a little bit too dark and the
white spots on the lips I don't know how
artists normally do that because
whatever uh pens I was using we're not
the tea but I feel like this is a solid
like a nine out of ten and I'm just
really really happy to be back in my
roots and what really got me into art in
the first place being at portraits I had
so much fun drawing sister died when you
said it and I really really hope I did
her justice she is by far one of my
all-time at biggest role models I am so
he loved her I think she is by far one
of the most talented vocalists of our
generation her vocals are truly
unmatched you can fight me on that in
the comments down below
she is so unapologetically herself and
she's also just the most stunning person
ever so I really really want to do her
makeup one day that would be so awesome
and I really really hope you guys
enjoyed this more like chillax
sit back James painting day it is not
very often that I get to just like sit
down and create I feel really really
weird not having any makeup on or my
hair done it feels very very off-brand
to me but you know what I had so much
fun while doing it and that's all that
matters and I really really hope you
guys enjoyed it too if you did it please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and show your support and
love it would really mean the absolute
world to me and definitely comment down
below and tell me if you want to see it
more painting or art videos in the
future I had so much fun doing this and
would love to do it again if you guys
are interested if you have not already
don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood it is a pretty lit
time I usually post makeup videos of
course and also click that belt like on
Sukie notified every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on a makeup store you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes heads up its James
Charles that extra s after Charles this
video sister shout-out goes to sister
Liv
thank you so much for always following
in supporting you I love you literally
is so so so much and if you like to be
in the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always reach for the
links Lego live on Twitter
alright sisters I love you so much thank
you for watching and I will see you
the next one by
[Music]