hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today today I have something a little
bit different and very very fun plan
that I'm actually so excited for this
morning I got up at the crack of dawn I
arose for my beauty sleep with a rude
alarm awakening but I went to the Grove
here in Los Angeles and waited in line
to get this the brand new iPhone acts in
case you missed an apple just released
two brand new iPhones beating the iPhone
8 and the iPhone acts I guess they
skipped the iPhone 9 because two seven
eight nine huh anyway regardless the
iPhone ACTU the iPhone 10 is the
brand-new anniversary I have one edition
and there are a lot of brand new
features to this phone that have never
been on an iPhone before one of the main
ones being that the way to unlock this
as you can see there was no home button
is a facial recognition unlock feature
there's been a lot of different
conspiracies about this some people
think it's really really dope some
people think that Apple is gathering a
facial recognition software to give to
the government I don't even know what
the hell is going on but this thing is
supposed to open up when I show my face
to it
and it's supposed to be really really
accurate you guys know that my job is
that makeup artist so most days also
enough like this but a lot of times
after a good long glam session I'll end
up with a even skin tone very very
contoured shakes a little bit I mean
lowered hairline with the facetune tool
a good highlight on the cheekbones
different eyebrows sometimes we have
crazy ass lashes on and sometimes even a
wig if it's a toggle as well so I'm
definitely very into the art of
transforming and pulling out different
looks so for today's video we're gonna
be using the brand new iPhone X and
we're gonna be applying a whole lot of
makeup today and seeing how much makeup
can really unpack the iPhone X to the
point where it won't recognize my face
anymore without further ado let's start
getting glam and transform as much as
possible to see if the iPhone will still
a mock once I glam session is complete
also make sure you stay tuned until the
very end of this video for to a very
very special announcements
[Music]
so before we actually apply any makeup
today I'm actually gonna go ahead and
set up the facial recognition software
so I'm gonna go into my settings on my
brand new iPhone and go into the face ID
and passcode I'm gonna turn on use face
Indy for iPhone unlock and I guess I'm
going to have to set my face ID so of
course I'm going to start this off by
using my bare face whoa this lady makes
my face look so bad
face ID is messed up I guess it was
literally that easy so let's hit done
and just to touch this out let's go
ahead and lock the phone and if I open
it up hello so I guess I've seen when
you put your face up to the phone it
would automatically open but that is not
the case as you can see there's a lock
icon at the top and when I put my face
in front of it it recognizes me and then
it turns to an open lock and then I can
swipe up hello and now the phone is open
this is complicated
jessa test is how I have sister Anthony
here with me as you can see the phone is
locked right now come on down I need you
to hold this up and test it to your face
and see if the thing changes to unlocked
no okay thank you so much we love
technology Hey so now we know that this
whole face ID thing works for now while
I have no makeup on let's go ahead and
put on a full face of Graham transform
ourselves and try again at the end and
see if this thing it still works I'm
first gonna shot off by applying my
makeup from from Ultra HD foundation SiC
don't forget to blend down the neck of
course and then I'm gonna grab a beauty
blender and blend this all in so based
on apples information face ID works on
your facial structure so I guess it's
supposed to measure the depth of your
face so even though we're gonna be
contouring a lot today it really Chezza
ourselves out and try to fool the camera
I'm sure that the technology may be
advanced enough to actually like do
measurements I'm really not sure how
this stuff works even though it says it
does measures distance I'm sure it does
measure things as well such as like eye
color and skin color obviously the goal
with your foundation is to get your skin
cloud to be as accurate as possible to
your normal skin color but for people
like me and my face is definitely a lot
more red than the rest of my body I do
have a lot of pimples and a lot of
rosacea as well so skin color may affect
it as well foundation is all apply it
I'm gonna grab my phone and I'm gonna
test this one out
still on lock's I'm not gonna get my
shake tape concealer in the shade light
sand and just highlight my face I'm
gonna make sure to make my highlights
and contours very very very intense
today to try my best to fool the system
I'm actually gonna take the Kat Von D
whiteout concealer as well obviously
this is in
show you white and I'm gonna play those
to the very high points of my face just
to once again intensify those highlights
this for the hell of that I'm gonna go
ahead and also try this wall the stuff
is on my face unblended still works once
again just gonna blend it out using a
and damp Beauty Blender oh oh oops I'm
still work I'm gonna take my sponge into
a little bit of laura mercier Jeb's is a
setting powder to set my face in place
so it doesn't move around so now that my
face is all set in place I'm going to
use the Kat Von D shade and light
palette and I'm going to contour the
crap out of my face using my morphe m
405 brush you guys know you can use
coded change for 10% off for a few
products and I'm really gonna go in
intense with this I'm gonna use and mix
up the middle and right hand shades
obviously I would never instruct on
doing a contour this straw I mean if you
really want to chill yourself out like I
don't blame you girl but I usually go
more soft contour but today we're trying
to create a completely false facial
structure here let's see if we can
really define these cheeks I'm gonna use
this contour brush and kind of pull it
down slightly right in this region as
well to create the illusion of a more
sunken in cheekbone to see if that will
flow as well of course we have to
contour the hell out of the forehead but
let's be real I do this in all my looks
regardless so does a normal step for me
then of course we're gonna contour our
jaw lines and make sure that the Dolan
twins aren't quaking I'm gonna contour
my nose as well using a really really
dark powder on a fluffy blending brush
oh my that looks the worst we're gonna
grab a lighter powder that's really
close to my skin tone and put this on
the sides my nose to really enhance the
look of the pinch okay so my faces a
little bit just lit out if I do say so
myself obviously this is not what my
normal makeup looks like I promise if
you're new to the sisterhood please
check out some of my other videos my
makeup usually looks a lot better than
this or at least I hope it does but
let's go ahead and try this out
it's still on locks oh my god
I'm gonna take a powder puff and we're
going to bake the highlights of my face
to really intensify this even more gonna
go right up against the line of the nose
contour okay I'm a little bit stuck
right now I really thought this is gonna
not work a whole lot sooner than it
already is and I'm not realizing that
I'm gonna have to probably go a lot
farther into my makeup routine then
anticipated so die of the mood to do
that right now but guys we have to
figure this out well my face is baking
in the oven I'm gonna go to my benefit
purse I see my brow pencil in the shade
at number 4 and to find out my eyebrows
who knows if it's not my freakin facial
shape maybe my eyebrows will fool that
oh you know what while we're at it let's
go ahead and try out the brand-new
camera on this too because it's
apparently supposed to be really oh my
god I'm scared my pores oh this is like
scary good quality okay let's go ahead
and try to use this as an actual mirror
oh you're kidding
okay this idea was cancelled alright
let's go ahead and see if brows the fact
this at this point I'm starting to lose
my hope here
No Oh virtually for this video I
honestly did not have high hopes for
this I thought I was gonna be able to
pull this really easily I was gonna do
my everyday makeup routine for you guys
but clearly this is not working out as
well as I had planned so instead of
doing my normal Lily lashes miami's I
let it go on my three oh ones which is
you guys know if you are drag fans that
these are the classic drag lashes they
are huge they're very very long and
they're gonna take out my entire eye but
maybe it'll look like a different person
okay so this is definitely not the look
I had intended on going for today but I
guess you got to do what you got to do
so would these lashes applied let's go
ahead and blend them together with some
mascara I'm going to mix together my
real lashes with the fake ones make this
look as real as possible despite the
fact that I have literal spiders glued
onto my eyes right now and we're going
to test this thing out okay iPhone locks
oh and this we're really not sure what I
can do to make this not work I guess I'm
just going to wipe off my bake here and
then apply a crazy-ass lip and some
highlighter and if that doesn't work
we're gonna have to take some drastic
measures here I'm next gonna take my
makeup of our pigment in the shade
number 13 this is probably the most
blinding highlighter that is in my
collection it is the most pigmented and
is so so so bright when I do use this I
only use the slightest bit I'm gonna pry
this using my more of um of 501 brush
you see what I'm talking about here to
the high points of my face so since none
of this work the last step in my makeup
routine is always gonna be the lipid you
doodahs
go for today it's like I'm gonna use the
Anasazi liquid lipstick in the shade of
paint and I'm going to go a little bit
crazy with the over lining
laughs injections never heard of her
let's try this you're kidding
you've got this is God to be a joke how
I'm out of makeup tips let's go ahead
and try a little bit harder here phone
oh my god I am so shocked right now
this is not what I wanted I thought this
video is gonna take me five minutes to
film I really thought my ass was gonna
have Apple quaking as soon as I got like
the nose contour I'm annoyed because not
only did I have to put on makeup for the
seven times today now I look really
stupid and I have places to go after
this so at this point I'm a little
stumped clearly the crazy makeup did not
work like I wanted it to the wigs did
not work like I wanted them to so my
last and final step today is gonna be to
try out a photo of myself no Apple seems
the photos do not work you have to be
like alive and breathing for the phone
to recognize you which is great
considering my job this ability to post
photos myself online so thank God if my
phone gets stolen at least on all that a
photo can open it up but let's go ahead
and try out and see the real tape all
right so this is my most recent
Instagram photo I just posted this
earlier on today if your true sister
will give it a double tap and if you're
not following me on Instagram
you should totally do that for a cute
very face to him selfies every once in a
while I promise it is a very very good
time come on shameless self-promotion
but I'm gonna take this photo on
Anthony's phone and my new iPhone X and
then hold them right up in front of each
other and see if this works
[Music]
hello she's not working Mary Wow that's
thought after an hour of making herself
look absolutely ridiculous all I needed
to do was hold up a photo of myself in
front of it it probably knows that it
was facetune Harbor okay so that's all I
have for this videos today clearly this
did not exactly go as I had planned
honestly at this point I am really
really shook and impressed by the new
iPhone X facial brush to make facial
bracket and honestly at this point I am
really really shocked and impressed by
the new iPhone facial recognition
software I really did not think I was
gonna be this good I thought I would
easily be able to crack it at some point
throughout this routine the only thing
we got it with today was the picture
which is actually a really really good
thing so I'm actually very glad to know
that my new iPhone is super secure if
you guys enjoy today's video please
don't forget to give a thumbs up down
below and definitely me comment as well
do plan on getting the iPhone X or do
you think it is some big huge government
conspiracy theory I know my ass was
definitely off really early this morning
to wait in line for it
I had to get mine I was very very
excited because I had an upgrade and not
only did I get one for myself but I also
may or may not have gotten a second
iPhone X for one of your sisters out
there for a giveaway because I just love
you guys so so much definitely stay
tuned because there's going to be a full
month of holiday giveaways coming very
very student this is gonna be one of the
prizes so you can't win this just yet
but it is coming so make sure you
subscribe down below if you have not
ready turn on my post notifications
because you can find out how to win this
and a few videos coming up soon alright
guys so I know I said to stage one for
the end of this video for a very very
special little announcement and here it
is normally you guys know that a posting
schedule it's line that I show a little
bit with I've definitely taken a lot of
breaks from YouTube and I'm pretty bad
let's be honest at keeping up a
consistent posting schedule but because
of a few videos that had to be uploaded
on a certain day coming up within the
next few days I figured might as well
make this week a big big bang so
starting today Saturday there will be a
new upload every single day up until
next Friday so this week overall is
gonna be so much fun and I hope you guys
are so pumped for six uploads in a row
I'm already stressed out thinking about
it but I know we can do this and I hope
you guys are ready for some awesome
videos if you guys like to follow me on
a makeup journey you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter up there bullet is
James Charles and my snapchat for behind
the scenes site itself is James Charles
and extra ass after Charles definitely
subscribe down below if you have not
ready and make sure to click that Bell
icon so you can we know
but every time I upload like I said
there's gonna be a lot of them coming in
the next few days and you were
definitely not gonna want to miss this
big sister shout out goes to a sister
Kayla
thank you so much being for always
falling in supporting you and I love you
so so so much and if you'd like to be
next week sister shout out make sure to
always share my video links and they go
live on Twitter alright guys thank you
so much for watching I love you so much
I'm gonna wipe out this crazy-ass makeup
and I will see you in the next one bye
guys
[Music]