[Music]
hi guys James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel this past
weekend I went to generation Beauty and
Los Angeles and I got to see everybody
and I got to meet so many of you guys
which was so much fun for today's look I
decided to do this monochromatic pink
glowing glam I love this look this is
what I were to generation Beauty at this
past weekend and so many of you guys are
asking questions about so I figured I
would sit down and do tutorial like I
said in my last video I have not done
any creative look in a long time and
let's be real one colors and the most
creative thing in the world but at least
it's not everyday wearable glam trust me
we'll be getting into more conceptual
crazy look soon especially with
Coachella coming up but for now if you
guys want to see how I created this look
make sure you would keep on watching I'm
first gonna start off by priming my face
as always with my benefit Porefessional
primer nothing new just sloppiness on
over to get a nice and smooth base her
foundation today I'm actually gonna be
trying a new combination I am very very
excited for this one of my friends
recommended this combo to me and he
always looks so freaking bomb with the
most beautiful flawless skin so I just
went to support earlier on tonight and
everything up and we're gonna do a
little bit of mixing I'm gonna use my
Giorgio Armani a luminous sub foundation
in the shade 3.5 this is way too dark
for me so I'm gonna be mixing it with
the Urban Decay Naked skin in the shade
2.5 and then the bare minerals
complexion rescue in opal which is the
lightest shade so hopefully that'll like
even everything out I guess well this is
very liquidy yeah oh wow oh this looks
gross until apply this today I will be
using my morphe 48 brush ok I'm
switching to a Beauty Blender I just
could not do the whole brush situation
alright I'm not too sure how I feel
about this just yet this is the first
time I've ever mixed foundations
I like the coverage is giving me it's
like a nice natural coverage not sure if
I'd like the texture but then again my
face is already really textured to begin
so I'm not really sure if it's just me
like imagining worst texture or like if
there's I don't know well I'm just gonna
keep going and see what it feels like
later on we're gonna see though I'm
gonna use of course my fav the
heart-shaped tape I use a lot less
concealer than normal today I want my
skin to look like really natural and
like really do
and Chloe with this look not as like
cakey like my normal everyday makeup
alright so overall actually really
liking how this is looking I didn't pre
oh sometimes take it back and then I'm
gonna stand under my eyes by Laura
Mercier secret under-eye brightening
powder well that's a mouthful
the foundation is separating a little
bit in the nose region but I mean are we
really surprised that gets Jim Charles
knows I have to pre prime like 15 layers
anyway to begin with so this is no
shocker I'm gonna really lightly dust
away the Laura Mercier powder oh that I
don't like oh you just took a turn for
the worst
am I seeing things I feel like I'm just
so used to my makeup forever stick at
this point that anything else is just
gonna look so strange to me I'm probably
just over exaggerating like I said I'm
just gonna keep going we'll figure it
out later
Gibran's today I'm using the middle
shade of the Kat Von D shade lamp out of
my morphe M 435 I did just buy a new
palette at Sephora earlier on today but
I'm gonna get all the way out of this
one that I possibly can I feel like this
secret under-eye brightening powder may
have secretly brightened up my under-eye
a little bit too much Laura Mercier girl
I trust that you and since the
foundation on my nose is separating a
little bit I'm going to lightly and I
mean super super lightly try to contour
my nose using my own 4-3-3 this is just
a normal blending brush a lot of you
guys asked to and what I do my nose
contour I always like to bring that
shadow just the tiniest bit into my brow
bone region it always looks kind of
strange if you have like a really
pinched nose contour going like all the
way up the bridge and then also just
like stops here so I always like to
blend it just a little bit open to like
the socket brow region just to kind of
make everything continuous and flow and
look as natural as we can get to start
off my brows I'm gonna be using my
benefit precisely my brow pencil in the
shade number 5 for this particular look
I'm keeping my brows super fluffy and
almost like natural I want them to be
very very like editorial but she push
top so I'm doing them the same way I did
in my last video the everyday makeup
routine just sketching in hairs and then
brushing upwards to blend them out I'm
gonna super lightly conceal and clean up
that browsing my e43 and its shape tape
concealer and then just the tiniest bit
of benefit gimme brow to brush the hairs
upwards and keep them in place
okay Wow for once I'm actually loving
how this bra is turning out maybe today
will be a good makeup day unlike the
last video I said very very similar to
my everyday makeup routine bras just
light fluffy and natural sort of to
prime my lids for shadow I'm just gonna
use a little bit more of that shape tape
concealer and then just setting those
lives in place using my at a 45 for more
P and my yet Cody ayersman powder come
on guys you know me how to fit it in
there somewhere for eyeshadow today I'm
gonna start off with my m4 for one from
morphe and the makeup geek single shadow
in the shade Ben I'm really lightly
placing this in the crease and on the
lid just making a kind of really blown
out pinky a cool toned red smokey eye
only go to use me I think like probably
one or two shadows for this entire color
and you could totally switch this up to
be any color that your heart desires I
just chose to do pink today grabbing
that same exact shadow on an m4 33 I'm
going to deepen up the lid and just
blend that into the crease and I'm also
using that brush in the same shape to
begin of shading my lower lash line for
the later I'm gonna spreads my ab 705
with a little bit of Urban Decay all
nighter setting spray and then I'm going
to use the untamed pressed pigment oh
wow that is so pretty and then going
back into my m4 33 to blend out the
edges okay I just did the other eye off
camera so we can save some time and not
be sitting here for a million years now
normally next I would do lashes but I'm
gonna kind of skip around and change up
the order a little bit for this
particular look taking Miami 5 on I'm
gonna dip into a little bit more of that
bit in a shadow I'm actually gonna be
using this eyeshadow for blush and it's
just a powder so it'll totally work and
I would normally use a blush but I don't
really have anything that'll match is
the exact color and I want this entire
thing to be monochromatic and really
really cohesive I'm gonna super lightly
dust this color over my cheekbones where
I would normally put my blush and my
highlighter as well so the two will mix
together next I'm gonna go to this
highlighter from a star crush minerals
in the shade
rosy future these products are so Bob
and I don't think I've talked about them
on my channel before I used to have a
code and expired but now it's back so I
wanted to feature this today if you use
code James on the ropes that you get 50%
off all products this video is not
sponsored I promise I just love
featuring brands that I love and support
especially the ones that are cheap
because I know
expensive makeup can be these guys are
four frickin dollars with the code and
I'm pretty sure they're single shadows
or like a dollar and fifty cents it's a
really good deal for really great
products and if you haven't checked them
out you totally should
oh that's what I'm freaking talking
about I obviously packed at Emma glow on
the cheek and I'm also gonna put it
underneath the brow bone and in the
inner corner and just as a side note I
would definitely recommend applying
these highlighters with a wet brush
using a tiny I'm 515 detail brush so I'm
going in with a little bit more of a
highlighter with a wet brush and I'm
just gonna intensify at the inner
corners I'm also going to use this brush
to highlight my nose next I'm gonna go
back into my blush brush in my in shade
and just go right over the blush and
highlighter again to make sure they are
nice and blended together to line my
waterlines today I'm going to use the
makeup rubber lip pencil in the shade of
20 this is just a pink liner that is
hopefully safe for the waterline I
honestly wish it didn't unrest gear up
but now that I did there's no going back
so I'm gonna pop on the Lily lashes in
the style Lux just so it doesn't look
funky so since I did everything out of
like a weird order I guess everything is
kind of done except for the lips which
is strange this feels really awkward I
feel like I've been million more things
to do but I guess we're done to be
perfectly honest this foundation
combination is not my favorite I do feel
pretty cakey but at least I tried
something new for all you guys that were
complaining I'll be using the same
products you're freaking welcome back to
the makeup forever stick for the next
video I don't really know what I want to
do with the lips for this look but my
first instinct is I need to block them
out and then do highlighter so I'm going
to try that first
mmm okay I hate this let me find a lip
color and I'll be right back
oh okay yes much better I just applied
my over liquid lipstick in the shade the
Bronx is my morphe 1 6 0 - 1/8 fresh
it's just a liner brush I always usually
do my black lips like with a liner brush
just because it's so much easier and
once you mess up you can never go back
so better to be safe rather than sorry
once my lipstick has dried down I'm
gonna go in once again with that soy
crushed minerals highlighter and my
morphe 705 brush to pack that oughta
make a metallic lip
alright guys and this is the completed a
monochromatic pink glam for today I'm
honestly loving for this whole like a
monochromatic one color glow thing it
was really fun to just sit down and
experiment like I said in my last video
I have not had time to do any creative
looks in a long long time so this is so
fun to do
also I wore this up to Gen Beauty this
past weekend in LA which was so fun it
was so nice meeting all of you guys and
I got so many questions about this
makeup so this is say this is what I
wore to answer all of your guys's
questions also you could do literally
any color you want in pink obviously
blue purple green would look so pretty
with this whole like a monochromatic
thing and if you try this yourself
please make sure any time you an
Instagram I'd love to see all of your
beautiful colorful monochromatic faces
that was a mouthful if you guys did
enjoy this video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below to
subscribe if you have not already I post
videos every single week and I would
love to have you join the family if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can check out my Instagram
and Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
the scenes I've stopped is James Charles
in the next row ask after Charles
alright guys thank you so much for
watching and I will see you next time
bye