hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
now the Halloween is officially over and
we are on to November that means it is
officially holiday season I am so so
excited because the following winter
time is by far my favorite time at the
entire year this is the only time that I
am slightly missing upstate New York but
I'm happy in LA I love a good breeze all
the leaves falling from the trees and of
course all the pumpkin spice latte
things but most of all all the makeup
brands out there holiday collections as
many of you guys know I'm currently
doing a sister upload week where I'm
uploading one video every single day for
an entire week we started this past
Saturday so make sure to check out the
previous videos if you have not seen
them yet and we have plenty of fun
videos coming soon as well that you will
have to say too and for but for today's
video I'm so pumped because I am gonna
showing you guys the brand new morphe
Holiday Collection you guys know I love
morphe so much I literally like one of
them all the time and even have my
coupon code for them on one of my
hoodie's but I really do love them as
both a brand and their products I think
they're really really great and this is
more B's first ever big big launch like
this and I had the absolute honor of
being able to actually model for the
collection and it was so so much fun so
without further ado if you want to see
all the new holiday items and how I
created this eyeshadow look today using
the Brady with 39a palette make sure you
keep on watching so a few days ago I got
a rather large package sent to my
doorstep and when I opened it up it came
with this then it literally cannot even
fit fully on the camera but this is the
pr package the morphe Holiday Collection
came in before we even get into the
actual products let's talk about this
freaking packaging because this is
absolutely stunning a lot of people
complained in the past about more V's
packaging being very very cheap looking
and I do not think that that argument is
if I want to make it all anymore there
are new stuff and new design and
products look so so good I've been so so
proud to watch them grow from the
beginning to where they are now it is
truly so exciting okay so looking at
this entire collection in front of me
there are a lot of things you have more
people's definitely not playing around
they said girl your stockings are going
to be stuffed let's go to knock out the
brush collections first so the first
thing I want to show you guys is the I
still a six piece brushed collection now
before we even talk about the actual
brushes inside once again the name
isolates so good the packaging off
stunning so opening us up you get six
different brushes for doing your
eyeshadow with and also a cute little
gold bag to store them all in I do not
even know this is a part of the
collection so cute you definitely have a
lot to talk about here so I'm just gonna
go through these drawers there quickly
but there is a tiny brush for doing
winged liner a pencil brush which you
guys know I always love to do for
highlighting my nose
but in our chorus my brow bones or any
detail work on the eyes of course a flat
top concealer brush for any cleanup work
I love using one of these to clean up
underneath my brows or sometimes my
winged liner or even my lip line if it's
looking a little bit wonky we have a
fluffy Packer brush which is perfect for
packing on any eyeshadow to the lid then
of course a fluffy blending brush whoo
that's a mouthful right there this will
be perfect for applying shadow into the
crease and on the eyelid and then of
course blending it out as well and then
of course a fluffy synthetic brush I
absolutely love using these for when it
comes to like blending work that needs
to be done a little bit more soft that
makes sense for instance like blending
out a nose contour or blending out a
shadow that's already applied like with
no product on it or I also use one of
these for blending out my eyelid primer
all the time so that is the ice layer
brush collection like I said it is a six
piece collection I'm gonna put the price
of it right down here so you guys can
see it because I don't know the prices
off the top of my head I think it
definitely has every different type of
brush that you would ever need to start
off and I sort of look so thinks it
would be a really really great look for
beginners so the next brush that is
called complexion goals in one skin the
packaging is so beyond beautiful and
this a five piece brush collection and
based on the name and the size of this
box I'm assuming this one is going to be
for skin and complexion style brushes
okay so opening this up once again we
get a cute little brush case and then of
course we have the five brushes that the
complexion collection comes with so
starting off in the order that I would
use them in we first have a flat top
kabuki brush physically perfect for
blending in your foundation and it is so
so soft next we have a fluffy a rounded
brush and I would use this to set my
face in place using a translucent
setting powder
nice to have this a fluffy angle brush
and I would use this to contour so I put
it right here just has all my cheekbones
of course we have two snaps a jawline
and the forehead as well so after I
contour you guys know that I like to
lightly bake my face a little bit after
baking I would go into this next fluffy
tapered rounded blending brush whoa and
use this to a whiteboy the baked or
deepen up my contours a little bit and
lastly finally not least we have of
course the classic fan brush which
everybody uses to highlight
get that blinding glow all right guys
that is the complexion of goals brush
collection all complete like I said it
is day five piece of brush - and I'll
put the price right down here I think
this is once again a really great set
for any beginner who likes to focus on
their skin I know my skin used to be a
really really big problem spot
especially when it came to my makeup and
I've been working so hard on it and it's
finally in a place that I'm like
relatively happy with so I would
definitely recommend this brush that to
anybody who wants to really have that
slate it's matched porcelain face tuned
in real life looking skin alright so
last but certainly not least brush
clicks that I want to tell you guys
about today is the bling it on brush
collection opening this case up you get
once again a cute little storage thing
and this is more of like a rose gold
envelope I think it is so cute and then
opening this up you fold this little
slope up and you get little individual
compartments for all your brushes so you
can keep them super neat and organized
so this right here is a seven piece of
brush collection it comes with three
different face brushes and four
different eye brushes and these retail
for a whopping $79 I know that price tag
is definitely a really really high it
but these are definitely a collector's
item these are rolls called brushes and
then they have the cute little crystal
with jeweled handles they are absolutely
stunning
these are definitely gonna be a
collector's item I would not recommend
these for the everyday and makeup wear
these are gonna be a really really great
gift for anybody that really really
loves makeup and the beauty world I know
that I personally will never use these
they'll be displayed proudly right next
to my diamond brush collection for more
free launched a few months ago these
will be a really really great gift for
anybody that absolutely loves the makeup
world alright so those are all the brush
collections all complete but before we
move on to the eyeshadow today which I
am so pumped for I do want to show you
guys two other sets that came out with
this Holiday Collection those being the
weapons of mass seduction sets literally
once again the names so good we have
pure nude and deep smoky and these are
basically five piece sets they've come
with is that as you can see those are
they black gel liner a black eyeliner
pencil a smudger fluffy brush and a tiny
detailed smudger brush and of course
this little trio of eyeshadow colors
right here a black brown and many more
bronze e copper shade then the same
exact thing comes in the set pure nude
but this is the eyeshadow trio comes
with instead and is like a brownie
cranberry shade a light pink shade and
then a light orange shade perfect for a
more natural everyday on-the-go
eyeshadow look I think these scents are
gonna be perfect for anybody who was
born
it's makeup or a beginner it's literally
$15 for a five piece set of everything
you could possibly need for either a
smoky eye or a more natural all right
finally we get to open to the eyeshadow
which is what I know all of you guys
have been waiting for and I'm so pumped
for before we actually get into the main
star of the show though we have two
smaller palettes being the night master
and the day it's layer so this is the
base layer palette it comes with 15
different shades and retails for $15 so
definitely super super cheap it has a
mirror at the top as well which a lot of
morphe problems that don't have so thank
God they out of this it is so incredibly
helpful that you can do your makeup on
the go and this palette comes with a lot
of warm tone shade such as oranges than
the classic Browns and then we even have
any more like ready burnt shade to put
on top of the lid definitely a beautiful
mix of mattes and metallics and I think
this one is kind of comparable to the 35
oh just a fewer shades for a more
concentrated look obviously not
everybody can carry around some huge ass
palette with them so I think this is a
really really great palette for travel
and then just like the dates later we
have the night master palette once again
this one is $15 for 15 shades and this
palette is more a cool tone with like
Browns still a few orangie tones up and
here but also the more purpley cranberry
tones for a more night on the town a
type of look finally the palette that
I've been so excited to tell you about
is the 39a which is the dare to create
palette so this is the 30 on a right
here and if you'll notice it is much
bigger than the typical morphe palette
that's because if you open it up this is
what you have inside most morphe palette
retail for $22 and have seven rows of
five-minute oh five rows of seven
shadows that's right and this pot is
definitely a lot different than the
typical morphe palette this one retails
for $32 and it comes with 39 shades
instead of 35 but as you'll notice the
middle row of this palette is all bigger
than the average pen size and these are
all transition shades I think this
Polly's absolute do this because not
only are there literally seven different
transition shades for seven different
skin tones or seven different looks the
pan sizes are also a lot bigger because
y'all know as soon as you get that
palette that you really really love the
first shade you're gonna hit pan on is
it transition shade because you use it
all the time trust me it happens to me
all the time so I think it is so smart
to make the transition shades bigger so
you never pan on them and you can use
them and love them forever without
further adieu I'm exhausted at talking
at this point y'all are probably getting
tired of hearing my voice so let's are
playing with these shadows so first
program in the shader to find me on the
light fluffy brush from the ice lay a
brush kit and putting that in at my
crease as a transition shade I'm just
putting this shade all over my crease to
get a light wash of color on there to
prepare for all the shadows coming soon
I'm not gonna grab the shade of vivid on
that flat pack or brush on the same
brush set and use this too to find out
the crease a little bit more I'm gonna
do a little bit of a halo eyes today so
when it comes to the crease I'm keeping
it pretty rounded and when I get to the
outer corner I'm not pulling it out and
winging it as much as I usually do you
guys know that I love doing that so this
is pretty hard for me but I think the
rounded I steep is gonna be beautiful
for today's look next under grab at 514
brush and dip into the shades passion
and vibrant and just mix them together
to deepen up the crease a little bit
next time to grab that flat Packer brush
that once again I use to to find the
crease and grab the shade thick goal and
start to pack that on the lid I can
honestly say I think it has been a month
since I've lost use green eyeshadow I
don't really light the color green but
these clubs in this palette are so
beautiful and it is perfect for holiday
season so I figured I would suck it up
and create a bomb-ass slang camo green
look today just for you guys I cannot
even tell you how good it feels to be
able to open a morphe palette and use a
mirror inside of it to blend my
eyeshadow today just because I've
modeled before this collection does not
mean I can't throw a little bit of shade
at my favorite brand this should have
been done a lot sooner and I'm so glad
they finally did it once that's all
blended out and I'm happy with where the
green is I'm gonna go to the other side
of that flat Packer brush and dip into
the shade so glam it is like this bronzy
antique greeny gold type of color it is
so beautiful and I'll grab a little bit
of my morphe setting spray and I'm going
to spritz the brush just to get it nice
and damp so the color is super pigmented
and then I'm just gonna pack this right
on the center of the lid that's
beautiful I'm next I take the pencil
brush on the ice like it and I'm gonna
dip into the shade pine and I'm going to
use this to blend out the edges and
deepen up the inner and outer corner of
this halo eye this pie and show you
deftly does have a little bit of kick
back so make sure to top off your brush
before you apply it or else you might be
looking a little crazy and then just for
a little bit more vibrancy I'm gonna dip
into the shade muse which is a block for
the palate once again so glad we're
finally adding blocks with our palettes
I always love a little bit of block to
define and just be everything a little
bit more deep and then back into that
original fluffy brush that we use for
the transition shade
for one final pop on the island before
we move on to the lower lash line I want
to show you guys saying that I am so
excited about and that is the master of
metallic sad so these are here are the
master of metallics and these are cream
eyeshadows and these are probably my
favorite item out of this entire
collection aside from the 39a palette of
course this set of three cream
eyeshadows comes for $12 meaning there
are four dollars each and these are so
beyond beautiful so comes with the shade
gold bronze and copper oh my god and my
opinion they're pretty comparable to the
steel at liquid metals they're
definitely not as like a glittery but
they're really really beautiful and
metallic and shiny and this is the only
$12 for a set of three meaning there are
four dollars each you guys you have to
get these that I really really hope that
more he comes out with more of these
soon because I definitely will be
needing a lot more colors for today's
I'm going to take a little bit of the
shade of gold and pop that right on the
center of my lid oh my god that is so
pretty then before choice that I'm just
gonna take my pencil brush to make sure
the edges are nice and blended out so
lesson learned these definitely dry down
really really fast which is definitely
not a bad thing but if you're gonna be
playing with these just be careful work
in small sections and blend fast because
this looks so bomb by the way speaking
of fast dry down times as well you're
kidding
so now that the top foot is all done
let's go in with the lower lash line and
the first thing I got that fluffy brush
once again from the ice light collection
and dip into the shade it defined me
just for a light wash the color for the
smooth blend on the lower lash and then
using an Adam 514 with a shade of
passion and deepening that up a little
bit and then placing the shade a fickle
on the inner and outer corner using that
pencil brush once you're gonna give me a
little bit of muse on a tiny liner brush
and I'm going to place that right on the
inner and outer corners just for a
little bit more definition and then just
putting a little dollop of the gold
cream shadow right in the center so next
we have two more kits from this
collection both beating to draw
attention sets they come in neutral and
bold and these are both sets of 10
different eyeliner pencils it has $19
each for 10 pencils per kit and this is
what they look like and for today's line
I'm gonna grab the shade coconut oh
looks today so I'm gonna grab the shade
coconut and I'm gonna use this to line
up my lower waterline for last day I'm
gonna quickly pop on a pair of house
Lasha psychotics once again thank God
for this mirror situation it is
literally a holiday miracle alright guys
and that is one holiday I'll complete
I'm gonna do the other one off camera
quickly to save some time and I'll be
right back to finish out the rest my
face and the collection alright guys
those are both holiday eyes all complete
I just went ahead and I quickly did my
highlight off cameras we get that
natural glow and now to move on to the
lipid II doodahs there are actually a
ton of lips launched with this
collection the first two items being
these two lip kits being painted the
town nude and paint the town red
both retailing for $12 each with three
different lips inside so $4 a liquid
lipstick so in the paint the town notes
that we have this shade Lulu
sweets which is the lightest of the
three and then dainty and then in the
paint the town red set we have the shade
of stunner which is a deep blue toned
rabbit Bonnie which is a true like
bright red perfect for the holiday
season and then finally the shade lovely
which is a more orange e tone red they
also launched five different metallic
liquid lipstick shades that all retail
for $12 each
just being straight-up honest metallic
low hood lipsticks are really not my
favorite I'm not the biggest fan of the
look of them but I'm gonna show you guys
anyway just in case you are because
that's 45 we had this like red metallic
shade which is called spotlight there's
also this bronzy shade called luster
this beautiful bright gold shade is
called Goldy this shade called
reflection is the very like muted
purpley Mavi color but on camera it's
showing up really really vibrant which
leads me to believe that this may be
more of like a duo chrome shade other
than a metallic which is super dope and
then we have the shade sleek which is
once again a more a red metallic shade
and this is it next to spotlight as you
can see it's a little more purpley and a
little bit deeper for lips today I'm
first gonna apply this shade of Lulu all
over and then layering over top the
shade of sweets
and then lhasa finally not least I'm
gonna finish off this look you see my
morphe setting spray I reckon this is
the completed look using the brand new
morphe Holiday Collection I'm honestly
living for this like I said it has been
so so long so I put on a green eyeshadow
because I just really not my favorite
color but today I'm like living the camo
fantasy definitely comment down below
tell me what you guys think of the brand
new collection do you like it - love it
do you hate it I can't wait to see what
all your sisters have to say like I said
it was such an honor to be working with
morphe on this collection just to make
everything very very very clear this is
not a collaboration this is not a James
Charles X morphe palette
although saying that does sound really
really nice and that would definitely be
something amazing for the future but
this is just a normal palette I just
happened to be the model for it I'm not
making any money off of this as always
if you want to use code James it gives
you 10% off this entire holiday season
like always you totally don't have to
that is a ok I just want to give it to
you guys because holiday season can be
so ridiculously expensive but trust me I
feel you makeup it's not cheap either
so Koh James 10% off you're welcome
sisters just a friendly reminder that
everything I just showed you guys like
just tomorrow morning November 7th and I
think 10 a.m. Pacific Standard Time not
100% sure make sure you're following me
on Twitter and snapchat for like
live-action updates on that stuff if you
guys enjoyed today's video please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and click Subscribe if you have
not already we're literally so close to
2 million subscribers I cannot believe
it also click that little bell icon it
for to be notified every time I upload a
new video in case you guys didn't know
we are currently in the middle of a
sister upload week I've been uploading a
video every single day so far and there
are plenty more videos to come so I am
so excited and you guys are definitely
not gonna want to miss them this week
sister shadow goes to Charlotte thank
you so much baby for always following
and supporting you know I love you so so
much
and if you would like to be next
accessory shout out make sure to always
reach me my video links and they go live
on Twitter all right sisters thank you
so much for watching I love you so so
much happy holidays and I'll see you
guys tomorrow