hi sisters at James house here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I do
apologize if I sound disgusting I'm very
very sick right now from traveling and
I've been filming all day long this is
video number 6 please save me but you
know what we're powering through cutting
right to the point for this video I
thought I wouldn't sit down today and
talk to you guys about my all-time
favorite brushes that you totally need
in your set I get messages geum's tweets
comments all the time from you guys
asking what brushes I love the most what
I use and what I use them for so today I
thought I would just sit down and pick
out my all-time faves that I think
everybody needs as their like base
starter brush set and recommend them to
you I'll say it now because there's
gonna be a ton of comments on it almost
every single one of these brushes are
from morphe except for a few outliers
this video is not sponsored morphe is
not sending me a check for posting this
video and i don't know why people will
always like comment speculating whether
or not things are sponsored in case you
didn't know it is literally illegal to
have a sponsored video and lie about it
like I'm trying to decorate my apartment
not a jail cell not being said I do have
a coupon code a wedmore fee it is James
and it gives you 10% off that 10% is
Commission so it goes to me you do not
have to use my color I really could not
care less trust me and it's just a
discount that is there for you guys I
truly do enjoy all these brushes I mean
the fact that they are this dirty and
gross should show you that I use them
and everything one might look so I
really do love their products alright
guys so grab a pencil and a piece of
paper and get ready to write down a ton
of brushes I'm just gonna go in the
order of which I do my makeup routine so
yeah if you want to see my all-time
favorites just keep on watching see you
guys know for my foundation I always do
see Beauty Blender and it's like my holy
grail tool I really do it truly truly
truly love it but some of you guys don't
so the foundation brush that I use when
I don't use my Beauty Blender is the
m4a3 9 and of course I left mine in
California and cannot find it so you're
gonna have to trust me on this one it is
a good foundation brush I'll put a
picture right here and it is $13.99 this
video is already off to an amazing start
the next purse that I want to talk about
is the RZ r and this is for 2299 this is
the most expensive brush I'll be talking
about today after I do all my foundation
and my concealer and blend it and I will
use this brush and go into my trends
powder to really really lightly like
doses all over the face just to get a
light coverage of powder and just to
kind of lock everything in before I go
in and really like bake it up and I
always use this to blend on my neck as
well because we don't want that line of
demarcation keep feeling sisters the
next brush that I use in my routine
always is the e-40 it is a pointed
powder brush it is $8.99 a this is
actually the first brush that I ever
bought for morphe after my face is all
set you guys know I love all the
coverage in the entire room so I've
always gone with my Mac Studio Fix
foundation powder in the shade and three
I don't know why I'm telling you that
doesn't matter but I always use this
brush just to pack this right under the
eyes and in the center of the forehead
chin and then right under the contour
area as well it's just like the perfect
brush and it really packs the color and
they're in place but doesn't make it too
harsh definitely would recommend this
one the next one I always use my routine
is the r7 and this one is $15.99 this is
my bronzing brush it is so freaking good
it's actually like pretty large for a
bronzing paddle fluffy type brush I love
English this is the perfect brush for
bronzing oh it really does a really good
job with like this person the color on
the cheeks and then I always lend it up
on the temple up to it the forehead the
other cheek and then on the jaw line as
well the only one my all-time favorite
brushes after bronzing my necks that was
always to contour and for that I
actually have two brushes that I always
use I have the m4 35 which is $8.99 in
the M 405 which is $7.99 and I actually
prefer the 405 a little bit better
they are both angled foamy brushes that
are perfect for getting right in the
hollows of the cheeks and right on the
edges at the forehead and carving out
the drawing as well I like this one
because it's a little bit more stiff
than this one it's a little bit less
fluffy so it's more of like a defined
line anyway they work exactly the same
it might as well just save the dollar
and get this one at the M 405 after I
contour my face I say a short prayer and
they brace myself because my next step
is contouring my nose you guys know that
contract my nose has been a long time
learning process for me it is something
that I have struggled with for a long
time because my nose is so early it
never looks good it still honestly could
look a whole lot better but the one
brush that literally save life in my
nose contra is the JT weighty a 182
brush with Luxy that is a mouthful but
this brush
literally was that from the hem
above this brush was gifted to me an
asset at generation Beauty so I never
actually bought it so I just went online
to luck see beauty com2 look at the
brushes and I lied this is the most
expensive brush in this video it is $24
but trust me when I say oh my god it is
so worth it I always use the angle tie
to kind of sketch out what I want the
nose contour to be and then this side is
perfect for blending it out and making
sure that looks like really really
snatched but not to like dry coin me
although we love that look - I don't
have a cold luck see and I know $24 may
seem like a lot of money to spend on
such a small brush but trust me this is
so worth it I'm not even kidding this
literally saved away from my nose
contour and is probably one of my
all-time favorite brushes as stupid and
cheesy as that sounds I seriously would
not look decent without it well my face
is faking my next step is always to do
my eyebrows if you've been following me
for a long time now you know that my
brows have gone through a drastic change
since the beginning my Instagram page
and it was definitely for the better
when I first started off my eyebrows
were huge I would pack on the Anasazi
Beverly Hills different in the shade i
bonita they were so freaking dark and
thick when I did do that silent brow I
would always use an angled brush like
this
this is the r44 and it is only 399 it
has a spoolie on one end and an angled
brush on the other end but recently I've
been loving using front pencils just to
go for the more light and fluffy look
that is why it now has pink look a
lipstick on this and because I don't use
this anymore but if you still like that
style of instar brow look definitely
recommend it this one to check out
once eyebrows are all signed plates
they're probably looking crazy messy so
I like to go in and clean them up using
my favorite concealer and a flat top
concealer brush does the e43 and it is
$4.99 this is the only concealer brush I
ever use and it is super easy to just go
right in and carve out a super straight
and on fleek brow that is all I have to
say about this brush it is just really
good once I concealer under my brows
it's all pointed out I like to go into
the more concealer on the eyelid to then
set my eyes in place to prime for
eyeshadow to do this I always use my e45
and my shape tape and then coating or
some powder I use the same brush
actually for the powder and liquid and
this brush is $5.99 it is just a short
domed powder brush and it says on the
website it is a mini detail contour
brush obviously it's a brush you can do
whatever the hell you want with it it's
never that serious but I really like
this for packing the eyelid
it gets all the concealer bended out
really really quickly and easily impacts
everything in place so I know that my
eyeshadow
not gonna go any winner with the face
all complete and be for the heavens we
are not ready for a shadow trust me when
I say you need this brush in your life
this is the m4 for one and it is $5.99
it says on the website that it is a pro
firm blending crease but there is
nothing firm about this brush it is
literally the best like big fluffy
crease brush ever and I'm not kidding I
think I have at least 1 2 3 4 5
I literally have six of them that are
just in front of me and this is just
from filling my looks today all many
other brushes are in the other room it
is always the first person I pick up
when I do I shadow I just use my
transition shade and I go all over the
crease the I'm four for one is
definitely need in your collection I
would definitely recommend ordering like
at least two or three them you will use
all of them I promise the next one I
want to talk about is the m4 33 and this
is probably my number one if you're a
brush from morphe this brush is $5.99
and is a fluffy crease brush and it is
basically the same thing as the Sigma
e25 in the Mac 217 I was like the holy
grail crease brush is that literally
every makeup whoever has at least like
50 of it is perfect for hitting right
into that crease area it is condensed to
the point where you distribute this
shadow where you want it but it's still
flopping so it blends and out while
you're putting it there six seven yeah
seven brushes right here once again one
of the ones that I have so many of but
literally use every single one of them
the next part I want to talk about today
is the m56 too and this is another one
of those that I have several of you know
when you're doing this multi eye or a
half cut crease and you want to deepen
out the darker corner and like you don't
have a darker shade so you know you have
to use black but you know if you go in
with a fluffy brush in the black it's
gonna make everything muddy and gross
and way too dark this is the brush you
need in your life it's really really
tiny but still fluffy so you can get
right into the crease and outer corner
and blend everything out really really
seamlessly I freaking love this brush
the next part I want to talk about is
the m22 four and this one is $2.99 I
always will go in with some fix+ or some
setting spray spritz this brush and then
dip into like a metallic shadow or a
pigment and then pack it right onto
either cut the crease or just do a
metallic eyelid it is super duper dense
so it is absolutely perfect for getting
the shadow on there and making sure it
is all there and SuperDuper pigmented
once the eye shadow is done on the top I
always want the bottom and I always
started the m56 to the same brush I just
talked about always get like even color
on there and then the brush I always use
the m2
13 this brush is $1.99 na just a small
detailed smudger brush it is perfect if
you have like anything in the water line
that you want to blend down or if you
just want to deep it up right up close
to the lash line or do any do to work in
general really this is perfect I also
use this brush for a smoky winged liner
back to that ways pop on lashes and
mascara and that's just using tweezers
and mascara not that deep nope artist
involved and the last step will be
highlighter my first live here for
highlighting my cheeks is the amma 501
and this one is $7.99 personally I am
NOT a fan of fan brushes but I'm right
for highlighting my face that was not
funny I feel like it doesn't
blend out the pigment evenly and a lot
of times on this end I would like a
straight line of highlighter which is
never ever the goal so I really like
this one instead it just gives like a
nice fluffy dispersed heavenly glow the
last and final brush in this favorite
series thank God is the m43 one this
brush is $4.99 and it is a tiny pencil
brush most pencil brushes are round at
the end but this one is a little bit
tapered off and it does have a slight
point so I always use the very tip of
this brush to go right in on the tip of
my nose and then I'll just go one line
right down the bridge to contour out my
nose then with the same brush and more
highlighter I'll just go right on my
inner corners just blending that out and
then I'll pop this on the brow bone as
well just for that even highlighter all
over and there we go guys that completes
this favorites of rush series thank God
oh damn it if you guys enjoyed this
video please don't forget to come to big
thumbs up down below ever if you have
not already I post videos every singly I
would love to have you join the
sisterhood if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup journey you can follow my
instagram and twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes type stuff is James
Charles and extra s after Charles
alright guys thank you so much for
watching I'll see you in the next video
bye
[Music]