what better person to try to follow a
beauty gurus makeup tutorial then sister
yeah doing very moist
feel like I did so we're all slow down
sister kind of dig the three I sister oh
my god we have to get you in some good
and fries also thank you so much to best
meet the sponsor I got today's video
which one would you like are you feeling
a gray vibe are you feeling a flashback
marry Bobby Flay your sisters are you
feeling oh you are loved and warm sISTAR
oh no no no no that is now how we take
shirts off with makeup on welcome to my
world
we also prepare of our sisters my fans
Wow you completed your sister
cancellation how do you feel beautiful
basically tell you're gonna be a walking
billboard just like me every day in my
life
at least I have a pretty pocket for us
not gonna lie so now that we're all
glammed up and all dressed up and ready
to go we're not gonna eat this party
because we are getting legit but we are
gonna do because we do have to get
fueled up somehow
can you take a guys
so how's it feel to be in town town la
ticker cutoff where the official full
feet glam makeup on
not really used to this but you know did
you think I was gonna say you think you
look beautiful and pretty on the whole
attitude there to own that you have to
own the confident
already getting sterilized welcome to a
world welcome to our humble abode
big drinks please light ice what ten
take a drink of these please no why
George a for 10% off ten things really
[Music]
nails yes it's funny you should ask that
because you're gonna find out real soon
we have an equipment about 12 minutes
he'll be served with me today is with
Jeffrey he's I heard no talk in the
entire world and also does the best
nails and downtown oh I thank God and
you re getting a full set of her college
today
wonderful can't believe hear that scream
even complaining about that what else am
I gonna do hey hi sisters James Charles
here welcome back to my nails thank you
do full set acrylic that was a very
natural like light pink - I was late
tail hello sisters I do not talk like
that en okay so now the girls are all
done today we have our next thing to do
and that is a photo shoot do you know
how to yeah I don't think should be
there what are you doing getting a
Scooby why I don't ride a nasty piece
bujji sisters or not we're on a budget
sisters who are trying to buy a house
sisters and indeed it budget for Piketty
drink it is the stars honestly pretty
much job like I usually try to answer
this you know for like to FaceTime
people well I've also been playing this
really fun game recently to what that
event so addicted to it's called best
fiends what are you doing that it's
literally so much fun here look I'll
show you
best means is a free adventure puzzle
game where you call out to cue fiends
and match the same colored objects to
defeat the slob just like that yeah we
definitely did not love this you sure
slugs I literally did not sound like
that yen there was a brand new update in
right now because it is finally spring
season there's a huge Easter egg hunt
going on on the app if you get all 12
eggs you'll get some super special
prizes sisters we have a special clue
from me to you if you want one of the
special eggs wait for some loot to drop
out of the sky you guys can download
best bees for free at using our link in
the description box down below we
download the game you can get five dogs
with a golden diamonds for free thank
you so much the best fiends to
sponsoring today's a brand new video we
literally just be five rounds on the way
here thank God for LA traffic leave us a
comment down below and tell me what you
guys are on but I think we've arrived
and the time for Ian to become a model
welcome back my management all I should
know
my sister Steve Charles here and we'll
go back to my photo shoot for our latest
photo show I have a present for everyone
[Music]
what did I sign up for you're selling at
their face I need you to slice with your
eyes excuse me do not give me this
attitude anymore you're not moving
give me more less than that that's too
much clench your jaw you huff spit in
the front of your mouth very unfriend
I should know if I look beautiful
fashion shoot I've created a monster
okay whoa what was bad you need to like
feel it now oh you have to save the
sisters I want you to buy this video
right now
you have Matt says oh I'm feeling it
Wow I just bought three huh do you oh
there's the four Oh too much
oh I just returned one that was Bob face
sister nail killers down to eight I
think how do you feel up to that photo
shoot it was very interesting
do you feel beautiful and glam no really
yeah do you think being a model is easy
no I don't even know what shamash
English it's not talking like that I've
had enough of this already literally
just like I feel like you did a pretty
sure oh oh it's just her new couch no
under seven no prettier first time
modeling I feel like you honestly did a
pretty good job we definitely have to
work on your poses a lot I'm over dish
gonna be done now
no this day has barely even begun you're
not even close to being done but I will
tell you next you have something very
very exciting plans watch - Tichenor oh
well if you're a true sister not only do
I love makeup but I also love music so
James I'm tone-deaf mmm well too bad I
booked you a voice lesson in 30 minutes
Shu Shu Qing's not with that attitude
you can't thank you sister so much for
all your help I don't think that is a
great question but I do have another way
that we can pass the time a lot better
if you know me you know that happen
exactly have the best luck when it comes
to relationships but I'm pretty well
known on the interim game for being the
first commentator of the century
so now you have to do that oh my god
first I think we need to go comment on
my two boyfriends page' is already being
the Dolan twin and so let's go to
Ethan's page first how about this one
what do you think will be a good cop
ssin for this one I love that yeah
uh-huh
why not this one okay I love that let's
go to my other boyfriend Grayson's page
now what could you about this one some
of you would say yeah so write her a
emoji and I'm like maybe like the three
water than the French fry emoji how
about this one what do you think you can
say for that whoa how about that's not
what I did grace is how we make up daddy
perfect I loved odd I think our last one
should really be on Shawn Mendes because
he's also my husband I was that kangaroo
Oh what were you gonna say you're
already on it you're having fun with
this don't even lie to my voice lesson
all right we are ready for a scaler to
do you know to scale Museum not sure
this is the easy part of the day all you
have to do is go how about just oh I
think he only nests by like one football
yeah
[Music]
I'm scared up there sister Ian to try a
song you think yeah sweet home how it's
done first I think you should okay
[Music]
beautiful
and I tried
[Music]
you
now I gotta find my own
beautiful now I just made a fool myself
we do something more up my alley please
can't take what everybody feels like
right now
[Music]
okay sister nothing your voice is
officially died how do you feel - I
think you did pretty great honestly yeah
during that my last nail came off so
finally down to zero oh my god I was
your face bi hard to make up overall I
didn't have lashes on I won't even like
know that I had makeup on so it's not
that bad change direction
no absolutely not
we sisters do not eat anywhere except
for our apartment we're post-meeting it
because we're socially awkward
[Music]
she's getting ridiculous
I would love to say James I'm not doing
anything else to do roads sometimes we
have to do a lot of different events
[Music]
oh my god that was one of the craziest
days of my entire life