hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I am actually so beyond
excited because like I always say we're
doing something different that I've
never done before but I've actually
wanted to this video for a very very
long time
and it is finally happening so in case
you happen to miss that which at this
point I don't even know how you would
have I mean literally like hello that's
me lifting up the rock that you've been
living under I've heard leasing a
full-on collection with more be
including a 39 shade artistry palette
for $39 and a 33 piece brush set and
custom Tubby and blending sponge as well
and has doodle heads up all your paper i
Russia's retailing for 149 dollars and
all that is launching in just a few days
now on November 13th at 8 a.m. Pacific
time on more feet calm and in all ultra
retail locations on November 16th it is
literally going to break makeup history
the model for this collection as I'm
sure you guys can see me right literally
I'm building at this point is unleash
your inner artist and I firmly did both
the palette and picked all the brushes
for the brush set to be for my working
artists out there to literally be able
to create any look possible and one of
my missions in the beauty community I
obviously kind of skyrocketed very very
quickly but I always love to shout out
smaller artists and to get inspiration
from them because I feel like small
artists the ones to keep this industry
going and I know from me they've been a
major source of inspiration for my more
creative looks if you've been following
on Instagram which if you're not you
need to go follow right now I'm doing
the sisterhood we were almost 10 million
sisters showing on Instagram as well
it's pretty good and fresh handle it you
would know that on Sundays sometimes I
do it sister takeovers where I basically
have a smaller artist come on and take
over my Instagram story for the day and
give a live tutorial and create a really
bomb and beautiful makeup look and I've
truly found so many amazing accounts
that I love getting inspiration from and
not to toot my own horn as well but
we've definitely been able to help my
few small artists gain upwards of 50,000
followers and only one day which has
been it so incredibly amazing here in
the makeup community it has been a known
fact that reviews aren't always exactly
the most genuine now I'm very confident
that you guys are going to love the
palette but in honor of my sister's
Sunday takeovers
on this launching and in honor of the
fact that I have not slept in about
three months now I hand chose four
artists that I love that I look up to
that have inspired me that I think have
really really amazing messages here in
the make up community and I asked them
to come here to California to film in
this studio so before the pilot actually
launches you sisters at home get to see
a few different artists all that have
different skin tones testing ethanol out
for the first time in using different
products different techniques different
colors and hopefully all creating
beautiful looks so you guys are able to
make a more educated decision on if you
want to buy it or not
every one that I pick today is so
incredibly talented and they all have a
very special place in my heart - I think
you guys are going to absolutely love
them so you better be sister supportive
and without further ado I'm going to
stop rambling you're welcome for once in
my life I'm going to chill out take a
little bit of a break and celebrate this
launch and I'm gonna let all four of
these people take the center stage and
let them all unleash their inner arms
[Music]
hi everyone so my name is Zachary and I
created this look with the new James
Charles palette that he collaborated
with morphe on I'm super super excited
to be able to show you guys how to
create this really colorful and vibrant
look so if you want to see how to do it
then please stay tuned so to start off
the eyes I'm gonna use the morphe 22 to
begin the blending process okay so I'm
gonna begin by applying the shade skip
right into the beginning of my crease
keeping it a lot closer to the nose
bridge you guys this palette is so
pigmented I just dipped into the first
shade and mind you this is the first
time that your girl is dipping into this
and let me tell you this pigment sister
James did not come to lady was alright
sisters so I went ahead and primed my
eyes with the Paint Pot from Mac in the
shade painterly just before I began
blending so I could really make these
eyeshadows hop and perform so now I'm
gonna pick up this m4 for one brush
which you can also find in the
collection that James is releasing with
this palette I'm gonna go ahead and pick
up the shade playground and place that
right in the center of my crease and
fade it out with the edges alright so on
the m4a1 brush I'm gonna go ahead and
pick up the color socialblade girl want
to check mine right now but I'm gonna go
ahead and pop out on the outer corner
and marry that in too so a little bit on
how I got into makeup actually the
Instagram brow friend the faded look in
the front started taking over and my
girlfriend who worked at Mac at the time
was like hey if you're interested in
doing makeup I have a brow product that
I think you would love to try but I went
ahead and I went over and she did one of
my brows and I was like wow like I love
this and then she gave me the pencil and
she was like okay I did one and
go ahead and do the other one and so she
kind of like give me a little lesson
that's really what inspired me to kind
of begin you know doing makeup and then
from brows came lips came Foundation and
then after that girl it was like a black
hole and now I just can't get enough of
makeup I'm gonna love it it's changed my
life
alright so now I'm gonna go ahead and
pick up an M 506 brush James has got us
covered in all departments this brush is
perfect for us
Asian girls who have tiny eyes or
anybody got tiny eyes I kind of suffer
put a little bit of a hood so there's
gonna be perfect for tucking that shadow
deep into your socket and making it look
sickening and sketch so taking the M 506
I'm gonna dip into the shade I love that
and I'm gonna deepen up the pink blue
and the green and we're gonna just carry
it along and create a nice little window
shape so go ahead and tuck this shade
love that right above your mobile lid so
you can create some power and intensity
so that when you cut your crease
it's nice and vibrant oh honey so I'm
gonna go ahead and repeat the same
process I'm gonna dip into the shade of
Cola I'm gonna deepen up the dilution in
the center so when I tell you that the
kids are not ready for this pigment
we're gonna dip into the darkest green
color which is called daddy we're gonna
dip into the shade daddy and we're gonna
go ahead and open up the green on the
edges
all right girls I'm gonna go ahead and
cut my crease now and hopefully that I'm
still this shade of tan when I come back
because holding your breath girl now go
ahead and do it off camera I'm gonna go
ahead and have some liner and it'll be
right back to finish up the lower lash
all right sister so I went ahead and cut
my crease with the M 124 and now I'm
placing the shade pinky be drinking tea
on my lid and the cut so I can go ahead
and set it and prep my provider and all
the others dish that we're about to add
so much super cool about this collection
of brushes that James is releasing with
this palette is that he includes doubles
of each brush so say I just cut my
crease with this brush right here which
is the M 124 I would want to go in and
set with the same one because it's the
tiniest perfect little eyeshadow brush
so I'm picking up the shaping can you
drinking it when I go ahead and do that
so say if it only had one in here I
would have to go back in and clean my
brush just to do the same thing over
again so it's really cool and I really
appreciate that coming from
our distant point that there is another
Russian here of the exact same one so
that you can go ahead and use it in the
same look we're gonna make a little
switch to the brush and I'm gonna pick
up this morphe m or eight brush a little
bit more dense so we can pack on more
color boom we're back you guys so I went
ahead and winged my liner off-camera as
well as look like some flashes and a bit
of bling and now we're gonna go ahead
and move on to a smokey on our under
eyes in order to do so I'm going to take
my favorite little more feet at 5:06 so
I'm gonna dip into the color playground
I'm gonna go ahead and smoke that out
lightly to just kind of determine this
shape kind of just sketch out where I
want the color to be it was really easy
for me especially to blow it out a
little too far so with this brush
precision is really easy which I really
like like I said I have really small
eyes so this is perfect for getting them
right under there and making it look
super nice and so the color looks good
I'm pretty happy with it it's just a
light wash of color I'm just to
determine where I want to really make it
intense so I'm gonna go ahead and pick
up this brush right here which is the m2
10 and I'm gonna pack on a lot of color
to make it really intense and pop hey
guys I wanted to talk a little bit about
my experiences as an influencer I mean
I'm pretty new in the game but I have
had so many crazy opportunities just
like this one that I'm doing right now
actually this video is gonna be featured
on James's channel it's really really
really inspired for me because I'm Asian
American and there isn't really very
much representation for us Asians in the
community and I'm actually from Laos but
there isn't really much representation
for Laos or asian-americans really at
all I think it's really cool that James
is giving me this opportunity and
morpheus giving me this opportunity to
kind of showcase my hardest street and
really like I don't know take it to the
next level I never would have thought in
a million years that like I would be
here today like filming a video with
Games's palette and you know even James
having a palette I mean he's paved the
way for the boys and makeup and it's
really cool and honestly like I can't
say it enough
inspiring it yeah I'm really really
grateful and I'm really happy to be here
so I just wanted to tell you guys I
didn't give James a thank you all right
so I'm not gonna go ahead and take my
morphe e36 it's a tiny little pencil
brush and I'm going to dip into the
shade of Cola it's a dark blue and I'm
gonna go ahead and intensify and then
I'm also gonna hop back into the m50 six
and defect into playground I'm really
happy with how this looks
and so now what I'm gonna do is I'm
gonna add a little bit of bling on my
lower lash line I love adding stone as
you guys can see like I put a little
stone on my eyebrow and I'm gonna go
ahead and add a couple more and then
we're gonna go ahead and add Center
corner highlight as well so I go ahead I
have a little bit of blue on here I'm
gonna go ahead and place right in the
center my people you just an extra pop
to your luck I think I'm gonna add one
more just right below that as well to
kind of give like a little tear effect
but I love it it's kind of signature to
me I guess I'm bling to my face so we're
gonna go ahead and add some inner corner
highlight now to add some light to our
inner corner so I'm gonna dip into the
shade hello which is a shimmery blue
we're gonna go ahead into some of our
more feet setting spray and just missed
it a couple times so that we can get
like a super shimmery effect we're gonna
go ahead you guys see that oh my god so
pretty I'm gonna go ahead and pop this
neon pink liner into my lower lash line
to really set off so I'm gonna take this
more feet M 518 brush it's a brow brush
but I'm gonna use it for my lower lashes
and I'm gonna take the shape of skip and
set the pink cream that we just put in
the waterline with be shadow alright you
guys so this is pretty much the finished
look I mean it's a really colorful
rainbow cut crease I'm gonna go ahead
and I'm
gara into the other eye off of camera
and I help you oh hey girls so this is
the final look I really hope you guys
like what I did I did find like a
watercolor I don't know kind of fun and
glitzy and glamorous with a little bit
of bling I absolutely love the palette
it's extremely blendable super creamy
and ultra pigmented I came up you guys
to get your hands on it honestly it's
probably one of the best murphy palettes
that you used the other palettes are
showgirl they're shaking in their booth
okay girl so don't forget to follow me
on all my social media it's at zachary
bangs the sdk is that really Kay and
yeah thank you so much for joining me I
hope you enjoyed this little tutorial
and we will see you very soon bye hey
guys it's Jake
that's raging on Instagram and I just
recreated the look I use for James's
campaign shoot so if you want to see how
I did this keep on watching so I'm gonna
be priming using the Mac soft ochre
Paint Pot using an M 2 to 4 brush just
to prime my eyes so how I met James was
a lot of people don't know this unless
you do but I was his first-ever fan page
so that's like where we met pretty much
and then he just inspired me to make my
own makeup page and I never really
thought that I would like be where it is
today
he helped me grow faster he this is
hoping a lot of ways giving me a lot of
like opportunities I never thought I
would get and I just wanna thank him for
that
James has inspired me to do a lot of how
the ordinary looks
that's probably why I've grown a little
faster it's because the looks I've done
aren't like a lot of like everyday looks
it's always something that is
eye-catching I think it was something
different that no one has seen so I'm
gonna be studying the Mac over Paint Pot
with a powder just so
and so I don't get any but yeah I was
saying I was James's first fan page
which is kind of embarrassing now but
honestly to me not really because it got
me where I am today I'll always support
them still and it's just amazing how you
can go from being something so little to
something so big like I'm from a small
town and I never thought I'd be working
with something so big and being friends
with someone and such a big spotlight
and it's just amazing that that can
happen I'm gonna be using a morphia amp
or for one so I'm gonna be dipping into
the sky blue sheet and I'm just gonna op
that like I'm right in the crease and
then just start to blend that out to
deepen that out I'm going to be using
the morphe M or three three and I'm
gonna be dipping into the slightly
darker blue just to add some depth in
the crease I'm gonna go back in with
that morphe m4 4-1 and blend out that
deeper color to deepen that even more
I'm going with the darker blue and I'm
just gonna do I'm gonna be cutting the
crease using the Mac soft ochre Paint
Pot again and a morphe two to four I'm
gonna be applying this light blue
shimmery shade onto the Aoi all over
there I'm gonna go back in with the
first shade we used which was that
lighter blue that like sky-blue now I'm
just gonna put it right in here to start
to blend that a line
go ahead and just use the access shadow
from that first shade we use just and I
just for a little bit of debt I'm gonna
go in with a little bit of block using
the morphe and four five six now to
start off the bottom lower lash line I'm
gonna use pretty much the same steps we
used for the top going from the lightest
blue to the darkest blue I'm gonna grab
that transition shade again that blue
and I'm gonna grab more and four three
three going with the next shade which is
a little darker than the fair shade a
little closer to the lash line and then
going in with the darker blue shade
we're gonna mix it with the black and
then plane right on the lower lash line
just having it right in there to finish
this I like I'm gonna grab me the morphe
color pencil and shake coconut and I'm
just going to pop that in the waterline
so that is what I all complete and now
I'm gonna go finish the other one off
camera and then we're gonna come back
and do the neck piece we're back that's
full theis complete I just thrown some
lashes to complete guys but now we're
gonna highlight the inner corner and it
just completes the look honestly so now
we're gonna do my out so I can start on
the neck piece for the neck piece you're
gonna need some bigger brushes and some
smaller brushes just so we can lay down
the first shade and then using the
smaller brushes to add more depth and
dimension when adding the clouds I'm
just gonna dip into pretty much the same
thing as we did on the eyes just like
adding the color onto the neck and just
laying it on there oh and I'm using the
morphe and 405 so once we have that
first color on I'm gonna dip into this
lighter darker blue and just like
throwing it on
anywhere right now you just want some
darker spots and then we're gonna add
more darker spots and right after we're
gonna apply the white - oh and the brush
I'm using to apply this color is the e43
to further deepen out those areas I'm
gonna take a morphe and by 10 and then
I'm gonna dip into it through blue just
a little bit of the black going back and
forth between those colors I'm just
gonna be using a little bit more of that
sky blue shadow and just popping it
right where we had it the middle so now
I'm just gonna be adding that pigna I
used on the inner corner all over the
neck just so it gives some really pretty
effect I'm going to be taking the morphe
m5 town dipping into that people so now
we're going to be adding the clouds on
the neck and I'm just gonna be dipping
into this white shade in the Jamestown
and will be packing on in a cloud shade
this white is probably the most
pigmented why I've ever used it's so
good and so pigmented and just to
brighten out my highlight I'm gonna be
taking a highlighter from morphe this is
an extra and I'm gonna so this is
complete I'm just gonna set my face with
some preference
[Music]
we're done and this looks amazing thanks
to the James pallet this took a while
but it's done it looks good the pigment
is so good so blues for me are very hard
to blend just in my opinion and this
blended like a dream like look at that I
don't know if you can see that but I can
see that
and it's so blended and the shadows just
performed so good the white was
phenomenal
like this palette you need and the blue
shades are just so good in like do you
see that ask for the brush get this look
I had to use so many different brushes
and that can't had it all so genius
different sizes and trios duo's of like
the same brush just genius and I'm
pretty sure you can create any look with
this kit and this palette and that's it
guys I hope you guys enjoyed this little
tutorial you can find Milius here i'm at
so that's why Jake YouTube app smash by
Jake and that's probably it for right
now I need to like extend my social
media but that's like where you didn't
made me find me on and I hope you guys
have a great day
hey guys my name is camera Lester and
today I am creating this look with a
James palette which is honestly it's so
fun and I'm like sistership by this you
guys are just going to get to hear a
little bit of my story and a little bit
of my background as you know a boy in
color and makeup and as me growing into
makeup and how I got into makeup and all
that so if you guys want to learn how to
get this eye look make sure you guys
continue to watch I am honestly so
excited and so nervous to be even like
on dream's Channel today we are doing an
eye look and we're playing with James
Anu I don't know if you can see it but
the more three times James Charles
palette I'm just so honored to even be
doing this and so grateful so thank you
James he actually reached out to me last
minute
and create this on kind of nervous and
I'm kind of like I don't know what to do
but today I think I'm gonna use some red
on my eyelid and just you know wing it
and try to figure it out as I go but I
know I'm gonna use red and then I'm
gonna tell you guys about my story if
you guys want to hear about more of me
make sure you guys watch this let's get
started so today I'm gonna be priming my
eyelids actually because I heard that
the eyeshadows actually worked really
well with the eyelid primer usually I
use concealer like James so this is kind
of different for me but you know hey
let's give it a shine they're trying you
know I'm using the m22 for morphe brush
to like you know basically just a base
on my eyelid you always use a lighter
color so that a shadow can just show up
more cuz it also is a little bit harder
for darker skin tones to like shadows to
show up but we're about to see how this
works I always use the lighter so look
it just like the vibrant as it can so I
have my eyelid primed and now I'm just
gonna go straight into this color this
palette is actually so cool because it's
so like big I don't know if this is like
huge like look like bigger than my face
so I'm gonna go straight into the red
with you're kidding with another morphe
brush from James's collection to M 4-3-3
brush and I'm just gonna start putting
this on my eyelid
hopefully the best but this is like a
true red and I chose the color red it's
kind of hard for me like to talk you
know Lynn but I chose the color red on
my just for this look is because I'm
actually HIV positive so when I I just
felt like you know just was spitting to
that because you know with like red
products and all that kind of stuff and
just like you know HIV so I just wanted
to do is red and then I wanted to do
the Ellis casino to tie into this I have
my whole story on actually on YouTube
that's my story about like this why I
chose red and the reason I got into
makeup was because makeup was kind of
like my calm or like the storm that was
going around me and like there was just
so much just like going on in my life so
at the time I just like picked up makeup
and just like started going in with it
and having fun with it you can just give
me something to do and like just really
grounded me and it just turned into me
just a wee makeup all the time and now I
do like Instagram videos and all that
kind of stuff and then just nightmare
which is kind of amazing
and I'm just gonna bring this out a
little bit dramatic because the name of
this palette is unleash your inner
artist and I couldn't want to just do
something dramatic and kind of you know
not to be so simple playing game today
so I'm gonna kind of drag it out so if
it looks crazy right now just trust the
process and it will come all together
I'm gonna take I believe it's called
Mary I'm gonna blend that into the top
so Kim like you see I'll just like blend
in with that eye and to give it a little
bit more of like depth I'm going to use
deke I'm going to just kind of like go
like right here on my it's like my
eyelid bone and just kind of like give
it some dimension in our depth there's
something like this so it's gonna be a
little bit darker okay so now that we
have the base kind of finished I think
I'm going to take now like a shimmer red
so I'm gonna do this shade shook and I
think I'm gonna use my finger and pack
that right on to the lid as I feel like
that look really pretty
alright so I'm gonna go to the shade
acapella I'm just gonna it's much of
blue and
4:31 brush blending and dragging it all
off and it's kind of like turning into a
purple but I like how dramatic this blue
is like right under the eye now I'm
gonna put something a little bit lighter
in the inner corner just to bring a
little bit more light to the eye and not
look so dark and you know just bring a
little life to you there's a lot of like
good highlighting shades in here too I
think this one is face I think I'm going
to take the m12 four brush by one and
take the shape face I'm going to bring
it in I kind of feel like I'm looking
like Harley Quinn right now but you know
cool and I'm gonna take this same face
and I'm gonna so now I'm just going to
use a blue liner and kind of lipstick
bring like brightness to the line so
more few more areas core Parker this is
my eye shadow look what I came up with
on the last minute on the spot I'm gonna
do the other eye
off-camera and put lashes on and finish
this lip are you guys
[Music]
I'm finally done I put lashes on I
finished the face the formula is amazing
the blending is on point I can't wait to
use more colors and kind of just like
create more looks no I definitely wanted
to do red because they just meant a lot
to me
I moved to LA at 20 and I just had a
dream to like start but YouTube career
and I got here and I got diagnosed with
HIV and when in September of last year I
think
yeah September of last year everything
just stopped like everything really just
stopped in my life like I lost my car I
was also homeless for a while and
everything felt like it was like against
me and I felt like there was no winning
fortunately you can stay with some
friends and stuck it out and now I'm
here today and it's just been such like
a blessing and I just want to thank
James - sorry but it's such a blessing
to just be here and have this
opportunity because it's also very hard
to be melon color and you know do this
every day and you know just push through
because we already have so many things
against you I just want to really say
thank you for this opportunity I just
don't even know
to wrap this up is honestly unreal the
palette is unreal if you guys want to
care more about me or know more about me
follow me on instagram at camp
underscore leicester on instagram and
then my youtube channel is Cameron
Leicester just my name thank you guys
for watching
hey guys my name is rocío seja and today
I will be showing you guys how to get
this really fierce
rainbow eye look you think something
really really special really really
awesome really really really cool the
morphe exchange Charles our districts
palettes I will be showing you look and
I hope thank you guys I really really
like it so I'm gonna get started and
what I'm gonna do first is I'm gonna
take a piece of tape because I really
want like a really nice precise look so
we're gonna add the tape the outer
portion of the eye like this and then
leave like a little gap right there so
that you can go back and add your
shadows right here and then we're gonna
zoom in closer on the eyes so that you
guys can really get a feel of the
shadows so I'm going to pick up max
Paint Pot and this is what we're gonna
use to prime our eyes and I'm picking up
this morphe M 224 flat brush and this is
what I'm gonna use to pack on the primer
I'm taking the m45 6 brush and I'm gonna
dip into the color escape which is a
very deep purple and I'm gonna pick up a
little bit and then tap the excess off
and then I'm gonna start from right here
just a little bit and do you see how
pigmented this shadow is and you only
need it like a little bit and it's
already so so pigmented like I just
dipped it once and that was it I'm gonna
go in with another brush this is a am 41
brush it's just a flip of your brush and
I just like to take this and I like to
blend the purple up now with the same
morphe and a four or five six brush I'm
gonna take a playground which is a
lighter blue and I'm gonna add it
right here so I'm creating like a
rainbow but I'm doing it backwards and
don't worry if it doesn't look blended
yet I just like to focus the shadow
right here first and then we go back and
blend everything out words you can
already see I only did my brush in one
time and it was already so so pigmented
now I'm gonna go back in the width and
for for one brush and just blend the
blue up with no additional product so
why I like color a lot I was always
really sad so when I started doing
makeup color really helped me become
more happy and when I do a colorful look
I just I'm just so happy i am taking the
morphe m45 six brush and i'm using
social blade and i'm putting this right
here next to the blue and then i'm
blending it upwards towards my brow now
what's really cool about the James and
morphe brush collection is that you're
not getting only one of each brush
you're getting multiples so in the first
collection you are getting I believe
it's three of the m45 six brushes and as
someone who does rainbow looks who does
multiple colors on one eye I need
multiple brushes so this collection
really does come in handy for an artist
like myself so again I'm taking the
morphe and four-five-six brush this is a
really good brush as you guys can tell
I've been using it throughout the whole
entire video and I'm gonna dip into the
yellow it's called B as you guys can
tell I also struggle with acne and just
being open and vulnerable about that I
get a lot of people that tell me that
that has helped them for James to ask me
to do this on his like platform makes me
happy because it's a message that's very
important to be inclusive to all skin
types and all skin tones so I'm very
happy and acne is normal and skin
positivity is something that we should
always push through I know I'm not the
only one that struggles with acne and if
you are someone that struggles with acne
no you're not you're beautiful and I
hope that in some sort of way I hope you
so I'm just gonna go back in a little
bit with socialblade in between you want
to go back in with the colors just so
they can blend together I don't feel
like I necessarily have to do that just
because they're blending if you guys can
see they're blending all together very
perfectly so I don't even really have to
go back and blend good so I'm gonna go
into some oranges and I'm going to mix
two I'm gonna make spy 1/8 and arrest it
rusted is more of like a deeper orange
but I want to mix them because I just
want them to create like a darker orange
if that makes sense now I'm using the
same morphe m45 six brush and this color
I'm gonna put it on that outer portion
of my eye just a little bit so I'm going
to go ahead and anchor my crease I'm
gonna give myself like I have cookies
you guys can use whatever concealer you
want I'm just gonna take my own and do
that so I just cut my crease and I
stopped right here and I'm going to add
the red I'm going to take this morphe
m56 tooth brush and I'm gonna dip in
just a little bit and I'm going to pack
it on right here in the outer portion of
the eye and the artistry palette I was
really happy that he included a white
and a black because I use a lot of white
shadow I like using white in my inner
corner I feel like it makes everything
pop but today I'm going to use that not
only in my inner corner it fits on my
lid so I'm taking this M 224 flat brush
and so I loaded my brush and I'm gonna
Pat in this white right here so I'm
going to take a little bit of pink which
is called skip and this morphe e36 brush
it's very tiny and I'm going to add this
pink right here and that's just because
I wanted to use the pink in this palette
it's really really pretty and as you
guys can see it's super super pigmented
and I'm just gonna add it right here by
the red and then
blend it with the red just a little bit
I'm gonna go ahead and remove the tape
you should get like a really nice clean
cut like that so I'm gonna take the
morphe and 3-2-1 brush and I'm gonna
take skip which is the pink and I'm
gonna add it right here on the waterline
so I'm going to take you're kidding on
the morphe e36 brush and just blend this
down here just a little bit I don't want
a lot so one of my signature lips that's
my inner corner store and I buy these
and Michael's you can get them at any
arts and crafts stores but I get my own
scent Michael I'd like to take some
tweezers and I will pop it right in my
inner corner like this this is James
palliate has a white which makes me
really happy I'm gonna use that white
and put it in my inner corner so I like
to use like a really bulky brush when it
comes to like my inner corner star I am
using the morphe 173 brush this is also
in James's brush collection so I like to
do this thing where I tap in and press
down on the inner corner store I like to
press down the shadow so I'm taking some
tweezers and then I like to remove it
you should get a stamp like that in your
inner corner so this is the completed
look I'm gonna go ahead and add some
mascara some lashes and then finish this
eye and I will be right back
[Music]
alright guys so this is the completed
look I did want to touch a little bit on
the palate and my thoughts on it so I
mean right away it's really pigmented I
work with color so I know what like I
know what I like and I know what I want
from a palette and this is definitely a
palette that I would use over and over
again the purple was really good
Purple's are not my favorite and this
purple was actually really solid and it
blended really really well the blues and
the greens were really really nice
greens I always have like an issue it
just because I feel like sometimes some
greens from some brands are like too
dark this one gives me like almost like
a very green lime neon kind of feel so I
really like that and then yellows are
really really important you can tell if
the palette is good if it has like a
really great bright yellow so I really
like the yellow in this palette oranges
are always like formulated really really
nice so I really like the orange and
then the Reds and the Pink's they're
just so good they're so pigmented and
just overall I really like the palette
thank you guys so much for watching if
you guys want to check me out you guys
can find me at or Co say I have with the
underscore altogether I'm both on my
Twitter my youtube channel and on
Instagram thank you guys so much for
watching and I'll see you guys next time
bye guys hi sisters I am back oh my god
you guys all four of those looks we're
literally so beyond insane
we have sisters Zachary sister Rocio we
have Jake and also cam they literally
all killed it so so so much I cannot
thank all for these artists enough for
coming all the way here and filming
today and this truly means so much me
that they got to test out the palette
first I definitely was so excited to see
all their opinions and feedback when it
comes to a real
artists using this and I think they've
all absolutely killed it I'm gonna leave
all those social media links down below
so you guys better be a sister
supportive I think that they're also
incredibly talented and that this
community is seriously built on the
smaller artists that are working so hard
every single day to make it to the top
so please be supportive please Phil show
them the love and tell them the sister
James ascent you all that being said you
guys if you liked today's video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below I would love to do more
videos like this in the future and bring
on more smaller artists of the channel
so let me know if you liked it leave me
a comment down below let me know which
of the artists look was your all-time
favorite I am so excited to see it your
guys's feedback on the palette if you
have not already don't forget to click
that big red subscribe button down below
as well come join the sisterhood we were
almost 10 million sisters strong and
also flick that little bell icon so you
can get a notification every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me and I make up journey you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both the same Charles and my
staff have to work behind the scenes and
stuff I am Charles with an extra s after
Charles don't forget that my sister
collection with more beeping my palette
and my brush set
launched on November 13th only a few
days from now at 8 a.m. Pacific Standard
Time on d'amore p.m. it is going to sell
out so fast little better be ready it
set your alarm tell your mom's your
dad's your sisters your brothers and
also if you miss it the first time it'll
be available at all Ultra retail
locations starting November 16 this
video sisters how that goes to sister
Sophia thank you so much love for always
following and supporting I love you so
much
and if you like to be in the next videos
sister shadow don't forget to always
reach me my video links letting go live
on Twitter if you like my cute little
sisters cropped hoodie moment you can
chop this and the entire other question
that sisters - two parallel calm and
don't forget as well that the entire
artistry collection of all the rainbow
pieces including the fan is launched on
November 15th the right sisters thank
you so much for watching this videos
today thank you so much again to all for
these amazing and talented artists I'll
[Music]
[Applause]
unleash your inner artist