hi sisters jean-charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel as you guys
can see today I'm done with some very
brilliant sisters special guests the
kitty girls yay so do you guys from
birth few months ago we actually got
together for our first video where we
did my best friend's expose me and that
was kind of like the sisters first time
ever actually meeting like the og
sisters like we've been best friends for
a very very long time I've known
everyone here except for drew for almost
more it's like almost four years now
yeah whoa that's so crazy all of us
starting a group chat together called at
the kitty girls and we literally talk
all day long every single day and we're
pretty what's together at least like
three to four times a week to open the
Kathy actually live with me and tours
here almost every night so it's pretty
much a family fiesta it's honestly a
good first time I think one of my
favorite videos that I've ever filmed on
this channel was a collab with pretty
much the entire vlog squad and we played
a game called a make up relay race
ironically the same exact game it would
dis been great because we've been
friends for such a long time now we've
been through so much together our
friendship has been tested and I feel
like we've always come out on top
stronger than ever
but we've never been tested as makeup
artists and that that's what my youtube
channel is all about so for today's
video we're going to be playing makeup
relay race everybody excited yeah in
case you guys into the first make up
relay race video basically how it works
is just like a normal relay race we have
our numbers 1 through 6 here and the
iconic wall power from last video which
by the way if you've not yet seen it
click right up here and go check it out
and everybody's going to pick a number
out of the Hat and then that is going to
be the order that all the Kitty girls
will have 5 minutes to do whatever part
of my makeup routine that they want the
whole point is that you're only as
strong as your weakest link
we do have makeup artists and the screw
so this could
okay I'm on the ride let's talk about
that my booking fee is low let's talk
about this for a second because I do
feel like the playfield it's like very
even like when it was the bomb squad
nobody knew anything about makeup but we
there's some advantages we have going on
here like Cassie oh yeah I'm a little
bit of aiming I'm dinosaur I've been
doing for ten years now
wow this is a passion Elias who've been
working in for like five years
yeah but then Lauren Viktor in their
hands well Victor we've done two videos
together so you know what went on I know
I know what's going on I just don't know
how to do it without further ado so we
figure out yes nobody nobody open the
other side open it so everyone can now
look at them oh god I'm so scared
alright you guys so it is official we
have our order one Oh order one two
three four five and finally six let's
see if my best friends that kitty girls
can all work together to put a beautiful
makeup look on this face right here
[Music]
all right artists number one wait stand
up oh that's good that's a good no I
think tract look I have high hopes for
you we've done two videos together on my
channel before do you feel confident at
all yeah I'm going number one so true
can't be too bad all right Vic you're
gonna have five minutes on the clock are
you ready yeah three two one go
you can like walk us through a process a
little bit two years well I need to like
prep the face oh wait moisturize you
sure but I don't know what moisturizer
it looks like okay I have to ask you a
question during this process okay
what are you using you don't know
they're for almost four years now for
you yeah and we've done two videos
together so how would you say like me as
a youtuber but like also me as like a
friend has changed over the past several
years you as a person or just a
consolation child I mean I feel like we
always start off with a good start so
that was always good that has never
changed but besides that I feel like you
mostly help me be a better person
really oh yes yeah you've taught me just
how to act more around people if I never
had to deal with the whole being in
public I yeah
so you definitely have taught me how to
be like that
which I'm you can ask a lot of my
friends I've never been the most
sociable person yeah so I definitely
have grown in that way foundation yes
great start with you later okay oh can I
say in one way that I think our
relationship has changed a lot yes I
feel like one thing that I really love
is that you've almost taken on like
almost like a fatherly role with me
along sided with Elden too obviously
sure especially when it comes to like
relationship stuff yeah dealt with a lot
of problems with it even like you'll
talk to me outside of the crew time big
nodine's I don't leave
that idea I think you should look at
this play or do it this way like this
isn't smart you're gonna get yourself
hurt I'm like I really respect that
because I really value your opinion as
someone who's older but also like I feel
like it's a really good husband in the
relationship I agree
I believe I've gotten really close to
you where I treat you like I would
protect Laura I protect you as well yeah
off to a pretty good start okay yeah
actually I'm a lot more proud of Wow
good job okay thank you
sento be tuned ready for kid you girl
number two
oh c'mon number two hopefully you
moisturize first foundation I think okay
the top five minutes on the clock
I have a few questions lined up to ask
you three two one go okay concealer even
ready to Cassie first six years now I
feel like you have to yeah but I don't
do her makeup she just does her own
thing so this is what a lot of people
may not know is that we actually work
together every day and live together -
were just kind of month Alden was
actually working as an aerospace a
machinist yeah beforehand so very smart
organized engineering type of person
like going from like aerospace machinery
to beauty guru full-time employees very
very different I would assume right
basically before I was like talking
clock out yeah coming to work at like
6:00 in the morning and then leaving
like at 3:00 yeah so like you climbing
yeah running out of time we're gonna
bake now so now our schedules like very
sporadic and we travel a lot there's
like so much different things going on
compared to like what I did before
before is like pretty routine yeah and
like this is like so different I want to
ask what would you say is the best part
of working together what would you say
is the worst part of working together
and you
be honest this is a good question for me
as they as human resources department
the best part is all the traveling and
everything yeah the I would say the
worst part is probably well a lot of
times Cassie gets to come with us too
but it's hard because we have to French
bulldogs that we have to leave behind
and sometimes Cassie isn't able to go
yeah which I would love like for all of
us to go well the whole group would be
awesome job
oh I want the worst part of not being
able to be there
well actually the worst part is we
usually have the same food every week
like repeated yeah so like week after
week it's like the same thing because
you have like your favorite meals and
everything I look at California Pizza
Kitchen barbeque chicken the way we go
around that is when you're out we get to
order whatever we want
we are always having a good time look
good increase I just ate by flowing so
there might like I think all right fine
that's all the talk I'm gonna ask you a
few questions about our friendship - I
don't want to answer those ones ready
three two one go okay okay this bronzer
brush I absolutely did learn which brush
is the bronzer brush because I like to
use
we're gonna bronze the face a little bit
today you know I don't ever do face
makeup on my clans I just did the I am
leave okay
yeah but I'm not good at the face like
I'm only good at with the eye okay you
could do I should do the eye we do a
little more up here your foreheads
looking big today mom being together
almost every single day what is your
favorite thing that we do together I
feel like honestly like we we like
brainstorming our jobs dot that is only
favorite things we do together
yeah those we both do you kind of the
same thing like I having YouTube channel
too but different from yours
yeah but James helps me with with mine
and I helped him with his because we
don't like we're not competitive at all
yeah there's like no over there's no
overlap but yeah yeah I truly feel like
some of my favorite most productive days
or when you and I to sit down together
and like just brainstorm ideas and just
like bounce ideas back and forth yeah
agreed
yeah okay I mean I just going with my
finger okay oh wow brave I know I'm a
makeup artist okay
as a fashion blogger true how do you
feel about my fashion I think it's good
I think it's definitely developed like
in a good way
yeah like I think when I first met you
it was very like just like Instagram boy
like like Instagram girl or whatever but
now it's definitely come more
high-fashion but I still wanna see you
like wear more color for sure for sure
like cuz you would still like very
Street and like wears a lot of black
which is fine like that's what you
personally like but I think if you want
to be more fashion which is introducing
a little more color
I know Oh IRA me my rates are really
affordable um reach dr. James's email or
mine do not retouch on my email and oh
wait bye I was gonna give you a nice hug
bye best friend fine please send in the
next yeah
miss Laura's boutique yes period to get
started ago three two one time
all right I'm gonna ask you some
questions about our friendship it's up
to so Laura we've known each other for
probably almost four years now and when
I first moved to LA I have told sorry
before about how I live did you and your
entire family and I'm forever grateful
for everything you guys did for me we're
not gonna get emotional because I have a
funny question to ask you no don't
after the last four years and us living
together or like traveling there all
together going to events together what
is one thing about either me or like my
job that you'll never get used to you
would like the meeting great so you have
those were like crazy you guys it's like
it's crazy see minimal like online and
stuff but like when you were actually in
there like you can actually feel like
the room like rumbling and like energy
the energy it's crazy like Australia
well typically Oh see you can't do that
Mall of America like it's crazy
I remember them all I'm Erica me Cassie
were like crying cuz really dude like
this is our friend like he's be here for
him also I think you walking around
naked all the times in as little undies
with Laura sorry you reading is that
possible I can't
you and Victor are the only ones out of
the friend group that have a child thank
God yeah Elliot and you obviously know
that I don't want kids afraid I'm
obviously still very young
do you think that I'd be a good parent
or a terrible parent if I want to change
my mind you know honestly I thought you
would be a bad book 1 but yesterday yes
you know Sunday that we were here I
think you took Elliot to play the piano
upstairs and I thought that was pretty
cute I think that'd be cute of you to
like absolutely I don't know you I
thought I was cute but I don't think you
would have one I think people would she
let you borrow what why don't you think
I'd be a good parent
oh I just don't think your patient like
you want everything like there oh I
don't mess you up though so yeah we're
actually pretty good if we're looking
okay so far
well now we're on to Cassidy and
hey-zeus - psychic or smooth sailing
[Applause]
[Music]
okay kitty girl number five didn't I
just do the glitter I have a feeling
today - well I feel like you would need
this being lost to us of hi Keith pretty
good flossing
cuz you measured the week before this if
anybody can fix that it's you - so
you're gonna have five minutes to do
whatever you want to pull this look
together
oh and I'm saving great moment yeah okay
we're gonna privates on the clock you're
gonna be able to do whatever steps you
want
from you I don't ask you a few questions
about our friendship and life too so it
sounds good
ready yes three two one go
okay what do you think first I'm going
to get rose and you already know I don't
do a quick route we're just gonna dig
into a little bit of plumbing and okay
just going right in yeah okay Cassie the
first thing that I want to ask you when
I was with health and I talked about how
are you and him kind of live with me at
this point literally my favorite thing
that ever happened to me just constant
fun and craziness at the house what has
been your favorite thing that's happened
with us living together so far and the
worst thing that you've seen like none
of it I like that I'll have to see you
the best part honestly is because I live
an hour but in LA always over two hours
with traffic oh wait yeah so like we're
always together anyway and it's just so
just pretty much live here at that point
because tape all the time and gas yeah
and we're such a big family here that it
is just so enjoyable to be together
every single day yeah but I would say
the worst part is literally it literally
comes in every single morning and wakes
my ass up Cassie I Cassie Cassie I come
in every single afternoon acting and
wait you are at roughly between 12:00
and 3:00 p.m. if you guys don't know I'm
nocturnal so I stay up till literally
sunrise and I sleep during the day but
miss Jamie Charlie over here like a good
old sunrise awakening so sometimes
they'll come in and like cuddle in bed
and then sometime Cassie
rise and shine
so that is our routine over here you're
never gonna break your routine if you
and your let you sleep until 4:00 p.m.
once you're going to absolutely do if we
don't wake you up - so cast a lot of my
followers have started to follow you
because you upload a lot of vlogs on
your channel a lot of times obviously
we're always traveling together so it
happens to be like vlogs
behind-the-scenes footage yes our meet
grace are different events would stop
what's one thing that people might not
know that goes on behind the scenes of
the vlogs
honestly I feel like we're very open and
pretty honest with you guys like we put
all of us out there but I would save it
we're not exactly always PG and so is
YouTube monetization I think we cut a
lot of like our playful vulgar names out
a lot of kids onto my videos of a lot of
kids watch my videos with their parents
I do try to always make sure my channel
is appropriate for everybody
we're definitely much crazier if that's
even possible behind the scenes yeah I
mean you definitely see more crazy stuff
on my channel then you're just very
inside inside look a little better but I
do get a little carried away talking
sometimes okay all right ready for you
sister hey Zeus we're gonna have five
minutes to do whatever you want to fix
that
over three two one go okay Oh get ready
you know I have a good question for you
to start off with huh out of the entire
friend group you were the one that I
knew first we started talking first I
want to know because you would have like
a hundred thousand our Instagram when I
first wasn't thinking I had zero you
know I remember sliding into your dance
first I think yeah like why did you
reply cuz honestly you I feel like you
were literally so town until they give
it from the beginning which was a good
deer looked at you had like done like a
long time ago see like it's hard for me
to find friends yeah another boy that's
like the community or whatever yeah
that's like trying to be my friend which
was like pretty cool so what has been
your favorite memory that we've had
together probably your graduation really
yeah this is like a specific memory but
one thing that I'm oh okay I'm finishing
one thing that I've always loved that
you did before I had this house when I
was still living downtown but every we
would hang out so she had Laura stops -
it always shy of me home yeah and we
almost died
so many times over here is a first-timer
oh no I'm not he's easier the worst is
your scary living in the first man no no
anyway Laura lifted Whittier when you
suppose in Orange County so what here's
like here or Chinese like here but
you're like I'm like way up here at
Laura's house would always trying the
all the way down to downtown a minute
all the way back home just I won't have
to like uber young
it's like we just good music and tell
you a little bit whenever we about to
get in a car crash yeah all six of you
mean literally the absolute most to me I
have terraced our friendship for a very
very long time now but I'm not sure it's
oh well you're about to see it you guys
all work together but separately doing
different parts my makeup routine at
five minute intervals each and it is
time for you guys to see the finished
look because it's not about the finished
product company three two one
Oh everyday makeup look Jane the eyes
look the best as I did though that ain't
good to make I'll rock you guys well I
guess that is obviously a cup a relay
race all complete with all my best
friends in the entire world I literally
love all these people so so so freakin
much maybe the offsuit most to me and I
truly would not be here for them if you
guys for this episode of makeup relay
race featuring the kitty girls don't
forget to give this video a big thumbs
up down below and also leave us a
comment do you like to finish look whose
makeup job and do you like the best
let us know if you're not ready as well
make sure you hit that big red button
down below and come right this is Sarah
I'm gonna kill both of you I click that
Bell icon so you can open every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me on our makeup journey can
tambien Instagram and Twitter they're
both so strange always tell Jeff more
behind the scenes of the Savior showers
that I dress after Charles I'm gonna
everyone's power plugs on them right now
if you guys wanna go check
no one follow you probably show that
excuse me what you guys I know who this
video is sisters how much should go
everybody
this is sisters not it goes to Kitty
girls family what my favorite she makes
the laugh mmm yeah yeah I love that she
supports both me and all my friends as
well it means so so so much and she just
alluded the sweetest so go check around
and circle and thank you for always
falling in supporting if you don't the
next videos sister shout-out rate your
videos link alive on Twitter or quite a
really bomb fan page with really fun
edits well also if you like all the
hoodies that we're all wearing make sure
you check out sisters apparel calm we're
officially live up back in business
thank you guys so much thank you by the
love and support on the summer
collection that launched a few days ago
I think motherhood this videos up and
the pride collection is going back up
very many students that make sure you
guys check that on it will give you all
the updates and all these other cute
hoodies have them available or Arsenal
available make sure you check it out all
right you guys thank you so much
watching this video today we all love
you so much and we will see you in the
next one
[Applause]
[Music]