hi James Charles here and welcome back
to my youtube channel as you guys can
see today I'm joined with several
separate special guys
as you guys heard I'm joined with this
way boys and today we're doing a minger
relay race now this is one of my
favorite series to film on my channel
because it always gets absolutely insane
basically all of these iconic we're
gonna pick an order and then every
single boy is gonna have five minutes
alone with me to do whatever they want
to do whatever they want to my makeup
routine
just to clarify basically it's a test to
see how well these boys can work
together to make me look good in the end
I want to know how do you guys think
you're all gonna do we got bling yeah we
took art you took art yeah we talked
about it before this and we both know
the draw trees
how does drawing a tree have anything to
do with this maybe even a tree yeah a
tree look at realtor are you down for
the tree look trees already bass we have
to pick out the order for this relay
race and nocturne definitely a fact
whether or not this is gonna be a good
finished product so pick wisely we have
a unreleased scissors the peril item
coming very soon Oh selector number wait
okay you say it in order one two three
four five six that's just going yeah
well that was so close to being an
actual order I have a bunch of questions
that I want to talk to all these meds
about it's gonna be a very interesting
next hour or so you guys will have to
wait and see what the finished product
looks like we will see if the sway boys
can work together and this makeup
[Music]
all right contestant number one hey rice
all here you are starting this look off
today yeah are you excited for that I
know there's foundation sure in primer
and that's like what I have to focus
okay that's good okay I have a lot that
I want to talk to you about today but
we're only gonna have five minutes to
discuss so the timer is right here on my
phone ready to go ready your time starts
now
go am i just using my hands did you wash
your hands yes I wash my I just wanted
to really make sure I put it all on
there oh sure okay so I don't even know
if people know we go so far back without
even fighting yeah like you wreck the
was it really 2017 yes even earlier than
that
you were literally one of my first
friends in social media Bryce and I met
from you know the long time ago we were
friends with somebody else we don't need
to discuss yeah and then when we finally
got to LA like we all got to hang out
for the first time and it was like I
don't know how she's like one of the
boys yeah I mean I came out here and
hung out with you before I even moved
isn't your YouTube video most somewhere
online is my channel it's like that era
of time would like the you know kids was
so they get this feels like it was like
a million years ago but it's so crazy
that like you've been able to navigate
through social media for so long you're
gonna speak and obviously we did go
through a time paper we weren't as close
friends either because I feel like you
were very much in like your party
animals stage yes still am and I know
you were also sober recently as well
yeah I am so still yeah that's all I
drink on July 4th
okay that was because of the whole like
pulling over a situation but how has it
been going are you enjoying it like no
no I love being sober I can see why you
did it for so long time we were like you
were just like getting in fights every
day and really so crazy
and always like involved so much drama
and I think now that's still very much
you but like it's a more mature version
if I appreciate that for sure well
there's only a minute left
how did you get involved this way house
in the first place we have like a
company yeah runs it and we're also
brothers like we're all like you guys do
all get along like a very very
very well it really does like a family
buy one you were all together which is
cool there's like a new rebrand of sway
like a lot of the members had to leave
because everyone had like different
goals and stuff right the new sway the
new rebrand everyone's like focused on
YouTube we're go ahead you know what
ticked off being banned soon don't say
that I don't want it to go well what
happened if I did get banned maybe a
youtuber whoa famous just in time sure
thank you bro love you though no problem
bro it also says no I'm proud of you
thank you for always being an amazing
friend thank you for inspiring me to
high-five let's see a little bit oh yeah
what do you think I feel like you caked
it too much okay maybe a little I'm
gonna have to fix it okay you can do it
every day that's the beauty of the make
a really race we have a lot to talk
about
we've known each other for a very long
time but we only are gonna have five
minutes to discuss and for you to either
fix what's happened so far and hopefully
continue as well I start with concealer
okay I will tell you that's not
concealer this isn't gonna tell me what
concealer which one this one
I thought those mascara what I heard you
go yes that's okay okay go alright so
I'm gonna start with the little T okay
wow you are makeup guru I know
okay so Blake we have known each other
for like almost probably four or five
years which is insane to think I think
we met at playlist I think so too I was
I don't know okay so I met Blake when
you were big on musically yeah and
you're like with our yeah yeah yeah that
was like when it was like Ariana take up
Sartori I think Lauren like you were
part of like that Oh Jo G group user
squad like with those little crowns on
basically yeah okay well there was a
time for you to wear like you were on
musically and then tick tock started and
you like weren't really doing it much
yeah it's like now randomly you like
puffed up time swag yeah
I think it was really cool how did that
like end up happening uh well I kind of
like did a break for a little just yeah
it's like on my mental health I thought
it was good for me good I'm back in the
game it's dope I joined the suede house
yeah be cool powder yeah it's same spot
well everywhere everywhere thank you
what it's like a daily day hence why oh
love that little rhyme we wake up we
work out like 9:30 every single day and
then we film some tic TOCs
okay and then we film you two okay every
single day I think it's looking pretty
good
how high are you are you liking it more
now yeah yeah would you say that you get
along with us in the house I feel like
we are all kind of like a huge family
yeah um you know like I feel like I can
it's not like anybody has like really
like that certain best friend in the
house I'm like we all just are like
that's okay no III honestly think we're
all you know really close which is cool
yeah I think I did good I think I think
Blake I think you're an amazing like yes
Thank You Jan and I appreciate that
thank you for having me
of course all right I'm nervous dude I'm
kind of shaking I don't know if I can
mess up that much worse I feel like
Bryce didn't do a good job sister
Wow is that the equipment I choose from
it's everything laying out here you're
gonna have five minutes on the clock
yeah I'm gonna ask you some questions
okay go I remember the first time that I
met you at this white house you
literally were the most like spaced out
person aisle it was like oh my gosh I'm
days I sweeten you're like I lingered
while I was space I have I literally was
like oh my god he wants like hate me or
something I think now that I've gotten
to know you like you're illiterate like
you're so outgoing and fine oh thank you
so much like I think you're pretty
outgoing fun they know you're from
Canada right yeah why did you move here
I moved here in January moved in with
this way boys yeah
so 17 was that weird for me going from
like being an everyday I'm assuming high
schooler to all the time being yeah
Tommy our high school was like it was
fun and it was cool and everything but
then like once I started doing social
yeah a lot of people started like just
like making like the stereotypical
musically kid jokes yeah you do a series
on YouTube called tea talk we're
basically every week right you go
through I'm so scared of the faces that
you're making go through the week
steaming drama on tick-tock right yeah
come on Linda Oh waiting drama at all
costs oh we don't we're not in drama
this way boy how did you get started
doing that and like why like why do you
like doing that in the first place
um so like I feel like people take drama
too seriously
definitely and like everyone like takes
it to heart and I'm just like why don't
we just joke about it and then like make
fun of it yeah and then I think people
just like take my things seriously so it
doesn't always end up working out but
then a lot of the comments will be like
you guys don't understand sway boys
humor that's just like how they are
they're joking around about it oh oh I
think I finished on time guys okay I
actually don't look that bad interesting
yes thank you for partaking in this
makeup really thank you for having me I
think I think I had the quickest time in
the relay I mean at the same time okay I
had the best for the my time that I will
see you in a little bit with the
finished I feel famous do you I feel
like that they aren't famous because the
the look is a little off by I have a lot
that I want to talk to you about there's
only gonna be five minutes on the clock
and then just look as bad as you're just
saying you're gonna you got a lot to do
ya girlfriend Johnson no Griffin so you
blew up on tik-tok because you were a
nurse yeah and medical school yeah I
want to know how you blew up in the
first place and how you decided to leave
nursing school because I think that's a
crazy decision that's when I first met
you I'll just say it too
okay I said into Griffin's do you have a
feeling about this case so Q is very
very smart but then we actually became
really good friends first off you can
always go back to scores yes I yes so my
idea of this was if I can go back and do
this later I always can like finish it I
I mean school is always pretty easy for
me right like this I feel like this is
an opportunity and
everyone you know gets and I was working
at it I really love that mindset because
at school is it super super important
like I always encourage my followers
they go to school pay attention in class
to your work like it's really really
important but at the same time school is
always there I'm like I'm a firm
believer like taking opportunities
taking risks so you got to a point I was
like okay I have enough of a following
and then I met the boys and we're all
gonna live together so yeah okay this is
worth it when was the first time that
you actually met all of that wasn't when
you came to LA first no it was on tour
last summer he went on tour kind of blew
up like we had like a really good summer
and then I was like okay well I guess I
can come back and like finish or do
whatever I want later if I do well this
next semester doing school yeah
everything works out and then I came
back to LA whenever I came to see you
yeah and that's whenever everything they
took off it wasn't really yeah pretty
much that's when we like this oh my god
not change my life yeah see you it
that's why I always tell you thank you
now shake you know you do you do you
always talk to you the nicest things and
I always appreciate it you're just a
really good sweet friend I love that
you've chosen to use the same exact
brush for all steps of the routine well
you see it was just conveniently there
you know there's lots to choose from
right but it all just kind of blends in
well girlfriend thank you so much love
you bye sisters I'm definitely gonna hit
the eyes all right dude hustler we're
gonna have five minutes on the clock
let's make a relay race ready set go
okay this looks pretty your makeup belt
is so pretty oh thank you so Jaden the
first thing that I want to talk to you
about when you first started on social
media there was photos of you and like
cowboy Hawks you were like a country boy
huh yes sadly okay so I was born in
Texas all right and then when I was 14 I
moved to Tennessee
you know I everyone out there if you
don't conform to what everyone else
wears you're just like weird yeah I
didn't want to be weird to be honest I'm
sorry
right just didn't post scared but now
obviously several years later I really
want to come I do because I think it's
really cool how you're so open about
your style your music and everything and
I definitely enjoy that so speaking of
like a major transformation I think
you're tweeted like how like you buy
like only girls pants
yeah and how like you buy like a lot of
girls clothes yes
to my viewers probably sounds completely
normal because obviously they're
watching me I got a lot of hate doing
the exact things I did now you're gonna
mean like especially in Tennessee I know
it's whenever I first started sicked I
started painting my nails because I
thought it wasn't oh yeah like I was
actually a fan of Chase which is really
funny but I was a fan of Chase and I was
like yo this is so dope maybe I should
try and I did and I liked it yeah and
then I got my ears pierced but everyone
in my school actually almost got
suspended what because I had my eye
nails painted and everyone was just like
hating on me for it is so stupid yeah it
was crazy so I got my ears pierced I was
like ah I got beers beers inside up I
was in the graduation and I was wearing
my capping down the doors were open all
the parents were looking and then my
principal ran up it was like screaming
at me he was like you're not gonna
graduate if you have your ears pierced
eyes literal most ridiculous thing that
I've ever heard
ya know it made me feel really
embarrassed where I'm in now I just love
Who I am now yeah is it I like having
that story better than just being
someone who is like perfect their whole
life that's awesome now I can relate to
people on a different level right so
that's been pretty cool like people it's
good to think about yourself and love
yourself but ultimately it up we're
gonna go over time again I love any
other people it's not worth it yeah and
that's all that matters and I didn't get
that so I actually came out to LA and I
was like you know what everyone should
just do whatever they want like wear
what you want so I wear women's pants
cuz it fits my tiny butt better and I do
whatever I want because that's what
matters I think that's so cool I really
do good I didn't make you look better
haha maybe if I had more time I could
definitely fix it okay thank you so much
good work bro thank you I appreciate it
and thank you for his being herself of
course
hey how are you good how are you
wonderful I'm nervous oh I don't know
what never done this but it looks good
so far actually does it yeah so you're
lost in this makeup relay race no about
I am so you're gonna have to really pull
it all together okay
finalize the love you're gonna have five
minutes on the clock okay to finalize
this look and make me look as beautiful
as possible okay for the final result of
this white house makeover in the race
are you ready let's go we're gonna start
with some mess yeah okay look your hands
look I know so you started on checked
off only a few months ago ha yes and now
you're literally the absolute most
popular person on the alpha everybody is
obsessed with what happened and like how
does that make you feel so I made a
video because my sister actually was
giving me crap because I didn't have as
many followers as her on tick tock and I
even have an account okay that kind of
lit a fire under me and I wanted to like
prove her wrong hmm so I made a couple
videos your head this literally I made a
few videos and like mid-january okay I
made my first one and it kind of blew up
I made a video it did pretty well for
like my first video it's turning out
amazing mother okay a few months later
you've literally become like one of the
biggest growing people on the app every
one is impressive every girl's a chance
the every boys have stuff to do okay
like how how do you go from just being
like a regular college student to that
all of a sudden like being literally the
world's heartthrob I don't answer that
like is it still like surreal to me
honestly it's really cool too because
like everyone I feel like at some point
in social media you know as you're
growing really fast it really easy to
let everything kind of get to your head
and the one thing that I really love
about you and that I feel like a lot of
the fans have noticed as well as like
every paparazzi video every video at the
high post like you're always smiling
you're always taking photos with fans
and Mike I think your smile really does
like rub off on others and I think
that's really cool I mean I just think
of it like if it was me and then she's
like I don't you want like the same
attention but yeah I mean I'm not by any
means calling myself
anything like that but I don't know like
if I were to see like Zac Efron or
something like that walking by I'd be
like that won't fix ER with them you saw
like I think it's just like a nice like
courtesy just yeah well I always say I
get the high I think you're very very
sweet you well know about thank on the
movie model love you the absolute most
thank you for having us you were all
complete and all just time to bring it
the rest of the boys at back-end okay
and reveal the final Jesus all right my
fellow sway boys after a very long day
of beautiful glam and getting to know
all of you a little bit more we have hit
the finish line for this makeup relay
race we're gonna open our eyes and
everybody's gonna see the beautiful look
can I use that term loosely three two
one all of you guys how was this makeup
experience I think I killed it I thought
it was gonna be easy I give you props
because makeup is low-key hard I was so
focused on answering the questions I
kept forgetting to do makeup okay I am
very proud of each and every single one
I think you guys have all brought
something really fun and exciting to my
life please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and show your
love and support it really does help us
out all set leave us a comment let us
know who you guys think did the master
in this makeup is really raised if
you're not ready please make sure to
click that Bryce what do you do
if you're not ready make sure it's like
that big red subscribe button down below
and come join up this sisterhood I would
love to have you guys in the family we
literally just hit 20 million
subscribers so so so much and if you're
not ready as well make sure you click
that Bell icon so you can under fight
every time I upload a brand new do it if
you like to follow me on that makeup
journey all my social media accounts
will be listed right here on the screen
and if you want to text me on my
personal phone number or I'll update on
new videos merged photos and so much
more is three 109.5 eight seven four six
if you guys under check out all this way
boys their social media links will be
tagged right now this video sister Leah
thank you so much love for always
falling in supporting I love you so so
so much and if you'd like to be the next
videos especially don't forget to always
read people we're links they gonna live
on Twitter and also to my YouTube of
post notifications all right you guys
that is all your first today's video
thank you so much for watching I love
you and I will see you in the next one
[Music]