hi sisters and Jacob Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel
it is currently 6:00 in the morning and
you're probably wondering James why do
you keep filling YouTube videos this
early I'm also wondering the same thing
for today's video we were going on a
road trip I wish I never did that oh my
god
today we together are going to be going
on a little bit of a road trip I am so
beyond excited because we're you going
somewhere very very special and for
today's video I'm going to be doing a
full face of makeup using makeup that I
am about to make so I've been evita guru
for about three very very long years at
this point and thanks to you guys I've
actually been able to turn up pinenut
makeup into a full-time job and I still
pinch myself every single day at this
point you guys see me pretty much to
every single makeup look in the book
from classic everyday glam to crazy
rainbow avant-garde realness but even
though my job is to play with these
makeup products and create art with them
on my face I really don't know that much
about what actually goes in to making
makeup so for today's video I thought
it'd be a really really fun and
educational to go behind the scenes and
I partnered with colour-pop cosmetics a
brand that you and I obviously know and
love and we're going to taking a
hour-long road trip over to Oxnard
California literally in the middle of
nowhere but that is where their
laboratory is located luckily after a
whole lotta convincing colour-pop was
kind enough to let me and my entire
camera crew go behind the scenes and
show you guys what actually goes on in
these labs and we're going to be making
a full face of makeup setting the
foundation that anyway lip gloss and
hopefully we'll be able to come up with
a really really beautiful look and the
end and give you guys a little bit more
information on the products that we're
all using every single day we have a
very long car ride and day ahead of us
so I'm going to quickly go hop in the
shower and get ready for the day this
bed head is not cute but I am so beyond
excited for what's to come so without
further ado let's go make some makeup
[Music]
three seconds in I already just stepped
in mud it's off to a rough start ladies
[Music]
we're all so excited she had right in
let's do it afterwards basically we own
like nine buildings like oh this is
gorgeous
hello feed me it seriously obviously I
do makeup every single day as a job but
like I've never really been a part of
like the actual production process for
and like school came pretty easy to me
about science and math or I to like
favorite subjects of all time I actually
really liked chemistry so I'm like
excited today
loke a little bit to like learn more
about it and like see what actually goes
into the products that I use on an
everyday basis yeah all those food
stations they are like so prep they're
ready
how long is called mob-like been around
and manufacturing here so it started
maybe like five six years ago as like a
little idea
so spats lavatories used to like
manufacture for like all the big makeup
brands that you know of and the owners
now draw more
over there decided like why don't we
just launched our own brands like we
know how to make up no they like came up
with the idea of color pop they
literally like used to have their office
in like a closet so it was like this
tiny little room and they would like go
make the makeup and they like pack the
order and then they'd like drive it to
the post office oh my god those muscley
grown from like a tiny little like
closet to this full-on like nine
building facility yeah that's everything
so color pop manufactures everything
right here in California in the US so
just like one of the major selling
points I feel like for a collar pop
makeup having everything in house means
things are faster so if a trend comes
out later that day like the lab will
have samples for us
oh my biggest thing I'm working with any
Brian is I'm very very impatient someone
I want to do that like well let's take
us Stefan's like I want it now so who
does it so fast it'll be right there
yeah like literally we've done overnight
so I feel like one of the other major
selling points of color pop is the
prices are very very low on most of the
products yeah and that's because
everything's in-house right so like we
literally like down to like a little
plastic mold that's right here - yeah
that's so cool well I'm really excited
let's get a quick sister snack and then
head over to the lab
[Music]
so I think we should go in the same
order that I would do my normal routine
then just to keep everything organized
so I could like figure it out inside so
I usually start my own foundation the
foundation is pretty much fixed it looks
like four different pigments that we
have white block and then red and yellow
so it's not easy and Colegrove has one
of the biggest changes no foundation
ever when I cover every single skin from
out there right right when I have like
every single shape or every single
person itself right I feel like home
does a really good job of that and I
think because it's all done in-house -
people always love to say like oh it's
really hard to formulate sort and shade
so when it's all done right here you're
watching the entire process go down so
you get to actually make it happen okay
let's figure out how to mix my shades
together
number one primary color is the white in
the white okay so about how much do you
think I should add just a poor gram for
how much is four grams okay so you're
gonna point out oh oh
that's point four so two for Milli 42
different shades bonus the face and then
from there which is create alright so
like how like what goes into actually
differentiating every single shade it's
just literally just mixing the other
different pigments and hoping for the
best
discard a bit too much okay today I
usually can't match on carnations anyway
so nothing will be different okay so one
more round
heavier than others see pop this one
senator discusses bigger one
oh yeah it's crazy because the littlest
little drop will actually nod to it
Killick may be point zero - that's good
it's just the eye shadow once you add
too much Barker going back like that oh
my gosh that one drop will change the
entire color - science is crazy
well then that looks like skin tone oh
my gosh that's me
maybe according to my foundation at home
can I not skin tone no will I make it
work yes it's only for pigment for all
the Browns who say oh we didn't formally
any dark shades it's too hard you heard
it right here folks take fine then it's
make it hop in it's not so hard to be
inclusive this is so squirt it in there
that was literally so easy let's do it
so our concealers already pre-mixed I'm
just gonna be killing it and my little
vial today it kind of odd
I guess not this show is really really
easy but what is like the difference in
formulation when it comes to concealer
because the form a little bit different
really different yeah completely deaf we
add more pigments the load of the
pigments is higher can we have more
coverage in the mother what is this hole
that's a wiper wiper it's just we shove
it on there there you go a good dough
fight well man that's so easy yeah yeah
hello I picked an egg bagel before the
first two steps of a retainer literally
all complete full coverage moment this
is probably a better match than the
foundation will be let's be real pale
and sad but good so what we do we have
our base formula which consists of
pretty much like cushion powders mmm and
then we have our fighters and we have
our pigment and then we have our liquid
so different from foundation a lot alike
the bronzers blushes and highlighters
are a powder base correct as opposed to
like a liquid right so then that's when
the pressing comes in because Limpopo
powders are mixed together then you
press and get into a pan yeah okay cool
so that's what we're doing today okay
we're gonna do afternoon delight okay
that's a great color for me so then
there's similar to the foundation
there's like a different way that goes
into each thing yeah so pretty much what
you want to do with
your spatula you're gonna spread it out
evenly over like the chunks out yeah try
to keep the palak look your bike they're
not really clear montage it's like would
that be good for crossing yes that's
good okay fun we just let me slide it
right in here
we lost a little bit of powder we can
actually fix that a little bit with the
psi so what this does this compresses
the powders right so since we lost a
little bit we can actually press it
lower so I looked a little bit fuller oh
that's good god I've never forgotten so
do you want to do this yeah okay so just
crank this down right here
like that well of the club popper
blizzard Paul proof you need that when
you're working with me oh my god nothing
little yay this is so this is a brother
no it's normally a most thing I didn't
drop of it onto the floor and then it's
Bluffs pretty much the same thing -
let's do it just once again mixing all
the pigments together yeah so like okay
so for example for me I usually like
more like peachy orange II types of
gloss for my skin tones that would just
be adding more yellow paper yeah yellow
and then an eyeshadow well right because
you don't want to put on the blush and
have it literally take over your entire
face so if it's less pigment than what
would be the other ingredients that are
in there so powders that are in your
base it contains a lot more of less than
your pigment when we have a lot of
liquids in it
sometimes you have to decrease because
then we have talked about it with techno
keep it in there this time and this
one's a little bit okay I'm definitely
just gonna happen it's a little bit
harder around a thousand a thousand five
hundred and fifteen hundred like there
you know everything you know for example
the bronzer and the blush you like how
it's fluffy
yeah a week said I kept requesting it oh
so heartless yeah cuz I know you see how
it looks a little bit it's a little you
have okay so for the next time I would
have pressed it a lot harder with about
higher psi to make sure it's more in the
pan yes sister you press it again so
we're not gonna press it they got okay
lesson learned so for next time I would
press this a little bit harder to make
sure it's in the pan one okay that's
cool so different formulas definitely
require a different amount of attention
so speaking of pilot or now that we're
done with faith products let's get our
glow so now we're moving needs lighter
so women II have some pieces fed okay
we're gonna do which is gonna put it
you're gonna put it under this pressure
you're gonna prep and see how this
already into really nice and low
put her into one of these so that we
really have eliminates are you just
gonna pretend to do this magnet and
we're just gonna make sure there is
first of all that is really fun and this
is how we make every single one of our
highlighters out there in production but
so what goes into like the making of a
highlighter for you as opposed to a
normal shop it's on there somewhere when
it's giving you this long is this say
depends on the size of the throw that
you want to use there's one like a
really high glitter effect right we're
gonna be looking for a larger a lot
bigger in a defense of the under color
of the pie night as well okay cool
one of the common issues that I feel are
highlighters is that when you put on a
highlighter and it doesn't really match
your skin tone sometimes the faith
you'll see like that gray calcium or if
it's like a letter 1 euro be darker
that's when the base is not right for
the skin tone and I'm not in the baby
all in the colors it's all a little rule
it's all whatever the pigment that you
use seen said it's making you look wait
okay yeah and that's one of the things
that we have to work on there right yeah
well we take it for a ballet show with
PD they're like oh it looks kind of grey
on my skin right so we have to get rid
of the photo about tweaking the cause
and every painter new for me make sure
that it works on all skin tone it
doesn't get by a great car yeah probably
you're ready yeah
into the walk literally already this is
so pretty Hello oh I'm just gonna put
down there the pressure okay
I'm just gonna just press all the way
down we thought she already has been
ordered on a job yeah so you're gonna
remove so I'll push it out push it up so
already has glue on it okay because the
magnet will do that for you oh my god
that's so cool can I just rub it over oh
who is way stronger than I expected
it is slide it to the side hey you go
and I was on there yep oh my gosh
try watching a good sister SWAT let's
see oh my god
hello that's the prettiest other that's
one of our number one yeah I could see
yeah look at it to the collection things
perfect oh my gosh okay okay let's move
on to the next step so for all the plans
we made so far today of course we're
doing the classic color pop fertilize
that we all know and love and that I
love so many times but we didn't want to
do at least one thing custom not a
half-bad so I'm gonna be making a custom
gloss today hopefully we're gonna be
that it looks good but I wanted to make
like a kind of like pinky peachy light
new shade like a go-to everyday new it's
pretty much the same thing here what are
you I want like a peachy pink for like
leading school we more towards pink and
peachy so therefore there should be more
red you're gonna add more red then
yellow I want less yellow right maybe
not that much like that cuz we're gonna
find out is there reasoning behind
putting the block in there what does it
do it's not gonna be too bright okay so
like how to mute the down a lot on that
like that much I think that's like
you're not that so like literally one
like extra little crumb of bonding your
entire color is wrong it makes a huge
impact oh I would be messing up
lipsticks left and right here so we have
my powders all mixed together mo now we
need to add at the liquid base that
makes it a glob so good enough to wet
the pigments
I just grind it together yeah you just
okay kinda fun kind of down oh that's a
good actual color we're just gonna be
like adding your pigments in here don't
put your hand in there
ya don't want to lose anything so I'm
just gonna pour it right over top of
here oh my god this is what I always see
in those Instagram videos oh my god I so
excited wait what is this work just for
you to get and then we pass it three
times ready yes this is literally those
Instagram paint mixing videos I watched
those four hours okay now you're gonna
mix it so once you pass it through three
times it gets like that guys it's my lip
gloss so now that suppose right under
here yeah I love these syringes kind of
I'm not gonna lie this is just the
plastic colourpop lip - oh my god there
it is that's a lip color oh my god
that's my gloss hello that's so cool I
just made this you all just watch that
happen comforter on yeah that's
everything I like the best
well I'm probably really good at that's
probably it should do this as a job
maybe perhaps okay yep let's do it
alright so we literally just finished
baking almost my entire maker routine in
one hour we to sit I have a rethink all
right here in-house custom made this is
so incredibly cool but we do have one
product left remaining and that is going
to be of course the eyebrows the eyebrow
pencils are actually many parts in a
different building on the same facility
so we're gonna head it right over there
right now so we can get my brows on
fleek what is that
dear down down gotta keep everything
sister sanitary
[Music]
okay we do the same repetitive
uh-huh oh please please get the dog yes
[Applause]
just press this one and this one
together and then the bread
I bet this is fully realized okay nobody
okay so obviously this is my first time
doing that but you're like it I start up
the brows how many do produce and like
an hour and hour
a day and all of the other hand yes that
is so cool
well I'll be taking one my videos that I
thought I'm doing brother this but I
it's so cool oh good around the assembly
line now all right sisters that is our
lab day aw complete we literally just
made every single product of our makeup
routine and only a few hours that was so
crazy and so cool to see everything here
in person obviously I'll put a link up
every single day we're getting to
actually see how hands-on it is I think
everybody involved from the start to the
end is such a cool amazing process
definitely has my wheels turning I'm
feeling very very inspired right now but
that is of course for the future for
right now I'm gonna take off my lab coat
oh and my hair and we're gonna head home
and actually do my makeup now using all
the makeup that's I made all these
sisters we are back for the lab and I
have here my little bag of DIY makeup
products that I made today I am so
beyond excited to actually put them on I
had so much fun learning and seeing the
behind the scenes process literally
everything was so cool so let's put on
the makeup and a talk about everything
started sorry makeup today I of course
like to go to my foundation first always
so I'm gonna grab the color pop no
filter foundation in the shade me
okay I'm gonna pray that this color is
like a somewhat decent match
[Music]
fedil too much yellow I literally had an
entire team of professionals who do this
every single day to help me with this
and I still managed to make my shade
wrong my disappointed yes surprised
absolutely not probably my favorite part
of the entire day today was actually the
foundation process just because I
defined chemistry to be very very
interesting and thing that actually goes
into like foundation is really really
cool over the past three years I've
tried probably hundreds of foundations
at this point but I've only really found
a few that actually really really worked
for me and my skin which is so crazy
because pretty much every major brand at
this White House the foundation line out
or is working on one and it seems like
always just foundation but you guys saw
the imagining out the ingredients today
and literally one wrong
drop of either pigmentation or color or
liquid or ingredient and the entire
batch would be completely wrong and
could actually ruin the entire
formulation so it's actually so cool to
see what goes into the first step of the
makeup process in order to even out all
of our skin tones although there are so
many ingredients and processes that go
into making complexion products probably
my favorite part of the entire day today
we'll see how easy it was to actually
mix together different pigments to make
different shades one of the biggest
problems in the makeup community whether
you want to admit it or not is racism
and unfortunately that is not a topic
that I am a stranger to but all that was
a nightmare at the time my old tweets
being brought back up and me being held
accountable for them oxy was probably
one of the best things that ever
happened to me it's truly changed the
person that I am today for the better
and it's made me realized that I have a
platform of a lot of people watching me
and of course they want to use that
platform for good and I want to educate
on behalf of issues that are really
really important and shade range is
definitely one of those topics I feel
like they're vetted quite a lot of
foundation line launches within the past
few years with shave ranges that can
only be described as like just really
really embarrassing and one of the
excuses that big brands always seem to
get when it comes to the issue is oh my
god it's so much harder to formulate the
darker shades because we don't want to
get the undertones wrong and as a
consumer as someone who has never really
been involved with the making of that
process I am definitely ashamed to say
that I've kind of fallen for that but
after seeing it behind the scenes there
is literally no excuse there's four
pigments add some more black add some
more red add some more yellow make it
work you saw here today folks it's
apparently
hard to be inclusive and I'm gonna let
you in on a little bit of a sister
secret and of course I don't speak for
anybody here but people of color would
probably be really excited to see their
shade range represented and it's a web
win situation for a business when you're
actually selling products I just thought
I'd put that out there all right sorry a
rant over faces all on I just said it in
place and now let's move on to it
chiseling this out getting nice and it's
not I'm just gonna grab Miami 405 brush
and dip into the custom bronzer shade
that I made so for the bronzer and blush
I actually found the whole egg pressing
process to be really really cool clearly
I struggled a little bit with getting
everything together and not spilling it
on the floor but you know what
is my first time accidents do happen I
was actually so surprised because I did
not realize that these processes were
all done by hand I really really thought
we were gonna be walking into the lab
and there's gonna be like 80 million
conveyor belts and machines all pressing
and packing and mixing things together
but almost every single one of the
products that I was part of the process
but today are actually all handmade in
the factory every single day by
hard-working employees I think that is
so cool so next time moving onto my
brows I made the shade at brunette today
and I'm just going to fill in my brows
like normal mmm that is a good brow tee
I also really really love the process of
making the eyebrow pencils too and let
me tell you why obviously it was a whole
lot different than all the chemistry and
ingredients and formulations that were
going on in the other love but when I
was a young kid I used to be obsessed
with the mechanics and figuring out how
things worked my dad was a self-employed
contractor when I was growing up and one
of the reasons he was super popular in
my town for jobs was that because he was
actually able to do so many of the jobs
involved everything from the design work
to the actual construction and building
to the plug into the electricity like he
truly was a jack-of-all-trades which is
definitely inspired my work ethic today
I always loved going to job with him
because of the fact that I got to sit
there and figure out how things were
made and how things worked
I love mechanics and pulleys and levers
I was obsessed with cords I don't know
how I never got electrocuted I had a
very very strange obsession with vacuum
cleaners don't ask because I literally
have no idea but I
found that realm very very interesting
so seeing the machines and the
mechanisms that actually put the brow
pencils together was so cool for me not
even gonna lie even though there was
machine involved once again though
almost all completely done by hand no
robots real human beings working at
these stations producing up to I think
2,000 brow pencils in a day which i
think is so incredibly cool so moving on
to the next step which of course is
going to be my eye shadow I'm just gonna
throw it and look quickly using the
colour-pop and give it to me straight
eyes shadow palette I did not formulate
one of these in labs today just because
I'm already familiar with the process so
I just thrown this for cut crease a
moment I haven't done one in a hot
minute now really liking how this is
turning out but obviously I have a whole
entire eyelid that I want to fill up so
I'm gonna grab this super shock shadow
that I created today at the lab and pop
it on there I'm just gonna pop this
shader right on the lid oh wow that's
pretty and I'm quickly just gonna pop on
a winged liner just to finish off the
eye look oh my god that eyeliner is is
eight inches thick I'm so scared of that
way oh my god keeps getting thicker this
is the worst eyeliner wing I've ever
done in my entire makeup history oh my
god how did this happen
oh my god if I take it off it's just
gonna get Messier so usually when a look
isn't going exactly as planned I'll just
like pop on a lot and it'll fix all my
problems that's not happening today but
it's not the makeups fault it's mine I
don't know how I got to 9 million
subscribers but alas my makeup is done
and I'm ready to move on to the rest of
the phase the next type of my routine is
of course going to be my highlighter I
need to get my glow on because I'm
looking a little bit a lot right now I'm
gonna use my super shocked highlighter
that I created with color palette today
and I am so excited I was actually
really excited to learn more about
highlighter and what goes into making it
just because I think it's that last step
that we all know and love and appreciate
I mean like who doesn't love a good glow
but I was actually so curious to see
like what goes into the formulation of a
highlighter does it really like there
are so many ways that I'd like a
highlighter has to perform and all at
the same time like I was saying at the
lab if the base color isn't right then
it can either look gray or orange
depending on the person's skin tone but
while doing that when you turn it has to
reflect on the light and look shine
there are different pearl sizes you can
either have like a tiny little pearl for
a subtle everyday woman on the goat
book low or you can have an intense
blinding and glittery glow which you all
know that I definitely uh I definitely
get similar to foundation that one thing
going wrong can literally change the
entire formula and either make it look
so beautiful or so bad which feels like
it's like a high-risk situation I mean
it's literally just creating a
highlighter but kind of some funny brush
so the last of my makeup routine today
is of course going to be in the lipid e
du das that I'm gonna use my cousin
gloss in a second but first I need to
start off by lining them so I'm just
gonna use my favorite lip liner of all
time which happens to be from colour-pop
with this one is not mine this is
actually the shade of curvy and
collaboration with Karen I love Saada II
not mine but wish it was because this is
literally the best lip liner color ever
and Carrodus my all-time favorite people
in the makeup community and last but
finally not least right over top of that
lip liner I'm gonna pop on my custom
ultra glossy lip that I created today I
wanted just a perfect peachy nude
leaning more towards pink than orange
and this is what I came up with oh he
didn't really mean to make the lip in
the eyeshadow be like a perfect match
today but I'm gonna pretend like I did
because it kind of looks really good and
fresh let's finish it off with some
sisters head its prey
alright sisters and that is my full face
of makeup that I made all complete I had
so much fun getting my hands dirty and
working behind the scenes today with
collar pop to really see what goes into
actually making a make a problem from
the start to finish I mean we get to
layer these products every single day
and we all use them to feel beautiful
and confident but there's actually so
much of a process that goes into it so
many amazing workers chemists scientists
assembly line people and major sound to
them and to color pop for allowing me it
to be educated and I hope you guys
learned a little bit as well I am so
thankful that I got to experience a
whole behind the scenes process that I
will definitely never forget it and who
knows maybe I'll be part of it one day
that is all I have for you today guys I
really really hope you enjoyed this
video have learned something new if you
enjoyed it please don't forget to give
me a thumbs up down below and show your
sister support it means the entire world
to me and also leave me a comment let me
know if you were to make a makeup
product what would it be and why also if
you have not already don't forget to
click that big red subscribe button down
below and come join this sisterhood we
are nine million sister strong oh my god
I cannot believe we were that close to
10 million it's going to be truly iconic
and also click that Bell icon so you can
get notification every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
and I make up to her you can follow me
on Instagram or Twitter they're opposed
to
Charles my son check for more but I had
the seat size up see you Charles the
next house after Charles this video is
sister shadow goes to sister Kiki do you
love me yes that was the cheesiest thing
I've ever done in my entire life
oh yes I love you so so so much and if
you like tune the next videos sister
said oh don't forget to always reach
peak my mother like something alive on
Twitter all right you guys thank you so
much watching this video today I hope
you enjoyed my time here as a sister
scientist and I will see you in the next
one
[Music]