hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see it we are not in our
normal filming location and that's
because first today's video we have
something very very fun planned but
before we jump into that I have a very
special announcement that I have
literally been waiting to tell you guys
I cannot believe that the day is finally
here oh my god when I released my first
ever collaboration with morphe I'm not
the opportunity to travel all around the
world and open up a bunch of their new
store locations and that has created
some of my favorite memories to date we
did meet and greets I got to hug you
guys to take photos together we sang
songs we had over 10,000 people show up
to a few different locations and we also
may or may not have literally shut down
entire cities which was like kind of fun
and fresh not gonna lie in fact it was
so fun and so fresh drumroll please that
we decided to do it all summer long I
swear to god you guys I have literally
been talking to my team about going on
tour for over two years now and we
wanted to wait and make sure to be
absolutely perfect and I cannot believe
that it is finally here and I get to
tell you guys about it but hopefully the
wait will be worth it because you guys
are about to be sister shook at the
shows we have planned
there are over 24 dates and 24 cities
all around the United States and each
one is going to be so incredibly special
we're gonna have of course makeup live
on stage with maybe a few sisters from
the audience will be playing games you
guys will be coming up will be doing at
the q and A's of course there'll be
music as well and da a whole lot of
Instagram selfies you will be able to
choose from four different ticket
packages from general admission all the
way to an extremely limited number of
our exclusive Sister Bips but I promise
no matter what you get it's going to be
an absolutely amazing day make sure you
check out sisters - tor.com for all
details and information on each
individual ticket package and what you
guys get but most importantly set your
alarms and mark your calendars for this
Friday because tickets are going on sale
at 10 a.m.
make sure you're following in all the
way social media platforms and to have
my post notifications turned on because
all week long oddly releasing more
information and a few exclusive
surprises as well that you guys will
definitely not want to mess I hope you
guys are excited this has literally been
in the works for so long like I said and
I absolutely can not wait to have an
amazing time on the road all of you
sisters alright you guys that that is
all I have for the special announcement
now let's jump in to today's brand new
video as many of you sisters now I have
a severe addiction to Starbucks I start
off my day every single morning with a
venti finca tea drink a tea with my ice
and also a slice a pumpkin bread I feel
like for a very very long time people
thought it was just like part of my
brand to snapchat it all the time but no
literally every single day I'm obsessed
with it I'm addicted and I've been
posting about it for a very very long
time too to try to get a brand deal and
alas here we are today still without
wine fun facts for you guys it actually
used to be on the Starbucks secret menu
as just a strawberry honestly refresher
but you how to add coconut milk to it
but after I started posting about it and
so many of you sisters started ordering
it
they literally added it to the permanent
menu like we actually did that which i
think is so cool this morning I rolled
out of bed and was craving a pink drink
as always but I really was feeling lazy
and did not want to leave the house and
I thought to myself I bet I can make
this myself right here at home so for
today's video I thought I'll be so much
fun to come downstairs to the Kitty
kitchen and see if I could recreate my
Starbucks order that I get every single
day from scratch let's get started all
right you guys I have a bunch of
ingredients in front of me are ready to
get started on our pumpkin bread today
I'm gonna do that first I can pop it in
the oven and then work on at the pinky
drinka tea which speaking of for this
video I am wearing my custom pinky
drinking hoodie that was made for me by
to my fan pages
Zoey and Brooke I love you guys the
absolute most but I do have something a
little bit more sister special to put on
over top and that is
my a pride hi welcome to Starbucks what
can I get started for you a lot of my
ingredients
I do have an actual spice of a pumpkin
bread up from Starbucks so you can use
it as a reference add Lopez as you can
see our loop has a beautiful thick slice
cut out of it
we do love a thick sister and is a
beautiful warm tone smoky pumpkin color
with a darkened soft crust there's also
some pistachio flake some peas
it's pumpkin really it's not for Sachi I
was the expert on all things not related
so we're trying to recreate this exact
loaf today so our first step we are go
ahead and preheated our oven to 350
degrees and she's in the back heating up
for a real one and now we have our large
mixing bowl for my mini kitchen and that
we are going to mix our dry ingredients
into so first we need 1 and 1/2 cups of
all-purpose flour really shove your
measuring cup in there how do I get it
full so there's one ich cup of flour and
now we have our half a cup 1 teaspoon of
baking soda that smells strong oh wow ok
1 teaspoon of ground nutmeg cinnamon
without cinnamon challenge let's go
ladies pasta I thought it was so easy I
just swallowed it it looks so good
Yatta is one teaspoon of cinnamon 1
teaspoon of ground what the clove
that sounds very strong it will just
look a little bit less than a teaspoon
of us I don't like this we have to use
baking powder too
I'm already bored how about teaspoon of
salt the covers on there's a lid on it
first of all I'm not stupid
oh we need to do this in separate bowls
I took a lot of work I'm gonna transfer
this powder mixture over to this bowl
because I need to beat my other things
together in this one now I have to beat
the eggs white sugar brown sugar and
vanilla extract in a large bowl of an
electric mixer on high speed until
combined about 30 seconds we're gonna
crack four eggs why well I am a
professional who'd ever get a cell in
there 1 cup of pure white sugar 1 1/4
cup of light brown sugar
how are you kidding 1/2 teaspoon of
vanilla extracts that's like another -
now we put it together we're gonna mix
it at high speed for 30 seconds being
pumpkin and oil Oh Oh God open this No
now we're gonna lower this down and lock
it and sorry I'll put a slow-speed we're
gonna start beating this in and now
we're going to add 3/4 cup of our oil 1
for our powder mixture until it's
blended and smooth this is too hard
whoo now it's getting nice and thick
it's let me like it's about done oh my
god it actually looks so good I'm a
personal Baker if you didn't know okay
now we're going to take our batter of
our pumpkin loaf cake when important
nice and good oh it looks so good I'm
gonna use it this good spoon it's really
scoop the excess out of here now we're
gonna grab our pumpkin seeds because we
need to sprinkle them on top so it
creates that nice crunchy crust on the
bread this ziplock bag and we're going
to put our pumpkin seeds in there and
now we're just gonna take this rolling
pin and really crunch it off what
somebody your pumpkin powder
we're sprinkle this right on top I know
I'm even thinking steak right none of
you are now 70 minutes all right you
guys now that our pumpkin bread is all
ready to go and nice and coated we're
going to pop this in the oven at 350
degrees for 70 minutes I thought this
was gonna be a quick video to film I was
wrong are we surprised no we're
basically gonna let this cook until the
top is a dark brown we can stick a
toothpick Anna and nothing comes out and
then we're gonna have to let it cool for
many more minutes so I'll see you looks
like a porn Tower
Oh time for the pink drink all right
sisters it is pink kitty drink any time
and we have all of our ingredients right
here
the pumpkin bright is about to be done
so it's the perfect time to start making
our drink so we can sister sip while we
get ready for our breakfast that has
taken us two hours so far using a large
measuring cup filled with 16 ounces of
cold water well that's all like that's
nothing so now that I started this
recipe is to identify at pocket of the
Starbucks insert refreshers now don't
get me wrong
I love Starbucks but I'm slightly
annoyed that I have to use this because
it definitely makes it feel less
homemade but at the same time we were
going for that authentic pink candy
drink edite so you gotta do what you
gotta do I picked it would be a very
very hibiscus refresher it's gonna pour
this in to our nice little cup here
right now in order to prepare I went
ahead and I boiled 1 cup water on top of
my stove so we can make some tea oh it's
hot oh now we're gonna get one pocket of
the itas Oh a passionate tea now if you
have been a long time with Starbucks the
sister before we had the pink drink all
of us typical white girls used to get
our passion tea lemonade and this is
what they used to make this stuff it's
honestly really good for us were just
going to put that in there
no we have to wait there's way too much
waiting in these recipes might as well
just go to Starbucks and get it I put a
bunch of Starbucks at least 10 times and
back by now and the time is taking us to
fill this video no yeah it cost forty
seven dollars for the ingredients of
this yeah you are kidding no oh my god
forty seven dollars no and this is not
worth it in any way shape and/or form
for the time nor the money this just
turned into a Starbucks prandial I mean
it already was even go get two three
drinks the pump everybody what the heck
now we've let our tea steep in the pot
and get nice and juicy for about five
minutes now so I'm just going to take
this and I'm going to squeeze the
remaining juices out this has been a way
too long of a process but I will say it
smells amazing and this kitchen right
now
my god so now we're going to take our
passion tea and mix it together with our
very very hibiscus refresher looking
beautiful is this it like even now now
we're just gonna take our reusable
Starbucks a tumbler with our reusable
straw and fill it with some nice chunks
of ice but like a little bit of ice Oh
tippy forming a cold drink from
Starbucks you said a 100% always order
light ice ordering light ice is just say
far better drink - iced ratio Assoc for
the price sisters not a budget now we're
gonna take our mixture and pour the cup
until it is halfway full
and obviously every brace that makes
pink drinks differently but I personally
prefer when there's a little bit more
pink and then there is drink a 4060
ratio of the pink drink and the coconut
milk but obviously personal preference
we're just gonna top the rest off with
some unsweetened coconut milk we're just
gonna fill the rest up beautiful oh our
pumpkin breads done a perfect timing
okay wait wait I don't know oh shoot Oh
oh wow look at how beautiful that is
that is good and fresh unless you are
cute a toast let's do our toothpick test
clean it's done okay now we have to put
this in at the fridge for 30 minutes to
cool down we don't have 30 minutes so
we're going to put this in the freezer
and hope that it gets chilly quickly
because we have to go this has taken
three hours already
for literally no reason I could have
gotten it in two minutes as our Luck's
right now put it on your plastic shelves
in the freezer the pan this is taking
three hours you get a godless desirable
trick to manage this is not worth that
since I have now been informed that
putting this in my freezer would burn a
hole through the plastic I am actually
going to leave this on my stove top and
holes down into the next 10 minutes
because I'm over this video and I have
things to do let's finish this drink
this looks awful
like what this toxin not good the race
here was a little wrong let's milk in it
oh that is not right Oh kick to chest
again
okay like there okay that's good we're
gonna try this with regular coconut milk
instead of unsweetened coconut I don't
know who what made that I figured
decision it was not me I'll tell you
that right now
but maybe this will taste a little bit
oh it's closed better let's see this now
oh that's so gross just color I've ever
seen this is not right it's purple
that's really dark purple last step I'm
going to grab these freeze-dried
strawberries it's like strawberry chips
can I eat this this would be the good
nor fries
our last tap stick this straw in there
oops
okay what I guess this completes our
venti pink candy drinking purply purply
this video is cancelled how do I get
this out of here oh my god girls don't
rob me good now we're gonna cut a nice
thick slice that is professional look at
that oh my god you guys oh it's still
sister's steaming for a real one alright
sisters oh my god three hours later we
are finally done with our breakfast
option for today I had truly thought
this is going to be an easy video to
film and of course I was wrong
I didn't however have a very good time
doing this and the pumpkin bread it
looks great the pink drink not so much
I think the only way to see how we
actually did is with the taste test so
I'm ready to dive right in and first one
Oh God but just my fort and like a nice
little slice of my pumpkin right here
Oh we're gonna look same-sex oh my god
I'm a professional Baker look at this
same beautiful golden a brown color
nice dark brown crust on the outside
with a good pumpkin seed crunchy texture
this is pretty good fresh you would
never even know if I put this in front
of you let's see how to actually compare
as taste wise oh my god that's laughs oh
my god
oh my god you were good that was such a
delicious and hearty piece of bread but
all of this chewing has left my throat
so dry I think I should maybe wash it
all down with a sip of my DIY Do It
Yourself
that's what GI right means done
thinkety thinkety that turned out purple
oh it doesn't taste like strawberries at
all it tastes like fashion tea lemonade
but like with milk instead of lemonade
which is not good I will tell you right
now I think it's because we use the very
very hibiscus refresher instead of the
like strawberry one but there was no
strawberry hace refresher to actually
use if they do this on purpose so we
cannot actually do this at home that's
so disappointing all that work and we
get this are you guys I guess this
concludes me trying to make my daily
Starbucks order at home from scratch let
me know what you guys think this pumpkin
bread recipe lochia slaps like ten out
of ten would recommend you guys should
definitely try this at home it's like a
really really good and fresh breakfast
item this pink candy drinkin tea however
is not a pink tea drinker tea as a
disgrace
pinkie drinkin tea sweetie I am so sorry
I was already suspicious going into this
but all the recipes recommended the
passion tea and the very very hibiscus
refresher is because I'm an avid at
Starbucks fanatic and neither one of
those two drinks are even close to the
taste of the pink drink and I was
definitely right because this tastes
absolutely awful although this is very
very far that secretes these things at
home today it took me at 3 hours I would
much rather run to Starbucks and take
five minutes and spend only five dollars
and have a far better and faster morning
time alright sisters if you guys enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
show your love and support it really
really helps me out and also leave me a
comment let me know what is your go-to
order at Starbucks obviously you guys
know mine
venti pink drink lay eyes slice of
pumpkin bread I guess my day started
every single day but what gets you
energized in the morning if you've not
already make sure click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join the sisterhood we are sixteen
million a sister strong I would love to
have you and join the family and also
click that Bella code so you get ovation
every time I upload a brand new video
click the link in our description box
down below or check out sisters -
tor.com for all the information on my
summer tour ticket prices and what's
going to be going on it is going to be
an absolute blast and I cannot wait to
see all of these
there and don't forget to set your alarm
for this Friday at 10 a.m. PST with all
the tickets go live on sale you don't
want to miss out if you like to follow
me I'm a make up turn you can follow me
on Instagram and Twitter they're both
the same Charles and myself char for
more behind the scenes i7 the everyday
pic you drinkin a snapchat is Gio
Charles an extra ass after Charles this
video is sister shadow goes the sister
Michelle thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting you know I
love you literally so so so much and if
you like through the next videos sister
shadow it don't forget to always reach
me I've been doing something go live on
Twitter and also turn my YouTube up post
notifications
alright sisters thank you so much
watching this video today I love you so
much and I will see you in the next one
[Music]