hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my you to tale or should
I say good morning sisters as you can
see I'm looking a little bit different I
literally just woke up I look like I got
hit by a bus I'm right here and this is
a studio because I have a very very fun
and fresh video for you guys today
some of my most requested videos of all
time have na a morning routine you guys
always asked for that a skincare routine
I'm really not sure why when my skin is
looking as super problematic oh haze and
also a how I do my hair routine which
also comes as a shock to me considering
it looks like a rat's nest half the time
but I figured why not kind of like merge
them all into one I just woke up it is
super early in the morning I have a lot
to do today I have to be on set in a few
hours I have a bunch of meetings and I
have a dinner to go to later on tonight
I do not have time to get fully glammed
this morning but I do want to get ready
and still look super super cute so I
figured for today's video I would take
you guys to my morning routine and show
you guys how I actually get ready in the
morning and go from looking like this to
actually kind of low-key a little bit
good look at him without actually my
full glam makeup process so if you guys
are interested in that keep on watching
[Music]
all right sisters rise and shine and
give God his the CSD I can't fail
I just don't mind put on a quick little
cute a sister's elfin without the
sisters dr. Carol calm but the person
that was doing the morning is coming
right into that master contacts if you
guys want to be on snapchat you know
that I wear glasses on an everyday basis
because a sister cannot see to say as
life but Ren glasses with makeup is a
little bit problematic since it always
leaves those annoying little lines right
there so I do like to pop in my colored
contacts by the way for those you guys
who always ask my contacts are from
Desio and i also saw that every morning
that brushing my teeth just every person
should plain brush water and toothpaste
what are you talking about I never wet
at first so normally now I would hop
right into the shower and get ciserek
squeaky clean I personally am a grenade
shower I have a lot of trouble getting
up in the morning so a shower really
helps me awaken and get ready for the
day I know some people into shower at
night personal preference please don't
attack me but for today I actually do
have a haircut appointment schedules
we're gonna have it right downstairs for
me my hair is like very very important I
don't know why but I always just have a
lot of insecurities on my hair growing
up as a kid I think probably one too
many
mortifying haircuts that maybe look even
I'm clear that I already well it's
grayed out so now I'm here in LA and I'm
so willing to eat my hair super super
clean it looks better in photos looks
better on video and I just feel a lot
more pop it with a fresh feed and a good
updo so let's head out our instances
were here with a sister Sophia living at
legenda
Harel quia something's been cutting my
hair an offer probably it's got over a
mere four cents downtown we have a
one-year anniversary coming up welcome
for us which is literally one of the
most haunted rubbers in the entire world
and she happens to be a kept woman
clearly which I now love something's
responsible for up might really been
impressed paid so we're going to get
sister stats today so I could be a
confident and get ready for the day okay
sister Sophia just finished cutting my
hair she has to run to her next
appointment she has I had crazy by the
day ahead of her just like we do is I
didn't get a chance to say it goodbye
but literally I'm so scared of how
goodbye her let's get out like are you
literally kidding me I feel already a
million percent better and ready to take
on the day but we still touchdown
because I probably smell gross and I
want to get everything else done and
clean so let's head upstairs
[Music]
okay those videos get do monetize
seating up I'm giving a lot of questions
about bathing suits we have four shorts
and also one piece bikini Queen very
brief signatures two sisters apparel
look over that for the sister summertime
party right I just know the longer this
completes heating up the first thing
that I'm gonna do is actually part one
of my skincare routine I'm gonna relay
it's Anita lemon cream a cleanser this
is like a really neat on one gosh my
skin I'm gonna go to translate a lot my
guns to really scrub it up a little bit
bigger than on the first ride I'm used
to it drop off my facial cleanser
because this also acts I had been
exfolia highway security that 2008 book
and
a kind of cycle simply wilfer girls what
my heart rates up it's all black I love
the brand of the spice and I love a
second as well so it's maybe just a port
in trouble I do a little bit more point
leadership I don't wash it every day but
the kind of the exam is very texture and
all of all when you're doing with each
other for rumps ought to have it sounded
like having a little bit of like wear in
your hair it grows enough sounds update
the style a whole I don't watch that
make sure that make sure you're getting
stains amharic sprays everywhere so that
foxes once I hear it all clean of course
we plumb up to you it was my body if box
before engine I do once here so if you
guys go on
[Music]
did you Missy I did all my shower and my
little sister Tina three weeks this is
the parallel bathrobes just thought of
that right now
kind of an approach to these sisters we
clean your sister by Dyson hair dryer
novice at this hair dryer is probably
the most ridiculously prices are in the
entire world being sold at a whopping
$400
you can't use hoji mr. Prasad either but
what I tell you this is also literally
the best hair during the entire rolls
I'm not kidding I mean I really wish I
was being paid to tell you that but I
can't deny the back so I have two
different tell
first always put on this one I think
this car drivers thank God I have a
hairdryer and I have a little rounder
brush so I basically just like go to my
hair I'm explaining this now consider
loud I'm going to go through my hair
brushing forwards in circular motions
and going forward so kind of like makes
the her leg do not even saying does this
make sense
very Jimmy Neutron forgot Jimmy Neutron
moment but then we're gonna on the
bacon a little messy
[Music]
now I'm going to go buy a mini a
straining all right and I'm going to
switch it on I believe this one is from
Sephora so far she doesn't make it fun
anymore I'm not sure why because it's
really bomb but they do sell solution
here one of the least right Aaron is how
I'm gonna do the same exact thing that I
do with the hairdryer which is basically
just grabbing little sections one at a
time holding my very slowly and pulling
it down and forward into a little curl
so beautiful now we don't do that so
literally my entire what most of my hair
it takes I know a lot of work to make it
look like I did no work if that makes
any sense but then surely the type of
look that I don't like to go for I'm not
going to grab my way not pomade but it's
going to rub it together in my hand so
kind of warms up a little bit and gets a
little bit more soft as my basically
just went like rub it in to my head I
definitely to focus most of it in the
front of my hair just so making these
pieces kind of come down and get texture
see how it's like nice and like funky
like that and then I put the excess cut
it in the back and then going to grab my
way of texturizing hairspray there is no
way that I could do any original out
this basically we're supposed to take a
little bit of this I'll see a lot of it
I'm kind of like you think bigger swing
open up my hair so kind of how my hair
you like to kind of keep it this way I'm
gonna grab my last product which is de
got to be glued Paris
okay if you know this is my hair routine
complete finally our last step before we
head out of the bathroom back to it the
makeup studio without my skincare
routine now of course you might not my
step one before we got into the shower
with these the Venus lemon cream a
cleanser and I'm just going to grab my
next up which is decent he doesn't bite
a minute to you sorry on I do have like
normal skin but I do get very very dry
actually it might be your area when I
get my laser treatments so I love using
this after my cleanser after the shower
just to get my skin a nice refresh the
vitamin C and hydration and it also
finally not Lisa following the vitamin C
Sarah what I always like to apply a
little bit of moisturizer to really lock
everything in place and to complete the
routine this is the touch-up do we skin
cream pro tip if you're someone like me
that has of nails
just use your knuckle it's done super
hard to get in there all gross so soft
looking at so doing hydrogen I am
obsessed with this I know that's super
super short I given everybody asked for
a skincare routine
there was talking like 100 million
products but I actually believe in
quality over quantity though for about a
million times on this channel but yeah
those are like these four to five
products that I use every single day
that really have worked great alright so
you're almost there I'm going to quickly
head into it the closet put on the
hoodie and a parent
and then I will see you in the sister
studio for a quick little no makeup get
rid of me
you're not already sisters so we are
back in the studio that you guys all
know and love and recognize from all of
our videos but today we are not going to
be doing a full glam routine this is
everyone took me like five minutes total
super easy in the morning starting off
with my base I really did not want any
coverage at all but I do have a few
spots that I would like to correct just
a little bit my beard area is obviously
a little bit great and for some reason
around my lips gets very very like
orange right here I don't know why and
of course if we all have a little bit of
under eyes and a few blemishes here and
there so what I'm going to do is grab
just a tiny little bit more of my oyster
Iser doesn't matter which one you are
using and putting it on the back of my
hand just like that and then describing
literally why not squirt of my favorite
foundation that this is the Too Faced
Born This Way which you guys know I love
in the shade nude which is like my
closest actual color match usually I go
a little bit more yellow or a little bit
darker this is like as close as we're
gonna get and just put that right on top
of the moisturizer just like dots that's
going to mix them together with my
finger on the back of my hand and mixing
it together the moisturizer is really
going to sheer it out there's gonna do a
little bit down here on the mustache
area on the sideburns I'm just gonna
take a foundation brush and stipple that
and and then just super quick with a
small powder brush this is the m-52 for
from morphe who's gonna dip into a
little bit of the Laura Mercier powder
and just put this right in some areas
that normally tend to a crease even
though we literally have it nothing on
it this is kind of just like a pro
vanity of it just in case any creasing
does decide to show up same thing with
the Cylons
once the skin is looking beautiful and
smooth the next I'm gonna do is my
eyebrows it's super quickly even on my
no makeup days I do always like my brows
to look it's super super snatched I
truly believe the brows afraid in the
face and obviously you guys know what
they look like before so I definitely
give them very very on fleek squinter
got my Anasazi a number 12 brush and a
little bit of a dip brow just going to
brush the hairs upwards but I'm doing my
boy brows I always it start off with the
tail because the tail is kind of the
only part that I like to be actually
defined just catching that
bringing that up but I'm doing my no
makeup at brows look I really try hard
to not have to play that with a
concealer because that's when it really
starts looking like faux glam makeup so
I'm definitely very very careful during
these steps to showing in a tiny little
hairlike strokes and I almost make them
look like
bushier then they really are definitely
not to the point of like what my 2016
brows used to look like but like I don't
want them to look as tame as they are
when I'm glam does this make any sense
at all basically I'm going for a very
rugged mask look try a little hairs
little crisscross motions in the
directions if they grow and I like that
that's a good there we go that's good
that is such a good brow oh I'm so happy
with that yeah okay okay great first
shot I say you're okay no it's gonna do
the same thing on the other eyebrows
what's amazing about this too is that
since I have literally nothing on my
face if I make a mistake all I have to
do is just go like that and rub it off
whereas before we have makeup wipes
concealer setting powder and a whole lot
of other things to worry about when it
comes to fixing now just to lock those
hairs in place I'm gonna grab the
anasazi a dip brow gel in the shade and
medium and brown this is pigmented so
I'm gonna go pretty light with it I'm
just gonna go in and brush these hairs
upwards and then once I get to the
middle I'm actually gonna pull them kind
of against the way they grow and just so
they kind of left the brows upwards
which not only fills in some areas but
also creates some more texture if
anything does get a little bit messed up
of course you can always grab a little
concealer brush and a little bit of a
foundation and just go right over that
area too but I really do avoid doing
this because it looks a lot better
without but they're looking a little too
thick today before we move on to the
next step well I still have my dip brow
gel I want to show you guys a fun little
check that I've been doing a lot
recently and I'm just going to grab my
last curler and start curling my lashes
I Pro my last every single day no matter
what I truly feel like curled lashes are
so cute on literally everybody
especially when boys have like really
really long lashes Oh literally it's so
hot and they really just open your eyes
and look so adorable so those are my
natural lashes feel a little bit kidding
me my lashes used to be it so long but
from wearing falsies all the time they
get ripped out but like still kind of
fun kind of rushed but instead of
grabbing a regular mascara because
that's gonna look a little bit too
intense or might
of days I'm just gonna grab my dip brow
gel and I'm going to just kind of brush
off any access that may be on the
spoolie because they don't want it to be
too intense but I'm just going to use a
little bit of this and run right through
it my lashes to give them a slight coat
and a slight lift and this is just gonna
make them look a little bit more intense
and a little bit more prominent but not
like you're wearing a full-on lash which
I love see it really does make a
difference oh my god like it's a slight
difference but it's a pretty difference
oh look at my lashes look at my lashes
all right sisters we're almost done one
of my favorite things that I like to do
when I'm not wearing a full glam makeup
look is freckles
I feel like freckles are so beautiful
they're so youthful they make it look
like I am being sunkissed as opposed to
sitting inside and working and filming
all day long and I love how I look in
them to do them I always got my Anasazi
at dipper hotel literally once again in
the shade Auburn and I'm just going to
grab a small little pencil brush like
this one this is just the e36 for morphe
and I go in and I just kind of like
wiggle the brush around a little bit
just to get some pigment on there and I
always go in on the back of my hand and
just rub off any excess and then I'll
literally just go in and start off with
the freckle layer but I kind of just
like watching this around my cheek
region I am going to add a little
freckled off in a second but this kind
of just lays down a little like
sunkissed base area and then grabbing a
little liner brush this into E 37 and my
two different dip brow shades
a burn and a medium brown I'm just going
to add tiny little freckles I'm just
using different pressures when applying
these freckles to some pressing a really
really hard and some barely even
touching my skin just to kind of create
different shapes and colors and sizes
because not all freckles are the same
and I'm just concentrating the most and
the darkest dots right in this X Center
nose area and fading them out as they go
towards the outside of my face now this
is definitely optional but you guys know
personally I like to look very very dewy
and glowy
so I'm just going to grab the James
Charles X morphe palette and literally
the tiniest
of face the highlighter shade from the
palette and I'm just gonna use it this
to put a subtle glow on the skin just
like that Oh gorgeous a little bit on
the chin and using that excess right
above the eyebrows just for some natural
radiance inner corners and then last but
not least a little bit on the brow bone
when it comes to highlighting for these
looks I actually like to skip out on the
nose highlight just because when my face
does get oily my nose is always the
first thing to turn into a kind of slip
and slide so I'm not gonna put any
highlighter on there just to kind of
keep it looking at natural give my face
a quick spritz of the mac's fix+
in the shade gold white which is like
it's like shiny fix+ it just has a tiny
little bit of shimmer in it which is
really going to add to that natural dewy
type of look my skin is like absolute
glowing and this looks so beautiful
right now and last the finally not least
I'm going to grab a makeup wipe and
clean out the back of my hands that I
was using as a palette and then just use
this to go right into my lips and
carefully clean up my lip line and last
but finally not least just to keep my
lips hydrated all day long I'm gonna pop
on a little tiny bit of the Fenty beauty
of gloss balm I love this gloss and it
is very very moisturizing and hydrating
which is perfect for this type of look
well they love being said it is
currently 9 18 in the morning we started
filming right around 8 o'clock give or
take a few minutes for me a resetting
the same thing a million times trying to
get the perfect take we're done at
getting ready for the day that took us
literally one hour and that is my shower
routine hair routine a skincare routine
and every day at no makeup makeup
routine all complete we just killed so
many birds one stone queen of efficiency
my assistant is curly all the way back
to the house right now of my Starbucks
at venti pink adage ain't giddy with
light ice my editor is downstairs
waiting for me to go over her video
notes with him and I manager is also on
the way over and we're gonna head over
to some work meetings for some very very
exciting projects all in all I am
feeling it was so beautiful so confident
and ready to take on the entire day
raising for this little morning routine
kind of get ready with me type of video
please give it a big thumbs up down
below this is actually Loki a really
really fun to film just to kind of hear
Freddy wake up in the morning with all
of you sisters
I think my videos are obviously very
very planned out and professional Wow
okay maybe not professional but like
planned out whereas this video is much
more go with the flow it's kind of
behind the scenes type South I love
doing this and if you guys want more of
this type of content definitely leave me
comment and let me know if you have not
already make sure to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join these sisterhood we're 15 million
sisters Charlotte I love to have you
join of the family and also click that
belt like on so you can get notification
every time I upload a brand new video if
you like to follow me on I make an
attorney you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both just changed
Charlotte's and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes nights out and more
good morning snapchat suburb stuff like
this is James Charles that extra ask
after Charles this video sisters how
that goes the sister Emily thank you so
much love for always the following and
supporting you know I love you literally
so so so much and if you like to the
next videos sister shadow don't forget
to always retweet my video links and
they go live on Twitter all right you
guys that is all I have for this videos
today thank you so much for watching it
I love you so much and I hope you all
have an amazing day bye
[Music]