one week ago I uploaded a video to my
youtube channel titled Tati this video
was a direct response to the video that
Tati Westberg uploaded to her channel
titled by a sister before I say anything
at all in this video I want to make it
very very clear that everything I said
in that video in regards to it my
sentiments towards Tati and my apology I
stand behind 100% and still rain true I
know I got emotional in the video I
apologize it was something very very
hard for him to deal with especially
when it came to talking about my very
own mother in talk to his video she
discusses many of the different reasons
as to why she was choosing to close a
chapter in her life that I was heavily
involved in making many of our private
issues very very very public and now
millions and millions of people have
weighed in with their opinions and
speculations on subjects that they
honestly know absolutely nothing about I
will not ask for sympathy and I will
definitely not ask for forgiveness
either but I will ask that you watch
this entire thing all the way through
before forming any further opinions or
talking about this story more hello
future James here popping in quickly
I know doing an insert in a video like
this is not professional trust me but I
filmed this several times now and as
time keeps going on more and more things
keep coming out into the public and more
people are speaking on the situation and
it is very important to me that this
video has all the information all the
facts all the receipts and is current
and present because I will not be
addressing it again after this matter
this morning when I was editing this
video I noticed that last night totsied
uploaded a video to her channel called
why I did it and this morning Geoffrey
Starr was on snapchat talking about the
whole situation first and foremost I do
want to issue a thank you to both
Jeffrey and Tati for taking some of the
responsibility for blowing this whole
thing up and for starting everything I
really respect that a lot and I also
appreciate the fact that they are trying
to redirect the hate away because I
think we're all aware at this point that
it has gotten way too far the past week
on the Internet has been at the darkest
I think we've all ever seen and it's
also been the darkest time that I've
ever had to go through and my life and
my thoughts gone to a really scary place
watching takis video it's clear to me
that she also is in a really dark place
as well and has been pained by this
whole situation if I've known anything
about talk to you over the past three
years it says she has a huge huge heart
there's no tonight
and I think that or I do believe her
when she says that she did not want this
to get so vile I don't really think any
of us thought it's gonna be as big as it
really was in both of their videos
Jeffrey and Tati both mentioned that
they hope that I'm able to change and
then we can all move on from the
situation and trust me I agree there's
nobody that wants it's over with as much
as I do
but in takis second video and in Jeffrey
snapshots they both said that they stand
behind everything that they mentioned
and unfortunately there have been
allegations made against me because of
these things and I don't really feel
comfortable just moving on from those I
would like to take this video today as
an opportunity to kind of explain
everything that has happened and address
literally everything there's a lot that
happened behind the scenes leading off
to talk days video and there's a lot
that happened behind the scenes and
publicly after takis video and I feel so
it is my responsibility to kind of let
you guys in on those because there's a
lot of misinformation going around and
it's just not really good just like
talking said in her video this whole
situation is a lot bigger in the despite
immense and I think anybody who's kind
of followed the situation is well aware
of that at this point trust me I am too
there are way bigger issues here that I
will be discussing and talking openly
and honestly about later on in this
video I have a few notes in front of me
here and I want to make sure that I hit
every single point and that I don't miss
anything but that being said to get to
those issues this did start with
vitamins it was kind of the catalyst so
I want to make sure we kind of go in
order and you guys are able to get the
full context and full story of
everything if that has happened starting
off my friends and I all tend to
Coachella weekend one from April 11th
through 15th and I had an artist pass
provided to me by a brand we had a
really really good weekend I mean you
guys saw the snapshots Instagram
pictures and outfits and my video it was
really really fun and we will definitely
never forget it but at Coachella I had
drama with a boy that I had been talking
with for five months prior and it all
kind of clouded at the overall memories
later on at that very same week on April
19th my best friends and I in the family
group chat made the last-minute decision
that we wanted to attend Coachella
weekend to again to kind of relive those
memories but boy free I texted my
manager Jake that very same night asking
it to be possible to get us in for the
next day since it was already Friday we
nee were missing the first day of the
festival so therefore we could only go
on Saturday because it was so at last
second we were only able to get VIP
tickets which is not the same as artists
but we had it over anyway and wanted to
have a really really good time for those
of you who may not be familiar with
Coachella I do want to quickly clarify
the different passes just because it
kind of is important to this whole
situation if the IP although VIP is
still very very open to the public
artists passes however our passes that
you can not buy the only way you can get
a hold of them is through a brand
getting them from the actual festival or
through having a personal connection to
one of the artists or bands that are
playing it's in a very very highly
secured area that is not open to the
public a lot of artist passes though
there's also something called a
performer pass and backstage passes and
a lot of other things that can keep you
more protected keep in mind weekend one
I did have an artist past weekend - I
had a VIP going into the situation when
we walked into weekend 2 with me my
friends on a Saturday April 20th and
Sunday April 21st we notice that there
was a major major difference and at the
crowd we were in the VIP section and I
started getting mobbed really really
quickly at a super unsafe capacity
because as many of you guys know when
I've always stopped to take a photo kind
of other people tend to come and it just
turns into a big situation and it
honestly it was not safe I had
remembered from weekend one that my
friend Nikita driving home is with a lot
of the time was brought by sugar bear
hair and had an artist pass personal
security and backstage passes and was
very very taken care of and safe what I
felt unsafe in the situation I panicked
and I text Nikita and asked her if she
had a connection to the sugar bear hair
team that could potentially help me out
Nikita replied right away and she gave
the sugar bear hair team at my personal
phone number to which they reached out
to me and offered to come rescue me with
a pass and backstage access and security
to make sure that I was okay and was
able to enjoy the festival along with my
friends you went to Coachella somehow
had a security issue and magically sugar
bear hair is there with a contract in
hand to save the day for you and all of
your friends no company would ever go
out of their way to have an extra you
know handful of passes that cost
thousands of dollars apiece
like just in case that leads me to
believe that this was orchestrated
beforehand but he had an emotional
conflict because of me and promises he
made
me behind the scenes so he had to come
up with a very clever story and didn't
tell me right when he got back but after
the little bit was posted on their
launch day despite we talked you said in
her video of this whole situation was
definitely not a big scheme that was
orchestrated beforehand it really did
happen on the spot the sugar bear hair
team texted me their proposal right away
no money was involved and with no time
to negotiate in a panic I signed and
that was out on that James Charles he
had nine days after Coachella to talk to
me on Monday April 22nd which was one
day after Coachella I was due to post my
stories based on my contract and up
until that moment I honestly had not
thought about the fact that talk to you
was a sugar bear hair a competitor and
in that moment I thought that as a
friend she deserved a courtesy text to
let her know the context on the
sponsorship and everything that was
going on to not even get a phone call to
not even get a text a few days prior but
right after that sponsored post went up
to have a text like hey mom love you I'm
stressed just so you know XYZ I just did
this post but it's no big before posting
my stories I actually did text 20 first
out of respect for her giving her heads
up about the sponsorship but she was
immediately upset I try my best to kind
of explain the entire situation and also
gave her a direct apology as well but at
this point I had signed the contract and
I absolutely had to post it there was no
getting out of it I then headed to the
airport and took off on a flight to San
Francisco
by the time that I had landed a one hour
later talk to you - uploaded all of her
Instagram stories of her crying talking
about the friends the community that
haven't really supported her how she was
alone and how she felt very very hurt
and betrayed very quickly people put two
and two together and realized that this
was clearly about me and I started
getting thousands and thousands of
tweets and comments and texts about the
whole situation throughout the next
several hours I made countless attempts
at text both Tati and her husband James
and many phone calls as well trying to
reach them all of which they did not
respond to and later on that night while
sitting in my hotel in San Francisco
because I could not reach talk to you I
assured a public apology directly on my
Instagram because
I really wanted to make sure she saw
that I was sorry and I wanted to end the
situation by taking full responsibility
for my actions over the next several
days I made countless attempts to
contact both Tati and her husband James
on all their different phone numbers I
texted and called a Tottie's business
number her family number and also
James's personal phone number as well
after a full entire week of trying to
reach out and handle things in private
with Tati on her husband James and
getting no response I figured at this
time it'd be best to just respect their
space give them their privacy and that
whenever talked to is ready she was
reached back out to me to handle things
in private and hopefully move on with
our friendship that is everything in
regards to the Instagram stories that
we've talked about that I want to
discuss a few of the things and talk to
this video that were misleading and
false the reason that James always said
that he couldn't promote halo on his
channel and really do like you know
heavy endorsement was because he has a
teenage audience and it would just be
inappropriate now this thing was just
confusing to me mostly because this
conversation never actually happened if
you guys know my channel you know that I
don't really do dedicated product
reviews ever which is what Tati is known
for but even though that is the case I
have still multiple times that talked
about her products are almost social
media networks I have to worry okay I
forgot to say - hello I'm going to a
really important event later on tonight
my best friend we are going to yes this
is true and this is a very important
loss to me because it is my best friend
- mopti it she's launching something new
on HeLa beauty I'm super proud of her by
the tennis videos oh it'll already be up
so go check it out
probably for talk to you love me the
most who doesn't need a little beauty
boost every now and then - the following
statements are real claims made by your
original halo beauty booster so oh can I
just say I love you guys for putting a
Halo question in there
as I just receive a package from a halo
beauty this is Todd he's a brand-new
brand mom I did not tell talk to you
that I was buying these going to pay for
these myself because I just wanted to
support her and I'm so happy because I
know she's worked so hard on these for
the past several years now
congratulations auntie I love you a
little you so much I do want to keep
this video strictly based on facts and
receipts but one of the most hurtful
things taki did and her video it was
bring up my mom and questions her
parenting no tears this time my mom is
the strongest woman I have ever met she
is kind she is creative and she is
caring she is a cancer survivor and she
balances a marriage a full-time job and
raising two boys absolutely crazy lives
she's taught me so much in the past and
when I made a mistake
she has never turned to public
humiliation as a form of punishment all
that being said I love my mom and I
think she's doing a damn good job if I
do say so myself
the last phone conversation that James
Charles and I had he said some things
telling me about a situation that
happened in Seattle at my birthday and
it literally made me want to vomit oh my
god you tried to trick a straight man
into thinking he's gay yet again and
somehow you're the victim you know it's
really disgusting to manipulate
someone's sexuality especially when they
are still you know emerging into
adulthood and don't quite have
everything figured out you are using
your fame your power your money to play
with people's emotions and you're doing
that to have them behave sexually in
your favor even if they're straight and
you know what that's not okay and how
dare you laugh about it and make me
master meme and retweet and this and
that and I love straight boys I love
straight boys and make it a joke because
this behavior is not normal it's not
okay
cracking someone's sexuality is not an
escape room first of all I am a 19 year
old virgin I talk about boys quite a lot
of my social media networks clearly at
this point and it's not acceptable
anymore
we're talking about that a little bit I
promise you but just thought I would
bring it up put it out into the universe
I don't really get a lot of action
we have probably guessed this at this
so that being said I have never and
would never and will never use my fame
money or power to manipulate or get any
sexual actions from a guy that is
disgusting it is not me and the fact
that Tati brought this up blows my mind
because she knows the real story the
story that were talking about here is a
situation that happened when I was in
Seattle for talking surprise party with
a boy named Sam now I'm going to tell
you the full story since everybody seems
to be leaving out literally every single
detail in talk to each video she
mentioned that she was disgusted and had
to apologize to her family for me
apparently saying things that I wanted
to do to a waiter and then just to find
those actions by saying I have a
celebrity okay this literally did not
happen what did happen is that me
Jeffrey Nate - my best friend drew all
flew to Seattle to surprise talk to you
for her birthday on February 14th that
night we went out to dinner with that
with Tontine James and her whole family
and we're in a restaurant there was a
cute boy across the restaurant that I
kept making eye contact with and that I
was interested in and the conversation
of dating for me and Jeffrey both came
up the dinner table and we were talking
about it for a very very short period of
time the conversation never got
inappropriate period the boy that was
involved in the story is named Sam now
when I originally wanted to do this
video addressing everything I did plan
on crossing his name and keeping him
completely private but he has since come
out and made a video of his oh not
talking about the situation just like
talk to you leading out many many
details but in his video and in the
screenshots that I have Sam mentioned
that he was perfectly fine and found the
flirting that I was doing flattering so
I'm not really sure why this got turned
into something much bigger but it simply
was not he was looking at me later on
that night he started asking me if I had
a Valentine this is this was on
Valentine's Day where he especially
thought that I was very attractive and
he wanted to get my phone
and all that but the waitstaff at my
restaurant didn't let that happen
he left and it kind of just went and
talked about the Imus Liberty thing is
really incredibly frustrating to me
because this is an inside joke between
my friends and I had that Tati is also
participated in and she twisted this to
be something far worse than what it is
this is the joke that really is where we
say I'm famous not I'm a celebrity and
it's thing that we don't say it in
public very often because without
context I get it it looks and sounds
really really bad trust me literally
famous is synonymous of anything good so
yeah my YouTube video does well one day
my friends was like oh my god James are
so famous but literally if my friend
takes a good Instagram photo oh my god
you're so famous if our boneless buffalo
wings that Chili's are extra delicious
one day oh my god these wings are so so
famous it has nothing to do at all with
fame power or money which is what Tati
eluded it to being and it is so
frustrating that she turned an innocent
and funny inside joke that she has
participated in into something so beyond
disgusting I'm going to try my best to
make it a long story very short the next
day Sampson into my DMS first and I
happened to see it we started talking
back and forth and he mentioned that he
was flattered by me flirting with him at
the night before head sorry about last
night you're very attractive and then I
was very flattering actually a few
minutes into the conversation I asked
about his sexuality and he told me
straight up that he was bisexual oh my
god you tried to trick a straight man
into thinking he's gay there was no
straight man at being manipulated
anywhere in this story like Tati
mentioned later on in the conversation
he asked when I was leaving Seattle and
I told him the next morning to which he
responded I wish we had time to hang out
and I said hey why do you come over to
my hotel tonight we can watch a movie
together
he said sounds good later on he messaged
me first and told me hey straight up
I've never done anything with a guy
before I'm a little bit nervous too
which I told him there was absolutely no
pressure this is all shown in the
screenshots Sam showed up at the hotel
we watched movies together and we
cuddled after the movie I asked him if
he wanted to kiss to which he said yes I
get to the hotel room we say hi it's all
fine we had watching a movie and
after that movie he asked to kiss me I
said yes and we ended up making out for
around an hour and if I'm being honest
he's the worst kisser I've ever kissed
way too much time all right
note taken um after making out Sam for
over an hour I did invite him to sleep
over at the hotel and he kept telling
you to stay like please say please say
don't leave me all this knob and I
really wanted to go home
so I left of course I want to spend more
time with him but he said that he wanted
to go home and be in his own bed and
think about everything that was going on
because it was quite a lot and I
definitely understood and did not blame
him he then left and sent me a message
afterwards thanking you for being so
understanding and I told him that I
would always be there for him if he
needed literally anything point being
everything that happened in the hotel
room was 100% consensual and this is
confirmed I said yes by the only two
parties that were actually they are
being myself and Sam after this night
Sam when I continued to talk for the
next several weeks at first it was
really really great
but I noticed that his feelings towards
me and sexuality were kind of wavering
quite a lot and I came to the collusion
that he needed to figure himself out and
that I needed to move on because I kept
getting hurt last important note to keep
in mind about the timeline of the whole
situation on May 2nd Sam texted me from
his friend's phone saying that he was
fully gay I needed to talk to me about
something important I called him and
instead talking about that he asked me
if I was talking to another guy at the
same time that I was talking to him I
was a little bit confused as to I as
being asked this but I did answer him
honestly and then I asked him what made
him come to conclusion with everything
to what she said
I'm actually not fully okay after doing
this a million times I was frustrated
and I hung up just to clarify so there
are no further questions the point of
including this screenshot is not to out
Sam Sam texted me saying he was fully
gay but it was a trap to get me on
FaceTime so he could illegally record
the conversation to include in the video
that he was planning later on like I
said at the end of the conversation I
asked and how he came to this conclusion
and then he told me he was not fully gay
to which I hung up out of frustration
later on he texted me saying he was
confirmed by this is why in Sam's video
he included a screenshot of me telling
him I did not think he was fully
straight this comment had a lot of
people really up
and confused as to why I was telling
somebody their sexuality but there's a
very simple explanation Stan when I
talked for a very very long time and his
sexuality like I said wavered a lot
every time that he was a little bit
confused we had open and honest
conversations about it and he always
asked me of my input and I gave it to
him I would never out somebody and I
have never ever tried to manipulate
somebody's sexuality including his
point-blank period the whole situation
that happened with Sam was very very
long and complicated and left both of us
very hurt and confused and through
trying to do this I reached out to many
of my different friends for advice um
there was one night in my kitchen where
Tatia James and Gabriel all came over
and I told them the same exact story and
showed them the same exact screenshots
to all of you guys just saw after
hearing this like Tati said in her video
Tati and James actually did have a
heart-to-heart conversation with me
about the boys that I could involve with
they told me that talking to curious
guys was going to continue to get me
hurt and that also it could look really
really bad from an outside perspective
if somebody tried to manipulate the
situation and for me this is a major
major wake-up call that I took to heart
because I honestly had never thought
about it and any other way because I
knew that everything that I was doing
was always consensual between both me
and the boy and I had receipts to back
it up but I wished I knew at the time
that Todd his advice was really a
warning because she did exactly what she
told me someone else may which was
telling my story with no details no
facts and no proof and twisted around
and now serious allegations have
surfaced that could permanently damage
my career now like I said the talk that
happened in my kitchen I really did
appreciate because it was the first time
I kind of took a step back and was able
to analyze what was going on and this
week has been a major eye-opener for me
as well I want to take a brief moment to
talk about boys boys have obviously met
a talent that has been discussed quite
in detail on my youtube channel and
social media networks this is no secret
I wish it hadn't been but if I'm gonna
talk about at one last time I definitely
want to be open and honest with you guys
the ones who matter I got out of the
closet as gay at age 12 which is
honestly really really young to kind of
figure all of that out I have two other
boys at school at the time who were gay
but we were all close friends so nothing
was happening there if you know what I
mean but all my other friends were
having their first kiss underneath the
playground slide or getting into their
first relationship and talking all about
it
and for me I was on poptropica and
social media networks trying to make
friends and trying to find out what else
I was interested in I never really got
the opportunity to experiment with love
and learn from that as a growing
teenager and I think that that's
honestly left me kind of underdeveloped
as a person in a lot of different ways
I've been forced to grow very very
quickly because of the job that I work
in in social media which I know excited
million times beforehand but love and
relationships is something that I have
barely any experience in and I honestly
think that that's why I'm a lot less
mature than others maybe in the
situations that I get myself into um I
definitely am emotional and I like it
the best me sometimes I can be dramatic
I'm reactive I'm forward I'm flirty and
these are qualities that I'm not
necessarily proud of at all but I can
confidently say that with each
experience I'm learning more and more
and I've been able to better myself but
a lot of times these situations have
become public my own fault my own fault
but having millions of people watching
you learn can be very very tricky when
it comes to experiences that I've
learned from in the past a lot of times
I've talked about being in two straight
guys now this conversation is saying
that has upset and also confused quite a
lot of people so in order to provide a
little bit more context I would like to
play a clip from Todd his friend Jeffrey
Starr's video titled the truth about my
relationship but a single for a long
time and the reason why is because I am
really not attracted to anyone but what
we call in this world as a straight male
or a normal dude and what I mean by that
is like you know I am really into
straight guys and I know that is going
to not be surprising to a lot of you so
you know from just travelling everywhere
and meeting dudes all the time and being
around that world for so long I really
kind of fell into a trap of always being
someone that was kept like the secret
and when you are someone like me who is
you know I get asked all the time even
every day on my channel you guys I get
comments are you a guy are you a girl
are you transgender are you trying to
transition what are you being someone
that is like me that is a guy that looks
like a woman right I keep doing this
because so many people are not into
labels these days and I love that I'm
all about that you do you call yourself
whatever you want whatever you believe
in I think that is the beauty and the
freedom of you know living is we can be
whoever we want to be I have always been
into straight men and the problem with
that my entire life is I never found
real love because straight men behind
closed doors they love people like me
they love hooking up they love having
fun
they love the relationship as long as
other people don't know I really like
the stuff from Jeffrey's video because
not only is everything in it very
accurate but I honestly feel like he did
a great job of explaining a topic that
is very confusing and complex and then
not a lot of people understand including
me fully to be honest yes as a gay man I
am attracted to men and in the past
whenever I have found a guy cute on
Instagram or on social media I have
stood in the dm's of the simple hello or
a nice compliment if anybody ever made
it clear that they were not interested
or were not gay and didn't want to talk
I always apologized for the unwanted
attention and the conversation was put
to a halt immediately I do take full
responsibility for sending these
messages in this situation has
definitely taught me that sending
messages that are so for and direct like
this are unacceptable and I no longer
will do that moving forward a few
different guys that I've talked to in
the past have since came forward with
their stories or posted screenshots of
conversations that I had with them
saying that I made them feel
uncomfortable and reading some of them I
honestly felt really really bad I
reached out to all the boys directly and
apologize to them for my actions but
aside from those few guys people are
treating a hashtag Jam Chavez over party
as an open invitation to add to the
narrative with lies which is not only
harmful to me but it's also creating
very very dangerous stereotypes around
the lgbtq+ community for example zara
larsson who's a pretty big singer
tweeted saying that i messaged her
boyfriend multiple times knowing he was
straight and this tweak on almost half a
million likes before it was deleted in
her defense she did later on say there
was only one message but it was way too
late because the media had already ran
with it saying that I was harassing
straight men and wouldn't leave him
alone had I known that he was dating
zara larsson I clearly never would have
messaged him in the first place but this
is all very hypocritical considering and
this is how's our Larson found her
boyfriend I'd like to pose a question to
you the audience
why is it okay for zara larsson a woman
with the public platform to tweet these
photos of a shirtless man and say who
are you where do you live how old are
you why are you so fine how do you like
your eggs cooked in the morning but for
me as a gay man to DM the same person in
private with a simple compliment is
predatory these stereotypes are on gay
men had been and continue to be very
very harmful to the community and have
been historically used to villainize gay
men in society someone completely
fabricated a whole entire story about me
touching another boy at a high school
Journal and it blew up this person that
came forward a few days later saying
that it was a social experiment but it
was too late people also completely
photoshopped Twitter DMS of me reaching
out to these people threatening legal
action if they were to tweet more things
when in reality I have literally not
even met on social media and I deleted
the Twitter app from my phone so all
these things are just so false and are
so fake and it's truly disgusting
also pretty much every boy that I've
ever even communicated with at this
point is posting screenshots of our
conversation at to make a spectacle of
me I've dealt with so many fake stories
in the past from Coachella the fake sex
tape and now this and I'm done I'm done
being the subject of these bandwagon
stories for length it's not okay now
that we've addressed and cleared the air
on the boys let's get back to our
Thailand because somehow there's still a
whole lot more to this story and more
claims as well in toc2 video she said
that she felt she needed to bring all
this to the public eye because people
need to just know what's going on behind
the scenes and I truly cannot believe
that I'm about to bring up what I'm
going to bring up but I feel the same
exact way on Monday May sex that Jeffrey
posted this tweet to his twitter which i
honestly started getting tagged in after
this tweet and a few other ones from him
and his friends i decided to reach out
to him and asked if there was something
going on and that i should be aware of
he replied to me and he said that it was
not about me and that it was about
another brand stealing his ideas this
message was in a voice memo which has
since disappeared from the screenshot
you'll just have to believe me I have
literally no reason to lie at this point
even though he said it wasn't about me I
still asked to talk to him but he said
he was unavailable a few hours later
while I was getting ready to forth and
back down
this text from Jeffrey concerned but
mostly really really confused I reached
out to him about meeting together in
private and hopes to speak together and
figure out the best understanding but he
didn't reply
three days later still no response I
decided to reach out again but he was
not available to talk I flew to
Australia on May 8th and on May 10th
hours before my scheduled meeting
reappearance where five thousand fans
were already waiting outside I was open
up at four in the morning by my friend
because Tonti had just uploaded a video
titled by a sister watching talk to his
video it was very clear to me that my
friend was still very hurt and even
though I had already apologized both
privately and publicly I wanted to make
a video right then and there with my raw
and honest emotions but because of the
time difference it took me the extra few
hours to film the video and get it up
and by the time I was about to hit
publish
I received an another text from Jeffrey
star I've already cleared up Sam and our
nights together being a hundred percent
consensual he was absolutely not trapped
at a hotel room but Jeffrey also brings
up Zack Zack is his boyfriend Nate's
brother and not only did I not pursue
Zack who identifies his mainly straight
but it was actually Jeffrey who
suggested that I talk to him in the
first place maintenance brother is
single and mainly strange alright after
Ali moved here work Zack and I talked on
South chat for maybe a total of 10
selfies parking port to each other he
was super super sweet but it was very
clear to me that he was not actually
interested and the conversation stopped
before anything could even get remotely
flirty at all with everything going on I
did not reply to Jeffrey's text in the
moment a few days later on Monday I woke
up again in the middle of the night from
a phone call my little brother Ian who
was very very upset he's only he had
tweeted saying why do people act so
tough online about somebody from his
hometown who was bullying him and a
Jeffrey star of all people had quote
tweeted Ian's tweet saying why is her
brother a predator why don't you really
move back to New York City exactly shut
the [ __ ] up many people were quick to
call out Jeffrey for bullying a kid who
had nothing to do with the situation
literally at all and he deleted it the
tweet after this I went to check my
and notice that Jeffrey had texted me a
few minutes prior and I opened my phone
to this I really want to read this text
out loud just so you all get to hear
exactly what I had to read but also so I
don't miss anything
Grayson is going on camera shortly to
finally tell the world how you tried to
molest him and touch him in his sleep
and made him uncomfortable for months
you sick [ __ ]
next Zach will be going on camera to
tell how twisted and sick you were
trying to get him to like you and then
make him feel bad what he didn't want to
send you photos back then Sam from
Seattle will be joining me in Cameron to
talk about you trapping him in his hotel
room
you need to be locked in prison for a
very long time you need the internet
taken away from you you are a danger to
society as disgusting as it is I have to
admit bringing up Graceland Dolan was
pretty clever at the height of all these
allegations and stories going around
both of the twins unfollowed me not
wanting to be associated and fans
started speculating that the rumors
could be as to why
too bad that aside from our pre-planned
collaborative jokes that happen did the
sisters want videos of me and Grayson
flirting nothing ever happened between
us and when all this went down
I knew Jeffrey was lying because the
twins were two of the first people to
call me and make sure that I was okay I
already mentioned Zach and I still have
no idea who the Cameron at Jeffrey's
referring to in this message is but he
also brought up Sam last who he also
already talked about later on that day
though Jeffrey was right Sam did upload
a video to his YouTube channel telling
the whole story he left out almost all
the details and included an illegally
recorded FaceTime call which was on May
2nd told you'd remember that but even
through all of this he still managed to
get the point across that our
interactions were 100% consensual next
was Jeffrey's tweets my little brother
Ian now I did say that this video was
going to be solely based on facts and I
of course can't prove what Jeffrey was
trying to imply here and I don't want to
put words into his mouth but since it's
now open for speculation might as well
clear the air he had actually went home
for a few different reasons but it's
temporary he had to get his with some
teeth taken out and he's also working on
different modeling opportunities in New
York City and I am so incredibly proud
of
but he was also having a really really
hard time in LA dealing with a public
breakup and negativity online sent him
into diagnosed clinical depression which
he is now being treated for and he
wanted to be with my parents nothing
more
last but finally not least Jeffrey
posted this tweet claiming he hadn't
seen me since February and that Nate
banned me from their home now this
so-called ban is the first time I'm ever
hearing of this and I just think it's
really funny that Jeffrey brought this
up could starting the fact that he's
tweeted me twice and between February
and now saying that he missed me
regardless he ended that tweet first
thing I was a danger to society and
everything in takis video was 100% true
adding insult to injury
not only did Jeffrey texted me but he
also went out of his way to text my best
friend drew this lovely message trying
to turn him against me Jeffrey's
messaging about me both in private and
in public was hurtful to fam'ly Torrey
extremely excessive but most importantly
literally all based on lies I wish I
knew why he was doing all this but at
the same time his track record with
public views makes under this a surprise
Totti made a video telling stories about
me and publicly humiliating me and now I
have serious allegations against me that
could be detrimental to my career hello
future games here popping in again I've
been completely honest my whole timeline
thus far and I obviously want to keep
doing so so I feel like it is only fair
to mention that only within the past few
days it pretty much everyone involved
with this situation has started to reach
out to me in some way shape or form
say I'm cook the boy from Seattle has
called me nine times and sent me a few
different text messages about the
situation and trying to make things
right
Totti and her husband James have tried
to reach out in order to schedule an
meeting but only through a mutual
YouTube rep that we share and I'd also
heard from that same person that Jeffrey
was open to a meeting as well this whole
thing has just been really difficult for
me because throughout the past three
weeks literally all I've wanted and all
I asked for was for communication from
these people and I tried really really
hard to get that and I did it so I
declined the meetings because I felt
like this was started publicly and it
was addressed publicly and I felt like
it was only fair
for me to address as publicly as well
before meeting behind the scenes and
talking further that sucks to say
because I still have love for these
people and I hope that one day we all
can sit down together in a meeting for
closure and also to discuss how in the
future if problems do come up we can
talk in private
with only us involved but right now I
just need time and space to kind of get
my head back to where it needs to be and
get my mental health back together
before I kind of rekindle those
friendships because everything that
happens still really really hurt and I I
like wouldn't wish what I went through
upon even my worst enemy no matter how
angry I was I've always tried to use my
platform to spread positivity but I feel
like at this point it's my
responsibility to be honest with you
guys and tell you that the last few
weeks of my life has literally been the
most painful time that I've ever had to
deal with and my head and brain for a
hot minute went to a place so dark that
I didn't think that I was going to come
back from and I thought I can't believe
I just mitad that on camera
people always say that being a
social-media influencer is an easy job
and this is some that I've talked about
time and time to time to get on YouTube
we get it but I don't think any human
being ever is prepared mentally or
physically to deal with the pain and
anxiety of what it feels like to have
millions and millions of people talking
to you at one time having to read the
hundreds of thousands of tweets and the
YouTube videos and the articles about me
and my character and my family based on
things that were almost all lies like it
messed me up it messed me up
is the best way that I can put it and
through all of this I've learned that if
I can get through this I can get through
anything
joy getting in on bandwagon hate and
cancel culture is incredibly incredibly
toxic and it's very concerning to me
that as a society we're becoming okay
with guilty until proven innocent
instead of the other way around I truly
hope that everyone who participated in
this whether it be fans influencers Java
channels or credible newest sources take
the time to think about your words and
the impact that they may have on others
because I assure you and I promise you
it's a lot stronger than you might you
may think right now I have a lot of
positive changes that I want to work on
in my life first and foremost I really
want to focus more on spending time in
person with the people that I love and
care about the absolute most and I also
have a lot of work to do in terms of
getting my mental health box where it
needs to be what's now when you guys
class my parents and little brother just
got to LA this morning and we all got to
hug and be together as a family for the
first time in a while and all my closest
friends that are not on my payroll May I
an are all here too we're celebrating my
birthday next week
I'm turning 20 gross many of you guys
noticed that the Socialists apparel
website was down I was so excited about
a lot of the things that
not coming very very soon and just the
lion in general I am so grateful for all
of your guys's love and support on it it
was really really fun to work on I also
love the team that I worked on it with
but unfortunately I had a sever ties
with Killer mercs I just don't see a
world that exists where I could ever be
in business with the team ran by someone
like Geoffrey star if you placed an
order on the website before it went down
everything will still be fulfilled don't
worry you'll get your items and if you
got a gift card beforehand make sure you
hold on to it because the balance will
be valid whenever we reopen because we
are coming back I promise
in regards to the sisters tour which
have gone quite a lot of questions about
despite the ticket scandal we are almost
completely sold out nationwide and that
is mind blowing to me and I'm so
grateful I know there's been a lot of
emails and speculation as of right now I
unfortunately do not have a full answer
on what is happening with the tour but I
will have an update for you guys by the
end of this week I promise going on tour
has been a dream of mine for so long now
and I really want this to happen I just
feel like meeting you guys hugging you
and just getting to thank you
face-to-face for what you've done for me
is exactly what I need in my heart right
now but at the same time towards a lot
and it's a big big commitment and I want
to make sure that I know what I'm
getting into and that when I walk on
stage every night it's with a genuine
smile and you guys can feel that and
you're able to smile as well so I'll
keep you posted as for my youtube
channel I decided that I'm gonna be
taking some much-needed time away from
content production on my last few videos
I've definitely noticed quite a lot of
comments talking about my ego or my
attitude getting the best of me and
getting to my head and I appreciate the
constructive criticism and feedback and
after a lot of reflection I think you're
right
I've lost focus and that sucks so much
but I want to get back to it so badly
and I want to get back to my original
goal when I have no motivation other
than just creating original content and
that'll happen for sure and I already
have some great ideas in the works but
it's just gonna take a little bit of
time ask my other social videos I pledge
to myself that I'm going to try to power
down as much as I can I'm sure I'll be
checking here and there of course but I
do really want to focus more on
in-person time and the people around me
that are loving and caring and that
includes all of you guys whenever I do
come back I don't know what it is but I
just cannot wait to show you guys a
better person with me I want to end this
video today with two things an apology
and a thank you to my sisters I'm sorry
if I disappointed you and I'm really
starting how to watch all this go down
you saw a side of me that I'm really not
proud of and that I know I need to work
on changing and trust me I will be I
recognize the fact that I haven't always
been the best role model and that sucks
I've tried but I will try way harder but
also to my sisters thank you thank you
for the messages and the tweets and the
emails and the comments that I've
received over the past week making sure
that I was okay and the same thank you
goes out to all the fans that were
concerned but offer constructive
criticism in hopes that I'd be better it
does not go unnoticed and you guys
helped fill my heart with love what I
truly didn't think anything would be
able to the same thank you also goes out
to all my influence her friends that
reached out to me in private to make
sure I was okay during all of this when
I felt like the entire world hated me it
was really comforting to know that there
were other people that understood the
situation that were willing to show
their love I know who you are you know
who you are and one day I'll make sure
that all of you guys know who they are
as well I think that is all I got at
this point thank you for watching if you
meet all the way to the end and in the
spirit of turning something negative
into a positive my sister