hi sisters genius trousered welcome back
to my youtube channel
okay you guys are all very very excited
and I've been waiting patiently for the
iconic collaboration between me and
sister jeffree star it is coming in a
few short seconds but I do have a very
very special sister surprise that I
wanted to announce to you guys before we
actually jump into the video so it is
the fish late December which basically
means this entire month is a Christmas
and I am so beyond excited because if
you guys didn't follow me for a very
very long time you know that last year
over on I think by YouTube Emma
interview I did my holiday give us
ladies where I basically gave away a ton
of makeup and gift cards and it was so
much fun I am so beyond excited to tell
you guys some holiday gimmicks lights
are officially for the holiday season oh
my god you guys I upload two videos a
week every Tuesday and Friday meaning
for every single upload in December all
a video store is going to be a huge
holiday giveaway to a very very special
sister out there and you guys these
prizes are going to have you sister
shucks so as you guys all know I just
released my first-ever makeup
cooperation of course with morphe and it
has been sold out over across the world
I am so beyond grateful for all of your
prizes sisters support so therefore for
the first item in the actual package is
it the James house are for p PR box this
one is nice and big and beefy so when
you open it up you get this beautiful
lenticular of me my face changes look at
how cool that is
messing the entire world and also the
James Charles X Martin cult and full on
34 peace process as well to go along
with the whole unleash your inner artist
theme and also speaking of selling out
the second item in all the game asleep
packages is one of the assisters apparel
artistry and logo hoodies these are so
incredibly cute they are just black and
they have the rainbow embroidered text
on the front these Liberty Sola at only
a few minutes online and I did say that
they are never coming back in stock so
literally these eight sisters will be
the last people on the entire planet to
receive one of these babies
I definitely saved the best for last
because the last item in all eight of
these sister holiday give us ladies is
drumroll please
a brand new of 2018 MacBook Air I really
hope you find
these price packages I will definitely
say in his point the sister step up from
last year's holiday give us ladies I
just want to get back and say thank you
for all that you guys have done for me
and this is a really fun way to do so so
how do you enter if you want to way that
one of these eight holiday give us a
packet is you must do a few things
number one you have to be subscribed to
my youtube channel if you click the big
red button down below come during the
sisterhood it is a pretty lit time and
also click the bell icon so you can make
sure you never miss an upload and always
get it on with acacia also make sure you
were following me to all my other social
media networks including my Instagram
and Twitter up there bull just James
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
the scenes and stuff is James Charles an
extra ask after Charles give this video
a big thumbs up down below to show your
sisters support and finally leave me a
comment down below literally any comment
you can tell me that you love this video
you can tell me what you want for
christmas you can tell me what you're
getting somebody else for Christmas you
can tell me what you want to eat right
now cuz I'm really hungry literally
anything at down below and you will
automatically be entered in it to win
that this giveaway all eight winners
will be chosen and contacted the day
before the next video goes live and will
be chosen completely at random as well
using a random name picker from the
YouTube comments to make sure that it's
fair for everybody involved the prize
package and rules will be remaining the
same through every single giveaway and
I'm gonna make sure to leave all the
information in the description box down
below so please make sure you guys read
it for all the official rules and
regulations not you guys I think that is
all I have it for the holiday gave us
lays I am so excited once again just to
get back to you guys and to see eight
sisters be super super happy for the
holiday seasons and keep in mind this
video going on right here is my first
upload during the month of December so
this is officially the opening to the
holiday give us plays all the rules
apply it to this video so good luck you
guys and I think that is all the
information that I have regarding the
giveaways thank you so much and without
further ado let's up to the video with
sister jeffree star hi sisters welcome
back to my channel
hi how are you
James Charles cheering tonight with a
very very special guy hi Jeffrey stars
in the building I'm so excited for
today's reading video you guys we have
not been together in a minute in a
minute
last time we filmed we were in a hot-air
balloon 3,000 feet up in the sky knows
to know so long lists you we both have
been keeping up all the time but like on
camera hello hi how are ya it's been a
minute girls what they needed
we sure do now I'm excited well let's
just dive into it because we have
there's gonna be a long video yeah it's
no I'm great at it because you just
recently launched something
extraordinary I did your first ever a
collaboration with morphe your first
palette I know I am excited because I
haven't even played with it yet so look
I know I have gotten literally thousands
or even thousands of tweets and messages
play with the James palette la has been
burning to the ground in case anyone
didn't know there was crazy fires so the
fires are over we're about it's home
thank God it's been a really crazy month
so that was all going on not only did I
launch my first ever trial as a
collection yeah also just launched if I
not get this in pure either his PR was
on the way to this house and I took it
and put it in my trunk literally so here
we are we're gonna do a palette swap
today yeah so okay first on my sob story
shadows for which me and Jeffrey that
was our first video we ever done for
today's video we're gonna do something
new and something fun and funky and fun
to see if both of our palettes are
Jeffrey's are approved and James Charles
of yes we're gonna do a little sister I
can't wait you're oh oh wha
no your palette has so many colors I
don't know what I'm gonna do today but
we're gonna head we're gonna figure it
out on the spot I can't wait I'm very
inspired by looking at all this already
exactly what I'm gonna do with that oh
my god okay putting it together in my
head yeah we obviously have no makeup on
today so we're gonna do a little
checkerboard with us and we'll see our
re are each other's palettes are each
other's palettes approved oh okay
probably
[Music]
so I haven't seen you in a minute a lots
happened you've moved we both launched
palace
everything's things are crazy you didn't
used to meet and greets like the world
is just they can't handle it it's sister
now it's sister doubt it hasn't crazy
like I have been obviously I mean you
know we've been talking about like this
launch for a very very long yes we're
like a super helpful advocate and friend
to me during the whole process so you've
kind of been involved with that that's a
beginning it's hard to like know a
secret and like keep it in yeah just be
so excited because yeah I've known about
this obviously for a while you guys and
it's just been so cool to watch James
like think of it create it execute it do
the shoots the ad campaigns everything
it's been just so fun I've been sitting
on this for so long now so it feels so
good until I finally put out well it's
been interesting it's been a wild ride
right okay watching some of these
reviews and stuff of people just talking
about it like both positive and negative
it's like a really really overwhelming
oh yeah I want to ask you about that oh
so someone that started right away right
that has created makeup it's so curious
to someone when they finally put
something out you're like what has been
the biggest struggles I guess besides
seeing reviews I don't to say the
biggest things went Ruggles because for
the most part all the reviews have been
so positive
and they've it they really have
literally like the whole point of the
campaign was to only shoot an artist as
I said 800,000 times last month but like
I love that looks that I've been seeing
people create are like blowing my mind
yeah oh my god even on the way here that
crazy yeah oh my god after this game ago
painting yes I've seen so many artists
that I've like loved and looked up to
test out the palette and just do the
coolest things with it and like I
literally sure to cry like looking
through
Just Cause like I mean like that's
exactly what I want it like I feel are
inspired and they're really going into
that's what I'm fairly gonna see in
their view if you would really look at
the palette and I'm inspired and I'm
like yes that is what I wanted overall
the sentiment has been nothing but like
amazing what's been hard is like
obviously I worked on this for a very
very long time and I'm super confident
out of like the product that we put out
but of course there's always many people
who don't like it and who want to
criticize which is fine because
everybody has a right to their opinion
but yeah it's really really frustrating
when I feel as though at least I've been
pretty transparent with like the
ingredients and what kind of can't be
used in different techniques that I
think work best that a horse has just
been like people love to make up like
stories and it's kind of hard because we
need when you own a brand or when you
pet a product you don't want it to seem
like you can't take criticism criticism
is great I love that that's how I've
learned it improved along the way but I
have seen some people making a blatant
lies I don't know if you want to address
that I mean I'm open about it like just
as a consumer I just think have kind of
upset seeing people not be honest I
guess or like just saying something for
attention well I think like the whole
press penguins thing has been really
quite a learning experience for both me
and the morphe team as well like okay I
obviously don't do makeup production
ever I don't have a company and my
channel is not reviews it's not testing
all new products ever it's literally
just like I'm gonna throw this look I
hope yes nicer news once in a while in a
blue moon right yeah exactly so for me
when I was working with the team and
wanted to create a really super matte
and pigmented rainbow palette I learned
that a lot of the shades could not be
firm elated as typical actually doesn't
know how to be considered press penguins
and yes dad because that's like the way
that you get those formulas to work and
our sleep blend out which definitely do
take a little bit of more extra love and
care what you have to
percent products but when I was filling
my attend million special video a few
days ago I made a reference to the knock
that's like the palette is made for
artists if you were trying to create a
watercolor painting you would never put
water clubs on campus or you've never
put kerlick paint or oil paint on
whatever because it would through if
something is formulated a certain way
and somebody's telling you hey this
works best this way it really blows my
mind that people like don't want to hear
that and instead they're yeah oh my god
like yours quaint with excuses like the
product just socks it's like no every
product has an instruction whether it's
this bottle or this sponge there's less
instructions over someone's giving you
advice you know you should take it right
it's not mandatory like you can still
put watercolor on campus you can so put
oil paint on watercolor paper it's just
not gonna look as good as it could if
you follow the recommended instructions
you know so just dealing with that has
been really eye-opening for me because
of course like I want to be as educated
as it possibly can when it comes to my
followers purchasing a palette because
my name is on it but at the same time
like I'm not a scientist already
learning and educating myself the entire
time there was obviously a few people
that made videos about it I'm like why
on different tangents stuff like
different staining which oh my god mark
can we talk about that I guess do you
want to yeah I don't think it's a bad
thing and I think it's cool that I'm
actually here because the blood sugar
palette that I created YUM earlier this
year has been a huge hit it's sold
astronomical but half the palette or
pressed pigment yeah psyche Lee talked
about this in the video I did not so I
okay a lot of tweets be like oh my god
James doesn't care about his consumers
Jeffery always cares he always lists
everything and I'm like you guys did
everything I did I'm also like Jeffrey's
been doing this on his channel for a
year he does this every single video
I've never done this before so it's like
so people were upset that you didn't
fully go into detail by or why so I got
I'm in full disclosure half the
polonaise pressed pigments I was very
clear about that and very open and
honest about that you'd have to use
certain techniques and products if you
want it to perform the best and because
of the fact that there
past payments by FDA standards a lot of
them technically are not I say yes but
that being said I abuse every sing one
of them on my eye and I've never had an
issue almost all my friends are almost
all my friends are but some people do
have sensitive skin and sages eyelids
yeah and it will stain some people I've
got insane by every single think I've
ever used things like that I don't care
what brand it is
every single thing I said I wouldn't
stay insane but I've never been
effective but the reality is some people
do have sensitive skin and can have
allergic reactions but yes it's up to
the consumer to of course read the
directions if you're allergic to
something
check the box before putting it on yeah
because everybody has different
allergies and different skin they do it
can be tricky but I think you just got
to read the box right I think that I
don't like here's what I think from
someone that is an onlooker and as a
friend I don't like when people try to
make it seem like you are out to do
something that you're not like you are
out to stay in everyone's limbs and not
tell anyone I'm like oh my god it's just
a ridiculous like and I don't want to
say that it's common sense because not
everyone is gonna be aware that's my
mistake because I obviously wouldn't
make up for a very very long time and I
said many times that I formulate this
palette for my fellow artists for people
to travel with for people to take with
them and be able to create literally
right but at the same time I was
watching a few videos and a lot of
people pointed out I do have a very very
diverse audience a few demos of makeup
but also have literally never put it on
and just watch my videos we want to
support you and try yes so I may not I
will admit that it I shouldn't have said
that it was common sense because I guess
it's really not but in my hat because I
do this every single day and I've always
been standard just like of course my
eyeshadows could stain sometimes but I
know I understand but not everyone knows
that right but I also think if you have
bought something from my brand or morphe
before and it's change your live like
you're you know bright shadows are gonna
stay in yeah but it's also a learning
experience I think that people lying and
trying to get attention from it is
annoying but that's part of the game
right right but it I guess it sucks when
you put so much love and care into
something and someone wants to flip it
and like it's bad and you're like girl
what are you talking about so yeah you
know you you get your feelings hurt
you know you get upset because you want
to defend it because you
you know it's like come on if you're
proud of your work that's your baby
exactly just gonna dip into a little
sister setting dinner how has been
driving really good I'm not very good at
that
okay but no crashes yeah good actually
crashing me either
you don't have noticed people here suck
at driving oh my god nobody uses their
turn signals no one can tell you why
because I'm from here I can tell you why
means - because when you do use your
turn signal in LA and you're in traffic
no one will let you work well yeah I've
noticed that too so no one does anymore
because it's like oh when you turn your
signal on in other parts of the world
like Michigan or in you know oh yes
please come into my lane yeah over here
it's like Oh like we're not letting you
win oh so I don't even bother with the
blinker you just gotta cut someone off
or you got to be really safe and keep it
moving people are crazy but I love that
we have matching cars let's see why does
ever I mean I think Tesla's are just so
sick though it's very youtube which is
kind of funny I mean it's literally like
driving an iPhone yes sister star yeah
how for you the James Charles artistry
palette yes and here is the alien
palette BAM both of which by now I'll
turn this videos up they'll be fully
Tommy back in stock in two days now okay
on December 6 yes your alarms let's pray
I have stock left it's set your alarms
okay so this is my first time ever I'm
doing two full first impressions um a
lot of people are gonna say well you're
sitting next to James I already know
just from all my friends using it that
this palette is great I also am NOT
concerned so exactly fine and also you
don't probably I mature enough
like we said criticism is everywhere yes
okay cool so I like to use a Paint Pot
oh my god yeah I need to see you okay
that's funny wait what color
painterly paint really this is not okay
what the hell I mean this is not planned
I always have been formulated to talk
for so long now when I came to promoting
these colors like we talked about
number-one priority with pigmentation
yes am i getting those rainbow mattes to
be super super vibrant which is hard and
if people don't know that in the lab and
in yeah you know the chemists they
really have to work hard to make a
beautiful formula they do it's really
really challenging it was important to
yeah so I'm the type of person I will
say that I'm definitely difficult to
work with because I know what I want and
I will never settle for loss which is
good love that hi I'm Sophie tv-like do
it they're like no we count like no I
want you to do it
yeah then we can't do that like yeah see
well you're gonna do it yeah I think
it's cool cuz maybe you pushed their
boundaries and I did which is kind of
cool I did and like I'm really part of
the finished product and I've heard like
the morphe team is really proud of it as
well good they were and they really are
and I think it's great because you
challenge them and they listen they
could have been like no we're good
sweetie but the fact that they like took
everything you said into consideration
and you leave me buddy vision come to
life that's awesome just like the bass
yeah I love morphe so much say well kind
of look at you feeling I'm feeling a lot
of color do like a red orange yellow and
then what I agree Boober well the other
are okay I mean yeah I'm you know I'm
down I love that I'm really down the
purple first I know I'm gonna grab the
shade of area 51 on my tablet four five
six brush this is from my brush that
more her okay now let's talk about
purple shades they are so hard to make I
know it's funny the purple is the only
pressed pigment in the alien pellet
really yeah blood sugar had like 12 cuz
you know breads are yes yes I don't know
how much I can say but I will say that
the purple shade gave me quite an issue
in black kala and honestly through
formulating the purple is actually how I
figured out that using an eye primer
like paint power or like really how's
what makes it work so much better
I mean use a packet on which I'm saying
the entire time hmm okay where do I
start
why am I feeling like blues and purples
on one eye yeah should I go in at purple
first two I'm gonna go the shady phone
the home now on my m-43 oh my god was
purple lays down really good yeah were
you nervous about this color yeah
horrified
oh my god
is this morphe 433 work I just I want
nothing but perfection like I'm such a
perfectionist I like I I refuse to do
anything that was like very scary going
into it I'm just gonna blend this out
right above that purple edge I'm just so
sad you have like a product out has
everyone asked you if you want to do
your own makeup brand when everybody's
an Aussie what snacks I'm like ready
hello three at least three seconds to
breathe I know right when you launch
something everyone will be like what's
next what's next really a girl let me
breathe for a second for me I definitely
don't think that I want my own brand
right now at least for right now but
honestly I don't even know about the
future I'm not that interested about
development to be honest with you it's
just got something like this palette for
me was like my main project that I'm
working on for so long and I'm super
passionate about and I've had an idea
for forever okay but I don't really have
that many other ideas up my sleeve that
I'm like oh this needs to be somebody I
love that you're not just doing it to do
it there's a lot of people have you in
your position we're just kind of like
okay well let's just wing it and let's
just go for and you're like no honey
there are all ways that I obviously can
make a living and make money and I just
don't want to put my name on products
just about anyone products like I refuse
to do that I don't need to have them
very blast of the following fan base
that supports whatever I do yeah so I
love those wait and see for right now
I'm really focused on sister's apparel
and I do have some other things in the
works as well but 30 it's not a
cosmetics brand okay yay I love that
you're actually here next to me so you
can tell me the shades oh it's a single
yes I love single
bring me mmm very not me but I love the
color hey minx brother is single and
mainly straight
alright after Ali huh and he just moved
here work I am designing this outer
crease region I'm really sure what I'm
doing but it's looking a pretty so far
what was your inspiration behind the
alien palette I've been called an alien
forever my nickname in high school was a
little alien was it really yeah cuz I
shaved my eyebrows in 10th grade so
matches yes so for the photo you did
yeah so the first imagine that the first
day I show up
no brows everyone was like Hello what
the heck is going on around here so
alien just kind of stuck and I just love
extraterrestrial things I think there's
obviously I believe in aliens I'm right
here
what they're not the balloon right but I
really wanted to perfect and have like
no kinks in my palate like perfect the
Greens just kind of you're like a whole
different story and I really want to do
a different shape I think I'm done
rectangles for all my palettes thus far
right stick in a while that's very
something different you're the packaging
is seconding I love it thank you
artistry is so ready that's what he was
on your leg literally yesterday yeah so
artistry is made to be like a topper
color so it performs best overtop of
like a black or a darker but we're like
a blue like it's meant to really bring
out those other shades
okay there's two shades like that in the
poet actually artistry and this
literally some people were sparked and
being like oh my god they're not that
pigmented but that's the point
actually they're supposed to be used
okay which ones that one this one this
one literally is bad it's literally
literally that's like peachy pink so you
can either use it for a highlighter if
you use it lightly which I love it looks
so stunning or what I like actually
using a lot of it and blending it really
blends your powder and blush together so
I see okay that's why all that later I
really like this color that which all
home color oh baby is like a weird Bobby
Brown yeah I'm gonna take more area 51
right now I'm gonna put it on this other
ain't gonna hurt he wants to do black in
the center with artistry over it
oh yeah I just dip into that once hi I
love a good black it's really pigmented
I was the drama around the palette to
the swatches oh my god I don't put on
eye shadow with my fingers unless it's
like a really crazy metallic so it's
like why does what swatches matter so
much
I think we're getting away from that
hopefully but it's like girl oh my God
look at that black looks like a liner
already look at that let me keep it like
that but some sure that's oh hi not
second hang okay I love that we love an
accident
look my birth oh sorry mom team okay I'm
gonna cut my crease okay I'm loving
where this is going oh right now we're
gonna dip into playground oh it's such a
right below look at this on my brush
like hi I'm still cutting my crease for
summers mm-hmm
I'm just gonna oh excuse me oh my god
she's gonna lightly dip into here all
right what are we feeling oh options
here I wanna take the shade alien online
em two to four and put that here oh wow
that's so pretty
Green's on you green is one of my least
favorite colors but we're living for her
to that yeah it looks really good yeah
I'm not really into greens either in
house like you know well I'm gonna make
it something that's more challenging for
me you know yeah we're more about oh my
god Alex stunning I second I guess
sooner just hop off this edge because
I'm gonna add the other shade in there
but I need them to like blend together
ain't gonna grab some one probe well I
can already tell this is really nice
mm-hmm
nobody uses to watch the other the green
in the purple oh wow probe
no just getting what you say Gary 51 and
blend that together I hate what I do cut
creases and the colors are all like
seamlessly mm-hmm
nothing I see more rather than a cut
crease with a blunt line oh I know I
know
okay well I'm taking playground and
slowly finessing it on my lash line I'm
gonna grab some a UFO now on the same
exact brush I cleaned it off of course
okay I'm literally diving into hello wow
that sky blue metallic is stunning I'll
go down the maunder glass mmm [ __ ] look
at that I love it rock kitty you know as
cool as that makeup actually makes me so
happy and excited like I was yes such a
long day and I couldn't wait to come
over here just play missed you the most
same girl coax chair Thanks I'm gonna
talk some area 51 okay no we're gonna
[Music]
miss Cola yes yes Wow see I don't want
to use black so to smoke out
that's sick probably not least I'm gonna
layer on Pluto okay into my inner corner
yes she's an inner corner color for sure
is this like really bright yes it's like
BAM oh okay yeah she's bright bright
when I go on to my problem oh look at
that that is Wow mmm-hmm
I mean I think it's time to go into
you're kidding like right now you're
kidding us they really knew I don't I
don't know it's so annoying I'm like
it's not gonna work
we're actually real friends so
sorry right isn't that sickening yes I'm
living and no my launch video talking I
wanted to make a full read because again
the most matte red so exists in the
market and I got a tax okay why I was
like the rabbit blood sugar is metallic
it's sickening yeah it's like was how it
mad this is this shade is not in blood
sugar okay I made it it's not it you
guys I love the blood sugar palette I
was like this is not me shading Geoffrey
but people want I know
like why stop when I designed it that
was the one shade that was the first
thing that I told her I wanted to do I
was like I want a matte red and they're
like yeah no it looks amazing
look at that hi okay I suppose I turned
out this is like spoil that sister James
approve yeah yes because of the shade hi
how are ya right this one and let's see
I'm doing bump Depina both so little
rusted a little 5 180 is so pretty Wow
she's like bright orange okay this one
is tuned right yes yes tuned oh whoa
wait a minute
hosting we love a good synchronization
oh wow I be there she is good she sure
is
oh look on camera oh I'm so sorry I love
what you just dip into something and it
works right away yeah that's
now that I expect anything less from me
but garlic yeah I was harsh she did that
that one went a lot too cuz that one is
a doctor my mother Chris TV oh okay
perfect yes mom
it was so cute my parents oh we have
like a we have two local malls to us
actually and they my mom like went to
both cuz she wanted to take a picture of
the display and altar and there she was
like that is so cool so she was bad so
yeah that is so awesome
my mom my dad actually went together and
they just posted on Twitter cuz I was so
excited yeah and even realize laughter
but in the photo what they're both
pointing to the shades that were named
after that oh you know I did um hello in
here yes
what should I do over here with the
yellow either so good the bright gold oh
wait it's like singing it okay so like I
said earlier this launch has been
obviously exciting for me but it's also
something new that I I've never dealt
with and there's definitely been
challenges with it and I've gotten upset
and stuff and I'm trying my best to
really handle myself maturely and be
professional because that my name is
attached obviously we were talking cuz
as soon as I announce that you obviously
wanted to film with it which was so cool
and meant the world to me yes I was like
give me that right now yeah it's not
obviously plans change when you had to
come homes we weren't able to get it to
you right away yes I know you've been
texting me updates all the time keeping
up with the launch keeping up with their
sales and stuff and like tax me a little
bit stuff like as someone who was a
friend of mine and has been watching at
all but also someone who was a brand
owner and does this all the time do you
have any honest advice for me like what
I do something else in the future
because I'm obviously learning a lot
about launches and like what I can and
shouldn't say or how I should react and
stuff yeah and opposite this has been
quite a learning experience but I'd love
to hear like what okay and put you wrong
you'll hear some Realty yes so I had to
learn this the hard way
it's like if something ever really does
happen or someone really does have an
issue is to really hear them out right
and not get so offended or on the
defense so ready for some real tea so
this happened when my highlighters first
launched my delivery people dropped and
higher palates we're talking like 30,000
units they dropped it off of the
forklift without ever telling anyone
know every highlighter was shattered so
imagine you don't know this right don't
know until later when all the units are
shipped out so when the first few people
were getting them I thought people were
just like coming from me like yeah oh
well your products are horrible right
like I had such success with liquid lips
and lip scrub so when I brought the
highlighter I was so proud of it and
people were getting broken but it was
only one shade the one shade of so
someone made a video really going in on
me like this whole thing was shattered
they're awful that it uh and I clap back
instead of like listening to the
complaint cuz I was like there's no way
my formula is amazing like you're just
trying to lie for attention yeah I
should have never done that and I
learned my lesson to really respect the
customer listen to them but it's hard
cuz we talked about being defensive and
like and I was it was new it was
literally my like one of my long yeah
first very first launch so to have it go
and have something go wrong it was
devastating so I had to do my research
and I had to really you know learn well
I had this like whole likes Campbell
thing happen I did definitely react
right away yeah annoyed by it and
there's been so many people being like
oh my god he's never had a real job so
he doesn't know how to talk to people
every time we know I did work retail
beforehand I know how to talk to me -
yeah make you talk to people I things
like I think huh oh my god first I raise
my guard let's hack up I think that in
the social media days when it comes to
influencers there's a very very
unrealistic expectation that influencers
I don't have said like a lot of people
just think like oh we don't have
feelings and that we're all just gonna
like if somebody's screaming in our face
we're just supposed to get over people
we're selling Nirvana
right we all really do have feelings
right if someone's
lying or like saying something I don't
know it's hot it's attached I really is
I'm definitely learning you know I
really wanna make people happy with this
I put my all into it and probably my
name is attached so I want to do like
what's right for everybody thank you
yeah I think going forward I mean you're
you're you're in a great position I mean
your palates amazing like just playing
with it now I'm like I mean hi baby did
that really quickly switching gears here
I'm going to dip into face and bring
light for a little problem because girl
and I love what you did the bigger pans
in the middle it's amazing always run
out of these and people are like okay
now I need to buy a whole new palette
yeah so you were like not today sweetie
the whole point in the pail is that you
can let me create any luck with that
obviously my favorite looks to do are
the rainbow lots but all the glam shades
are in there for all my everyday people
that don't want to do that - yes all but
you can do whatever you want
I loved your soft like little brown yeah
you can literally create any luck with
that that includes warm tones smokey
eyes although I wanted to be used for
the rainbow clothes obviously to unleash
people's inner artist obviously I know
that a lot of my fans and followers are
gonna want to do everyday looks I can't
blame them and it's not like I'm gonna
you know what I mean they forced him to
do color I know that no matter how many
calls did put in that's still gonna be
the most used shades so I really wanted
to add the bigger pants and their so
they're there
well I think I live for it so hi oh wow
white in the water land with the blue
yeah mm-hmm are we both doing mascara
okay I'm gonna pop on a lily lash in the
style of Miami of course okay Little
Miami 1500 we have a code I mean I'm
using Little Ashes in style was lela
lela when are we getting Co Jane's for
cosmetics oh you wanna be the only
lutely okay do we all need that comment
down below one lashes I just really do
want her to say really
oh wow yeah Miami's with the alien look
with every look I have literally hate
Klingon lashes there's nothing I hate
more my entire covert an insulated anger
beat anger and staying her over at dawn
waiting over here on this inner quiet
almost their lashes are on looking at so
fabulous Wow about my living okay I kind
of live that you did that by the way
okay I'm gonna sort over to my pal
quickly okay and what are we dipping
into I'm gonna go a little bit I'm gonna
take these birds to highlight my combo
of face and ring light is like a little
I know already highlighted but just to
be even extra wet dream supreme frost on
top the camera might break after this
[Music]
every day I'm like oh you went a little
goes a long way layering ours together
was like supernova all right we are
highlighted oh okay so I want to mix us
together a little bit because that is
looking a little harsh sister saturate
so I'm gonna yeah I'm gonna kind of my
e4 that's my favorite blush brush game
did the shade literally for my palate
this is what I was texting texting so
that's telling Jeffery bar earlier I
really like this shade it to mix
together the blush and highlight
it's like a metallic oh yeah she's there
what did you do this one yes oh okay
right yeah it's like really pretty huh
what Silas doesn't really show up that
wall in camera but anniversary I didn't
see the pink shaft what are we gonna do
for the lives probably just a nude for
me I don't know about yes so we have
like a lilac moment or straight-up nude
maybe nude actually uh-huh I think one
time I'm gonna do a little glitter lip
mo and Tom and alien tears well I really
like this lip combo yeah I know this is
really really pretty for my skin tone
[Laughter]
we're done a little sister spray I'm
feeling really good and really fresh Sam
I'm really really good and
simultaneously also fresh I feel really
good I can't believe it
I'm like I'm actually really stoked I
got to play with your palette with you I
think it's pretty cool I'm in love with
it even I know everyone's got it
oh you're sitting next to him you're
just gonna say that no like I'm
genuinely just so proud of you this is
such a sick moment of course and just to
see it from an idea to in my hands is so
major so congratulations thank you
sister um I live for it I I love all the
colors to be honest obviously I played
with a lot of brights today but girl
James did that all right I'm gonna say
it for you the James Charles ex morphe
brushes palette is Jeffrey star approved
BAM a breath of fresh air
okay that means always yes a friend and
also a cosmetics owner that I have
looked up to
through literally everything I've told
you a million times and thank God
the alien palette my first thought I was
so excited by the greens and the purple
because those colors do not happen in
palettes a lot and at first looking at I
will say I was like I was really trying
to rock a tree like what look so I want
to create like yeah definitely is a
little bit of a trickier color scheme or
not the everyday makeup where yes a lot
like the awareness and you like playing
with colors these like yeah they blend
out beautifully the purple is so good
I'm obsessed with this purple thing and
like this color scheme hi how are ya oh
yeah officially turned out so beautiful
and the Haley palette is sister James a
pretty yes bob says today I believe this
is being uploaded on December 4 okay and
after much long awaiting lots of angry
emails lots of angry tweets about this
sister selling finally back it's coming
back in two days
on December 6 yeah it'll be online at
more Fiat calm at 8 a.m. Pacific
Standard Time do not forget to use go
chains for tempers on your purchase
don't forget it baby anything and I'm
gonna say it for you I know how it is
and people sell out a lot of people do
nothing it's shady but some people do
like fake sellouts oh yeah like I'm very
close with morphe you guys know my brand
is sold in all their stores so almost
tell James candidly I hear a lot of
information behind the scenes and every
unit is sold or not holding back they're
not faking it they are gone which is off
the shelf lying
it's so exciting to me I cannot wait so
it is officially all the guys who wanted
to grab it so get ready
two days December 6 hop on it baby yeah
well thank you for having me over
thank you so much thank you for coming I
really hope you guys enjoy this video
today this palace talk was so bad you
know it doesn't know Bob oh my god we
love being on cloud I could be loved
being a first in its kind
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up and down below come
show your sisters support and love it
means and so so so much to me
also click that big red subscribe button
down below come join the sisterhood I
don't even know how I know is not
slowing down oh yeah
so fast and take you guys better love
and support it also click that Bell icon
so you and get a notification every time
I upload a brand new video
BAM if you like to follow me and I make
up thirteen follow me in sermons but oh
they're both the same Charles my stop
talking seems like a shame Charles the
lecture has after Charles he's Jeffrey's
are everywhere everywhere good I love
that you remind me like when they're
finishing a commercial maybe yeah I love
about all the facts
this video is sister shadow goes to
sister Kylie thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting I love you
literally it's so so so much and at home
willing to be the next videos the sister
shout out don't forget to always read to
my new videos and they go live on
Twitter all right sisters well I think
that is only half our today's a brand
new video thank you so much for watching
we love it and we will see you in the
next one
[Music]