hi sisters change Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel you
guys I am very very pumped for today's
video because I am just gonna be sitting
down and playing good makeup which is
saying that I have not gotten to do in a
very very long periodically time a lot
of periodically time
I really hope everyone had an amazing
week I can concretely say that I did
have an amazing week and I have not been
able to say that in a very very long
time and I'm just super super happy I'm
in a really good mood and I'm so excited
to be filming today for today's video
judging by the title we are doing a pink
kitty drink idiot makeup look and we're
going to sit down chit chatting me and
just do it find a makeup block this
morning you guys know I start off my day
every single day when they Starbucks
pinky drink it me not sponsored but I
can't believe it hasn't met at this
point and I also had to put on right
pink kitty drink edid this hoodie that
was actually custom made for you by two
of my favorite bands Zoe and Brooke
shadow cheese guys love these at
absolute most and also a few days ago I
broke the nail which was so great but my
nail tech came over really quickly and
gave me a new set and for once we
decided to not do a nude but instead we
went with these pink drink nails which
are literally oh oh what you're
literally is so cute like are you
kidding me there's little stop oh stop
and we decided to do these pink drink
nails which are literally it's so cute
they look like the little strawberries
are embedded into my fingers just like
an actual oh oh my god just like an
actual pink drink from Starbucks I think
they turned out so so cute I do want to
give up proper credit to my friend
Leslie and her no time crazy Calderon
for inspiring these nails that did at
first and I just wanted to recreate them
and that keeps my don't talk Queenie for
doing them anyway clearly at this point
everyone knows that the obsession with
me and pink drinks has gone very very
far and somehow after being on YouTube
and doing makeup for almost four years I
have never actually done a pink drink
makeup look so if I could say would be
the perfect time to do so to just sit
down and play with makeup also while I
was thinking of ways that I could do it
this pink drink makeup look I remembered
that what my favorite accounts of all
time shine shadows so check them out
actually did a pink drink makeup look on
my face on his arm oh my god they're
gonna be so much better tried to
recreate that look today but obviously
add my own twist with all that being
said I grab a snack or grab your pink
Annie Trinity and let's hit with some
I have so many things that I want to
talk to you guys about today it started
with some puppet updates the I thought
11 a Meyer card for iPhones and so much
more so let's just have a fun time and
jump right
[Music]
alright guys just going right into my up
dragon a beauty a color corrector just
to get rid of these absolutely
disgusting five oclock shadows that for
some reason that my body is still home
producing then I'm just gonna jump right
in and get started with my foundation of
course do you guys know I love the Too
Faced Born This Way I'm gonna mix
together the shade up pearl add a little
bit of warm beige and mix that together
just to try to get as close as a back as
I can possibly get all right you guys
there's so many things that I want to
talk to you about today I started off
with of course my update on being an
official mother of a puppy oh my gosh
you are at the last two weeks have been
so hectic and I know that you guys have
been complaining that I have not been
posting as much on my stories or really
on anything and that is because being a
puppy at Mother has taken up all my life
and I've never been happier in my entire
life having him is literally been so
much fun so far and it's also really
really helped my overall like mood and
happiness which is obviously amazing
because I want to get back to being a
super super happy and working really
really hard and honestly he's helping
with that which I could not be more
excited about the response on the first
video is so incredibly positive which by
the way if you guys have not yet watched
make sure you go check it out in case
you missed it we adopted a puppy into
the family and it was amazing we
documented the entire journey of
adopting him on YouTube so make sure you
click right up here if you want to see
that video I also want to say thank you
for everybody who's giving a really
really helpful tips about training a
puppy
in the comments because it was really it
really appreciated like I said in the
video I did at train at my puppy back
home when he grew up and my editor who
lives me Louis also trained his puppy
but of course it's always helpful to
learn and new tips and tricks from
anybody who's went through the same
situation
and anybody who may learn more we
honestly want him to be raised in the
best way possible but it's really
important that he learns quickly and
it's very very obedient because we do
a crazy life who want him to be happy
and healthy in terms of the training it
is going up really really well so far
thank God knock out what I hope it stays
that way it but we are about two weeks
in and he's pretty much fully a
potty-trained which we are so pumped
about I don't know how he managed to
pick it up so fast but he is such a
smart little puppy a lot of my close
friends and family have came over to him
which has been that so much fun as well
and he is my mom the absolute best
behavior with everybody I just like
don't know how we lucked out so much but
he is probably like one of the most calm
but most fun but most of all behaved
dogs I've ever seen in my entire life
and I'm really sad about it
sisters say my sister's every tether we
try to pick him up he literally just
like collapses in our arms and will fall
asleep too he's such a little shoe tell
him your name you guys after going
through it literally hundreds and
hundreds of different name suggestions
we've finally picked out the perfect one
for this little baby or right here I
want to thank you guys so much for
commenting on the last video and giving
so many suggestions so many people says
actually amazing names I love that
everyone wanted me to name him an angel
that'll because a little bit of a
nickname but we finally picked out the
perfect one we were ready to tell them
should we tell them your name you guys
welcome to the family officially you
guys we've officially beside your name
have Fenig Anna but fan for short so fan
unless he's in trouble and it's been a
given I think it is just so cute and
like fun and very very playful I'm not
gonna hold over here too long because
he's literally falling asleep in my arms
this is what he does all the time but
then again thank you for joining the
family hope you're happy here Oh a big
yawn I'm gonna go put him down it is bad
because he's literally falling asleep in
my arms right now but thank you for
making a little bit of appearance and if
you guys want to follow him on his a
puppy Germany you can officially call
him on his bring your Instagram account
at Finn Charles all right you guys you
all better head over to Instagram right
now and go fall a little fat but for now
and it's time to move on to our next
have makeup routine I was gonna I think
I'm hello I'm just going to get my face
[Music]
whoa hey quick spreads of the war be up
in seconds having spray that's my
all-time favorite setting spray use
cocaine with the firt time for soccer
practice it's been a while since I've
actually gotten a chance to say that and
now we're gonna move into up contouring
and for that I'm actually gonna grab at
the brand new dragon at beauty face
palette this is Nikita's face which i
think is so cool i ops it web cess of
this packaging and this is a brand new
product coming out and I want to support
my sister so I'm just going to a contour
in and do some blush and highlight using
this palette I think it is very very
beautiful I'm gonna grab my morphe M 405
and dip into the shade femme and let's
test this out so there's two other
colors in here for contouring we have a
femine also is heard we love a good cert
so that is the soft contour color and
Serge is for really deepening out some
of those areas looks really pretty on my
skin tone okay love this so far no
chisel out the chin of course the shade
femoris working out really really nicely
and I honestly like how this color looks
on my skintone quite a lot I'm gonna go
to my better go to mo I'm gonna go up
into a but one two five zero brush from
morphe which is a little bit of a bigger
fluffy brush and dip into the shade of
Serge this one looks like it is a very
very pivot that I'm gonna be very
careful about this but I'm gonna use its
color to do you bit up the cheekbone
okay that is very very parented I'm
gonna bomb that out in a second I like
how that's close deeper but still has
the neutral undertone so it doesn't look
absolutely crazy
I do however think this is a little bit
dark for my skin tone this is looking a
little bit intense so I'm not going to
choose any more of that but I think for
a medium to tan skin tones that color is
going to be absolutely perfect oh we
thought so looks good Isaiah chiseled
contour if I ever did see one I'm gonna
grab my nose a contouring brush and grab
a little bit of a femme again and we're
going to snatch this sister schnoz that
sentence was ridiculously annoying sorry
about that color looks really good on my
nose contour oh my god okay that looks
really really dope I'm really excited
about this now for blush of enduring by
ea4 brush and debated the shade BB a
girl which is the more pinky rose tone
color in the palette normally I would go
with tea girl and I'm very very excited
to try this but census as a more a pink
team to makeup look today I figure this
one the match a lot better and there's
gonna pop this on my cheeks that's a
really pretty blush color why don't I
just like that's a really pretty that's
a really pretty blush color no another
quick spritz of Mya
satya spray and i was gonna pop out a
little bit of a highlight so i'm gonna
grab these shade fantasy which is this
thick reflective a pink shade in a
little bit of a silicone as well Nikita
you are absolutely crazy and just add a
little bit of this on the cheekbone oh
wow that is really really pretty I like
that it's a little bit more of a subtle
glow you can definitely layer it up but
also it's like really pretty but has a
little bit of a larger particle size so
it's more glittery than just like a
normal glow from within type of
highlighter that is really beautiful I
promise that this video was not
sponsored by an Aikido dragon or a
dragon video but I won't be texting
after this and sending her an invoice so
now that that is all autumn's better
grab a little bit of my setting powder
on my saying about blending it sponge
and just bait decides when those and
under up my eyes just to bring back some
of that brightness and now I'm just
gonna quickly go do my brows off-camera
at same exact way as always use my
Anasazi up brow products bad my roots
have grown in a thank God at the lodge a
little better to who my hair although
this is looking a little bit of a mess
and is about ready for a change as well
so I'll be right back you guys is acid
acidic oh wow
that's worse than my farts you have to
admit that as worse than my farts and
not a lot of things are worse than my
farts alright you guys we are back in
both eyebrows are now complete they are
not looking in the past I literally do
my eyebrows for 45 minutes straight
because I could not get them even it is
one of those days but you know what
we're gonna hopefully redeem ourselves
with the eye shadow portion so for this
look tonight we're using it two
different palettes of course the James
house next morphe palette but also the
Anasazi beverly hills nor vina volume at
three palette that just came out these
colors are so beyond study and I feel
like this screen of this great and this
pink will be really really good for
creating at these Starbucks pinky
chickadee colors alright you guys so to
start off we're gonna grab a tiny little
angle brush and dip into the shade of
course pinky drink Kitty and at the
James house
power I'm gonna give that a little bit
of a spritz of the prepping settings
right just so it is a little bit more
sticky and I'm gonna start sketching out
my winged liner that is looking nice and
sharp amazing obviously you're gonna
clean that up with concealer in a second
anyway with whatever's excess on my
brush is going to use this concealer to
cut that wing and then with a tiny
little liner brush I'm going to go in
and start sketching out the little
triplets going on those are so cute I
love the little pink drinks flying liner
normally for a colored liner like this I
would normally use a liquid lipstick but
I could not find a color like a pink a
teaching kitty and my actual collection
despite the fact that it's like a light
pink all my nudes are more peachy tones
so the shadow will work just as well I
know this looks ridiculous right now but
give it a few seconds it's gonna come
together I'm now gonna grab a tiny
little a liner brush and dip into the
shade a little bit of a daddy from my
palette and a little bit of a one from
the verbena palette pretty much makes
like the exact
Starbucks a green I'm just gonna do the
same exact thing this person is a little
bit of prep and set I'm going to use
this color to make a double wing now
that is all laid out and I got my Tom
Florida black eyeliner and very very
very carefully outline the pink section
there are a lot of areas that I still
tried to get better and make up every
single time that I do it but the
absolute one thing that I am so bad at
that I wish I was better at is wholly an
eyeliner study I cannot make an even
straight line for the life of me it is
so beyond annoying okay that looks
honestly good great okay now let's do a
line in between the pink and the green
so close okay let's try and cover that
up in the meantime let me add some
little white highlights
[Music]
okay that looks kind of good let's go
ahead and move on to the lower lash line
I'm gonna grab those same a little bit
of a pink shadows on my little liner
brush and put them in my waterline and
in this run he actually added a really
long pink drip underneath the eye which
i think is super super cool so I'm going
to go ahead and do that as well and the
lower quarter this I hear he has like
this red part which I believe is like
the strawberry guts for lack of a better
term because they have the freeze dried
strawberries in the actual drink so I'm
going to grab a red liquid lipstick and
try to do that eyes Wow I'm gonna add a
little bit of a reddit shadowing on the
drip just like in the original photo
maybe another little dollop of white
just for highlights
I feel like this little dollop should
have an outline it doesn't in the
original photo but I'm gonna add this
little red inner corner light or thing
that we have going on because that is
there's no photo and it looks super chic
and now it's a little bit of a green and
the lower lash line this is strawberry a
little bit of you're kidding from the
palette yep that's what okay now that
actually you can make a strawberry on my
eyebrow this I am concerned about I am
going to rob do you read at first this
the top of the strawberry is usually
pretty flat so let's go ahead and do
that now we can go ahead and safely it
fill this in completely with red should
it be bigger than this yeah yeah oh let
me set that in place using you're
kidding from my palette and a little bit
of c2 from the verbena pellet having a
little bit of a boutique from my palette
I'm going to add a little bit of like a
darker area of the strawberry over here
leaving the side highlighted and
I'm going to grab my liner brush which
is right here and add some white and I'm
gonna add in the seeds back so it should
actually be a pure white blob at first
now what the red once again let's add
some seeds back in there let's go ahead
and add these stem of the strawberry now
a darker green for some shadow using it
daddy from the pallet to shade this in
wow that's so much harder to do that I
thought it was gonna be oh my gosh that
looks okay
it looks okay but it's time to move on
first or now it's time for the other eye
and this eye is going to be the actual
pink train okay let's all in the drink
first there we go okay that's actually
that's a good shape
great great great great let's talk about
tick-tock oh my gosh if any you guys
watching this video have a tick-tock
which I'm sure you do first of all
follow me lady's name isn't James
Charles and I am not afraid to admit
that I am officially obsessed the Tech
Talk it is so much fun it is not even
funny do you guys want me to actually
start making tic TOCs please let me know
I literally posted one that was just
like a posing video I wanted to do I
literally started filming a pink drink
like transformation Tech Talk at the
beginning of this video and then got
distracted and forgot so that's really
really great but let me know if you guys
want to see me actually do tic TOCs
because it's kind of fun it's kind of
rushed I mean all my should be a tick
tock clean okay that shape looks great
driving ajh of 41 Russians gonna grab
some a pink Adia drink Adia from the
palette and set that in place now let's
add some little strawberry bits in there
okay so then for these shell guys are
gonna top some of them in and cover them
with a little bit of shadow as well
that way we'll add some and dimension in
and it'll look like some of the shaw
berries or like right up against the
edge of the cup but some are like
actually floating kind of in the middle
of the drink and those would therefore
be like a little bit more cloudy and
then the ones that the edge would look
like bright red if that makes sense and
then whatever's left on that brush was
gonna add in some with nice little like
patches of darker red all around the
drink just for somebody's added
dimension just so doesn't look like
one color like that looks really really
good now taking that drink once again
I'm gonna add in something could you
drink it right over top of this so it
looks like the shower buddies are cloudy
just like I said that looks really
really good okay now with that same
technique I'm gonna add a little bit of
white splotches in the top of the drink
to kind of look like ice cubes but also
the foam that comes to the top when you
first order I think I need a few more
little red splotches in here is taking a
long time I'm gonna take that flat brush
from before that I use to fill in the
pink kitty drink a tea cup and just
clean it off with a little bit of a
makeup wipe and I'm going to dip fully
into the white so I'm gonna add on a
rectangle for the top that'll be the lid
now I'm gonna grab a tiny little brush
and some flash back and set that way in
place that looks so good Wow okay it's
turning out great okay now I want to add
the little bit of like shadows that
basically are like the dividers in the
cup so what I need to do first is a
taste like paint drink okay so I'm gonna
add a shadow below also gonna add a
slight outline to the entire drink now
I'm gonna add my two little dividend
lines in the bottom I'm actually gonna
go to the shade is C 4 and a little bit
of B 3 from the marina pellet to those
because it'll be like a deeper pink
which I think will be good instead of
like a brown yeah yeah oh my god yes and
then one more time for here just buffing
that out using a little bit of a pink
add a trinket Ian let me are gonna miss
Starbucks this is where I'm actually
worried the circle hostel like and here
well I don't really know how I'm gonna
do this with my eyelid fold there well
the original look was cleared on
somebody's arm where an eyelid fold is
not an issue but this is definitely a
problem yeah I guess I could just do the
green circle instead of doing the entire
Starbucks logo this is falling apart
rather quickly
let's leave a little bit out I'm gonna
add the three little lines that are like
D little measuring lines on the side of
the cuff so we're gonna do that we're
here that they're gonna be like in my
actual pupils we're not gonna include
that one okay so I'm gonna add a straw
to this cup just to it match the
original and so the drink is more
recognizable as an actual drink but
y'all know I did not use a plastic
straws my local Starbucks actually has
these reusable lids which is a super
super awesome save the turtles and I
hope you guys are so close to being done
okay now I'm just gonna add it some
green and liner to match the
left-hand-side end with that same red
color for that little rat point just a
little bit of green on the lash line I
am obsessed with all this look is
looking so far I will say and but this
took way way longer than anticipated oh
my god those are the eyes all complete I
decided it was best to not actually
include the Starbucks logo I normally
would be down for the challenge of
drawing it but because of the eyelid
fold it it's really just not going to
work her head will be flopping all
around in there and it's just not gonna
be good I'm gonna leave it the way it is
I might even Photoshop about the dancer
and picture who knows regardless I'm
gonna behad on some mascara oh my god
forgot the word I'm gonna grab the a
brand new Lily lashes ox ox ox mascara
it is really really bobby guys oh my
good you know what I also want to talk
about with you guys okay Mario Kart tour
for the iPhone oh my god after literally
in 3 million years of waiting Nintendo
finally released Mario Kart for iPhone
and I've never been more excited for
anything literally in my entire life I
have an absolute Mario Kart scene it was
my all-time favorite game as a kid this
is before my minecraft era
we go home from school every single day
and stand on my base and play at Mario
Kart Wii and I was so good at it I don't
know if it's embarrassing or impressive
to a bit but I literally used to hold a
few different world records in the game
I can't believe two submitted that on
camera when it comes to makeup I would
definitely say like I'm pretty good at
it I mean it is my job I do all the time
I come up with some pretty beautiful
looks but there's so many artists that I
genuinely think are like a million miles
ahead of me and that's awesome because
it gives me room to always grow and
practice more and more but Mario Kart on
the other hand I can't even be humble
about it you guys Mario Kart I'm so good
like I'm I'm truly a queen of Mario Kart
and I've been waiting four years now for
them to finally bring it up for the
iPhone and it is here I downloaded a few
minutes ago for pre-order and last night
it finally became available and I've
been playing it non-stop and I have
quite a lot of thoughts okay on a
positive note the graphics and
performance of the actual app absolutely
stunning it looks so it I've honestly
never even seen an iPhone game with like
that level of quality it looks visually
phenomenal the controls on the other
hand they just make no sense when I was
first playing it orion's we have that
meme of the Kardashians episode when
Khloe is driving the car around and then
it cuts to the clip of the van just
floating around in the sky
because that's what I literally felt
like what's going on with my cart no
matter which way I turn toward my
fingers I would go the complete wrong
way so steering is definitely a little
bit of a challenge and I hope that they
kind of improve the controls as an avid
fan I'm definitely a little bit
disappointed but I'm definitely looking
forward to hearing what you guys have to
say about it I am a very very Punk for
them to open up multiplayer mode in a
few days from now when it doesn't up
releasing I will probably post my friend
call on my Twitter so you guys can all
add me and then I can it whoop all of
your asses in the game and regards of
whatever I think about it I'm still
clearly addictively playing it and so is
literally the entire world now so let me
know what your guys thoughts are and
down below and let's get ready to race
alright you guys now that that is all
I'm gonna get my face a nice spritz of
some wrapping stuff settings right just
to kind of melt everything I'm back into
place because it has been done literally
like three or four hours since I put on
my base routine and she's looking a
little bit crusty I'm gonna dip it back
into the dragon a beauty of palette and
got me a smaller brush and we're just
gonna add our second layer of
highlighter onto the other side in the
original photo by shine and shadows he
did give me a little bit of freckles so
I am gonna put some nice pink and orange
blush on my nose and add those and just
because they're very very cute and
youthful and then I was gonna add it a
few freckles like a normal head last but
finally and not least to finish off this
makeup look I'm just gonna grab a nude
lip liner has a lace and then I was
gonna finish it off with a little bit of
a gloss it's nice and juicy already you
go use this several hours and several
pink kitty drink it is later this is
number three just like the mario kart
not sure if i want to be proud or
embarrassed by this but this biggity
drinking inspired makeup look is all
complete I honestly had so much fun
doing this video today and I really
really hope that you guys enjoyed it I
don't do it sit-down tutorials or chit
check out Yogi's often up but this is a
lot of fun and if you guys did enjoy it
give it a big thumbs up down below and
leave me comment let me know if you guys
want to see more because I would love to
do this all the time but I'm more scared
I don't know if you guys were into this
type of stuff so let her sister know and
think he once again to my amazing friend
that shine shadows for creating and
sparking this look today I make sure you
sisters go check them out and share some
love if you got ready after a thumbs up
don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come
join at this sisterhood
I'd absolutely Lube
absolutely live to have you with the
family and absolutely love to have you
in the family and also click that Bell
icon so you get notifications every time
I upload a brand-new it video just like
this one if you like to follow me on my
makeup dirty can follow me on Instagram
Twitter twitch and tik-tok or all James
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
than C times up is James Charleston
extra ass after Charles and if you guys
want to follow fit on his puppy journey
make sure you follow him on Instagram
Dana Charles we're not so cute puppy
pics home wiggly this video is sisters
how that goes to sister Julia thank you
so much love for always a falling and
supporting you know I love you so so so
much and if you would like to be next
videos sister shadow don't forget to
always recruit middle east in they go
live on Twitter and also turn on my
YouTube post notifications
alright you guys thank you so talked in
this videos today I love you so much and
I'll see you in the next one bye
[Music]