hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel in
the comment on my videos I get a lot of
requests to do other videos and most of
the time they make sense and are great
ideas and then there's videos like the
one we're gonna be doing today I do not
understand why you guys keep asking me
to do cooking videos but here we are I
James Charles can not cook I'm admitting
it right now before I even get into this
okay it is just not a skill that I have
in my repertoire if you will I post
mates three out of three meals of the
day it's just not really a skill that
I've ever like gotten good at but that
being said okay I love cooking I love
the Food Network i watch the bone
Appetit videos on YouTube all day every
single day and on a more serious note
obviously the world right now is in a
little bit of a crisis we're dealing
with a Copa 19 also known as the
provirus
and a lot of places such as la are on
lockdown and we can't really leave our
houses that also means a lot of
restaurants are closed down as well now
if you guys know me you know my favorite
food of all time is Cannes and it's only
four items on the menu it is fried
chicken french fries coleslaw and Texas
toast and oh my god it is literally the
best food on the entire planet but right
now I can't get it okay I'm deprived I
want it more than anything so for
today's video I'm here in my kitchen and
I'm gonna try to recreate a Kane's me
all from scratch hopefully while we're
learning this together you guys can pick
up some fun cooking at tips and
techniques so you guys can be self
efficient and we can all do our best at
isolating cooking and providing for
ourselves of being independent sisters
so yeah if you want to watch me try not
to burn down my house and hopefully cook
some really delicious food keep on
watching
[Music]
all right so to prepare this recipe
today I'm going to open my sister's
laptop and actually found a recipe
online by the website healthy junk food
which shallots then they're an amazing
channel here on YouTube actually not
done a few weeks why playlists they were
super super nice and they have a recipe
on how to recreate Cannes so I'm gonna
be following this I'll leave the link
down below in case any of you guys want
to recreate it as well but let's go
ahead and get started
it said this is only gonna take 10
minutes to prepare and four minutes to
cook yeah I guarantee all will be here
for at least two hours together so sit
down side well but you know hope that
this turns out good our ingredients are
going to be some nice chicken breasts
two cups of flour some salt sitting on
our 2 eggs 2 cups of buttermilk which we
could not find so we have a regular milk
we also have half in half butter I'm not
really sure if we can like combine
butter and mill to make buttermilk that
might be one of the most ignorant
sentence ever
but do you know what we're gonna figure
it out because we have to make do with
what we got and then finally one
tablespoon of garlic powder let's make
some check-in before we think it started
on the chicken the first thing that I
want to do is put my oil into my pot so
I can get heated up and ready to fry by
the time that I'm done prepping at the
chicken another slight issue that we ran
into
we don't have vegetable oil which is
what you're supposed to fry things in we
only have olive oil so I'm not even sure
if this is gonna work to be quite honest
with you I feel like a shed so I'm just
way to take my oil hi guys
nice olive oil drink we're gonna first
do a lot about is it olive oil all the
recipe at first said this is exact word
cut your thick juicy chicken breasts
into straps oh can I open this here
those chicken juices everywhere okay
we're gonna cut these into some nice
strips so we're gonna take our Bowl and
some nice natural eggs doesn't the
problem mean they're natural really yeah
what is the brown egg mean that's what I
meant
now what do I do for the buttermilk
let's go black or 1 cup of milk into a
bowl I'll grab one small fresh lemon or
white vinegar this mixture will get us
thick and creamy as better enough but it
will perform its role in the batter just
as well what about great and one
tablespoon of garlic powder
that's how you ask you just like right
like little circular motion it's like
blending eyeshadow now we're going to
take our chicken breasts and we're going
to put it in our saw our sauce and the
healthy junk food website says that we
need to refrigerate it for two to four
hours so we're gonna go ahead and put
this in our refrigerator for two to four
minutes cuz I did not and we're gonna
make our dry mixture to actually do the
fry we need 2 cups of all-purpose flour
1 cup of seasoned breadcrumbs I love
bread crumbs 2 teaspoons of salt and
then also treat the 2 teaspoons of salt
and then 2 teaspoons of baking powder ok
so now our dry ingredients are all
complete so we're gonna get started on
our French fry Kane's fries are really
good but I will say that they're nothing
like crazy
I was literally planning on just doing
like the frozen crinkle-cut fries that
you can get from the grocery store and
of course those were also missing so
there's gonna be a lot harder than it
needed to be I was so sure we had pickle
in the fridge right here oh are you
serious a little bit frozen now while
we're ready for the oven to preheat for
our nicely pre-made french fries thank
God I'm gonna work on making it at the
Kane's on hopefully my next sentence is
not offend anybody but I don't love King
sauce I'm very much a catch up in
barbecue type of girl but I know a lot
of people are right or dies and maybe if
I make my own it won't be that bad so
we're gonna actually try it today
no wonder the mayonnaise you you you
absolutely not is that what's in it
that's why I hate it babies is
disgusting I am NOT doing a cup of
mayonnaise littell you down right now
that is enough for me out of ketchup
what is what's worse desire sauce you
know this is disgusting really that's
definitely yeah like that is that skin
sauce okay where do we put the fries
enough gonna go ahead and put our fries
enough so the chicken is marinated for a
lovely 20 minutes roughly we're not
gonna put it into our dry mixture and
we're going to get a nice amount of a
coating on there now it goes back into
the wet mixture again and now back into
the dry mixture once again for our
second layer let's just fast you know
I'm just gonna repeat this with all of
our chicken strips and then we'll pop
them into the fire so in the ground of
our care of hogs and we're going to do a
little test strip here I'll grab this
nice one oh no that's fine oh my god did
I do it
okay it worked I just let it sit in
there deep fryer three to four minutes
I'll leave it at that I put these and
just leave it Oh turn down the volume or
slightly the volume oh wow
once it's smoking here okay
a few moments later oh that is cold it
was cooking for one minute I'm gonna go
out on a limb and say your oil burned
cut the cameras lay down we have one
chicken breast laughs that is on birds
so we are going to make this our last
attempt at making cans before we
Livingstone McDonald's which is open
during this course so we found a meat
thermometer in our drawer which is great
because in there we're good okay that's
a good tender does look pretty good yeah
that's what could never go to Remzi
shaking Giada home still at home cuz
she's quarantined but I love her this
time step which is going to be their
canes toast the best part of the entire
meal oh my god I would literally go to
Cannes if it just meant eating the toast
like I'd be completely throw that it's a
full meal in my book
and we're gonna try our best to recreate
it today I don't even think we can get
anywhere close I don't know what they
bake it way that it must be magic for
rich rot so so we have our two slices of
bread and Kane's bread is known for
being a both like really really sweet
and salty at the same time so our bread
is of course a little bit salty and we
got some garlic flavored infused extra
virgin olive oil I'm just going to put
into here so it's gonna take a little
cooking a brush what is this like a nice
like a c-47 seven products crab some
butter from the tub really brush it on
there giving the bread a nice coating
perhaps a stippling motion for all you
makeup lovers out there a little bit of
extra virgin olive oil extra virgin just
like me unfortunately and lots of
Pauline at least we're gonna pop our
bread into the oven to toast for like
four to five ish to eight depending on
how long this takes to cook with it so
dunno alright you guys we are finally
done that with this Kane's DIY meal
contrary to the blog that we read it did
not take fourteen minutes but rather two
hours time for the taste test this was a
roller coaster to get here but I will
see the finished plate in front of us
looks like no that bad let's try the
thighs first pick your like fine
french fry whatever I will see your
chicken tenders do not work out great
the first time everything but this one
looks okay take a look inside fully
cooked taken a little bit of king sauce
[Music]
oh you are kidding you've gotta be
kidding me there is no way that after
all that this tastes good I'm speechless
take some lemonade don't know our toast
no not even close I'm so bad it's just
not nothing can come truly compete with
canes it's not it's too sweet there's
not nearly enough salt it was just so
good oh my god this is so good
well I wish I had all the Tundra's and
not only just one yo so good no although
you guys will most like that is our DIY
canes meal all completes this process
today it was really something like it
says begin this video I just don't
understand why you guys keep requesting
cooking videos I'm clearly not very good
at them I will say though okay in the
end the finish was all kind of slop
really enjoyed this obviously Kane's is
I'm way way way better but let's just I
love canes and I'm deprived of it and
I'm missing it and McDonald's is gonna
have to do during these scary times if
you enjoyed this cooking with James
videos today please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below into your
love and support it really helps me and
my channel out so so so much also click
that subscribe button and come join at
this sisterhood we are 17 million a
sister songs we love to have you join
the family and also click that belt like
until you get notifications every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me out I make them turn it you
can follow me on Instagram Twitter
tik-tok and Facebook or I'll just change
myself chopped Lord behind the scenes I
stop it's Ju Charles that extra ass
after Charles and if you want to text me
it you can reach me at 3 one out nine oh
five eight seven four six
this video is sisters how that goes to
baddie Charles thank you so much love
for always following and supporting I
love you so so so much and if you would
like to the next videos sisters now
don't forget to always reach people who
do things when they go live on Twitter
and also turn on my YouTube posts on
vacations already sisters and that is
all I have for today's video thank you
so much for watching it stay safe wash
your hands
I love you and I will see you at the
next one bye
[Music]