[Music]
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
[Music]
this past weekend here in Los Angeles
was the annual Pride Parade I am so
honored and proud to be part of the
LGBTQ community it is such an amazing
place to be but unfortunately I did not
get to actually go to the parade as you
guys know I did just moved to Los
Angeles and I was so looking forward to
going to the first-ever pride event
I have never actually been to one before
so I was so pumped toward like some glam
makeup and meet a ton of you guys but I
had something a little bit more
important to do that weekend I was
actually shooting a very very exciting
campaign commercial that I cannot talk
to you guys about just yet
but I promise you'll be finding out very
very soon but being said however it was
and prior to baste commercial and I was
wearing this look for the shooting I
posted on Instagram and snapchat so many
of you guys aren't crazy over this
rainbow cut crease prime and spine look
I have to miss makeup a total of five
times out and after number four on the
set for the commercial I literally
tweeted saying I would never ever ever
to a rainbow cut crease ever again but
so many of you guys asked for tutorial
on this and it was something that was
very very hard to explain this is
definitely a very very intricate look so
I figured let me just suck it up put it
back on for the fifth and final time and
film a freaking tutorial
that being said that this look is
definitely not the easiest thing in the
world it's definitely pretty tricky and
extravagant so I definitely just go into
James tutorial mode and teach you guys
these little techniques and tricks that
I use to get this look so if you want to
see how I created this rainbow pride cut
crease make sure you keep on watching
all right babes so I'm starting off with
my face and eyebrows already completely
on and done this look is very very
focused on the eye region obviously so I
don't want to take too long on the base
I just use my makeup primer ultra HD
stick and then my turn shape tape as
always my Laura Mercier and then my
benefit brow products so just a normal
routine like always every single video
and now let's just go ahead and move
right on with the eyes and get into the
glam I already went ahead and Pat my
eyelids using some concealer and then
some loose powder and the first part I'm
gonna go often is my morphe 35n palette
of course any ways that you can use code
Jase or 10% off your
yes this problem is my all-time favorite
develop that I used to my colorful looks
as you can see it is very very used and
damaged but as my holder krill that I'm
gonna start with this angle brush I'll
just dip into the yellow shade down in
the bottom to start sketching out my
crease so you guys know my cut crease I
do do that a little bit of a strange way
and that as I sketch out of the crease
first and then gotten with the shadows
and went upward after this is not a very
very common technique but it's what
works best for me so follow it don't
follow it that's on you to decide sister
YouTube you this is just my eyelid
crease I wonder if this works really
really well for me just because it gives
me a really really good guideline when
it comes to the concealer I can just
super easily cut it right in half and I
don't have to really worry about like
shaping or anything like that I don't
know this is my personal favorite and
then I'm going to use the same exact
brush and I'm gonna dip into the orange
shade and kind of place that in the
middle of the cut crease and then with
that same exact brush dipping right into
the red and then finally winging that
out using the bright pink shade when I
sketch out my cut crease as you can see
I do got a little bit of hooded eye it's
when I look shape for it at the camera
there's not much actual lid space you
can see so when I draw my crease in I
really like to go above my natural
crease or what I look for it you can
still see pretty much all the cut crease
this just once again my style you don't
have to do this I know a lot of people
like to put their concrete in their
actual crate you spin that into say cut
crease you get what I'm saying
put your diffic a star ever you want it
personally I've heard a draw above the
crease and I feel like this gives a deep
best result but once again you do you
next I'm gonna go away I'm four three
three brush and dip right back into that
yellow shade and I'm just gonna really
focus this clear right on the inner
corner of that crease area that's great
my morphe amma one five one brush
dipping into my Anasazi a-blazing single
shadow i'm going to use this color and
I'm going to keep it up the orange part
of the crease I'm just going right in
where I drew that original crease line
and darkening up the bottom a portion of
not Creed's just to create a little bit
more dimension and then carving another
and 4:33 brush I'm gonna dip into the
bright orange a to the 35b palette and
blend that out next we're gonna have a
clean a morphe m151 brush again and dip
into my jeffree star and drogyny palette
and the shade fetish same thing with the
orange I'm just placing this cloth at
the bottom of that crease line from
before just to create some dimension
bang carving another m33 burps I'm going
to dip into that red shake from the 35b
palette and I'm going to blend that out
[Music]
and then finally with one less I'm four
three three I'm going to dip into the
bright pink shade and just blend out the
outside of that line and smoke it out
and those are all the colors are already
on there like I told you guys the
segment yes super easy and definitely my
favorite I've been doing it since
beginning if you have not tried this
technique to do a concrete definitely a
ton of Ted water go ahead just try it
let me know what you think at least I
promise you will not regret it
but that being said as you can see
there's already a super easy guide
already drawn out because we sketch it
out originally but now just to clean it
up I'm gonna go back and buy a
heart-shaped Cape concealer em I have a
makeup shock t-80 sticks brush and I'm
just going to clean up that line I'm
just going to slowly trace right
underneath that crease line being really
careful not to mess it up because that
blending is already looking a bomb
oh yeah I think we don't have to go
around and we do it so I'm just tracing
the bottom of that line and driving it
right into the inner corner and then
with a new job uh concealer and down
onto the eyelid just set that concealer
at replacing just to brighten up the
island itself and get ready for it the
liner I'm just gonna use the makeup shot
t6 brush in the white shade in the 35b
and just packing it right on there
for awaiting today I can use my Kat Von
D tattoo and locket Lila this is my
all-time favorite winged liner
now looking at this this wing is
definitely way bigger than normal but
keep in mind it is a very very large cut
crease almost like drag style makeup
look so we definitely want to try to
balance it out at least a little bit
when it comes to the Atlanta because
this would look very very shake there's
a huge boat on crease and then a tiny
little baby baby wings so once again a
theme of this video do what you want but
this stuff to the style that I feel like
well the best for this look and just
what I came up with
honestly this wing is ready to cut a
[ __ ] I am living for it let's go ahead
and move on for my bottom lash I have
today I'm first gonna start off by
letting my waterline using the Mac
fascinating.i Kohl pencil
I love the formula it is so creamy and
smooth and doesn't irritate my eyes you
guys know that I'm really really not a
fan of honestly been kind of skip me on
that stuff recently but this firmware is
one that doesn't irritate me and for
this look at that really looks super
cute to have a little bit of white in
the inner corner just to open up the
eyes make them look a little bit bigger
a little more for the little pump
because we are to be gluing some
Swarovski crystals in there too so I'm
just gonna use this to really brighten
up that lower lash line and get ready
for a whole lot of color for the first
color on my waterline I'm gonna grab you
guessed it the morphe 35n white m33
brush and I'm just gonna dip into this
sky blue shade up in the top right
corner I'm just focusing this color
right on the center of the lower lash
line and blending it lightly out to the
left and the right I definitely didn't
want to take the shadow too low down or
else it's gonna really accentuate those
eye bags but I am being careful just to
make sure it is still blown out because
we don't want a SuperDuper harsh line
that is boys against the rules when it
comes to makeup with sister J Nexen I go
back in with a 35 B and my Sigma e55
eyes shading brush this is just a a flat
definer brush that I'm just gonna dip
into this bright green shade right up in
here and I'm just gonna place this in
the inner corner or right underneath
that white shadow
out of all the colors in the rainbow
green is probably my least favorite
color so like I was saying personal
preference I'm gonna probably use the
least amount of green shadow and best
luck and I'm just gonna really focus
this right on the inner corner and
there's gonna hot pocket of my blue
blending brush and make sure that those
shades are very well blended together
for the last clone I'm gonna grab Miami
5 6 - a tiny tapered blending brush and
dip right into this with right ass
purple to finish off the lower lash line
I'm just taking this purple shade and
I'm putting it right in the outer corner
on the outer third of the lid pulling
into the blue a little bit and then just
pulling it up and out and blending it
into the bottom of that wing then to
finish off the eye look I'm gonna grab a
UH Swarovski crystal and the size 14 and
just pop her right on to deny that are
you just stopped my last sentence
midweek I apologize I just popped on a
Swarovski crystal on the size number 14
using a tiny dollop of flash fill in the
inner corner hmm I'm so sorry about that
now we're gonna move on with the lashes
and for today I'm using the house lash
psychotics as always I always love these
for crazy so I'm just going to glue her
right on then to finish off this eye
look I'm just gonna use my benefit
roller lash mascara you guys know this
is my all-time babe just to blend
together my fake lashes with my aren't
real ones
alright guys that is one prayin rainbow
cut crease I all complete I'm gonna
gonna do the one off-camera now just
save some time and I'll be right back
okay finish off the rest of the face all
right we'll be right along for blush
that I'm gonna use the Mac dolly mix
blush with my morphe okay this has no
name on it so this brush I am packing
the blush a little bit heavier than
normal today for James Krause I like oh
this is definitely not my usual luck but
I'm using a pink highlighter today and
for the commercial that I shot this for
they really wanted a very very intense
private that would show well my camera
so this is just exactly what I did once
again if you don't want to wear that
much blush you do use this terms this is
getting so annoying I apologize and
therefore highlighters today I'm going
to use the Eclipse highlighter from a
Jeffrey's are in collaboration with
Mandy MUA I freaking love this thing it
is so blinding pull and I'm just gonna
lay out right over top of that blush so
it gives a little bit of a pink
iridescent glow I'm also poppin is how
later right onto the brow bone for a
little bit more glow up there then I'm
just wrapping i'm 4:33 angle right over
that line between the two just make sure
that however is not too defined we're
just saying that I never thought I would
send my tan line but we just want to
settle down that glow just the slightest
bit to make sure they're evenly blended
between the highlight the brow and like
the red crease to finish this look off
my lips today I'm gonna use the over
liquid lipstick in the shade at Pasadena
I felt like a nude lip was it definitely
necessary for this look just being that
if I'd chose any a bright color it would
probably a really really unbalanced the
eye look I didn't want to like a red or
anything because then there'd be too
much red or like a blue you get what I
mean I feel like they need to be the
perfect happy medium between all three
and Pasadena so my all-time faves and
you guys know you can use code James I'm
sorry 2% off all over up products as
well
all right and to finish this look off
once and for all I'm gonna drench myself
in the Urban Decay all nighter setting
spray if you're gonna be wearing this
look to a prime event is gonna be very
very hot probably very very sweaty and
probably very brief item celebratory so
you definitely gonna make sure you lock
in your makeup all day long
alright guys and that is the completed
pride a rainbow cut crease inspired
tutorial for today I really really hope
you enjoyed this video I apologize that
it wasn't more like tennety charity I do
usually love it doing those videos but
for today I just wanted to sit down and
focus and like I said in the intro I
have done this look this is the fifth
time now host I'm very very sick and
tired of it I just wanted to get it done
teach you guys how to do because it's
definitely not that you see singing in
the world and move on that being said if
you guys said enjoy this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below if you have not already I
posted two videos a week on Mondays and
Fridays and I would love to have you
join this sisterhood if you'd like to
follow me on my makeup journey to follow
me on Instagram and Twitter out there
bulges at James Charles and my snapchat
for more behind-the-scenes I'm stop is
James Charles the next rose after charm
Phaedra shout out to sister Nicole for
retweeting last week's video link when I
went live love you girl
alright sisters thank you so much for
watching and I will see you in the next
one
[Music]