hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I'm gonna be doing
something completely different that I
have never done on this channel before
and I'm honestly so excited for and I
hope you guys are too in case you miss
it or been living under a rock
Sigma just relaunched their lip switched
lip glosses that is such a mouthful but
these lip glosses are like holographic
rainbow glosses like ass and they aren't
so beyond beautiful they launched a few
months back and they took the internet
by storm everybody was doing a crazy
looks at them and they sold out and have
not been available since it's been like
3 or 4 months but they finally just
relaunched a few days ago and now I got
my hands on all four of the shades as
soon as I got these I was so freaking
excited and my first instinct was
obviously to open them right up and do
some swatches over on snapchat and if
you don't follow me on SAP you
definitely shed when you save as James
Charles and then extra ass after Charles
I was do PR on boxes and openings on
there than when I did get products like
these they're always getting swatched as
soon as I got these in swatch if I
wanted to do a look so so badly because
they were so cool so goo does this like
black smokey eye glossy lid and rainbow
lip situation post it on Instagram and
you guys went crazy over it I got so
many comments and so many requests to
film a video on this look and reality
it's literally just a black lip and
black smokey eye with these glosses over
tough anybody can do that it's just the
gloss I guess that are the cool part so
instead of doing like a tutorial because
I feel like that's boring and it's super
super easy I want to do like a full-on
type of like review swatch type of
situation and then I'll pour see how I
created their lips from the look the
gloves the eye part is so much fun and
photographs beautifully but it's
definitely not from practical wear at
all trust me I was like blinking and
glosses getting all my eye lids after
like three three minutes so definitely
would not recommend so I figured I would
just skip out on the eyes and do only
the lips for today that further ado
let's get into the review I just pulled
up the signal website right now and
these are the lip switch lip glosses
from Sigma Beauty they are $14 each
definitely not too badly price for a lip
gloss I know most lip glosses are
usually like 18 or 21 dollars similar
price
they're sick so you are definitely
getting a few dollars off for sure
it describes on the website as a
holographic lipgloss is that a prismatic
lightweight and a d-dimensional new
layer tier favorite lip color these lips
which lip glosses come in four different
shades the first one is called flip flop
and this one is orange holographic the
next lips which is called pink lotus and
is basically pink holographic next one
is called it transcend and it is this
blue holographic gloss and the last one
is called a double whammy and it is this
purple blue green trio chrome gloss type
of situation so those are all four
shades swatched
on the skin and I don't really know how
these are gonna show up on camera
looking at the monitor you can't really
tell how actually holographic in here it
doesn't they look and person they are so
beautiful and really color changing I'm
really really hoping that it looks okay
on the footage but anyways envelopes it
does say that the glosses look the
coolest when they're layered over a dark
liquid lipstick and of course I have a
nude on right now so I'm going to go
ahead and remove this and replace it
with a black one then do some cool lip
swatches on the actual lips I'm gonna
show you guys how to created that oil
spell look that I post it on the
Instagram everybody was crazy over it is
such a cool look still let's go ahead
and take this liquid lipstick off and
I'll show you guys what these glosses
can really do alright so I just went
ahead and applied my favorite black
liquid lipstick I use jeffree star a
weirdo for this particular day and I'm
not gonna go to these glosses and crank
this oil slick
the first thing they're going to go on
with this double whammy and this is the
purpley blue green holographic one out
of the four one this is probably my
least favorite um before I really it's
not as pigmented it doesn't really show
up as well
but it does make a good transition color
to kind of blend all the other ones
together and help create those like
inner colors like the orcs and the
greens so I'm going to do this one first
when I go to play this I'm gonna kind of
or there I'm not gonna go to the pink
lotus and put this on at the outer
corner once again same situation car
being a lot of gloss I'm gonna I'm just
going in super randomly and placing this
on it different areas next gonna grab
the shade it transcend and I'm gonna
layer this on as well out of the four of
them this one is probably my favorite I
feel like it's so pigmented and you can
oh yeah
you can really you can really see that
on camera thank God
then I'm also gonna go flip-flop and
layer that on as well all right guys and
this is how I created the oil slick lips
they look so freaking cool I really
really hope that the camera is like
doing it justice I can see on the
monitor that they definitely look very
very involved and person they look
literally out of this world
holographic rainbow realness being that
these glasses are only 14 does I would
definitely say that these products are
James Charles approved they are so cool
you definitely did not need to wear all
four of them stocked over a black
lipstick like I am these do look really
really cool on their own and could look
really really great over just a nude lip
or any other colored lip that you might
have a sitting in your drawer there are
so many cool combinations that you could
try out with these so if you get that
make sure to send me pictures and tweet
me all your different combinations I
would love to see your crazy holographic
lips alright guys that being said thank
you so much for watching this video if
you did like it please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below let's
even get this to 20,000 likes it lets me
know that you guys like this review
because I can totally do more crazy
product reviews coming in the near
future and you haven't already make sure
you go click that big red subscribe
button down below
we just hit 1 million subscribers oh my
god I am so thankful and so excited
there are so many amazing things in the
works coming soon so definitely keep
your eyes peeled just thank you guys so
much with the bottom of my heart it
truly means so much it is so cool crazy
that over 1 million of you guys have
stuck with me on my youtube journey it
has been very very rocky and crazy 1 but
like I said I'm so glad that we're now
getting into the real swing of things
I'm doing two videos a week everything I
can conquer the world and there are so
many cool things coming soon as I said
it before if you'd like to follow me on
my makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they both just
James Charles psi out so close to 2
million on Instagram I am getting very
very excited so if you don't follow me
on there I'm definitely gonna hit that
follow button and now is the time and
for more behind the scenes type stuff my
Twitter and you now or both James
Charles the next your ask dr. Charles
alright guys thank you so much for
watching this video and I will see you
in the next one bye
[Music]