hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel I
just want to jump right into the video
today because we definitely have a lot
going on so we're gonna do that oh we
can go here than this YouTube channel I
uploaded a really fun video called I
tried drawing myself it would make up if
you have not yet seen it make sure to
click right up here I drew a portrait of
myself using only makeup I'm lovely here
the makeup interest you like to call a
face chart and this is the finished
result spoiler alert you're not really
really good honestly so proud of it and
in the video I had so much fun doing it
that I actually decided to turn it into
a contest okay the hashtag sister face
chart contests I gave all you sisters
that download link to the blank face
charts it said go crazy create a
beautiful creative look on my face I'm
gonna be popping up some notable entries
right here on the screen you guys are
always it was so amazing and I also
announced a huge prize for the winner as
well being a MacBook Air and headed back
to school supplies a $200 Target gift
card and pink drinks on me for the
entire first month of school and they
also said as well that the kind of
second part of the prize which of course
is a lot less exciting than all the nice
to give away stuff but I would be
recreating the winners face shirt right
here on my face but like actually on my
face instead of on paper over ten
thousand how Wow I'll be sisters created
artwork for the sister face art contest
which literally first of all just thank
you that is so cool that 10,000 of you
guys put hours and hours of your own
time and creativity and passion into
these face charts looking through them
they're all so incredibly beautiful I
have so many of them saved to my phone
to recreate later on with credit of
course so if you guys definitely keep
your eyes out for that but we can only
have one winner or honestly can we
surprise make sure you stay tuned until
the end of the video because I have a
special sister surprise for our places
number two and three but definitely be
one winner who gets everything so I am
sociated to tell you guys that the
winning fascia that I'm gonna be
creating on my face today is drumroll
please
sister Miko with this amazing a
beautiful rainbow speckled a paint faced
her oh my god you guys this is literally
so sunny all the colors on it are
literally so vibrant I'm feeling so
inspired and I want to put this on my
face right now so without further ado I
already have my full base on of course
this is gonna be a mostly eye shadow
kissed look once I got think it
everybody else who entered but let's get
started
I went ahead and do two guys in a little
bit welcome to my base all I know I get
a lot of complaints a lot when I do do
makeup and videos that you guys can't
actually see what I'm doing
sorry about that as usual I'm gonna
focus on one eye intensely on camera
here just because we kind of have a lot
going on and I don't want to sit here
for eight hours and neither do you so
that's the tea on that I think we're
gonna start off with just a little brush
this is the my 14 years coating for 10%
off and dip all four more feet you guys
already knew that and dip into kind of a
yellow shade and pop that yeah just
gonna pop that right here on the inner
corner I'm not really sure the order in
which I'm gonna kind of do this look
today I think we're just gonna really
throw on some colors and hope and pray
that it looks good that's kinda what I
do in all my makeup tutorials and it
usually or so kind of so that's what
we're doing great it's henna cool
because
Enrico's drawing here all the colors are
placed really really close together but
are still very wounded out which is
extremely hard to do so props to him I'm
gonna take a kind of bright peachy ready
orange shade with an M 506 and place
that right in the crease return that
color shift between the yellow and red
and then the purple and blue kind of
happens like here-ish so I think I'm
just gonna pack a little bit more on
[Music]
maybe that looks not good oh my god it's
so hard to blend yellow oh please go on
there that might be a facetune moment
now I'm gonna take an am up to 13 and a
dark red shade and use this to really
cut out where I'm gonna place that
crease which is gonna be right here
hopefully that looks so busted a hole oh
my god
it's just gonna work it's gonna work
right now okay great next I'm gonna take
a curve ball shade on an M 514 once
again and I'm gonna place that next door
to that like burgundy area kind of right
up in here
oh that's pretty T and then before I
actually go and blend that further I'm
going to grab that dark red shade once
again and use that to kind of easily
transition the purple into oh
James Charles forgetting how to do
makeup for five minutes Trey I'm scared
mostly the purple it goes down and
really cuts out the crease moment and
then we have some blue that is there too
I'm gonna grab that same purple on a
kind of liner I think this is a lip
brush I have no idea and put that in the
crease once again just like we did with
this front part kind of lining where I
want the colors to go or at least like
where I think they're gonna go there's
lots of purple and up here so I'm just
gonna put that there yeah we're gonna
regret that later I'm gonna blend these
two together so it doesn't look like
gross and it's watching I'm gonna kind
of fun okay cool
now I'm gonna grab a medium tone of blue
shade and this I want to use kind of
like a Hawking brush since I really want
this blue shade to be kind of a quite
pigmented so I'm going to grab that and
place that right there
oh well that blue is so pretty
T
[Music]
that looks bad
who's GERD okay then I'm just gonna go
out like a lighter blue and place that
right over that to blend that ow and I'm
gonna be putting a blue highlight in the
brow oh my god this looks disgusting on
camera what's happening then it's going
to go the anasazi up moonchild palette
this literally it used to be my favorite
highlighting palette of all time this is
like one of the og makeup lover moments
like when this released though nation
was shaking including me and as you can
tell this is bana clearly quite used so
under got the shade star and I'm gonna
place this right on lieth brow bone to
hopefully pick some of this horrible
blending that I have going on I don't
know what I'm doing what is that that is
it doesn't even look oh okay I guess
that's okay it's really pretty if you
look at it like from this angle I'm like
only that angle
okay this looks absolutely the absolute
worst but you know what maybe when we
cut it in a look a little bit better I'm
gonna grab a shape tape in the shade
fair I was like to cut my crease no
matter what look it's using a really
light concealer just to kind of act as
like an eyeshadow base and my favorite
brush to cut the crease is going to be
the Mac 242
no discount code but it's still good oh
[Music]
my god wait this looks actually pretty
now that it's getting kind o T cool if
you guys went sister subscribers for a
long time you would know that this is
actually not the way that I used to do
cut creases I used to draw out the
bottom line first and then blend the
shadows upwards which was definitely a
more complicated process but for some
reason I had never best up when it came
to actually drawing the shape now that I
switch over to the dark side and do this
technique of drawing creases can never
get them even should it is stuck to I
got it you all lied now that the creases
all caught I'm just gonna take a flat
top little brush and just pack on some
of my face powder
really carefully obviously not to mess
the shape up but I want to set this in
place once again it before I put on any
eyeshadow and also just because that's
what you do oh this is looking good now
okay now I'm kind of happy I excited a
little bit low key okay let me stay
humble for a second before this gets
ugly again okay so it looks like there
is her weight yeah I don't think there's
purple on the lid I think I wonder what
they want me to do while I decide what's
gonna go on the lid I'm gonna go ahead
and line this with white
now that we have the crease all cut we
have the lid to do and I'm honestly
having a little bit of trouble telling
what's on the lid it looks like there's
kind of like a purple moment with a like
sparkly moment in the middle which I'm
definitely down for so I think I'm just
gonna kind of line this with purple and
two hour goes I'm just gonna use an
angle brush to do this just because I do
want to be a little bit precise I'm
gonna be really careful and just tuck
that purple right up against that white
line I do have a feeling that I'm gonna
have to go back in once I finish the
purple portion and realign it which is
fine but obviously no ideal because
that's like a lot of work that I don't
really want to do this winged portion is
gonna go like here since I haven't had
as much time to really sit down and do a
lot of this creative looks anymore which
hurts my soul every single day I think
every time I do actually try to do that
I think I'm literally changing my plan
in freaking out every single look
because halfway through all hate it and
then five minutes later I'll be in love
with it and then every step just keeps
changing like that does not look good
we're fresh gonna put some purple right
here and then I guess I'm gonna put
glitter on the lid I don't know what
color I want to do yet but we're gonna
make that decision together probably
take a light blue I should probably just
I'm right literally right back into blue
like this blue
and I'm gonna pull it all the way into
the inner corner because there will be a
pop of white there eventually
[Music]
that's like good enough whatever I'm
gonna play some reflect steal from Mac
right on the center of that lid to
really make that blue pop us a little
bit and create the effect of the halo I
oh yeah that's pretty
I was probably about idea what am i
doing
finally that looks like okay now that we
have all the liner done kind of I'm
gonna start sketching out death because
this is getting really hard then it's
gonna pack on some purple right over
here and blend that out for a real one
[Music]
kind of happy with that okay I'm gonna
take that bright burnt red shade from
before and place that right next order
this Powerball below the liner and kind
of blend those two together and pull the
shade right off into the lower lash line
[Music]
great looks actually good for once just
gonna use a few different m-43 threes
with some different oranges and reds on
them to really make sure everything is
kind of blended together I'm gonna take
the atom up five to one it's kind of
like a bigger pocket - and I'm gonna
place this like orange shade kind of
like right here and actually tuck this
orange right into the highlight and into
the blushed region as well because on
this photo this blush is like gorgeous
pink orange moment I kind of want to
just pull the eyeshadow right and
everything and have it all blend it
together which looks so what's done to
you see this is where I get and the look
is starts to come together and then I
stop complaining every three seconds
don't take that red shade once again and
blend this purple region together I'm
gonna bring back a little bit about
purple shade and then I want to take a
peachy metallic blush shade that is
literally my favorite thing the entire
world right now and I'm gonna use this
and put it right over the blush region
oh my god and finally last but not least
to complete that cheap region I'm just
gonna grab up my favorite blush Mac
peaches which is like this little orange
e moment I'm just a kind of really
intense rocker brush and I'm going to
for once really pack on that peach blush
right below that pink highlight moment
to really tie it all together oh you're
kidding me I'm so talented just gonna
put a little the excess right on my nose
because it's a little bit peachy in the
photo looks so cute oh he gonna go back
into that white shade because this is
looking a little bit crusted
now I'm gonna grab some yellow and put
docked right in at the center of the
lower lash line and then finally since
it is by far my least favorite color in
the entire rainbow I'm just gonna place
a little bit of the green shade right
here on in a corner and I'm gonna make a
little bit of room for it to be a kind
of the inner corner second Cui's moment
as well green is literally the ugliest
colors right well sorry no offense it's
just the truth tea
like literally who made green that is
gonna mount a great um I need a white
gel liner oh I did it ready oh my god
great I love when that happens
okay this I literally just took me two
hours to do um that was neither good nor
fresh but that being said I'm gonna go
to the other eye off-camera hopefully it
does not take me two hours or you may
not see me even back here but assuming
that I'm able to get it done I'll be
right back in a few seconds to finish
off the rest of the vlog I'll raise this
is we are back up old lights are now
done it literally it did take me two
hours to do the other eye so that's good
I am exhausted and very hungry but you
know we're gonna get through this
together just like we always do so I
finished you there I um I also popped on
the lash Lily lashes in the South Miami
using proteins for 15% off and now I'm
going to highlight my face
so pretty
right on the center of the nose hello I
like this look it's kind of like rainbow
dragon balls find a bigger lash line
hello maybe not looking at the face
shirt this picture has a lot of like
rainbow coloured freckles all over which
is kind of really cool and fun and fresh
so I'm gonna grab a white liner and I
guess I'm just gonna dot this like all
over my face this looks really pretty I
don't know if I want to put have to oh
oh that's too big
oh no gonna put on the center of the
eyelid oh god please don't get on the
lashes no okay
[Music]
there's definitely some definition
within the actual little colored dots
that we have on the space chart so I
just grabbed the NYX vivid bright liquid
liners and also a karlie liquid lipstick
in a bright pink shade I think this is
say no more and I'm going to use all
these different colors as well to add in
some more dots just to provide some
variation
[Music]
oh my god I actually love this you're
kidding yeah we love a polka-dotted
sister for a real one here at leather
Academy hello okay I think we are
literally done aside from the lip I am
obsessed with this look I think a little
polka-dotted sister love it
I'm gonna play the anasazi liquid
lipstick in the shade up Pierre
Hollywood yep
[Music]
could I finish it off on some skins and
Aviat setting spray and then I'm gonna
get both of the mac fix+ and both the
pink light and gold light I really like
these and they have like they're
basically fixed puzzle with a little bit
of glitter in it let me give myself a
good squish and then at the pink one on
the top too because why not
alright you guys oh my god and literally
six hours later here is the finished
face chart inspired by McLean true ache
a sister Miko all complete oh my god you
guys I love how this turned out let's be
real and process was definitely a little
bit of an emotional roller coaster when
I first started out I was having a lot
of trouble getting the clothes pigmented
blending them together cutting it on the
crease getting everything even it was
truly a little bit of a sister struggle
to say the least but we got there in the
end and I think like I was saying in the
video it is definitely one of those
looks that had a quite a few ugly
moments in between but in the end it
always turns out looking pretty and this
is the finished result and I literally
am so happy with that sister Miko thank
you so much for being a so talented at
taking your time to create this patient
and for submitting your amazing art I
have sent you to Instagram DM so make
sure to check it and send me your
address and everything so I can get your
prize to you ASAP everybody go check
them out and share the love please
please please and to all of you guys as
well thank you to all 10,000 sisters who
submitted face charts literally I cannot
even believe that that many people took
time out of their day to create are
obviously my time every single day is to
share my art with you guys and the fact
that you guys want to do that with me
literally it's so cool it was really
really hard to choose the final winner
but I'm definitely happy with the one I
selected and that being said though
because of all your guys's love and
support on the contest and because of
the fact that this video is uploaded a
little bit late due to some legalities
try not to get sister soon I decided
it'd be so cool to say thank you to not
only Miko but also to give a second and
third place price away as well being a
hundred dollar Target gift card
Jon roll please once again I'm saying
that as if I'm not doing it myself
literally Maddie ray tart with her piece
called contrast girl what I saw this
literally I was so obsessed shook and
it's not even funny I want to recreate
it
so bad but this is definitely one that
I'm gonna do to several hours to sit
down and focus on that is not one for a
YouTube video I will definitely be
jumping out of my building if I tried to
do that and Ciroc I with this amazing
jellyfish makeup look it is so beautiful
in so sunny I just love how detailed
today's you guys are both such talented
artists and thank you for sharing your
art with me if don't forget to check out
Instagram deals so I can sign you at the
little gift cards for back-to-school
season all right sisters and I think
that is all I have for today's little
sister face chart contest and it's so so
so much fun doing this and I really hope
you guys did as well if you did enjoy it
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and leave me a
comment if you guys will be to do more
giveaways and more contests more stuff
like this in the future I'm loading in
love with this I love saying your guys's
are I love it recreating your guys's
makeup looks every hope you guys like
this video and if you've not already it
don't forget to click the big red
subscribe button down below and come
join this sisterhood it's a pretty lit
time it clearly we do with lots of good
and fresh and fun things I'd love to
have you at join the family
and also click that Bell icon see be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you like to follow me on my
makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
James Charles and my snapchat for more
behind the scenes type stuff is James
Charles of the next your ass after
Charles if you like my amazing and
beautiful hoodie that I cannot believe I
managed to keep white drinking about
this video don't forget to check out
sisters - apparel calm for all your cute
sisters gear I am so proud of the new
line it just launched I'd love to have
you guys wearing all the good and fresh
pieces including the good and fresh
honey this videos sister snow togusa
sister Audrey thank you so much Laura
always falling and supporting you I love
you literally it's so so so much and if
you like to be the next videos sister
shout out don't forget to always retweet
my over links and they go live on a
Twitter alright guys I hope you enjoyed
this video today thank you so much for
watching I love you and I will see you
in the next one bye
you