hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today so do I have something super fun
plan that I'm actually so excited for
but I'm still used to watch TV with my
mom all the time and the one thing that
I loved watching every single year was
award season I don't know why but
something about a red carpet just always
intrigued me so much and one of my
biggest goals growing up was to walk a
red carpet and now because of my amazing
job I pinch myself every single day
because at this point I feel like every
other week I'm walking some red carpet
and doing interviews which is so crazy
to me most celebrities when getting
photographed walking red carpet and
doing interviews like to look absolutely
perfect I mean of course who doesn't but
that usually includes a very expensive
gowns very very beautifully done hair
and intense glam makeup for some of the
best artists in the entire world but
that process can be extremely costly
today I want to try to get red carpet
ready full makeup full outfit full
accessories in under $100 I have my $100
bill right in front of me left it over
to the stores and see if we can get red
carpet ready and under $100 all right
guys we're here at CVS is gonna be our
first stop of today's video hashtag not
sponsored you guys know I don't really
use drugstore products that often I mean
my regular foundation alone would
literally eat up half of our budget so
we're gonna do our best to find as many
products as we possibly can here to
still look good on a budget
the first was gonna be a foundation I
heard the new maybelline superstay
foundation is so bomb this one is $12 so
definitely a little bit pricy and
sealing I'm gonna grab the Maybelline
fit me concealer in the lightest shade
this one is 749 all right I know that
Nicki also owns the Maybelline fit me
loose it setting powder I'm gonna try to
save myself $2 and look for the Cote air
some powder at a different store and all
that one
six dollars however that is the powder
the created logic Mary oh and I've got
carpets you have to be photographed so
hopefully we're looking smooth sober
mascara is gonna pick up the covergirl
so ah she won't care which I was
literally the face for hello that is me
but it's $11.99 and that is way out of
budget at this point like give me a
discount or something I was in the
commercial to the prognoses $10.50 the
pomade is $7.50 and so is the brown
shell I do have a pretty bushy brows but
Wow a sister a family cannot have brows
on fleek on a budget we're going with
this and said this is the NYX eyebrow
pencil this one is $5 didn't even see
her highlighting in contour palette is
$24.99 that's literally a quarter of our
budget I don't get it together sister
let's go for mascara today I'm gonna
grab the Maybelline a great lash mascara
that's one $5.99 and I know the
Maybelline is known for having really
great mascaras so we're gonna pop that
one in hopefully it'll be a budget saver
because mascara can be crazy expensive
it's six to horse for a single shadow
from L'Oreal I don't think so sweetie
what in wild has liquid liners for only
three dollars so I'm gonna throw one of
those in there and then I also still
really badly need a highlighter okay so
what we're gonna do instead is I read
about the blush and highlighter do which
is $5.99 and also the contour and banana
powder drew which is also $5.99 so the
tools together equal the same price but
I'm gonna put this one back sorry sister
elf I still love you
that way we're killing four birds with
two stones
yeah okay so you just hotel at CVS and
we have a bunch of products our total
came to 44 something and that means we
have 55 dollars and one cent left for
the rest of this video not too bad but
we did already spend almost half our
budget and that's just on makeup we
still have clothes and accessories and
shoes I don't know if we can do this guy
that's not looking too great so far away
guys we're on our second stop of sister
or Walgreens we only have a few items
left to complete our full autumn makeup
look today all these loose motions from
kesab are $6.99 which is honestly not
much better than the old ones and before
but it is saving at two dollars and he's
kind of look relatively normal so we're
gonna pick out these four cities look at
hope and pray that they work see about I
said it was launched in let's take our
total is going to be $10.83 399 clothing
store or less that's all you need so at
our last let's say we're going to view
Friday and we only need a powder and a
lipstick left and our total right now is
at forty four dollars and eight cents
from a name
$9 for lipstick hello $8 $9 hello it's
lipstick $7 we're gonna have like 4
cents for clothes I built your coach
that I got in the next level we're at
CVS oh we might actually have to go back
for that privacy biessing has apparently
lip products cost a trillion dollars
ease so cream which are still $7 the
liner in the shade in now she'll which
is three dollars and fifty cents and the
soft matte lip cream in the shade of
Stockholm which is six dollars and 49
cents totaling to another $10 who's
gonna leave or clothing budget at around
30 bucks I'm really hungry so I think
I'm gonna use a dollar 69 on my budget
on a snack okay guys so since we're here
earlier and already bought a bunch of
stuff we have a nine dollar off CVS
coupon design but oil CBS member so that
means it's ten dollars and ninety three
cents of lipstick and lip liner that we
just bought is now going to come to one
dollar in seventh wheel of a bargaining
couponing sister extreme couponers is
quaking right now alright guys we just
got back we finished our entire face of
makeup except for one thing and that is
the trends there's a powder I know the
Cody Arizona is one of the cheapest and
best powders on the market but it's
always a little bit a Walmart which we
don't really have a lot of so what I'm
gonna do is that is five dollars and
ninety seven cents and sales tax is
eight percent so if we do five wait nine
eight times 1.08 we get six dollars and
forty-five cents and subtract that from
the budget
3 34 35 36 36 dollars and 56 cents and
when you just get an entire outfit so
the one option that I have left that
they can actually be a really great
solution is Santee alley if you don't
know what Santee alley it is basically a
really long street here in downtown LA
where you can get everything in the
entire world from fake makeup to Liberty
knock-off designer handbags Jorian
outfits for a super super low price it
is our ticketing really late so nice
everything is closed down I think we're
going to call it a night but tomorrow
morning we will wake up early it gonna
early start and go clothes shopping and
find holy an entire outfit from head to
toe only $36.50 see you guys tomorrow
good morning sisters below it is the
next day I'm up ready and looking
fabulous kind of tonight it's our red
carpet event and I am so beyond excited
we have thirty six dollars and fifty six
cents left and today we have to get a
full-on look I'm talking shoes shirt
pants accessories the full shebang in
order to get ready for this event and we
only have a few hours to do so hopefully
we'll be able to complete this look on a
budget
[Music]
we've shared a bunch of store stuff on
but we're coming to the same issue in
that everything is actually really cute
here but a lot of the stuff is like
literally taking of the entire budget if
we found a pair of shoes that were super
cute but there are 25 dollars we've got
a paragraph they're really cute but
there were 31 dollars we can't get those
the album only five dollars this is
coming to be quite the dilemma up again
I'm super Lindsay of Gucci so good but
I'm not thinking that a jumpsuit might
be a really good option because it's
like two-in-one for one price so the
search has moved to a jumpsuit that'll
be our game plan
[Music]
okay so we ended up getting that
jumpsuit it was retailing for $34.99 but
we ended up being able to talk them down
to actually $20 even thank God but that
is still a huge chunk of our ad budget
that means we have sixteen dollars and
fifty six cents exactly left to finish
off this entire outfit we don't have
shoes we don't have accessories and
there's a slave home too
there's a million shoe shops here in
Santee alley but almost every single one
of them is just heel like I've seen an
87 billion pairs let's play but I've
seen like three pairs of boys shoes
which is like fine I guess I mean high
definitely a lot of a good a pair of
heels oh my god guys look we just found
these knockoff uses for homie $15 Lilly
they're not even close to real as you
can see I have mine on right up in here
but they are black and red which they
match perfectly in my jumpsuit and I
would so much other have a sneaker then
a heel on because lord knows I can't
walk in here to save my life and I'd
probably fall over so these might be the
guy okay guys so my shoes earned nine
and a half ten but we only have a size
eight so I'm gonna see if my sister
could do a squeeze we I actually fit
them they fit I need these right now
okay guys we have our jumpsuit and our
shoes now and the only thing that's left
is accessories but our only problem is
we have a remaining balance of 56 cent
so we might have to go a few dollars
over budget to get this perfect red
carpet look but I'm willing to do so
it's a lot we're gonna break the bank by
just 56 cents it could really make or
break a look so let's see what we can
find
not only we have budgets ahem okay guys
we just found this bracelet and three
ring trio for only 99 cents that does
actually put us over budget by a few
cents but I think accessories can really
make or break a look
we are an you sent over budget but we
did it we are super close to $100 and
now that we're over budget oh well I
think I have one last thing that I want
to buy before we go to today's law all
right sisters this should be a super
easy and quick joke so makeup tutorial
today we certainly do not have many
items to work with so starting off we do
not pry in the skin that because that
was out of budget so I'm gonna go to the
Maybelline a brand new super state
foundation I got the shake lassic i
erase all I am praying this matches oh
okay honestly not a bad match at all I'm
just going to blend this all over the
skin like normal oh this foundation
looks amazing oh my god how much what
it's only $11 I'm Chuck the one really
annoying thing about drugs are makeup
shopping no matter how good a product is
is that you can't actually test it out
in store so as you can see it this
foundation definitely oxidized a little
bit and is a little bit darker than my
skin tone so I'm gonna go to my next
step being the Maybelline fit me
concealer and I got the lightest shade
so hopefully this will help kind of
brighten everything up and kind of make
it match a little bit better I'm gonna
put this right in the center of my
forehead and then right under my eyes
and a triangle shape and you guys know
used to be my concealer all the way out
up into here for that really snatched
look but more recently I've been kind of
focusing on my highlights only on the
very center of my face it's a very Kim
case I love holiday and contouring but I
really really love how it makes my skin
look and how it brings attention right
here to the center of my face it's got a
cover of the mustache you guys not even
gonna lie I am absolutely in love with
how my skin looks right now I am so
shocked to the core it looks so
beautiful oh my god
I'm gonna go Mike oh dear some powder
and just set underneath the eyes today
you guys know I usually love to kind of
make a face and plays but I also love to
go in with a setting sprays and like a
mac fix+
in between at my powder steps to really
melt everything in and $20 for mac fix+
was definitely not in the budget I mean
literally fix+ bodysuit fix+ bodysuit
the last night I went to the gym was
never so I'd rather not go naked
oh you're literally kidding me so I'm
gonna temp to bronze and copper in phase
using what's left of this way while do
oh crap oh that is very pigmented maybe
because it's broken into a million
pieces can't forget to chisel out the
hairline of course let's be real though
the true test of a contour sauce
Broadway promoter is can it snatch a
sister knows I'm not not at the nose
contour but I'm also not like happy with
her she's like okay I'm gonna grab a
flat powder brush and dip into the
highlighting excuse me
banana powder side of this duo and I'm
gonna pop this in the center of my
forehead to bring back some of the
lights and I'm also gonna place this
right underneath my eyes and right up to
the sides of my nose to really brighten
everything up and further the illusion
of a pinched and snatched rhinoplasty
next to finish off my skin and base I'm
gonna open up this blush and highlight
our duo from Al I think this one was
literally only a $5 which is a snow bomb
and I'm just gonna play a both of these
to my cheekbones starting off with a
highlighter hello
I'm gonna try digging my brush into this
and actually breaking it a little bit to
see if that way the pigment will
actually you know show up oh there she
is
okay I actually love how this looks I'm
gonna go with a little bit of blush on
an angled brush just to kind of blend
the contour and highlight together or
not
don't love doing this for some reason
you literally have to scrape the top
layer off of this I think it's because
it's a baked formula but the actual
pigmentation of the product underneath
is really really bomb and I'm loving how
my skin looks right now before I do my
brows my eyes as usual I'm just gonna
grab my damp Beauty Blender and
literally the lightest bit of powder and
just bake along the sides of my nose to
really snatch it in a place and then
just right underneath that contour as
well moving right along this is going to
be our brows and for this one we're
using the NYX eyebrow pencil that's
almost four dollars it was the only the
only one that was within budget let's
see how this one compares to our normal
I think
21 or 22 dollar benefit personally my
brow pencil oh this is big I mean let's
be real we do usually love a good sister
a big tip but right now this might not
be very helpful let's see what we can do
here this brow pencil supposed to be
dark brown but it started coming off as
like red on my skin this is not what we
need right now not the worst
I know but definitely not the best I'm
gonna grab my Maybelline fit me
concealer on the back of my hand and
just a flat top concealer brush and
attempt to clean them up a little bit
although I'm really not sure how much
that is gonna help being that the main
issue here is definitely the color of
the brow but I'm not gonna complain
because clearly we have not a single
penny left to go exchanges or trying to
get a new one so gotta make do with what
you got honestly it really doesn't look
top out I'm definitely being dramatic
and the rest my face looks amazing so
far so I don't want to get discouraged
by it just the brows no next of course
comes the eyes and if you're an avid and
creative makeup lover like I am you
would know that I shadow can sometimes
get really really expensive or really
fast for some reason though I was not
able to find a single big eye shadow
palette anywhere at any of the drugstore
as he went to I either found these ones
like white and wild is what I'm gonna be
using today or tiny little single
shadows from like L'Oreal that were like
$12 each hello
I absolutely did not think so so I
picked this but I'm gonna do my best to
create a soft claim look from it today
I'm first gonna go over tiny powder
blush in the shade this has a brow bone
and pop
right on the top my brow bone to give it
a nice little highlight and left before
I apply some shadow oh that's actually
kind of pretty I'll also go to place a
little bit of that right on the inner
corner to really make that area of my
face pop and bring attention to the eyes
I'm then gonna grab my fluffy brush this
is the morphe I'm a four-for-one use
cochise for 10% off for all your future
budget discount shopping and dip into
the shade up transition right up here at
the top tap off the excess and I'm gonna
pop that right in the crease as my
transition shade
well that pigmentation is definitely
rather unfortunate I guess and they say
transition they really mean transition
because that color is literally barely
even there I am like dying to put a
darker brown in the crease really define
it but the crease shade in this palette
is HTML shade which is a major major
makeup no no you do not put shimmers in
the crease literally ever there are
barely any rules to make up with that is
one of them for sure so I'm gonna do is
crack back open my very very shattered
wet-and-wild bronzer and dip into that
with a fluffy crease brush and use that
to define out the crease a little bit
more okay now we're getting somewhere
popping back into the little eyeshadow
pot I'm gonna grab this pinkish shade
called
eyelid right on a dense packing brush
and pack that right on but I would oh
that's actually kind of pretty with that
okay down I can work with that this
eyeshadow honestly is not looking back
at all I'm kind of taking it I'm gonna
finish off by adding a little bit of a
wing using the Wet n Wild mega liner
this was only three dollars you know
those days where our letter just keeps
getting thicker and thicker and thicker
because you keep messing up and putting
on concealer and then adding more liner
then messing up then putting on more
liner than adding more concealer today
is one of those days I really wanted to
find my lower lash in just a little bit
more but clearly we don't have any Tarte
brown eyeshadow so what I'm actually
gonna do is grab my brow pencil from
before and really lightly and carefully
run this right up against my lower lash
line to create a little bit
dimension oh oh that kind of actually
looks good hello hack this outlook isn't
even that bad but I think that lash is
directly gonna take it to the next level
so I'm gonna give my lashes a good and
fresh curl and then apply a layer of the
Maybelline a great laughs that I found
at CVS this one was only seven dollars I
usually love Maybelline mascaras but
honestly not gonna lie I am definitely
not impressed with this one I feel like
with mascara it is definitely one of
those products that when you pay more
you usually do get more bang for your
buck but all-time favorites are the
benefit roller lash and Mac extended
play and this one will definitely not be
replacing either of those anytime soon
so to add a little bit more oomph on my
eyes I'm gonna pop on these lashes from
kiss that I found at Walgreens these are
in the style horse it and I got them
because they kind of loosely sorry Lily
arrived me of Miami looking at these
lashes if I could describe I would
simply say that they are underwhelming
the actual style of the lash is
literally so pretty and for only I think
they were six dollars and fifty cents
they're really really nice lashes
they're 3d they're separated they're
nice and fluffy the band is comfortable
but I would say that the hairs
themselves on the actual lashes are too
short and they don't make a big enough
impact so those are the eyes all
complete and that was definitely a
little bit of a struggle but I feel like
we came through I'm honestly a pretty
happy with these results
it looks pretty beautiful so I'm gonna
go ahead and wipe away the bake and it's
been on there for quite a long time now
I'm gonna go ahead and line my lips
quickly he's in the NYX liner and the
shade natural I really like this color
it was one religion by a few days ago
she uses one and she said this is her
all-time favorite so I had to pick it up
for today's look and it was only three
dollars and then last but certainly not
least I'm gonna fill in my lips using
the NYX soft matte lip cream in the
shade of Stockholm all right sisters I
guess this look is complete normal you
know I would give myself a good spritz
of a setting spray but that was out of
budget for today so I'm gonna go ahead
and change into my red carpet-ready
outfit and I'll be right back to show
you guys the finished completed
oh you guys this is the finished
completed look particularly I have
something else hold on did I send an
extra twenty one dollars of the budget
that we didn't have to create a red
cover for myself
absolutely alright you guys so this is
the Braddock carpet both look complete
clearly I do not have a red carpet to
attend tonight but you know what it's
the thought that counts we have a full
look from head all the way down to the
toes and I'm honestly kind of living for
it not gonna lie it if we look in the
mirror overall this challenge was
honestly really really challenging but
also really really incredibly fun to do
although I definitely love to treat
myself going makeup shopping with
friends or buying a new Alfa or even
getting a new piece of jewelry for
hitting a milestone on social media if
you guys think you guys want your
four-legged such as I get some African
examples of hopefully on YouTube it was
honestly a really fun challenge today to
shop on a budget and this just goes to
show that you don't need to spend
thousands of dollars on a new dress or
$100 on a new foundation or to look a
beautiful and sunny and fabulous because
hello I'm standing right here
alright sisters that is all I have for
this little makeup challenge today like
I said it was a so much fun to film and
I really hope you guys enjoyed it as
well if you did don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below and next time
you go out with friends I need a brand
new outfits and glam try doing it all
under $100 it actually is a really
really fun challenge to do and I want to
see what you guys can come up with if
you have not already don't forget to hit
that big red button down below and come
subscribe join the syste we would love
to have you and also click that little
bell iPhone so you can be notified every
time I upload our brand new video if
you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey and see me on all the red
carpets hopefully in the future you can
follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they're both the same URL in my snapchat
for more or how the teens itself is
genius charleston extra ask after
charles all right sisters i love you so
much thank you for watching and i will
see you in the next one bye
[Music]