[Music]
I'm not your sister
hello all these teams a jerk or
something else is not as a huge truth
James you're rude don't do this as a bad
thing but are you a boy I'm so confused
you are so ugly
you make my ears bleed guards at Adam
and Eve not Adam and Steve this makes
you look fat the voice cracks you are a
copycat he speaks too fast there's so
much hate but I'm feeling great cuz
every viral post you make just helps me
gain there so much hate but I'm feeling
fine you're just a Blake account being
on
[Music]
where are his parents my mom bought me
my first makeup they build my studio and
helped me forward to grab my love your
dad must be proud
yes I swear he practiced her all his
friends as little boys and panda please
kill yourself all these copies your job
is so easy take you for a day your
sweater you cry yourself to sleep
there's so much
I've got a fake smile just trying ignore
it it will be worth there's so much hey
I guess I'm fine I'd rather it be me
than you as a punching bag there's so
much
Oh
you are so beautiful so creative smart
and sweet my heart is so full you mean
the world to me you always blows me
[Music]
there's so much love
that helps me come seeing positivity it
gives me hope there's so much love
can't say thank you enough I look to you
when time cater of their so much love
[Music]
there's so much love
No
all of these comments I can finally say
that I'm happy you guys have saved my
life
[Music]
hi sisters two sprouts here and welcome
back to our YouTube channel of course
that enter normally comes before my
videos but I felt like this one was
appropriate to just kind of go right
into things I really hope you guys
enjoyed this little song moment that
just happened there for today's video
there's been a huge trend going around
recently where different youtubers are
making their own districts and you guys
know me I definitely love a bit of self
roast this morning I was actually
pulling through hate comments getting
ready to record a thing you may hate
comments video inspired by Colleen
ballinger and everybody else who is
doing this trend including at Gabby
Hannah and laurdiy and literally writing
this first some reason just kept getting
more and more and more deep this is kind
of sauce to be a light-hearted moment
but I kind of realized said hey comments
are a really really serious topic and I
know a lot of youtubers including myself
all the time like to pretend like they
don't really get to us and that we're
above them and that were just happy
positive people but in reality they do
get to us sometimes and they've really
shaped me to be Who I am today and both
a good way and unfortunately bad ways
too but it is really important to focus
on the love and positivity because of
you guys I've really been able to be the
person I am today and your comments have
been able to keep me positive if they're
really really really dark times all
these comments are very very real and
these are words and phrases and things
that I have to read every single day on
content that I am really really proud of
and work really really hard at and I
know it may seem like being youtubers
such an easy job but if you really strip
everything away we're just kids sitting
behind a camera and trying our best make
other people happy and to keep ourselves
inspired and at the end of the day it's
so much easier to just spread love and
positivity and not be me and I urge you
guys every single day to do the same
thing if you guys didn't do this video
to say please don't forget to give it a
big thumbs up down below and subscribe
if you have not already come during The
Sisterhood we were seven million sisters
show and also click that Bell icon so
you could notified every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on my makeup journey can follow me on
Instagram and Twitter they're both just
jams Charles and my snapchat for more I
haven't seen side of self and shames
Charles that extra ass after Charles if
you have not yet seen a Friday's a
YouTube video you should definitely
click right up here and go check it out
I announced a very very super sister
special contest and not are pitting 7
million subscribers basically it is a
competition where you get to put
whatever makeup look you want on me and
the winner is getting a brand new
err a ton of back-to-school supplies
$230 Target gift card and Starbucks pink
drinks on me for the entire first month
of school to help you go through the day
and the winner will be announced next
Friday's video coming out so deftly go
what's that if you want to enter and
then watch the next video if you want to
win and if you're watching this no good
luck
also if you like the hoodie that I'm
wearing right now sis's apparel is
officially relaunching next coming
Friday August 17th I'm getting so many
questions about it and I know apparel
has been a very very touchy subject here
in the gym channels YouTube channel I've
worked with many different partners and
they've done a lot of issues in the past
with shipping with prices and with does
everything and it's even a goal of mine
to create a really really affordable and
amazing overall clothing line and it has
finally happened
and you guys have no idea how excited I
am I'll pre warn you now the launch
coming out on Friday it's kind of like
the soft launch it has a lot of items
that we've already had but the quality
is way better and they'll actually ship
on time which I know it's just lovely
but there's also a few new items coming
out as well I'm working on a huge major
second lunch so just stay tuned but
overall I am so beyond excited to have
such as imperils back up and running and
to have all of you sisters looking so
cute and your sisters gear this video
sister shoutout goes to sister Brianna
thank you so much baby boys following
it's a burning oil of you literally it's
so so so much and if you'd like to be
the next videos sister shadow don't
forget to always retweet my buddy links
like a go live on Twitter awful sister
shot that goes to everything one of you
guys out there
alright sisters I think that is only
half of this video today and I really
really hope you enjoyed it
I know it was a little bit of a
different one and a shorter one and kind
of a very drastic twist on a current
YouTube trend but it really meant a lot
to me and everything that I was saying
was coming from the heart regardless of
how cheesy it was and I just want you
guys to know that I love you I'm so
appreciative of you and you truly have
changed my life for the better and
although there's a lot of hate your
guys's love always speaks louder and I'm
so thankful for that and I love you guys
and I will see you in the next one bye