James Charles here and welcome back to
my youtube channel as you can see today
we are not in my normal makeup studio we
are here and the center of Los Angeles
on Hollywood Boulevard and for today's
video I thought we'd do something
probably crazy I may be regretting this
on the end of it but I'm gonna have
strangers walking down the street do you
my makeup hopefully I'll see some
scissors along the way because I have a
very exciting surprise for them as well
but without further ado let's get
started and wish me luck what's your
like your makeup expertise level would
you say I'm too lazy to wear makeup I
feel on a spiritual level sometimes wear
foundation if I'm breaking out once
again feel that on a spiritual level
so as you're gonna play this one Dacians
way I want you to steal my career be a
beauty guru and tell the sisters what
you're doing alright so right now I'm
gonna grab the two face and the color
nude one little squirt
she's have like it covered today ladies
we got Tyler's doing a score as well we
gotta cover everything I likes mr. Tyler
okay are we happy I'm happy with my size
just look at this Wow
natural oh I think this is the fact that
you guys need to have maybe not on
camera I don't want to get too monetized
okay I think the next up is going to be
[Music]
my youtube video just can see whatever
you think a sister could use a little
help track me gal really going for a
concealed look you're not doing your
best work it's the thought that counts I
guess guys thank you for participating
today's video please take a Sephora gift
card and buy whatever you want
we're all concealed but we need to set
definitely so hopefully we can find
someone else and it looks like hello
sister your eyebrows look amazing my
goal is to have your brows I loved on
that's a present artistry right there
well if you leave the next step is
powder but I really should help you do
my eyebrows now I'm kind of sad about
this but do you think you can powder me
up gal yeah turn me into vanilla cake
yes okay let's see what you got let's do
this
we're going for a really powdery look
today sisters all right the side of the
nose you know oh okay thank you sister
you know what you're doing well I have
something for you because yours are the
best please take a Sephora game card and
buy whatever you want
I love this powder that I just got and
chemises things right here we were
clearly baking in the oven gal okay do
you think you can contour my face are
you gonna stop me right up
I love that attitude we have Sinise's
friends outside dragging her for her
lack of knowledge I love do you guys
want to help out too I think sister
Shanice need some help guys okay so
sister Malia picked up what did you pick
up hopefully walk us through your
process well we have all the brushes you
can pick whatever your heart desires
we're not gonna burn oh my god okay do
you know what the goal of contouring is
I think it's like to define your
cheekbone it is yeah
you're really pretty I could tell you
don't really wear much makeup ah yeah
must be nice to not need it you just
look brown for a very sunkissed look
today that's our tour do you think
interesting beyond my video okay I could
do that okay so you just contoured yeah
we caught my light okay I know fan brush
is popular but I'm gonna use like I
found did he just say a fan brush on the
Jamestown's YouTube channel it's the
worst brush ever in the brushes are the
joke of the make up rods yeah good
choice what brushes not the m500 one
brush uh-huh do we want to be like
blinding everybody on Hollywood
Boulevard or like this I thought that
attitude going for the glazed donut look
today of course what is your name re re
we're on Twitter CI sister Stan how did
you know that I was here no I did it
literally pick me up right here then
running behind you and I think there's a
little footage of me running to get to
my friend pull the clips I'm gonna hug
strangers walking down the street do my
makeup
you got this go I have faith in you
faith trusted a little bit of
translucent powder dust there are so
many really hot boys walking down
Hollywood Boulevard have you noticed
sure that did not seem too confident
we're lifting the brow bone okay with a
good brow left you know no need for
surgery no we're not role sisters I say
as my Juvederm is overwhelming my lips i
watch everything about every six months
stop talking to me i feel like you
definitely ought you ready when it comes
to your makeup game I tried my best I
love that attitude do you want to do my
eyeshadow today oh yes I'd love to okay
I'm gonna pick up my shadow pal straight
to use I love more I'm sorry what was
that Brent Morse I really thought I
could have faith in your golf I know
exactly what I'm doing but like
sometimes I just like throws the fondant
this is falling apart really fast guy
alright so I'm doing like a little bit
of highlight ish under the brow okay
that was rude
you just interrupted us so rude not cool
very homophobic what are we doing now a
little dark base okay so we're starting
off dark am i doing this all backwards
you do ever do whatever you want I feel
like you don't have faith in me
I do have anything you hi sister
I feel like doing eyeliner standing up
is gonna be a spooky situation should
try to like sit down that's okay I love
a good sister Bachrach hanging out walk
us through the process I here we go
Oh blow me blow me go what's going on
hello this is very rude you're
interrupting my video I'm suing they
will be hearing for my lawyer
if you want to celebrities [ __ ] look
right here ago do you think you hate
this look today I don't think I can
replicate it but I can attempt to make
something similar I just have naked too
and that's all I own so let's scared
ready all right so we're baking you kind
of want to put a lot because when you
wipe it away it's gonna take the fall
out with it I love that everybody's the
beauty guru here on Hollywood Boulevard
today I'm so sorry to be such a burden
on your life today Maddy Maddy the love
are you done thank you guys okay the
eyes are complete and I guess our next
step is lashes good lord
so do you guys both want to apply an
eyelash do you think you can do mama
[Laughter]
you're the best person reading is how
faith in yourself thank you I try like
yeah let's go back to rested versed now
I think my eyelid right now okay mom was
taken over oh I can feel my being shot
I'd like to give you something very very
special we have a lot of different
options in here you can pick whatever
you want
what does this offer Oprah we were the
red lips today okay are you messing up
my look no you make me look beautiful
hello can people stop parking Bexley
this is so rude
holding a blue left today okay you read
wherever you are I love that we've heard
from red to blue to not nude I'm just
applying it to his lower lip with gentle
strokes I'm trying to stay in the line
because without lip liner difficult I'm
so sorry everyone is trying me today you
are the worst sister except for my lack
of lip liner are we done um yeah that's
very confident and we are just about
done but I would be blast to help you
finish me off with some good sister
setting spray would you be down
absolutely let's do it got you
everywhere everywhere go before I get
myself to grand reveal I'm gonna go
through quickly and ask everybody for
one word to describe my finished look
today okay tell me your name in one word
to describe my makeup look for today my
name is Rachel and her look is
interesting battlin okay okay Rick and
it's amazing I love thanks ray my name
is Kirsten you look marvelous my name is
Shannon sister Shannon beautifully
two-faced oh love that my name is Alina
you look kind of interesting but you
make it look really good though thank
you sister Lena that's what matters
thank you I'm finally ready to see the
finished lock one two three okay we
definitely have a two different looks
going on right now but literally like
we're kind of living the skin looks
amazing it love this contour going on we
definitely have two very different looks
right now but that's okay overall I
think you guys really really killed this
today going into this video I'm gonna be
honest I really did expect this to be
strangers do my makeup here in Los and
us but it has been so crazy meeting all
these sisters I think it has like been
such a heartwarming vote for me to
realize that I literally have people all
around the world that are supporting me
truly I had such an amazing day today
and I'm building so happy so thank you
guys out there for always falling and
supporting you all mean so much to me
and I said that all the time but I love
you the most ever this has been such a
crazy and fun experiment today for being
literally the best in the entire world I
a $500 Sephora gift card that is gonna
be going to one of you sisters out there
all you guys have to do is give this to
do a big thumb so rude you're a little
bit kidding me all you guys have to do
is give this video a big thumbs up down
below you must be subscribed to my
youtube channel and then just leave me a
comment I'll be reading through them and
I'll be picking one winner to ship this
out to so you guys can go crazy and buy
all the makeup in the world if you guys
in business videos today and you'd like
to see a little bit more of me you can
follow me on my makeup journey on
Instagram and Twitter I both just James
Charles and my snapchat for more behind
the scenes side stuff is James Rosen
extra ass after Charles if you guys
liked my good in first
sister outfit for today's video don't
forget to check out sisters Esther Perel
comm for all your cute adorable
comfortable assisters merch this to do
sister shadow cosas sister Maddie thank
you so much for your 4 he's falling at
the party no I love you so so so much
and if you look through the next idiom
sister shout out maybe surprise retreat
of the link so they go live on Twitter
alright guys thank you so much watching
this video today I love you so much and
I will see you in the next one
[Music]