hi sisters I know you guys are all dying
to see the video with me and sister
Jeffrey's are today when I tell you it
is I Connick
you guys better sit down saddle up and
hold on to your wigs because they're
about to be snatched right out of your
head I'm gonna try to make this super
super sore but Before we jump into this
video today I just wanted to tell you
that I'm going on tour in Australia this
month and oh my god I have literally
never been more excited for something in
my entire life sponsored a Barbie coyote
I'm playing down under this month to do
a tour a makeup seminar and a lot of
other fun surprises along the way
so if you're an Aussie baby and you want
to come say hi and want to take sister
selfies you want to learn a little bit
about makeup you want to singing
performance and some fun other things
don't forget to check out James Charles
Australia calm for all your tour
information dates tickets and prices
I'll see you mate very very soon but
until then let's jump into today's brand
new video hi sisters James Charles -
you're welcome back it's why you to
channel as you guys can see it today
we're doing a very very special guest
Jeffrey star - fitted we have been
wanting to film together for such a hot
minute oh man and for today's video
we're gonna do an episode of style swap
and I can't believe sister James got me
over here we're gonna go out of my
comfort zone and we are literally we're
swap swapping tell me how this works
okay so basically I style swap is a
series that I do here on my channel
where I pick another friend in the
beauty community and we are not only
going to challenge each other we're
doing one of each other's iconic looks
but also trade makeup bags as well Wow
so just gonna be like a little bit of a
chit checker ready with us we have a lot
of team just all going to use for sure
so you show each other the looks we
picked out oh my god
ready one two three bam bam
alright so we we literally switch make a
bag yeah I'm nervous
iPod together all the products that I
would have used to create this look okay
gonna hand this to you
BAM alright thank you and I packed all
mine
I use a lot of of course it's a baton
bag alright so we just dive in right
it's just go right in okay well by
covering my brows with the glue stag
well I am gonna do my makeup like I
think James to do alright so sister
James loves the Born This Way to face
foundation all tea all shade or no tea
no shade because it's a really good
formula yeah now did we bring my color
no let's see what happens you can oh wow
you can make a work that's okay I'm
going to Hawaii so I guess we'll have a
sister's hand yeah
now that the Browns all out I'm gonna
use a jeffree star liquid lipstick in
the shade through yes a kind of like
color corrector because I forgot an
orange concealer
okay this is really good luck for me I
think for me you have the YSL all our
foundation yeah I've never tried this
one before so it's cool excited she's a
little light who the dark ones late yeah
let's go right over the bar I was ready
for this okay let's see it we'll know if
the foundations full coverage if Oh
looks like you just literally shaved it
with a mach3 razor BAM if you like we
have a lot of things we want to talk
about today so I'm down I'm an open book
what I'm sure you guys all probably know
if you were like well-versed in the
makeup community slash industry is that
when I started the beauty industry me
and Jeff we've had serious be kinda have
we did huh yeah like bad turn off my
sister scandal there's been a few
moments we just talked about them all
yeah great alright so we met in New York
at actually the Jacqueline's lon doctor
champagne pop James is at the party I
had flown to New York with some friends
and we were there and I'd never met
James before remember you came up to me
I did I was super excited to meet
Geoffrey yeah you guys know that I came
into this industry pretty fast
even though I was so growing as an
influencer I was still a major fan of
all the people that were up there yeah
which I didn't even know at the time so
looking back on like ouch like people
were a little mean girl
so I remember someone I was with was
like uh I don't really want you to take
a picture of James and did it and it's
like this whole weird thing and I'm like
I mean he's [ __ ] cool he's a boy and
beauty like let's meet him he's younger
like I lived for and I loved your
artistry thank you I saw you use my
liquid lips like his liner and you were
just like full-on taking it there so I
was excited but it sucks when and I
could admit it even at my age that
people do have an influence in like it
on you yeah and when someone's in your
ear like kind of staying you kind of
follow along we're stuck so I was a
follower in a situation that I
definitely regret it yeah I mean I
apologize for that night being so short
and annoying but you know looking back
I'm like oh my god it's just so high
school you know it sucks energy really
is very high school the next thing that
happened was a Twitter battle and this
is when I was very small
Oh mystery and I was doing a lot of like
the crazy looks all the time that you
were just talking about like every day I
was pulling out some new look yeah and I
wasn't growing as fast as obviously I am
now because the thought that I was doing
these crazy creative looks I will admit
I definitely did have a little bit of
like an ego when I first came in ok and
lovely a groaner to say that though yeah
yeah absolutely
and in my eyes I was getting frustrated
the people like Jeffery or Manny who did
more classic lamb were growing and
skyrocketing of Fame when I was pulling
out these crazy career books and no one
has ever seen before and I was staying
at the bottom yeah I remember tweeting
asking for my followers to send me ideas
for creative videos or creative makeup
look ok yes somebody replied and said
like oh do swing inspired by Manny and I
quoted it and literally said girl I said
creative you did take it there and I was
with Manny at that time and we were
sitting in a car going somewhere and oh
girl I was it was it was rough
ridiculous and it was so childish but at
the time I was literally 16 I just how
about sorority convicts and I had an ego
and I will definitely be able to admit
that now
of course my hurt feelings no it came
off very conscious I can't read things
on the internet I can't read how
someone's talking it so it came off a
little harsh and I remember you
definitely hurt his feelings no like oh
girl James yeah so I know what's the
thing about James at that time me and
Manny were just in the car like it was
bad once it turned into kind of like a
group beef with friends yes I mean know
when people are really friends you're
loyal and you want to chime in like what
so I remember me and Joffrey start
arguing on Twitter and then you had
addressed me and you had talked about
how if I introduced myself to you that
night at the dock on the back call
yourself the next big thing of the
beauty industry and I was just like wait
a sec that
I may be a little bit you go testicle
but I would never ever ever ever ever
write say that so I was so spooked I
instantly had texted Manny trying to
squash the beef I'll apologise but it
was a little bit too late I couldn't
take back what I said yeah a little too
soon like sometimes people aren't ready
to hear sorry right away be like get
over being angry or like their feelings
which obviously we both can definitely
attest get annoying for snap but it was
a very interesting situation to say the
least
hmm but it sucked because I'm like every
number to like fix it oh really call you
I was just more on the bane of like okay
whatever like you made that coming up
Manny you guys can fix it but you guys
ended up fixing it yeah obviously I
apologize on a personal level too but
even in a business sense which I
definitely talk about later on in this
video here okay it's stupid to burn
bridges the people in your industry that
you're forced to work with and you're
forced to see all the time so all the
time I always try to say drama-free
which Geoffrey can't relate cannot
relate at all times but I think that is
why we're so different and I think
that'll be an interesting conversation
later on as well I'm gonna contour okay
I'm gonna use the lemare the pill dude
the powder it's literally called the
powder it's so boozy that's all you get
how much it cost that's like with tax
$97 yeah I'm just gonna set my entire
face with this and my Beauty Blender
okay I'm gonna start contouring with the
Anastacio classic contour kit all right
and I'm gonna go in with my morphe M 5
to 7 brush you can use code James at
checkout for 10% much your sister yes we
got foam drama to discuss the star I
mean look I'm carving out my cheekbones
hit me what's in him what's another good
moment oh that we would love to address
a makeup repre party Oh sister James
wants to go for the beheading I think we
do help me what really got us going good
here
whoo-hoo I'm sweating and my actual
indirect beef with Geoffrey and it was
with Nikita yes and one day I was gonna
make up forevers party I had gotten
ready and I did a crazy blue glitter
look right I wasn't there
you were not there no this is right when
Kylie was first launching her makeup
line yes and I wore a black liquid
lipstick and it was a hundred percent
Jefferies there's whether or not I hated
him there was no denying that he has a
good formula yeah and I tagged it when I
posted an insert picture as Kylie no
shade literally just wanted the kylie
repos I was really close friends with
Nikita still AM and she came up to me
and was like talking up my lips and
stuff and talking right look
and she's like oh is that like a Jeffrey
weirdo moment crush like she kind of
figured she had the best black on the
scene you know is this the Kylie lip but
I was like no it's Jefferies and oh you
told her that yeah I did think nothing
of it
Nikita hops right on snapchat and puts
her phone in my face it's driving me to
hell and back but I'm thinking if the
Joe
once the stop had kind of completed I
realized oh my god wait this isn't a
joke at all and she was like looking
over I said please don't post that like
please do not post that actually here in
the snapshots
he's saying please do not post that but
she did it went up anyway and I of
course was at the party so I don't know
that it went up until two hours later
after I had already left and was getting
thousands and thousands and thousands of
hate tweets from Nikita's fans from your
fans from that whole squad calling me
out for being shady and for lying and
okay for being just like a shitty person
I was so shocked and so upset you're
like does he not still be happening yeah
so I called Nikita like super scared
alarm like what the heck is going on
like help me Sue's in the club so she
did not get my call finally after like
two hours of texting her she finally
answered and like we ended up solving
and apologizing and resolving it but
because like so using my lipsticks but
y'all didn't tag it like which I been
that before too because same that's the
way I talked about this a few times
before but that's literally one of the
main reasons like rusev asked was
because I Allah we cannot afford a lot
of brands makeup so I lied about it and
then the brands will repost me I love
that we live a market ballin on a budget
oh absolutely
uh-huh you know I can appreciate that hi
BAM okay I'm ready to highlight we're
gonna use the classic James the full
sister highlight moment now we're gonna
use both of these yeah Anasazi is so
Hollywood and the tar chrome paint in a
top band alright let's take the classic
all jokes aside and more p.m. five-10
brush every little sister spritz mm-hmm
anyway like you do it BAM I feel like
I'm doing a drag tutorial right now if
you are okay so I'm gonna go ahead and
start my eyebrows now and these need to
be right pink which I am a floor full
scared okay so I'm gonna use the vivid
bright scream color those are unreal and
then probably mix it with a little bit
of druglord as well but we're gonna
fully start this transformation no James
did give me the iconic morphe palette
the 35b
okay we got the 35b I've never really
used this one the last one if you
haven't heard of this I'm sure you have
because it's James here it is oh wow
full rainbow okay you definitely have a
thinner eyebrow than I do a little bit
more of an arched brow yeah due to load
do it like a uh-huh here yeah and then
all right now I'm gonna start painting
some blue oh look at that brush okay the
structure is getting there now have you
ever done a pink brow for fun no I've
done dry brows yes but not pink amazing
oh we have one more drama thing to talk
about
okay wait ten more we actually ended up
squashing our beef oh my god you were
already yeah oh my god okay I was there
yeah didn't even know you're gonna be
there no and in walks James and I was
like okay and I was like and the beef
and like any drama had happened like
months ago and I was just in a different
place mentally and I was like okay you
know what like let's talk about it talk
about it yeah me and James went outside
on the patio for an hour while everyone
is drunk and smoking cigarettes come out
really and Kay not really ooh and we
just talk about everything and it was
really nice we talk to each other like
normal people yeah you know with no one
else chiming in those energy can be
really overwhelming which a lot of
people I'm sure you guys can understand
after like just watching us but the one
thing that like is really common with a
lot of people in this industry is the
fakeness yeah and there's a lot of
people who are very very two-faced and
are fake and despite the fact that I did
hate Jeffrey for a long time because of
really stupid stuff I did always respect
him and always made a note of this one
talking about him as well that I not
only respected his ability to be blunt
and honest but also has a business
mindset what's to talk about later but I
think the fact that we were able to just
sit down and just be face-to-face and
just own everything that we have both a
dozen barium
it was important and it's something that
not a lot of people are able to do it
was really really cool I'm really
thankful we're able to do it because now
of course we're fine I think the problem
is you have people chime in your ear or
you hear something online or someone
tells you what James maybe no it's nice
to just go with a source like I have
James's number we're really cool so if
there's any ever a problem was like girl
someone said he maybe has said this and
he's like oh just trying to make up some
it never said that great have a hope
it'll be a good day like it's so easy to
have a normal conversation and people
don't communicate I think in this
industry a lot yeah and it's not healthy
that's not okay enough with the drama
we've had it quite the journey but no
yeah we would have no issues for months
and probably never again girl adults ok
sister James is testing me right here
with this moment I love it
I'm trying to conceal my pink eyebrows
I'm scared oh wow I've even really
looked up yes now when someone says that
brows can only be sisters and not twins
can't relate because that's look pretty
identical honey they're still sisters
though have you ever done like crazy
look like this before no oh yeah this is
the first I love that you're taking me
out of my comfort zone we're really just
going there and okay something that's
been on my mind is yeah I have seen a
lot of people come and go on this
industry right I'm gonna call myself an
OG yeah yes and it's really cool to just
watch you from far away and see your
business sense because there's a lot of
people that thank you you know and I
really appreciate and admire how you are
about your business at such a young age
definitely something that a lot of
people should look up to and admire
because you don't play around
thank you yeah oh my god hearing that
from you honestly means the world
I always said and you can ask anybody
this I hate Geoffrey but I think that
the way you handle yourself although may
not be the most professional sometimes
there's a reason you've been around for
ten years and are not falling off
anytime soon and I think that that's
something to really pay attention to oh
that flushes wait - it does ha ha -
really pay attention to and sling that
has made me look up to you it's kind of
a role model in the sense
I've just seen so many kids that are my
age get into this and grow quickly and
then completely throw it away and just
make stupid decisions you know I've
always been thrown who's very calculated
I love numbers I love statistics I love
always singles addicting it really is
honestly and I would so much rather be
focusing on that and being brainstorming
with my team and seeing what can we
really do next to end everything up
rather than like going to a party or
like getting coffee yeah
I just love it because you really remind
me of me at a younger age I think what I
really admire about how you're handling
things is like you're not overspending
like mine is rolling and but you're
being really responsible and I don't
know who taught you that whether it's
your parents and you can tell me in a
second yeah
but it's cool that you're not just being
wild because I've seen so many people
come and go in this industry they start
making money and they literally spend at
all I think it's gonna it's just like
yeah every month it's like forever and
it's like you know it's good to treat
yourself like I love you treat yourself
once in a while yeah but you're not
being crazy and like irresponsible right
which at your age I can't believe you're
not being amazing
once again I've seen so many people do
it and I think that's part of the reason
why I'm not also like with my family I
didn't grow up poor per se but we
definitely didn't have any extra money
at all yeah and I'm mom and dad honestly
did a really great job of lying to me my
brother about it and trying to just
provide for us in any way that they
possibly could to make us happy which
still to this day means so much so
basically you come along you're saying
like they didn't really tell you the
financials just rip right guys out right
from being a child ed you know has
experienced those moment it's cool
because I didn't get that so I'm gonna
share some not it's not dark it's just
you know it's a sick childhood stuff so
my mom definitely did not know any of
that stuff she had bad credit she was in
debt when I was young and there was
constant like money problems that were
always stressing us out no it's cool
that your parents didn't let you guys
feel that stress yes I remember
definitely feeling a lot of that stress
I'm very just thankful for the way that
I was raised with that in the sense that
I did always save my money and I've
always been very very like versed in the
technology and like social media area
even yeah a must before like had a
business where I would make stuffed
animals of the girl in my school
Instagram accounts in the Twitter house
I got bored and didn't want to do it
anymore I would just sell it or just
move on
I met a person where I like to go big or
go home and every project that I'm
working on and if I'm not feeling
inspired anymore I'm like I'm out yeah
and I'm not gonna waste I'd housing that
I don't care about and when I first
started doing makeup my mom was like oh
we were gonna get bored of this in 20
minutes yeah we're not buying you these
lights we're not buying you this makeup
you're gonna get bored in 20 minutes
surprisingly I'm still here after almost
three years of doing a Thai fans because
now that thankfully I have been able to
grow in the beauty space I'm constantly
challenged with new things and I'm able
to kind of keep growing creatively was
just really awesome
I like how you were honest last year and
you were like look
like I don't want to be someone that
just does little bronzy tutorials and
reviews like this doesn't get me off
yeah and I love how you were just honest
about that like I don't want to be just
a review channel and no tea no shade
because like review channels are awesome
when I go to review channels when new
products be exactly yeah today we're
still consumers as well yeah and I look
to my peers especially taught to eat but
abused to see if something that's really
really good in a lot of other channels
as well so nothing against them but for
me person tin spire me to sit down and
do that type of stuff I love overview
yeah where I get to just be really
really yeah time it just bring in from
you too like I said use the same
products every video oh my god I didn't
know yeah I didn't know most like
followers or that I use the same stuff
in every single video a very very rarely
like I think my most recent addition was
the k'kaw highlighting powder but other
than that nothing has been added in - at
all
so for me to sit down even oh yeah guys
this concealer is really really good
everyone's like no it's not yeah
absolutely liya so for me I only do
reviews if I like know that it's gonna
be like a good video and like bacon
sounds like we want to hear you review
right Kim K - today but for the most
part I just try to keep myself inspired
creatively because I know the second
thought I'm not inspired I'm out I
really love making they love this
community and I love my followers that I
have built so it's kind of like an
incentive for me to like not get bored
yeah so I'm trying to close myself to
stay on top of things and really push
the boundaries so thank you for saying
that yes yes of course
alright we are blending oh yeah eyes
coming together oh my god this way so
pigmented come on blue clothes is white
right it's like your butter
mm-hmm Wow sister snapped okay I have a
question for you
what is next for James like do you want
to do a collab with a brand are you
working on something secretly do you
want to put out a makeup line what do
you want to do for right now I'm just
focusing on just getting content and
really like having everybody shaking
like literally I went into this year
like with my team and I said by the end
of 2018 I'm not everybody to look back
on everything that I did and say holy
[ __ ] how did he do all that Wow I think
for right now I'm really focused on my
youtube right now but I'm also going on
tour soon which I've obviously been
hinting that ya know
we talked about that a little no we can
okay so I'm going to Australia for the
first time oh so the times up I think
the tickets will already be on sale oh
you think so yeah the tickets will
already be on sale so if you guys want
to come see me in Australia yeah okay
tickets BAM that'll be very very soon
after this video goes live so my god
come see me down under mates ah yes I do
you so you've never been there never but
it's amazing there's a lot of hot men
there that's my whole point was a lot of
hot Australian men definitely be getting
some sister schlong yeah and Australia
hope there is some hotties there what
are you gonna do there since I don't
even know what's going on I want to hear
the tea so basically the tour is going
to be like a live get ready with me but
also a Q&A it'll be kind of like a mix
of like a regular tour but also like a
makeup seminar yep so like definitely
teaching people but not like the same
educational level as like a lipstick NIC
type or like a makeup by Marriott or
just a little just try out for the
everyday type of people you know I love
that and so will be a live Q&A as well
for all the sisters to just chit chat
ask questions talk about dramas fill the
tea life advice anything you guys want
to talk about and then there at the end
there's gonna be a musical performance
oh my god I'm so excited for Stan Lee so
you're doing a lot I don't know how much
anything is but it sounds like you're
getting a lot for your money's worth a
lot for the money yeah it was gonna be
super super awsome
this very first time ever actually like
performing live which is gonna be fun
yeah the general mission yeah let me
have like the VIP then we also have the
sister package so then all the sister
package people will get to eat dinner
with me after and get a really awesome
makeup goodie bag with all my favorite
oh I love that it's definitely like a
lot going on oh and of course a
meet-and-greet hello I gotta get this
sister pictures together hi your fortune
air flight you're doing a mean great
great so I'm just super excited and I
will be going on a US tour as well yeah
it'll be the same exact show format just
here in the United States in a bunch of
different cities so you guys have to
stay tuned for more details but in
general I'm just so excited just meet
everybody and just yeah all together and
get to really thank the people that have
supported me since day one
it's so like
to hug and be around the people that
really support you and just like hang
out I'm truly so beyond excited and I
said to be so much fun
I just like wanted to start right now
yeah that's amazing I love that you got
me to do something that I would normally
never do it myself think it's really
cool well I think that's the beauty of
this series - it's like it really pushes
people out of their comfort zone so like
if I can have my friends do something
cool and to have a little fun while
doing it
y know a lot of my looks like this I
always like to add a lot of dimension
and a lot of different like colors and
pigments and shadows too just so they
like photograph really nicely and also
would you like more than just a makeup
look I really these two feel like a
piece of art they sure look like one
when I saw this year for the first time
I was like she did that oh thank you sir
I had one thought for you that you need
to leave downtown girl I'm well aware I
do to us I am trying I'm trying to buy
house which I talked about a few videos
ago but oh you did yeah let's get back
to the sister update as you guys know
I'm 18 but because I'm 18 I just got a
credit card last year for the first time
yeah and my account is set up so all my
credit card bills get wiped in sleep in
my account her my credit score should
technically be perfect but because this
is my first year credit it's not perfect
right when you get a house they averaged
together your last two years of income
and of course this year with income I
made a lot of money and I've been saving
all my money very wisely I'm really
making sure that I keep everything
because I have known that I wanted to my
house but last year I made nothing okay
not nothing but I made very little
compared compared to this year of course
and when those two numbers are outfits
together they're not good so clearly I'm
stuck in that situation but my best
friend's Mother's was actually willing
to co-sign on my mortgage with me for a
house which is why insane yeah that's a
big thing yeah but and apparently to
have a cosigner you need three lines of
credit I don't even have one good line
of credit how would I ever have three
lines of credit on a house which is also
so stupid because the point of a
cosigner is to adjust your credit yeah
but like so now they're like being in a
little impulse so now they're being
impossible so it looks like I'm sister
stock but at this what I'm trying to
figure out anything that I can in five
years so now I hope to be moving on to
the next big thing and yes we chilling
in my mansion and yeah
you know like not have to worry about
the type of stuff but I just really want
to get the house and I want to be able
to I want for my parents and honestly
yeah my brother move in with me and get
a car and a dog and lately that place of
my editors and my team and it is most
fulfilling to help others yeah I got my
mom a house buy my mom a brand new car
just always I help all my you know all
my friends people like I've had cousins
and family members I just can't get
ahead because they're in debt I wipe it
clean you know if you know I hear about
that and people really don't ask me the
good day mate there's been some family
members that literally think they but
you're like they're present yeah I am
Bank of America so when people act
entitled yeah get blog your I don't care
here my mom's sisters cousins whatever
like girl I and if you haven't talked to
me in 10 years maybe not maybe just say
how are you cousin not oh my god I need
to borrow money and my girl that's crazy
so family can't also hurt you and
sometimes but they can also be really
great you have really supportive parents
which yeah awesome you have a like one
brother how many siblings one brother
okay sister en yeah and yeah keep you
know obviously you keep those people
close but people will start coming out
of the woodwork and oh they already are
not family thank God my family's amazing
and affordable yep France eeeh and
actually had an experience where a few
of his friends started asking him for
money when we filled our video soon your
Chuck yeah 16 16 oh my god Furion what
is another 16 year old neat what's wrong
what do they need easy's and makeup or
what do they need it was stop it
absolutely insane oh that was gonna
disappoint experience for him this is
rains between me and Ian has really
brought us closer together because yeah
we didn't really help the best childhood
growing up and so many people thought
that I was just using en for views on
our videos together which I mean I get
it the videos do really well so like I
could see where you might think that but
I'm like he's my brother and because we
didn't really have the brush childhood
together sorry I'm taking every possible
champion
spend time with me carry to the bond
yeah and it's in a really amazing strain
stress together and I'm so thankful and
because of that we have gotten so much
closer we've been talking a lot more and
when that happened he actually faced
coming in was so upset I was talking to
you about it and I really had a sit him
down and be like listen you're gonna
lose a lot of friends right yes and it
sucks because you think that more people
would come and try to leech off you and
of course they will they will you're
also gonna get a lot of people that
don't really care for you and you
realize that they were only there for
what you had to offer that yeah yeah
which is hurtful and you gotta let him
go it's well at least he has you to tell
him that yeah well I learned that the
hard way and I had so many people that I
was close friends with for years on end
but I had to cut off for my own
well-being and same in the long run I'm
not thankful that I did but it sucked
and I remember crying I thought to sleep
so many times over it and wishing and
praying that it would be different that
I could keep those people in my life but
at the end of the day I now don't miss
any of them and it sucks to think like
that
and they gotta be you know it's a grow
some people start to turn a different
way or they have a different mindset as
you or things has changed and it's
healthy yeah you know alright so the
only part I'm a little what's right word
sister spooked sister spooked about is
the white steepling I want that galaxy
effect yeah so while I'm getting there a
fluffy brush like that's okay and kind
of jiggle it around a little bit got a
little bit messy and I took a white
cream shadow I'm gonna kind of grab it
on here we'd have to add a little bit
more dimension so that's gonna be like
what kind of looks like stars Oh see I
was afraid that was too much okay well
no cuz if you go over the law it kind of
balances it out there especially if you
add in black to the similar effect
uh-huh oh I got it BAM we live a little
sister steepling sticks are weird
steepling stifling a steeples were horse
asleep
oh no it's a sable steeple is Church
like all right so we're doing mascara
um James gave me the extended play
gigablack lash from Mac sty free I hope
yup I use her but I do not have a style
great so we're doing lashes okay we're
both doing Miami I wear Miami unless you
can't even make that up the last coach
aims for money off oh give a call with
lilies how the photos everybody okay
these go James gets you money off your
morphe brushes your Lily lashes your
Oprah liquid lipsticks your life
insurance your car payment your
McDonald's so James I use it talk about
it works
Oh what is your favorite and least
favorite part of your makeup routine Oh
least favorite drawing on brows it's
just like taking the time sometimes I
mean I love an alien look this year I've
been very anti brown haven't worn bras
in so long that's why I was so excited
to do our collaborative on brows thank
God I just left skin and glow like I
love getting my skin to perfection from
making all the discoloration and
everything go away to full matte Barbie
like I love that and yeah highlighting
and just love yeah I feel like you're
definitely ask in person all right now
we're gonna dive in and use a drug lord
which is vegan and safe around the eyes
and the face and we're just gonna do a
little lightning a little lightning them
message strike a full sister storm
strike love that I'm gonna gather a
little bit of sarcophagus a little bit
of legendary - I want that binky tone in
there okay you know now it almost hit
pound sarcophagus cuz Tana took her
whole brush and just went right in there
so thank you for that this thing mahsa
are we surprised no no we're not
definitely not I have another question
for you Jeffrey hit me baby one more
time yes we were talking earlier kind of
about like the solution mean how is ever
changing and we did mention how you have
been someone who's kind of like the
cockroach video G does not die me and
Shane Dawson I've been doing this since
were too long yes for too long no kind
of rock your brain from being online for
so long what do you think really
separates a creator from being like just
a little fad - like a long lasting
person oh wow and do you have any advice
for me to do that do you think yeah I
think you've already learned a lot at
your age you yeah I went through what
most people go through in like seven
years oh yeah in like one same with me
yeah like I addressed controversy years
ago and then it got Bri brought up ten
years later so imagine like imagining
you you're like twenty eight you're like
ten years later and someone's still
running a mouth
you're like girl it's so far from who
you are but it's the Internet nothing
goes away right so my advice is really
just stay true to who you are which is
exactly what you're doing don't get
mixed up with any more both than people
in our industry I think what's really
kept me let's say relevant and current I
mean it's been a long time right we're
talking from yeah
Friendster to MySpace to Facebook to
Instagram to YouTube it's been a wild
journey and I've always been very
authentic and I've just always been
myself I know it sounds so like boring
almost or like bland but yeah I've just
never been a different person I've
always been me and I've always stuck up
for what I believe in and I've always
been passionate about you know my
thoughts and feelings which I know a lot
all though that we know but you just
gotta stick to doing you and I think
that you're discovering yourself right
now as you get older and you're you're
on the right path and no matter what
anyone says about you you are a hard
worker and I love watching your journey
and I know people whether it's Coachella
or something else people are always
gonna say something about you but you're
you're doing it the right way and you're
being authentic and don't ever let
anyone take that away from you thank you
what that's what I got to say that means
the world even in the short time that
I've been it's industry like alongside
of you I'll actually the change in you
as well because like let's be real when
I first joined you were very oh yeah
loud and it was there's a lot going on
it was every day it was like I was like
oh my god Jeffrey's I was calling out
somebody else on social media yes and I
knew you on a personal level and but we
weren't that close of friends yeah
because there were so many times I
wanted to text you and be like you are a
genius
stop talking yeah and I wish you would
have yeah I wish I would have to get
today why yeah let me tell you why I
wish you would have okay and I've never
said this out loud before is because a
lot of people that were around me were
making it worse it takes a real friend
to be able to sit there and call you out
on your bi yes yeah yeah and I didn't
have that really a lot of learning and
that's okay you're never too young or
old to learn I'll tell you that
yeah well that's very much my
personality as well and like I've i'm
definitely blunt and i've definitely can
hold out for being a little rude or a
little Starkie before to people but in
the long run all like what I am that way
towards people have sleeve my close
friends yeah even though it may seem
real
harsh and kind of like aggressive in the
moment it takes a real us friend to be
able to say that with confidence know
that this is coming from a place of love
not hate and not being angry to me I'm
the same type of person like I want
someone to come to me and be like listen
sister love you the most
you need to shut up you're being awful
right now I'm thankful for those people
in my life and I want people to do that
to me so I think that that's why I had
the same nature to do that to other
people cause like I wish I had somebody
to stop me before I tweeted stupid
things but at the end of the day it does
shape us as a person and it really
allows us to grow and become better but
I find that with that for the people
that are and you're on top of it yeah
and have your back exactly yeah okay so
we have one last step of course for
every makeup routine yeah of course and
these looks are iconic so I think we
have step them in place we sure do we're
gonna use Jeffrey's morphia presence up
setting spray and I'm gonna use James
the makeup finishing spray from
Scandinavia I love this actually so I'm
so glad you have this oh so good really
good
but you guys this transformation is not
completely complete you know it's not we
have one thing left we want to do of
course this is our makeup but I think we
have a little surprise for you so we'll
be right back hi sisters I'm living and
scared at the same time I'm living for
my code 10% off hoodie I love it I have
this one yeah please keep it how do you
feel and miss Gucci I feel it I think
I'll be taking this home with me as well
okay green the pink brows are spooking
me like I am I'm scared
also I always notice in your brows you
don't do much detail either now like you
don't draw hair Ashok sir just like one
little shade oh I want to take a white
and little darker pink I know but so you
inspired me when you transform me which
high of course that video is up yeah
cause I don't I he did actual brush hair
strokes and I was like wow this looks so
real the brows looked real and there was
nothing there I think I said it was like
micro bleeding in my jaw what
definitely go check out the video over
on Jeffrey's channel but overall I had
so much fun a swamp in Southeast today
saying this so cool we've definitely had
quite the ride together in the beauty
industry if you will
sure how recopy and going over and
talking about our ups and downs has been
honestly selling him but at the end of
the day like I said even through
everything I've always respected you for
being an absolute genius businessman and
there's a reason you've been here for so
long and thank you for inspiring me to
work really hard and I'll be the same
way we'll be sister cockroaches yes well
thank you for saying that that is
amazing and thank you for getting me out
of my comfort zone today this was so fun
when I first saw it I was like can I do
that I might get of course I can but I
didn't know how we would get there but
I'm really happy with it I'm like doom
its second and it's fun it gets you in
your like quiet place and you're just
creating art which I'm sure in the bad
for Lily what keeps me going in this
industry yes well thank you for having
on your channel at such an amazing time
this is amazing style swap bam if you
guys know the studio's today please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below if you have not already come
to the sisters I would love to have you
in the family as if that Bell icon so
you notified every time I upload a brand
new video and feel like to follow me on
our makeup store new Palomita Instagram
or Twitter they're both just James
Charles and my snapchat from where if I
haven't seen that stuff is James Charles
and extra ass after Charles and if you
love this video you can also click down
below watch James Rose transformed me
into my name's Charles but with 50 inch
hair we have some other magic in the
works for some content we're definitely
gem and I can't wait for more I had so
much fun today - we do well you guys
thank you so much for watching I love
you and we will see you in the next one