hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel
jumping right to the point because
today's video is probably going to be
very long and talkative but we're going
to be doing a full review of the brand
new tart shape tape foundation there's
been so much controversy and drama
regarding this launched and I really
wasn't sure if it was my position or
place to be talking about it however so
many of you guys asked for a full
interview of the actual product and I
definitely want to talk about the launch
because let's be real this is definitely
not tarts best move there are a lot of
problems with this particular launch
that we will get into in a few short
seconds I am an influencer that's been
blessed with a very very large platform
and I definitely want to use my voice
for good and I believe this launch was
definitely not good so I want to talk
about it with you guys without further
ado let's jump right into the review of
the tarte safety foundation's just for a
quick little backstory in case you have
no idea what's going on here at the very
end of 2016
tarte cosmetics released a concealer
called shave tape it was picked up by
both beauty gurus and consumers from all
around the world who quickly fell in
love with it for its full coverage
easily blendable formula and by the end
of 2017 it was the world's number one
best-selling concealer a few weeks ago
out of literally nowhere tarte pulses
that the shaved hip concealer was going
to be made into a Tarte shaped ape
foundation and the world was a literal a
shock I live in California and I've
never actually experienced a real-life
earthquake since I moved here but I
swear to God I think that on that day
that this foundation was announced I
could feel the ground moving just a
little bit from everybody jumping up and
down from excitement including myself I
was so excited and so ready for this if
you were a true sister you know that I
literally use a shave tape in every
single video it is like the staple of my
makeup routine so I was so ready for
this foundation launch and so is
everybody else and told this picture was
posted this photo has since been deleted
from tarts Instagram page but I remember
when they posted this my mouth literally
dropped to the floor there's absolutely
no other word to describe this other
than embarrassing tart release two
different formulas of this foundation
for different skin types a matte version
and a hydrating version we'll be testing
out both in a few short minutes but each
version came with 15 different shades
now even though 15 shades isn't a lot
there can very easily be a full and
beautiful
from very very light to a very very dark
the undertones might not be the best in
all them but at least there would be a
full-on gradient so most people could
find their skin tone if you look at the
photo that Tarte posted however this
gradient that I'm talking about is
nowhere in sight in the map version
there is literally 10 light shades 3
borderline medium shades or like light
medium shades and then 2 dark shades
just slapped right on at the end and the
hydrating one is even worse with
literally 13 light shades and then the
biggest jump I've ever seen in a
foundation line and then at just two
dark shades at the end just looking at
the swatches again on my phone I think I
could probably wear shades number 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9 10 and maybe even shade number
11 if I had a tan and get away with it
matching literally the person's arm who
these foundations is swatch on it does
not even have a shade match for them
hello it is 2018 and I just cannot wrap
my head around how this launch even
passed in the first place like whoever
put the stamp of approval on this I just
want to talk not only is a launch like
this racist but it's just really really
stupid morals aside and from a business
standpoint women of color equate for
eighty percent of all money going into
the beauty industry but for some reason
they are still overlooked the lack of
inclusion is a lose-lose situation
because you look dumb and now you're
losing money get it together
as a makeup artist who happens to be why
I definitely recognize that privilege in
this situation I know that I can walk
into Sephora and find at least 10
different foundation lines that will
have a perfect match for my skin tone
but so many people of color cannot say
the same thing I just cannot imagine
what it would feel like to be forgotten
about like that and to be a person of
color and to be so excited for a launch
like this and then to see the shade
range launched and just feel completely
excluded and to know that there is
nothing even close to your skin tone
since all the drama and controversy has
started at Tarte has come on said that
they're launching five additional shades
to each line but even those shades are
all really really dark the line would
still be predominantly lighter shades
and we haven't even seen the five
additional colors yet so literally if
four of them could still be lighter
colors at this point they're like six
colors that all look exactly the same so
might as well just add four more this
announcement came with the classic
respond
there are a lot of shades still in the
works that are taking a lot of our time
and a lot of money but we were so
excited about these so we just wanted to
get them out ahead of time for you guys
they're definitely not wrong in the
sense that developing complexion
products is a timely and expensive
process but heart takes influencers on
huge brand trips all the time and shave
tape is the world's number one best
selling concealer and at twenty dollars
a pop we know y'all got money and as
consumers we have plenty of time we all
have our favorite foundations that we
know and love and use every single day
and nobody was even excited about this
launch until it was announced just a few
weeks ago tart really easily could have
worked on perfecting their shade range
to be a fully inclusive over the next
few months and then launch them all
together at once we've already waited
for over a year for this foundation to
launch we could wait a few more months
if that means everybody would be able to
try it out simply put people of color
should not be an afterthought I want to
make it very clear that the point of
this video is not to bash tar I'm
definitely someone in the past who has
also come under fire for racial things
but I can tell you firsthand that the
way to fight ignorant is not through
actually fighting it it's through
education hopefully by myself other
Beauty influencers and the thousands of
customers speaking up and using their
voice for good about this issue
tark realizes what they did was very
very wrong and they'll work in the
future to be a much more inclusive and
diverse brand I am a makeup Channel and
the whole point of doing a review is to
test out an actual makeup product I will
be putting this foundation on my skin
today and seeing how it looks how it
wears and how it feels but no matter
what the results of this review are I
want you to know that I do not support
this foundation I'm gonna wear this once
and I will not feature the tart shaped a
foundation again on my channel unless
the shade range is massively expanded
now that I have all my thoughts and
opinions on the table let's go ahead and
see what the real TIA is on the
foundation so as I said before Tarte
launched two different formulas each
with 15 different shades a match formula
and a more hydrating formula now these
foundations retail for $39 each and each
come with 30 milliliters or one fluid
ounce of product which is honestly
average and very very comparable to many
of the other most popular foundations on
the market thar sent over three
different shades that they thought would
match me best in a PR package but I
wasn't sure if these were glia and PR so
I actually ordered them on
as well so I have four different shades
to try out for today and see which one
matches me best
this is light/medium honey this is fair
light neutral a little bit light for me
I think flashlights Mary is shaking this
is light neutral and this is light
medium neutral looking at all four of
these colors completely dried down I'm
gonna go with light neutral as my shade
today I'm gonna go ahead and apply it
the matte foundation to the left side of
my face just like always it has a doe
foot applicator similar to shave tape
which I actually honestly really really
like for a foundation
I definitely been having some skin
issues recently and Shay tape is very
known for being a full coverage so
hopefully that'll reign true with this
foundation because lord knows we could
use some coverage right now I'm just
gonna blend the matte foundation in
using my normal beauty blender thar sent
over their brand new blending sponge and
also this brush to blend the foundation
in but I personally can really not stand
when brands do that I definitely should
not have to spend extra money on
products just to blend in and use my
foundation
okay well that's actually dried down are
really really fast it's not even like
blending in that easily
[Music]
this foundation definitely oxidizes a
little bit I think because as you can
see when I'm applying it I just applied
a little bit more over my beard area for
some more coverage it definitely goes on
way lighter than it dries down up here
interesting looking in the mirror and
honestly underwhelmed my skin looks fine
it definitely did a really good job of
evening everything out it is very very
full coverage light the claim says which
is great but I feel like I was like
really ready to just be shuck out of my
mind with this foundation because shave
tape let's be real literally change to
makeup game for so many people including
myself but this just feels like a normal
everyday foundation to me okay woah
touching my face the foundation is
already almost completely dry I feel
like I might not even need to start this
with translucent setting powder I'm
spooked mcgoofy
I can already tell you that this
foundation is probably not gonna be
ideal for people with a very very dry
skin I have oily skin and the fact that
this still dry down is a little bit
alarming but there is still the
hydrating formula which does not write
down as much has a light to medium
coverage finish and contains hyaluronic
acid for those of you guys who want to
have a more moisturize Foundation brace
I know I def
love a go to do a skin look and this
might be a little bit better for those
you guys who have dry skin so I'm gonna
grab this same exact shade light neutral
and apply that to the right side of my
face okay wow so even just applying this
foundation it definitely has a way
different consistency I would say that
the matte foundation honestly feels a
lot like the regular shave tape
concealer it definitely has a very very
thick consistency that we're all used to
but I would say that the hydrating
formula it's more of like a gel / watery
type formula it definitely feels more
lightweight oh my god the color
difference
flashback mary says hi are you kidding
what oh my god
I'm gonna blend this side out as well
using a Beauty Blender this one
definitely does have a more hydrating
consistency my skin definitely does look
a little bit more dewy a little bit more
radiant I feel like they're probably
going for a your skin about better type
of foundation my skin tone is even out a
little bit but you can definitely still
see my natural skin it coming through
from underneath I actually do not like
how my skin looks on the hydrated side
and all right now I feel like the
texture is very very intense I can very
much see all my pores in this region and
as well as my acne on my forehead is
looking not the best that's for sure
since this is both a shave tape and a
foundation review I feel like it would
only be right to use the same tape
concealer like normal to finish off my
base today I'm gonna apply this just as
normal and all the high points in my
face
and I'm using the shade light sand okay
well this is actually really hard to
blend on the matte side this foundation
definitely did not lie when it says it
dries down
[Music]
now that concealers all blended out I'm
just gonna powder as always using my
Laura Mercier translucent setting powder
and I'm gonna first start off by packing
that underneath my eyes on both sides
and then just going over my nose because
Lord knows that that gets pretty oily
and wearing a hydrating foundation has
me a little bit scared at this point I'm
also gonna plop that right in the middle
of my forehead days to everything in
place and make sure I don't get any
creases and then just use the excess on
the rest of my face it's just to lock
everything in place okay guys so that is
the foundation all of height and
completely set in place I will say
looking in the mirror the two sides now
look almost exactly identical there was
clearly a huge difference when applying
this side dry down matte real quick and
the side was very very hydrated but with
the addition of powder they look really
really similar
who knows that may change throughout the
next few hours during wearing it this
side may wear down up much much quicker
but I really have no idea we're gonna
have to find out all that being said I'm
gonna go ahead and finish the rest my
makeup off camera and I'll be right back
to show you guys the finished look and
my final thoughts all right sisters
hello I am back it has been about three
hours three hours now since I last left
you guys I finished up my makeup clearly
as you can see I went a little bit crazy
with my look today but I honestly love
how this turned out I'm not going to
play with color in so long and this look
is literally stunning just in case
you're wondering I use the morphe 35c
palette you guys know you can use coach
James for 10% off and now with this eye
look mermaids are shaking back to the
point of this video we're talking about
foundation today and I think I have
finally gathered my final thoughts for
you guys when I first heard that Tarte
was releasing a foundation version of
the iconic shape tape concealer I was so
beyond excited I was honestly ready to
have this be my new holy grail product I
was ready to throw my Too Faced Born
This Way literally out the window and
have it be my new favorite foundation
but not gonna lie after trying the
sounds today I'm underwhelmed
I think the matte foundation does
exactly what it claims to do it is very
very full coverage as you can see my
skin tone is very very even which I love
my under eye bags a 5 o'clock shadow and
acne is pretty much all even out and
covered over which is great because
clearly we have a lot going on on the
face right now the one thing that I will
say that I don't really love about the
matte foundation is that when it says it
dries down matte it dries down
real real Matt while applying it it was
actually drying down as I put it on my
face so when I went into my Beauty
Blender I almost could barely even blend
in because it was literally already dry
if you're someone like me who has only
skin I think that this foundation would
be passable for you being that both the
oils on my skin and the dryness of the
foundation are kind of like fighting
against each other to create like a
pretty good base but if you have normal
or dry skin this is gonna be a major
major no for you you probably are gonna
look like vanilla cake mix and that is
obviously never the move so look to the
matte side I believe that the hydrating
formula pretty much does exactly as it
claims to us well it is definitely a
more medium coverage rather than full
coverage it did a really great job of
evening out my skin tone which obviously
we want in a foundation but there is a
little bit more of my skin up peeking
through I'm pretty lucky to usually have
really really smooth skin and texture is
usually not a big problem for me I'm not
gonna discuss my forehead region because
clearly we have a little bit of a
situation going on up there right now
but on the side of my nose and in this
region like on my cheek where my pores
are my texture actually looks pretty bad
I really don't even have that big of
pores but for some reason this
foundation I feel like is making them
look really really large and definitely
emphasizing them which is never fun and
the size of my nose actually looks
pretty rough which I feel like is kind
of just trumping my whole nose contour
which you guys know it's absolutely
vital to my makeup routine so I'm really
not loving how this region looks on the
hydrating side after testing and wearing
both of the Tarte shape key foundations
I will say that I do like them I think
it works beautifully on the skin and
would be a really really great full
coverage option to all of you guys but I
just simply don't fear control
recommending a foundation that has a
shade range that so many of you guys are
excluded from if you do decide to check
out this foundation that is totally up
to you I honestly cannot control you or
tell you how to spend your money at
least you know in this case that if you
are spending your hard-earned coins on
this that you're getting a good product
in return but for me personally I will
not be using this again or promoting it
on my channel until tart decides to
diversify and make their shade range
more inclusive because as it stands
right now it is very very embarrassing
turn I love you guys that I know so many
avid Beauty fans out there really really
love you as well we are rooting for you
we were all rooting for you but this
launch was a major major disappointment
I really hope you guys are able to take
all this feedback and constructive
criticism into consideration for future
launches there's so many people of color
out there who would love to rock your
products but
let's be real a lot of the products are
really really bomb and I hope you guys
are able to take this situation and
learn from it and do better
all right sisters that is all I have for
this video today if you enjoyed it
please don't forget to give it a big
thumbs up down below and subscribe if
you have not already click that Bell
icon so you can be notified every time I
upload a brand new video if you'd like
to follow me on my makeup journey you
can follow me on Instagram and Twitter
they are both just James Charles and my
snapchat for Barbara hadn't seen same
stuff is James Charles an extra ask
after Charles this week's SEO shout-out
goes to sister Danielle thank you so
much Jane for always falling in
supporting you I love you so much and if
you would like to be the next video
sister shadow makes it always retweet
over the links and they go live on
Twitter all right sisters that is all I
have for this video today thank you so
much for watching I love you and I will
see you in the next one
[Music]