hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel
today I'm done to the very special guest
BAE's rug I thought this is a club you
never thought you would see coming no me
either I know thank you
first today's video has something very
very plagued I obviously am in the
beauty community and Brian is in the
vlogging community but before he was a
blogger he was a gamer a full-time
gaming a nerd and I just feel like those
worlds are two opposites and right now
we're having likely opposites collide so
for today's video I'm gonna teach Brian
how to do my makeup and then after that
he's gonna teach me how to be
professional gamer and we're gonna face
off in black ops I'm so excited to do
this
me too even though we have virtually
nothing in common I think this will
probably be really really funny and a
definite awesome challenge
for the two of us to try out each
other's the thing that we do best also
if you guys want to check out the video
we did on my channel James here turned
me into a beautiful drag queen and he
did a 10 out of 10 job so if you guys
want to see that work come over to my
channel and check out the check it out
it was a great love a good beard and
sister alright guys so since part one of
this video is gonna be teaching at
sister Brian how to do my full face of
makeup
I clearly already have a full-on look so
let's go ahead and take it off and get
started with the video let's do it
[Music]
okay so now a bare face and ready to go
as you could see my face is looking a
little bit bad right now
I had a facial this morning my sister
Yoli glow popped all my pimples for me
just let you know beauty gurus can have
pimples 217 million layers of foundation
we are definitely far from perfect but
without further ado let's go ahead and
cover this up please let's do it
I got you so do you know what the first
step of this is going to be foundation
yeah really yeah okay there I don't
really know what foundation is but is it
this yeah no way yeah okay see I did
learn a thing or two from her
yeah I love that we just did a quick
sister switcheroo already yeah oh my god
okay so you're gonna want to pounce it
in as opposed to like rubbing it you
know like this yeah okay okay that looks
better
yeah all right all right so you're just
talking about how you broke out like
extremely bad do you know I'm not bad
but do you use makeup to like feel more
confident about her like just to hide in
stuff or yeah I actually wear makeup
like as an art makeup for me has never
been something as the way to like hide
insecurities or anything although I
definitely feel like really confident
and pretty where the full face that
makeup off for me I basically just wear
makeup like as an art form and to kind
of express myself I never really need it
to like feel pretty but I I mean like
definitely some people do yeah as like a
straight guy who's like dates girls
obviously what is your opinion on like
when girls wear makeup to me not to
sound cheesy at all like girls don't
need make-up to express how they look
but like if it's something like you said
like it's an art like if it's something
that they enjoy doing that of course
they're gonna do it if anything if
anyone is into makeup and passionate
about it like that just makes them more
attractive like their personality true
it is so true honestly after spending
the day with you like I've learned so
much about makeup and how it's really
not only about the looks like I swear
like it it it feels like I'm being
artistic now yeah it's weird like I love
it isn't it fun it is you want basically
all the comes to that are we focus on
the highlights of your face it's going
brightness and attention to the center
all right perfect
[Music]
okay so next time is gonna be our powder
so Brian is gonna use the Beauty Blender
it is going to dip it in and then he's
gonna set first I always start with
underneath my eyes okay cuz that's what
crease is first okay so I have a
question for you yeah you started on
YouTube I think five and a half years
ago now that's a little bit crazy but
you just turned 21 correct yeah okay so
me and Brian are really not that far off
age wise but you do vlogs correct yeah
now there's definitely been some drama
and the vlogging community of people
making a fool of themselves
I'm not gonna name any names here all
right was it strange for you as someone
who like shares our entire life
the Internet and obviously I do this as
well but to go from being a normal
everyday like high school student to all
of a sudden being watched by millions of
people and now considered a role model
honestly the transition from like not
being anything to becoming something is
a blessing first cuz like it's it's
insane that like this many people
actually want to watch my videos wanna
like stay updated with my life I never
really started to pop off until after
high school huh but honestly it's crazy
to me because I have a bunch of my old
friends that snapchat me to this day
like watching my videos and I'm like
that's so crazy that like that is weird
that they stick with my life that like
Emily we don't really talk that much but
like they still like like keep up with
my day to day life yeah okay so I was
doing my sister research on your channel
and I saw that you joined like I think
it was two years ago
mhm so it was not too long ago mm-hmm
how has that changed your life it's
definitely like a blessing to have so
many people like looking up to as like a
role model but I think that it's
definitely also a really scary thing as
well because like we never really knew
where we're gonna be like it's exact
five years ago you knew you're gonna be
like where you are now I felt like when
I first put on makeup I knew I was gonna
sign with carpet girl and yeah blow up
to where I am not like never in a
million years what I haven't imagined so
it's not like I really started doing
this to become like a role model yeah so
what all of sudden millions of people
are watching and I feel like you do
instantly get that tag as a role model
there's really nothing you could do to
kind of get rid of it we're gonna
contour our face using the Kat Von D
shade my palate right now but it's kind
of like a really really overwhelming
feeling to all the sudden how that many
people watching and looking up to I feel
like it's definitely like scary and you
obviously have to like be on your best
behavior and not make a really stupid
mistakes yeah of course many names yeah
I mean I myself have made tons and tons
and tons of mistakes my it's I think
it's really really awesome to like be a
role model for young people and get
people like watching you looking up to
you that placement is perfect really
okay and then just blend it in so the
point of contouring is basically like it
adds shadows to the face when you're
putting up there on my cheekbones
because it's like the very bottom my
cheekbone it makes it look like I have
like really snatched okay she phones
have that makes any sense no it does
it's looking really good right now
laughter I think I'm doing a good job
what do you guys think I love that
confidence yeah it looks pretty good so
basically with nose Kondo we're gonna be
putting
uline's on the side of my nose as
closely as possible so it looks really
really pinched okay does that make sense
no you don't want to follow the natural
shape in the nose that's kind of the
whole point you try to fake it oh oh
yeah our next one's gonna be to add a
little bit of blush before we move on to
the eyes and this goes on the apples of
my cheeks the apples like a nice smile
like do they look like
even definitely have a lot of color
going on our next one's gonna be to bake
definitely help me out yeah gonna take
the beauty run with a powder on it right
I'm gonna go right up against your nose
contour so right there all the way down
and see how that line is perfectly
parallel yeah yeah yeah on the other
side
perfect yeah so while we're baking in
the oven our next step is going to be
the eyebrows oh no we're on that level
yeah
oh hey not the worst I used to at aside
without brow no I'm gonna make this one
better don't give up on this one
always okay watch I can fix it yeah all
right all right I got this
I feel so concentrated it's ridiculous
I wanna show you how I would do this
yeah okay once you get to the tail
there's clearly like a lot going on over
here right now that's okay if you clean
it up so I'm gonna bring it out and then
up top also needs a little bit more
definition okay I'm gonna pull this up
right here and then bring it down
so has a nice arch and shape and then
I'm gonna go right under
[Music]
oh yeah come up the Little Miss I made
oh that actually looks good interesting
wait this one's hard like the eyes are
actually harder to do than the face yeah
yeah for sure okay so now the brows are
all complete next up it's going to be
the eye shadow yes first gonna dip into
like a light Warren shade us then we
called our transition color and that's
gonna go right in the eyelid and that
like makes everything blend really
nicely together okay and I'm gonna dip
into a more burnt orange shade and
that's going to go in the crease again
but it's gonna keep it more concentrated
so that's gonna add more dimension
there's no way I could possibly mess
this one up you'd be surprised I think
that same shader I'm gonna pack it on
like the outer portion of the lid I
don't dip into like this dark brown
shade right here and I'm pop that right
into the outer area of the violet so
right on that outer corner just like
that see okay I'm gonna grab this
shimmery shade up here I'm gonna spritz
it with a little bit of fix+
and by adding water to a shimmery shadow
it makes it more vibrant okay I'm gonna
pop that right on the inner corner and
hug it right up there that's good yeah
that actually does that fit and then
grab our eyeliner I'm gonna do a winged
liner with the one right here uh-huh
okay all right so like this I'm gonna
take a tiny line think you can recreate
that on the other eye
I can probably recreate like all this
like the first steps then this part
where I have to actually draw it I don't
think I'm gonna be able to do that no
that's true actually I'll make it better
that's the thought let's do it so you're
gonna hold that like this
that way I kind of went a little bit too
high okay so you can see that for yeah I
could see so in that case you're gonna
want to grab a clean brush and just go
over that edge to kind of make sure like
the color is diffused and that'll how we
make sure the colors like evenly
distribute everywhere
there aren't many rules to make up it's
a lot about self-expression but the
number one rule that is a rule is you
have to blend okay blend blend blend
blend blend
alright I'll keep that in mind there you
go okay so the way you're holding it
right now it's bad yeah hahaha since
you've got a little bit of makeup on the
side of the brush if you hold it like
this
not only is it putting it in the crease
but it's also putting it all up here -
because you're rubbing it on so when
you're applying I should especially when
you want to make it more defined you
want to make sure to hold it that brush
as parallel as possible so it's really
only getting the point
right in that crease or even lower so
sometimes you can get a little bit on
the lid but that's okay because you're
gonna cover up anyway - okay is this
like the the glam one okay so it's it's
this one right here no that one no
[Music]
you're ready for the winged liner oh man
my favorite part okay I'm ready for this
all right I used to take art class in um
sixth grade oh I got an F but Picasso is
Shh
[Music]
you ought to end to be as points at as
you can possibly get I try try let's see
if you could fix it up that is
definitely not fixable oh well she's
gonna be really thick so even if you
mess up you could just fix it with
concealer is that like the concealer is
like the go-to of the mix okay like when
you have a good concealer you're pretty
much unstoppable so if I go like this
ready I'll take my concealer there's
like to make it thinner kinda looks
great I think I did a great job on that
uh-huh if I have two glasses here these
are my all-time favorites I'll there are
really lodges in the style
Miami's and you're gonna glue them on to
me today okay all right I got this you
basically want to put it right at my
eyelashes as close to like the lashline
as you can get then you want to make
sure it's sticking you know happy I get
one yeah good get that excited yeah when
I do something right love a good sister
eyelash application
[Music]
so while that was on your face they
didn't do anything yeah so basically
like leaving the powder on there for a
little while it kind of brightens
everything up so like I was telling you
how you put the contour to kind of
create those shadows yeah
the baking powder helps intensify the
highlights to just further the illusion
of like more chiseled features okay okay
so our next one's gonna be the
highlighter this is the one time where
you do want a lot of product on the
brush it off and then you're gonna put
it right on top of the cheekbone that
doesn't seem like something I can mess
up but we've said that about everything
see that glow oh that's nice give it a
little world this world huh yeah so good
okay okay so I also like to do
highlighting on my nose to make my nose
look nice and pinched so you want to
make sure to draw this smallest line you
possibly can right down the center cuz
that really creates like starting from
right here yeah mm-hmm perfect but this
is the liquid lipstick meeting goes on
obviously a liquid it has this little
doe foot applicator we like to call it
but it dries down a fully mapped like a
normal lipstick so you get like a little
bit of wiggle room so you're gonna go
ahead and apply this on me and I like to
over line a little bit only on the top
left so basically I go a little bit over
my natural lip line to make them look
nice and juicy
okay I got this
[Music]
as you can see I'm not like a good
tracer that was something I wasn't good
at as a kid so staying inside the lines
yeah I can tell
when in doubt when something goes wrong
conceal it yeah okay okay so we have one
final step which is gonna be to set our
face in place so it last through all the
sweat blood and tears it's about to go
down in our gaming session okay all
right
quick spritz when you do setting spray
it's really great to use like a pallet
or a fan to kind of Fanning the liquid
out for the back and that kind of makes
all the powders and stuff like meld
together and look more like skin as
opposed to okay a million products just
kind of like slightly yeah all right
really proud of you really yeah thank
you literally like you were being so
patient the entire time you really were
like asking a lot of questions to make
sure you're doing the right thing yeah
if something was wrong you asked me how
we could fix it and I feel like the
finish result came out like pretty good
thank you yeah no there's just so much
that I was interested in like there's so
much more to make up than I thought
there's a lot it's all I was really
interested this is like a class yeah
it's like an art class I feel like when
guys are always like getting their girl
writing like oh my god babe like why are
you ready yet we did go this is why
that's Louise okay I don't blame them
for taking back for real yeah do you
think you could ever like recreate this
look again do you think you have like
enough makeup knowledge No - I think I
actually do yeah yeah I should do my
mom's you see double your house makeup
first show that I had so much fun
teaching you I'm so appreciative that
you were like willing to hear everything
that I wanted to tell you or just tips
and tricks and stuff regardless I think
it's now your turn to teach me catch a
game let's game let's do it okay guys so
we're here on black ops 3 and I guess
we're gonna be playing some zombies
today okay so now that you taught me how
to do your makeup you have to teach you
how to game this is where it all started
for me yeah so I'm gonna turn you into
the best gamer ever okay are you ready I
think
okay I actually haven't played zombies
in a while but I am pretty good at
Bobby's Oh gotta be learning from the
bass I used to be like an avid gamer
though but not like Xbox I used to play
minecraft I used to play minecraft
really I used to look I was addicted to
it because I used to play this thing
called The Hunger Games I was just gonna
say that I swear I used to only play the
honey so you move with this like you
like sprint when you press it down give
me a long day alright okay you aim in
with this with this the right hand okay
I got it
how's your sensitivity here I'll let you
take care of those two zombies in front
of you so aim in and shoot don't die
I'll help you out furnace crowd saving
sister thanks so much
okay oh you know how to knife - yeah yep
gonna rebuild the barrier
I remember this this is fun that uh
makes it three or four years since ive
played bombings but I know it's so much
fun there we go that was a nuke oh I'm
down no no
I'm running I see you guys use this gun
I don't know god no you got this
it's nothing there we go come on and
remember we love saving sisters really
oh there we go good job alright so the
reason why I have to kill them under
this dragon right here it's that the
dragon eats them and then there's three
dragons on the mat and if the dragons of
all at me has started by the zombies
then you get a boat oh we love a hungry
sister you should start like running
looking here I just put weight on to
these dogs I'm right behind you I just
opened this Oh the main thing we have to
do is try to find the power switch no
way I guess so okay alright that's good
wait no please no oh what's this oh my
god you found the mystery box no you're
gonna get a good look
oh it's the monkey school what is that
bro it attracts all the zombies in one
place and it blows up
how do I throw ass did you get it did
you pick it out and throw it okay I
should go get you right yeah now they're
gonna go to that monkey are you oh I
think I'm for a they're not gonna hurt
you
people is up oh no okay it's not looking
too good oh it's the kill you'll kill
him with one bullet good job come on
I used to miss when I was younger with
my brother but I remember before I would
leap out of the closet to him we'd be
planning on like Xbox Live and like
literally every 15 seconds in here oh my
god you're [ __ ] fat can't believe you
just killed nearly I died that's so gay
I would always like people hate me they
don't even know me
yeah it's so intact no I know that it
sucks yeah because like when people say
oh that's so gay they really mean to say
like oh this sucks you suck like I don't
think they need to say in an offensive
way but like some people just don't
realize what's coming out of their mouth
but I always remember like trying to be
in this like gaming world I guess but
like always instantly yeah because it's
like kind of tough when like people are
screaming out Gaelic every five seconds
but there's nothing wrong with being gay
people just say how the pinger okay I
don't realize that like it was actually
in the fencing now say I just went down
again hold on the pro gamer goes down
four times you know just kill them for
now honestly nine round nine rounds
that's a really good sister I'm proud
I'm actually surprised I'm shocked just
how you were shocked like I could do
like some stuff with makeup I'm shocked
that you could actually like kill a
zombie yeah you went down more than I
know actually I did you did better than
me
I'm the naming pro-gamers i her are
shaking based I'd watch out sisters
Faye's Charles Oh sister okay sister
that was so intense I literally feel
like I could take over a zombie
apocalypse being you
yeah sesame yeah okay all right sister
so that is all we have for this
challenge today I literally had so much
fun today even though like I said
earlier me and Bryan don't really have a
lot in common I think it was so cool to
kind of like trade places and see into
the other person's like industry and
what they really really loved to do we
were definitely brought together by a
strange Instagram live occurrence but
I'm say never in a million years did I
think I'd be into makeup like that yeah
and like after today I kind of want to
actually go home and try to do my mom's
makeup I think years old I don't really
how devoted you were to it like you
really cared you took your time with
like thought was so cool it really is
like an art like yeah it's it's not just
makeup like you throw on makeup it's
like precision and like creativity
yeah it's stuff like that so like I
actually enjoyed it yeah and I never in
a million years expected to like be
playing freaking black ops or a
professional gamer but without one we
killed it we got so far
and it was really awesome to kind of
participate in a world that I was once
literally horrified out because of some
like the nasty comments and stuff but
you do have to understand that like
these are really really young kids yeah
are educated and exactly fingers crossed
they will find their cost and they
definitely what they're saying is
offensive sometimes but there's people
like you who are like leading a
community of people especially young
kids as well and you like teach them
right from wrong and that that's super
super awkward if you guys enjoyed
today's video please don't forget to
give it a big thumbs up down below and
not only for Bryan's amazing makeup but
for my amazing zombie-killing skills
Leslie real they were pretty good it was
like that big red subscribe button and
click that little bell icon so you can
be notified every time I upload a brand
new video and come join the sisterhood
if you guys love to me and sister Bryan
together and you want to see more of us
go check out the video we did over on
his channel where I put him into fall
drop we love a bearded system yes and
is an interesting experience to say the
least you know thank you guys are tough
leave it wanna see the finish result all
right sisters thank you so much for
watching this video I had so much fun at
trading places with sister Brian and I
love you so much and I will see you in
the next one