okay
hi guys my name is James Charles welcome
back to my youtube channel today as you
can see how very special Gus with me
hello hi this is just some random guy
out on the street and yeah Angela's on
me and I don't video and obviously I'm
here with enjoy yourself on YouTube
legend a legend a legend does that mean
I'm old so today we decided to sit down
and film two videos together and on my
channel I want to kind of do a guarantee
with us to have a video where alright we
did our glam together and I kind of like
did my makeup and then also show Joey
how we make up I I don't know how to do
it so if you taught me everything I know
now I brought a ton of stuff my brushes
palette stone products and we just kind
of got them together so I created this
green look enjoy create this really
natural boy glam so if you want to see
how your kid of his Luck's just stay
tuned keep on watching first we got our
faces and I'm going to use a benefit
professional it's really good because
well I have a whole skin you tell myself
oh yes I do
well it's this primer primer so you can
rub this all over your face
but you're not gonna put it too much on
the nose area because it'll slip around
oh it's slippery slippery decreed ah
hello oh my god it's so smooth right I'd
like make everything so nice so you're
just gonna rub that all over just my dry
rub it we're not my contouring with this
no you're just like rub it on in yeah
I'm scared
oh I'm going to be better because the
only 80 different the about the area
primer haha like a filled in circle or
the outline of a circle circle I mean
try gosh this is such a good lesson to
teach people you know the bill oh honey
to go laughter
okay okay I always smile when I do
videos yeah yeah I know I know yeah it's
also a musical instrument true you know
you're gonna want to blend downwards and
now I wanted you to point that out
oh I did it for them you're welcome
everyone yeah we was a test as if I was
that stupid minority R is like not have
any kids like bigger towards at mm-hmm
this Balthus mm but now I have to be
really really careful doing this because
the Foundation's gonna go off my nose
Topher bought foundation that's a if
just was talking off to him
jalisa yeah just a she's a good girl
hopefully she does I think she needs to
know how much I really care about her
being there yeah I think it's like the
amount maybe it's like the emotion
behind that maybe that could be so you
oh my god fuzzy fuzzy wuzzy get out of
there she good okay that's it what are
you doing with your picture now first of
all you're covering oh wow I believe you
know Cree says you leave your head back
and put the beer down so that way you're
literally somebody to lean your head
back
yeah and then put them down I fell over
here
and you go to my makeup brushes you
don't have to I like eighty million
different ones yeah like I know like if
you like haven't painted your house just
use the paintbrush for your foundation
yeah if you have any pets and they have
like one of those pet cones like just
who's that camera or hairbrush something
for your eyebrows hey relax it's not
that serious yeah I am
we're gonna move on to eyelashes now
we're decided not to eyeshadow for this
stuff because the video that we're
filming for Joanna is gonna have a whole
lot of eye shadow everywhere but the
eyes so check out that if you want we
got there that we finished the sentence
we're just doing like basic a boy glam
today so nothing too crazy that was so
terrifying right like it was more scary
seeing that box just come through and
they look like little spiders literally
mouths here faces were the ugliest face
it's really good I just want my mascara
right now I'm gonna have some policies
because I want to look cute joey is just
gonna stick with best care for this one
he has really really long lashes you
know make sure you get all the way to
the Ritter to my lab room the room of
the lobster all the way up there
oh yeah Joey is gonna be wearing falsies
in the next look so we've been let's
spin out the crying I just just move
along it's gone it's still there no it's
gone it's gone
oh no I literally just put my eye with
the mascara Joey
we're going to be sticking really yeah
well I just wanted you to know
thank you so much go long ago I'm gonna
write this president that's I'm gonna
campaign no a nation of false lashes
equality oh do you want to do a
highlighter her freckles matte
highlighter okay I lie there
we're gonna use some highly
Impressionism from morphe is like my
fingers by the way that's what yeah this
one by the way um right before musical
change for Chapter seven literally my
uncle James litter code names and we
want to be blinding people like left and
right putting too much on them it was
like are you blind [ __ ] we just made so
many people like oh my gosh you're such
really good too he's your baby right now
you could come a bit literally not the
root of freckles and I love adding
pebbles like all my looks it comes my
favorite signature yeah definitely let's
look at J Charles Signature Edition
until I got me look okay that's
whereabouts we can hide a little bit Oh
girlfriend something that you didn't
know that this is that actually it was
just enough
why are you gripping that one extra
tight I wasn't trying to do the green oh
my god I'm like kind of brilliant like
green like I'd really look for a bag
with a job no wait now this brush that's
so big wait oh oh oh
learn looks so perfect
you're insane I hope I recognized oh my
god you're crazy
mr. frog lips and that's it we're done
we're done okay
if you guys enjoyed this video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and subscribe if you have not
already I post videos everyone's around
I'm gonna try to not be a shitty
youtuber anymore but it's the thought
that good luck yeah literally also if
you wanna go check out the video we did
on Joey's channel I did a super awesome
makeup on him we're not gonna spoil
anything so go check it out it is very
good and it definitely has something
incorporated that we both love and joy
is virtually no Hannah and you're not
subscribed to Joey then like first of
all who even are you but if you
genuinely are then go subscribe to him
all has like sabia below its channel
it's a wonderful time I've been a
longtime fan so I have a really cool
experience for me and we got to go ahead
together I love my fans and follow me on
my social media and my makeup journey
all their links will be below or to
search James Charles whatever tickles
your fancy yeah I'll see you next time
goodbye
whoa look at sit down hold like picture
your card sit go down to know the
highway and like now there's oil like
spilling everywhere I think that's like
the situation that of course um I know
like I don't know I guess I'll just eat
this in the meantime burger so hard know
the roots holy is he trying to save
James