hi sister damn Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel first today's
video I'm joined with Maya sister squad
first today today we have something very
very special plan James is going to be
doing her makeup without actually doing
her makeup you may be kind of confused
how he's gonna do that James is gonna be
wearing a blindfold give me another
chance
Jake okay James is gonna be on the other
side of a wall and he's gonna be telling
us how to do our makeup and he's not
gonna be able to see us and some other
side of wall we're gonna walk we're
gonna love us dividing the you know
dividing it to say like that because
they know that he's in a different room
okay try again try again well they're
gonna see it I'm like 10 seconds anyway
what textures the wall styrofoam here's
the cat there's there's gonna be a
little divider between us and James and
so when James is like he has to explain
it to us he can't touch us or see us yes
this is probably hard for me because I
can definitely man I am a little bit of
an egotistical person and I definitely
like haha I also enjoy helping people
too so this is gonna be really hard for
me to try to explain this to them
without doing it and I probably gonna
get really frustrated sister Emma what
is your experience in makeup oh my god I
was a cheerleader and I did like pretty
crazy eye shadow for that the girls on
the team would like make me do their eye
shadow because I was like actually kind
of good please take that with a grain of
salt okay but like I don't think I'm
gonna do too bad today
okay don't twins are going down you
don't I mean don't winds that sounds
weird okay Grayson honest go how do you
think you're gonna do today on a scale
of what on a scale how I think I'm gonna
do on a scale I think I'm gonna do good
what you just did on a scale how do you
know that I just hate one today today
we're gonna do seven okay I'm trying to
win this is it is it a challenge yes
alright let me try to win this challenge
okay what has been your makeup
experience the only time that you
my makeup and I did half of your face
okay are you ready I don't know what any
of this is to be honest
all right I promise you and I promise
myself I'm not gonna be like oh and and
do like oh I don't know how to do makeup
and make it really because it's funny
when it's not really funny
okay so first we're gonna start off with
your foundation so that's gonna be the
tan jar that has a black cap to it did
you find that there's two of those
neither of them were jars well it's like
a circle it's like a longer fit that the
long one was Emma's shade take you the
back of your hand and put like three
squirts on there but shake it up first
tell me a little bit sister sister
separated yeah oh my god she knows
you're not squirt like three two forests
worked on the back of her hand four
squirts this thing's running all over
the place
yeah you're gonna need a lot looks a
good big goop now use the bigger end of
the button how am i okay well I was
gonna say how am i doing but you can't
see me no can Ozzy so you put on my ear
too late it's on it pounce it yes it
kind of hurts when I go on my eyeball
don't push so hard no they are my actual
eyeball what and then make sure you get
your neck too and your ears a little
orange oh is it the same one that
Grayson you guys oh yeah this is pretty
too tan for you yeah I'm kind of pale
there should be another shade there what
do I do now it's all over my face me
over James I'm you use Grayson's
foundation that's not our problem I put
the two ones there for you specifically
you said the tan one not the pale one I
said a tan boy aback so you're gonna
grab um it's like a tan jar with a black
cap on it yeah it's okay no you know we
can't have flashback Mary flashback Mary
was she was cute oh okay
obviously next was gonna be concealer so
we have tart shave tape in there you're
gonna draw two upside-down triangles on
your face so you're gonna go basically
right from the inner corner of your eye
downward you should have said on your
eye before I started drawing it on my
face jeans what is on your face
so you basically want to draw a triangle
connecting the inner corner of your eye
like are you doing some alumina or
anything on my face right now yes that's
exactly yet to tell that we are all
green socialblade because we're part of
the Illuminati and then bring a little
bit of that concealer up to like the
side of your nose to a sister snatch Naz
yeah
now I also put a dot right in the center
of your forehead above your eyebrows
like right in the middle got it okay no
this is a prank no okay
another center here ten who invented
this
can someone me did you really know do
you feel like around Ted so like it's
hard for me to find it but yes okay and
then like draw a line like underneath
that like tracing the bottom of your
cheekbone all right now time for powder
you gotta set it blend my eyes into yeah
you didn't say that okay now you're
gonna guard the laura mercier
translucent setting powder it's like the
bait tub with the cop okay open it up
and pour a little bit into the cap okay
this smells kind of good the powder
supposedly vanilla yogurt a little bit
but in a good way and you like I'm gonna
going to look like flashback Mary I
think this is where my downfall is no
there's a lot of other places that you
can fall down later
now we're gonna contour so now that
you're all flat skin tone and you have
your concealer on to brighten up the
center of your face we need to use
contouring to chisel out the outside
edges of your face it's nap time
yeah let's do it where is this brush
jeans it should be it's in there it's a
it's a bigger brush yeah it's this I
can't see it I don't see it angle on a
brush it's just it's a like mushroom cat
mmm
turn to the side and there should be it
still really got a slight angle like one
end to be like taller than the other one
no some of the brochure should be
talking yeah there's more like that but
it's dark brown you said a light one
there's another one that's white and it
might have like some kind of brown at
the tip of the brown no sis oh wait yeah
yeah yeah but it's like red don't tell
me it's not red I can't see it well you
will in the future
hold your James don't tell me this is
not red well someone down future James
okay pause this video text me an apology
right now and you're gonna want to dip
into the metal
shade and the bottom row bottom ooh yes
and they're gonna want to use that to
chisel out the corners of your forehead
and then also your cheekbones how would
you put on there the whole thing okay
great now we have to contour your nose
so there's a brush and this is when we
snatch up so there's a brush and they're
angled a fluffy brush but it's small and
it has a pink handle and it's dual ended
now you're gonna dip into this contra
palette again but it's the bottom left
shade not the bottom metal and use the
fluffy and what I'm trying to do as a
tree Domino's don't blend it like all
the way down the side to like just keep
the two lines like right at the top
Center with a little sisters that brings
get made fun of in middle school they
nose was so small I thought it sounds
like the opposite of a problem 100
reading an issue it was like your eyes
are so small it's so weird I was like
dude that's not like all evoke Twitter
are creating it as you are there is none
see James and Emma getting political
play so now we're gonna grab the blunt
okay that's when me second Billy
understand you're saying is that's not
English that's Miranda sings grab the
brush its it has a black handle its
fluffy and angled okay all of them have
a black handle so that's not gonna be
myself or me well I didn't ask for the
attitude okay and it has a little bit of
pink on the tip so yeah those we love a
good picnic tag okay now put that right
on your cheekbone kind of like on like
the apple of your cheek right kind of
like above your contour okay what's the
apple of my cheek liquid what Oh Rosie
do you mm-hmm now you're gonna wanna
grab the Beauty Blender once again and
dip into the powder and we're gonna bake
how does he do big in this a makeup
video not cooking so really get a lot of
the pink on there right the pink yeah
use of the powder the powder the pink
powder the Mac alone no James you need
to specify the Dana put a little bit
right on the center but what put a
little bit kind of a lot of that you
just said that we good
this is not bully James Charles time
who's helping you
Thank You Grayson love you
okay now you're baking yep that is that
what is that what it's called
yes sir bake in the oven at 300 degrees
babe as I say you and I already have
pretty like full eyebrow so maybe we
should just skip filling the man yeah
there's like a silver container in there
do you see it the bronze oh yeah
okay so you're just gonna like brushed
up through your brows and like kind of
like brush them upward so just kind of
like put them in the right place I think
they're in the right place
well yeah but like making sure that get
long don't argue with me just do it
no not gonna do it and don't listening
to you Jean I'm just gonna do this by
myself
Oh My yes we were doing so good up until
now no I'm on do it I tried James oh
this one's even more first no I was
doing so good too
do you think I could like clean it up
with concealer y'all ready attacks okay
I feel like that good sister help you're
gonna grab the concealer again and then
in there there's a brush that has a
black handle and it's like a it's a flat
like square brush you're gonna define
underneath your eyebrow like you know
how my dough is very sharp yes you do
just go right under the brow and they
carve it out it's like making like a
lime does that make sense or sense okay
great Wow not be able to see your help
is so sister stressful okay how do I
like blend that out it's a fluffy brush
it has the block Brussels in like a
brownish top mm 335 yes yes yes I'm
doing my eyelids right you said yeah put
a little all the concealer on there
you've done how often do you do your
makeup like this every day usually or
every few days whenever I'm filming oh
yeah doesn't go round brush in there
it's like kinda like a dome shape and
like it definitely is already dirty with
concealer on it all these brushes are
doing yes they are but this one is like
dirty with concealer on it okay did you
find it yeah is it big it's like kind of
bad
it sits in between big and small yes
medium medium yes got it
I'll then use that to pack the powder on
top of the eyelid to set everything in
place
if I'd use the powder that's on my shirt
to pack everything to say to employees
humbly I ate a little bit of it and it
doesn't taste in my mouth
yeah that's pretty good can I eat it if
you would love to I know I won't love to
we're all hungry so yeah tastes like
vanilla yogurt oh my god that's what
Grayson's had that's what I said before
oh did you just do James overworking me
he's not feeding me me powder it taste
so bad Triana and you sure you eat it
yes sort of God a little bit like ways
like gets on your tongue whenever you're
blending it it's so good well I mean no
but anyway oh my god how much you eat
Aang wait not supposed to eat that much
so I like do look like flashback Mary
with a little bit of contour right now I
think I'm on the right track with some
nice little eyebrows they're not that
bad anymore they were way worse before
so feeling really nice and confident and
fresh and clean about it and good and
good and fresh yeah yeah okay I shadow
all right what are we feeling um let's
just like a warm smoky eye look so grab
on one of the funky brushes that I gave
you that has white hairs and probably
has a little bit of oil orange on the
tap
now on the top left-hand side of the
palette lives like a mac and cheese type
color yes yes dip into that one lightly
and then you're gonna put that right in
the crease of your eyelash okay I I kind
of know how to do this okay cool
we'll see how this goes okay cousin what
are you doing I'm trying to do my eyelid
crease but it's giving me a little
trouble I can't get in
I can't get in the inside of my eye does
it matter what I only got like the
outside half of my eye
a little bit a fall out but I mean
that's that's expected right how much
are you using I mean not that much but I
just also didn't have my brush enough
well sister James listen to me you know
you're on the outside half like you've
got outer edge like towards your temple
yeah yeah why'd you get on the inside
because it's a Fed brush that's why it's
not that big what are you doing the
brush I'm sucking it hitting okay grab
another fluffy brush smaller than that
one
okay and I probably should have like a
burnt orange shadow on it Oh hope that
whistle I think so
now you're gonna want to dip into it
it's like a burnt orange there's no yes
okay the one next the one on the right
of it is no the one on the left of that
is the more orange with all the right of
it when your advisers colorblind we'll
just go with this color okay gray and
you wouldnt want to play tap off the
excess because you don't want too much
to that color and you're gonna want to
put that also in your crease but more on
the outer like the outer half kind of
link blend and like as if it was like
like a hook like kinda like going from
the outside of your eyeball - like
upwards into the crease like kind of
ground a little bit like a drag queen Oh
but like any good way though it should
be the same color but you should pack it
like right and I'm like the outer area
of your eyelid probably did that already
well I'm a step ahead of you I'm done
okay okay next okay I think so
next up is gonna be um the glitter whoa
yay sister sparkle oh hey did I why I
was really good okay oh where did you
cut the crease then we're ready to cut
the crease okay I love when you're I
never cut the crease there's like a
rectangular object in there and has a
gold cap and it's like how do you
remember all this I'm just like thinking
right now holy how do you remember all
this so since we just ordered a pizza
right picture like a corner of a pizza I
think it's better be the cheesiest thing
ever shut up so start from the tear duct
and go up around dad like towards the
middle of your crease and then fill it
in so the entire inner half of your
eyelid is glitter tilt your head back
and look in the mirror
so then you have access to it without
having to like access to it I've
unlocked access to my eyelid how's it
look actually not bad like I mean it's
not my best work
this is like the tutorial for somebody
who like it's like me
it's an attainable look you know what
I'm saying right now it's time for
eyeliner I need the support that I want
to skip don't get that off sad when
James Charles forces you into doing
things that you don't want to do excuse
me have you ever done a winged liner
before no oh okay let's get a nose wire
okay so grab it's like a brown stick got
it it's shimmery it says Tom for your on
it okay there's two ends to it wine it's
like a really really tiny point and
one's like more of like a felt tip
marker point got it you want the felt
tip side okay so you're gonna start off
by drawing a line from like a very thin
line from the very outer like corner of
your eye it should be like thin thin
yeah right about that um help think did
you make it um that's what she said I'm
when I get nervous I start saying that's
what she said jokes I could clean that
up with concealer though I think
basically it's like your boyfriend
cheats on you right and you thought he
was the man of your dreams he was
beautiful he was perfect and then you
know a new man comes into your life and
he's like 30 times hotter not only that
listens to the same type of music as you
not only that but also I'm not gonna say
that on James's channel and moral the
story is you're now winning right it's
like the best rebound you've ever had
and that is how I'm feeling right now
with this winged eyeliner except for
that I am still lonely and single that's
the difference
me that looks good that looks good woah
really yeah naughty front of you is
where you lose me James why
hello yeah I was focusing that step just
ruined it for me
what did you do you ruin down you ruined
a James I did not what the [ __ ] ever I
just ruined it no Kristen I'm so pissed
right now
why cuz you can ruin my face I just
actually ruined my wing blinder I just
tell you how to do it so Wow
I'm so pissed right now why cuz I don't
want to lose okay so next is gonna be
laches do I have to pick these up with
tweezers yes now got the mini pair of
scissors in there you want to trim off
like a tiny little bit on each under the
lash got it okay now there's the glue in
there on it okay now just paint that
onto the lash band okay so is the glue
on there yes okay so you want to like
blow on it a little bit so grab it with
the tweezer okay tilt your head back
slightly and put your face I close to
the mirror and then you want to plop
your lash on going from the center of
your eye and place it like right on
there as close to the lash line as
possible and then once the center of the
lash is like on the center of your
eyelid use the tweezers to make sure
that the outer corner and inner corner
are both on your eyelid fully so just
take the top okay tape whoa really good
and you want to put it down as close to
your lash line as you possibly can it's
like it looks like it's growing out of
your lens it's not make sense
it didn't stick I stuck it right where
you told me to stay take the lock off
okay and then put more glue on there and
then blow on it a little bit now like
we've it around a little bit don't put
it on right away like wait for it to get
tacky and it's so cute how you're
focusing so hard on me yeah use it work
okay now we're gonna put our mascara on
the upper and lower you're gonna put it
on the upper lashes really carefully
because if you go on too hard it can
pull the wash off so you just kind of
want to use that and do it lightly to
blend together your real lashes or the
one's and just kind of brushed them
upwards I put my something I am is your
crank no I'm a man people leave their
mascara all chunky like it's really easy
right I don't understand
Wow okay yeah I'm good
okay oh my god James you're gonna hate
this should I blend out the big now I'm
so sick of it yeah you can get rid of it
now we're done with last chance so fresh
wanna grab a big fluffy brush and wipe
off the baked powder that's sitting
there there's a big powder on me
it should be wait at all did you already
wipe it off I blended it in how long ago
when I first put it on I look at it were
supposed to be there that whole time Oh
is there no powder there anymore no no
really
Oh where'd it go I don't think it was
ever there really
okay so first you're gonna want to
spritz your face with the fix+ like ever
something in my flake sister spreads
oh no dip the brush into the highlighter
okay and put it on the very top of your
cheekbones I'm actually like not bad at
highlight because I feel like that's the
easiest part
yeah just like right on the cheekbone
I'm like right at the top are you
glowing for the gods glowing for the god
sister what's next okay now there's a
little pencil brush in there and four
three one yes okay I mean you're gonna
dip into the highlighter again okay and
then you're gonna use that highlighter
and you're gonna want to put it right in
the inner corners of your eyes okay
right like under the arch of your
eyebrow but below it oh yes I do this -
okay great on your brow bone
okay show you oh my nose that's my part
the nose see how I'm a basically told
like an exclamation point so like draw a
line right down the center of the bridge
right in between those two contour lines
don't make it too wide or that ruins the
illusion and then stock right before the
tip and then leave a little space then
put a dot right on the tip like to blind
all the haters 100% sister yeah they
give her face like a good spreads
chuckles my first probably yeah don't
hold it too close either - this is
giving me trooper phobia
it has a quartz in it what ties this
doesn't it
no it's disgusting okay is that are you
sad opening the highlighter again beauty
is pain all right good yeah no I lost
the final stop
yep look buddy doodahs oh yeah okay so
it's like a pinky nude shade and it's
bra got it
oh you know just fill in your lips just
like normal I'll just follow me lip boy
yes on the top lip you want to over line
just a little bit slightly you supposed
to look stupid we use a little bit yeah
just go slightly over your top lab
uh-huh I see just want to like draw
though upset and then for the upper lip
you're gonna want to over draw it a
little bit cuz your upper lip is kind of
small
uh-huh okay I'm done are you done yeah
whoo you're done yes I thought I did
good these flashback mary who do you
think did the best james overall out of
10 give everyone an out of 10 yes even
zeis give you 10 out of 10 but his skin
is that up 1 out of 10 it all adds up
face out of 10 everything yep
start that millions okay yeah we need to
server the tyranny work over here yeah
there you go okay I'm on your cut crease
is actually really phenomenal thank you
um it's falling off a little bit I do me
now for two hours the true skin doesn't
look that bad I'm gonna give it okay you
stand out your skin looks the best it
looks the smoothest yeah by far okay I'm
gonna give Emma a
that is generous a sex a sex okay I'm
gonna give you a seven and a half eight
oh no a seven okay for 7mf okay seven
them how your eyes look great it's
literally my first time ever doing
makeup and I'm gonna have to give place
in honestly a nine
don't make me boy I give myself a night
as well I get worse overnight as well
the idol if you literally said that I
shadow is perfect it's not it's blended
very well the only thing I'm I suppose
is the weight I was about to put you to
face it those are hard
you killed it was so good he's at the
bottom of your wing is awful like he
says some flaws about his wings they're
not my one look at me look down look at
me look he looks creepy I can't even
look at him yeah it actually is very
frightening yeah all right let's go I
want to eat I'm gonna remember okay
don't hey do not touch what I figure I'm
gonna rip your fake lash off I wouldn't
be freaked lashes on with mighty hungry
obviously we resist eels with lipstick
on them these lips you gonna see that's
when you know yeah it's trash yeah yeah
alright guys today I am honestly so
proud of everyone today and the sisters
spawn I think you all absolutely killed
it and thank you for taking the time and
listening and learning I hope you all
enjoyed yourselves if you guys know the
series today please don't forget to give
it a huge thumbs up down below this took
us way too long to film and so much work
from them so major applause and also
leave us a comment down below and tell
me who you think won this mini makeup
challenge also we were throwing up back
to the olden days of YouTube and we I
say today three way sister Club which
was honestly it's so much fun over on
8th in Grayson channel we did a sister
book bong and over at Emma's channel we
are teaching her how to be an LA sister
the links to all those videos will be
down below slipper get to go check them
out as described in that if you have not
already they're pretty good and press if
you like to follow me on the make up
dirty girl band scratch but are they
able to same shelves my support behind
see there's no stress after Charles that
was so good our childhood don't twins
grease and it's evening and subscribe we
post videos and I don't even have an
upload schedule I said I'm ready I'm
ready for the gym Sherlock really
flirting the Dolphins are two minutes
compilation yeah someone make that
please it's gonna happen it's I'm having
a million you didn't subscribe to me if
you want or don't it's fine with me
this videos sure shot it goes to
Veronica thank you so much ray boys
falling in supporting do I love you so
so so much and if you'd like to in the
next videos sister shadow don't forget
to way street we're dealing something go
live on a Twitter alright guys thank you
so much for watching I love you and I
will see you in the next one