hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video I have something very very
special plan that I actually don't do
very often and that is a review I really
don't do reviews that often mostly
because I have my favorite products that
I like to stick to an every single
makeup look but also when it comes to
reviews people love love love to share
their opinions and if you love a product
you're eating somebody's ass or you're
being paid to do so and if you hate a
product you're jealous you're angry
because you're not on a PR list or who
freaking knows every time I do a review
and I read the comment I could just feel
the brain cells being sucked right out
of my head but when I saw this launch
and when I saw the price tag and you
guys know exactly what I'm talking about
based on the title of the video I'm
talking about the brand new Kylie
cosmetics 360 dollar brush that I had to
show you guys the Realty I am gonna do
my entire makeup routine today using the
brand new Kylie brushes I'm gonna try to
use every single brush in here in some
difference that with my makeup routine
to show you guys if the brushes are
really worth the three hundred and sixty
dollars I haven't even started yet but
just going into it I will tell you guys
they're probably not gonna be worth it
so I picked up dupes of every single one
of the Kylie brushes from morphe I'll
tell you guys right now they are much
much much cheaper so I'm gonna doing a
1/2 my face using the Kylie brushes and
the other half my face using the same
exact brush do and we're gonna see what
style looks better in the end
before we get to the full review I do
want to disclose something because this
video will not go all the way up my
Fenty Beauty video went I absolutely
love Kylie she's honestly one of my role
models I think she is beautiful and I'm
very very hard-working woman I am very
proud of her and her makeup line I think
so it's been absolutely incredible and
she is obviously killing it regardless
of what you think about her those are my
opinions you don't have to share them
not being said I am NOT on her PR list I
did not get these brushes sent to me
early in the mail I was actually gonna
have to wait another two weeks to get
them and order them just like everybody
else when they went online to the public
but major shout out to my baby but Kris
and Dominique who let me borrow her set
early I'm gonna give these brushes a
fair shot if they are amazing you will
see if they suck you guys will
definitely see I really could not care
less about the fact that I'm not on her
PR list
like I said beforehand influencers
literally cannot win I love currently
but I'm not on her PR list so apparently
I'm so angry
so hopefully this evens out the playing
field so I can give you guys a full
unbiased review that would have been
unbiased Vergara
last by these comments Oh there are a
lot sometimes now that that is all been
said let's jump into the damn brushes so
for the holiday season Kylie cosmetics
launched chart silver luxury brushed sat
which is right here it comes with 16
different brushes and the set of all 16
retails online for 360 dollars oh my god
you get all the brushes and a little
silver carrying case with them as you
can see all the brushes have little
white hairs some of them are dual fiber
and some of them are just a regular
brushes and apparently Kylie said on
Twitter that these are all real hair as
well they are not synthetic
so that means they are I think not
cruelty free and not vegan so if that's
something that you were very out of it
about this brush is probably not the
brush that for you
I've talked about this a few times
before but I per say I'm really not the
biggest fan of brush sets when people
ask me what types of brushes to order I
always tell them to go through a website
and really pick up brushes that they
know they're going to use based on their
different steps of their makeup routine
everybody has different techniques and
different brushes that they like to use
for different things and I think when
you order a brush that they're always
gonna be a few brushes in there that you
will literally never touch simply
because of your personal choices when it
comes to makeup and that is really okay
but it's obviously money down the drain
I will say though looking at all the
Kylie brushes laid down next to each
other there really are not that many
brushes that I don't think I would pick
up and I feel like I could get a good
use out of all of them so at least
that's a really great thing if you are
someone like me though and don't like
brush sets all the brushes will be sold
individually online as well when the
full set launches I'm gonna go through
all the individual prices as I go
through my makeup routine but all
together these brushes equate to three
hundred and seventy eight dollars and if
you buy the set it takes eighteen
dollars off and goes to 360 what a steal
on the contrary I told her of all the
closest dupes I could find from morphe
and if you order all of these sixteen
brushes your total comes to one hundred
and fifteen dollars but if we use Co
change or ten percent of your purchase
which you've definitely should it
becomes one hundred and four dollars
which is two hundred and fifty six
dollars cheaper than the Kylie brushes
now that we have the price is all fully
broken down let's go ahead and start our
makeup on this side of my face I'm gonna
use the Kylie brushes and on this side
I'm gonna using the same dupes from
morphe and we're gonna see what side
performs better
let's go sir do my foundation today I'm
gonna use my Too Faced Born This Way
Foundation do you guys know this is my
all-time favorite and for my less on my
face I'm gonna use the Kylie brush
number two which is the large stippling
brush this brush has and his
multi-purpose face and body brush ideal
for blending liquid or cream makeup and
that retails for $30
the closest dupe I could find for morphe
was the mb5 brush as you can see the
color is different but obviously they're
both duo fiber brushes of a very very
similar shape and this one is $10 this
is definitely an interesting feeling you
guys know that I don't really do my
foundation where the brush is that often
and also this is a duo fiber brush so
it's really not that dense which is
definitely giving us like my coverage
but oh I really like this for the neck
so big so it lets me blend it in easily
that was good but over the face I don't
know how I'm feeling for a duo fiber
brush I'm honestly pleasantly surprised
with this application it definitely did
a really good job of giving me even
coverage all throughout but I will say
that census is duo-fiber
you can obviously see that there's a lot
of product in the brush now left over
and it's really not that dense so I do
feel like the coverage as an S fill as
normal if I applied it with a sponge
looking in the mirror the application
looks absolutely identical on both sides
they both honestly did a really good job
of blending it out the coverage is
decent I'm gonna take a little bit more
of that on a Beauty Blender and apply it
to my nose because both brushes did
leave my nose a little bit sad and you
guys know that is always a struggle area
for me these brushes both did a
perfectly fine job of doing my
foundation except one is $30 and one is
$10 and Kylie's line she does not have a
brush dedicated to concealer and I
personally never use the brush when it
comes to concealer either so I'm just
gonna go ahead and apply my shake paper
in the shade light as normal before I go
in and blend this out I'm going to cream
contour my face today using my benefit
hoola stick you guys know that I really
don't do this that often but Kylie does
have a good a cream contour so for my
Kylie side i'm gonna using the kylie
jenner brush number seven which is the
medium stippling brush and these retails
for $22 and on my morphe side i'm gonna
using the m49 to literally the exact
same brush and this retails for $8 I'm
gonna put this in in the hollows of my
cheeks
on the jawline and then in the corners
on my forehead as well
oh just like the first brush as you can
see this is doing a really really great
job blending everything out there are no
streaky lines that everything is looking
at really really seamless I'm not gonna
go over to the morphe side so before
actually use these I thought that these
brushes were really really similar
shapes as you can see from this angle
but if we turn them to the side the
Kylie brush is actually a lot more thick
than the morphe brush I am noticing
right away that I have to blend a little
bit harder for the morphe brush and this
shape is actually not gonna lie a little
bit better but then again $22 $8 here's
the Kylie side and here's the morphe
side once again application looks
exactly the same I'm just gonna add a
lot about a shade table right here to
cut the contour and then I'm going to
blend everything out just up my face in
place today I'm going to using my
setting powder mixture you guys almost
my all-time favorite and for my Kylie
side I'm gonna be using the Kylie brush
number three which is the medium tapered
brush which retails for $28 and
originally for the morphe side I had
picked out the m5 30 but now looking at
these I'm realizing that these shapes
are nowhere near similar so I definitely
will take on that one and instead I'm
gonna be using the morphe r3 brush which
retails for or $12 you guys know that I
usually use my Beauty Blender when it
comes to setting powder so this is gonna
be a little bit interesting in this
definite a little bit babe to be an
under eye setting powder brush but you
know what we're gonna give it a try to
see but this is very very round
I would definitely prefer a more tapered
brush to do this something like this one
from its sigmod like this can really get
like right under there as you can see
but honestly the fact that this morphe
brush is a little bit more tapered and
synthetic I feel like it's applying the
powder better because it is a little bit
more dense and kind of packs it in there
whereas the Kylie brush is obviously
real hair so it kind of feels a little
bit strange to apply a setting powder
with but once again application looks
exactly the same to set the rest I face
in place I'm gonna use in the Kylie
brush number one which is the large
powder brush perfect for blending all of
her face and body powders and this one
retails for a whopping 48 dollars the
closest dupe I could find it was the
morphe m42 for the shape is slightly
different but they're both
huge dense powder brushes except this
one is $10 so you're saving yourself a
whopping 38 bucks I'm just going to take
this brush and tap off the excess oh my
god whoa that actually caught a lot of
powder I'm certainly not mad at it let's
go ahead and try the morphe brush oh
whoa
once again picked up a tip on a powder
once again application looks exactly the
same for bronzer today I'm gonna apply
the benefit hoola bronzer and I'm gonna
use the Kylie brush number four on this
side of my face this one retails for $26
and on my morphe sign I'm gonna use my a
matte 5 to 3 which we chose for $15 what
I do like about these brushes is that
they are pretty dense so when I go and
would like something like bronzer or
like a cream contour and kind of stipple
it into my face and kind of blend it it
doesn't pick up the product underneath
which it's a really really good thing
I'm gonna do the same exact thing on my
morphe side once again applications
exactly the same next for a more precise
contour I'm gonna go my Kat Von D shade
and light palette as always and I might
highly say it I'm gonna grab my number 5
brush which retails for $24 and on my
morphe side I'm gonna grab my M for all
five it retails for eight dollars and as
you can see these are literally the
exact same brush I'm just gonna tuck
that right into the cheekbone and then
same exact thing I really doubt you can
tell on camera but in person I feel like
I can tell just because they look at my
face with makeup on almost every single
day the bristles on the M 405 from
morphe are a lot softer so it's making
I'm much more diffused contour wears on
the Kylie brush so brushes are a lot
more dense which makes it a little bit
harder for a diffused application but to
the everyday makeup person nobody can
tell it looks the exact same let's be
real next I'm gonna play my blush which
is gonna be a Mac peach is my all-time
favorite and from the Kylie site I'm
gonna be using my number six brush which
is the rounded blush brush this retails
for $28 mmm I'm or if we say I'm gonna
use my g1 brush which is the closest
dupe I could find this one is eight
dollars now looking at these obviously
this is a synthetic brush so I would
really never use this for blush that's
definitely more like a buffer brush for
like blending in found a
but you know what sister Kylie says it's
for blush we're gonna use it for blush
oh yeah I do not like that I would just
never reach for this shape or type of
brush when it comes to blush application
I usually use my p4 brush which as you
can see it's very very soft an ankle -
lets you get a very very like diffused
light wash of color this is very very
done so I'm probably spooked to try out
the G one oh my god Kylie side morphe
side it certainly doesn't look bad I
would just literally never reach for
those brushes when it comes to blush one
fly condors are all in place I'm going
to bake my face as usual using my Beauty
Blender
while I'm picking the oven I'm gonna go
ahead and quickly dry brows off-camera
then it will come back for the cleanup
process Kylie did not release any angled
brushes so I'm just gonna use my eyebrow
pencil I'll be right back
alright scissors back to business I'm
gonna go my tart shape table as always
my Kylie brush number 14 this one is $18
and my m22 for $3
you guys know that I usually do my
concealer application using a flat top
concealer brush so I really don't think
that I'm going to enjoy the application
on either side but the brush did fine
to stop my eyelid concealer in place and
prime for eyeshadow I'm gonna use my
Kylie number 10 brush this is $20 and is
the large shader brush although it is
super super dense this is literally not
an eyeshadow brush I don't know what she
thinks she's doing calling this a large
shader brush trying to get this to put
any eyeshadow on the eyelid and make it
like any sort of defined or blended out
it's not happening I really do like the
shape and density of this brush for
packing on trends with a primer to the
list but this is classified as a large
shader brush that I would literally
never use this for any sort of shading
on the eyeshadow so I think this would
be one of the brushes that like I said
it's useless to the set for the more of
you said I'm gonna grab my five to four
brush and this one is $6 so you're
saving yourself $14 just to set your
frickin eyelid concealer in place I want
to do it very Kylie I look today and I
do have a red carpet later on so I don't
want to do anything too too intense I'm
gonna grab the MAC Cosmetics Act
Patrick Starr eyes shadow quads I am so
happy and proud of sisters are for these
amazing collaborations they are so dope
so I'm just gonna doing a fun I liquid
these today for transition shade I'm
going to dip into this light brown shade
in this quad with my Kylie number 15
brush this is the tapered blending brush
and it is $28 and on the morphe said I'm
gonna do the same exact thing using
Miami 5:13 and this one is $6 oh whoa
okay not gonna lie this feels really
really nice on the eyelid next I'm gonna
dip into it this shade right here using
my Kylie number 12 brush this one is $20
and I'm going to use the exact dupe
which is the morphe I'm up for 3 3 which
is $6 interesting even though these
brushes are two very very similar shapes
and sizes the Kylie brush actually
doesn't really taper out on the top it
kind of stays the same density whereas
the morphe brush does taper out a little
bit more so I think in this scenario I
do prefer the M 4-3-3 from morphe simply
because it allows for a much more
blended application I'm next gonna dip
into this brown shade using my number
thirteen brush this is the small shader
brush and it is $18 and on the other
side I'm gonna grab my a matte one five
three foot morpheus same exact shape
this one is $2
I'm just gonna pack the shade right on
that outer V it too deep out that edge
and then pull it slightly into the
crease same situation with this lash
brush as you can see over here it kind
of looks a little bit unblended
that's because the top edge doesn't
taper off at all it's actually more of a
rounded thing it makes it really really
hard for a precise application in the
crease I'm gonna go over those I just
make sure they're really blend it out
using my number eleven brush from Kylie
which is sixteen dollars it is this
angled blending brush I personally hate
these brushes and think there's
literally no point of them they do
absolutely nothing but just to this
think of it I do want to use all the
brushes and for the morphe dupe is my m5
16 this one is six dollars for my eyelid
I'm gonna grab the Kylee concealer brush
this is the number fourteen brush that I
use for my brows earlier and dip into
this shade right up in here and I'm
going to give it a little bit of a
spritz with some fix+ and then I'm just
gonna pack this right onto the inner
eyelid I know this is a kylie review but
Wow sister Patrick snapped on these
shots so good
for my lower lash that I'm going to dip
into that same warm brown shade on my
number thirteen brush and also my m1 5/3
brush that I'm gonna use this to define
it
oh that was way easier with that brush
and then finally with my number 12 slash
m4a3 three brush I'm gonna dip into the
original transition shade and just go
right over that bottom edge
all right scissors off Kara I quickly
just went apply of some wing liner on in
both eyes to snatch up this look popped
on some lashes these are the new bounds
I'm a dragon lean mini and then of
course a mascara to blend them together
looking in the mirror this eye look is
beautiful sister Patrick you killed it
with this collection but that is not the
focus of this video let's be real both
of these eyes look exactly the same
let's go ahead finish off the rest of
the face I'm gonna grab both my big
powder brushes and brush away the bake
before we highly I'm gonna get my skin a
quick spritz of my mac fix+
just to kind of meld all those powders
together because let's be real we
definitely have a lot on today for
highlighter on my Kylie said I'm gonna
grab my number eight brush which is
these small fluff brush and dip into my
Anasazi so hollywood illuminator you
guys know it's my all-time favorite and
this one retails for a whopping up $22
she's gonna give this a slight spritz as
well and pop this right on the cheekbone
oh whoa okay obviously this is doing a
really great job of applying a blinding
highly I mean damn I will say though
once again this brush is not really
tapered on the top it is kind of more
like slightly rounded almost even flat
and it is pretty dense so it's
definitely not like blending it out as
much as I would love it to my Murphy
said I'm gonna grab my our 31 brush this
one is a total of five dollars once
again giving it a light sprit and then
popping it on the cheekbone yep same
exact glow you guys know when it comes
to highlight in my face I usually will
reach for a looking am 501 brush
obviously the shape is very very
different but I am going for exact dupes
today I do wish this brush was more
tapered like this one for a more precise
application but you know what we can't
always get what we want in life I'm
gonna go back into like highly number 5
brush and just make sure that my contour
and highlighter are nice and blended
together and not looking too
and same exact thing on the work piece
out of Miami 405 next we have the number
nine brush and then do my heart for this
is the morphe three one you guys know
that I really am not the biggest fan of
fan brush especially when it comes to
hiding I just don't like the application
work are all this I'm gonna use it today
just the sake of the video this one is
twenty dollars and this one is five
dollars I'm gonna dip into the slightest
bit of artist Couture Illuminati and
just place that right on the high points
of my highlighter I feel like that did
nothing once again make that did nothing
can people just stop making fan brushes
literally this has been a PSA James
Charles hates me eye brushes and last
but certainly not least we have the
Kylie brush number six teen this is a
tiny pencil brush this one retails for
eighteen whopping dollars compared to
the morphe m43 one which retails for as
you can see they're both tiny pencil
brushes i will say that the morphe want
is a little bit more tapered so that is
my fault but let's be real based on a
trend of all the brushes we've tried so
far they're gonna perform exactly the
same for my inner corner i'm gonna be
using one of the Tarte chrome pots and
this is the shade of top yacht this is a
check that I tried a few days ago and I
absolutely loved how it look this is
just so bright and blinding and of
course I'm using my Kylie number 16
brush I'm gonna spritz it the slightest
bit and just pop it right on you see how
bright that is oh my god this is
literally the best thing that ever it's
so freakin pretty hello alright guys I
just wanna hadn't thrown a lip quickly
off camera this is the ofra liquid
lipstick in the shade
and that completes this luck as you can
see here we have the Kylie brush aside
totaling at three hundred and sixty
dollars and on the other side we have
morphe brushes totaling at one hundred
and four dollars now my face is all
complete and I've used every single one
of these brushes from both collections
let's go ahead and spill the tea once
another Kylie brushes on line let's be
real we were all shook as hell by the
price point three hundred sixty dollars
especially for a new brand like Kylie is
way way too high that being said though
almost every single products news
release in the past has been pretty good
like I said I'm not on her PR let so
everything that I've tried from
has been a personally bought from me not
being paid to say anything but it is
pretty good stuff so major props to
Kelly for that based on Carly's past
product has 3ik going into this I really
didn't think the brushes were gonna be
bad at all and let's be real they really
weren't most of the brushes did exactly
what they were supposed to do and one of
them being number seven in my opinion
even performed better than the dupe from
morphe on the other hand Harbor there
were a few more view brushes that in my
opinion outperformed Kylie mostly being
the eye brushes a lot of the blending
brushes specifically number 12 did a
really really great job at packing the
color on there but I will say that I
wish they were more tapered all the tops
of these brushes are very very rounded
which is great however they're very very
dense at the top and don't really taper
out which makes it a little bit harder
to get a more precise application that's
actually when it comes to crease work
overall what I recommend the Kylie
cosmetics silver luxury brush sat
absolutely not the brushes all did
exactly what they're supposed to do and
applied the makeup perfectly fine just
like normal
none of the brushes are fraying and they
are really really good-quality I just
don't think it's worth the price point I
really just can't justify spending three
hundred sixty dollars on her brush set
when their brands out there like morphe
making the exact same dupes for way
cheaper I mean literally I think the
cheapest morphe brush was $2.00 and the
cheapest Kylie brush was $18 I mean
there's even like BH Cosmetics out there
where you can literally get the same
exact brush set for $15 don't get me
wrong I really really love Kylie but
that's literally some people's entire
like house payment or rent payment or
car payment like that is just way too
much it is not like these brushes are
literally doing our makeup for us or
face tuning our photos after I'm not
gonna tell Kylie how to run her brand
because clearly she's doing a perfectly
fine job on her own she made almost five
hundred million dollars last year
literally a living legend but I do wish
she would make her mice a lot more
affordable so more people could get them
and not just a beauty gurus all that
being said though if you are a huge
Kylie stand like myself and you want to
support her on this brush launch at
least you know you're getting good
quality brushes for your money
all right guys notice all I have for
this video today definitely give this
video a big thumbs up if you enjoyed it
leave me a comment down below and tell
me what side you think looks better and
my opinion they look exactly the same
but who knows maybe you guys are seeing
something that I'm not what's the T are
you gonna buy the Kylie brushes
definitely let me know your thoughts
down below
don't forget every single day leading up
to Christmas I am doing 12 days of
sister Christmas give us lays on my
snapchat story
make sure you add me over there at James
Charles as an extra
after Charles thumbs up this video
subscribe to my youtube channel and
leave me a comment down below telling
your name your age and what you want for
Christmas and you will automatically be
entered to win I already say go prize
package and winner will be announced on
my snapchat story so don't forget to add
me over there if you like to follow me
on my makeup journey can Palmilla and
circum at twitter they are both just
James Charles and my snapchat is well I
just told you twice this week sister
shoutout goes to sister Nancy thank you
so much me for always following and
supporting you I love you so so so much
and if you would like to be the next
video sister shadow make sure it always
retreive a video link and they go live
on a Twitter our right sister thank you
so much for watching this video I love
you so much
[Music]