hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to our YouTube channel if
[Music]
you take a quick look at me right now
you may be noticing seeing a little bit
weird and that is that I have on the
phone Blair but I'm missing one thing
and that is the list currently I'm also
missing the snail bumper talk about that
because I'm the man appointment tomorrow
don't talk with me lately that's what oh
there's been a very very viral tweet
going around of a screenshot of a clip
from the show of the doctor once to tell
that boy viral is a video of a woman are
talking about how the color of your
nipple may be the best way to tell how
to find your perfect nude lipstick shade
so that is exactly what we're going to
do for today's do I have ten of my
all-time favorite nude liquid lipstick
shade I'm going to my shirt off and
we're going to swatch all ten and see
which 3's match the closest then we're
going to try them on and see at the end
which nude liquid lipstick shades wins
and if it matches the color of my
nipples so without further ado let's get
my shirt off and let's get on with the
video
okay not only are we not going to talk
about my broken nail but we're also not
going to talk about my lawsuit phrasing
listen the girls is busy I have not gone
in three weeks
let's just say this is foundation color
it did not stress to my body
it still exists like seven here I don't
even know if you can see on camera just
don't call it about it please
so like I said I have ten of my all-time
favorite nude and liquid lipsticks and
I'm going to be swatching a thigh around
each nipple to see which colors match
the closest that'll be picking to get
top three of putting them on and seeing
which suit I like the best I also have a
piece of paper and a pen so I can keep
track of where each color is on the nips
so I don't forget anything but yeah I
guess let's get started the first thing
I'm going to be trying to say is the Kat
Von D's liquid lipstick of the shade a
bow and arrow
this is my all-time favorite nude
lipstick I was all the time to most my
offense and mostly photo shoot so I just
want like a natural look and putting
this next to the nipple
oh my god they look really really really
similar this could actually work not bad
of a color match honestly that's going
to grab the anasazi lip in the shade
Asha and I'm going to put that right
next to a bow and arrow the toll of an
options are
not a little bit better 2d am I going to
need to pluck out this new pointer
I don't know how about trading on camera
but in person the action liquid lipstick
is definitely a lot more red than my
actual nipple itself so we're going to
move on of course and actually I'm going
to using is crush also from anna sophia
cross is definitely a lot more pinky
toned of course showing the other two
but it is still pretty close with the
nipple color I don't know
but the next one I'm going to use potato
light G from as you a cosmetics light is
that with a lot more pinky tone to my
nipple Millie Nevelson work like orange
II totally average person is that normal
so you saw every time I think they're
fun to do because it could be saying it
way too much
unless you're underage then take a shot
of apple juice either way so sorry for
all the nipples for my lashing on this
tip I'm gonna be using the daddy liquid
lipstick from jeffree star cosmetics in
collaboration with many anyway this is a
lot more brown tones I'm thinking this
one might be a closer and then the brown
tones in it daddy definitely matched
closer to my nipple it is going to be
driving a little bit darker I feelings
but when all these drives we will
definitely compare but for now dot
elastica cookies definitely a
front-runner I'm going to let all these
colors dry it out completely and while
we do that we're going to move on to it
the other nipple so for the first song
we need more people lipstick in the
shapes of vanity and you guys know you
can use go to James for 10% off all more
P products
okay so definitely same situation as
crush and light see over here the change
is definitely way too pink to be
matching at the end missile provide
actually and I squeezing the colour-pop
liquid lipstick in the shade where ES
and I'm now realizing this is a ultra
fluffy lip and not a matte one so I'm
not really sure how's it going to work
on my chest but we're going to do it
anyway because this shade has it more
orgy hunter told a little bit in the
other J so this might be good match
which is not going to dry I guess which
might be interesting that's will head in
I think so that this one is a gloss is a
lot harder to see on Chandler because
the lights are reflecting obviously
there
but this one is actually not too far off
it's obviously a lot less pigmented and
then liquid lipsticks that are not
because it is a gloss or they usually
limit more complete the color is pretty
close to the ordinary chosen there's
definitely a lot closer to the nipple so
yeah the squad with the next one
for my next column museum target crowd
lip paint and the shade festival this
color is not very closely but honestly
I've never used this apartment really
producers definitely might be ending up
in look sometimes to whom this one is
ever like a mob but has more purpley
undertones so definitely not gonna shame
me like orangie round tones of relatable
so I don't think this one's gonna be a
very very high contender
we're next color I'm using the over
lifted up Sigma shade at mocha this is
one of my all-time favorite liquid
lipsticks period this is one of the
first things I ever bought from Oprah
and it still remains to this day one of
my all-time favorite colors I love this
one some really cool things that it does
the job not its color definitely a whole
lot darker than the nipple itself which
breaks my heart but who knows it's
definitely my favorite change so maybe
this staying with my favorites and
matching debunks this whole nipple miss
color but we're going to finish off and
find out for sure last but not leave
mine amazing the over liquid lipstick in
the shade at Pasadena and I forgot to
mention this before but code James just
like more bees don't get you 30% of all
of the little six and the over lizard
lipsticks had like all times paper
formula they are so low and they wear
all day long
definitely recommend checking it out if
you have not already Pasadena is very
similar to walk up but it's a little bit
lighter in a little bit more thorn cheek
so this doesn't looks like it is a
critic attached to the nipple region I
like this one for sure alright guys so
this all-century is completely dry down
except of course the left off but that
was my to follow sorry about it just
feels very very strange right now but
I'm going to pick the top three that I
think much feedback and we're going to
wash them and try them on going in the
same water that we came in if you leave
top of the bow narrow is a very very
good contender so is a daddy for sure
like G is definitely way too pinks I
think that was out of the question
squash is also a little bit too pink and
a little bit too light and ashen is way
too red moving over to as if nipple baby
festival are a little bit too purpley to
make the cut my nipples are not purple
unfortunately that would probably be
pretty cool to be honest
tell us off Boston affairs which is a
little bit too preachy to its really
much and the mocha liquid lipstick is
obviously way too dark felt these are
final contender for the top three as
Pasadena from Oprah as we are all over
the nipple area
thank God it's one of him soon do you
guys back incest full HD quality but I
present to you our three winners for
today we have the Kat Von D liquid
lipstick in the shade beau narrow Oprah
Pasadena and the Jeffrey sizes lipstick
in the shade is daddy I'm first going to
tap on be a bow and arrow so here is
bone arrow all completely applied and
dry to the lips I absolutely love with
color so much I feel like it matched my
skin tone very very very well it's
something with my ultimate favorite news
emergence wash it daddy from the jeffree
star cosmetics alright so here is daddy
all applied and completely dry I do
really really love this shade as well I
feel like it also suits my skin tone it
is a little bit more growl tone than
bolero is but I feel like it still looks
really really well if the last month
we're going to be applying the over
Pasadena with the lipstick alright so
here is Pasadena fully applied and dry
so into the other two colors I really
really like those it's lips on me this
one a little bit more pinky tone then
bow and arrow and daddy's epic still
love this color and here are all three
shades compared to each other alright
and that is the test I'll complete it
not being biased to any of them I am
going to leave this last of the lipstick
on because I feel like if I take my lips
off one more time they would literally
get crusty and then all of completely so
I'm just going to try to avoid that
today I was so skeptical at first but
all in all these three liquid lipstick
shades that did not my nipple or
honestly some of my favorite music all
time and I feel like they did all look
really really good suck you liked this
test is counted a complete success after
saying the 3 different colors to watch
that matched best with my nipples I want
you guys leaving a comment down below
and tell me which color out of the three
that you like the best on my skin tone
this challenge was so crazy but I
honestly feel like your work so if you
guys are looking for your favorite nude
lip definitely test it out and give it a
try and tell you which one worked better
for your skin
but maybe you should lock the door first
because if somebody wants and this may
look a little bit weird if you enjoyed
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below
let's if we can get this to 30,000 like
for me putting title of the lipsticks
all over my chest this is very efficient
so it was very very fun if you haven't
already please make sure to hit that
subscribe button down below and click
that notification mount so you see all
my videos I would love to have you join
the sisterhood and I post two videos a
week on Mondays and Friday
if you'd like to follow me on my makeup
journey you can follow me on Instagram
and Twitter they're both just James Chao
and my snapchat you now for more behind
the scenes I stuff on James Charles an
extra ass after Charles thank you so
much for watching and I will see you in
the next one bye
[Music]