hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back with my youtube channel as
you guys can see I have a very very
special guest for today's a new video
and what did we do in here what's the
title of this video job perks today's
video if you guys saw my video a few
weeks ago with the vlog squad Jeff was
there and made a cute little cameo
moment and after our little collab but
pretty much every single comment on the
video was about our relation David
stupid haircut oh I really yeah yeah
okay yeah it's true my whole life has
become James Charles my entire tag
photos has all been taken over by the
sisters jumping us it's pretty cool it's
really good force us into a relationship
and now we're here for this video today
yeah
clear this show cuz I got a lot of hate
at one point you broke down crying in a
hotel room I did or something and then
everybody says it's Jeff first of all we
met one time doing video I'm the guy
that broke your heart John did well
Binda one it was not job I'm getting
backlash top Jeff would it canceled or
nothing
I mean you could have been there for me
but I just as a straight man business
tremens mystery man but we're good
friends now yes this is sure to share
your Valentine's Day texting you
something I was gonna break that off
later on in the video mode you can just
what I say tell me right now what did I
say yeah say it you talk to me late at
all times it's that how the college is a
beautiful oh well let's just need me a
friendly uh I said that to David oh my
friends in prison yeah of course yeah
first today's video
Donnie Jeff is here and we're teaming up
because Jeff is going to do my makeup
and I pulled a bunch of questions from
the boyfriend tag and we're going to ask
each other the questions and figure out
if maybe one day we would be compatible
okay deal
but whatever I don't know how to cut
hair and I make videos on cutting hair
so yeah that's my favorite part
okay let's jump into it okay are you
ready for this I learned in the video
your first one you rub some primer on
yes do I rub that on your face yes
please is that what you do
professionally yes you don't tell them
you put this on
No okay that you just rub this on yeah
please touch me all over okay just two
dudes doing each other's makeup okay
that's on there pretty good now what do
I do with the hands just lotion later
you're the one that in the last video
requested lotion for a full body massage
okay you're right I did
you did it I got a dry sense of humor
come off very sarcastic you don't know
what I'm joking or not neither do I do
you want to give me a little like walk
through yeah yeah so your next time is
gonna be foundation shots okay this is
the horn this way you can put on like
the back of your hand okay the back yeah
teach me those little tricks like that
that's good okay copy this we basically
just rub all over your face right you
pulse it on start on the forehead right
sure oh man this is like paint is you're
an artiste today thank you like a French
girl why didn't you just ask me to give
you a haircut much better at haircuts
than make up hotels in two days for not
gonna have a botched haircut for
Coachella
I would never bought your hair I never
have in my life
I've never met somebody here that's a
total lie you have video documentation
on your YouTube channel you know what
I'm gonna take those down because those
are jokes and it's affecting my business
yeah clearly and I had like my ex be
like oh you flirted with that video I
know how you flirt you used to flirt
with me you did fire your love video I'm
just being sarcastic no no I mean like
yeah I'm being nice and like I'm like
joking around but I don't want to mess
with anybody's heads here you know this
is true I called you on Valentine's Day
after you said about today how do you
get into the hair you just kind of blend
it it's blended yeah what are three
qualities that you would look for in a
long-term relationship this is a good
question you gotta have a good sense of
humor yeah that's the most important you
tell me I'm funny every single day my
son do yeah okay second one you have to
be a woman you just gotta have some sort
of ambition yeah life you know like
you're my son you do I'm famous you got
two out of three it's pretty good yeah I
watched the first video what we don't
want your eyebrows back this ha just
take it a sharpie I know there are bad
what's your three qualities you look for
in a partner I would say my link biggest
one is also sense of humor I did save my
number two would be like understanding
is a huge thing for me yeah just because
like the life that I live is strange and
like I need someone who like not gets it
but consoling common sense yeah and then
my third would be like it'll be a hot
barber oh okay it's just like a haircut
all the time you know I know one year
barber Sophie okay taste of my own
medicine yeah
ethnic that's next concealer okay
concealer you just claw blonde yes mix
it around there good give it a shake
Jeff where do we first meet question -
yeah right
we met on FaceTime we did meet on facing
for the first time yeah no we met here
in this room yeah we did but all the
magic we've never left is he's had me
chained up in here please help if you
see this smash like two million likes
and they'll release me
okay blend it back in yeah I think I fit
into your genomes for the first time no
it's not true yeah did you find out sure
I am damned you first on January 19th at
119 p.m. and said can you marry me cut
my hair every other week dad what did I
say
you said of course hey we throw teams I
mean yeah I don't know my favorite lime
for less mm well I see I'm doing said
while you're so hot and I remind you
again you said it while you look so good
you said oMG so do I said I said
oMFG so do you okay I sent back the gasp
emoji and he said lol within the cute
little I'm not good at taking
compliments no I can tell and you asked
me what I was doing I said just
Photoshop makeup set you a selfie and
you said can you do my makeup and I'll
give you a haircut I said he I gasp I
said I hate putting hot guys and makeup
yeah which is Cheryl smart I wouldn't
want to be in it but I was just trying
to make conversation then you said favor
light here we go here we go
ello I probably wouldn't like it but
I'll try anything once haha almost
everything I love trying lots of things
one of my favorite pastimes Thanks have
you ever looked up with a girl
yes yeah yeah like made out but like it
was this before that you realized that
you yeah
before and after I'll see you went back
for fun yeah Wow have you ever hooked up
with a guy before
no oh my kid that I said I just thought
it only flirting with straight guys who
are and trust that and he said no you're
doing great so after all this I didn't
know much about you at this point I'm
just joking around and stuff but you
told me that you have
turned out straight guys it elaborate on
that because you are famous celebrity
and you do you do live in Hollywood yes
where there's a lot of guys that will be
clout chasers is the new term yeah they
were using so you think it was somebody
that was maybe looking for something to
return from you yeah okay cool yeah
let's talk about it in science in
regards like LGBTQ people there's what's
called the Kinsey scale so the get this
goes for like zero to sex zero being
like completely straight yeah and six
being like completely gay okay and I
truly believe that the amount of people
that are a flat-out zero or a flat-out
six is like very very small I think that
most people are very close to the ends
but there's a huge percentage in the
middle too if I had to put myself on it
I would put myself at like a 5.5 so
you're not even full gay I mean know
there have been girls in the past that I
if I thought were really really
beautiful there's also been like trans
guys in the pasta too that I would like
really early into for a moment in time
especially living in LA where
everybody's like a lot more open-minded
I think that honestly like the majority
of guys are like wanting to experiment I
used to hear rumors like that all the
time I like big big celebrities that
growing up already is like what really
that's crazy because I grew up in Staten
Island where it was like and I'm and you
know couple years older than you so my
group of friends growing up everybody
was going for that same like tough guy
yeah straight guy image and I didn't
have any gay friends so it wasn't until
I moved out that like I finally started
meeting gay guys and working with them
and like barber shops or salons I'm just
like really having a relationship or
like you get to talk to them about more
than just the same [ __ ] yeah so like
for me for example like I am a guy
identify as a guy but I still call
myself a woman all the time yeah as a
joke and stuff but like I do try
everyone said well I have full nails I
have a hair on occasionally yeah so it's
like for a lot of people like those
the--my as someone who's just pretty as
opposed to mimic a man which is fine
like that's how I like to see myself as
to is just someone who's like a pretty
human person yeah so like a lot of
people are willing to look past and
experiment and see like if they'd be
into it to choose a song that they
either always wondered or they're into
me as a person and I
that's super super cool and
unfortunately that a lot of times leads
to a hookup or like making out or
hanging out and then the next day
they're like we're adding and never
talking to me guys or there's
internalized homophobia that has been
built up so long that led to them
wanting to experiment in the first place
but then once they do it they're like eh
Oh gross and then I'll start getting all
sorts of death threats and angry
messages from them the next day after
you guys monster it'll be or it'll be
like a repetitive thing where it's like
hey let's keep doing this on the DL and
it's a very very strange we're all but
it's like you know what you're kind of
getting into when you're behind the
scenes but I truly do feel like there's
like a spectrum and everybody falls on
it at some point and like especially
right now - like in the world I feel
like there's a major emphasis on like
labels and for me personally like I do
think labels are really really important
because it obviously spreads awareness
people can be educated and also like
young kids that don't feel welcome can
be a part of something and can label
themselves but at the same time - I also
think like putting a label on something
especially yes there is a sexuality
before you're fully understanding what
it is can be really really toxic come
fix your the memes that are gonna be
made from the soup into me like what am
I thinking in my head I'm taking it yeah
I get it and that's like that's you can
like you should be able to experiment
and like test out different things and
talk to different people as like long as
there's some sort of instruction that
whether it be to their personality to
their image even D is actually - and
link doesn't necessarily feels like that
you have to put a label on how do you
deal with homophobic comments I don't
care you don't start this and you never
did know did you like girl out of that
oh is this the one where I brush on the
highway no this is where you contour my
face okay this is where the video I
didn't get to see the rest of it did you
get 42 minutes in there long video video
so this goes around the bones yeah like
right like wrap it here make it look
nice and chest hold okay I want to I
want a little overboard on that side
pounce at him have it in yeah yeah I
have a question for you job speaking and
like relation to what you just asked me
yeah because like after our video that
we did together there are a lot of
people come to me like wow James and
Jeff's like interaction was so cool
Jeffersonian Earth himself public I knew
we were straight obviously believe
looking back yeah it was really cool to
watch and like it was funny too because
I think a lot of kites aren't
comfortable enough with themselves to be
able to make those type of jokes how was
that reaction for you the fan reaction
was mostly positive sometimes in person
people will come to me that I don't know
and they joke around with my sense of
humor and they'll come up to me and be
like Oh where's your boyfriend at or
something like that I'm like what the
hell you're talking about it first but
then I get it they're your fans and
stuff like that they just know that I
grew up around a lot yeah they want to
make that first impression memorable
yeah yes I was interesting I'm getting
used to it but I'm always growing him
and trying to learn as a person but I
did see on Twitter some really positive
tweets and that was really cool to see
that people could kind of move past that
toxic masculinity if I could have my
audience and and kind of do do something
positive yeah then I think that'd be
pretty cool that we have that effect on
you on Twitter yeah at least you know
we're gonna do how are you - yes let's
keep it up
nice I think we're pretty good on this
stuff I'm ready to move to the next step
oh hi I think you just gonna pull out a
sharpie No okay so kind of what happens
in barber and you stretch the skin up
yeah with this - yeah I'm a natural
here's something mister start my own
makeup channel oh wow look at this this
available right now it is sisters -
apparel calm do I choose the iconic
James Charles like morphe palette oh wow
yeah about time a James Charles product
comes out here it's the only one I have
is it yes how come every time I hear
somebody talking about James Charles
they're like all these things sold out
in minutes cousin yes but this is what
it is this is the James stroke all like
this thing alright now I'm looking at
this I have no idea what's going on
there's so many different colors this is
harder than I thought no it's not let's
do last year's Coachella look okay
what was her first impression of me very
funny and like good at delegating
responsibility to everybody and kind of
organizing a shoe thank you buddy and
organized for two great qualities do me
know what was your first appreciated my
first impression was that you were
insanely hot people know me for making
like jokes at hot guys and stuff but I
was not ready for you to start making
them back at me so I would like I was
shocked that was nothing about the head
the next question is could you tell that
your significant other liked you I mean
yeah what is your favorite thing your
significant other has ever said to you I
mean probably just that like you thought
my videos are funny because like you
give me the compliments about like being
good-looking I don't know how to take
those what was your favorite thing I've
ever said to you I can't I can't I can't
do this man it was a joke and welcome to
joke it was just a friendly text I send
it to all my guy friends I don't think
you dad you're right next question so
I'm gonna teach you guys a little trick
you guys at home this I learned from
barbering but it could also work for a
situation like whenever you go into a
job on a new person you're a little
nervous no matter what I don't care what
you say it's like you have that fear of
messing off yeah however that you know
so what I would do on like a lineup cuz
the line if you can't repair so I would
keep like one finger on the skin and now
if you move or I'm a little shaky my
hand moves with your face so you kind of
have that like extra stability so I
think that'll work for something like
this
all right put a little extra finger is
that okay don't be shy get in on there
and use that as as your as your base job
that actually looks so good thank you
that's funny the that's like the thought
swing letter anybody's ever dying now
this is really my favorite part about
makeup uh I never stood back I never pay
attention at any other part oh he could
to the other side it's not done yet it's
almost how did you do what I literally
perfect and you can't get the amount
even you know I got overly confident
it's not the same at all yeah you're
right it is next you want to do the
highlighter sorry did I get it right use
highlighters to highlight your bone
structure yes so we're gonna highlight
the areas where the light would hit you
yes you want to do a little tap yeah
what do you think you're gonna put I
think here right if we got married who
would win an argument I always let the
other significant other wins oh my god
yeah I'm winning what a massage yeah I
just don't even bother great for rent to
me well what's next
weird you like to put a lipstick on so
you can really taste something I don't
like lipstick man Oh easier to make out
without it yeah just like this is true
it's just like all this stuff on your
face and you go to kiss it's just
something in the way that's gonna get on
me now and I'm not a fan of lipstick
never where he loves me describe me like
your dream date oh I like I pick yeah
the movie theater yeah super fun it's a
movie theater out here in LA where you
can like it's like lounge chair like you
can't like recliners all the way you
could fully sleep if you want is a
pillow blankets
Islanders oh it brings you whatever you
want you can order candy from the waiter
it's not just regular food yeah that's
kind of fun what is your dream date I
would say I love a good movie like a
good horror movie premiere would be
amazing
I do love escape rooms that's not the
biggest fan of escape rooms really yeah
I don't like how they treat you in there
it kind of reminds me of I rather yeah
favorite things you normally put myself
in those observation course of course
check it out are you ready for our date
job this was it I thought Jeff the
swingline are so good
thank you all right you guys well I
think this is the finished look from the
daddy Jeff let me know you dig you
hungry from every comment here's so
annoying thank you Jeff so much for
coming all this time
tonight think you might have it's good
to be here I've learned a lot and I'm
gonna carry this knowledge on for the
rest of my life not just about makeup
about life and thank you James
you taught me so much my mind is open
that's good I'm gonna be thinking about
this for the whole day I'm definitely
open as well if your sisters intro this
video today please don't forget to be
with Vegas thumbs up down below and
leave us a comment let us know how you
think Jeff did if you've not ready make
sure it's like that big red subscribe
button down below as well and come to
the sisterhood we are 16 million is
sisters strong oh my god you guys we
literally just hit it this morning when
we were filming this video thank you so
so so much like the support continues
flowing line I've honestly had a little
bit of a rough month the past few weeks
and at your guys's constant support
constant kind of messages and just
everything in general like literally it
has kept me going it so so so much so I
love you the obstacles in the entire
world if you have not already as well
click that Melancon so you it can
notification every time I upload a brand
new video if you want to go check out
Jeff that's right I just hit 16
subscribers I'm so grateful for all
these 16 people yeah he does have some
pretty funny haircut and content I will
say oh that's so nice of you I didn't
know you're gonna do a shout out for me
thank you
yeah if they follow me on I make up
journey can follow me up in so you want
Twitter they're both the same Charles my
snapchat for more behind the scenes I
set co-stars the next ask after Charles
if you like to follow Jeff it's just
Jeff yeah if we get a million likes on
this video James was talking about
release me back into the public taking
the chains off of my leg
this video is sister shot it goes to and
James as a queen at loving the absolute
most sister thank you so much for always
falling in supporting and if you would
like to the next videos sister shadow
don't forget to always a retweet my
video a something called live on Twitter
and turn to my youtube post of a huge by
clicking that that icon
alright you guys think you saw shocked
in this videos today thank you again
it's my incredible thank you to full
future husband Jeff we love you and we
will see you in the next one bye bye bye
bye please let me out
[Music]