hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
I'm currently holding back in Europe for
the holiday season and I'm of course
with sister en not playing this game
again when he wasn't he brought in
California a few months ago we had so
much fun throwing our videos together I
know he looked like he wanted to die the
entire time but deep down he definitely
did enjoy and oh yes you're just a liar
not only did we get to have fun quality
sister time tell me those things
together but you guys absolutely love
them as well they did it so well I got
so many comment saying that you guys all
the videos sister in gained a ton of
followers on Instagram which was so dope
and he's definitely been enjoying the
fame so for today's video we decided to
step it up a notch and I have all I wake
up here in front of me back home in New
York we set up a DIY filming studio and
today we're gonna be putting it in drag
and you said it out this No so do you
know like anything really about drag all
I know is you makes you look for your
girl oh hey do you like anything else
well I know it's not when you're
transgender it's like for performances
good okay yeah so the art of drag is
basically it's just for performance
purposes and to get everybody excited
and to get you to put those bills in the
drag queens panties so today we're
putting even though jaya hills and
things that you guys enjoyed the last
video so much give us a thumbs up and
seedling it to 200,000 likes i know your
sisters can do it that was good
we love that youtuber in training so
that further ado if you'd like to see
brother Ian I guess get transformed into
sister en that was clever keep on
watching
[Music]
so this will keep with the makeup oh
dude this isn't just crazy this gonna
keep the makeup using a glue stick
forward we have to glue down your
eyebrows so we can give you know I can't
do that chance you're not gloom on those
no no you got glue you're not you're not
gluing my eyebrow evils while we're
playing
Ian's base makeup when we post the
original video so many of you guys
thought sister in with soul track but
not only didn't get enough followers but
you also got a lot of interesting
comments a little weird
we thought it'd be funny to read so on
to you guys today so we're voice said no
don't you can see their name why not
this DM says hey in I know this may
sound a little weird but could I see a
picture of the bottoms of your feet no
what are you doing open your eyes and
look there you go no don't worry gyros
one girl asked for my snap and then
continue the conversation hang on by
saying do you know how to calculate the
percent by mass of water loss by the
chemical sister needed some help with
her chemistry homework wait so how do
not look recognized in public to me
really well it's like the where's and
what's happened you so far
I think really where that's happened I
haven't actually got like a lot of weird
sister recovers either you guys are
usually pretty good which I super
appreciate and it's another boy 80 asked
have you guys ever liked the same person
at the same time well naughty question
but show the camera what you guys got
each other for Christmas
it's November 1 - I don't buy anything
for Christmas for him Oh Louis easily
asked you can be someone really famous
who and why soon as that voice hello
suicide voice those guys are they
robbers
yeah that's dope why would say probably
know Kylie so it definitely has a pretty
hooded eyelids as you can see doesn't
have much validation it opens its eyes
so I'm gonna make his bra March pretty
high tonight so I can give him some
bigwig liner to kind of completely fake
his eye shape so this should be
interesting
Allah asked biggest lie you've ever told
each other I wasn't gay last few idiom
swap positions what do you think Ian
would be famous for and what does he an
think you'd be doing without theme
really good question question go you
Kayla I think you would definitely be I
don't Phoebe making YouTube videos but I
think you'd be like famous for like
buying sneakers for sure that's what you
already do what do you think I hope you
doing if they wasn't we're going to a
magnet school cuz your grades are good
thing is how do I be studying some weird
thing I personally don't like it morphe
35o palette use code james for tempeh so
i'm going to use this to set the
concealer underneath
Ian's brows beautiful and then I'm gonna
be using the Jacqueline help out of
course shutout charmville
oh my gentleness don't know you go so
soon preschool
forecast or any girls interested in me
and because of you look how girls like
from like yeah really let's started
talking to me again once I mean yes I
don't know you how does that make you
feel
I guess Pat the turbo last what would
you do if you were invincible for a day
invincible or invisible hope you know
who's better at reading someone asked do
you all like pineapple pizza no dude
you're getting in my eye that's not in
your eyes Bernie it's not sister sayin
asking brother Ian Singh no you also
like I've never actually heard you try
yeah cuz I'm not gonna embarrass myself
I got points off in eighth grade on
music test cuz I couldn't sing thanks
for trying
hello yeah make up oh my god holy crap
we're stopped hello Patricia asked
what's the worst thing we've got in
trouble for I don't think the worst
thing I've ever gotten to a four is well
this is gonna sound crazy by in eighth
grade I actually got punched I went home
with a headache and he actually ended up
breaking his arm which was like nice
karma so I got called in to look up I
got called it's like the school
principal's office talk about it
obviously and I'm expecting him till I
get in trouble right and I literally get
called in and like Dean is asking me
what happened like are you okay what's
going on and I explained to him like
this kid makes fun of me all the time
and I finally stood up for myself and
they front of him back then I got
punished and I started out he literally
goes mmm that's where your sarcastic
mouth will get you I was like oh no miss
[ __ ] so I literally it went home and of
course like might well itself literally
just hopped on Twitter and started
tweeting about it and I was like this
then he literally called Mia again in
the next day I was like I thought you
have some few choice words to say on
Twitter and I had literal printouts like
all my tweets on printer hey
and I was like oh no girl we're not
playing this game today I know your ass
is not about to blame me for the fact
that I got punched I set up for myself
it is so important to not victim blame
and then I walked out of his office
garbage I guess it was really kind of
like getting a tool but that was the
closer or under getting a trouble that's
a pretty good kid now we have all has
completely miss looking so beautiful I
know I'm gonna apply it the lucious and
I have these custom stocked excuse me
pair of lashes itching your ass no don't
do that
oh I mean what are you they said next
we're gonna apply the highlighter and
let it glow James what is that you're
saying I don't know yeah
oh yeah oh okay you tell me no I guess
you're gonna have to find out pretty
soon find out pretty soon what Oh
oh my god it's like a stamp paper you
need to chop stick without further ado
let's go ahead and change the ends
outfit and put on some hair change my
outfit that's a joke I'm not changing my
outfit well you're not wearing that yes
I am we'll be right back sisters you
look beautiful you've got quality
bonding time with your favorite no okay
so what did you learn something about
the art of drag that it takes a long
time it's not fun it's painful so you
know like you obviously think you look
crazy and I'm not used to seeing
yourself like this could you ever see
yourself doing this again in the future
never but the people that do do it I get
respect to them because it seems pretty
difficult
yeah definitely true that's awesome all
right guys that is all we have for the
semi a poor sister yet a really one I'll
take this sister yeah really wants to
take this wig off and I'm definitely too
time playing man if you guys enjoyed
this video please don't forget to give
it a big thumbs up down below like
sister Keehan said that's good to
200,000 I know you guys can do it if you
like to follow me on a makeup show you
can follow me on instagram you know that
repulses James Ross and my snapchat for
more hasn't seen himself is James
Charles in the neck should ask dr.
Charles what to follow me on Instagram
or Instagram is Ian JD 12 stop leaving
him creepy comments please this
accessory shadow goes to sister Beulah
so guys thank you so much girl boys
falling it's a party you know I love you
so so so much and if you'd like to be in
the next week's sister shop we should
always we treatment legal life plan hi
all right sisters thank you so much for
watching this video
much love from me and sister Ian over at
the trans family we really do love you
guys so so much and we'll see you in the
next one bye give like a side angle nope
you're out of the camera what are you
doing