hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel for
today's video we're doing something that
I've never actually done on the channel
before but a lot of people have okay and
that is a makeup box video now I will be
honest to do and tell you okay that
there is a reason that I've never done
and makeup hacks video and that is
because I think may come have some
stupid can I would say God listen I am
all here and I'm super supportive of
whatever tips techniques and tricks that
you want to do to finish your makeup
routine and for being honest if you're a
beginner makeup artist a gift can be a
really really tricky and sometimes there
are really helpful tips and techniques
online and as long as you feel beautiful
and confident with the finished result
that is truly all it matters so do
whatever you got to do but the reason
that I personally hate these like makeup
hacks videos that have been popping up
on tik-tok and on YouTube and on my
Instagram is because 99% of the time
they just do not work so for the past
few weeks I've been paying very very
close attention across the different
social video platforms at these
advertisements for these makeup hack
products that claim to make my routine
18 million times easier they're all
sitting here in front of me and for
today's video we're going to put these
makeup hacks to the test
so let's get started
[Music]
I'll write you faces when we jump into
our actual makeup routine this at first
hack is something that has to be done
before the makeup goes on and that is an
eyebrow lamination now I do not know
what laminating and eyebrows is
basically it's like a technique that
like locks your hairs in a certain
direction that sounds crazy mother just
open this up and get this started so we
can see what we're talking about here
it's like if you just like put brow gel
in your hair and then just like left it
there for a few weeks
eyebrow elimination upkeep eyebrows dry
for 24 hours I mean if I'm just careful
with my foundation I feel like it'll be
fine right
Yolo so first it says use a cleanser
which is solution number 4 use a clean
micro brush to apply lift solution oh my
god that smells rotten
ok I'm gonna just brush this through the
hairs yeah oh it's worm it's a chemical
reaction okay so I feel like in the
meantime of at the brothel is really
laminating we could get started on
another makeup ha and this one I have
honestly been the most hated to try and
that is this makeup brush cleanser so
basically what this is is a fun little
fishbowl is the what this looks like a
thing that looks like a nose hair
trimmer we're gonna grab this morphe i'm
5 to 7 this is normally my bronzer brush
and as you can see it is very very dirty
it normally looks like this so clearly
quite the color difference going on and
I'm gonna grab and wanted like the
little rubber thing he said shove it on
the end we're gonna shove this now onto
our spinner like this what does what
whoa
give her a nice fish bowl filled with
some cleansing solution and our water
dip oh whoa
really turning around this is taking too
long
I'm all over this oh that's definitely
not clean now like okay let's does a few
other brushes before we make our
decision so we took out this morphe i'm
4-3-3 and as you can see this one has it
some nice red a shadow on it and if you
remember back to 2018 when I really like
how we know that this color stains yeah
now we're gonna clean it off oh no can
you give a nice zoom into that wait here
oh yeah that's a nice and a ruined brush
right there ooh okay I'm gonna go ahead
and call it quits on this makeup brush
cleaning huh as you guys can see both
brushes are in fact actually cleaned
which is not really surprising to me I
mean it's water and makeup soap and
brushes which is always gonna be a
foolproof thing we're really talking
about this whole spitting situation as
the actual high and I'm gonna say this
actually would not recommend and I'm
going to tell you why okay when you're
cleaning your maker brushes obviously
everybody has different techniques some
people don't even ever clean them which
okay hello there are some definite
recommendations and spinning your
brushes at a very very high speed to the
point where they get flattened
and ruin their shape is definitely not
the ideal technique I'll tell you that
right now they're going to basically
like to stay the shape forever and then
you're a twenty dollar bronzer brush
that you spent your hard-earned money on
is now going to be a nice little
mushroom situation alright so moving on
at this point I'm pretty sure we are
right oh that is triggering the lifting
solution has been on for 12 minutes now
so we're going to peel this off now
we're going to take another clean brush
with a solution at number two which is
blue oh this one smells fine thank God
okay and we're going to apply this to
the brows once again and I guess the
solution that's going to like lock the
brows in place so we're going to make
sure that we get them in the
right position okay now that we have
this around a pond I'm going to let the
solution set once again for eight to
twelve minutes and this time I do not
have any Hawks to do in the meantime so
I'm going to set my alarm right now on
at my phone and we're going to cut and I
will see you guys hopefully with some
very very fluffy brows malleus has used
the nutrition who's gonna nourish and
stimulate my eyebrows stimulate I think
the point is just again whatever
direction you push them in they'll go I
mean cool I feel like it kind of yeah
this is good all right you guys well I
think that is the eye brow and lash
lamination part of this makeup hack all
complete and I will honestly say I feel
like this was a definite success which I
was not expecting at all I think this
kit was like $40 on Amazon and I'm gonna
put the link below if any of you guys
want to actually check it out I do not
think that for me this was necessary but
I do like the result a lot I feel like
this would be so so useful to people who
have a little bit of thinner brows or
not as many brow hairs I would
definitely definitely recommend just
don't sniff a solution to number one and
you should be good to go yeah let's move
on all right you guys we're back in our
base is all on it but as you can see
we're looking a little bit flat we're
all one color which means it is time to
contour now normally I would describe up
my contour kit lying around and a nice
fluffy contouring brush but for today's
video we have this it looks like a
flamingo this PC a contouring tool and
apparently if you hook it on your ear
like this and then well contour should
never be like why would it go this way
yeah I can already say this is stupid I
feel like the biggest mistake that
people make when conjuring is they don't
know where to put the actual product and
like the angle of which to put it and
this doesn't help like because you could
literally rotate this at any angle and
put your conch parts still anywhere no
it's not no idea 3d I am so sorry
while I'm trying to fix this and blend
this out as best as I can general rule
of thumb if you were somebody at home
that has struggled with contour in the
past and you would ever feel like you
might need a hack to help you out the
best trick that I ever learned is to
pretend that there's a line from the top
of your ear to the corner of your mouth
and that is where you should start the
contour also if you literally just take
the end of your makeup brush they can
you can feel where your cheekbone is
mine is right here and you want to keep
that product right on like the base of
your cheekbone and blend upwards to
create a natural shadow alright you may
sit for the Isetta portion of this look
today I actually have a ton of different
Beauty hawks some of them I'm excited
about and some of them I am just
dreading and horrified to even try at
this point but we just need to go ahead
and get started and the first thing
we're gonna do for our shadow is of
course crabber eyeshadow palette now we
picked up this one right here that I've
seen a few different ads about and if
you open it up it just looks like a
plain you know eyeshadow palette there's
a ton of different colors nothing really
that special for being honest but what
makes this crazy is you actually take
off the top layer and there's some more
in there Plus long and then you can take
off that layer and there's even more in
there this eyeshadow palette is 250
colors for twenty to twenty dollars or
twenty dollars the James Charles export
yourself it could never of course I'm
laughing at this because two hundred
fifty two shades for twenty dollars
probably means that these shadows are
gonna be pretty cheap quality but we're
gonna give them a fair shot and try them
out and this is almost like nostalgic to
me because that the first thing that I
ever bought when I first started doing
makeup was one of those BH Cosmetics
palettes that have like a million
different colors in it I saved up for
weeks on end and I bought it and the
shadows were definitely not great VHS
shadows are really really good now so
they've improved quite a lot but if you
are an OG at makeup community
probably had one of these in your
collection this is sidewalk chalk oh
this is hey I definitely want to put
that to the test today for a finer
rainbow look since it is June it is
Pride Month happy Pride to all my fellow
lgbtq+ sisters out there I'm sorry for
how homophobic this eye shadow look is
probably about to turn now so first I'm
gonna dip into this beautiful yellow
shade called miracles right it's gonna
really pop it onto the eye next I'm
gonna dip into this nice Tropicana shade
right up in here and we're gonna blend
that next to the bumble bee this isn't
supposed to be like a pastel look but
like if you were going for a pastel bark
like next I'm gonna dip into the shade
called Tampa and right up in here and
we're going to and we're gonna blend it
into emergency tablet okay so next one's
gonna dip into this a nice light pink
shade right here called labia minora
this is a good nice like pastel look so
now I'm gonna dip into this nice green
shade called Lima Bean right here and
we're going to a little bit of this one
too I just really place it now gonna dip
into this blue shade called bubble bath
yeah oh yeah every literally about a
follow up that's happening here all
jokes aside is like that's from
literally dipping into the blue shake
like one this is chalk the house
downwards and then if I I'm gonna dip
into this nice purple shade called
Barney was arrested and we're going to
finish off the cut crease all right so
now all the colors are laid on there and
honestly at this point it's not looking
it's too bad like I said in the
beginning okay this is one of like the
first products that ever bought and
although the quality is definitely not
ideal you're able to make looks work I
mean I definitely did it I know a lot of
people out there have as well so you can
make your own decision or whether not
this makeup Hawk is a fail or a success
but anyway I decide to onto our next
thing which is going to be a cutting my
crease and instead of using a brush and
some concealer we have this cut crease
stamp now this for me I feel like is
where this look is going to go very very
self very very fast but we're gonna try
it out and see what we can actually do
basically you're supposed to grab you
want to like crease cutter of choice
whether it be a light concealer or like
a liner put it on here and then you
stamp it onto the eyeball and it's
supposed to be a perfect cut alright you
guys so I just went ahead and put on my
favorite white concealer and now me too
oh no it Louis no it doesn't why did
this one end up so much higher than the
other one I mean come on
we knew that was gonna be a fail horse
Liza so now to set these really
beautifully cut creases in place I'm
just gonna grab this shade right here
called goat's milk our next step so this
apparently life-changing eyeliner
product is called the flexed and now my
liner is still to this day probably the
thing that I get the absolute most
questions comments team's emails about
like everyone said oh how to do their
eyeliner and it is very very tricky so I
can definitely see why a eyeliner Hawk
would be very very helpful but
apparently this flick stick is an
eyeliner stamp the tip of this marker is
not an actual tip it's literally it's a
stamp and it looks like the wing of an
eyeliner so I guess you're just supposed
to stamp this on your face and then the
other side it's a regular eyeliner I
mean it okay yeah it definitely creates
like the stamp let's see no it's not
let's go ahead and finish the wing using
the other side this literally feels like
I'm using a sharpie oh all right you
guys finally we are on to our last
makeup hack of the day and this is one
that is notorious and the makeup world
you all I am positive at some point I've
seen an advertisement for these and
these are magnetic eyelashes now before
I even put these on I'm gonna tell you
spoiler alert
these are a scam and they're stupid they
do not work like why okay so these
eyelashes are longer on this side so I'm
gonna take these like this and I'm gonna
put them how do you even get them just
like to these tweezers are also metal so
the magnet is sticking to them oh I'm
gonna literally scream I'm getting mad
now
[Music]
okay it this way I have had enough of
the makeup Hawks cut it quit its video
it's over weigh the Fallen all okay I
stand behind what I said in the
beginning of today's video if you were a
fellow makeup artist it really does not
matter what you want to do to get to the
final step there's so many different
tips and techniques and products that
you can use that I am fully supportive
of doing those that I would almost
teachers recommend checking out some
different channels here on YouTube and
if you do want to be an artist I would
definitely recommend learning the actual
techniques rather than taking stupid
shortcuts like this or like yes that
being said if you guys enjoyed it
today's video testing out these Hawks
please make sure to give it a big thumbs
up down below to show your love and
support and leave me a comment down
below and let me know what was the one
tip or technique that change your makeup
game forever if you have not ready makes
you click that big red subscribe button
down below and come join this sisterhood
we are 19 million sisters so I would
love to have you in the family and also
click the bell icon so you can be
notified every time I upload a brand new
video if you want to all be animated
journey all the way social media
accounts are listed right here and if
you want to touch me on my Clinton off
phone number right here for new updates
on everything it is three one oh nine oh
five eight seven at four six
this video is sisters how that goes to
at Maddie thank you so much to love her
always following you reporting I love
you so so so much and if you like you
the next videos a sister shadow don't
forget to please and reach people buddy
like something go live on Twitter thank
you for watching I love you so much and
I will see you
[Music]