hi sister James Charles here and welcome
back to my youtube channel today I am
bursting with excitement for today I am
bursting with excitement excited I am
bursting with excitement I would like to
see you guys this is Ashley Stratton me
winner instant influencers number one
our first ever instant influencer is
Ashley the channel I'm so happy to have
you here as you guys obviously know
Ashley was the winner of season one I'm
sorry if that's a spoiler okay you
shouldn't watch the attention to watch
it's been like what three days yeah it's
been a few days if you've not yet
checked it up make sure you click right
up here even though this is the spoiler
okay it's still definitely worth
watching and and miss Ashley took home
with the crowd after slaying the
competition lane and part of her prize
package was a club with me on my youtube
channel now it was such a pleasure
watching you slayed the entire
competition you were so talented and
this collab like I have been looking
forward to actually happening since the
minute you walk onto set so this is also
equally as much as the prize for me okay
thank you for having me I'm so excited
to be here of course tell me all about
that
honestly like I am dying dying dying to
do my finale look on you from the judges
including yours you have the mind of the
of the mastermind I have the mind of a
master master I have the mind of a
master if you guys want to see Ashley
create her winning finale look on me all
we talk about all things and to
influence or how your life has changed
over the past few weeks we have a lot of
things we want to talk about so I mean
there's so much really juicy finally we
can talk about it you guys get ready
[Music]
all right great so we're gonna we're
gonna get started on the look for today
and I have so many things that I want to
talk to you about how is the past few
weeks been what has changed I know you
it's absolutely insane I'm waiting for
my plaque in the mail I've seen yours
honestly and like life's just been so
crazy cause it's just like so many new
people all at the same time and I'm just
really excited to get started on this
brand-new journey so I know with that
I'm gonna totally explain the white skin
I feel like that was kind of like way
too on-trend I want this to be more
inspired by not as literal as Mario says
so we're gonna do the colors instead of
the black and white we're gonna do what
color you would put there looks like a
pink area for like blood like white fry
light yeah oh my god I leave out that
idea okay cool and then we'll just leave
the skin bare so just be like snatch
dope I'm never gonna do a half face yes
her face is good yep okay so what has
been like the biggest changes so far
since you announced it was made
obviously my engagement yeah I feel like
I blew up overnight and is super it's
like very in say influence or ass and I
think just like overall where I want to
go in the industry I think it's
definitely changed this is this has been
a super huge positive impact really yeah
anything new with like comments videos
like what'swhat's this situation because
I know earlier you're saying like you
feel like a lot of pressure now yeah now
I feel this unbelievable pressure to be
posting like super good juicy content so
I'm getting like a taste of what I feel
like you might be going through on a
daily basis like yeah so definitely
making sure that I mean remaining
interesting and open yeah is on the
porphyrin that pressure and like that
drive to continue posting it's going to
be what keeps you growing in as folks
kept all the other contestants growing
as well like for example like Kailyn as
well healings at like almost 300,000
followers by the time the mercury is in
can I have a second and I think like
she's written even over a million views
such good examples of like what the show
can do beyond you winning yeah you know
what I mean and how real is it that like
sometimes good that don't win right are
also just as successful if not more you
know what I mean so I think next we
should do the contour okay go for it
okay I want to know from you when we
finish talking first because I feel like
it's gonna like what were your
expectations going into the show
because obviously I've never done a
reality competition show before burn and
like what was the experience like for
you
honestly like I didn't have many
expectations but what I thought it was
gonna be like was like a big like Airbnb
and I thought you were gonna put all the
contestants in like a house
kind of like whole other side yeah so
that's what I thought was gonna be I
thought it was gonna be more like blog
style just like more laid-back I when I
got into the set it was like a
full-blown production and like I was
like whoa I was like did not expect that
how was your cruise on the show and you
can do this all your working as well be
watching well keep my mouth shut so you
can speak the experience in the show was
super intense
obviously like I've never done a
competition show before you gave us no
time to adjust what he was like
immediately like next day my competition
so I think for me it was just really
intense but what I will say is I learned
new things about myself and how I work
under pressure yeah okay wait are
contour oh is the night cont no you know
okay I want to know from you what do you
think was the hardest challenge on the
show and what was your favorite moment
from the show
okay hardest challenge ooh let's see the
hardest challenge I think was probably
the first one really cuz it was the
first one yeah that was like the hardest
one it was like really gonna set the
tone for what you were looking for any
we were going to be able to like you
know I was actually gonna hear you
critique me yeah first time so I think
it was gonna set the tone for like how I
was gonna compete it was such a cool I
mean so many other artists I mean like
Abe Reles luck was incredible for that
as well really cool but I feel like
yours was not only artistic but I also
connected like I told me a little bit
about you and how you do percent
yourself as an artisan person and that's
what it was about so blush should be
here or like on top of it like more
further back here is over that was your
favorite moment of the show and you can
do this while you're working winning now
my favorite moment outside of that it
was in the finale and it was when Kailen
like basically cornered me and she like
this close to my face that she was like
I'm in tonight
love you so much and I was like you're
gonna make me cry please stop one thing
that I want to know that we talked a
little bit about on the show but didn't
get too far into yet was your son I'm
scared that you are a mom yeah this is
so cool how did your son react to
winning personal um he could care less
no he's excited more so about like the
status and what this means for like his
friends and like their birthday
shoutouts
oh my god Elessar ready dude yes of
course but mostly he's just proud of me
and I think that my son doesn't he won't
ever admit this probably but I think
that he does get a little bit inspired
about me just having a really unorthodox
lifestyle yeah you know I'm not your
typical mom I'm the cool mom
so I really want to learn more about
like just your Teen Mom dirty I thought
- do they like talking about that on
your channel 100% okay yeah I'm ready
for that I am totally I'm down to
dedicate a lot of time actually to
talking about it cuz I think that
there's so many moms that get
discouraged from this industry because I
don't think they can or they're not you
know I don't know there's like moms get
discouraged about so much like your mom
had some issues or she like you know put
some things on the back burner for you
guys so I think moms do that as an
instinct right not me baby we can have
it all that's all so that you are
excited like the hot to tell him that I
said hello yes oh my god I know it's
like whiteout whoa God mr. peanut really
knows how to make a good product
oh okay so do me a favor and just look
down okay we look at me again sorry okay
with them okay actually I have a fun
question especially since you are not
great at showing your boobs
what was your first impression of both
the contestants and the judges oh that's
a good one okay so actually I was in the
car with Caitlin first which is so funny
Oh were you yeah so we couldn't talk to
each other on the show but Caitlin can't
help it she's very like so much of a
person she couldn't talk to me but she
was talking to the talent manager and so
my first impression of Caitlin was she
talks when she's nervous yeah and then
when I first saw the other contestants
was like on set
so my first impression of indigo was oh
my god he looks like a Babbage like he
is definitely going like I kind of
targeted him as like my biggest threat
immediately I was he has a presence
about him in the real life definitely
one of the artists that I was looking
forward most to seeing I think he's
gonna take everything that happened with
the show and run with that oh yes I hope
he does he's the perfect example of like
you don't need to win to have success
for sure but he I kind of sized him up
because he just has this aura about him
very bad [ __ ] vibe so I was kind of
like okay and then Benny
I've been protective and very maternal
over Benny since the moment I saw him he
was very quiet and kind of meek and
although he has a very big boisterous
personality his energy is very still an
eighteen year old so I felt really
maternal over him
yeah I didn't talk much with Gabriel
until actually after indigo went home
that's when Gabriel really started to
show his personality to us he was really
quiet I was surprised he's very shy so I
actually mean Gabriel what you don't see
is that we had really long conversations
about like zodiacs and like crystals and
like the earth and the planet cuz I'm
into that kind of stuff too like no one
would ever know that but so my
impressions of Gabriel was that he was
really quiet and then after I got to
know him he was just actually a really
deeply caring person yeah my first
impression of Brittany was she had the
cutest style so Brittany had on like a
really cute little cropped like black
windbreaker and he's like cute ripped-up
high-waisted jeans so I actually looked
at Brittany and I was like oh my god
she's so cute which is like she's so
pretty that was my first impression brt
mm-hmm my first impression of you was
that oh yeah please tell me my first
impression of James was like this isn't
a YouTube channel like why is he talking
in real life like it just didn't
register to me and he looked like he was
still in his channel but in real life so
like very bright shiny super sparkly
that's what I like most sparkly in
person oh my god okay so concealer I
don't know if it's not fit James I'll
show you to bake
yeah right right to bake in this region
perfect
like the tick box where are you getting
your hair kind of the members
bro if you don't stop looking at me I
swear I'm cutting all your hair off
how was it when you got to watch the
episode to see the judgment deliberation
like that you weren't there for you guys
said so much to us like to our faces I
know so and nothing like shocked me
about it I think where I was like oh is
that in those moments we just had no
idea of what you guys were saying yeah
like we just had no idea how you guys
were coming up with the decision right
so the dance were like our long
deliberation yeah let's make sure we
made the right choice I guess I didn't
realize how much you guys you know put
into the making the decision so even
more privilege okay glad to know it
wasn't like a crazy shady no no no it
was good it was all right so Ashley just
apply to do lips to the lips and then
also added the other eye on camera so
even though we're gonna take the photo
half way just in case
a lot of TVs there are no angles you
know we're gonna pop on at the lashes
and I have one final question for you
that I think will be a great way to end
off this video and that is what can of
both your new fans and the fans events
influence or expect to see from this
Ashley strong missus trust me moving
forward and know that you are the victor
what are you gonna do definitely open up
some more honestly you guys I didn't
realize how cold and kind of nonchalant
I come off on camera so you know I read
all the comments I got all the feedback
I definitely take it as constructive
criticism yeah and I want to be open and
more connected with you guys so I'm
definitely to be opening up more being a
lot more vulnerable I also want to
incorporate my son into my channel okay
which is something that I've never
really even considered so I am so
excited to just evolve and become a lot
more multi-faceted for you guys and show
you guys all the different sides of me
my time doesn't makeup would be the
cutest video ever I am really excited to
start a whole series actually also don't
be shy you guys totally shot tell me
what you guys want to see in the
comments as well all right you guys I
think this off-white look is complete
obviously this looks so cool I think
this is such a fine a twist on the
original look from the challenge yeah I
love that you wanted to take your time
and take the judges like criticism I
think this looks so cool this is gonna
be a mega makeup mo man it looks like a
filter this would be a good filter I
think this is gonna go viral
Ashley thank you so much for joining us
today I love you and thank you for being
here thank you for being on the show
thank you first like every single
challenge I told you this as soon as
like the balloons were all falling down
but I was like it was such a pleasure
watching you slay and season one was
amazing and I'm just really excited for
people to be able to watch your journey
and to be inspired by it and to see your
growth and to see how much you killed it
and hopefully my first thing earlier
you guys will all on Edition for season
2 whatever we do open that up I've set
the bar I need good luck who knows maybe
I still have to come back for an episode
or two we'll have to keep you guys
posted a judge and if you guys like this
awfully inspired look to actually paint
it on me today and if you want to
recreate it please tag us we would love
love love to see your guys's looks I
know you can reposting so many on your
soil is the hash tag off me I already
have a hash tag you guys so make sure
you using a hash tag so that we can see
it and we can repost yes he's so cute
but regardless thank you guys so much
for watching today's video and just
thank you overall for watching all
events influence or this club officially
is like the end of a chapter I mean
through era yeah wouldn't have been
possible if it were not for you guys so
thank you so much thank you so much if
you guys enjoyed today's video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below so if you have not already
cooking this is your head we're 19
million sister strong and I would love
to have you join the family and finally
click that Bell icon so you know
depending time I upload a brand new
video don't forget to visit my channel
you guys we are 400 plus sisters strong
yes I Thunder oh my god we didn't have a
slice of that cake we definitely do
we're gonna go clap over there as well
yeah I'm gonna do we're gonna be reading
your natal chart if you like to follow
me on my makeup Turner you can follow me
on Instagram Twitter tick-tocking
Facebook are all just jams huh a
snapchat for more behind-the-scenes
efficacy of Charles the next your ass
after Charles Anna my phone number if
you want to text me for any updates on
new videos photos merch and so much more
exclusive information is three one now
at nine oh five eight seven four six
I see where could they find you you can
find me at strache me on all of my
platforms except for Twitter I have two
E's on my Twitter and you guys can also
text me at 747 to 0-6 1587
this video sister shout out goes the
sister Kyle thank you so much love for
always falling in supporting I love you
so so so much and if you like to you
next video sister shadow don't forget to
always reach me middle east [ __ ] live
on Twitter and also to my youtube post
occasion all right you guys thank you so
much for watching this videos today and
thank you Asli once again
all the way from Anchorage Alaska and
for slang to beauty community I'm so
excited to continue watching you girl
and I hope that you guys will check her
out as well I love you and I'll see you
in the next one bye I never see my
sister's maladroit she's done oh okay
I'm taking the one back Marty here baby
[Music]