hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel in
last night's episode of instant
influencer which if you have not seen
make sure you click right up here and go
watch it first so you don't get any
spoilers in today's video I challenged
my artists to team up with the biggest
names in beauty for an ultimate collab
challenge as you guys know for my
Tuesday uploads in between regular
episodes I thought I'd be really fun to
do a video inspired by the last
episode's challenge but because of copán
19 and the stay at home orders a collab
challenge just isn't really possible or
is it so for today's video inspired by
inset influencer episode of 3 I am
wrangled together all my favorite
friends in the beauty community for a
virtual collab pretty much the biggest
get ready with me and YouTube history
and we're all gonna do it one step of
our makeup routine make sure that you
did not click on for this video and you
watch all the way to the end because you
may see it your favorite beauty guru
let's get started
[Music]
to start off this video today is one of
the kindest and in my opinion most
talented artists in the beauty community
she inspired me to get my channel
started and has always pushed me to take
my content to the next level Nikki
you're up girl all right hi everybody it
is an honor to be here I hope you're
ready for all the glam that is about to
come at you because oh boy we've got
some stars lined up I am the first one
to kick it off for you today and I am
doing foundation but the number one rule
before applying any foundation is
surprise because not true prime is a the
foundation I'll be wearing today is my
NARS this right here is the natural
radiant foundation so how is everyone
holding up during this quarantine
madness and not just quarantine madness
I'm talking 2020 madness a lot of you
guys know that earlier this year I came
out as transgender not by free will
unfortunately for the full story please
check out my video but if there's one
thing that 20/20 has made very clear for
me is that there are so many good people
left in this world
I know as beauty gurus face negativity
every single day we faced backlash every
single day but the moment I opened up
and showed my vulnerable side and told
you my truth the warmth and the love
that I received was unmatched it was so
unreal and I cannot believe that I'm
living my truth so openly and freely and
feeling so loved by all of you and one
thing and that's why I'm really excited
that we're doing this here today one
thing that has really helped me through
the stress and the anxiety and just all
of it concerning my coming-out was
makeup makeup will always and forever be
that one thing in my life that keeps me
grounded and is sort of like my coping
mechanism like if what I'm doing here
right now do my makeup is what keeps me
me honestly so I am so excited for the
people that you're about to see on your
screen in this collab because they are
phenomenal stars and the fact that we as
a group got together for this video is
exactly what 2020 needs all right so my
foundation is on and now it is time for
concealer and free concealer we're gonna
be moving along to our next star and not
just any star a star with three R's
please welcome the concealer and
bacon king of YouTube Patrick star here
we go
Thank You Nikki good catch
alright guys of my section is concealer
and baking I'm a little bit extra so I
like to take two concealers and two
powders for my face and let's just go
ahead and get sealers that I'm using is
mac studio finish at the benefit bling
concealer a cream and a liquid that's my
secret concoction for my face I know
it's a little bit extra and it's not for
everyone
but that's what works for me and other
tickets on a synthetic brush right here
and painful battle alright guys this is
the face that I'd love to highlight with
I'm gonna go ahead and just blend that
out like so I just make sure you blend
shout out to James for instant
influencer I love what he's doing for
the community it's a very beautiful
industry it's a very crazy industry but
I think it's really meant to be and
speaking of industry I've been
discovering new talent on tik-tok and
that's what I've been doing during my
quarantine and keeping me busy and away
from the reality that we are living in
just to kind of get my mind off things
like I said the powder that I'm going to
use is my Patrick Starr powder that I
did with Matt cosmetics I poured it onto
a plate like pouring it onto a plate so
I have more control just any ol plate
I'm just baking right under the eye okay
so last but not least for this step of
the concealer I'm baking this airspun
powder is so thick so heavy it's a drag
queen staple if you ask me like to take
this with my pub and you really just
warm up strength
a little yoga okay all right guys that
concludes of my concealing and baking I
hope you guys learned some techniques
from me to you so that's in this path of
the makeup tutorial I'd love to
introduce a very fabulous dragon among
all the beauty community the one and the
only Nikita
dragon here you go [ __ ] thanks P star
hi sisters it's Nikita and today I'm
gonna show you how it's you contour and
add a little blush because we look a
little scared right now
come on we need to look cute let's go
listen sisters Warren teen has been so
crazy I'm gonna be honest you guys they
definitely have been going through it I
think you know even bad [ __ ] have
feels as well and I feel like this is
just a moment to be extremely reflective
and kind of pause I mean the world is on
pause so we all need to you know you
know I feel like I was humans and just
in this crazy lifestyle we're so used to
being on to the next thing on to them
what can I do more and just wanting to
be so rampant I think we never like slow
down and really look at all we have and
I feel like it especially at this time
we we kind of see how valuable just like
health is without even realizing it you
become so selfish you become so like oh
my god what do I need oh my god I need
to do this I need to do that but you
really don't need those things you know
like I said I think we're all kind of
going through it in a way and
reminiscing and replaying little moments
over and over again and I just want to
say to you guys stop it stop just as a
little reminder because I have been
driving myself crazy replaying all these
situations and moments let this at least
be a reminder to you a wake-up call the
girl every day is not guaranteed you
know that time that you went out and you
were scared to put on that outfit or
that time you were scared to have that
moment [ __ ] have the moment no regrets
[Music]
okay and now for the undisputed special
effects queen miss glam and gore miss
mikey is about to show you guys how to
snatch your eyebrows I'm jealous because
I clearly don't have any catch [ __ ]
thanks Nikita let's find my eyebrows so
I'm using Katie D's super brow pomade to
start filling in
missing eyebrows you're probably
wondering what happened to my eyebrows
and the truth is I lost them in a fight
with squirrel is that but anyway in
quarantine I've been spending a lot of
time with my favorite creatures on earth
that includes my boyfriend Anthony been
getting to spend a lot of quality time
with him which I really really really
enjoy and spending it with my dog Ripley
and my newest favorite creature in the
house my new dog his name is creature
since creature is new to the world I've
been spending a lot of Quarantine time
teaching him new tricks and trying to
teach my first dog how to adapt to our
new dog there has never been a more
appropriate time to say this but I aim
for sister's squirrels can't stop me now
okay I think it's time for eyeshadow so
I will be passing at this palette on to
the most super sister there is a man who
needs no introduction because it's his
channel no one the only James Charles
thank you so much Mikey
hello you guys James here of course of
my mini palette let's just dive right
into the eyeshadow portion the one thing
that has really been helping me get
through quarantine and keep a positive
attitude has honestly been watching a
lot of nude YouTube content that is not
related to beauty since beauty is my job
and I do it every day I really don't
watch that much beauty content on
YouTube anyway but during this
quarantine I have been going deeper and
deeper into the depths of YouTube and
watching a lot of content that you guys
probably never expect a few days ago I
actually put out a tweet saying I had
experienced new levels of boredom
because I spending my night watching
somebody play a Sudoku puzzles on
YouTube I discovered this puzzle channel
on YouTube called cracking it at the
cryptic and I have fallen in love with
their videos my absolute favorite
pastime in the entire world is doing
escape rooms but since the road is
obviously closed out I'm not able to do
that so if you guys are fellow nerds
like me and you love solving puzzles I
would deathly recommend checking out
their channel I've also been watching an
alarming amount of Minecraft videos I
would definitely recommend checking out
mumbo jumbo and also exhume avoid oh my
god I almost forgot to mention to you
guys I have just recently got into a
survivor the TV show okay I know I'm
super super late in fact I'm 40 seasons
late but my friend caught me into this
new season two winners at war and I have
become so addicted I'm literally ready
to give up a month of my life and go
survive on a deserted island at this
point because it seems so far but I
haven't been watching
the show literally non-stop you guys
should definitely leave me a comment
down below and let me know what you've
been watching to stay entertained it
during this quarantine and helpful hint
it better be it's the influencer alright
that is the eyeshadow portion all
complete but as you guys can see we
still have a little bit left to go on
the eyes and of course the rest of the
face so I'm gonna grab a fresh pair of
Lillie lashes and I'm gonna hand them to
somebody who could always make me smile
no matter what I'm going through and it
was also taught me that even though this
is my job it's okay to have fun I never
take life too seriously and most
importantly it to be a bad [ __ ] well
duh baddest Brooklyn here you go since
you guys are probably so bored watching
James do his eyeshadow I am here to save
the day so the past couple of days /
honestly months at this point I have a
just been hanging out with my plants
hanging out with my boyfriend
I literally have been quarantine myself
trying my hardest to the place anytime I
have to go to the store I don't I make
my brother or my man do it or sometimes
mrs. King other than that I really feel
like this whole quarantine thing I
really thought that you know this is the
time to really play with your look so I
don't know how much time we have left in
quarantine but I'm really glad that I
really was taking this time to like
switch up my hair I got a nose piercing
on I know a lot of people were dying
their hair during quarantine ah I even
cut my hair really short and beginning
but now it's back to my regular regular
style [ __ ] Tyler Lee was poking my I am
[Music]
super laughs just today we're gonna be
using miss Liliana lash iana's in the
color Miami Flair
I'm gonna be the cutest one in this
collab I didn't know it I got it now
let's move on to the bearded Queen I'm
mr. CEO of lunar Beauty and mr. and
mattie MUA oh my god Binks Redmond mom
hey guys if you were to you Wow
hey guys what's up so today I'm gonna be
showing you guys a little bit of a
highlighting moment together with this
goddess this Greek goddess when James
asked me to be part of this video I was
so excited to do except I would be so so
so fun to just show a community in
solidarity in a tough time and you know
you guys we are with you every step of
the way and we hope that you're doing
amazing and doing the best that you can
during quarantine that's all we can
really ask for right is just doing the
best that we can and it's crazy because
I feel like this quarantine has made me
get closer to my family has anyone else
like noticed that like I've never felt
closer to my family that I do right now
in quarantine and it's so crazy cuz I
feel like I'm really making lemonade out
of lemons and it's such a you know
crappy situation and it sucks for
everyone it really really does but you
guys know it's so so important to just
show solidarity do the right thing be
safe out there be responsible and be
just aware of your surroundings at all
times you know oh I would a little ham
Rudolph's nose gay cousin but I will say
if I play another board game I play
guitar one more time I play Catan with
my family every single day so I hope you
guys are staying safe out there and
being good I love you guys so so so much
and I just want to pass this k'kaw
beauty lip liner to the most sickening
para the true para of you to she's
stunning she's latina Louis this one's
for you [ __ ]
thanks Manny me hey guys I am so happy
that I was able to be a part of this
virtual collab since we weren't all able
to hang out and film this in person I
hope you and your family are staying
safe at home taking care of yourselves
so I'm going to be doing it my nails so
while a quarantine I've been spending
time with my family since normally we
all have a really busy days I feel like
I never really get to spend that time
with them so now that we're all at home
I finally get that family time I'm very
family-oriented so I'm definitely taking
advantage of this time to spend it with
my family since I'm always on the road
working taking flags just a little
overlay moment I've also taken this time
to finally clean my house I have such a
mess in my film room so I was able to
organize clean these around I even
painted up my beauty room oh okay so now
I have my lab wheels all dead and
complete I'm just really happy that I'll
be able to spend this time with my
family at home and finally getting stuff
done I hope you guys are also taking
advantage of this time to take care of
yourself do what you want to do spend
with your family
do your makeup whatever they have sick
babies alright I hope you all stay safe
take care and love you guys bye Massa
let me disinfect out with some setting
spray
[Music]
all right you guys I hope you enjoyed it
this virtual collab the past the brush
challenge with all my friends in the
beauty community this was so much fun to
film and put together and I really
really hope that you guys enjoyed in it
put a smile on in your face on behalf of
all of us I just wanted to say thank you
for watching and you know as beauty
gurus and youtubers we are incredibly
lucky and grateful to still be able to
do our jobs during this really awful
global pandemic and we know that
unfortunately that is not the case for
everybody else we are all super super
grateful for all of you guys watching us
and supporting us on a daily basis
because this video is so special today
to say thank you for supporting us we
wanted to do our part as youtubers and
support people who have been affected by
the virus and Cova 19 our relief if you
look over right here on your YouTube
screen you will see a donation button it
is definitely not necessary or required
but if you have a little bit of extra
money lying around and you're able to
donate I strongly encourage you guys to
use the box right up here and what's
even cooler about this is that Google
actually made a valve to match every
single dollar donated it with two so
basically three dollars from every one
dollar which is super super cool and I
would love to work together as the
beauty community to make a positive
impact just wanted to add it since we
were able to put this together for my
youtube channel
I thought it'd be only appropriate to
get the fundraiser started I'll be
personally donating at $25,000 to copa90
relief which thanks to Google becomes
75,000 I know these times are really
hard if we work together as a community
we can get through this always remember
to stay safe wash your hands and most
importantly stay at home [ __ ] my
sisters my sisters bye sisters bye
sisters bye beach boy
[Music]