hi Suze James Charles here involved um
back to YouTube channel you guys this
club okay she has been in the works
because they believe this was supposed
to happen last year okay one Halloween
ago 365 days ago and it did not happen
it was my file take full responsibility
with the time of years back there are
spooky scary skeletons sending shivers
down your spine it was Halloween time
and you guys doing how to have Mikey
other table to do an iconic Halloween
transformation Anna and I'm just so
excited you guys she's literally the
sweetest the most talented ever on the
entire world it's so let me tell you
something sister hope I'm disappointed
in you of all the years that you've been
a sister yes you've never been a real
sister wears coloring we're turning you
into a nun it's like a sister and the
movie okay how are you the sister who
has never been assistant why did do it
not like a nun like I'm not Dean done
but like a nun look a few years ago for
Halloween and I had a car across carved
in 24 head upside down with blood
but the nun is a really buff I would say
it's a bob movie it's a decent movie but
the character itself don't put this in
there yeah Mikey it was okay
I do like James on a lot so I love it I
mean it it's not like to do this okay
okay we can watch it together after the
clock okay great papers are the way to
go we'll get into the video well in
honor of Mikey's channel being called
glam angora as you can see right now I'm
very glam we're gonna transform into
something very core and it's gonna be
very very fun so if you guys want to
come along on this spooky makeup
transformation journey keep on watching
[Music]
okay so the first thing we need to do
before we make you super ugly is we need
to put teeth in your mouth and mail them
to your party I'm already mad about this
nope okay my teeth are like the absolute
once they got on my face that I am happy
with everything else okay we're not here
to be pretty house dusters okay what do
we have to do to apply these so we're
gonna stick them in boiling water okay
stick these in boiling water just look
like when you were singing our yeah
spooky retainer oh okay so she IG glam
Taliban yes take it all off okay I'm
gonna be glam and we'll see you guys
downstairs in the kitchen in a second
okay so what are we doing with this hot
cup of water and these disgusting so
we're pouring Kalamata lastik into hot
water okay if you watch it us it's a lot
like your mug see what's happening
that's oh yeah Wow it's disappearing
what the how does that even work it
turns clear when it's fully warmed and
then we're gonna oh my god I saw what ok
so then once it's still hot you can bend
it like that you push it in there and
then your job and you're going to gently
push this against your teeth and then
hold it there for about a minute and the
plastics gonna start the hardener on
your teeth we might need to do this a
couple times because it's a little
finicky to get the mold
right but once it's just right they just
pop right in they're gonna do the same
thing to the bottom one where you just
mold it to the arch already fixed we
were back and the teeth are all molded
20s we show them or so we wear the end
yes okay oh okay great so um I get let's
are our next steps I guess okay the next
step is to get rid of these eyebrows
yeah okay great
oh my God my poor disgust Ahab I like it
it's dad so you can obviously cover your
brows the old-fashioned way with the
glue stick and the stuff or you can use
FX brow covers which are just little
pieces of foam latex glue it right on
top of your brow okay all these are just
gonna use a pros-aide then yeah I
already spilt sit on the table you done
I've always had a major infatuation with
special effects makeup I think it is so
cool I know the basics I'm not an expert
in any way shape or form but I can get
to a finished product that looks
possible passable is what we yeah yeah
for sure it's definitely all I aim for
it okay well your I would say your a
little bit better than possible if I
judging based on you were fooled you
good that's like what movie horror
movies could load up a paper topic in
the entire world to discuss and I don't
talk about a very often because most
people I feel like don't like horror
movies which is really sad what are your
top favorites because I have mine and I
have my list memorize what are your
favorites as far as classics go I love
The Exorcist I think that a lot of
people think that it's like silly now
cuz it doesn't hold up to the times yeah
but at the time it scared people so bad
that they were running out of the
theaters vomiting they had priests in
the theaters because people were so
freaked imagine that happening today I
don't think that whatever happened no
there's nothing like they kept on camera
no the internet desensitized us to
everything okay I'm gonna get my list of
favorites no I don't want your feedback
okay
my top two are probably tied between
hereditary and sinister and obviously
that are very different movies
hereditary was one of the first movies
that I ever saw that actually left me
like frightened there was not a lot of
jump scares the movie but I actually
left the theater and went home was like
oh well I had a little bit spooked to go
to sleep tonight
like left my stomach churning and that's
what it was it's disturbing it's a good
way to
that was a good movie I love love love
hurts Harry my next favorite as above so
below
great did you see scary stories to tell
in the dark but I heard that the FX was
really good
phenomenal there's one theme that
literally it was so uncomfortable to
watch that I like felt like I was gonna
throw up but also could not take my eyes
off the screen so I was so intrigued by
both the visuals and just the thought of
what went on to create what I was
watching
so one of the stories is like this boy
he lives on a farm then you have the
Scarecrow he always kicks it with this
friend and then one day the Scarecrow
comes to life and kills him and then
when he kills them with the boy turns
into a scarecrow
the Scarecrow stabs him starts coughing
and hay starts coming out of his mouth
he sees his arms and like hey stars are
coming out of his sleeves and like his
finger so he turns into the Scarecrow
bunny like it's literally like
suffocating out hey and there's like
vines and like oh my god literally just
thinking about it make me feel
uncomfortable but they did it so it was
insane to watch so now unless we were in
a powder oh thank you can I make a
confession I'm awful at scar wax we all
are it's just the nature of the beast
are you serious yeah it's very hard to
work with but impossible I literally
thought I was just like incompetent and
couldn't figure out the right math you
know it's hard to work with but for
something like what we're doing today if
we can get it to work it is our best
shot at it looking great it's a great
out of kit option guidance its
difficulties there's a couple tricks
that make it easier one of which is
putting prosy down first Oh hasn't it
has something to stick to
okay right now okay and the other thing
you can do to make it easier is you need
a Vaseline uh-huh so that it doesn't
stick to your hands
so you grease up your hands first and
then you
the nose and scar wax and then it's
easier to use oh my god Wow I'm changing
yeah that does actually feel like it
would be a major help every time that
I've ever had to use it just molds to my
fingers and you start sticking and then
you can't achieve anything
yes what is your favorite transformation
that you have her done I turned myself
into a realistic or Ursula last
Halloween oh okay I think I remember
that video she was cute I'm gonna push
on your nose a little bit but let me
know if I hurt you no I'm not gonna stop
you know what
the Mona Lisa wasn't done in a day okay
my nose is like the one thing my face
that I used to be really really insecure
about but thank you hey hey did when I
first heard you make it because I could
not figure out how to contour it for the
life of me and I thought it was so ugly
plus you're young I mean honestly I feel
like people grow into their face and
their noses yeah there's probably melts
in there no it's just scar wax but it
looks like boogers this noses everything
so I'm just making sure I get it right
[Applause]
that's really accurate I feel like you
say that's your nose and if you disagree
oh well okay so our just powdering this
as well using 501 for this interesting
choice choice great for FX to not just
clam promo pick it up at your local
Murphy store today or Murphy calm yes
James 4:7 she actually does have the
brush that with her that is really cute
I also oh your legend do you actually
like using it I usually use a mini
palette that's too late all right let's
go Owen okay so now we're just gonna
play a light base layer right so just
wait Oliver yeah pretty much
great and luckily her foundation there's
a little splotchy she's not a beauty
guru there's like ever like a little
highlight on the cheekbone thank you I
bring it up and bring attention to the
face you know mm-hmm
I'm gonna start stippling your face with
some green okay and Browns and tans
because her face has got some texture
and using a sponge like this is good cuz
it's automatic - okay I should turn this
for full rekkles but not this color I
literally use an FX punished for a faux
freckle tutorial from like years really
that's so cool you know what you kind of
look like be really careful what you're
about to say right now you kind of look
like when you know you've seen a statue
that a bird is pooped on a lot of times
yeah okay I'm gonna need you a black eye
great pretty margin yes like live on
camera the drama which also go crazy
about that one oh you want to just stage
it no yeah cuz that's what she's got
going on she's got a very messy intense
smoky eye okay a beauty guru for sure
for sure
when's the last time someone made you
ugly this morning Lois oh my god
only the Lawson that I got transformed
for like the beauty convention video I
don't really have a lot of people do my
makeup kind of period let alone
special-effects stuff yeah this is like
my second time I are having special
effects like apply it to my face I think
yeah Mikey what are your favorite ways
to stay inspired for actual Halloween
looks what I tend to do is I think of
something that I just really like like a
movie that I really like or show or a
character and then I try to think of
some kind of twist to put on it or
whether it's like a gender bender or
it's a glam thing and I put an FX twist
on it and like that or just if all else
fails pick a really common costumer
character and then some
this year for Halloween I was feeling a
little and inspired I found this really
beautiful pirate dress mmm I'm just
gonna be a zombie pirate love Bob he's a
little too spooky from the new what Davy
Jones likes more people mini pallet
perfect for clamming on the go including
all the we make up now I'm gonna give
you a black map really emphasizes the
lips luscious pouty did you know that
the shadows cookie from the James
Charles X morphe palette is great as a
lipstick I have never tried it before I
know all the shade names do you yeah
what's this one murder no show this one
vomit no exorcist puke green yes that is
do you actually got that one right wait
is there teeth yeah socialblade mixed
with that one daddy yeah daddy cut that
out when we set the team's falsehood
truly creative all right now I'm just
giving you some contour really emphasize
the cheekbones
all right you guys as well we've run a
clothing or goring rather for a few
hours now so we're gonna take a quick
break for some fried chicken oh it
should be an interesting eating
experience who see what back here - my
god yeah are you guys we're back from
eating some nice chicken dinners and
fries that surprisingly the face is not
that messed out we're professional
eaters there's also a fly that is
getting so brave always so close to mint
oh my god you saw it
do you remember your earliest Halloween
costume as a kid yeah yes I remember
being a mummy in preschool and my mom
and I took toilet paper and like robbed
and are like soaked in like T to get it
like a nice like my spoken brown color
spoken
we ate my mom and I made all my costumes
DIY when I was a young kid just cuz the
guy so I'm trusting my mom was very
crafty yes what was always awesome I was
a clown and preschool still oh you are
really getting brave Mikey oh my god I'm
taking I can still blow your mouth shut
okay
so I'm going to add some veins a little
bit of detailing and then I think it's
gonna be about time for accessories just
as he walk clacking cream paint yeah bit
of things okay you just happened with
out with water and it just disappeared
that's kind of the secret to veins is if
you tap it out when it's water based or
alcohol based it looks like it's under
the skin a little bit more that's so
cool that looks crazy Mikey oh my gosh
contacts time context okay they're so
scared for cuz I might be able to see
for the ranger of this video so I
literally won't even see the finished
look and toll oh gosh we look back at
the footage already bracing now we have
to look pretty much all on I have my
contacts and they are actually like
comfortable I can see but I can't see so
that's good I guess we're pretty much
almost that all we have left is the
costume and teeth so we're going to
quickly get changed off-camera and then
we will show you guys the finished look
[Music]
all right sisters well I think tuck
completes this done translations with
the incredible Mikey at glamma Gore all
of my god you killed this murder best
for lack of better Halloween word this
looks great of you yeah I don't know who
that is that's nineteen you could walk
around outside right now and no one
would ever know yes why does that sound
so fun already nice and I really hope
you enjoyed this little Halloween that
transformation that thank you so much
again like you for coming I went yes I
had such a good with you and I really
hope that you guys you sisters there you
go enjoy this video as well if you did
it don't forget to give it a huge thumbs
up down below and show your love and
support it really does help us help so
so so much and also leave us a comment
let us know what is your favorite horror
movie of all time
people don't let's have a horror little
discussion give us some recommendations
as well because we might even have a
[ __ ] night very very soon together and
we love to watch one of your crisis
all-time favorites if you've not ready
we should click that Baker at subscribe
button down below and come join at this
sister and I'd love to have you and the
family also click that Bell icon so you
could ovation every time I upload a
brand new video but more importantly
also head over to a Mikey channel over
on YouTube please subscribe she is so
good with Alton has literally the
craziest tutorials of both clam but
mostly Gore all year round if you like
to follow me on Instagram Twitter twitch
and now also a tip top a little bit
follow me on James Charles is also my
snapchat for more behind-the-scenes like
chopper senior Charles an extra s after
Charles that video sisters not a ghost
his sister Abby thank you so much love
for always falling in supporting you
know I love you it so so so much and if
you would like to be the next videos a
sister so I think it looks so weird that
I have this well based on into sick
normal hands like hey girl
if you guys do that's videos that sister
shadow don't forget to always reach
people
and also turn on YouTube post on
vacations already guys thank you so much
watching this video today I will see you
on Friday and happy Halloween
[Music]