hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel in
today's video I'm going to be finally
addressing and talking about something
that you guys have been asking me about
for years now I've avoided this topic
completely if that I have gotten
thousands of comments there have been
news articles written about it and there
have been countless tweets that ago on a
ridiculously viral with hundreds and
thousands of different likes on them all
asking James are you Julie pav
now I will say the public is never
actually seen it myself and du liebe in
the same place at the same time so you
can form your own opinions but we have
seen a lot of Dooley pose iconic musical
moments and you think we've also seen
some of my less iconic musical moments
so I think it is safe to say
unfortunately I'm not do a lip balm but
that being sad I've seen your tweets
I've seen your posts sometimes I just
don't see it but there's other times
where I'm like oh my gosh we look so so
similar so for today's video I thought
it'd be super fun to transcend that I've
never actually done before on my youtube
channel and that is a celebrity
transformation in to do a Lipa let's get
started
[Music]
okay you guys I am so excited for the
transformation at today at du liebe is
by far my favorite pop stars right now
her music is so good she just keeps
releasing a bomb after bomb after bomb
after bomb
I also think she is it so stunning it
starting off I popped on this a fun
little green turtleneck because she
wears a lot of a bright colors and I
also popped on up my darker brown
contacts because she has super dark eyes
the first step we're going to do before
actually applying any makeup is
something super fine that but I'm also a
little bit nervous about and that is
face tapes if you don't know what these
are these are a super like
behind-the-scenes about a beauty Hawk
that are used in a lot of Hollywood
movies and on set all the time they are
a tiny little plastic sheet and you
stick it to your face and then used it
the other one to the other side and you
pull and it gives you a super snatch
look so I thought this would be good for
today transformation it because do it
does have a little bit more of a pull to
I than I do what I love the look of so
we're gonna try this up for the first
time I actually watched on my favorite
makeup artist makeup by her roots to an
entire video on these so I'm going to a
try my best to apply these today but if
you guys want to check these up for
yourself check out her brushes video so
I definitely want a little facelift so
this whole thing will stick better now
oh my god this one looks a little long
that's one notch loser tell us about her
okay cool I know these face tapes look
absolutely insane right now but don't
worry it the makeup will go on over top
of them and they won't be noticeable and
then once the wig goes on if you'll even
see them at all these are not for
everyday use although if you want to be
stash off the time be my guest
I think this looks super cool but it's
now time to do all the makeup on top
before doing this video today I left
through to his entire Instagram page cuz
I really want to emulate her makeup
style
best way that I possibly can and the one
thing that I noticed is that she does
always do I find that pop of color on
the eyes but for the base it's honestly
like kind of natural she does always
have like a little bit of a medium
coverage foundation a little bit of
blush a little bit of glow but there's
never too much contour never too much
under-eye brightening it's like kind of
even which is definitely very different
for my typical makeup style but I
definitely wanna emulate that today so
I'm gonna grab the Effendi Beauty at Pro
feltzer hydrating it foundation who
actually I do want to color cut a tiny
bit first just because duly put is in
fact a woman and I'm not and and a 3 and
a 4 o'clock a 645 shadow as well now I'm
gonna go in that foundation and to start
buffing it into the skin I'm actually
gonna add it just a little bit of at the
pro filter foundation in the shade at
210 which I know is a little bit darker
than my natural skin tone I did say the
20/20 is gonna be the year I'm matching
my foundation but I do want to make this
transformation as accurate as possible
and I feel like do it it's a little bit
more tan and than I am so I wanna make
sure that that is reflected for
concealer today as always I'm just gonna
use my Tarte shape tape but I'm only
gonna put a little bit of this
underneath my eyes where I have some
slight discoloration a little bit on or
a lot a bit on my beard area and then
the center of the forehead and then I'm
also going to use my brush to above and
now before I go in and set this all in
place a powder for a bronzer today I'm
actually gonna grab a cream bronzer just
this la 10 so gosh it's too late hon
Deschanel and I'm gonna put this on in
the same type of like a shapes that I
normally do because the one thing that
is super similar about us is our facial
structure oh my god you literally can't
even see the face tapes on camera whoa
and then just using a flat brush this
one is I don't know the label is robbed
off of it I'm just gonna grab some alarm
RCA translucent setting powder and cut
this so for contour today it's always in
this figure my Anasazi a contour kit and
I am 405 bucks but I'm going to
literally use like none of this I just
want to kind of reinforce a little bit
about bronzer that I put on it almost
looks like she has like a little bit of
like wander on her chin Darry even say
like at least in a lot of these photos
it does oh now this nose contour I'm
scared about because dewa doesn't
actually contour her nose like at all
and
but he's been watching my channel for
more than approximately three minutes
you would know that nose contour is
pretty much like the most vital step to
my makeup routine I love a pinched and
snatched nose but I'm not getting that
in today's video she definitely has a
much more like almost like triangular
squared off nose tip whereas mine is
very round and bulbous so although she
doesn't know contour I am gonna try to
add some of those shadows in to make my
nose shape look a little bit more like
hers so I'm going to grab some of that
powder and I'm going to run that along
the bottom edge of my nose okay that's
like it was crazy okay that's like
exactly it though I'm also gonna grab a
little bit of that darker powder and I'm
gonna make two dots like right above my
nostril she has a shadow here in her
nose before I jump into anything else
I'm gonna finish up the base so for
highlighter today I'm gonna grab at the
morphe dimension a stick in the shade
effect one I don't remember what video
ideas is then but I have been using this
so much since then it is such a good a
cream highlighting formula so I'm just
going to I never start drawing this on
and do it definitely likes a lot of
highlight in the center of her forehead
which I've got a respect to it okay and
then for nose highlight once again it's
very square so I'm gonna draw in like a
kind of straight line across the top of
my nose now the one thing that do a does
like use a lot of in her looks is blush
and you guys know I have been obsessed a
blush recently this one is the brand new
Kylie cosmetics blush in the shade of
pink dreams that this color is a
stunning so I'm going to apply this
using my morphe X chocolate Hill @jh o-6
brush and I'm just going to put that
right over top now we get to move on to
the part of the look that I have been
looking forward to since the beginning
of this video and that is do as eyebrows
she has super super bushy unruly brows
which I love so so so much and so my
favorite brow sales to do obviously I
have very very thick brows myself so
this shouldn't be too hard to achieve
but I do want to add at some hairs and
make sure that they are nice and shaped
so I'm first angle and with just a clear
brow gel to brush the hairs upwards it's
so I kind of know like what direction
they're gonna go in for this lift today
I'm gonna grab my Urban Decay a brow
blade in the shade dark drapes because
that this product is actually do ended
and one end has a super super tiny and
sharp brown marker
to do I'll and that I'm not adding in
tiny little lines to make sure the brow
is defined but by doing it this way I'm
getting that bushy look without it being
super super structure that looks so good
20 square face keeps like always
this is everything all right you base
that it's pretty much the brows all
complete I'm not even going to go in and
conceal them because I am a loving
husband look right now and I am going to
go ahead and zoom you and s we can get
started on the eye shadow look so a for
the slope today I'm gonna do something
at green inspired by a dis a photo of do
up from her new music video now I am
personally it not the biggest fan of
green but this green turtleneck happened
to be one of the only colorful pieces
that I own in my closet so we're gonna
make do it with what we got
make so we're gonna make doula but we
got burn scrubbing my palate I'm just
gonna grow up a little bit of the dark
green shade it called Daddy on an AM
before fightsticks brush and I'm gonna
put this in the outer corner just to lay
down a deep green on there
so next I'm gonna grab my it nor veena
palette and my m4 33 brush and dip into
this shade right here d3 and I'm just
gonna lightly buff out that green I'm
not going to take this eyeshadow color
too high just making sure that it's
nicely diffused and now in my inner
corner I'm actually gonna pick up the be
perfect cosmetics X Stacy and Marie
palette and dip into this beautiful and
neon green shade called ecstasy using
another M 4 5 6 I'm gonna pop this
shader right into my inner corner oh
yeah Oh guys associate color oh my gosh
oh my lord I'm also gonna tuck this
color into my lower lash line as well
and then connecting it back up with a
little bit of a dotty and then on the
center of the lid I'm just gonna grab
the morphia prior to collection a
palette and then grab this metallic
green shade which is called activism and
I'm just going to pop this right in the
center of my lid and then lhasa finally
not least I'm just gonna grab a little
bit of the Urban Decay heavy metals
liner this one is in the shade of gold
line and I was gonna put a little bit of
this on the back of my hand
and then I also have the shade
Distortion you mix them together and
then just with my finger I'm gonna apply
a little bit of this right to the center
of my lid there's some nice glitters in
there now it does look like do it has a
slight eyeliner on so I'm gonna grab my
tum pour a liquid liner and just add on
a very very tiny wing never losses today
from looking into his photos that
honestly looks like she doesn't really
do fall see it's kind of like ever it
seems like she just curls in does
mascara which I love unfortunately for
me after years and years of wearing
falsies and ripping them out with glue I
do not have as beautiful ashes as I used
to so I'm just gonna grab a pair of
ardell demi wispies would you like the
tiniest most natural-looking lash ever
but hopefully this will just be a little
bit of dimension back to my eyes all
right you guys and that is one eye off
complete this was soo easy to put
together so I'm gonna go to the other
one off camera quickly and I'll be right
back for the rest of the transformation
all right you guys we're back both eyes
are now done and now we only have a few
steps remaining and before the final
transformation it up for my lips I'm
just going to go ahead and first take a
makeup point and take off this excess
cross and then for lips today I do it
almost always does HS superlight nude
pink look some first kind of land my
lifes using the morphe lip liner in the
shade of backseats love these coat
change for 10% off alright you guys and
that is officially the makeup portion of
this dual Ipoh transformation all
completes but we have one a very vital
stop left and that is going to be at the
wig so I'm going to go ahead and pop
that on hide the tapes and show you guys
the final oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh this is absolutely crazy holy crap
I've gotten the references I've seen
this little molarities but oh my god you
guys I just did a full 180 crazy
thinking about the wait was yes now look
I am literally do Lipa oh my gosh you
guys this transformation it was
absolutely and saying a holy crap like
if you think I care about you no boy I
don't give a Frick I had so much fun
doing this inspiration today I really
hope you guys enjoyed it if you did it
please don't forget to give a big thumbs
up down below and share your love and
support it really means a lot
also please do me a favor and tweet a
screenshot of this video to do leave
herself how iconic gonna be to actually
do a video together talking about music
or career and also turning us into twins
like also leave me comment down below
and let me know if you guys want to see
me do this type of video or
transformation again let me know if
there's any other celebrities you guys
want to see me transform into if you
have not ready don't forget to click
that bigger subscribe button down below
and come to in the sisterhood also if
like that Bell icon so you notification
every time I upload a brand new video
also I have a very very special
announcement for you guys when I biggest
goals for 2020 was finding more ways to
talk to you at one-on-one when I'm not
able to get to hug you in person at me
and greets and I found the perfect way
to do so and that is by texting me I
know that sounds super crazy but texting
is by far the most direct form of
communication and we're all on our
phones all day long so I figured this be
the perfect way to get to chat with you
guys tell you all about new videos new
Instagram photos secret merch launches a
special discount codes and so much more
so if you guys want to send me a text
you can message me at three one zero
nine oh five eight seven four six talk
to you soon
if you like to follow me on my social
media journey all my social medias are
just do a leap up just kidding but
Instagram it tik-tok Facebook and
Twitter or all Justine Charles and my
snapchat form or if I hadn't seen sent
up who seems Ross that extra ass after
this video is sister shout out goes to
sister Nicole thank you so much love for
always falling and supporting you I love
you so so so much and if you would like
to the next
sister shadow don't forget to always
reach me Avenue least legal live on
Twitter and also to know my youtube at
post notifications all right you guys
that's all I have for this video today
and now I'm a doula you all a favor and
Lipa you alone
[Music]