hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel oh my
god you guys I am so beyond excited to
be sitting down in filming today's a
brand new video I think it has been
weeks since they actually filmed oh my
god so many things have been going on I
literally just got off the plane from
London
super super late last night I am so
beyond jet-lagged before I even jump in
first of all I want to say thank you
it's so so so much to all of my UK
London and Birmingham sisters that I met
at the begin greet last weekend it was
actually my first time ever in the UK
which is so crazy I wanted to go for so
long but maganda
I had such an amazing and kind of looks
pretty across the con and getting the
chance to open the first ever more
Feaster in Birmingham it is now
confirmed that over 10,000 sisters
showed up to the mall meet in this
moment biggest meets of all time and
it's Tuesday night I never forget the
pun was unreal and other lots of hemming
home is actually insane the city may or
may not have temporarily shut down for a
few hours
oopsies it was such a world welcomed by
all the Murphy staff members who were
all wearing my palette on the eyes such
beautiful looks and speaking of
beautiful looks I've ever been more shut
by a meet and greet card in my entire
life because so many of the sisters
there had the most beautiful eye makeup
looks I have ever ever seen and they're
all so beyond nice and for the UK media
but regardless it was an incredible
experience that I will truly never
forget and I'm definitely looking
forward to going back very very soon but
we are now home back in LA for his warm
and cozy and it is time to get work done
and that brings us to today's a brand
new video
while I was over in the UK between
London and LA there was an 8 hour time
difference and I usually can pass out
literally just about anywhere but for
some reason I was having really really
bad at sleep issues while I was there so
I found myself strolling through
Instagram a lot and I discovered that
there is a brand new trend going on here
in the beauty community called the Bratz
challenge basically there are super cool
artists out there with Instagram
accounts that are literally dedicated to
taking dolls such as Barbies or Bratz
dolls and giving them full Instagram
body makeovers full hair color changes
stylings really cute outfits and of
course makeup as well and apparently the
beauty community has discovered these
accounts because there's a
really cool trying going on right now
we're makeup artists are literally
becoming Bratz dolls I remember watching
the literal Queen of transformations
promise fan did this a few years ago now
and I've seen so many incredible makeup
artists that I follow on Instagram do
this as well
so definitely go check out their work a
proper credit for this video it goes to
them but since I just got home from
traveling and I'm not gonna text me with
makeup in a very very long time I
thought I'd be so much fun to try out
this challenge for myself to use a whole
lot of makeup my palate a wig and outfit
to turn myself into a Bratz doll
[Music]
all right sisters this is going to be
quite the transformation so I just want
to go ahead and get right into the video
well I was traveling I came across and
stalked so many of these different doll
accounts kind of figure out what's look
I wanted to recreate there were so many
of them and I think it's so cool that
this actually can art form that people
are doing right now somebody even said
one of me that I found out oh my god
shout out to hacks Tianna by that I'm
gonna link his video in the description
box down below
he literally turned a Barbie into my
jock which I thought was so cool but
after going through and finding a bunch
of different ones I came across a
Bisping sure posted by monster lol oh my
god look at her she is literally so
beyond chic we have like a pink acrylic
going on a utility best with chains
super long blonde hair slicked back
fishnets thigh highs that of course a
cute little for a backpack I think this
bra stall is literally like the
sportswear a female version of me and
I'm so excited to become her today I'm
first gonna start by putting a wig cap
on at first all because my hair is
looking at literally disgusting I'm
gonna make my head look like the AG that
broke the answer I'm like record if I
have a kind of a plain base to work on
so the first of the transformation is
going to be to glue down at my eyebrows
obviously I have very thick and dark
bushy brows whereas this bra still has
nice and lifted
thin blonde eyebrows so I'm gonna grab
my Elmer's a washable school glue stick
and just go right in I've done a few
different tutorials on carving my brows
before Oh still they should link them
right up here but I'm just gonna speed
through this and we'll go on to the next
step
[Music]
all right so we've made it to this
lovely stop right here at the browser
laid down and ready to be covered and
normally next I'll go into the
foundation which I definitely it's still
not going to but you guys know I
definitely - laid out a kind of base
first that we're not going to be doing
today because the fact that this eye
look is so interpreted it's gonna be a
lot of like kind of art and fine details
I don't want to laid out a full base and
then God forbid I mess up and have to
wipe it all off so I'm just gonna kind
of focus the foundation in this area and
then kind of build up the rest later
I've never really done this before but
hopefully it works out regardless I'm
gonna use the Krylon TV paint stick in
the shade and be and cover everything
right up there taking morphia beauty
sponge and blend this right now it no no
actually I'll use the fenty beauty
sponge TV that blends it so well no
matter how many times I do drag or I'll
cover this is always so horrifying to me
okay so well my foundation is still I'm
gonna go in with an angled brush and the
anasazi a dip brow pomade in the shade
taupe because obviously you want to do a
blonde brown today I'll do this my
foundation is still wet so just in case
I mess up I can easily fix it before
it's all set with powder so I'm just
gonna go right in and I'm just going to
start sketching at this Brown oh I'm
gonna start the bottom line of the brow
in the same place as I normally would
but we're obviously gonna make this a
lot more arched than normal and I'm
keeping the photo right next to me for
reference and then if I look forward
right about at the edge of my people I'm
gonna start turning that brow kind of a
little bit more down if you guys have
seen my drawing videos before even
honestly like my regular makeup - and
you definitely know that I like to have
my brow tail out really really far and
make this kind of like a super super
straight but in this photo she does have
a little bit of a shorter tail so I'm
definitely try to emulate that as close
as possible and then it's gonna sketch
in the other end of the tail I really
really like using the anasazi at Deborah
for this stuff just because like I said
it is a cream product so if I mess up I
can really easily wipe it away and fix
it but it's also a really really
buildable product so I could either use
a little bit of it and get kind of a
lighter coverage like I'm going to do in
the inner portion or a packet on for
that full coverage kind of Instagram
prowl 2016 James wouldn't really
recommend for that but it is possible if
you want to do that okay so she just
fully hosted very very like straight all
the way through once we have the shape
all outlined I'm gonna grab the shade of
blonde of dipbrow which I definitely
should have used to out what I just
couldn't find it and now I did um and
also the shade Albert as well it kind of
mixed them a little bit together just
because the brown so does definitely
have like strawberry blonde type of hair
and coincidentally so is the week that I
have for later on it so I just so make
sure everything matches its going to
lightly feather that color in there okay
I'm gonna clear this table concealer in
a second but this is looking pretty good
so far so I'm gonna try my best to
mirror this on the other side they are
not even okay let me just conceal this
before I go crazy and then we'll worry
about reshaping okay I don't go to take
shave tape and this is in the shade fair
beige just like a little bit of a
lighter under Brown moment gonna blend
this up using a mac 242 brush now that
that is all looking and really really
good and I definitely do not want to
change out I'm gonna grab some
translucent powder once again in a
powder puff and I'm going to lock this
in place now that the brows are all set
and not going anywhere
thank God we get to move on to the fun
part which is going to be the eyes now
this is obviously going to be a lot so
before I actually go in and put anything
on I do want to go ahead and try to
sketch this out just my face kind of
lightly just we get kind of like a
general idea of where this is gonna go
so I don't look really really stupid
wiping it off later on I'm just gonna
grab a regular Anasazi eyebrow pencil
and I'm going to start doing this okay
so I'm debating if I want to do like the
anime eye where people actually draw in
the pupil on the lower lash line or just
expand the white I probably should draw
on the eye I'm gonna continue my upper
lash line down to right about there just
imagining like the liner and then it's
gonna come to about here like I said I'm
just like lightly sketching this into
definitely does it have to be perfect
I'm obviously going to cover this all up
but I just want to kind of get a rough
idea okay
the winged liner will be will come up to
here okay and then winged liner going up
there we go okay so when later we'll be
like right here yeah okay not bad so far
that I need to put in her like actually
defined crease which looks like it's
about I don't know I shouldn't put the
crease in my actual crease no no no no
no that'll ruin the illusion so I'm
gonna draw the crease higher than my
regular crease but we're gonna actually
like draw a black line in there and make
it look like it's a new crease does that
make sense
that's it that's the shape right there
so this is the shape of one on kind of
all mapped out obviously we're going to
add a shadow and like always I'm gonna
do one eye at a time but just make sure
everything looks kind of symmetrical in
the end I'm gonna go ahead and knock
this one out quickly and then move on to
the eye shadow so give me once again I
think I want to start off with the I set
off first and then do the outlines later
hopefully that doesn't mess me up but
I'm gonna grab of course the James house
X morphe palette and I'm gonna dip into
the shade at boutique and use this and
layer that's all over the lid gonna lay
down some Mac Paint Pot in the shade of
painterly on the lid then bringing this
all the way down to my nose area as well
then is packing on a boutique with an m1
to floor brush this is literally the
perfect color for this look I'm
literally just filling in this entire
area
this is definitely gonna be one of those
looks that looks so wrong until it gets
right you guys have no idea how excited
I was to be doing this challenge today
oh my god I don't look like a [ __ ]
before on my channel but I used to play
it with a black and Barbie dolls
religiously as a little boy I don't they
actually make it anymore but I used to
have this brought styling head thing
that was literally just a gigantic a
broad stalk with like a long hair they
literally just sit there and play with
it and do its hair all day long and
different braids and updos and styles I
remember one time actually drawing on
the Barbie head with pencils too and
getting screamed at by my mom who was so
mad that I mess up her poor face but in
my five-year-old had a house making her
beautiful but I just think it's so funny
that literally brought stalls is how I
actually learned how to do hair and a
later on in life I actually started
doing hair for girls for prom and ball
and then my love for hair send it to me
a love for makeup so like in a really
weird way without Bratz dolls I might
not even be doing this job today
it's so cool helpful circle that is
right now I'm using lob down an m4 3 3
by the way to buff out that edge next
we're going to shade it you're kidding
on an m4 3 3 and just pop this on
just to kind of lighten it up a little
bit I noticed in the original picture
I brought sell definitely had a little
bit more of a light lit compared to her
crease and I forgot to do that so oops
okay so now I want to do her eye liner
I'm gonna grab the next liquid liner in
black and I'm going to use this to start
sketching out keep in mind we obviously
have this gets going too so I'm actually
not gonna start my eyeliner at the
normal place we're gonna pull that from
the outer edge and pull it back and then
we're gonna sketch it in and fill in the
lines he's gonna look really stupid at
first but just have patience this
eyeliner line needs to come down here so
now I have to draw like the little D
like crease oh god here we go okay so
this is going like here this is so hard
holy crap
now for the bottom I'm gonna start by
grabbing the Jeffrey's our liquid
lipstick in the shade a drug lord this
is a really great white kind of product
we're gonna use and I'm gonna just
basically fill my eyeball and looking
good so far and I'm also gonna put this
in my waterline as well this is so
creepy looking oh okay I'm just gonna
have a little bit of a flashback from of
course DJ halls palette I'm just the
flat packing brush and set that right in
place now I'm gonna grab the black liner
once again we're gonna outline the
bottom of the eye
who's gonna follow that eyeliner oh my
god okay it's starting to come together
great okay I'm gonna add more cranberry
on eyeshadow and lashes of course later
on but I'm going to do that after the
base um so now I think I have to draw in
the eyeball okay so this is where things
get tricky so now we have to do like the
whole illusion part which is basically
making my eyes look like they are huge
we're already running into one issue of
this is that when you do this you're
supposed to wear a circle lenses which
are basically just really really large
contacts I can't wear those because they
wasn't actually able to find any that
come in prescription and a lot of
prescription I can't see anything so
this Barbie would have looked botched um
therefore we're just gonna have to make
it work I'm going to Photoshop the
picture that I post on Instagram heads
up as if I don't Photoshop every other
picture anyway we're gonna have to do
your best to visualize it but regardless
we're drawing on another eyeball to make
it look like my eyes are bigger when I
do this I'm going to look forward I also
have very long lower eyelashes which is
going to make this illusion even more
difficult because they're going to get
in the way I have to paint them as well
so
lord help me great house looks good now
I'm going to fill this in with a white
brown color to match my contacts gonna
grab an Emma 2:30 brush and dip into the
chain to punch me in the palate then I'm
gonna have a little bit of tea and use
this to shade the what is this this is
the iris the iris okay now I have to
draw in the new people okay
now I just need a white dot alright and
finally last up I'm just gonna grab a
tiny little pencil brush this is the e30
7 and the tiniest tiniest tiniest
tiniest little bit of spooky and used on
the back of my hand just rub on any
excess and then use this too lightly
shade all right sisters so I know this
absolutely looks crazy right now
but this is pretty much the illusion all
complete all we have left is like the
lashes and the lower lash line but I
don't want to do this until later on
once I have my face and foundation
already on so I'm just gonna crack for a
second or probably rather a good hour or
so and try my absolute best to mirror
this eye over to this side I feel like
symmetry is very very important when it
comes to Bratz dolls and really just
recreating all dolls so wish me luck and
I'll be right back oh my god you guys
look at this
we're still missing the watch then the
lower lashline shadow but it's
definitely trying to come together oh my
god I'm so excited
I just never honestly like pulling this
off at least kind of so now just going
to do the rest of everything else so I'm
gonna grab my krylon TV paint stick once
again and now we're just gonna lay down
the kind of base all over and I saved
this for later just because obviously we
have a new set of eyes now so I had to
kind of put that around back okay and I
was gonna buff this in once again this
is so this is also kind of scary low-key
oh my god okay so now we're gonna grab
once again of the white that we use to
highlight
earlier and I'm gonna use this to add in
some highlights to the face I'm gonna
keep this very centered in like the
middle of the face I'm just having my
face exactly like normal except just a
little bit lower underneath
eyes right up along that lash line this
is so crazy now I'm going to upon this
out okay I set this now more powder this
I keep looking in the monitor and
getting shocked this is so crazy
oh my gosh now that the face is all set
we were looking a little bit flat and I
want to add in some dimension now
looking at this photo the brazo doesn't
really have that much contour or
highlight going on it's mostly just a
little bit of a blush but that is
because it is a doll with a perfect face
shape um I don't really have that so
therefore I'm going to contour a little
bit more to kind of round everything out
but I'm gonna try to keep it a little
bit more subtle then we'll see how that
actually works just cover my Anasazi out
contour kit gonna kind of hit this a
little bit more rounded than normal kind
of pulling this in a little bit lower
still going to contour my jawline so it
looks like I got liposuction for a real
one
just because Bratz dolls definitely do
have a very very distinctive facial
shape and I'm just going to try to round
out my forehead as much as possible
same thing with the nose contour
definitely not a lot going on but then
again doll nose is definitely nowhere
near this baby right here so we're gonna
try our best to contour definitely try
to emphasize like the ball on the end of
the nose I want to make the sides look
really tiny so I'm gonna put this the
lines here and then blend them up into
the eyeshadow okay so this is probably
like the best we're gonna get the nose
contour I already work miracles with my
regular boy and makeup doing a whole lot
of nose country and a whole lot of face
tuned there's no saving this so we're
just gonna have to go with it and hope
for the best but next is blush so I'm
gonna grab the Kylie blush in the shade
of pink
power this one is so cute from her new
collection and the morphe of 4 brush I
normally don't go over like more pinky
tone blushes you guys know I love a good
quarrel on that but I think this is
going to match the look so well open it
does and we thought this is so pretty
and once again being very very rounded
with this shape kind of pulling it down
and inwards now that I had that all in
place I'm gonna go ahead and bake my
face like normal but instead of my
irregular powder I'm going to use the
been night super white powder now this
stuff is very very intense but we
definitely are going for a very high
contrast type of look today so I'm just
going to grab once again at my same at
Beauty wonderin tip it right in
I'm gonna press that powder right up
against the sides of this nose and this
might help a little bit with the contour
illusion well we know we're crossing our
fingers and well that's it sir let's go
ahead and work on the lower lash line
I'm gonna grab a tiny little buffing
brush and dipping into a boutique just
like before we're going to go in and
we're going to blend that right along
the lower edge of the liner and I'm
gonna keep this very very tight to that
line as well because the Brachfeld
definitely does not blend hers down very
far I'm gonna use an even tiny little
buffing brush dip into the littlest bit
of spooky and use that to blend together
deep black liner and boutique then it's
never gonna have about four or five six
my tiny little custom blending brush and
dipping into a little bit of love that
it's going to blend out that outer edge
I'm just realizing now too for the
crease that I put in I just drew a line
but in a real eye crease obviously
there's like a tiny little bit of shadow
can't leave out any details we want this
look as realistic as possible I'm just
gonna go into a 506 person took it to a
little bit more spooky time off the
excess because I want this to be a very
very tiny detail but I'm just gonna go
over that crease line and just blend
very very lightly as if there is a
shadow because I'm a fold further laughs
I'm gonna glue on my lash it to the top
in a quick second but for the bronze
bottom lashes she actually has it three
tiny little spikes so I'm gonna draw
those in using a liquid eyeliner this
one is from a Tom Ford that looks so bad
I'm not really sure what I can do about
that okay if I clean up with consider it
right now without this is so hard
oh no okay that's better than nothing
now to make them even on the other side
oh I didn't know where I want to put the
lashes on my actual eyelids because I'm
not really gonna use a good at 3:01
these are from the crime shop I love
them they're super super just like big
these are what I usually use for drawing
because of the fact we put the white
here and the eyeliner starts here
technically the outer edge of my eyelash
should be like here which is where I
should glue the lash but I feel like
this wrong side because if I feel like
my eyeliner is there it just like will
look really
what the hot why does it look at that
okay so to fix that last night it took a
little bit of hairspray this is the got
to be glue that I always used to really
lock my normal hair in place I just
sprayed out the lash and then pinch them
together
look a little bit more like spidery doll
like hopefully this will look a little
bit better
I don't really know so we're gonna
figure out together I also don't really
know where I'm gonna put this lash kind
of put the inner corner that looks good
well that worked way better than
anticipated oh my god well I'm so sated
okay great oh these look like freakin a
smile from em first
alright you guys this is Lily look at
you so good and also so creepy at the
same time I've ready to move on to the
next step those of the eyes literally
all complete like I said the lashes
definitely pulled it all together oh I
can't believe I actually pulled this off
oh my god okay I'm gonna go ahead and
wipe off this baby it's been sitting
because it's been really sitting there
for quite a while now and I don't want
to get crusted for Holly we're gonna
keep it relatively subtle and going with
a little bit of a face for my palate
actually really use regular Einstein
once again keeping that very rounded
shape going here gonna bring a little
bit of that down the nose as well as
always also it might distract a little
bit for everything else going on sounds
good oh nice then all we get to do the
fun part which is of course going to be
the ellipse at the last and final stop
this is going to be a really good and
fresh because we get to over line the
crap out of them I'm gonna try my best
model of this video so their lips come
up my mouth is very very very wide and
large if you haven't noticed over the
course last few years quite a lot comes
out of it both good and bad but a big
mouth is a problem when you have a tiny
little Barbie mouth away the very large
lip so I'm just gonna have to pose like
[Music]
now I'm going to use the jeffree star
cosmetics liquid lipstick in the shade
of a birthday suit to fill this end and
then grabbing a little bit of it drug
lord and then just like I did with that
tiny little white line and the pupil of
the eye I'm just gonna use the same
exact method to add on little highlights
to literally six hours later I think
that is the makeup portion of this look
all complete I'm obsessed with how this
turned out I was so scared at first I
did not know if this was going to turn
out even remotely okay this is probably
one of the hardest looks I've ever done
but I am so credibly proud of this but
but look it's not over yet because we
still have a lot of transforming left
still to do as you can tell so I'm gonna
go off camera quickly put on my wigs at
some clips in my outfit and I'll be
right back to show you the finished
transformation
[Music]
it's so good do you like it yeah oh so
we have pretty much everything for the
transformation laid out right here and
I'm gonna get dressed right now we have
of course Maya pads from a jar public
you guys a member of the transformation
video and I'll see you guys are guys
final or I'll put you back my best
friends explosive video boutique and
amazing believe is this out here and at
Whittier California shameless little
plugs my best friend she was down in LA
this morning shopping for some for her
website and I sent her the photo and I
was like girl I need your help
we need to recreate this look and she
literally could not have done any better
feel the same big oversized little
crewneck from the photo we also have
fishnet stockings we have and we also
have these boots that are like of course
we have over there because so she
brought offers everything have a utility
very - that aren't these with most
products shoes you've ever seen him so
good
[Music]
did we kill the challenge or a day that
we kill this challenge I feel like brat
cells everywhere are shaking I'm
actually doing just fine this is scary
how good this looks
oh my god you guys I am so proud of how
this finished look turned out holy crap
going into this video today I was really
really nervous not gonna lie obviously I
do like creative artistic makeup looks
all the time but I've never actually
tried to turn my face into another face
of four and realistic transformations is
definitely something that I do not have
any experience with but that being said
I was so excited because Bronson Barbies
were a major part of my childhood in the
making of a gay icon I mean I literally
learned how to braid on an actual brass
styling head and I used to do their
makeup all the time and that love for
creativity and making people feel
beautiful and confident is exactly what
stemmed into this job today if you guys
enjoyed this crazy transformation today
and think I did a good job please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below into your sisters love and support
it really means so so so much to me also
if you have not already don't forget to
click that big red subscribe button down
below and come join this sisterhood for
more fun and makeup tutorials just like
this and it's pretty good infraction not
gonna lie we are almost to 14 million
sisters that I'd love to have you join
the family and also click that Bell icon
so you can get over using every time I
upload a brand new video if you like to
follow me on my makeup journey can
follow me on Instagram Twitter there
both to change her awesome I snapchat
some more behind the scenes iteself is
James Charles of the duck stressed after
Charles this video is sister shout out
goes the sister Tita thank you so much
love for always falling and supporting
you I love you literally so so so much
and if you at home between those videos
sister shadow don't forget to always
retrieve it'll easily go live on Twitter
and also turn on my post notifications
here on YouTube all right sisters thank
you so much for watching this video
today I love you so much and I will see
you
[Music]