hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel as
you guys can see today I'm joined with a
very very special guest
professional cosmetics competition judge
yes you turn this about you or I am
literally so excited to finally have you
here this club I feel like is bad I
think we have discussed for like years
now a long word so those of you guys who
may not know we're about to find out
Trixie is literally in my opinion
probably the best drag queen in the
entire world
Routledge a great seasons have been a
winner of all-stars season 3 and also
now professional guest judge a yes
piranha and CEO of checks to Cosmetics
[Music]
its influence are airing every single
Friday right here streaming for free on
my channel every Tuesday I'm uploading a
fun video that somehow ties back to the
last episode and if you guys saw it
which if you've not make sure you click
right up here because there will be no
alerts in today's video we challenged a
contestants to do their ultimate drive
at transformation doing drag is not easy
and do direct for the first time at a
competition I mean that is not no those
people were struggling but a lot of them
really did it turn it out so for today's
video
I thought it'd be really fun at 4 tricks
tonight to sit down together and do our
ultimate Drive transformations I know
that there's probably people that are
like matha that you're not transforming
me but I feel like you've done so many
trips to transformations at this point
yeah only I'm not my makeup on other
people we all look exactly the same
that's great it's such a signature like
damn thing every time so that'll be it
much more fun to just get ready together
in drag do our own ultimate drug
transformations talk all about to try
grace the different shows you've worked
on it into influencer behind the scenes
t from the show and so much more so if
you guys want to see us go from this to
this and then we're exactly the same
keep on hunting
[Music]
you clean your brows down yeah I don't
know this you didn't have to snap so
hard pop off why did you say that what
is that problem I'm just very young and
I like I like I say a lot of young
things I will say when I got to judge
innocent but it when I got to judge on
instant influencer it was exciting but I
had to judge after Paris Hilton so it
was a little bit like oh you know Paris
Hilton was just here she is so yeah but
your check secret oh yeah but I was so
jealous she was there the day before me
like oh okay to be honest I literally
love Paris but do you were honestly
probably the guest judge that I was most
excited about
I got the opportunity to work with
because I wrote Alice I have met before
and I've gotten to work with before you
were like kind of the one person that I
have like loved and respected and looked
up to for so long I'd like Deanne back
and forth like a few times and stuff but
never really got the opportunity to
actually like murk on a project together
building was so much fun for me but I'd
be completely lying if I said that like
being on set wasn't also really
stressful because it was like 14-hour
days for me so you yeah being on set
made me smile so hard and made me laugh
the entire time and like made Ian
experience so enjoyable so she does her
own makeup who you oh I don't know if
people know that you put your own makeup
on the show yeah always who why to be
judging a makeup competition if I can't
even do my own makeup T there we go and
also I was so excited to do it because
I'm not like a TV watcher I'm a like
digital media consumer I'm upset I mean
everything I love is from YouTube so
especially since it was a youtube
original I was like this is my HBO time
young I am only 30 but I know that in
this room that means 50 okay I normally
don't even do this I just want to feel
included I want to talk about the first
time that we met it was at the movie
premiere for than 9
[Applause]
[Music]
like I said I was literally like the
biggest fan of you I like sat down and
like heard you talking behind me does it
I was so scared to even look back
because I let me thought that you hated
me well I didn't help that I got really
close to here and said well it was
because of the fandom drama that had
started because oh right the show what
that mean my little brother had on
YouTube yeah also I mean listen I didn't
invent editing I didn't invent two
people sitting on a chair talking if
some drama that may or may not be real
gives you something fun to discuss over
a roll of Froot Loops I'm happy for you
I don't need to talk to the president of
being canceled but I would love to be
just canceled me mom I'm so scared of
the color that I chose to put on myself
yeah what okay I know doesn't look that
breezy I got really burn in the Sun I'm
gonna listen it's okay to go darker here
when you go lighter here right we're
gonna later that's all right don't worry
with the show thing like literally it
was so crazy to you that that started
such a like war in between my fans and
yours because literally like people knew
that I was the biggest fan of you and
like we talked about it and the episode
be like yeah this is inspired by oh this
is so crazy
didn't Chris edit it yes okay the guy
who edited that was originally an editor
on on so like we hired at the original
artists which I definitely think a
support like we had people that were
offering to like try to replicate it but
I was like you know if we're gonna do
this sound inspired by that I'm like I
want to pay the original person who like
did it you know yeah by the way speaking
of inspiring you know confident I get to
use this every single day oh god do you
really yes because what's like a DM
getting a drag usually and she is not
that like her relationship with makeup
is completely utility based if you can
get ready fast and easy she likes it
okay I have a fun question for you I
love fun after being on drag race season
7 and then winning all stars 3 I know
that you said you never wanted to
compete in like again yeah now that
you've also judged into influencer do
you like competing or judging better
Chachi
oh my controversial opinion
plugs on you because you don't like the
judges they do nothing they do not lies
they're lit well and they're giving
their opinion of others but competing is
so anxiety-ridden yeah I am such a
competitive person that like you are yes
would you ever do a competition yes what
would you do my issue is like like
Amazing Race I want to do so bad it is
something about yelling for loud boy
sticks ayah text you that I wanted you
to be a guest on the show uh-huh
and I was so excited that you wanted to
do it I want to know what were your
expectations of an influencer before
you've out there oh this is really good
question what were you thinking after
you finished and now what do you think
now that you've seen the episode it was
filmed at the YouTube original space
look at the YouTube space which is like
a whole day Airport hangar right yeah so
it's huge she was really really
high-quality like he said your story is
not interesting I love that you've been
sadly one of the only Queens to really
embrace YouTube for a contest I mean
especially like with um I owe everything
to that show right and everything to the
fact that people watch my show on the
Internet so like especially when I
started producing more Beauty content
but kind of like making it which by the
way my channel is just Trixie Mattel as
well it's like how can we marry Beauty
content but make it really comedy
content you know what I mean yeah I mean
even my channels like it's makeup at the
end of a but like it's so much more
idiocy I'm so horrified how my face is
looking right now I'm looking incredible
you really are your favorite drug means
you don't have to say me but it would be
love honestly you like that's being done
UN but aside from you Bianca Del Rio
it's like hilarious the funniest person
ever like it's so clear how hard she
works I mean honestly this season has
been in my opinion one of the best
seasons of Darger's ever really are you
living I really like it I also love GG
this season you guys think you look like
yes like I've gotten so many people that
are really oh you look like this person
you look like this person and it's never
accurate I truly do see it with GG
especially when I've been trying
well this eyebrow actually looks
sickening but I can't I'm not gonna get
the other one to map what are you using
like a Dipper no just a powder
she gives you this look what do you do
[Music]
you look even in the monitor of a girl
you can't go by me I don't know what I'm
doing you can always go in and clean it
with my life same that's it
bye thanks for watching does my look is
actually how was kind of a throwback we
saw each other outside of drag Con two
years ago and me and kimchi were like
sitting on a sock no wig on my krottas
and then you came around the corner in
that white gown how was your drag calm
it was so fun it's look if you guys
never been a drag Con it really is
Disneyland I mean it's crazy
it was so fun I had the best experience
cuz like I had done transformations I
have done the makeup I've done the wigs
and stuff but like I have never been
like how to coerce it before that I had
never like actually the house like a
full you know the full moment but I also
got to meet so many queens that I have
been looking up to forever I'm either
meeting people or I'm doing the press so
I'm like just go on right if you want to
meet Trixie you have to cut through a
line of 100 teenage girls and they will
kill you mmm don't get me started on
cutting the lines at our club you know
people heard people still to this day
bring that up about me still would you
like to clear the air yes I would love
to clear the air so two years ago I got
invited to go to Drakon and I was
supposed to do a meet and greet this is
what I held like a million followers I
think and I woke up that morning feeling
like really nauseous just like it was
not a good day to wake up with 6:00 in
the morning to get into full drag to
then go in and for five people so later
on that day like right when it's about
to end I notified like the team that I
was working with and I was like hey I
would really still love to go and just
pop in like how I still go oh my gosh
yes of course like we'd love to have you
and I got there and started getting mom
like it was like crazy so as soon as I
got there they gave me a full security
team to walk me around I wanted to see a
few different drag queens itself and the
security team that was with me brought
me to the front of the lines so I could
meet the Queen's get a photo and get out
and listen I get it like even I like
don't like honey Lyons but the reality
is you have to be saved but you have to
be smart so they wanted to get me in and
get me out because the DA is gonna start
a problem like that it's when kids start
lining up or asking for photos or
crowding and then that's when the people
in line get angry that some people get
hurt some people get trampled and it was
never
attention to her anybody or to make
anybody feel lost data but still doesn't
say that scandal follows me around the
drug community I've heard that before
too so they are three years later I
still do not think that I'm superior to
anybody I don't think time superior to
drive me literally to seeing it to get
and James Charles at drag con punched a
teenager confirmed oh I mean that 40 on
say is quaking you know what the t of
quarantine is too cocky now because I've
been doing the YouTube videos and then
filming with Katya it is really an odd
feeling to get in drag and not leave
your house really yesterday I was like I
had to film during the day and then I
had a stream at night sick sitting and
full drag at my kitchen dining room
table eating a salad like a normal
person like it was weird to be in drag I
felt like I said oh my god I love the
sounds I used to play it for hours as I
can that's amazing okay
it's blush time it's lunch time I have
one for you Oh a new one
yeah brand new wonder famous yes blossom
Rothwell palette I already had this in
my closet that I texted checks to
earlier saying that I wanted you to
bring your makeup I'm taking the shade a
side check first which is the bright
vibrant pink and I'm getting into this
after-school special I love a
highlighter that is like clear but
shines paint purple look at that you
weren't over the first drag queen to
start your own makeup line yes I haven't
even talked about that yet how has it
been writing Trixie cosmetics and like
what is it like to have that type of
representation in the cosmetics industry
if you've ever supported independent
makeup company now that I've seen what
it's like to make makeup I can't tell
you how important that is yes when
you're supporting a huge company you
don't know but like when it's a small
company you're just giving them a little
pat on the back saying like please keep
doing it yeah I love Pro formulas you
know I love makeup forever America
Smashbox whatever and I love super fun
packaging yeah is there a way we can
have like pro formula and like packaging
from Claire's
if you don't I mean like yes oh that
looks great
oh my god that just don't that's a
literal arachnid I know I have one
see before we finish off our looks so I
said throughout this video that you are
by far my favorite drag queens I know
you've said before that Tammy Brown is
your favorite of course how do you feel
as a drawing artist that you and have
like inspired so many young kids to get
into the art of drag and like what
advice would you give to future Queens
I've been doing drag 12 years I'm at the
point where people who are now 18 or
whatever I'm their first reference now
like that's what ya do it especially
with kotti I'm like ah because people
like comedy or they like country music
I'm what gets them into drag it's really
cool because when I try to draw
parallels in my own life I'm like oh my
god what if I'm I love Lady Bunny what
if I'm someone's Lady Bunny you know
like that's oh it's just cool definitely
one of the ones that caught me in spirit
oh really yeah
I told I'm yeah I'll write you guys well
about 80 pounds of makeup and several
hours of good conversation later these
are our books all complete but we
obviously have a little bit left of this
transformation that left to go so we're
gonna get changed
put on some hair and we'll be back with
more woman
[Music]
you look sick and I mean everything
you look like you would be in line at
DragonCon and yes and you would cry when
you got up there yes and then I would
cut the line
yeah oh my gosh you guys well I really
really hope that you enjoyed it these
ultimate drive transformations of course
inspired by episode 2 of insta
influencer if you guys have not given
the episode of watch go click right up
here
I am so proud of the series thing hope
you guys are enjoying it and you guys
are not gonna want to miss out on this
Friday's episode coming soon as always
streaming right here on my youtube
channel for free at 12 p.m. at PST
repair baby haha
Trixie thank you so much for coming on
my tail and thank you for gasps judging
the episode as well it was such a
pleasure to finally get to work together
look at those two women hug anytime you
want me to show up and judge you met at
your house you want me to come by and
judge you I'll do it please if you guys
have not yet follow Trixie dosha career
Trixie Mattel also shop Trixie cosmetics
as well if you guys enjoyed today's
ultra Drive transformation please don't
forget to give it a big thumbs up down
below and show your love and support it
really does help us out so so so much
and if you've not ready make sure you
click that big red subscribe button down
below and conjoint at this sisterhood
we're 18 million sister strong and I
love to have you join the family
it also slipped that battle icon so do
you know houston every time I upload a
brand new video if you like to follow me
on my makeup turn you can follow me on
Instagram Twitter check out the Facebook
elder scrolls my snapchat for behind the
scenes in chiapas James Charles the next
Russell for Charles it if you want to
text me on my personal phone number for
all exclusive updates on videos emerge
and so much more my phone number is 300
at nine oh five eight seven for sex this
video sister shadow goes to Mari thank
you so much love for always falling in
supporting I love you so so so much and
if you like to the next videos sister
shadow don't forget to always reach me
little eggle I'm on Twitter and also to
know my you see my post-op vacations and
don't forget to follow me joe-joe see
wha all right you guys that is all we
have for today's ultimate drive
transformation thank you so much for
watching I'll see you on Friday for an
influencer bye
[Music]