I let those thieves in I was so nearly
stop stop stop
[Music]
hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel so
[Music]
I've been so busy lately doing so many
different shoots and so many different
projects that I have barely had any time
to get a creative look done so today I
really wanted to sit down and throw
something together that was cool and
conceptual it is the fish library which
means this month is Valentine's Day I'm
not excited it was my least here at
Holiday because I've been single for it
for 17 years now and let's be real it's
gonna be 18 in just a few days since
unfortunately I will not be sharing this
special day with anybody special and
I'll be staying at home I thought I
would do a more non wearable look so
today I created this super fun glittery
pink inspired
Valentine's Day look with hearts that's
cute I don't know what else to say if
you guys like to see how I created this
look just make sure you keep on watching
to begin today I'm gonna prime my face
using my benefit Porefessional primer as
always if by some miracle we do end up
getting a Valentine's Day kiss we're
gonna get a whole lot of sweaty and a
whole lot of excited the last thing you
want to do is sweat our makeup off the
foundation today I'm going to use my
Holy Grail my Make Up For Ever Ultra HD
foundation stick in the shade of y 315 a
few guys commented on my last video
asking my it and pre prime my nose like
usual and it is still my favorite trick
but I lost my Mac concealer that is used
for it and I've been way too lazy to buy
any one so yeah as always I'm gonna use
my guitar shaped Eva concealer to
conceal and highlight my face
I'm speeding to the basepart today
pretty fast you guys that see me do this
the same exact routine literally 50
million times y'all know I don't really
like to switch up my products and this
eye look is super intricate so I want to
make sure all the focus is teaching you
guys how to achieve this valentine's day
look bronzed and consorts at Anthony's
eye fair a combination the Kat Von D
shade and light palette the morphe are 7
brush and the M for 35 and then I'm just
gonna bake my face quickly using my at
Cody or some powder and a powder puff oh
well my face is baking in the oven at
350 degrees I'm gonna leave this on for
about 5 to 10 minutes and while that
bakes I would normally go ahead and do
my brows but today I want to show you
guys this game that I've been loving
lately I've been absolutely addicted to
playing best fiends lately I'm sure you
guys have heard of it because a ton of
youtubers have talked about it so a
major shout outs bestie and source on
sharing this video
when they originally reached out I was
like mmm no thank you and then I
actually download the app and started
playing and then I was like oh you know
what yes thank you
this is so fun and not even gonna lie
I've been playing it non-stop best
fiends is a free adventure puzzle game
where you connect objects of the same
color to it defeat the slugs you guys
follow me on snapchat you hear me talk
all the time about like escape rooms and
like wanting to escape from prison one
day and all this weird type of stuff I
know I'm weird but I like thinking and
using strategy so this game is literally
it's so much fun for me since it is
February and this is a Valentine's Day
tutorial I thought this would be perfect
to mention this entire month up until
February 26 there will be a Valentine's
Day themes that characters and all types
of puzzles that you can solve and
there's gonna be a special price on
Valentine's Day as well so make sure you
play it then I'm currently on at level
34 but I just sorted playing a few days
ago so I think I'm doing it pretty well
so far
and if you want to check it out the link
will be in the description below to
download for free like I said I've
literally been playing non-stop so let's
see if you guys can beat my level
comment down below how far you are and
good luck sisters I may have got a
little bit distracted but at least I
beat the level but now that the bag is
all done I'm gonna go ahead and just
wipe it off so we can move on with the
rest of the face just hurt my brows
today I'm gonna use my benefit
processing my brow pencil in the shade
at number 6
I've been doing my brows a lot more like
light and fluffy lately with the pencil
as opposed to my usual Anasazi at depo
and honestly I'm kind of like loving it
so maybe we're saying goodbye to the
James Charles brick of an eyebrow
r.i.p she will maybe be mixed with this
new style of brow that I've been loving
lately as I said I like to kind of fill
them in as least as possible and just
shape them and then I'll use the gel to
kind of brush the hair upwards and then
fill in any gaps that I have just to
make them look really really light
fluffy and like natural and then just
setting my eyelid in place using my
morphe e45 brush and some more
heart-shaped tape concealer and then
just going over with my translucent
powder so show off my eyes today I'm
going to be using my very very damaged
violet balls holy Vera shadow palette
I'm first gonna start off with my m4 4-1
dipping into a wine and dine and putting
that in my crease as a transition color
I'm just putting this in my crease and
circular motions and when I get to the
outer corner I'm also going to pull this
eyeshadow out and up in it like a
outward V wingy shape next I'm going to
grab an m4 33 on the same shade wine and
dine and deepen up my crease and outer V
I'm also dragging whatever the excess
product is on this brush into the lower
lash line because we're going to have a
lot of stuff going on down here and then
taking that m4 / one with no product on
it and just blending out those edges
I'm Mexican to grab the shade a teddy
bear on the same brush and deepen up
that outer corner
[Music]
Oxana take my 35 B and Miami 5/6 to it
dip that into that black shade just to
define the very very outer part I'm
gonna be super gentle and light with
this to be careful that it doesn't get
too dark and messy
this look is taking a whole lot of
blending and for some reason my eye
shadow is not being a cooperative today
I mean are we really surprised will
there ever be a video with James Charles
where something doesn't go wrong
honestly it probably not clearly it's
not this one
to do a half cut crease today I'm going
to use my m17 0-0 and this oil pink
shade on my lid
I forgot my glitter glue at home classic
James so I just use my eyelash glue and
some craft store glitter both things
that are typically not safe and just did
this half cut crease I would not
recommend that strategy I would
definitely recommend using regular glue
and cosmetics great glitter but when
you're me sometimes things don't always
work out for the lower lash line I'm
going back in with my m4 for one and the
same shade wine and dine from the violet
Voss palette and I'm going to start to
blow out that bottom shadow I'm also
making sure to connect that pink up to
the upper lash line EXA going to grab
teddy bear on the m4 3/3 and deepen up
that outer corner
and then with a 562 and the black from
the 35 B I'm going to just hug the
lashline
for the lower lash that I'm going to be
gluing on all sorts of different styles
of glitter I'm going to use this really
pink fine glitter [ __ ] litter that's a
little bit more chunky and then these
pink heart sequins
oh my god this is pretty I just wanna
have in line my upper and lower
waterline using my NYX jumbo eye pencil
in black bean to make the lashes blend
together then I'm just going to go to
Miami 213 in the black shape from the 35
B just make sure there's no skin showing
between the waterline and the lash line
alright guys and that is when I all
complete of course obviously at minus
the lashes I'm gonna do that the one
off-camera quickly to save some time
then we can finish up with the rest of
the face all right there we go that is
the finished eye look upper lashes today
I'm gonna pop on D Lily lashes in the
style of Janice okay so I just filmed a
video with Tana mojo and I found out
that apparently I'm like the only person
in human history that puts on mascara
then lashes so today I just did lashes
then I'm gonna put on mascara to blend
them together and that was the easiest
and eyelash has ever gone on to my eye
and now I'm very very angry that I did
not know this sooner even out of times
that I've been putting on a lash in the
lid I spent like 20 minutes sitting
there gluing it down a million times oh
wow I feel betrayed I feel lighter I
feel left out like I read all of my
comments and literally not a single one
of you who has ever commented saying Oh
James you should try to put on your
eyelash first and then do most secure
off her because it'll make your life a
million times easier instead of spending
17 years bring them on for once your
sisters have let me diamond life
highlighter today I'm gonna start off
with my Anasazi moonchild palette and
the shade pink heart using my morphe and
501 remember you can use code James for
10% off all morphe products and then I'm
gonna layer over top using my star
crushed minerals highlighter in the
shade rosy feature and you can use coda
James for 50% off all their products I'm
also gonna use the same highlighter to
highlight the tip of my nose for lips
today I could be using the open liquid
lipstick in the shade of the Kuna Beach
never mind okay I take it back okay
let's try this again I'm gonna use the
morphe liquid lipstick in the shade
now
I don't like this one either well last
time I'm gonna use Santa Anna from Oprah
hopefully this color will be yet
honestly whatever at this point I give
up I still hate this lip so I'm gonna
layer the shade Angeles on top at this
point I don't know where we're going
with this honestly just like giving up
but I think this is the best we're
probably gonna get today we're done I
just put on those two liquid lipsticks
then I added at the highlighter on top
from star-crossed minerals and a little
bit of glitter
nobody's gonna wear this look anyways
somewhere just go all out and be extra
and I'm gonna set this in place with my
all better settings right because after
all this I do not want this to come off
I think Urban Decay is sending a message
that they want this to come off because
I just ran out of a setting spray oh
alright guys and this is the completed
Valentine's Day glam I really really
hope you enjoyed this video I'll see you
guys before Valentine's Day with the
next video but I wish you the best of
luck of fighting somebody for the day
because lord knows I will not have
anybody if you guys did enjoy this video
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and subscribe if you have not
already I post videos every single week
and I would love to have you join the
family okay this sisterhood if you'd
like to follow me on my makeup journey
you can follow my instagram and twitter
they're both just James Charles and my
snapchat for more behind-the-scenes ice
up is James Charles the next your ass
after Charles alright guys thank you so
much for watching much love and see you
next time bye
[Music]