hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my youtube channel first
today's YouTube video we were doing
something so much fun that I'm actually
really really pumped for him right now
going around there's a huge trend where
people are having their dogs and their
cats pick their makeup I believe that
Jake kiss was the first ones to do this
when she had her dog pick her makeup
I know nikkietutorials did a video I
know a few people had their cats picked
her makeup and yes all these videos are
insanely cute and so much fun to watch I
really couldn't help but think boring
here on the sisters dreams travel to
YouTube channel we like to take things
just one step further
you guys I'm literally so excited for
today's video you guys know we always
like to make things very very extra on
this YouTube channel and today's video
is literally the definition of extra we
are awake so early right now and is
currently 7:30 in the morning here in
California and for today's video we
partnered with the LA Zoo and I'm gonna
be having some my favorite zoo animals
pick my makeup now this is gonna be so
much fun
the zoo is actually gonna be taking us
around today on a private tour which is
so so exciting so be able to give you
guys kind of the inside scoop give you
guys lots of information and all the
animals I have a ton of makeup here with
me today for all the animals to pick
through and as well all the makeup
products were using in today's video are
cruelty free of course in honor of at
the zoo and we have a lot of animals to
me and say hi to today so let's get
started alright sisters I am so excited
to get started and the first step of our
routine today of course is going to be
our foundation alright sister so the
first animal we are here today with are
the flamingos that I'm so excited
because they're all so cute and tiny and
perched on their one leg so for today
they'll be choosing between the Too
Faced Born This Way and the LA girl Pro
matte I really like both of these
foundations so gonna be a good choice
regardless there are some riskier
choices later on in the video I promise
come on come here
they all have Harry Potter names so
hotter hello I have food okay Caitie
girls what noise do flamingos like I
have food someone comes to act they want
to come join the party come on guys it's
fun over here oh no I'm see we're having
your dog or cat cheese is easier come
here come here
yes come here no there are a lot lighter
in color than I thought flamingos would
be I'm gonna be one with the flamingos
so may be able to trust me more
hello do you trust me now come on oh yes
queen of bribing let's go come on guys
two-faced or la girl I know this is a
life-changing decision for you you have
got to be kidding me
to face pulling this layer I'll a girl
chrome axe make it a song hello
you seem like you're a good candidate to
choose I feel like this one definitely
knows playing okay good that's a chicken
hello
Dobby the house-elf is so soft without
they're so tall and skinny like me the
skinniest Legends which one do you like
better let's take a poll can you twos
hello oh wow hello thank you okay touch
it out they all voted for to pay for in
this place oh it looks like my holy girl
is a winner
good taste thank you alright so picking
this one was definitely a little bit of
a task and that is for sure the full
mangoes were definitely not wanting to
play it's okay it was very early in the
morning I don't blame them I really had
to be one with the flamingos in order to
get them to recognize me to trust me to
appreciate me and to help me actually
choose the foundation and luckily Potter
though the lingo was nice enough in the
end and he ended up choosing the Too
Faced Born This Way Foundation that you
guys know this is my all-time favorites
so Potter definitely has good taste
and I was gonna go ahead and apply this
and his recommendation you guys meeting
these flamingos was literally so much
fun and such a good first step of this
video they were all so funny and
everything one of them was named after
Harry Potter character and if you know
me I literally grew up being the biggest
Harry Potter Stan ever I went to all the
movies at the midnight premiere is there
like my all-time favorites so getting to
walk around with Hermione and Potter and
Weasley just really made my morning but
I will say they were definitely not
giving me the time of day at first I
really had to work pretty hard to get
them to trust me and to accept me into
their squad of flamingoes but once they
finally did it they were so much fun
that we were just working around with
them for a real one I was really
surprised because all the fooling those
were very much like kind of white really
really light pink and all the babies
were gray and I was like what the hawk
these do not look like flamingos but
apparently flamingos actually don't get
their full-on bright pink color until
they're around three years of age and it
actually comes from the food they we
learned that like backwards leg that the
flamingos have isn't actually their knee
where you'd think it would be it's
actually their ankle so their legs are
like weird and I don't know if you guys
have ever picked up on this or noticed
this but if you ever look at a video of
me standing or if you meet me in person
my legs are always crossed no matter
what if I'm standing still my legs are
100% out like a weird tea angle and it's
because I have scoliosis of all my hips
is higher than the other one but I just
thought it was so funny because I've
been made fun about my entire life
flamingos sisters I feel you we can just
be weird standing people together
alright sister so thanks for the
flamingos our foundation is all on and
ready to go and our next that was going
to be our concealer oh my god she's so
fluffy okay guys so this is all of it
the porcupine and we're gonna be having
her choose between up my two concealers
today can't Pat her a because it will
hurt the most that's right so she has
some really really long quills they're
all underneath that outside whoa and
then she can shoot those out right
though she can't shoot it out she can't
throw it something actually has to touch
it and their guard so when they stick to
something pull away really oh my god all
I'm saying i sister know how sharp are
the actual quills they're very sharp she
sheds them like regular hair so it's
like the worst house cat in the world
when you accidentally sit down on them
accidentally pull yourself there barb so
once they're in they actually have
microscopic Barb's and they'll expand
and make it hard for them to come out
they actually will only move in one
direction and that's in so they'll
actually move all the way through the
animal that they quill so it's a really
bad day for anything that decides to try
and eat a porcupine yeah so definitely
not having myself oh my god totally this
is a MUFON video Trisha Paytas is
shaking all of us coming for her career
ended over
I almost an all at the porcupine
tomorrow to listen to that okay let's
have her pick yeah okay guys so for
concealer so that we have our two
different options being the Tarts tape
tape and then also the color pop no
filter concealer I'm a huge fan of both
of these so regardless of whatever
sister olive picks I'll be happy but
they will definitely change how the base
actually looks on camera so let's see
what sister all of us preferring today
for our shoes right now which one do you
want oh oh my god
looks like I'll have picked the color
pop no filter concealer we don't even
have to bribe her with some food so look
so we're gonna be getting glam B's in
the color pop no filter concealer thanks
always all right guys so all of the
porcupine chose the color pop and no
filter concealer today I'm gonna be
using the shade a fair and number five
just to highlight the inner parts of my
face and literally olive was so nice I
was little bit nervous to meet a
porcupine but she was literally so sweet
and so fluffy like she looked so cute
that I wanted to touch her but the
zookeeper said probably shouldn't do
that unless you want to get sister
stabbed well what I didn't realize is
that those white spikes were not
actually her spikes they're part of her
fur and all the spikes are like inside
of the fur and really kind of hidden so
she looks soft and fluffy and nice and
fine and fresh but you get to host her
and she's sister stabs of you and then
you die which is just lovely and fine
what I did not know and I actually found
so funny is that apparently porcupines
are considered the lordís of rodent in
North America first of all I thought
that was me I'm so funny
I did not know that they were part of
the rodent family is the fun fact of the
day
contrary to popular belief as well
because I asked this quest
and porcupines can't shoot their quills
which maybe you'd know but I did not I
thought that if a porcupine was like the
right hand it could have sister shoot
out their quills and like aim at their
prey and get them good but that's
definitely not the case at all it
actually has to make a physical contact
and
the quill that goes in the skin and then
like opens up so it you can't really
pull it out and you can only go further
and then it kills them this is getting
dark really fast
point-blank being don't get caught by
porcupine is the moral of story but all
of us really nice to find in brush and
our concealer is done so we have our
whole based on looking at so beautiful
I've actually not used this combination
in a very long time and I am loving how
this is looking so far so I'm super
super excited these animals definitely
have really really great taste but we
need to work fast and set this in place
so let's find a speedy and energetic
animal to help us out sister so we're
currently in the petting zoo and we have
our goat here sets our Poncho's gonna
help us choose a setting powder today
we're choosing between the RCM a no
color powder and the coverfx powder I'm
a little bit over sosam because this one
is not my favor I've tried this before
and it gives me flash like Mary
sometimes and this powder I have not
tried I've heard of great things but you
never know so I have some carrots to
incentivize them and to say a little
thank you for helping us shoes today but
let's see what punch of the goat has
decided for us I love him he's gonna
come home with me
Pelle part of the glam squad team sister
oh my god you could be our new editor we
are hiring oh hello ha ha yeah ouch
handshake oh you're welcome do you like
that does that feel good I love a good
sister scratch which one do you want
carrot oh he wants ball ok locally we're
gonna be using the cover of X powder
today thanks Pancho alright guys so
punch of the goat was so excited to help
us out today he was literally so sweet
love him the most ever in the entire
world
I think I probably need to adopt a pet
goat right now and he chose the coverfx
powder and I was gonna use this and the
shade light does it my face in place
today honestly probably my favorite fact
of the entire day is that goats can
spend up to 14 hours a day eating mood
hello that is me I also thought it was
really cool too because the goats were
in a like petting zoo so a lot of the
kids can actually go in and
they're one of the few animals that you
can really interact with at the zoo and
although you can actually go in and pet
the goats and feed them they had
actually a roped-off area inside of
their pen that if the goats are feeling
overwhelmed or tired or just bored and
don't want to talk to people anymore
they can just go in the robes and then
you can't touch them
I need that at all times hello also -
one thing that I noticed when I was
closed up with poncho feeding him is
that goats actually have a rectangular
pupil in their eyeball and because of
this they actually have a 330 degree
like peripheral vision and meaning that
they can see almost entirely around them
without having to move their heads hello
that is the coolest thing ever can you
imagine how many fun things we could do
if we could see 330° around us like you
could sister spot straight boys from all
angles you could that's a little matters
honestly or I guess if you're a goat you
can like spot predators but then again
spotting straight boys far more fun
alright guys sorry face it's all set in
place and locked in everybody needs to
go it is literally a trillion degrees in
Los Angeles today I am sister sweating
it for a real one so they got we have a
lot of powder but now we need to contour
because we're looking a little bit flat
so let's see how we can really chisel
out our face and look nice and sculpted
hey girl
we're here with the draw sister sister
Athena and today she's gonna be choosing
our bronzer / contour so we have the
next Pro contouring palette and also the
Too Faced chocolate Soleil bronzer
giraffes remember the species people
don't think about as being endangered
because we have a lot of pictures of
them you can kind of imagine that
they're really ubiquitous in Africa but
a lot of them their populations are
shrinking because their habitats are
shrinking so that's why every baby born
at the zoo is a really good
really good news for species oh my god
the way giraffe society kind of works is
that the biggest strongest guy gets a
group of ladies to be his so we've got
one adult male in here Philip and he's
got two adult females that are his
girlfriend so to speak one adult female
that he's kind of interested in and then
learning to giraffes that are there are
his babies his kids sounds like me with
all the Instagram hot boys that I've
comment on their photos multiple
boyfriends
okay sister which one do you want Oh oh
my god okay Wow what's that tongue do
looks like a Cena chose of the Knicks a
pro contouring palette all right sisters
so after much deliberation and much
bribery a senior the giraffe finally
ended up picking the next pro contour
palette I'm a huge fan of this product
else I really loved the Too Faced
bronzer as well so he's done was
definitely gonna be a winner but let's
go ahead and contour our face it was so
cool learning about the drafts today
they were literally all so beautiful and
just so like majestic which sounds so
weird to say but I did not know that
giraffes are actually on the verge of
being endangered right now they're
definitely considered vulnerable which
means that they're one step away from
actually being on the endangered list
it's so incredibly sad because their
habitats are being taken away and I know
that there's kind of like a common
misconception in zoos of like oh like
these animals should not be captain zoos
like just put them back in their
habitats but a lot of these animals
don't actually have habitats to go back
to because they're being destroyed and
DeForest and so quickly and it was
really really sad it was actually so
cool too because we got to meet the lead
giraffe keeper who was at the zoo and he
had literally just gotten back from a
several weeks
trip to Africa to be part of a draft
conservation program also which I
thought was literally the funniest thing
ever
a lot of the drafts and the actual
exhibit were little babies which at
first I was so confused because they
were all equally as tall hello that's
what John Stehr known for and I asked
how old they were because I wanted to
know how quickly they grew and
apparently giraffes are literally born
out of their mothers
at 6 feet tall already hello
I need all boys to be like that first of
all second of all like oh my god that
mother all right I say this what I had
and I baked my face to really reinforce
those highlights but I'm realizing that
I was just
excited about talking about the draw so
much that it actually forgot blush let's
go ahead and see which animal can always
get a little bit of color back alright
guys so we're here at the ostriches and
we're going to ask sister David I love
how all the animals help like fun and
fresh names then this ostrich is just
David I have the anasazi at Beverly
Hills blush trio in the shade of peachy
love you guys some I love a good peach
blush and then also this your way at
blush duo in the shades adore so the
last out of the bowl is gonna be honest
tiles here and the bright stars gonna be
G Wyatt let's see which one they eat
from oh hello oh they picked the middle
you're kidding me really a little
getting ready right side okay Joey it is
that was a reach oh she looked at me too
she knew she said I'm not helping you
girl you're welcome for that content she
said I do not work for free contact my
manager beforehand Hollywood of course
Wow ostriches apparently love doing
charity work today I think we're gonna
go with this away blush in a door
alright k so David the ostrich is being
a little bit sister sassy with us today
he did not want to help us out so rude
but finally we ended up going with the
joy blush in the shades adore I really
really love it this blush to us is gonna
go ahead and apply this fun asha talk
for you just in case you want to learn a
little bit more ostriches are the
fastest animal on earth that walk on two
legs so fun we love a speedy sister
alright guys so the next type of our
makeup routine is going to be the browse
the course browse will hire a lot of
concentration a lot of precision you got
to have your brows on fleek
and what better animal to choose brow
products say than chimps chimps are
super super intelligent so today they're
going to be choosing between the wet and
wild brow pencil and also the anasazi i
beverly hills one let's see which one is
gonna snatch our brows today
Oh me
oh my god how long can I ask you to
choose between these which one can you
help me Oh which one oh definitely
someone while pencil hello I'm sure most
of you guys already know this but
chimpanzees are actually the closest
cousin to humans so like they're
technically our sisters kind of so fun
love that for us but literally just
let's talk about beforehand chimpanzees
are already endangered which is once
again so sad and they're closely related
to us - how are we humans ruining that
so sad like a little bit this blows my
mind it's like disgusting all right man
eyebrows are finally kind of done that
loda just took me 30 minutes
what in wild ancestor chimpanzees I love
you guys the most ever in the entire
world but we'll never be using this
again so we're definitely gonna take the
owl here move on to the next step which
is going to be our I shadow alright guys
we're here with sister Evelyn at the
karela and we're gonna hopefully have
her choose our eyeshadow today so you
have the Anasazi a soft palate and also
the jeffree star cosmetics thirsty
palette - definitely very very different
color schemes and let's do it sister
Evelyn was feeling today Evelyn do you
like the soft glam no she said no too
soft glam
she said we wanted to color today ladies
anasazi softly I'm sorry girl out the
window
looks like using the Geoffrey start
thirsty kala today I'm down for those
have not gotta play with this cat sister
Evelyn do you like these colors great
alright guys so Evelyn the gorilla ended
up choosing the jeffree star thirsty
palette I'm so excited to play this one
today and also as well which I thought
was so cute and I just realized
literally now filming this video Evelyn
was a western lowland gorilla and she
actually had orange and blue on her face
and look at the palette she picked
literally hello orange blue queen I'm
gonna start archiving a fluffy crease
brush and dipping into this shade right
here at the name of which I cannot say
on camera being that this is a
family-friendly youtube channel but it
is calling my name and I'm gonna pop
this right in the crease just to kind of
start off our eye look today
honestly have no idea what I'm doing yet
I'm just gonna play around just like the
gorillas dead that was a really bad pot
let's see what I could come up with this
is like a hybrid between like an orange
and a pink and a peach this color is so
pretty I'm obsessive oh wow
next under up a little fluffy brush and
dip into the shade quench it's this
bright yellow shade in the bottom right
here and I'm just gonna lightly go over
those edges to make sure they're nice
and blended out super super similarly
and obviously unfortunately to the
giraffes and the chimpanzees the
gorillas are actually endangered and not
only are they endangered by they're
actually what's called critically
endangered meaning that they're you're
literally about to be extinct
fortunately though there are so many
programs and so many people working
tirelessly and putting in so much effort
to do everything that they possibly can
to keep Carlos alive and well and with
us here on planet Earth similar to the
giraffe keeper the gorilla keeper Tania
actually travels to Africa all the time
to work actively towards gorilla
conservation in the field we also found
out - on the very very Geo so I don't
know if I'm supposed to tell you guys
this but Tanya actually personally funds
trekking permits in order to send
Rangers out there to protect the
gorillas against poaching which I
literally think is so so so cool so
honorable and I hope I'm allowed to say
that but I just think that is really
really dope and it shows that there are
truly good people out there working
actively to save these animals next time
to grab the shade a stroke in the upper
right hand corner and use this to deepen
up the crease just a little bit I'm
gonna grab the shade - rizal and I tried
a little fluffy brush in the bottom
corner and use this to deepen up the
crease in the outer V I literally have
no idea where this look is going just
like none of these animals know where
their habitat is going
that was a good pun but a serious pun
I'm gonna use the excess concealer and
cut the crease and then right on top of
the concealer I'm just gonna grab the
shade a filthy rich and packed that
right on for a nice little pop and then
just going right back into the original
shade I'm just going to blend out that
edge make sure there's no harsh lines oh
that's pretty
hello all right guys need to finish off
this I looked today for the lower lash
and is gonna be super simple and it's
going to add in a bright pop of blue so
I'm gonna grab the shade submerge right
down here this color is so so so so
ending and I'm just gonna put this right
up against the lower lash I think this
needs a winged liner so
like separated Oh supposed to be a small
Wang she's big and beefy
I reckon that is one gorilla inspired I
have looked all complete I'm gonna go
finish the other one off the camera and
I'll be right back to finish off the
rest of the look
all right scissors I am back i just did
the other eye on camera and i popped on
a pair of lashes cruelty free and
definitely not mink of course i felt
that a pair of house eyelashes ikonics i
used to herd these lashes literally all
the time and they are so beautiful and
stunning hello
most we have moved on to the next step
which is going to be our highlighter
alright guys so the otters are coming in
to play with us today I heard that they
love sparkly and shiny things and hello
is same so I'm gonna have the twos my
highlighter today and I have the Wet n
Wild highlighter and also the brand-new
k'kaw Beauty highlighter so let's see
which ones these guys want to choose
hello would you like this one oh oh this
one really likes sister cam alright
sister said between the two of these are
on our friend definitely chose the k'kaw
highlighter he's following this one all
around in the pool it was so so so cute
I'm little obsessive otters but they
just rent down the water side and left
us very very rude because her keeper is
feeding them but also I don't blame them
for leaving us for food I would also do
the same thing so for her later today of
course so gonna be using it the
brand-new k'kaw BD highlighter palette
could have dip into these two shades as
chosen by at my otter friends I was
literally convinced that I like wanted
to adopt an otter after meeting them
they're also so so adorable and so cute
but otters submerged a lot of the other
animals were like you know today are
actually endangered due to habitat
destruction which is so incredibly sad
and our target at the zoo is actually
telling us how it's a really really
awesome thing at the zoo when they
actually get a new litter of otters
because of the fact that it's like
giving them a home and it's furthering
the population because there aren't much
of them left and zoos are kind of one of
the only place that can actually exist
safely
[Music]
alright guys so now that we are all
glowing for the God our last up of the
day is going to be our lips for this
we're heading into the one exhibit that
are you know we don't want to turn today
and that is the layer with all of the
reptiles and amphibians if you guys know
me you know that I have a major fear of
snakes whoa and a lot of other reptiles
so hopefully this using process will be
okay I know we'll be safe but just a
little bit concerned and hopefully one
of them will be able to choose our lipid
you do dots we have our morphe lipsticks
and you change to 10% off and then also
a Kylie liquid lipstick both really
great options to finish off this lock
hello career what one do you like Oh
does he like the more feel about it he
definitely likes the morphe lipstick
oh good taste hold on I'm still in the
bouton definitely just show us the
morphe lipstick I'm really excited
because these just came out the formula
is literally at the last minute I wrote
good taste sister longer though thanks
to our sister a boot on front end he
ended up picking the abort be a brand
new lipsticks of course use code change
for 10% off I'm gonna mix together the
shades caught and flirt super fun fact
about the bouton now that my lips are
done and I'm gonna set my face in place
since we've been talking it so
negatively about extinction and
engagement this entire video it was
thought that the bouton was actually
extinct and told in the 1980s when they
actually discovered the species living
again and alive hello we love a safe
sister literally me coming back for all
my scandals are my sisters I think my
makeup look fully chosen by different
zoo animals is now complete and oh my
god I literally love how this lecture
notes today like hello I feel so
beautiful all these animals had
obviously amazing taste and today was
generally so much fun I want to say a
major major thank you to the LA Zoo for
working with me on those videos today I
know the zoo sometimes can have a
negative connotation with them and have
had a little bit of a controversial past
and not even gonna lie going into this
video today I was a little bit nervous
and skeptical but everything that I saw
and everybody that I met and everything
that I learned today taught me the exact
opposite every single person we met from
the zoo right from our tour guide
Katherine who is literally the sweetest
in the entire world to all the different
zoo keepers you could tell we're so
passionate and so knowledgeable
about their jobs every single question
they asked they had a million different
answers for and we're really just so
excited to tell us everything about each
animal it was so blatantly obvious to us
how much each different zookeeper
actually took care of their animals and
was so passionate about their jobs some
of them literally even making at their
own personally funded trucks to the
animals natural habitat to work on
preservation and to learn more I know
there's a common misconception about
zoos and the mistreatment of animals and
listen guys I was very skeptical when I
went into this as well and it was
actually really cool because I did get
to actually ask Katherine our tour guide
about this and she even admitted that
this definitely was a huge issue in the
past but a lot of zoos now are working
actively on preservation and
conservation to fix the reputation that
was given to them so many years ago I
know it's very easy to see an exotic
animal in an enclosure and think oh my
god this animal needs to be released
back into the wild it doesn't belong
here but in reality a lot of the animals
that we got to meet and interact with
and learn about today we're critically
endangered meaning that they don't
really have habitats to actually go back
to zoos are kind of one of the only
places left where they can actually
exist safely as a species and at least
humans will get to learn about them and
appreciate them and do anything we
possibly can to keep them here for as
long as possible I want to say a major
major thank you to the LA Zoo for
working with me on those videos today
this video was not sponsored at all but
they really went above and beyond to
help us out today and make sure that we
got an amazing fitting with a bunch of
amazing animals the LA Zoo actually won
an international award last year for
conservation which literally is just so
cool and truly shows how much work and
love they put into their jobs every
single day so I encourage you guys to do
research visit learn more and see what
you can do actively to help because I
know I'm going to I had such an amazing
days today and I genuinely cannot wait
to go back and learn so much more and I
want to see what I can do to help and I
advise you guys to all do the same if
you guys until this videos today and you
love this little extra twist on a very
very classic YouTube challenge don't
forget to give this video a big thumbs
up down below enjoy your love and
support it would truly mean so much to
me and if you've not already it don't
forget to click that big red subscribe
button down below and come join the
sisterhood it is a pretty lit time I'd
love to have you join the family and
click the bow like on seek we don't find
every time I upload a brand new video
you don't want to miss out if you like
to follow me on my makeup tour you can
follow me on Instagram or Twitter
they're both
Charles - out tougher work but haven't
seen types off is Charles that extra ask
after Charles this videos that sister
Sara Costa sister Chloe thank you so
much love for always following in
supporting you I love you literally it's
so so so much and if you believe to be
the next videos
sister shadow don't forget to always
retweet brother links when they go live
on Twitter all right sisters thank you
so much for watching this videos today I
need to go I am very late for a dinner
reservation right now who I love you and
I will see you in the next one