you challenged us to do the most
expensive slime dump ever not $100 not
$500 million well I guess there's now
the $999
well let's go we are making $1,000
Grabeel is over there's gonna be slime
so step number one you have to crack
open some glue luckily this one is
already cracked open all right here we
go let's add it in look I didn't act
like dump it out man it's coming out of
two old all right so he's add all the
glue in this container I don't think
we'll be able to contain it I've got a
little bit of a different method
actually yeah it's spat out everywhere
the weird sound oh no dude rut oh my
gosh it's like spider-man Brahmas going
everywhere I tried to see what I did a
video was done with Karina because this
video is actually inspired by that video
I had to learn slime from the queen of
slime herself Karina Garcia and she
taught Manon a fluffy slime we made $500
worth so basically I doubled the recipe
so this is now $1,000 worth of it it's
gonna be lit brows then we're gonna do a
race right now we're gonna see who can
finish up their side fast wait what it's
a race again I'm gone for Thoreau oh
sorry bro I'm sorry giggling ten points
on your side let's go bro you're going
so fast I can always yeah dude I'm not
get a witness
I've already two bottles behind then
attitude you'll never win with us what
there you go two at one time
[Applause]
wow that's heavy it's so heavy I can't
even hold them on brand new restaurant
oh my god holy cow I'm gonna try to do
three at one time well bro it might be
we don't know yet uncharted Lance of
glue three at one time
what up bro I know from experience that
you're gonna go a lot slower really yep
should I abort now okay alright Barney
wonders like if we're a little bit too
lit for this style of video because I've
noticed everyone else goes blind video
show me to calm it down real quick yeah
let's calm it down okay this is great
another one down another case it's like
worse than a jump here bro it intends to
do that was it like I scared myself with
that this is not yeah the containers
bending the tables bending under it as
well all right you want to do last one
there's two more on your side dude oh
you did you're talking at the table ones
too we were not even close at all we are
under equipped and overexcited way do it
that applies just about every video
we've ever done alright here we go
nice I was the clean kits we're coming
down to it next up I think we got the
shaving cream and that's nothing you're
going to be crazy I can't wait for the
shaving fees the glue is now added this
thing is seriously warped like this
container I know I'm not gonna be able
to hold it at all and broke this stuff
like quadruples aside really how we
might have to eat this dumb bro and just
kind of like make normal slime and
sleeved of no nice line no all out bro
if it overflows it does not matter all
right Devin said we're going for it here
we go three
- one no no first we have a challenge
for you guys I wanna see if you guys
been society to this channel turn on the
channel post notifications video a
thumbs up in seven seconds
here we go 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 done comment
down below
keeper squad right now but bro no need
to the big reductive be productive think
think about the bigger picture
my hair isn't it yeah no not enough
button fill er up didn't work no problem
you can take so long my fingers are
gonna be exhausted so for those of you
guys wondering what the exact
measurements are from this I learned the
master tip from Kareena is called
eyeballing it dude you missed half of
the bucket already so here comes the fun
part Devin now we're about to mix it up
get our hands kind of dirty white you
wear a long sleeve shirt he didn't tell
me what we're doing and if you know I
didn't go up to like here on you bro
I'll sacrifice my shirt yup two shirts
on yeah it's cold out well I actually
take off my key necklace right now
because I'm like your shirt I'm not
willing to sacrifice I go find my key
necklace it's how to get some shaving
cream on it will give me one side you
are risking like a giant plunge into it
or I'm just gonna get everywhere what so
be it 3 2 1 go whoa I hate glue it feels
like a go warm this feels like I'm
touching clouds this is amazing I've
always wanted to jump on clouds this is
the closest thing ever it's actually
doing pretty good it's not actually
overflowing it's more the broth I'm
gonna have a bunch of this on my shirt
it is insane it's not even close to
fitting in this bucket and we're not
even done yet
I got a mixes glue up and around it oh
we're getting some overflowing okay
overflowing I've got on the front are we
get on the front I don't know take a
peek bro keep it out alright I'm keeping
it up oh oh yeah yeah got it gotta get
some back in here it's actually doing
pretty good that I got a mitt like I
thought this would be a lot worse see
how am I supposed to mix all this this
would be so much easier if everybody bro
I'm not like a boxer yeah you ready look
at what your arm goes out looking it
looks like whipped cream deliciousness
like I'm so tempted like this right now
but it's glue and shaving cream
time to shave my arms what would happen
if you like shaved with glue and shaving
cream what are you doing what are you
doing bro bro bro grab it like it's soft
boy it's overflowing with it Oh horrible
idea wait you are too hard
dude no sorry dude what we do not see
the front at all there's an overflowing
on the front there's so much oh no we
should not trying to make fluffy fine we
should like stayed within her comfort
zone and made regular slime but we tried
to be extra fancy huh we're not extra
fancy
well we've clearly made way too much of
the fluffy slime so right now I think
we're gonna continue down the path and
we are going to add the coloring to it
now but first high-five
I'm so down
[Music]
Oh whoo your eye shine oh not bro bro
bro whoa
after consulting with our in-house
paramedic my mom she says I'm good to go
so let's continue here you go Devin we
got some green dye nice your hands are
so disgusting bro all right here we go
time to add it three cheers to one whoa
bro
oh that's flashed everywhere that was a
gnarly mama everywhere here we go oh my
gosh this is so much food coloring bro
oh my gosh this is so much oh this mix
it up let's mix it up let's mix it now
this is the messiest video I think we've
done today - bro I don't know about that
all right well we now have the color
added to it and now it's the part you've
all been waiting for time to turn this
into slime so for that we have the stuff
called stop flow right over here so I
learned a tip from the master you only
add a little bit of stop flow at a time
and then really mix it together okay you
haven't even Rita appreciate your help
here we go
you can add a little bit that's a little
bit it's probably a lot Wow that's
insane it's truck wait wait hold on look
at this but why I just want to leave it
as that fluffy cloud no bro yeah we
really just got to work it all in
because you don't want a gloopy at all
right that's not slime I learned this
from the master it's like a drum bro
dude it sounds so back off back off for
one second this is so legit before
feeling through felt like a cloud but
now you just feel these little spider
webs almost okay so we gotta make sure
we mix it up immediately so kind of like
really get in there oh my gosh there's
we've lost so much of this stuff in the
process of the everything it's all on my
feet this feels like an alien substance
in a way like this doesn't even feel
real yeah it's green like aliens know I
have an idea what bro what I've got a
special technique that I've actually
developed patented you ready for this
I'm ready
oh yeah oh this how you doing oh yeah I
almost got elbowed in the face only
problem bro you get super tax super
quick and we lost about half of it over
there here we go we made and now one of
us is about to jump into it but first
guys it turned out so cool like first of
all check us out look at this I want to
try to bowl a massive sign bro here we
go come out here yeah what dude that
looks awesome
I don't have enough power like you did
Foley like make it float away into the
distance but this is slime chef Colin's
making the very first ever slime I don't
know like pizza roll Pizza roll massive
like slime ball huh okay okay cut it off
cut it off cut it up dude not my hand
okay let me help cultivate this all
cultivate the ball we got a we got it
it's a slime ball I'll give you a toss
up on cattle 301 no make it better
the crazy thing about this is to get the
slime off you just grab a little chunk
of it and there's like pull what it
comes right off like this is crazy look
guys no oh god Devin for some reason I
have too much on my arms hohoho to find
out who has to get covered in this line
we are going to consult the grapefruit
decima know what by tapping it we will
randomly select which one of us has to
jump in here here we go Devin we're both
going to tap it on the count of three
one by this thing yep
the grapefruit destiny go for watching
it two three tap my most powerful yeet
to date not a big fan of the grapefruit
of destiny right now is like I'm the one
who's gonna be getting covered in this
stuff if you want to be featured by the
way in the next video comment down below
how much money should we spend on our
next slime video huh go crazy with the
number and by the way congratulations at
the key for the week if you want to be
the keeper that week check the
description down below to find out how
about right now let's let's go a few
moments later oh this is no good
we've tried everything we've tried
lifting this thing we tried dumping it
and I'm very upset right now because we
said we would do the most expensive
slime dump and we can't even lift this
on us so much can't even dump it so how
are you doing I think Devin's gonna pick
up giant handfuls dump them on my head
we're gonna go like that so go for it
done three two one oh it didn't even
stick to my hand why didn't it stick see
I gotta get me outta here to help with
the dump because like you good are you
good
all right none of this stuff is working
we're just gonna have to go for it yeah
bro dude you good not cool bro no no no
no dude