are you guys losing some magic magic all
right check it out hey guys so we're
gonna do here is I want you to uh once
here you want do this your pull out a
card sure you're bored I take the
product take it shut around to everyone
like everyone here pass around okay I've
got actually see it though
well basically how this works what I'm
gonna tell you you got it camera got it
well so how this works what I'm gonna
have you do is um here once you hand me
one do this
I'm gonna have you do is take the
sharpie and just sign your name on the
card okay right here yeah basically what
you do is when you sign a card looks
like that that means I cannot duplicate
this card there's only one of these
cards in the whole world to hear with
the Sharpie away for second all right so
this is basically this is your card all
right cool so how this works you were
gonna take it sweet your card I'm going
to have you do is here hold it up what I
want you do is here do can you say
carton just bite down on it yeah and
then I'll use a card my card to be the
King of Hearts Oh check this out already
put my little initials on there like
that okay all right here we go so you've
got your card leave right there check
out mine Jamie you're good if you fall
into the deck for me yes yeah all right
cool check us out
stay right here all right ready so we
want you to here take my hand
hey hey hey
yeah I guess you