it's okay actually want to try something
with your catcher things with your hair
bands yeah sure cool a huge hair bit bag
okay it's all good I'm in there Jeff
just I don't even have like a bill or
something it's like a one dollar bill
[Music]
cool okay
get to check out so we got a bill and
here we go I got the paper clip of doom
so here this I hold on to these two for
me and what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
use these two hair bands and you guys
see what's called like the linking metal
rings right yeah yeah we take a teeny
like linked together this is kind like
the budget version of that but the goal
is still the same right it's still
trying to get the two bands to link
together and so basically how this works
here we go let's can take it right down
the middle watch we go one we go to
right there three the two bands that you
link together I'll say they're really
linked here oh yeah yeah
all right here going to check us out
here what I want you to do is just go
forward pinch on the hair bands and then
kind of rub back and forth yeah it's
like that yeah don't let go right there
I hear would you try something else
we'll use the bill this time so what I
want you to do is um you got two right
there perfect we're gonna use these two
hair bands to create basically like a
metaphorical ladder almost you have the
top the ladder second step third step
then you got the bottom the ladder so
take the bill unfold it once for us yeah
just like that take it right here and
then paper clip the ends together where
there's no way to get to build off it
doesn't like me okay awesome it's like
that perfect so the bill is clearly
there on the top now the goal is to
actually get the bill to melt down to
the second step so check this out to go
one two here we go watch every watch
we'll do it again one two garage
three what I want you to is here for the
last one can you hold on to the bill
this way here I want to show you those
see the bows clearly on there keep
holding it watch me one two like that
all the way down the body you can take
off the paperclip it's still on there
everything right hand you got the bill
yes keep your hair bands thanks I'll
take the paperclip your money yeah so
rub it on