so first of all welcome to the Thursday
vlog it's a little bit unconventional
because of course I'm going down the
stairs which I don't normally go
downstairs my blog if I fall that's
gonna suck basically is update time on
the America's Got Talent or this season
see this this is sketchy part okay sorry
I'll get the whip the heck I no longer
feel safe
it says no exit here don't think oh my
god
holy crap oh my god are you Keaney look
at this place
alright let a little bit more like it
okay so this is uh this is a lot better
okay
that was sketchy it's all good that was
so scary in there so now I'm like on
some sort of roof top I don't even know
where the heck I am I'm just chilling
here I got my tripod thought I was gonna
be filming something like whoa look at
that sketchy up there so yeah so
basically I'm on the America's Got
Talent - we're gonna be going to 36
cities over the next six weeks so if you
guys haven't already got your tickets
make sure you get those ASAP keepers out
there if you guys are coming to the show
it's very important when you guys to
make awesome signs like keeper and
Collins key signs bring them to the show
like support just hold them up the air
I'll give you guys like shout out some
stuff also be sure to make like homemade
t-shirt that's also wanna posted
pictures on Instagram
use hashtag Collins key on tour I'm
gonna follow you guys and like your
photos right now I am in Philly
Philadelphia York town and it's really
cool I hear there's like there's a lot
of cool stuff sketchy freakin sketchy
hotels sketchy without one place with
Jilly scared the heck out of me like oh
my goodness oh my gosh that place is
scary selfie alright great now it is
time for hashtag ask Colin's key on the
flippin rooftop so let's do this kiss
key said can you come to my house haha
I'm not that I'm not that ninja your
parents probably kick me out immediately
anyway oh sorry guys losing my place on
my phone this kills my arm this is like
an arm workout this vlogging I need to
get like an arm stand or something this
legs now offered never look all awkward
dang it yeah
Selena Keith said if you were stranded
on an island and you could only bring
one thing with you what would it be my
phone eventually they're going to create
a teleportation apps like a teleport off
of that Island my vlogging arm is
getting stronger calls Kiwi heart you
said would you rather only be able to
whisper or only be able to shout well I
pretty much already shout anyways so I
probably be able to shout shout
something now
keepers place is scary now I'm in some
sort of like sketchy garage I don't like
it here I don't like this all I'm going
back Oh
Dalen
could've sworn I heard someone like over
there
holy God this is scary why why did I
ever come to the rooftop like if I was
out here no one would know that I mean
like abducted [ __ ] yella keepers at
the top of my lungs no one even notices
that I am officially done if someone
tries to like get me out here
[Music]
whose sworn sworn there was someone over
there oh that's all the time I have for
ask a call ins key today now if you guys
have any more questions be sure to hit
me up on there's someone over there
swear to god there is like legit someone
over there and now this is the epic
journey back to my room so oh my god I'm
actually in luck because I have this
handy-dandy tripod this is like a club
right here so I'm gonna have to smack
someone if they come close to me do this
I'm so scared right now it's a bit like
honestly like I am honestly scared right
now
some kind of bike
South Karen
I will suspect something
don't ever come back see that door
what didn't get killed good thing I
don't know where I am now where this did
I go I thought I thought it's all
someone so yeah so now I'm on the street
to Philly again I was up there on that
roof before now I'm down here can I go
in this door smile tell nice yes this
has been the first day of logged if you
guys enjoyed it please give this video a
huge thumbs up and of course don't
forget subscribe to my channel new magic
Monday videos are back to be sure to
look forward to those those are
happening every Monday now got to go
check out it's cool elevators I don't
know how maybe the disappearing thing if
I'm holding the camera once you guys in
Holland key thank you very much watching
peace
[Music]