what's up everyone is Colin's key
welcome to the first ever Thursday blog
that was actually my first vlog I've
never done a blog before so please just
bear with me and I lost you didn't I
moving on and check out the sweet desk
behind me I'm gonna get out of the way
got out of Star Wars comment piggy The
Hunger Games oh yeah for shizzle let me
get some playing cards action figures
and magic has a mug act I got this
because I perform that's a lot of dust
one let's clear that out get a smoke
point to this line man open its own
awesome little mini tour of my desk
welcoming this video even more awesome
oh yeah
jumbo glasses what up that's key Colin's
key this has no eye protection I can
really be punched in the face right now
Oh enough with the glasses
oh snap they're gone a lot of you been
asking to keep them sending me stuff and
the answer is absolutely I'm going to
put the address in my peel box in the
description behind me as you can see
this is my fan wall and it's it is
rather empty right now so that's where
you guys come in basically all the
letters and pictures and postcards II
thumbtack just going to go up here on
this fan wall I'm gonna lead a totally a
few guys wherever you guys want to send
some things are not acceptable but for
the most part whatever you want goes up
on that wall neither can send me
everything except for two things fruits
and vegetables homemade food right the
reason because they will go bad in the
nails I'm gonna get to my house the
giant stink bomb no good for anyone we
don't have all the stuff you guys send
me a video about it post it give you
guys shout outs the whole nine yards
how long's nine yards that can be that
long this like a foot how do you even
judge nine yards like my front yard is
more than 15 feet to 9 times 15 I gotta
figure this out calculator time oh I got
a new tweet ok stay focused sorry back
next calculator to let's see my front
yard is like 15 feet and it's 9 yards to
9 of my yards times 9 equals it went
away
15 times 9 equals 130 yards no you 130
feet yeah the whole 130 feet was a 30 or
35 it's 35 the whole 935 930
five Dyson moving on I am SuperDuper
excited to be on America's Got Talent
or as we like to say in the business egt
know if you saw me on the show hit the
thumbs-up button show me some love I've
always watched American talent but never
in a million years did I ever think that
I would actually be on the show so to
actually be on the show this season is
it's really a dream come true
because I something I've always kind of
wanted to do but the magic that I
perform is not really meant for
America's Got Talent because more
close-up magic
whereas America's Got Talent usually all
the big stage illusion so I thought I
was going to boot off the stage because
the audience would be able to see the
close-up magic now I'm going to get a
couple axes and they get torn apart by
the judges so that's why it was such a
shock when I got a scathing ovation and
the judges had nothing but great things
to say that is a love thing over there
whatever that is now we got some like
air conditioning finger just went off
yeah I got a guy I got shut that off
it's messing with my video flow of
homies let's shuffle this summer is
going to be amazing a full of magic on
America's Got Talent
now in addition to our Thursday vlog I'm
going to be doing a magic Mondays which
basically means every Monday I'm going
to be doing a new magic themed video
please subscribe to this channel that
way you can get all of the latest videos
now every week I'm going to be answering
a few fan questions so if you've any
questions for me drop them in the
comments box below I guys thank you for
watching I'll see you next Thursday
[Music]