once if everyone is calm ski and welcome
to the Thursday vlog today is actually a
very special day it is Halloween it but
looked like a giant pumpkin one of the
reasons that I love Halloween so much is
because I'm able to dress up and be a
completely different person for an
entire night unfortunately I haven't
been trick-or-treating in three whole
years I've either had classes or
performances and this year I am actually
on tour with America's Got Talent
I'm probably be on a bus for six hours
while you guys are all having the time
of your life
now today since I cannot go
trick-or-treating I thought it'd be kind
of fun take a look back at some of my
older Halloween costumes so welcome to
the first ever reacting to my old
Halloween costumes tag first of all
shout out to my mom for looking all of
these up last night alright let's get to
it
oh god I'm Chris angel and I don't know
what the heck this costume has to do
with Chris angel
duck face really why am i pulling off a
duck face but I'm sure that I'm wearing
is far too big oh that's actually a fun
fact that is the 3d Cohen's key necklace
I put on a necklace and then I thought
of super gangster so I put like paper
clips on the necklace and stuff I'm
gonna wearing a beanie I have honestly
never worn a beanie in my entire life I
just can't get over that duck face I
don't know when I ever thought Chris
angels in a duck face is too
embarrassing Jambi Criss Angel let me
put on what I normally wear oh my god
next cute Wow Wow
I don't know what the heck I am I think
I'm like a crossbreed I am a fireman
pirate repin Disney shirt which makes no
sense and then I've got a shield and
like I saw like a knight in shining
armor I don't know what I was wearing
this was obviously before I knew what
actually worked in what actual
professions were so I was a fireman
pirate Lego wearing people smacking
little kid and then I've got some sort
of like shawl around my waist just for
no apparent reason and that looks stone
oh I look so stoned I'm like one is
totally covered I think I ran into a lot
of stuff that Halloween what the heck am
i doing apparently I am straddling a toy
house I look like I'm about to take a
poop that's that's like my pre poop face
let's point out the obvious I'm dressed
up as a flippin tiger that has human
feet and human hands so like I'm a
monkey tiger by the end of it like all
the fur had fallen out I was like an old
person who lost all their hair oh the
grapes costume whatever so obviously
attempting to be a firefighter but what
I in fact did that is put on a poncho
which I have honestly never seen a
firefighter to walk into like a burning
building wearing a poncho I walked
actually into a fire station I had the
ball there's a little kid to walk into a
fire stage wearing a poncho and telling
them that I was a firefighter and then
I'm on some sort of intercom talking to
absolutely no one that's pretty awesome
now I have levelled up my fireman outfit
I don't know what's going on my face
yeah I look pretty depressed but there's
a creeper horse in the back room now
I've got a poncho
I've got boots I've got an old awarenes
pant it looks like a giant diaper oh
that's that's real gangster I've got a
headset that actually have stole from my
parents off our home phone I've got some
sort of fireman badge I've got a helmet
and then I'm making the light fade this
is probably post fire department visit
because now I realize the fireman's
don't actually only wear clip and poncho
I've now obtained a wristwatch don't
know where I got that wristwatch from
Wow ladies watch out this is the
construction worker outfit trade bans on
flex look at my arm is broken actually
hoarse I'm wearing my construction
helmet ever no it's gonna fall on top of
your head looks like I've got a potbelly
with my shirt for some reason when I
look at my real man fades oh this is the
sexy vulcan i was talking about in my 25
facts video and now got face paint on to
make this tiger costume even worse look
like some half breed of animal and
monkey that face paint though really
really oh snap who's hardcore I'm not
obviously as you can tell it I'm wearing
a spaceman outfit that's totally ratchet
and ghetto because I put on night a
night helmet doesn't fit on my head it's
supposed to fit all the way over your
head and come down your face but this
thing was just so small and to hit like
the top of my head and like the mass was
like just like right here on my nose
obviously I'm a spaceman don't even set
up the spaceman oh my god your spaceman
they're so cute and I'm like go away I'm
a knight in shining armor oh wow I am a
fabulous construction worker chief I'm
fabulous
I don't know why working on a wooden
fence that it's in perfect condition
here oh my god you have got to be
kidding me
what the heck honestly what the heck I
cannot put this one in too worried I'll
embarrass you guys
looking at this what the Frick was I
thinking six feeded Collins if there's a
picture four feet is calling visit fetus
Collins I was wearing Harry Potter
glasses a pink tank top God knows where
I got that probably I would like my mom
drawer not even my mom would wear that
with a tank
bathing suits that it just hide up to
above the navel line a crock no one
should ever wear Crocs period Crocs no
just just no and long socks with cross
no that is no no this hurts and then we
got my fabulous I'm a fetus
I am honestly a fetus I can't even look
at this one anymore we are moving on
your minds will be erased and you will
not remember that right now we traveled
through time and space look at that
smile
my brother smile is much better than
Devin's gonna kill me for putting this
in here I want you all to know that I
actually am a good brother because my
brother you wanted a skeleton costume so
we bought the costume and like a few
days later he changed his mind you want
to be an army man you're not allowed to
return the costume which is kind of a
bummer so that you know I'll sacrifice
myself all we have the skeleton costume
so you guys can buy Devon another
costume that's why I ended up being a
skeleton that costume sucks because I
was trapped inside that mask and I was
at a hardcore Halloween er two colours
up a Halloween er there was a rule you
put on a mask for Halloween you can't
take that mask off because get hot in
there no it's a code of ethics you keep
that mask on until that Halloween trick
training is over
this was another ratchet get a costume
but I had no idea what to do and it was
like we were going to a Halloween party
I told you about this for months and
callings you have no costume we're
leaving in two minutes I'm like I'm
gonna be a like button on Facebook what
the heck honestly what the heck what was
I thinking that is not even a costume I
thought when I couldn't smile as well I
was like oh yes the ultra sexy Indian
all of you been asking for a shirtless
picture so I thought this would be the
perfect time to give it to you but I've
been is not what you're looking for
three year old me with red blood all
over why why do i blood on my face why
don't I put paint on my armpits look up
the feathers sticking straight up to
signify that I'm a warrior that's not
even a spear that's like the most
crooked if I try to throw that it will
probably like boomerang you're getting
in the face oh then the mushroom cut
that just accentuates it shows the
fierceness of the warrior and shows how
powerful they are in a combat battle
that's why the most of their
one so far just appreciate dat belly dat
Valley right dur
appreciate it looking up a big booty too
what the heck because of where my arm is
this is my big booty big belly Indian
costume I think was supposed to be
fierce but I just was like I'm so
shocker there that is never be spoken of
ever again can't even believe that I
wore any of this stuff and last but not
least it selects my favorite costume
this was last year's costume took a lot
of times really you know get all the
proportions right and make sure that
looked exactly like the Joker it looks
so much like the Joker I know it looked
a little bit different in the photo but
I assure you that is I percent me in the
photo you guys like seeing all those old
pictures of me please give this video a
huge thumbs up of course you guys it is
Halloween so I have to leave you with
one final thing although I am NOT going
trick-or-treating tonight it's up to you
guys carry on the tradition so go out
there have a blast go trick-or-treating
get crazy amounts of candy scare people
for no apparent reason please give this
video a huge thumbs up if you enjoyed it
also don't forget of course subscribe to
this channel and I want to know what you
guys are dressing up for Halloween - let
me know in the comments down below what
your costume is and the most creative
costume might get a shout out in next
week's video once again you guys I'm
columns key thank you so much for
watching the Thursday blog happy
Halloween
peace oh sorry one more thing tomorrow
I've actually got something extremely
exciting I have a big announcement that
I'm gonna be releasing on can't wait for
all of you guys to find out what it is
I'm gonna put the link to the video
right over here once it's up check it
out it's gonna be up tomorrow morning I
guess now I'm actually gonna leave so
bye
I'm a little pumpkin short and stout