what's up everyone its columns key and
welcome to magic Mondays now remember
the point of magic Mondays is to take
your ideas and then turn them into
actual videos now Mona Kisa do magic at
VidCon that would be awesome a lot of
explanation points afterwards Alex Brad
sure said you so need to do magic at
VidCon that would be the best thing ever
and Tina Keith said do magic at VidCon
for your keepers see I do read the
comments and I thought that it was an
awesome idea going to VidCon was a blast
I got to do a lot of crazy magic for a
lot of awesome youtubers check it out
you're watching that Monday's
[Music]
fear
like the other brittle
[Music]
no straight now is off
like a favorite hard
in my hand as well that looks very funny
brother realize you're broken
come back to
we have our magic Monday back VidCon was
not absolutely awesome off the chain oh
please give this video a big thumbs up
if you enjoy the vid con magic and let
me know in the comments section who your
favorite youtuber was that you saw in my
video now remember from magic Mondays to
work I need your ideas it can be
anything like like turning a Justin
Bieber poster into a One Direction
poster we're making Liam Hemsworth
appear in one of my videos or we're
going to instantly paint your nails with
magic yeah do you tell I'm not really
good at that one yet now those were a
couple of my ideas but I really want to
hear your ideas so let me know in the
comments section below
what you think would be cool now if you
minima at VidCon definitely post a photo
of it make some gifs of it I want to see
the photos I'm really excited because
the Thursday blogs will be I just shook
the camera I'm really excited because
the Thursday's long is gonna be all
about my experience at VidCon everything
from collapse giant sharks and VIP pity
party carpet FM I bet that so get ready
for that that's gonna be coming out on
Thursday
you got enjoyed this video please give a
huge thumbs up and don't forget to
subscribe to this channel once again on
Colin's key piece
[Music]
mmm-hmm
the video is over bye-bye