any of this one I've officially peed
myself what's up it's called key and
fortunate ease video as you guys can
tell I'm doing a challenge I've already
got this thing on my hand and all I need
now is just a super special guest to
join me so please welcome of my friend
Jake Creek way to teleport from Robin
London for today's video we are going to
be doing the wet head challenge and so
basically how this challenge works we
have water contained above our heads
right here he came up with a list of
British slang that I probably don't know
and I came up with a list of American
slang and so in a moment we're gonna be
asking each other a question so let's
say that I ask him a question and he
gets it right then he gets to pull out
one of these pins but then if I ask
question and you get it wrong then I get
to pull one of the pins out of your head
and one of these pins will release all
the water on to our head so I'm not
exactly sure how many rounds gonna be
doing what I will let you guys know
whoever wins the majority of the rounds
at the end of this video they have to
jump in a swimming pool we're taking the
white hat challenge to the next level
also want to let you guys know that we
did a video over on Jake's channel that
we did you guys noticed this shirt is a
little bit wet right now and that's
because things got pretty messy so go
check out that video go subscribe to
Jake his channel is awesome I love his
videos and if you guys are coming from
my videos make sure you guys give me to
be a big thumbs up and also comment down
on his video that my channel since you
guys but like I said make sure you guys
subscribe to his channel and you guys
love British accents let me know by
liking is this video because trust me
you're gonna be getting a whole lot of
British accent right here Lucy Jackson
also gonna let you guys know I'm doing a
big giveaway on my channel right now
giving away a MacBook so if you guys
want to win that let me know by liking
this video comment down below what's
your favorite video that has ever posted
of course you must be subscribed to this
channel without any further ado right
now let's jump in and this is American
vs. British like a wet head challenge
Lego down so first one is a road map
Gino lies a road man either one like the
traffic cops it like wrecks traffic or
something
a road man is somebody with your mouth
is like yeah like like a satchel yeah
like a little baguette is often like a
DDoS or something hands they roll around
and they're not know like they're like
quite well in it right man
okay that is likely sheriff I totally
understand the definition of a road man
you gotta let me know yeah let me tell
my eyes I know you know what age so I
guess you get to pull out a pin so only
oh my gosh this is really weird
so um but the hands are now soaked I'm
soaked in my underwear I'm gonna go
refill this and I guess you're gonna go
for round two all right well you know
that did not go according to plan at all
but um yeah now it's my turn to ask him
a question so here is the term jack up
okay Jack up means if you mess something
up no jack up like like you jack up the
prices so I'll give you go to the store
and like something's more expensive than
usual man I think I've got this cool so
I'm gonna give this a spin now you know
if I get on the first one how are you so
happy I think I love it
I'm feeling this one right here no yes
yeah no so my second one is right you
know what a crow is agro yeah oh no I
feel like it's agriculture but I don't
think it is no like you aggravate
someone like you're a growed no yeah we
really like oh let me to aggro yeah
American for the week Hey
all right let's see I'm gonna go I mean
I'm gonna stay in like lying here
yes how is this happening
how is this not there all right for this
one the word is bail bail right okay so
if I'm doing something and I don't wanna
do I made out of it getting it I didn't
know you got no one so quick I'm alive
okay number two are in the pool now this
is a very British thing to say I'm not
sure if you'll get this one on the pole
if you're on the pull on the pole um I
want to give you a Cleveland I don't get
wet you means a little clue cuz I really
have no idea like eggs I'm gonna pull
you out all night in your on the post oh
we can finally get a girl oh my god yeah
I would have said that like it yeah
bring a quick decision there on the pole
and it's gotta make a decision how about
this how do we each remove one from each
other's cuz can they hang really help me
out and then I would have got anybody
want to cut hair woman I know yeah so Q
at this time I get one point I guess cuz
I didn't get everything all right cool I
don't know if that's something that you
guys say but take a rain check
what is black yes yes hey so you want to
go outside you'll know a jacket no no
okay I owe you a clue it has to do with
with social gatherings so you need to be
prepared so your final answer yes no
take a raincheck is like if you if
you're gonna hang out with someone and
then something else comes up or you
can't hang out it's like hey I still
have to hang out with you let's take a
rain check will do another time yeah
like my mom does right sure take a rain
check
that's very American artists and here we
go I got you angry that was a grim no
number fool
cheerio cheery is like bye
I bring again the cereal no of course
not it's like violet cheerio I think one
of those exterior British things if you
possibly say cheerio Geoff yes all right
here we go well I'd better get one of
these out this one is tight I think it's
a typical tight between stretch it too
tight yeah and that's the other one
where it's like oh you'll be means
they'll be too tight no one you were
close like it's not being tight no it's
actually give me a time
that's crazy no cuz I get America it's
the exact opposite look if you're tight
with something I need you really close
up but like you're like best friend yes
that also means that as well in England
like oh yeah we're tight but I was you
mean sighs I'm just tied give me that oh
yeah we we never use it like tight of
like balloons so complicate it all the
toes all right you are kidding me
this is not tight number five oops my
dog's back gulps night I love it
and you guess what it is it's like
something like really delicious like
something like gobsmacking good
basically if someone said to me
completely like horrible to you or or
surprising to you and you like ah
gobsmacked Oh like you say gobsmacked
oh that actually make sense right well
now you had to pull one okay knowing my
luck your obably gonna get the one that
will I'm good all right cool here's my
next one you ready for this spill the
beans
okay so I feel excellent Oh someone's
keeping something away from you come on
just those beans yeah I'm good done bro
Oh number six overall July's a what boat
roll bog roll yes keep your food bog
roll is it is it when you roll down a
hill like grass I'm real I never say
ball roll is something we're going to
the ballroom I don't know why wow you're
gonna get me no that's not okay you just
so much water how is it contained so
much water I've officially peed myself
I'm about go refill my hat and then
we're about to finish this up I think
I'm in the lead points wise right now
but I'm definitely losing in the getting
wet department so hope that you have to
jump in the pool because I marry a girl
right now yeah well I'm back I've
refilled my water so this one I'm gonna
go for my hardest one trying to stump
you because I need to get you soaking
wet bro this is not fair if you get this
one I'll be very disappointed
the word is cramp okay so there's not
much room in like home to the car okay
you gotta cram it all in there your
final answer that is actually wrong
maybe you could use it like that look
water you still driven on me but the
other we could use it is I thought what
people who usually use it for is I have
to cram for finals or like I've gotta
scram and do a whole bunch of studying
okay
Oh finally God finally got him well so I
think we'll call it the end for this
part of the challenge and I believe I'm
in the lead right now so you know that
means Jake jump in the pool you got a
bad now but like I did get so why it's
like real bad
so yeah let's go let's go do this you
can see my skin through my t-shirt I'll
have to blur that out censor the image
give this video a thumbs up right now
for the fact that he literally just
jumped into the freezing pool yeah he's
like you should worry a little bit right
now it also makes you guys go check out
the video we did on Jade's channel he
got messy but you know bro there's been
a blast but I got to make you teleport
back to London right now oh man I'm it's
already bye guys