this is the most insane hot versus cold
challenge and if you make it all the way
through
you decide walk on fire or swim through
ice if you choose correctly you could
win a thousand dollars so right now
let's go for the first challenge you can
either cross the hot sticky human fly
trap or climb the slippery ice wall so
contestant choose your challenge
now go choose it where you guys gonna go
all right so you guys have chosen the
hot sticky human fly trap over here
olivia what's your strategy going into
this one
pushing niko in oh he said he was gonna
use you as a plank what
what that never happened the
competition's already heating up all
right guys turn around here we go
okay so the rules are super easy last
person to make it across
is eliminated all right guys here we go
you ready three
two one go
oh nico he can't even move
dude they're stuck yo i gotta say i'm
happy i'm not competing in this one man
yeah i got it i gotta go
i feel like this is a game of twister
[Music]
look at nico it's the final stretch
right now i'm the last person to finish
is eliminated
and gets no chance at the thousand
dollars come on
you're so close ah
no oh no he's in the split
feet goes way back there let's go nico
let's go
oh you all right that's him
okay there he goes
[Applause]
oh my gosh i got it
and the challenge is over and
unfortunately nico has been eliminated
it is now time to climb the slippery ice
slope you guys ready
all right rules are super easy all you
got to do make it to the top of the
slippery ice slope
grab a flag the last person to complete
it is eliminated all right guys the
competition begins in three
two one go
[Applause]
i think we made this a little bit too
difficult man oh no
there's like an ice avalanche just
coming down on them it's so
cold okay he's going for it he's going
for it yeah
is ben like spider-man
oh my goodness michaela's going for it
he's got a good strategy though she's
just like winding it around her hand
grab it grab it
yeah keep going let's see let's go go
that's the key right there if you get to
the nut you can make it up easy
oh man she's grabbing that rope over
there let's see yes
okay guys there are still three flags
left
i come back for you i promise got it you
got it i got it
i got it
yeah down to coley versus david only one
makes it through
yeah come on oh
if coley can just get to that second
notch she's got it
he missed the crap
[Applause]
david bro i'm so sorry so those are the
four competitors moving on all right
everyone this is the hot or not food
roulette challenge
the rules are super easy there are eight
different foods six of them
are ridiculously spicy but two of them
are normal and cool and if you choose a
spicy food you stay in the game
if not you're eliminated the first up is
olivia
which food do you want to choose
remember only a spicy food gets you
through to the next round and the chance
of winning a thousand dollars but i will
warn you some of these foods are meant
to trick you so don't take them at face
value and make sure you choose very
carefully this is diabolical
i'm gonna go for the cupcake the cupcake
all right i mean yeah i mean the cupcake
zooms normal so you wanna
you wanna pick it up you wanna go for it
here we go three two
one let's see what is it we need we need
the reaction
it is actually like it seems like it's
like a nice nice spice oh i took a
really big bite
it's like slowly coming over right now
yeah it's got a kick i can tell by the
handshake
great olivia still in the game all right
devin you are up what i mean so come on
up this is the first time i've actually
chosen to eat something really spicy
i'm sorry i didn't smell anything but
delicious doritos
i think he has to choose the chips
that's good penalty what do you think
devin
i'm down all right all right i'm i'm in
i'm in i'm right here you
commit to the chip all right devin you
got your chip you ready for this you
gotta secure the bag for the fam
exactly did you do me right here i don't
know it's up to you i have nothing on
this here we go three
three two one you took the whole chip
man
oh is it spicy yeah oh it's spicy
devin got spice are you good no it's so
hot
that's right give me some milk get this
man some milk
oh my gosh dude are you burning up right
now ah sweet relief
it's back now look at my eyes is not
normal
all right nina you're next so what are
you thinking in terms of food wise
i do kind of want to try pepperoni
pepper all right so you chose the pepper
it could be complete decoy or it could
be very hot we'll have to see i mean it
is a pepper so you ready here we go you
ready three
two one that was that was a strong bite
of it what's what's
hot it's hot
oh man oh is it so it was hot
okay so congratulations you made it
through
all right ben you're up next man
remember you have to choose a hot food
to make it onto the next thing
i think what are you thinking that guy
oh but it's so cute that's exactly it
that's exactly it this little gummy bear
i think that it's
too cute you think it's too cute see
this one over here it's nine million
scoville which is absolutely
insane this is by far the hottest one
here and i do not envy whoever picks
that one they're gonna need a lot of
milk because that is gonna be seriously
spicy all right so here we go three
two way back to the subscribe challenge
we wanna see if you can subscribe to the
channel and turn on the channel post
notifications
in five seconds you're ready here we go
five
four three two one done you're gonna do
that comment down below keep your squad
right now three
two one let's go nothing he's out of the
game
the most hot item on the entire table
you just ate right now are you good okay
here we go
oh dude holy cow is it that hot
it's that hot oh my god all right thank
you ben yeah
all right so next up lindsay if you
choose correctly you get to move on if
not and you are limited which one do you
think is the spicy food which one's not
what are you thinking popcorn okay
popcorn is the choice can i take a
handful
yeah just take it to you take a handful
all right it's not spicy if you're
telling me to take it oh see
is it spicy is there i gotta look no
spice
no no oh no limsey
kayla you are up next so one of them is
still regular the rest are all spicy so
i'm gonna
go with the donut the donut hold up what
is that in the back i don't know
it's a jelly filled donut i'm a little
scared now he gave a look
here we go you ready take a big bite
here we go three three two
one let's see all right
is it hot no oh man she's on it oh man
congratulations on to the next one so
now let's go for the final one here
so bennett and coley if you guys want to
step down it's a 50 50 right now so we
have a wing or a piece of sushi so i
guess between you guys what do you
initially think i mean
sushi is my favorite food so initially i
want to go there because i feel like it
wouldn't wrong me
i'll do it i'll do it all right so there
we go you get the wing you get the sushi
all right one person is leaving the
competition right now there's a sudden
death round here we go you ready
three two one best of luck let's see
where is it he put the whole thing in
here then it went for the whole thing
oh no oh no see that's a spicy one
oh man
all right i'm sorry but bennett you
joined lindsay all right six people
remain in the game but only
two will have the chance to walk on fire
or swim through ice for a thousand
dollars so stay tuned to see who wins
all right next up is the hot versus cold
balance beam race so the rules are super
easy you either get a hot full of water
or a cold bowl of water and whoever
spills the least amount of water on
their journey down
they are safe the other person is
eliminated so let's do this olivia ben
you guys will be first up all right oh
snap one bullet is filled with hot water
one bowl is filled with cold water and
the race begins now go yes
oh snap ben's already spilled this out
i'm getting hit more than everyone
else's
yo oh dude that one's soaring right over
olivia oh my gosh
ben is definitely spilling some okay
holy cow oh all right here we go okay
okay ben's throwing
oh
olivia's made it yay here we go thank
you congratulations
all right well you know what i gotta say
looking at the two bowls i'm
sorry ben all right olivia since you
made it through right now you get the
first choice you go the hot sauce dunk
tank or the slushy dunk tank
i'm going that way he's going slushy all
right
next up we've got devin and we've got
michaela so if you guys want to hop in
all right here we go you guys ready yes
throwers are you guys ready
three two one go oh my dude i am like in
the middle of all the fire zones
super concentration oh
snap i think coley is just actually
throwing a switch
you're almost there you're almost there
you're almost there right there and
devin is done
there we go and done locked in oh this
is going to be a close one i think we
need to place these down let's
do this let's place them down over here
i think cold side edged it out
great job though congratulations all
right so devin do you want to go
in the hot sauce dunk tank or join
olivia and compete against her in
the slushy dunk tank uh i don't want to
compete against her i'm going over this
all right devon's in the hot sauce dunk
tank all right
all right the final round again if you
win this you have a chance at a thousand
dollars you guys ready
all right here we go the race begins in
three two one go oh
no no no no so far coley is like very
very still but nina she spilled a little
bit but she's like she's recovered very
nicely
the balls are coming in hot and heavy oh
my gosh okay
oh no are you all right she's falling
off but she's still not out of there
it's too late it's not too late the
balls are coming in the ball is coming
in and
done okay there we go
[Applause]
oh my gosh with the most dramatic exit
wow
give it up with these two dunk tanks
you're either gonna be going up against
devon in the hot sauce dunk tank or up
against olivia in the slushy dunk tank
so
which dunk tank and which competitor are
you going to choose
i'm i'm feeling hot you're going to go
against devin
oh all right competition's on so you can
join devin over here
yo bonus challenge alert we're doing
something absolutely insane right now
i'm gonna give one of you the
opportunity to join this challenge and
get back in the game we have six torches
six eliminated competitors five of these
torches will turn on unfortunately it's
hot and you are not able to rejoin the
game the only torque that will allow you
to rejoin the game
is the cold one and on the count of
three go to the table decide your choice
here we go three two one go
oh man all right here we go so on the
count of three flip the switch three
two one let's see
what so coley you move on
right now to the final challenge give it
up for them right now
to determine who will walk on fire or
swim through ice for a thousand dollars
the contestants must first make it
through the hot sauce versus slushy dunk
tank challenge
let's do it all you have to do is just
dunk the person in front of your butt
you only have three throws and if you
miss
all of them you have to switch places
and whoever gets dunked first is
eliminated and right now let's kick it
off with the slushy dunk tank here you
go outside the line
you have three attempts to hit you ready
okay i'm ready here we go
little ready okay remember for a
thousand dollars come on baby
here we go
all right time to switch all right here
we go olivia this is it for a thousand
dollars first of all
all right let's do it all right let's
see this here we go go for this let's
see it
oh
you guys are lucky man because this is
only the slushy one like the hot sauce
that's gonna be a whole nother level of
drama over there man
you can miss you can miss it'll be so
fun if you missed
ah you're going now you're going down
ready let's go
here we
god go oh my gosh
are you all right it's really good oh my
gosh
i'm right here i'm right here i'm so
sorry she's out of the game
i had fun i got a lot of fun all right
guys it is now time for the hot sauce
dunk
ready oh boy no i'm not ready nina you
get the first throws we'll grab these
over here
if you go in you're eliminated and you
make it on to the next one you can win a
thousand dollars you ready
yes i'm ready all right here we go go
for it let's see let's see the throw
oh oh oh
oh oh you got this
winding up
all right guys time to switch go for it
all right devin so now it's your chance
man
finally my chance you can make it
through devin ready move the brother's
proud
i'm ready here we go three two one
you're throwing so hard yeah i want to
make sure she goes in bro oh my gosh
all right secure the bag for the fan
ready yep
oh my gosh no no
devin here we go three two one
oh my gosh yo i gotta say like this one
over here was like a little bit like
nicer kind of like some nicer tosses
yeah
it's going down over here i did not want
to get hit by a straight ball on this
one
[Music]
[Applause]
last one you are one with the ball oh
come on oh come on
come on
[Music]
my eyes well let's get out of getting
cleaned off dude great job and nina
you're on to the finals
they decide who walks on fire or swims
through ice we're gonna be playing a
round of our brand new fake food mystery
wheel challenge and remember
there is a thousand dollars on the line
you guys are making a hamburger
you can spin the wheels first to find
out what compounds you get you got green
all right nina now it's your turn yep
you get to spin
blue okay all right here we go you ready
three two one
go what's the game plan here these are
the patty or the patties
okay oh so usually that's like the slime
you'd use it as a cheese you're using it
as the buns yeah
you guys coming down here we go three
two one
done hands off okay so here's the deal
guys it all comes down to the mystery
wheel spin and whoever wins this decides
whether you want to swim through ice or
walk on fire so here we go you ready
three two
one oh what is it going to be the
neatest
congratulations so here's a question
nina what do you want to do do you want
to swim
through ice or walk on fire i don't
think my feet are built for this so i'm
gonna go with the ice you're gonna go
with the ice
all right so right now let's get to the
ice swim and then coley you're gonna
have to walk on fire man i'm already hot
just thinking about it all right cool
let's get into it right now all right so
you ready nina so this here is the ice
swim
i put my hand in it it is oh i know
you have a game plan like how you're
going to keep yourself warm going across
it i will be
in the desert oh like mentally in the
desert it's a good idea okay all right
so here's the deal you cross it you
could win a thousand dollars but cool
you then have to cross fire coming up
here in a second
i don't know who's actually got it worth
but nina you ready i'm so ready okay
here we go i want to counter in here we
go
three two one
and we just launched our brand new
lineup toys games and challenges
inspired by the best parts of our videos
and is now available exclusively at
walmart so click the top link in the
description right now to get yours and
now
let's do it
[Applause]
holy time for you to cross the fire oh
my god congratulations
holy cow that was insane dude you just
went
through that nice little time wow
all right congratulations yeah you gotta
have you let's get you in like a shower
or something right now it's kind of
warmed up all right we have now seen the
ice swim so now it's your turn the fire
water how you feeling
it's gonna be hot nina it was it was
mind over matter right
right all in here exactly so i think
it's kind of a similar thing here with
the with the fire right
i mean i could burn but yeah mine over
here
at this point i think the best way to do
it from what i've heard is to put a
blindfold on that you don't actually see
the fire and then cover your ears as
well for right now because kind of like
like sensory deprivation you basically
won't feel the flames if you can't see
them or hear them okay okay
seems legit right yeah yeah yep you pop
the blindfold on okay
yep just like that and if you want to
cover your ears that way you won't be
able to hear anything
all right yep so jacob keeps like
sensory deprivation come on come on come
on come on
come on up here come on over here all
right so here's the game plan we've got
a second board that's completely safe
with no fire no flames no nothing it's
not hot at all so do not worry she will
not be stepping on anything hot but
she's gonna think that jeans we're
pulling a crazy prank on her right now
all right let's do the call actually
you can take you can take the ears off
right now you uncover yours if you want
to if you want to walk over here
oh my god it was hot right it looks oh
that looks so hot on the count of three
you can feel the heat
here we go so on the counter you're
gonna take your first step and remember
if you feel uncomfortable any time you
you can stop it if you make it all the
way down you've got a chance of a
thousand dollars you ready
i'm a little nervous it's okay you got
this
all right
[Applause]
oh
take a quick look down it's not actually
fire
it was much more like a bravery test to
see if you would actually make it
and you had it so congratulations
you guys each will get a thousand
dollars
[Applause]
once it reopens again massive thank you
to all of you guys for being on this
video
if you want to see another video click
right over here you have five seconds
here we go five
four three two one done
love you bye