Bella: Okay, if you ever see me running, it's either free cake, pizza or zombies are real.
Christie: *gasp* But you think that zombies like pizza?
Bella: Duh Christie, even vegans like pizza.
Pull up on you
Standing with your girls looking good
I just gotta have you
Started conversatin' then you asked me all about my shampoo
Thinkin' "What's that about?"
0:33.0 But it kinda made me laugh so I told ya come through
You know what we gon' do
Candles are lit, lights are down, playing Cody Simpson
Running your fingers through all of this blonde ambition
Till I found you in the shower but the water ain't runnin' and you still got all your clothes on
Got my products on the counter and I put it all together
I just can't get you outta my hair
Can't get you outta my hair
And I know it ain't fair
Tryna blow dry and brush it, you just wanna touch it
I just can't get you outta my hair
Woke up feeling funny but the do is money so it's okay
Walking down the stairs saw your purse sittin' in the hallway
Thinkin' "What's that about?"
Came around the corner with a can of hairspray
Let me hit the replay
Candles are out, lights are up, I'm still on a mission
She said "I just wanna give you a deep condition"
Cause I'm lookin' so good and I'm feelin' even betta and I'm smellin' like a rainstorm
She said I got body but she ain't talkin' body
I just can't get you outta my hair
Can't get you outta my hair
And I know it ain't fair
Tryna blow dry and brush it, you just wanna touch it
just can't get you outta my hair
I just can't get you outta my
Outta my
Logan: Tryna blow dry and brush it, you just wanna touch it, I can't get you outta my- *gets slapped* Oh my gosh...
Bella: *pushes him* You're...weird! Stay away from me.
Christie: We're gonna get pizza.
Logan: I'm Logan...pizza...pizza, okay bye. *walks off awkwardly* (Poor Logie
I just can't get you outta my, outta my