Hey!
Hey, what's going on?
I don't know, Franke
I just haven't been feeling inspired lately...
You go in there
And you sing from the heart!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
9, 10, 11, 12
13, 14
15, 16, 17
18, 19, 20
21, 22
23, 24, 25
26, 27, 28, 29
30!!!
Fuck all the haters, that said I couldn't do it
I said I'd count to 30 and you know I'd fuckin' do it
I'm that boy
That's my boy
And I love to count
I'm that boy
That's my boy
That's my boy!
I'm that boy!
That's my fuckin' boy!
That's my boy!
I'm that boy!!!
I fuck with you if you say you love to count
Counting is my favorite and that's what this song's about
Sing it loud
And sing it proud
'Cause no this ain't the alphabet, just in case you had a doubt
It's like
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14,
15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20,
21, 22,
23, 24, 25,
26, 27, 28, 29,
I saw your face
When I counted up to 10, you knew it wasn't 30
My mom's ashamed
I know if I don't finish, you'll probably disown me
Is it Einstein? Is it Newton? Galileo? Maybe Uller?
That's giving me this power
To finish what I started!
'Cause I never though that numbers were better!
I could never wrap my head around that letter!
I know I have to follow my (heart)!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8,
9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14,
15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20,
21, 22,
23, 24, 25,
26, 27, 28, 29,
30!!!
I fuck with you if you say you love to count
Counting is my favorite and that's what this song's about