Yall ready for somthin'
Yall ready for something that will shock the world
Yall ready to turn up
Oh,Yall ready to turn up
oh, yall ready to turn up
One more time, Yall ready to turn up
Here he comes yall
Its the man him self
LOGAN PAUL!
Lets go fam!
(song)
Yo
You ready for this?
A L.A WHAT GOOD!
L.A Whats Good!
WHO'S READY FOR THE BIGGEST INTERNET EVENT IN HISTORY!
WHO IS READY TO WATCH ME BEAT THIS MAN ASS!
You ain't ready
Alright champ alright champ
We love you champ
Touch me one time
Lets go champ
Alright yall ,alright yall
This is a Q&A
And we got the big dogs out now
We got the dogs out now look at em yall, look at em yall
Finally you look me in my eyes bi*tch!
OOOH : Finally you look me in my eyes
OOOH
Finally, looks like you grew a little d*ck today
But its a little one
Yo!, and I'm vegan and I'm vegan so I recognize a baby carrot when i see one
OOOOOH
WAAALLMARRTT!