-Has this ever happened to you?
-This gun is so fake! Ugh!
-Well, look no further thanks to the
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun!
You'll never not not have a
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun again! Again!
You're probably wondering, well what will I ever use this
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun for?
Well, let me show you.
With the Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun,
you can defend your home!
-Freeze!
-Ow!
-Defend yourself!
[slap] -Ow!
[slap] Ow!!
-Defriend your friend!
-Ow!
-See, there's many different uses for the
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun!
Use it as a ruler.
Use it as a paperweight.
Use it as a back-scratcher.
A hat. Headphones.
Shoes.
Even use it as a gun!
-Freeze!
-But wait! We'll also throw in another
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun!
-Ha-ha-ha, now you freeze.
-But wait! If you order now, we'll throw in a bigger
Hard-&-Black-Realistic-But-Not-Real-Gun!
But wait! Did we mention that we'll throw in the biggest
But wait! Call now and we'll throw in a banana!
But wait! You'll also get this lamp!
But wait! -Shut up!
Just shut up! If you say "but wait" one more time,
I'm gonna shoot you!
-Shoot him? I'm gonna shoot you!
-But wait! -Shut up!
Just shut up! -No, you shut up!
-I will kill both of you!
-Don't you mean the both of me? 'Cause I am you.
-No, I am you. -I am me!
[all arguing simultaneously]
[guns firing]
-Guns don't kill people...
People kill... guns!
Teehee! But wait!