*Sniff*
Hey Guys
So you probably already heard
all the hype around Pokemon GO Right now.
Unless you've been living under a GEOdude
*Motor Laugh*
It's literally everywhere
Youtube, Twitter, Facebook, Instagram
and that's just online
turn off the cumputer they are talking about it on TV
you go outside to a park or grocery store or anything public
there is probably people playing it there too
I mean there's been so much hype on POKEMON GO
that I've been that I started to see it in places that is not
*don't do drugs kids*
*and also don't play pokemon go in the hood*
*is that an ONIX*
*naaaaaah it's just poop*
* F/CK OFF MARLEY *
* HELLO MF *
* Greg's parents are the proudest ever*
* how meek mill catch Nicki Minaj *
* my anaconda don't*
*don't what*
* I don't know :(*
*yaaay congraaats OMG*
What ?!
Don't act like you wouldn't catch her too
I mean she's still rare
it's better than catching Taylor swift again (LOL)
and STDs xD
that's all there's around here
and NO before you swifties jump to conclusions
I'm not saying that taylor swift is a rattata (nice pic ryan lol)
because she looks like a rat
Rattata rattata RATTATA (WTF)
it's a vine meme (ah ok thanks ryan)
RATTATAAAA
she's a rattata because rattatas are everywhere (like swifties)
and even if you don't wanna see or hear another one
you're still going to
and also because rattata can learn the ability to swift
and just like taylor swift they might not be the best attack (Kim was the goalkeeper)
it's still gonna be a hit
because swift doesn't miss
ok enough pokemon Jorgging (is that a word)
jorgging ?!!?!?!?!
I don't know why I used that word ( me neither)
I've never used that word before
it's sounds like a pokemon (idk)
jorgging JORGGING jorgging jorgging JOOOORGGIIIIING
see this is exactly what I was talking about
it's the 90's again (yaaay !!!)
it is all about pokemon
it's taking over the world AGAIN
and this time its not something you should've been ashamed off
when I played pokemon and collected pokemon cards as a kid I've got to it like almost in secret
because back then play pokemon make you a nerd make you uncool
and now the table have turned and the chairs well
we now live in a teenage where pokemon does not make you ...
well I mean we are all still nerds
but there's more of us now
Pokemon go has once again make pokemon the biggest thing in the world right now *except for my :) *
and no one should be happier about it than me
I've always been a super-Pokemon fan
I mean I've played all the games from the beginning
Pokemon RED BLUE GREEN YELLOW (why not black)
pokemon snap pokemon pinball
I've watched every episode of pokemon that was on TV
I've even had the pokemon sound track so I can memorize all the songs
* I'm not writing that *
Part of my life I'm particularly proud of
but you need to know how big a pokemon fan I'm in order to truely understand me when I say this
I'm not trying to be a hater or a downer or anything but I can't be the only one who absolustely loves pokemon
that dosn't love pokemon go *me too Ryan*
*STFU loosers*
sean : you're just jealous
diana : you just suck that's why !
paco yellow : oh no sh*t
*ok screw it I'm not writing all those beeps *
*is someone dying*
*call a doctor*
*Oh Hi Ryan !*
Oh I forgot to put the black bars
and now the text
*nice ryan*
*magic of editing *
Pretty accurate
Look I don't hate the game
but in my honest opinion I was a little disapointed
specially after all the commercials they put out
that .. to get every body excited about it and trust me I had normal expectations I wasn't expecting the game to look like the commercial
it's an unrealistic expectation
well maybe not I mean there's virtual reality now
but to go from this to this
it's a little missleading
i still think it's a great idea
and I know the game took like 10 or 20 years (WTF) to get done
but I still think it wasn't ready to be released
.... it's not really pokemon yet
it's a google maps styled with pokemon
it's pokemon least like pokemon game WHAT I'M I saying?!
that did not make sense
how do I describe that better in 2016
*wtf you looking at ryan*
Oh
*magic snaps*
pokemon go is basically google maps mixed with four square with a pokemon snapchat filter on it
fam
*are you okey ryan ?*
with no chill
lit
savage
*I have no idea what he just said*
*stop watching too much ricegum*
DDDAAAAAAABBB
*and KSI*
I'm still hyped
but you know what its not even the look of pokemon go that bothers me
I can get pass that
It's the fact that half the time you cant sign into the game
because the servers are down
or they're experiencing difficulties
and maybe it's just me but even when you can sign in
when you are playing the game it just freezes randomly *get an samsung galaxy note 7 man* *and for me too pls*
specially for some reason when you finally catch something (other than STDs)
something that you spent a lot of time looking for (you could be making more videos at that time )
and it kills batterie faster than any game I ever played before
I can go on for a long time *pls stop*
but I didn't made this video to hate on pokemon go
in fact I actually hope the game becomes more successful so that they can put some money into it and then I can finally play it
and who knows (1.0)
the game is so popular and they're making so much money that they probably are working on a second version that looks like the commercial
so for all of you that haven't given a shot yet specially if you're someone who loves pokemon like me *or me*
Don't have high expectations and it's still a fun game *and don't get high too *
I mean when you can actually play it *good luck*
just don't expect it to look like the commercials
Don't expect it to be what we all wish for as kids POKEMON in the real world
cuz it's not quiet there yet
in the downtime that I was actually waiting for the pokemon go servers to come back I wiped something together to help you with that
Here's a more honest commercial for what Pokemon go is really like
in the form of the same show that we all grow up with and loved watching except for the kids who did not know that show existed
fam lit savage no chill *never say never to drugs*
DAAAB
OMG I'm not gonna put that in YES I'M
*hahaha it's my time to shine*
*what's up guys*
*close enough*
ok it's written now so I'm gonna take a break and come back later see you guys
*miss me yet ?*
*how about you?*
Ryan's car is a MASERATI
*no problem just kill'EM all*
*facebook ... really ryan it's dead like myspace*
*team blue Mystic YEAAAH*
*I don't Actually play*
DAAAAMN GREG BACK AT IT AGAIN WITH THE NICKI MINAJ LOOK
* +18 *
*Hi again Back to work*
on the last episode of pokemon go Ryan finally spotted the rarest pokemon MEWTOW
with only seconds to react Ryan finally throw his pokeball and ...
*it's not frozen*
*maybe it is*
*don't be silly it's just pokemon servers*
*see I told you*
*bye guys I'll miss you*
*GTFO*
*tape mr1b in comment to confuse others *
*TEEHEE*
*Hi again*
I'm not even joking look what poped out
Our servers are humbled by your incredible response we are working to resolve this issue please try again soon !
*fake happy face*
I love this game *Bye again*
*TEEHEE again*