- Hey, guys. So if you guys didn't know,
I just hit 6 million subscribers, thanks to you guys!
YEAAAHH!!!
And I didn't want to make another boring thank-you video,
but I couldn't really come up with another creative way
of telling you guys how--
(sighs) Damn it.
(switch clicks)
It's just an ordinary ball, right? Wrong!
It's not just a ball.
It's a big bouncing inflatable green ball!
What?!
There's many different-- (fades)
♪ (reminiscent pop music) ♪
Thanks to Hook on Fonik, we make your dumb ass smart!
Boom! Wrong! I was the lamp!
Shut up! Just shut up!
You shut up!
I will kill both of you!
♪ Things that ruin Thanksgiving! ♪ - Boom!
- Boom! - Ryan, happy Thanksgiving!
♪ (music swells) ♪
(clips speaking)
♪ (guitar strumming) ♪
(simultaneous teehee's)