Hey guys! So if you follow what's going on in the YouTube community
and I'm not just talking about my channel, I'm talking about like all of YouTube
You've probably seen some, or at least heard of some YouTube drama
And by drama I mean like you know, YouTubers fighting online
And it's all public for everyone to see
And I'm pretty sceptic so at first you know I thought these YouTubers were pairing up and agreeing to have drama
So that you know it would create some publicity for them and honestly, we'll never know
But I think it's real! I think it's 100% real
I mean they're not just like tweeting like snide, passive aggressive remarks
They are literally calling each other out
They are making dedicated vlogs to like talk crap about each other
I've even seen some YouTubers make raps about each other
Like it's some kind of "Rap battle", like the whole Drake and Meek Mills thing
And I'm just sitting here thinking
I feel a little left out
I want to be part of the Drama life!
I- I- I can have beef with someone, I know how to roast
I've had roast beef
Like okay... uh. PewDiePie, more like Poo-diepie
Poop-diepie
is what I meant
Ohhhhh
ROASTED!!!
KSI? Uhhh what does that stand for?
kilopounds per square inch?
OOOOHHHH
GET REKT!
Jenna Marbles?
More like Jenna More Bowls
Of Poop
-Diepie
That's measured in KSI
OOOHHH
Why don't you apply some water?
Ointment...
On your burn...
Put the wa...
Put the water first...
Okay ya... a you can see I'm not a good roaster
I'm a great one
But as much as I want to be a part of the whole drama scene...like I don't want to fight with anyone
I don't like confrontations
I mean the closest thing to ever being a part of the drama life was literally when I made a draw my life
But back in the day when I first started, like 2005... 2006
Youtubers didn't really fight with each other, we all got along for the most part
We helped each other out, you know we supported one another. We all collabed.
And if there was drama you wouldn't necessarily see people posting about so publicly online.
I guess people are more open about that stuff these days
But it's obviously completely different now...
and I'm missing out,
which is why I came up with this idea
You probably already know it because of the title. It is the... ROAST YOURSELF CHALLENGE!!
It's easy to call out someone out on something or it's easy make fun of someone else.
We as humans naturally do that, were always judging other people.
He is so short
Ew, look at how that girl's dressed
Look at how fat that guy is
She needs to take off her makeup and put on some clothes.
The idea behind this challenge is basically to look at yourself as if you were another person, and then do exactly what the title says...
Roast Yourself
And like I said I-I don't how to do it exactly.
I think it's pretty open.
As long as you're roasting yourself, making fun of yourself then I think you've done it.
You could vlog roast yourself. You know literally do what I'm doing right now but talk bad about yourself.
You could create a clone character of yourself and have that character roast you...
or you could even do one of those rap battles with yourself like we mentioned earlier. Like the whole Meek Mills and Drake thing.
Except it be you just roasting you
I mean it is a little bit more work but I actually think that would be the most fun way to do it.
Anyway just do it however you want.
The only rule in this challenge is to make fun of yourself, it's to call yourself out.
Because like I said so many times before were always so quick to judge other people, but alot of times we don't even realise but we have just as many flaws as everyone else.
And once you realise and all yourself out on these flaws it's alot harder to make fun of someone else's flaws .
So lets stop the drama. Stop making fun of people, stop mocking and judging people and just take a long look at ourselves...
and just tear ourselves a new one. I'm Ryan Higa and this is the 'Roast Yourself Challenge'.
See? When you roast yourself no one gets hurt. It's a good challenge.
I'm just trying to make the world a better place.
*sob*
So like I said earlier, the next time you feel the need to make fun of someone, take a look at yourself first.
If you're go and judge for something then go ahead but know that you're not perfect either and you should be judging yourself as well.
And just like any challenge I'm gonna be doing some call out to Youtubers who I want to see roast themselves.
But it doesn't mean that you guys can't do it either. In fact I look forward to seeing a bunch of you guys do your own roast.
In fact ya. I'm calling all of you guys out aswell.
Anyways, specifically I'm going be calling out a bunch of my friends to do this challenge that I think not only would be good at it but these are all people I think that aren't afraid to make fun of themselves
and I think for this challenge you have to be pretty confident cause you have to be comfortable calling out your flaws.
So with that being said... I'm calling out the following people.
Jenna Marbles
D-Trix
Pewdiepie
KSI
Timothy DeLaGhetto
IISuperWomanII
and Jeremy Lin
If I didn't call out a outuber you guys want to see roast themselves as well then you call them out.
Go leave them some tweets or comments or whatever.
With that being said ``Thank you guys so much for watching``
Looking forward to seeing all you guys roast yourselves.
Oh ya and if you guys want to buy this, you know this epic smash hit rap diss track on Itunes... you can't. Cause I'm not going to put it on there.
OOHHHH!!!!