-Have you ever happened to this?
I spilled table all over my liquids!
Well, that's perfectly normal.
But now I'm gonna be telling you about this great new product.
It's called the Teehee! Band.
Not the Teehee Band,
the Teehee! Band. Say it like that.
Similar products like those magnetic bands
claim that they help you to fake-balance desks.
But thanks to the Teehee! Band,
not only does it help you to fake-balance,
but it give you another fist. [pow!]
Anyway, the Teehee! Band
does many other things as well,
like help you to read, run, laugh, cry, tickle, giggle,
pickle, fly, look your enemies in the eye,
and figure out the end of pi.
There's never not nothing that the Teehee! Band
can't not do.
For the simple price of tree.99,
all your wildest dreams could possibly
might not come true!
You want a dog?
Teehee! It's there.
You want a cat?
You want another band?
Teehee! Well, that's another 3.99.
All you have to do is call this number...
-HigaTV.com
-So what are you waiting for? Or--
-This video! Shut up already!
-Order... order... order... order now.
Woohoo! Teehee!
[laughs]