I know what you're thinking this looks
bad but I assure you I have everything
under control
okay maybe not Oh such a dirty shoe
first things first I'm not your average
teenager I never got to grow up with a
family with bikes and candy my family
was an international network of dealers
my bike was the Falcon reading on 23 X
and the closest thing I ever got to
candy was well I did get a lollipop once
but that's not the point as long as I
can remember I've been training to
become an ass an agent of secret stuff
for 17 years I trained alongside one of
the cruelest boldest most heartless
killers of all the asses Tracy it's a
man's name three months ago on the final
day of my training Tracy brought me in
front of a panel the highest ranked
asses I'm talking top-quality
ass Eden
for the past 17 years you've been like a
son to me
we've been on missions around the world
prevented various global disasters and
saved countless lives and now it's time
for you to become an official agent of
secret stuff but before I give you your
honorary operative license entitlement
you're you have one more assignment you
must complete but but Sir with all the
respect I devoted my life to training
you will follow orders but why I already
did all the hard stuff we are active we
do not complain when things get too hard
push through but you said you know
please tell me this assignment hey Dad
we need you for a special assignment
that only you can execute the society
involving not-so-good stuff aka the sins
they have been our mortal enemies for
decades and now a new target Taylor
ranch Oh a high school senior we need an
agent on the inside we believe that the
sins have already infiltrated the school
with Assassins of their own your mission
is to pose as a high school student and
protect Taylor from impending threats
but why are they after Taylor that will
be revealed at a later time in like 30
minutes we have already made
preparations for your enrollment as spot
has remained a little bit all of
Taylor's classes she must not know that
she is in danger this is a new world for
you
high school students are the most
dangerous and misunderstood citizens
that you will never come across you must
operate cautiously I will not fail cool
be silenced
oh yeah come on guys I need your
attention just for one second hey shut
up we have a new student his name is uh
Jose McDonald yeah obviously I want you
to say hi Jose right on man you're gonna
fit in perfectly won't you take a seat
right in front of Bieber there you guys
open up your vision books to chapter 14
hey I'm Taylor can I help you something
Paula I'm Josie isn't it no it's Tuesday
it's not what you want it to be it's
gonna be like our code word for danger
no I'll be Jose you be post kids are
trying to learn hey Taylor
Govardhan pencil sharpener yeah sure
thanks suspect walk our pants charming
to us to convert the writing stick into
a weapon by inserting a yellow thing
into the green thing the dull thing were
turned into a sharp thing he would then
proceed to jump behind his target while
she is preoccupied and I'll have fatal
and manning a weapon into her jugular
artery
there you go give the sharpener back
what's your problem what are you taking
for a fresh man give the sharpener back
Jose what do you do me fine geez what
was that all about Jose don't worry I
got you
must be
[Music]
all right class that's it remember
chapter 15 read it
we're not your futures oh by the way pop
quiz next week you guys another drill Oh
Taylor I need to speak with you after
class good work today guys that was
kidding
remember these days kids you'll miss
them tomorrow thing you're planning it
with the student council yeah we do have
a lot of volunteer events coming up
don't make sure you still have time to
do that definitely it should be fine
we're almost on running stops right now
okay alright I trust you mean I don't
like these other bastards in this mess
don't you ever do that again
excuse me I said don't you ever do that
again keeping Taylor in a room alone is
not safe oh oh yeah
no I forgot you're right do you know
what else thinking otherwise I'd be good
how are you
well I'm I'm a new kid remember you just
introduced me get the hell out of my
class I'm glad we had this talk
[Music]
hey there son I'm glad I found you I
hope you enjoyed your first day of
school so far I just wanted to give you
your new Locker assignment actually
you're quite Black Knight and do what
just opened up the other day oh hey Wow
your lockers next to mine
wonder where Billy went yeah strange huh
ha ha ha well if we're gonna be seeing
each other this much why don't we just
start over
hi Jose I'm Taylor nice to meet you nice
to meet you too
it's called the handshake Jose yes so
silly it's like you've never made a
friend before okay
what's up how are you I'm good hey did
you finish that paper and he loves you
no not yet
does it do soon suspect come across
someone examines his target his eyes in
the key that he's aiming for the most
exposed and vital area her chest only 3
steps away from pummeling her with a
barrage of bullet punch is straight to a
rib cage which will no doubt stop her
heart forever for life
[Music]
what are you looking at why I said what
were you looking at chill out man I was
just checking out Taylor's rack it's
looking especially hot today a wreck
yeah man her knockers so you were trying
to knock her no man I'm talking about
her boobs you know these things oh okay
then as long as you weren't looking at
that rib cage you should stay the hell
away from the big cage Royston new guy
I'm gonna destroy you your face is gonna
be so ugly when I'm done with your face
cuz it's kind of handsome right now but
I wasn't ready I wasn't ready I want a
rematch target is greatly outnumbered by
opposition each of them possesses some
sort of NetID stick with me surrounded
and unaware she's vulnerable to attacks
from all directions
[Music]
Hosea where did you come from you almost
took a shuttlecock to the base but how
did you what are you doing come on let
me go what they beget here let me go
he's like incredibly fast and strong
he's like a mystical creature it's fast
and strong I know right
he's like a a unicorn but a human a
human core stop it guys he's just
different he's a freak I don't know I
think he's kind of cute the way he takes
everything so seriously it's kind of
creepy don't you think he's harmless
he's like a little puppy that just wants
all your attention oh you can cross our
ridiculous let's go Taylor has a crush
- students are the most dangerous
what happened slippery floors probably
didn't see the pie so mojo sang yeah
let's just
uh yes so I hope you had a good first
day at school
you're still alive so it's a great day
okay I'll see you later
oh are you coming this way too
hey so it's not going to mr. Anderson
about that coming up right after
homecoming I am going to need a lot of
help planning that event you just just
calm down okay are you trying to get
yourself killed
do you know what you almost did but
didn't do because I didn't let you do
what you wanted to do yeah no you don't
do you even know what this is these are
Little Miss double rainbow girly cookies
and you almost eat them all the way
you're even know with handle this who
could have poisoned this brick look I've
been trying to stay undercover but you
are making this too damn difficult first
first you hand over a pencil sharpeners
or someone with a pencil do you want to
get stabbed through the neck and then
you almost like a shuttle come to the
face do you know how much that hurts
have you ever had a shuttle to your
face before no you haven't
it hurts I know and now you're eating
cookies you're any cookies do you want
to get poisoned and that you're careless
is driving me insane I'm driving you
insane
my friends are right you are a freak I
know exactly what you are oh you do
alright then say it say it out loud what
you know unicorns don't even exist in
North America probably then who what are
you alright look
I'm gonna be completely honest with you
I'm not really Mexican my name isn't
Josie its Aaden and I'm an ass yeah you
are no you don't understand look I'm in
the final stages of becoming an agent of
secret stuff and my last mission was to
come here and protect you protect me
from who the sins this is all just to
get me to go to church oh my god you're
stupid all right okay here here's the
whole story back in World War two a
group of fleeing Nazi special agents
from the Society of assassins to seek
revenge in the axis of power this group
was called the Society involving
not-so-good stuff one of the assassins
only known as X but he could no longer
support such evil in the world and fled
the sins to start his own group of
killers to battle all the sins
horrendous plans they were known as the
agents of secret stuff the battle
between the acids and sin still
continues today
you're the son's latest target which
I've been assigned being killed but why
me I have no idea why but I never
question my orders
but why already deal the hard stuff wow
you are seriously out of your mind can
you you Eve potato you're in danger stop
no I'm not I'm a normal girl who goes to
a normal high school and nothing is
going to happen the more you say that
the more it freaks me out so please just
stay out of my life no just leave please
just go
I'm sorry I never meant to upset you I
just I don't know what it's like to be a
normal kid ever since I was young almost
always taught to it to never trust
people to kill them instead that's
really sad I've already filled my
mission anyway so stay out of your life
wait again I'm sorry I know you meant
well but there's really no reason to be
worried for me look I think you're a
cool guy and I'd rather just learn to
have fun instead of secret agent stuff
do you trust me know everything I just
said
[Music]
[Applause]
I do enjoy my time making the best of
everything we do work on the child
something new we'll make it
[Music]
do care to be honest I feel like I've
been waiting for this for forever oh my
god I know alright okay so the DJ side
photographer said could you I want to
take a salesgirl I think we're ready for
tonight but there's one thing that isn't
set what what did I miss a days maybe I
even can help you out with that
so that dance sounds pretty interesting
yeah it's been a lot of work to plan and
you don't you don't have anyone to go
away no not yet I just have just been
too busy right I see okay bye hi Taylor
oh hey Melvin well the dance is tonight
and call me you know you're planning it
anyways I just wanted to ask you you
would go to the dance with me
but you know he was gonna attack you
with this
are you crazy that's a flower I swear
there was a blade right here I taught
you anything you still don't trust me
you know I thought you'd changed but
you're still in your stupid crazy world
and now you're just hurting innocent
people but I swear there was snow just
stop it just stay away leave me alone
I tried a tit I really do know what
momen great going eating maybe Taylor
was right I don't belong here
this whole missions just stupid this is
what it takes to get my [ __ ]
then maybe I don't even want it
[Music]
and he's escaping to secret warehouse
turn left
[Music]
where are they tell me where the
training wheels are
[Music]
what it's too late Aidan no oh okay but
it's a trap no no it's not don't listen
to her
oh okay no listen to me it's a trap
right there a trap
I destroyed your trap Melvin it's over
oh is it I beg to differ if anything
it's the exact opposite of over it's
under anyway xiri party 1 now that we
have Taylor we The Sims have everything
we need to overthrow you
stinky asses wait Taylor wait what you
don't know about her well I know some
things I know that she can only read
from left to right this is really good
at hitting the shuttle with a
netted stick then she's really smart
funny and cute and then that she's my
best friend
ah Aidan I mean but I was thinking along
the lines of that she's the future all
the asses
she is jeez don't they teach you
anything over there you are one dumb ass
nobody calls me dumb
[Music]
[Laughter]
real cute now get back in your fix your
chair and get back in it how could you
do this Melvin we've been friends for
years
and for years I've been trying to kill
you because of people like you that ad
can't live a normal life
and you made me miss my own homecoming
dance ha
don't you mean home no one's coming
dance one zero Melvin
what the hell Taylor one dance Melvin
[Music]
oh that's real bad thanks for coming
after me tell you something
Tracy what what are you doing here I was
informed you're in danger by who by me
who are you I am you're my father
what No how is that even possible I'm
like the same age as you that's
disgusting
I'm your step step brother-in-law you
know what don't worry about it
your dad was like really promiscuous
forget it long story he's been watching
over you avin we all have Taylor was in
grave danger and clean even protector on
the contrary you have succeeded not only
have you discovered the sins agent
within the high school but you've
brought out taylor's full potential in
reaching what she is destined to become
I did what okay cool me what does that
mean
Taylor where are all these people
community have you ever wondered why
your parents are black I was adopted and
while you speak ten languages straight-a
student and very good at first-person
shooters and now you have defeated a
since agent with no training ever
because I couldn't them that too
it is in your blood Daler to be an
amazing ass you are the daughter of
agent X the founder of all the asses
you are my daughter but she's so old but
your mama was so young Nathan I am a
father
no Hayden no one hears your freaking
father man
he abandoned you at birth he is not
coming back
Hayden I am very proud to present you
with the whole you are now an official
agent of Secrets stop and ask for
[Music]
you are part of the whole world the sins
will be following you and Aiden more
intensely than ever before thirsty for
you we want to kill you and I'm bragging
rights and
[Music]
the dances ending right now oh yeah
speaking of what that dance I was
wondering
and then you want to go to the
homecoming dance with me yeah sure I
mean I got nothing better to do
[Music]
we're too late
sorry we missed your dance being a
secret agent just really hard it's okay
it's not your fault
will you move to musical notes of me hi
girl you just caught my eye thought I
should give it a try and catch your name
and your number go grab some lunch and
eat some cucumbers so Aidan you have all
the gadgets fight you're brave you're
smart and now you have your home but you
know there's still one thing missing if
you want to be a six agent wait what
that's impossible what could I be
missing well everyone knows the real
secret agent always has the girl in the
end I've honestly never heard that
before
that's something
[Music]
but maybe maybe you can open with them
whoosh somebody's there I'll go left
alright ready one two wait there's one
more thing
[Music]
yeah man her knockers she what just call
white noise thousands and thousands of
miles
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway
thank you guys so much for watching this
medium film we're welcome productions we
had a lot of fun with working with
writing yeah we made this whole thing
without any big budgets or big crews or
companies it was just for you guys thank
you so much for your support and if you
liked it pass it on to your friends
there's an honor working with you goes
on no there's not no really though we
made all this like just us four and some
other people but it's not a production
so stop writing it in the comments well
we hope you have fun watching it now I
know watch some other stuff like that
guy right there
[Applause]