oh hey guys so as you can see I'm moving
right all the boxes universal symbol for
moving this is all stage this is just to
get the point across I'm not actually
taking any I just I don't know what I'm
talking about let's get started
dear Ryan can you jump over a moving car
[Music]
dear Ryan would you do it you laughs you
lose dad jokes challenge with the crew
you go first
it's cuz I know I can't laugh what do
you call a thousand dad jokes how do you
make a Kleenex dance boogie in it what
do you call prisoners who take their own
mug shots what do you call a motor with
ears no idea engineers sexy chicken and
a sexy cow that's brown brown chicken
brown cow your dog you want some more
privacy when he poops what does he tell
you hey have you seen that movie about
constipation no sorry cuz I said come
out yet every single one and it's not
even funny I don't even think it's funny
what was the first thing you said when
you were born from Australia so what
sound does it make after you make a joke
about a dad head what that hatch why
don't have wait scratch that why don't
why don't vampires attack Taylor Swift
cuz they suck her blood she has bad
blood
what would a feminist Ryan Higa say at
the end of his video what t she why did
the chicken cross the road
product placement what would a feminist
Ryan Higa say at the end of his other
video dear Ryan can you brush your teeth
and then drink orange juice why do I
don't understand why people always send
me this and I know this is a challenge
from like a while back I should know
this I honestly have no idea what this
challenge is and I'm not letting any of
the guys tell me I really don't know
what's gonna happen and I didn't look it
up I promise so this is a hundred
percent genuine reaction I guess let's
try it alright I just finished brushing
my teeth and I guess I'm just gonna try
it why you smiling like heavy teeth turn
yellow is that what it does permanent
yellow
wait a minute right girls
isn't that bad oh I did it no it's not
bad at all how is this even a challenge
like what like what is supposed to
happen from drinking this Avenue dear
Ryan can you do if children's songs were
realistic I've always wanted to be a
children's song writer there must be
like one of the easiest jobs in the
world you have a dr. Troy Ken in the Hat
I always believe that you should be
honest with kids if I have a kid and I
and he asked me where do babies come
from I'm not gonna lie to him and that's
how you should be with kids you make
them smarter okay boys and girls now
let's give our guest performer a nice
warm welcome its first question do any
of you know how to play the guitar
no okay then we're just gonna use this
the wheels on the bus go round and round
slowing traffic down everyone's proud
wheels on the bus [ __ ] change lanes now
[Music]
thank you we could've finally started it
next song with a sirloin here and rib
eye there tri-tip brisket marinated rib
strips Old MacDonald had a cow there's a
reason I said because they ate him okay
maybe let's try the next song twinkle
twinkle ball of gas hydrogen and helium
another element
thousands of light-years far away what
to see is in the past they're all dead
today when you wish upon a ball again
it's equivalent to wishing upon the
gases from here okay I think that's
enough for today we don't use that kind
of language in here do we
oh no no I'm just gonna see a seclusion
from the gases from your ass not thank
you dear right can you kiss Shawn wait
what I never screenshotted that dear
Ryan did you oh yeah um someone just
keeps sending these over and over I mean
just look at it I thought you could just
tell them that it's not gonna happen oh
right yeah sure sure I'm serious people
keep spamming it you can just like look
at my screen right now right I you know
what I think I have to go have this are
you serious Ryan you know that I'm not
gay I know I know I'm just I'm a girl
really good have this done we've been
friends for over is there's someone
something completely unrelated are you
serious there's one big closet do-right
and you're at a deer Ryan to yourself
should be good
yeah maybe 20 30 more dear Ryan do a
parody of Stephen King's in I don't know
if you guys never saw the first one but
I remember watching it when I was a
little kid and I was terrified of it and
when I was watching the MU it movie the
sequel of the 2017 version I kind of
thought to myself this movie doesn't
really work anymore
[Laughter]
hiya Georgie what a nice boat do you
want it back
what are you doing in the sewer oh what
a storm blew me away
blew the whole circus away can you smell
the circus
Georgie Bob there's peanuts cotton candy
hot dogs and no no it's a circus circus
George popcorn popcorn decision beef
yeah I think I should leave now
[Music]
no that's okay I have an Xbox so leave
your questions in the comments below and
you could be responsible for the next
video
Oh what is the Vietnamese in sync sir
[Music]
Oh McDonald had a cow it was the loudest
type of pet you can have trumpet Sean
taking a break vacation honey did you
know rode sent us these not even plugged
in oh well I'm Japanese penny wise also
known as he and why's that
Japanese clown geisha what did the horse
say when it fell down help
I can't et up why don't the notice have
children because there may kids bring
your chain today but if you were old
your name be
what do you call Dana wearing a chain
when she's extra girly looking so Gina
Oh
[Music]