how to light a light bar with only a
potato
[Music]
how to read minds
so you want to learn how to read minds
huh all you have to do let's pick up my
new book how to read minds
I Ryan Higa that's me this is not as
interesting as I thought I'd be how to
have to get out of navigating so we've
been friends for a long time now and
also wondering would you go all with me
no because we've been friends for a
really long time and I thought you were
dating somebody else and I thought you
like oh my god what are you doing you'll
need to get out of here so you do want
to go out how to type bad day
[Music]
now to revive a damn man how to make a
kid song that would be popular today I
have no God I got so frustrated power i
got that power huh what comes next
how's it pin top again
kick it bum there's nut don't but the
tentacle stop okay I have the business
test
stop testicle II mean he just has a bit
of a girl
is everything all right look period
scuse me yeah I said you look pretty
weird today something wrong oh it's it's
just oh I know what it is is it because
you're on your rag right now and it's
getting dirty what yeah you probably
shouldn't leave it on the ground if you
don't want it you know if you want to
stay clean so Oh got it it's your next
period huh yeah you have math with mr.
Anderson next period right oh yeah and I
know exactly what you're going through I
know what your pain I mean just sitting
in class thinking oh such a heavy flow
of math equations you know P equals M as
it just totally cramps our style you
know that fake French accent every time
you come to class late and he's like oh
why of you late and don't even get me
started with this straightened hair it's
like it's so weird men straightening
hair men straightening men straight hair
it just doesn't go together why is it
always so hot in there you know he's
always like do you want the temp awful
temp on and all the kids are always like
temple please stop Wow someone is
definitely on their period I will see
you in three to five days how'd that be
a very good boy no maybe I keep reading
it like that just read it normal what
are you talking about that's what I'm
doing no you're singing or weird just
say how to be a really good voice Neri
how to be a really good voice narrator
yes now record it okay
hard to be a really good boy and even in
order to blow someone's mind all you
have to do is recite the infamous porn
if roses are red and violets are blue
and by the commutative property the
color blue is actually violated and what
two colors make violet red and blue
which means you need red to make violet
and since file it is actually blue that
means you need red to make blue but what
makes red the past tense of read because
the word you read more than any other
word so far in this equation blue you
read blue creating violet and because
violets are actually blue it proves that
not only that I just blow your mind but
everything you just read past tense
actually just blew your mind
how to find out how much of your life
you wasted today still going now what