hey guys so I guess with the title of
bub you know what this video is gonna be
about that's right platypuses the
platypus is one of the only mammals that
can lay eggs
other than dogs no you know what I
actually wanted to make this a serious
video for a change
cue emotional music I just wanted to
thank each and every one of you who
supported me and helped me to reach 2
million subscribers I mean 2 million
people that's amazing you know I'm an
average kid from Hawaii shout out to all
my Hawaiian is out there hiki Michael ah
a lava lake like owner I don't know what
I just said sorry and I know everyone
says this but I honestly believe that
you guys are the best fans I've ever
seen even some of the other youtubers
tell me about how amazed they are
because you guys are so supportive and
protective of me and I cannot stress
this enough I could not have done this
without you guys each and every one of
you so thank you I know this is one of
the videos that I'm supposed to cry in
and make it all emotional and stuff but
trust me I am speaking from the bottom
of my heart which is like right here ok
and I mean everything I say despite the
stupid little jokes I throwing so
without further ado I'm gonna read you
the most beautiful poem I have ever
written ever in life alright I know I'm
not a poet but I think it's pretty
decent so just just don't laugh okay if
roses are red and violets are blue then
what the hell is the color violet
you