hey guys sorry I have to posted a video
know what as you can see I'm in away
again and boy have I been having a ball
this used to be bigger anyway I'm back
and I just want to say welcome to the
new year 2012 done dog dog
anyway it's finally 2012 and that dog
dog I just wanted to say I'm really
looking forward to the new year
dog dog you done yeah what are you doing
you know like in the movies when
something bad is about to happen
it goes dum dum dum uh what hello it's
2012 the world is gonna end
oh no it's not yes it is the mine said
so do you even know a Mayan no do you
even know what a mine is some type of
cabbage I'm sick of people saying that
2012 is the end of the world
specifically the people that say well
the Mayans said so that's all they talk
like this you probably don't even know a
lion and even if you did they're not
psychics they made a calendar I can do
that
my theory is this people they say the
world is ending are they're depressed
because they've walked the world
generally go to I believe everything
they hear and read on Google or just a
prick because they want to scare people
into buying useless things for the end
of the world
fired up falling down earthquakes why
those pesky meteors keeping you up at
night well look no further lakes in 2012
see if you rock on the end of the world
problems will be solved with a simple
price of $100,000 three diamonds and a
rock you can get the safety rock
earthquakes no problem thanks to the
2012 sake you rotten you would never
call
Mears keeping you up at night by - city
rocks and sleepin the zebra disgusting
comments like the same comments are
stupid throw city rocks at them so why
do you wait for call this number reports
too late and remember keep rockin this
plan okay so maybe there's nothing that
stupid but people really are selling
useless crap to people just because I
think the world isn't which brings me to
my next point the next time someone
tells you that the world is anything
tell them okay in that case give me your
money your cat your dog your waffles
because you won't be needing that stuff
anyway right my point is that no one
knows what the world is gonna end no one
knows when your world is gonna end so
why worry about it that's why it's
cliche as it sounds you have to live
life to its fullest
so have a wonderful 2012 you'll be
seeing more of me and I promise you I
will see you in 2013 are you sure about
that or I'm making a song for you
visit my great
do you even know about yes you were it's
something bad
[Music]