hey guys soul I have been noticing that
my subscribers are over five million and
I'm a lot of you I've been asking to
Ryan where's your five million thank you
video I don't need you guys talk like
that I'm just trying to do a different
voice anyway the reason I haven't made
this video to now is because YouTube is
deleting a lot of YouTube accounts that
are inactive so technically I don't even
know if I have find it in yet either way
I wanted to thank you guys so much
please subscribe yesterday or five years
ago when I first started I truly
appreciate it seriously the bottom my
esophagus to the top of my sternum I
thank you guys so much I don't have a
weekly schedule like a lot of youtubers
but writing filming and editing a video
that I'm happy with these a lot longer
than you probably think and I don't have
a production company working for me in
fact this is what my production company
looks like here at the Ryan Eagle
production company we believe that we
are good take a look at our writers in
action no that's not funny beautiful one
of the most important parts of making a
right here production video is well the
filming take a look at our film team on
the ground terrific lastly but not
leastly we take you to the editing room
where all the magic happens and yet
we're having fun so come on down to the
Ryan Higa production company and your
video could look like this that's Ryan
he got production company where a real
production company and we make music
yeah maybe I should get a real
production company anyway I'm already
working on my next video here's a
preview to the ending of my next video
it might look something like that
day