either we have a special assignment that
only you can execute we believe that the
sins have already infiltrated the school
with Assassins of their own
we even agent on the inside we have a
new student name is uh I'm Josie I'm
Taylor
nice to meet you your mission is to pose
as a high school student and protect
Ella from impending threats do you wanna
get poison and that this is a new world
for you high school students are the
most dangerous and misunderstood
citizens that you will ever come across
I'm going to destroy you it's like
you've never made a friend before yeah
strange huh ha ha ha
who the hell are you I've been trying to
stay undercover but you are making this
too damn difficult
this is driving me insane
please just stay out of my life I just
wanted to ask if you would go to the
dance with me
where are they tell me where the
training wheels are