I was like rice do a pull-up and he
couldn't get off the ground
Alexson sprinted over there pick that
kid up by the neck with one hand girl
all right let's do the clappy claps hey
we're rolling this episode of off the
pill podcast is brought to you by
Skillshare Skillshare is an online
learning community with thousands of
amazing classes covering dozens of
creative and entrepreneurial skills you
can take classes in everything from
photography and creative writing to
design productivity and more so whether
you're returning a longtime passion
project challenging yourself to get
outside your comfort zone or simply
exploring something new skill shares
classes for you join the millions of
students already learning on skill shoot
today with a special offer just for my
listeners get two three months that's
right skill share is offering off the
pill listeners two months of unlimited
access to thousands of classes for free
to sign up go discuss or calm saga again
go to Skillshare calm slash good to get
your free months right now you can do it
go there and it'll make us look a lot
better if you guys sign up so again
secure comm Skillshare comm slash ego
make sure you use that link because it
shows them that you know you guys came
from here and you look a lot cooler
thank you welcome back to another
episode of off the bottom use ik to a
little bit see we had this yesterday but
anyway i'm ryan higa we have david choi
right here we got pocket lethal sitting
right here and we have a very special
guest mr. alex wasabi lu actually don't
know if I was supposed to see her really
last is that public info yeah people can
find it so for people who don't know
alex has over 4.2 billion total views
11.5 million subscribers on YouTube and
it was a channel that you actually
started with Roy
mmm-hmm who is what's his glob
squabble juice yeah he has his own
channel as well and you're still pretty
active mm-hmm I mean I mean I know at
one point you were doing
you're almost daily right yeah I was
doing daily you slow down yeah that was
just crazy
it was crazy yeah it was not worth it
like the numbers are way up but how long
did you keep that up for I think like
every day like yeah like six times a
week cuz I've missed days yeah okay well
what else is new we were just talking
about I don't know how us to bring it up
but you just had a little boxing match
I'm weird just talking about that so
it's weird because I want to read bring
that up though so you just had a boxing
match with I didn't know this with Busey
yeah it was far more as a sport I don't
know that's no they just told me right
before you got here yeah and I was like
oh I didn't even know that happened why
don't you tell me and apparently he did
but I I don't recall Ryan likes to
ignore me when I yeah but I mean so you
you boxed him where did that come from
so first like I used to like play around
and like train a little bit nothing
serious and then so I knew a little bit
about boxing and he said he wanted to
spar me on his live stream a long time
ago like a couple months ago I was like
all right so he's part of in his live
stream and I like just messing with him
a lot and he was doing horrible and so
then he trained a couple weeks and he's
like hey I've been training let's spar
again and I'm like okay let's far but
like you know sparring is like 70% you
go like 70% or 60 but when we both got
in there we just started swinging I
think I turned it up at the beginning
cuz I was like trying to keep him away
cuz I knew he was bigger and heavier and
he had the power heads he's big yeah
he's a big dude how much heavier is he
uh he likes to say he's 10 pounds
heavier but he's like 15 at least that's
unfair right I mean I mean if they're
just sparring yeah but you weren't
sporting we were that's like yeah were
you guys was there any like was it
called
trash-talker yeah I mean were you guys
like fighting like on friendly terms or
like oh yeah I mean was there some kind
of beef there no
there's no beef we were just fighting
for fun and then we both just kept
turning it up and then he started
swinging as hard as he could and he got
me because I didn't have any defense or
anything cuz I knew how to like throw a
punch but I didn't know how to dodge
dodge I didn't know how to like put
power in it I just knew like the basics
so you have like a any lasting effect
from that no big black did you black out
I didn't black out because like when you
get punched if you get knocked out yeah
you don't you don't feel it yeah it's
like wake up on the ground you're like
ah I must have lost I never got punched
that hard I was a little I was like
actually like a little foggy for like a
couple hours after but yeah other than
that there's nothing did you at any
point during the fight feel a little bit
of anger no but if I would have made it
past that big punch I would have been
like oh he's going 100% it's game time
but I didn't do you think Suzy was you
in that first round you were you're
punching him a lot and then the second
round he went to his corner and the
coaches were like hey okay he's keeping
you away just break through take the
punches and just get in there and just
get them and he did what did your corner
say my corner was just like he Dortch
doing like he can't do anything we
didn't expect him to come out like that
I was not prepared but now I mean I've
watched the footage I think I'm prepared
you learned from it yeah I think I'm
pretty good now because you said okay so
you guys box yeah and then you are you
sparred and then he trained after that
for sparring
yeah then this happened yeah now okay so
it's analogy yeah now I I'm down this
farm again
oh yeah I mean do you have more fear
since that has happened no I have more
awareness like I've watched the footage
a bunch of times I'm never gonna be like
this again and that's it like but I
think watching the footage once you see
what you did wrong just fixing himself I
mean that's a silly thing like he's so
much bigger than he is and it also
brings me to question
because you were talking hella trash
back in the day to guess I and I know
him he's huge he's way because I don't
know but he's huge gigantic man I don't
like 6:1 you're crazy like do you want
to get hurt like I could I think I could
put up a good match but he is heavier
like we know the thing is you could
probably tag him
yeah but I think I think if he tags you
once it's gonna hurt a lot yes arm
wrestle him basically two people two of
us arm wrestle him and we at the same
time yeah at the same time we couldn't
barely the same so freaking strong it's
crazy what do you mean at the same time
like we had well I had one arm and Derek
had the other arm and we just tried to
arm wrestle him and he'd like well he
Derek beat him but I lost him it took
like so long he's just so strong it's
okay how about since you know how strong
yeah I can arm wrestle you too okay
we'll do that at the end of the podcast
and I'll be like oh you know what maybe
okay wait so you think how much do you
think he weighs like 200 he's got to be
at least 200 I'm gonna say right thank
him and Logan fought at 190 so well how
much do you know there's no way he's 190
he's huge what are you what is your
weight right now right now I'm like 175
but do you cut to get there no I
actually been trying to put on weight
I'm usually at 170 naturally I'm gonna
guess their natural weight is like 200
something yeah but okay well youtuber
and influencers like fighting like I
love fighting but I'll never fight like
I mean I don't know how it's just fun
you get to get in there it's all on you
alright usually keep me up back at then
he's like hey let's go do this let's go
fight I was like no no you're so much
stronger than me like what the hell and
your help Helbig like I see your
Instagram post I'm like naturally I'm
like 160 like 160 okay I would say if
I'm in shape though I actually a little
heavier mm-hmm but naturally out like in
the 60s but I shouldn't be that heavy so
you think I'm too you're too big not me
I'm too small to go against ksi so I
think I think
if you I mean yeah you'd have to yell I
don't think I can both because you can't
like yeah it wouldn't worry he'll and
he's just naturally big dude yeah but so
is load about edgy I don't know actually
I've never met him I think I think
you're shorter and lighter yeah whatever
that's a good yeah I'm here to talk
trash to him I don't know I maybe one
day I don't actually train well even
like well you we were saying like even
like that even though it's like 15
pounds doesn't seem like a lot like 15
pounds of muscle like natural you know
build is a lot and it can be like
dangerous you know that's what you do
yeah I thought it was funny because um
during that time when all that was
happening like we talked I was like
saying the same thing I was like I'm not
gonna fight you dude you're way bigger
than I am and and then rice come hit me
up and he's like hey you one do this
that's not safety and that's not funny
then I look like a if I wait I'm a bad
guy if I lose it's embarrassing you know
he's like a lot I mean well maybe he's a
really good boxer I don't know he's
pretty good he's got the reach you know
but we were at my house one time you
boxed him no oh I was like right do a
pull-up and he couldn't get off the
ground
yeah first morgs now you maybe was
messing with you I know Alex can only do
two bullets do you have a prior fighting
or training experience like did you do
what did you do sports in high school no
you look like you play soccer actually
you're really good at basketball - yeah
that's it
I was lighting the boxing's I feel like
I'm potential yeah cuz I'll do like jab
steps and like the fakes and stuff see
like you know who would be a good match
actually I'm not for boxing basket boys
if he played keV good he's good he's
good and you guys are like same height
and like similar builds kids kids a
little skinnier right now but I don't
know I think that would be a good
matchup let's do it
and if he if he starts beating you you
just punch him and it turns into a
boxing match you know do that yeah but
um so I'm curious because you did a
little bit of boxing or at least
experimenting with in and stuff do you
like how much more respect in that
aspect do you have for like fighters
does that grow also when you're walking
around and you see people threatening
you oh well it's more yeah I've got a
lot of respect for fighters wait what do
you mean by three who's threatening who
just people step up or try to Punk Oh
cuz there's been a time where actually
have it we bring up this story here so
essentially so I used to work for Alex
and there's one VidCon where we were
walking back to our room yeah and in the
lobby near the elevators this one like
like black kid was like swinging this
girl around by her hair what yeah like
yeah she grabbed her by the hair and it
was like dragging her around and like
swing her around and I didn't notice
this at first we had another person with
us Kyle he's like hey stop that look and
I was like oh I was like cut that and
before I could finish cut that out Alex
it's printed over there pick that kid up
by the neck with one hand like up
against the wall and I was like how are
you that strong and then I got kicked
out of the hotel we're protecting a girl
well I think I've got a little gressive
yeah but he was literally swinging her
around that's a great that sounds a
little aggressive
I asked why later I went back to the
corrals why was he doing that as she
said because she threw water on his face
from her water bottle and he overreacted
well she probably shouldn't have done
that either
not the appropriate response yeah why
did she do that I don't know it was just
like 3:00 in the morning they were tired
mm-hmm
I guess picked up a person with one hand
maybe yes I don't know so poppy you
mentioned that you worked with Alex yeah
yeah it was him and Roy mm-hmm yeah are
you guys are you guys you guys are cool
right yeah okay a basketball like almost
every week every other week right it's
pretty good too right yeah Rose good
yeah I remember we played at the is a
thing I was like surprised and like oh
you actually know what he's doing he's
unpredictable yeah what he's about to do
pretty quick you might have answered
this a few times already quite a few
times but I don't really know the
history of you and Roy but I just
briefly know that you guys work together
you started something and then you you
broke apart he first started he made a
youtube channel and he had all his
friends come on and there's like there's
a bunch of us there's like eight of us I
think and we're just all friends or just
making silly videos and then the other
guys in the group decided to go talk to
girls or start doing sports and me and
Roy were like the normal things just
make more videos like Sonia Roy stayed
in it and then we did it for a few years
and then it took off and then we moved
here we just film in and doing stuff but
then as we got older we like both wanted
to do different things than what we were
doing but he wanted to go into gaming
and then eventually Interlake what he
does now and then I wanted to get more
lifestyle and more vloggy so we just
split up and then he's doing his own
thing and they're both doing good yeah
we still hang out do you feel like at
the point of separation though do you
feel like there's a lot of tension
between you guys and to the point where
you guys split apart yet to have that
space and then that space created that
that absence created fondness and that's
kind of like how I actually think we're
better friends now then we were back
then because it's not work
yeah when we see each other we're not
like we don't have a schedule we're just
like there to play basketball or they're
out of
and just hang out and talk so yeah it
took a while but it's I think it's
better now yeah so you're you're living
right now with your brother yeah I'm
with my brother and Matt my man but
you're so your brother is also he makes
videos too right yeah yeah and he's like
pretty popular how much how many
subscribers does he have over a million
for sure yeah yeah and okay so oh I
didn't know he was doing it that long
five years that's that's a long time
he's yeah he's been her own he's been
doing it we live I just got a new house
oh yeah yeah he's moving with me and
Matt's moving with me and then JP all
right on so okay and my mom sometimes
she's there so but we're with your
brother you know there's a with a lot of
YouTube stuff you know there's always
speculation and shipping between people
and people like ship yeah
shipping it ship him with the naming of
the RonRon or whatever and stuff and
then recently you started to do videos
with her sister Oh what Vanessa
me yes I said yeah I saw you wrote
something on Twitter I don't know where
it was but you're like my fake
girlfriend yeah like that so what is
that about everybody was shipping us
together all the time and were like so
let's just play into it instead of like
being like no no let's just so your
brother is being shipped with Veronica
and you're bitching so like whoever if
this were to happen whoever were to get
married first is like incestual cuz like
you know I'm saying I always wonder what
that like if you were a your brothers
are to marry each other that's incest
like that's your step as true of your
step something but like you see like
sometimes twins will marry other sway no
but like whoever gets married first
you're like marrying your family but
like exact same
I'm a great question yeah I mean no no
we have to find some twins at hairy
twins okay so I mean where does that
stem from any truth like do you guys
have anything going on oh I would have
never had anything going on like I guess
we've been flirting before but never on
line like four cameras or just flirty
people Wow right it's just like this is
how we talked so I don't know we started
I made a music video like she's my fake
girlfriend now she's my fake
ex-girlfriend so I made a video like
sneaking into my fake ex-girlfriends
birthday party
but it's obvious that we're died but
yeah they can tell that it's obvious but
they still were like maybe would you
date her I would bring this up cuz uh
there was a I think at a convention
awhile ago or something someone said if
you were to date three youtubers or
something who would it be and she was
one that you mentioned I believe and the
other two was Ryan yes remember the
collab we did in Vegas ed you Flo
yeah yeah basically will you fight me or
whatever yeah all the comments just gay
gay the point of the joke but like yeah
we have our own we have our own ship
going on yeah wait who are the other
ones though Vanessa a Youtube way this
was a long time ago but I do remember
the Nessa the name was one of them okay
so I have to list three YouTube girls I
would date it you guys have to do it too
I would think of him but I can't really
he doesn't know
damn I was a lot he keeps me up to date
actually put it out there are you dating
right now though yeah you know with
someone right now you're just beating
what kind of girls what kind of girls
are you into half-asian Pappas really oh
like you're selling you yeah you love
yourself that's why a lot of a couple
they look similar very very true yeah
yeah wait so you're you really did
you're you're like set you like half
asian
I like half whatever half anything so
like I like exotic oh I like mixes like
exotic like it's like what is you what
about is yeah
what about mixes do you do you like it's
nice to look or just a uniqueness and
the exotic know how those are
good-looking usually they're it always
ends up like an interesting combo like
they have like Asian eyes but they look
white it's very like different I think
there's something when I first maybe I
didn't know you were part Asian to be
honest oh yeah some people in in like
elementary school people I guess I
didn't settle into my Asian this yet and
they just thought I was a white dude
again your bad Filipino have felt you
don't have your mom is just ripping away
I've seen you post oh I had no idea
there were so many Filipinos and you
guys you and Roy grew up in North
Carolina yeah we did yeah there's a lot
communities everywhere yeah it's just
nice like there is like so there was a
lot of us but like when we got together
there's alone and then in my class I was
like the only Asian in every class yeah
it's like magnet suit because there may
not be a lot but they somehow find
themselves coming together type of thing
I heard I don't know if this is true or
not but in Charlotte that there's a lot
of racism towards Asians there is that
true um I don't know it's like well have
you experienced racism growing up not
actually because I would ask Roy because
you hope yeah yeah we uh the school I
went to was like 80% african-american
temporarily or maybe like 70% African
20% Caucasian and then 10% miscellaneous
like you know god Roy do you think that
contributed to why you guys stay on
YouTube I don't know maybe possibly
sounds I mean that's kind of sounds like
me and Sean honestly like kind of like
losers yeah yeah we didn't go out like
you know to parties and stuff that we
didn't like do bad thing but we're
drinking is a little kids and we just
made stay at home made videos yeah
bored I didn't have a car like where am
I gonna go let's make a video town even
when we had a car we stayed home yeah we
were losers okay
well that's interesting yeah
how do you I have a question yeah
brought to you by ninja milk what's your
question I'd be a good match for do you
know anybody Vanessa
actually yeah well let me ask you this
what kind of girls are you into besides
besides the physical hapa look like what
kind of person I think cares about the
look that's all that matters
numbers no matter personality no matter
how many people I know it means I know
that a passion or they're like working
toward something hmm like and they're
not like making excuses like they're
just they're like doing it they got
Drive yeah and so like that they always
they're like oh do this I'm like oh girl
and then do you like do you like when
the girls have more energy or more
they're more like reserved I like funny
so like I don't care as long as they
make me laugh it's what type of funny
goofy funny
dry funny goofy witty witty funny
jokester yeah not afraid to look stupid
but also like smart too yeah hmm Vanessa
gosh I don't really know they're like
three times yeah I don't know your other
two like you didn't okay the other two
[Music]
[Laughter]
on the spot I can just go back to other
things and I mean let's go back to your
content because a lot of your content
you know it is lifestyle and a lot of
times it will be about girls or you'll
have a lot of like girls in your videos
and you're aware that you know it can
bring views mm-hmm and what is your
thought process when constructing video
ideas you know because uh you're talking
about you know trying to come up with
like better ideas and that's always
thing you're trying to top yourself in a
way so I guess well it's just like
just whatever go is going on in my life
you'll see it on the vlog so I don't
have much going on or if I'm like not
motivated you can tell it's bad but when
I am motivated I'll make videos and
they're better and like this or like
that but a lot of people think I make
videos because about love and about
girls about cute stuff because my fans
like that and they do like that but
that's not the reason I'm making it it's
because I really am always looking for
love I'm always on the search for the
ones like hey there you are
done that I'd be happy then ever every
videos about her yeah I mean it would be
yeah my life with a revolver on whenever
I find the one my life is gonna revolve
around her you're a romantic
yeah so you're really into uh I'm
guessing you like romance films like not
straight romance movies cause you watch
the old book i watch like we're gonna
take comedy rom-com yeah action romance
never just romance you see why there's
nothing wrong with that you ever watch
The Notebook
okay I do ask the notebook for a walk to
remember a lot of people will say like
love will find you like when you're not
searching you know when you're waiting
but I also think it's difficult for you
because liger you're like you're a very
attractive guy objectively and oh but
anyways you're um you're an objectively
like very attractive person you know and
you're very charismatic so I'm sure a
lot of girls are very infatuated with
you they're interested they want to get
to know you more so you have to like go
through and like weed them out tough
problem man you're almost like la la
girl's frustrating because I've heard
that was that they always want something
more early want something else or like
they want
oh why don't you tell ventually they're
always like why don't you tag me in that
story oh you should post this picture of
I don't like girls don't tell me what to
post so the ulterior motives yeah like
they know like they enjoy like I'm sure
they and we have fun together but then
they're also like keeping an eye on like
I could get numbers yeah I'm this too so
make me Bert there you go how many
girlfriends serious girlfriends have you
had okay I'm sure you've dated a lot but
let me think okay serious serious I
would count so over a year there's one
high school doesn't count that she
doesn't calendar okay so there's Vanessa
Shanna Daniela
on glass they don't know they don't
watch me Loren's the the youtuber we
yeah yeah at the most recent
she's a hispanic youtuber no I didn't
I've never heard of her either but we we
met up and then it was awesome how long
was that too much issue unless there's a
quick quick one with Lauren for a little
bit three years is that your longest
yeah as a long time your shortest is two
months I think so
probably but that two months was magical
mm-hmm would you say everything has been
magical though for you because you're
such a hopeless romantic you might
romanticize that you age I do I every
time I'm in a relationship they're
always like man it's like a movie and
I'm like I know
I'll run outside just cuz it's raining
and she'll chase me I'll do it like I'll
show up I'll be like what would they do
it over the cheesy dream guy that girls
love yeah yeah what would you say is the
biggest lesson you learned about
yourself and about what you like from
your past relationships oh that's a deep
one what's the biggest thing I learned
about myself
is I I realized that I go for the
perfect girl but there's no perfect girl
like everybody's gonna have problems or
everybody's gonna be different so you
have to adapt you can't just find
somebody perfect for you you gotta find
somebody and then you guys gotta adapt
together and become the perfect person
so that's what was the second part of
the question weight in terms of what you
like in a girl what you I guess what you
don't like you know because the more you
date the more girlfriend's you have the
more you kind of refine what what you
want yourself and then what you want in
the other person yes well people they're
always like why are you always dating
youtubers oh wait the last three like
the last two were youtubers and then
like girls I dated they're uh they're
often youtubers gotcha because they're
just like I just vibe with them because
they're like funny and like they're
witty and they're quick and it's like
they're ready for camera all the time
yeah yeah they don't understand your
struggles like oh like uploading times
yeah doing well the algorithm and like
I'm on my phone tweeting or Instagram
they know I'm working yeah even though
like somebody's not a youtuber doing
that it's not working does it cross your
mind that like you know I'm sure it does
to a certain degree where it's like man
we can help each other too in our work I
mean like being together being in a
relationship oftentimes it helps your
career as well on YouTube right yeah or
does it take it does it take away it's
just difficult to because then like it
blurs the line whether it's for YouTube
or right it's real exactly I'm kind of
trying to get out right now like how
does that affect how has it affect your
previous relationships it it doesn't
really affect me as much but I've had
exes where they're like oh why are you
filming this
or like I'll take them on a vacation and
I'm blocking it and they're like why you
vlogging and I'm like because like it's
not because it's good for views but if
we're going on this awesome trip why not
film it like we're two fights yeah
because of that I get that yeah all
right one that berries dark no we're
gonna take a quick break and we'll be
right back
[Music]
this episode of off the peel podcast is
brought to you by a Skillshare
Skillshare is an online learning
community with thousands of amazing
classes covering dozens of creative and
entrepreneurial skills you can take
classes and everything from photography
free of writing design productivity and
more for me personally I just don't even
ever it really checked out was the film
and video one but I thought that was
pretty cool so whether you're returning
to a long time passion project
challenging yourself to get outside your
comfort zone or simply exploring
something new Skillshare has classes for
you like I said there's a lot more than
what I mentioned but that's the only one
I checked out so I can't vouch for all
of them you guys can join millions of
students already on Skillshare today
with a free two months actually if you
guys use our link and that is Skillshare
comm slash Higa make sure you guys use
that link because it makes it list it
makes us look a lot better and it makes
us look cool to Skillshare so use
Skillshare comm slash EAGA and it'll
help us a lot so thank you guys sign up
get you two free month's Skillshare comm
Sachiko and we're back
we're just talking about your muscles
yes no I mean we're saying they call you
you got jack'd recently what's your
what's your training regimen is it just
boxing well I mean I tried a box but
it's more lifting so like I've been
lifting which everybody tells me if you
spar again it's gonna make you a lot
slower it's more slower could it make
you like you could be a little bit
slower but not that one's slower from
lifting cuz I'm just too skinny I need
to get some size you're actually not
that skinny though I mean like I was
saying you got a lot bigger but maybe
that is maybe that is making you slower
mm-hmm I don't know phousi was I mean
he's a big dude he's a big dude but I
should have seen that guy have you ever
been in a fight outside of this this
boxing uh no not really cuz like I've
been in like we puffed our chests so
we're like push each other and I'm ready
like we're ready to go but then
something will break it up or my mom
will be like style
hey when was this in your household my
brother like started like something like
it gets stopped or like any fight I get
stopped even at a club like I've had
people kicked out before but good but
it's cuz like they're trying to come in
to my table or something and then the
bouncer will grab them so right it never
escalated past that but I don't I don't
want it to escalate past that I don't
think I've ever been in that scenario
you've been like the whole pushing thing
never ever
well I punched a girl in the stomach
once as a kid but that's it I was in
kindergarten she cut the line okay
actually in kindergarten one time I was
a girl no but I slapped that girl's butt
Wow I didn't know it was a sexual thing
I was a door holder and I took my job
very good job mate yeah and no and like
you have to run ahead of the line hold
the door and then when the last rows out
you got to go to the next door hold the
door so I got there and this one girl
was dilly dally and hard and at the end
I was like come on and pop and then she
hurried up and I was like done and then
I like ran to the next door my teacher
guy was like don't ever do that and I
was like I'm sorry I just didn't want to
miss the next door I didn't know and I
didn't know yeah now I would never do
that
unless she was really dilly dallying
[Laughter]
how'd you do in school when you were
young so bad yeah high school too
all school any school not for me I was
doing bad I got FS and DS detention
nearly past yeah I shouldn't have passed
there's a lot of times get on you for
that they're like oh he's making videos
so that'll be his career no they were
like before it took off they're like you
should focus on school and then it's
about it yeah what's it like proved to
be worse in the beginning it wasn't I
mean I remember when you guys we were
doing lip sings are on the same time and
obviously you can't monetize those even
when they became I don't know when
monetizes monetization Kames about 2008
or so yeah but I did I was late on that
train on oh boy you
no I was late - we actually found out
because of you oh really
yeah so we were in North Carolina and
there was like nobody back then YouTube
wise so we're just doing our thing like
we don't know anything about anything
low quality videos not using lights
whatever yeah and people watching and
then one day my dad was like hey I just
saw this article and that Ryan guy is
getting paid by YouTube for his videos
and I was like what and then here's a
yeah you got a sign up for his Adsense
thing you know we did and we start
getting paid what what year was that do
you remember oh it was like oh yeah
there's a lot right cuz you guys stopped
for a little bit right
we stopped cuz he went to college right
college and then I was like I want to
keep making videos and then he was like
okay let's start again
so he started yeah I remember when you
guys started up yeah and then and then
it just got crazy and it hasn't stopped
yet yeah how do you feel do you feel the
burn out yeah yeah yeah I think I've
gotten past the burn out but now I'm
just looking for like a new motivation
right and it's I'm I'm waiting for the
one is so funny I know it's not even
like a YouTube character literally a TV
show like that's like like the premise
for most TV shows the guy who was just
looking for a girl yeah everything else
is secondary yeah yeah how i met your
mother basically yeah would you ever
date a fan yeah have you no I don't
think so oh I actually did this one girl
one time and we became boyfriend
girlfriend like three months in she told
me she's watch my videos and she's
little that's weird but at that point it
does it didn't matter right and she
could have been just scared that she
didn't oh I should have said the first
date oh I didn't say the second date
yeah he's like man I got to tell him at
some point yeah after you fell in love
yeah she's like do it well talking about
being burnt out and like you know
looking for the one but you're also
still focusing on your career you're
looking towards other things to do
because I know recently you're on Hulu
show right you were also on
voiceover actor for Nickelodeon yeah
came out recently are the Hulu show
called light as a feather or I just I
had little parts in that and then I was
the voice of a character and a new
Nickelodeon show that just came out
Sunday and it's every Sunday well middle
school mobile so on Nickelodeon yeah oh
it's awesome I know they send in a self
tape and I looked at the script and it
said Filipino are a middle school for
geniuses and I was like all right and
the character looks like me it was crazy
I've never had them animate Maya's crazy
ways to like a cartoon it's weird I've
always said you had an interesting voice
though yeah so it's that's probably good
that could be a good route for you and
look you're doing what you got into a
genius school maybe not you but your
voice with these NFC kids there's still
hope
[Laughter]
yeah that's not very sterile yeah that's
the white side yeah I was just like not
obedient you didn't care
yeah so like I would be super class
clown mm-hmm like all the time and the
teacher would be laughing while writing
me a detention slip like on see yeah so
you had a gift and you knew you had a
gift yeah I was Roy I was Roy because
you guys were just go together right he
was like yeah it is moments where he
would be like oh like do something crazy
but it was more like on the quiet side I
don't know why I just figured he would
be like super into his studies he was
really smart yeah yeah he had no problem
with school mm-hmm I would be the kid
that waited before class every morning
for the bell to ring and then slide in
like a secret agent on my side everyday
funny when I was like 13
funny Johnny you would be if tick tock
was around you'd be huge
it was fun and my teacher would always
be like wow you almost missed you almost
made it later likes it I'm like I know
sir that was a close one every morning
what was your uh the third thing that
was coming out for you though
Oh escape tonight I did escape tonight
again no all-star one that's so fun that
was Joey's stinger yeah Joey's thing
yeah it's like where's that on it's on
that YouTube premiere yeah okay what is
that about what is the so basically it's
a it's a live-action escape room so
everything's set up but we don't know
what's gonna happen so well like put a
key in a wall and then like all these
Cowboys will run in on like horses and
back Pio Pio Pio I guess this is a
cowboy episode or like Oh pirates like
all right like we freaked out and it was
super cool because they had like real
monster actors from like Walking Dead
calm and play these monsters and they
would chase us and we said this is real
it's like yes it's not like scripted no
oh dude this whole time it's scripted
but not for the cast like we don't
recommend right but they know what's
gonna happen when we do this this is
gonna happen when we do this this
unlocks mm-hmm so it was cool I know how
do people get voted off or they die you
die usually compete and die yeah got it
yeah
it's fun a lot of youtubers in that is
there anyone that you want to spill the
tea about who's the most diva youtuber
you've met on the on the season just in
general you know a lot that's why you
met where they're both on the show yeah
that's kinda I mean that's kind of like
the new yeah it's not like a bad thing
anymore it's almost like oh that's what
kids are into yeah he's the kind of diva
kind of like you know showing off we
just have to be there we had to be there
from 5:00 p.m. until like 5:00 a.m. like
for a week no that's crazy so people
will show their true colors in that time
and people some people can't handle all
of it so that at like 3:00 a.m. they
just become super diva or like they just
get super irritated even though we're
all going through the same thing some of
us complained and some of us just it was
like whatever we're on she that is a
long time though it is like back-to-back
at that time you go home go to sleep get
back at like 5:00 again yeah I could see
I could see a lot of people getting
irritated by that so but Joey was great
joey is like he just remain calm the
whole time he never got frustrated or he
got first with other people but like he
kept it professional and he checked on
people even some of them the people that
were acting like divas are being crazy
he would be like okay what do you need
okay I'll help you
mm-hmm even though the rest those are
like just irritated yeah I mean is his
project or yeah yeah yeah that's um
that's some crazy hours how are you yeah
I mean we're you did you get frustrated
and were you like diva-ish
no I just got annoyed people that were
complaining because I'm like we're all
in this together all of our feet hurt
all of our backs hurt everybody's cold
well I'm glad I didn't do it than the
acid I'm gonna do it every time you ask
me I'm gonna do it yeah I'm gonna see
what the hours are first yeah it's cool
I did I thought it was actually out
filming this I didn't want to do it no
it's fun like you're in there with
everybody and everybody real yeah okay
everybody's confused nice yeah you
should try out the I feel like escape
rooms you try out the saw escape room we
just did it in Vegas how was it it's
pretty cool man it was like it was not
what I was expecting it's a long
experience I'm horrible this gabriel's
all really yeah after like 20 minutes my
ADHD kicks in and I'm just more of a
burden on the group like I bring
everybody down that's kind of me too
actually guys come look at this it's so
cool so I looks like we got some fan
questions here mm you ready I think so
so here's one from believe Alex mmm how
do you deal with the recent hate you got
from the ksi army mmm so maybe maybe
give us a little background on what yeah
what does that mean Yusef phousi sparred
case I reacted to it and he made an
entire video about me oh he's my biggest
fan and he told all his fans to go to my
Instagram and comment cloud emojis so
like I had like a thousand comments on
my newest picture and then he
he commented that and it got over like
150,000 comments of clowns Wow so after
the next day I was like what should I do
and then so I put a change the caption
after 150,000 people commented and said
comment if you're my biggest fan coming
clown so now they're all like go no to
retracted a lot of great a lot of the
comments are like oh he got us this time
but we'll get on I'm sure your
engagement did well on that big so why
why did he call you a clown just cuz I
challenged him before yeah yeah asked
what so why um where is this I mean I
know there's history between you two we
had ksi on I don't think he'd he
mentioned demons Alex I don't think so
yeah he didn't really mention it but um
I know I couldn't remember if there was
actual like dislike there or if it was
just like an internet thing well where's
that stem from you and ksi why is that a
thing I remember is it because you said
you want to fight him but it wasn't in
like a bad way like you were yeah I
don't know I just I think I wanted to
spar and then I I think just the way
they go about talking about things or
like doing things and just makes me mad
cuz like makes you mad it makes me mad
cuz like they're just like they they're
not classy about anything they're more
like I would stomp you in the crowd or
like you're whatever and then I'm just
like oh I just want to spar guys so then
it got into it and then Deji started
commenting on the breakup with me and
Lauren and then Lauren got mad it got
personal
yeah I saw Lauren get mad and that
triggered me to get mad and I was trying
not to but once you see your girl or
like the love of your life at the time
get mad that you're so you have to jump
in so it was real anger and hate then I
don't know it's gotta be cuz I mean you
seem like I did I thought it was you
guys were just doing a thing like you
know I really didn't know we asked kiss
that same thing with his whole thing
with Mugen and he actually said we asked
him could you ever be friends with Logan
no he said he could be friends with
Logan he thinks in the future how it
would never be friends with Jake he
genuinely hates him what yeah strange
but I was wondering the same thing with
you do you think you and
yes I could ever be homies yeah I think
I think if we all if we ever saw each
other in person like me cuz I'd edgy
whoever like everybody's fine with each
other just online it's just there's like
oh hey you don't like no I don't I don't
hate anybody
I probably dislike nobody I don't know I
don't hate anybody like nobody it's all
in person I would be like I don't want
to see you or I don't want to be in the
same room or are there people in your
past that you know on your come up that
kind of like talk down to you or Roy and
you're like I'm gonna show them and I
guess when you got to that point did you
feel like oh yeah like I'm better than
them or you kind of just like you let it
go cuz you're like I'm too busy with the
kind of thing yeah I mean I never got
inspired by haters so like I did have
friends in high school that were like
like all the guys that were in wasabi
that left to go talk to girls in sports
they super regretted it they all they
probably all have asked me to if I could
hire them to do something like after
college they're like can I be your
assistant can I do this I don't like oh
man I can't then I had to move you out
here then at the Patriot shelter where
you gonna live who's gonna your shelter
like oh yeah I don't have money so then
I'm like I can't I have to focus on this
so I don't know I I don't think I ever
was like ah in your face yeah so are you
gonna box ksi I would take cuz is dead
GE I don't think he's fighting is he I
don't see me to do my research but I
don't know either from what I saw
Logan's boxing ksi and the under cards
all real boxers yeah like real fights
not that you guys are in real fights but
like actual professional boxers which is
interesting and I kind of like that what
their explanation is like they want to
expose you know real boxing to a
different audience yeah I think that's
cool but like I don't know where I don't
know anything else about like where
everyone else is fighting I don't even
know when you and phousi fought like I
don't know about that that was like note
involved for me at all was just having
fun and let's go see what happens
but I would box Deji cuz he's not
training for anything I think I could
take him like I don't think did you ever
call did you call him out yet no I don't
know that's someone you wanna fight I
would yeah oh it's borrowed edgy well I
don't know if I would do it in an event
it'd just be for fun anyone else you
want to spar um Ryan but he said no if I
if I like took some classes and stuff
and you like taught me I would I'll do
it I'm not like to like knock each other
out but like it was just for fun yeah
yeah I'll do it
yeah just for fun to be calling him out
right now I mean I have to learn you
gotta teach me how to do it first
you had an all-time low actually spot
right now as if it was like giving me
cuz then I you can use boxing and then I
can use but it'd be interesting I mean
are you guys like I guess he's bigger
than me I think a little bit taller and
that's the only reason I'm heavier we
weight-wise know he's also more muscular
there's how much more power I haven't
been working well I just started working
on again so I'm probably gonna lose
weight 175 early 176 now yeah I've never
been in the seventies now what's your
height five eight oh yeah we're like
pretty close to the 510 I'm six foot are
you really yeah that's the only reason
I'm heavier is cuz that's four inches no
it's because you have like a lot of
muscles and stuff oh yeah well with that
being said make sure you guys go and
check out Alex's muscles he post some
very nice pictures of itself I'm like I
always like man dude I that could have
been me if I worked out yeah well I mean
you look good and it's great and I'm
looking forward to your your next fight
I guess yeah I'll let you know generally
like a couple days before yeah and if we
ever spar well I'm sure we'll make some
kind of announcement
yeah just for fun with that being said
you can follow Alex at
yeah what are you uh on everything yeah
Twitter Instagram Twitter Instagram
lobby do you have any other projects
that you want to plug March whatever I
have merge coming out on Thursday nice
listen me it comes out like monthly I
have this already be it already
yeah yeah perfect so you go check
awesome well you can follow us at off
the pill on Twitter at off the pill
podcast and Instagram and with that
being said how we end these is we just
breathe into the mic oh we can do that
too if you want
well let's bring into the mic and then
we'll do it all right in three two one
all right all right we got changed this
angle then we have Alex wasabi and Ryan
Higa
first official first official arm
wrestling it looks like both biceps are
flexing Alex as you lead he's on your
marks get set go one two one
well he wasn't he's hurt although I will
say this hurt yeah all right now you
guys get injured gotta fight together
yes I'll throw laughs yeah so yeah ksi
stronger I'm sorry he's he was like a
rock it's it was crazy
I couldn't even it was crazy okay okay
yeah yeah fight Dungey okay I don't know
if that's a thing but he's gonna fight
[Laughter]