dude stop pushing so hard that's why you
keep getting hemorrhoids remember Yugi
when you start to stutter go ahead and
calm down and take it slow time to do
duel very good just hope credited Mon
and now the peloton where a local man is
found guilty of animal cruelty no
comment what about the threesome with
you Brock and Misty hey that's always
just broke Oh Sasuke what oh did you
just call me sausage that's not even a
good joke no no sorry the script must
have auto corrected Sasuke - sausage no
it's just going to hurt you Naruto but
now I'm going to kill you hey yourself
are you gonna do it or shut up okay you
have any idea how hard it is for me to
remember all this I mean do you really
have to do all that sign language I mean
we already have subtitles shut up okay
sorry geez
seriously how much longer you know it
was done can you just let me finish fine
just hurry okay no where was I they can
find them it's cool that they put us in
this magazine and all but I don't really
appreciate how they photoshopped the
Sailor Mona I mean I know you're the
leader and all but I was wondering maybe
we could switch plans for this year yeah
we should do that what do you know
Sailor Jupiter we've been through this
the planets represent who we are I want
to be Sailor Moon you're too big to be a
moon you're the biggest one that's why
you're Jupiter oh you [ __ ] I'm so
punches and Sailor Saturn you're the
only one that can hula hoop here I said
I know hula I never say you're not gonna
hula hoop a little bit I can switch your
Saturn oh because you have to be Mars
you're the manliest one and men are from
Mars well men are from Mars then women
have to be from Venus and Sailor Venus
don't look very womanly actually that
saying is wrong what women aren't from
Venus hermaphrodites are in matha types
you mean people with both parts yeah a
penis and a vagina how do you know wanna
switch planets I'm proud to have a
vagina penis I'm proud to have a penis
well why can I be Sailor Moon I'm moon
just as many people as you do yeah but I
keep my shorts on Sailor Uranus are
useless can I not be to do any more guys
oh yeah not part of the group hey you
guys know your arm beds
girls right what is that supposed to
mean no no I just meant that girls fight
a lot and guys don't yeah I mean but we
just use our fists not away you're
looking for strength you are looking for
a strong blade if you're looking and
stronger than you've ever been before
without all that
Oh Oh what
yeah your shoelaces are untied he almost
fell and uh hit these bricks top hey
thanks man
that's really nice yeah yeah one punch
man are you supposed to be one punch man
yeah I can pretty much defeat any anime
hero with one punch every anime hero
yeah oh not too sure what I could do
with that I guess I could paint an arrow
on your head you can look like a
delivery oh thank god sign here remember
ordering anything but wait I don't think
I ordered this from Bleach right yeah
yeah that was for you I don't even know
what these are what are these like
colored rocks it says here that they're
rocks but it's a French brand so it's
not color it's coal or rocks
what's Clorox bleach
what leave what are you doing here
just dragonballs say hey men once with
all the commotion shoes keep coming
untied no matter how hard time now I got
the perfect thing for you what is that
it's a tack how is that gonna help me
tighten my shoe just stick it in your
shoe laces and it gets tighter so attack
the Titan
oh cool this fairytale shirts only $9.99
I guess you could say it's some pretty
fair retail you suck okay you know what
the bad puns already okay I get it
one punch man okay you make puns very
funny I get actually I'm not one punch
man anymore what this square root of
four what I don't get it I'm for root
punch
seriously fruit punch that's the best
you can do see okay oh you really did go
too far you can't make that joke you're
Asian I know that's why now I'm punching
okay you really did just cross the line
on that one actually I'm uh I'm still on
it look enough is enough already
aren't you supposed to be one punch just
one pun how many puns have you made
already I don't know anywhere from one
to a ton what see I tricked you you
crossed a too many pun for one video
line and now you can't make anymore you
know I can finally ahead in this video
without a dumped on me you didn't say
that was the room well it is you crossed
the line so you can't make any more
funds if you say so yes I do but just so
I'm clear this line represents the last
part of the video right yeah so
technically then this line is kind of
like the line that I'm seeing right now
what because it's the last punch line
the thing guys again so much for
watching if you want to see bloopers and
behind the scenes clicked on the left if
you want to see last week's video click
top on the right and if you want to see
a video similar to this you can watch
Christmas songs in real life I believe
the name was by clicking the one on the
bottom
the one in the bottom