all right who's first me you can call me
Sam Uncle Sam okay almost time let's see
what you got Uncle Sam Uncle Sam dude
Uncle Jim
uncle Chet's the unconscious Uncle Jim
Uncle Sam and I'll coach it to Uncle Sam
and uncle chip look at my fate babe boy
look like I have faulty like an animal
what the hell was that I was dancing
pong was that dancing it was kind of you
and you get out next yes Duke I'm here
to answer you guys I hope you guys like
don't worry I saw this guy dance before
he's really good
oh you better be good pong because if
he's not I'm living of that drawing you
made for me this morning
hi I'm Vanessa and I'll be doing my
routine five six seven eight give me a
big B II give you get the hell out of my
office next what what what what are you
doing here what do you make it's my last
time we just saw you five minutes ago
no that was my twin brother Uncle Sam
who doesn't have the moustache like
money you're clearly the same person
you're wearing the same clothes what L
mean my brother's not as handsome as me
what's that one next I don't need that
girl in my life I don't this is a dance
audition oh you're right right okay I
don't need that girl in my life I don't
need that girl my son get out I'm gonna
do the dancing
hi we're here for the audition whatever
Wow
that was that was amazing stunning that
was incredible so beautiful you guys are
exactly what we don't need I don't need
you we wanted a third member not forth
nothing good comes in fours
you know what comes of course squares
well think one of you one of us well we
don't y'all way
look at those stupid bumblebee office I
don't even know what that is hmm you
call yourself a crew you'll never be a
crew
you shut your dirty mouth ray don't
listen to them as long as we believe in
each other right I don't believe in you
but I believe in you twice as much who
are you are you here for the audition
you ready mmm thanks ray this is the
best day ever
hey you guys like ice cream
there's a birthday at mature design
right guy
yes Gavin this my this isn't what I'm
here that anything