hey guys so the Super Bowl is right
around the corner how did he know and
I'm pretty excited this year but I'm not
gonna lie I haven't always growing up I
was never the biggest football fan for
those of you that don't live in the u.s.
I don't mean this kind of football or
this kind of football or even these kind
of footballs that I'm talking about this
kind of football that's when I was
younger I never enjoyed watching
football but for some reason all of my
friends seem to obsess over
I was just that kid that wanted to fit
in whenever my friends would watch it
[Applause]
wait something my Twitter
hold hold in one head headshot
let's go 49ers yeah but wouldn't you
lick foot bar now one of the best parts
of the Super Bowl has got to be the
commercial I feel like that's the one
part that everyone looks for guys girls
moms dads grandpa's grandma's cats
platypuses Latta pie cactuses cacti well
this year something big happened to me
Fester Jesus I pretty much got a call
and well let me just show it to take a
look yes yes no no that that's perfect
I'm gonna thank you so much okay bye
dude I just got asked to audition for a
Super Bowl commercial account man
Wonderful Pistachios wants me to
audition for them and send in a taint
way.this Wonderful Pistachios
yes this wonderful procession - that's
freaking awesome man how do you how do
you have that bag I'm holding it right
here continuity continuity
anyway that's awesome that what you have
to do well you see kids all they wanted
me to do was send in a regular audition
tape reading a few lines but I thought
I'd give them a little bit more well
they want me to record myself reading a
few lines but I want my audition to
stand out so I think I'm gonna add just
a little bit more and so I did
hey Ryan go along
[Music]
oh wait hold on what continuity
well that's my call a Wonderful
Pistachios Wonderful Pistachios get
crappy Ryan could I have some of those
pistachios if you pick writing go you
can enter some too
yes I understand sir okay thank you
there's Senna got it no way yeah they
said that they liked it so much they
just might air my audition tape as the
commercial of the state money to it that
is friggin amazing yeah the only way
it's not gonna happen is if they find
the better and more popular Asian in the
next day or so you see kids back in the
day there weren't very many popular
agents in entertainment why do you keep
talking to us yeah we don't even know
yeah we're not your kids and that's when
I realize kids that I did not have kids
you can't freeze-frame whilst you're
telling us the story we're not actually
in the story so but I totally could you
see kids I'm telling you a story about
me telling a story about how your kids
either that was the worst episode apart
never mmmm I know so can you please put
the game back on fine see I told you
we're gonna miss the third quarter if we
change the channel just to watch check
it out in from pistachios get cracking
that was so good thinking the exact same
they not understand why don't you take
your audition if that whole scenario
happened in that how I never met your
mother episode and how do we just watch
that commercial outside of the show and
how did I even audition in that reality
when I'm here in this one
and that's pretty much the whole story
of how I almost got a commercial but I
did it because of psy or so I thought
you see kids