we are in focus okay here we go hey guys
I don't know why I always start videos
like this is like the natural thing when
you're on YouTube everybody says hey
guys no they don't say that I see that
penny a new intro starting from next
year all the vlogs are gonna start with
uh yo oh that's so bad other people say
yo what up yo yo yo yo yo yo up y'all I
don't know why I'm going gangster yo
Chico superwoman everybody that's a
little racist hey guys wondering Moodle
sup lamps nope what if what if I started
all my videos with the teehee nobody
would expect that and then I end it with
hey guys that would be weird
I'll figure something out anyway hey
guys so I've never really done one of
these videos before but last year we
kind of did one for psych for my higatv
channel my second channel I just want to
do something to just close the year I'm
in a while you guys know at the end of
the year I always try and make you know
at least one really big video and it
always like it ties up all my time and I
always want to make this video but I
never get the chance to while I have the
chance and I have a spare moment today
I'm gonna I decided I'm gonna make this
video before I have no time but before
we get to like the best of moment I just
want to talk to you guys directly and
say uh thank you guys so much can
honestly say 2015 was a great year a lot
of you guys already know but like a
couple years ago I was I was going
through a really rough stretch and doing
this for like eight years nine years now
and I was you know eventually it gets to
you coming up with a new thing every
single week is not eating I was
literally going crazy for a little bit
you know I was worried about saying
things that would offend people is
worried about doing too many blogs like
this because more people want the skits
and when I do too many skits more people
want the vlogs like I was just stressing
myself out way too much worried about
what everybody else wanted except for
myself but this year from the beginning
of the year I just decided that I'm
gonna let go of all of it I just went
back to my roots and created videos that
I wanted to create videos that nobody
liked I made videos that were offensive
to be my main videos that you know we're
30 minutes long that is probably the
stupidest decision you could ever make
on YouTube because for one who's gonna
sit through that but even doing all of
that stuff you know even doing every
single thing I wanted to do posting
controversial videos of 30 minute video
the best thing about this year is that
you guys are still here
even after all that I'm just really
really grateful and you have you have no
idea how much I appreciate it but that
being said here is a look back at the
entire year and some of the best moments
from it you guys you guys you guys you
guys you guys you guys guys so today I'm
gonna be shaving first
on a serious note I love you so much you
do so much for me
ma'am someone just texted me to my
Instagram got hacked down all your
pictures are gone dude you guys wanna go
get Taco Bell yes
yes we did okay 30 hulks scuse me I
don't know what that always doing inside
has a lot over itself cool why a mirror
you are my mirror is that hair in a jar
we're growing apart up dude tap out
just another simple line fast Rennell is
for lemonade
so once again thank you guys so much for
such a wonderful year see you guys in
hey guys