the body positive movement has evolved
so much over the past several years that
now if somebody wants to lose weight or
lose fat all of a sudden you are an
antibody positive and you get kicked out
of the community the great thing about
problems is it makes me my most creative
shall we clap e claps yep welcome back
to another episode of multiple podcasts
you're a little premature there we got
David in the moderator see pock was
right next to me I'm Ryan and we have a
very special guest miss Cassie home aka
I was gonna say the other one I was
telling them earlier I don't know why
but for the longest time this doesn't
make any sense I don't know why I bring
it up
I thought your YouTube I called you bio
gates bio gates I thought for the
longest don't know why okay that makes
more sense because it looks like that I
it's like a little bio Games is like a
little like bio hacker II don't know I
just wasn't reading I just don't read so
anyway for people who don't know you are
probably if not the biggest Fitness
youtuber or blogger or youtuber you are
the biggest Fitness youtuber right right
and primarily I mean you do you do kind
of like vlog stuff it's not just being
an instructor right started out with
instructor and then people wanted to
know what oh well what do you eat what
do you do and so it got which is better
cuz they care about you more right yes
sometimes it's not just you yelling at
them no but sometimes they care too much
what does that mean you know I don't it
means it means that you you feel
obligated to know everything that's
going on in your life and they feel like
they have control over what you do and
if you don't do something that's
quote-unquote on-brand
and all of a sudden you're wrong and
you're a bad person and all this kind of
stuff I sense some tension there
I feel like is I mean something on your
mind she's like you know what let's just
get right in yeah I know I like this or
anything open up
goods already right now did you want to
warm up no we're going wherever so this
is caught off the pill because it's
pretty much off the adderall at off the
Ritalin
basically just our minds will go
everywhere so wherever we want to go and
we're gonna start right there so just
get right to it
no calisthenics we're going straight in
okay well yesterday was the end of my
90-day journey so let me tell you what
that is it started on August 16th and I
decided that I wanted to get to an
athlete level body fat percentage and I
wanted to lose some weight along the way
because that obviously is what happens
and when I announced that because I was
gonna be blogging the entire time people
went crazy why yeah why exactly right I
preach eating healthy I preach working
out and that's exactly how I was going
to attain these goals and I got called
out for being not body-positive
for hating myself for being a bad role
model for women for being psycho and
needing to go see a mental health
specialist like the craziest things and
the meanest stuff but I told myself that
I wanted to go on this journey because I
needed to find my authentic self
throughout this journey I wanted to blog
every day for 90 days which I hadn't
done for a long time because I've been
getting a lot of you know opinions and
people wanting to shape me a certain way
in their head and so I over the past
several years have become a vanilla
cupcake trying to be what everyone wants
me to be and so the beginning of this 90
days was me speaking my mind again and
so of course when I speak my mind with
very like tame stuff it's not only doing
anything crazy you know women's health
writes about it about me being
controversial BuzzFeed Daily Mail and it
was it became this thing anyway I was
like oh my god like I'm literally gonna
lose a little bit of weight and I'm
doing it in a healthy way this all
happened yesterday no no so that
happened on August 16 yesterday was the
end of my 90 days see congratulations
yes that's awesome that just very
coincidental we weren't playing
just do this after that yeah but okay
well how has the since that happened
kind of a while ago how is the response
been since like I'm sure people have
kind of come to their senses right like
I'm sure they I mean I'm sure there's
people who are still just like they
don't even read what your explanation is
they just know oh she's not for was it
body-positive body-positive
[Music]
yeah but I feel like that is that's been
your thing I don't know I guess maybe
that's why they might have jumped so I'm
gonna I'm gonna cuz I've tried to
analyze this so much because I know that
if other Fitness youtubers are bloggers
and now it's the same thing they
wouldn't get the response that I got so
I'm gonna go back about to like 2013-14
or something I released this video where
I was photoshopping myself to look like
what the comments were telling me to
look like why don't you have a smaller
waist why don't you have a bigger butt
you don't have abs you're not a real
fitness instructor which is really mean
because it doesn't matter what you look
like when you're teaching fitness you're
just teaching anyway so the video was me
photoshopping myself and that went viral
and I was on Good Morning America and
all these things it was crazy I really
didn't expect it but it was way for me
to battle the haters and after that
moment any time any media outlet spoke
about me it was body-positive fitness
influencer Cassie ho body-positive
youtuber Cassie ho it became like my
thing
yes the the the media branded me that
way but the reason why I even made that
video was because I was just a Pilates
instructor and I was doing videos but I
just didn't have visible ABS and
literally that caused the comment which
caused the media which now cause me to
be labeled as a body positive person or
something which is fine like that's fine
but the body positive movement has
evolved so much over the past several
years that now if somebody wants to lose
weight or lose fat all of a sudden you
are antibody positive and you get kicked
out of the community and so that's kind
of like what happens that's so
hypocritical though because it's it's
your you can be positive about a skinny
body right or you can be positive about
I mean it's not like you're saying hey
this is what the standard of beauty
is I mean like if you want to lose
weight and you're happy about it then I
mean I don't see why that's an issue
yeah and I mean that's how I feel about
it - as long as you're loving your body
along the whole journey whether you're
trying to gain weight or lose weight
like who cares even if you're trying to
get plastic surgery and you just like
love yourself you want it like that's
that person's choice and we shouldn't be
here to judge them but yeah it's just
really changed the the evolution of
body-positive you have changed over the
years and when I announced it people
went crazy they were like unsubscribe
you're terrible human you need to get
psychological help you're mentally ill
like these words kept repeating over and
over and it was interesting because this
for me was a blog journey so a lot of it
was writing I didn't release a video on
YouTube and the meanest comments
actually came from YouTube not from
Facebook or Instagram YouTube was really
critical because they didn't go over to
read my blog I think and just like judge
me based on like you know a little
caption and then go read here for the
rest they just like went wild and so
anyway it was lots of drama in the
beginning towards the middle still drama
little less a little less I just like
actually stopped posting on the YouTube
community tab as much because it just
fired people up for some reason even if
when it was positive stuff and then
towards the end now I'm about to do my
finale recap and I think that's gonna be
drama drama - but I am happy to tell you
that I did reach my goals which is
really cool because yes who's in the
beginning when I announce my goals here
are so many people saying oh you're
number yeah you're so irresponsible for
announcing your numbers you make me feel
bad and all the kind of stuff and it was
just like insane yeah but you know what
I kept going before you even did this 90
day challenge did you expect that sort
of response or at least think like maybe
I'll get this or was that like not even
in your thought process well I knew that
it was gonna stir something but I didn't
know it would stir as much as it did it
was like I there was hatred like actual
like you are a bad human I did not
expect that so that was a lecture I was
actually really hard to deal with and
still is right now because I thought for
me with diet and exercise diet would be
hard because I like to
everything I can like literally eat
forever but dealing with the negativity
that's been pushed on me that's been the
hardest thing yeah
well it almost seems like you're just
another victim to cancer culture
somebody who's just like you know
Fanning the Flint that people just like
to be upset about something and I mean I
think if people actually took the time
to hear what your side of the story was
and not just I mean I'm assuming they're
just seeing things in a very broad scope
like reading up like reading a headline
in an article and not reading the
article exactly and it just seems like I
don't mean I personally can't see how
that's negative like I can't I can't
understand that you just wanted to go on
and die it how is that gonna I don't
know there's some mind blowing to me
well I think like I I read the comments
and you know there's hateful ones and
then there's constructive and I
understand where some of these girls are
coming from because some of them may
have an eating disorder I myself had an
eating disorder like way back then where
I was scared of bananas and things like
that and so mentally there was a time
period where I needed to heal myself
luckily through lots of work I am healed
now and so I think some fans were
generally concerned that I was falling
back into something dangerous so I get
that but after explaining myself and
them seeing me being on this thing for
45 days I'm totally fine like and still
getting that it's like you really just
don't want to see that I am better and
I'm getting better so and I think maybe
a lot of people look to influencers to
validate what they're doing because it's
like oh I look like her and it's okay to
eat like that or work out like that and
whatever and all of a sudden your idol
is now changing it's like I'm lost who
do I follow now you've betrayed me I
kind of think like that's probably what
happened yeah I could understand that I
guess when you say eating disorder does
that mean eating too much or eating too
little so there's a lot of forms of
eating disorders there's you know
there's anorexia where you don't eat
anything you eat very very little
there's bulimia where you throw up the
food that you eat
I had orthorexia which means I only ate
healthy food and I was scared of
anything that wasn't healthy it's a
disorder you know I
I hate it is I don't know if it's like
medically a disorder but like something
just made it up like I like only healthy
food so I'm going to call it this is it
making me was it unhealthy well it was
because the fear of food so I always
felt like I was in food Jail so I wait
so I was in a bikini competition and for
that I was super high protein low fat
pretty much eating just like egg whites
protein powder counted my almonds and
like very very low calorie during that
period when I was getting lean and after
that period I was terrified of eating
bananas and apples I just thought they
were gonna make me fat and so mentally I
was messed up and I it took me a while
like actually a few years to break out
of that cycle because I also messed up
my body and had metabolic damage meaning
that sometimes I ate pizza and I would
lose weight and sometimes we eat salad
and gain weight and nothing worked and
so yeah kinda messed up my body when you
when you talk about like the people who
are complaining about like the the fact
that you're not body positive right
are these if are these types of people
are they a certain type like do they
have a certain type of disorder or is it
because I'm thinking that maybe the fact
that you're trying to lose weight
there's the the people are saying that
you're not positive about being
overweight is it is that what they're
basically saying vice are you asking if
the people that are commenting that are
overweight people yes basically I did in
a very peaceful yeah because I
understand that I understand that like
you should love your body even if you
are overweight and I know there may be
people who have issues with being
overweight and it's tough for them to
lose it but I mean I think it's general
knowledge that being overweight is
unhealthy right here's my problem with
terms like overweight and obese it's
based off of a standard yes a healthier
nose what was it a bunch of Caucasian
people or what was it like what was it
like do you like our Asian standards the
same as whatever the standards in the
you know these medical textbooks are so
I I don't feel comfortable with
standards I think they help doctors make
a decision
and I think when it comes down to it
it's a very individual thing do I know
if the people who are mad at me were
overweight or not I literally have no
idea but I can say that there they are
people most likely with insecurities I'm
gonna say whether it be that they're
overweight or not yeah or or whatever
yeah or something and so I mean I don't
want to say that they're just projecting
on me or whatever but it very much felt
that way and it was interesting to have
your own fan base kind of just judge you
so hard and yeah but it's all good right
now internally because I don't ever
regret going on this I feel amazing I
have so much more energy I'm stronger
I'm faster and I'm just glad I did this
to prove to myself that I could make
some goals and then reach them I asked
what diet you did and what did you do
exactly what change
what did I change so um the first month
I did keto have any of you guys done
Kido yeah okay cool I did keto but I I'm
lactose intolerant but I wanted to eat
the cheese and the yogurts and stuff and
I started breaking out a lot but I did
lose a 5,000 the first month but
anything I do in the first month I was
about five pounds then I ate so many
nuts that I kept gaining weight steadily
for a couple weeks and is like oh my god
what's happening and then I realize okay
Cassie like let's be honest with
yourself you are just overeating and
like I told you I can eat forever like
take me to a buffet and I will out eat
anyone I actually want to be a
competitive eater but I'm not gonna do
that but I really want to have a burrito
that's as big as a baby have you seen
those no no okay I kind of bit that's
not a normal baby right there are like
three footballs well something about
your dieting oh dieting yes so
overeating realize that I was probably
overeating even though as eating healthy
things um so the thing that really
changed it for me was tracking my food
in my fitness pal and writing down okay
I had this much and this and it really
taught me you know I feel like I know
portions but you can always feel your
hand a little extra make your tablespoon
like
twice as much and so really logging
everything weighing my food kept me
really strict in in a good way because I
knew exactly what I was doing what was
ingesting in my body I knew the macros
and everything and so that really
changed it for me
yeah and workouts though I mean for the
most part I did like one rest day a week
I started dancing more towards the end
of my journey and that made me less
stressed and were happy I feel like if
you didn't work out you wouldn't be as
hungry I think you're so hungry because
you work out so much people work out eat
more right I mean you need more energy
okay so I did this blood test a genetic
fit test and I've also done 23andme have
you guys done that okay so in my 23andme
it says that I am genetically more
predisposed to be overweight and my
sister has fetus - predisposed to be
underweight also my dad I think my mom
was like normal Sam my husband is
predisposed to be underweight so or the
same weight so I already have the genes
that make it difficult for me to be able
to have a lean body which is interesting
because I'm in the fitness industry and
almost everyone has a lean body so where
was I going with this I lost my train of
thought again well that's fine I mean I
think I was just saying that I
personally the people I need to work out
the most eat the most right because you
need energy and anyway so I took at this
genetic fit test that not only confirmed
that but it also said that I had like
some genetic variant that said I like to
eat a lot so I know that was you know
the thing I mean I probably have that
too I can eat a lot well you also seem
to have high metabolism I think no I got
gained a lot really gained a lot of
weight really quickly and then he was a
lot of weight really quick oh wow I used
to wrestle so I did really unhealthy
crash diets I say you know yeah a couple
days and were you doing like this mostly
water weight but yeah but yeah I mean
there was this like when I start myself
it was like the worst I mean you know
wrestlers yeah I'm sure you know those
weight classes yeah yeah so that was a
thing and we did the whole you know they
would do the whole body fat testing
hydration test we'd have to measure your
fat yeah yeah yeah all that stuff and
and there's always people that there's
ways around it like it's a very
unhealthy do you tell me about it
I mean I don't want to encourage other
people wrestling right now I'm sure they
have better ways but they would
essentially the hydration test would
measure how much it your body fat is
there's a minimum right I think it's
like for guys it's like 7% or six six or
something like that I don't know what it
is the healthy body fat and then they
compare that to your weight and how
hydrated you are see pee in a cup okay
so I need people that would just use
like little Visine bottles and just use
that to hydrate their pee a little bit
more Oh so they'd be completely
dehydrated but they'd pee a little
add some water to it and using that that
I don't know what that thing is where
they look into this like a little
crystal tube thing and they see how
hydrated you are it basically that's the
way a lot of people cheated that stuff
oh wow okay so yeah resting is a very
dangerous sport
we're spitting into a bucket what that's
what that's what they did with my I did
wrestling as well oh you didn't there
were some people who spit into a bucket
like they would chew gum just to lose
weight I mean it was like not much
weight obviously oh if you keep doing it
all day long you'll you'll have some
water weight that could you cry it out
I'm sure we watch some sad movies you'd
be surprised I mean we did some
dangerous stuff like we used to like
we're trash bags uh-huh and then go
running and then just sit sit in a hot
car choke the heaters and then you know
take X Lacs and all that stuff oh my
gosh so you think you did damage to
yourself I think I did a good good
amount yeah that sounds like you used to
make weight and just bad habits I think
over it and I started like you know we'd
eat so much and then like see you our
weight increased by like 10 pounds and
then just crash and just lose it all and
then
mentality kind of stayed with me so
surgeon degree I don't do that as crazy
but like I think it's a very dangerous
habit to get I mean I think it's a habit
because I think I still do that to a
certain degree not start myself like oh
I'm gonna just lose it in a couple weeks
and then if I gain it back I'll just
lose it again huh yeah that's crazy and
it's interesting because we never really
talked about been dieting or men's view
of their bodies and how they feel about
it
yeah and a lot of I mean I don't call it
names a lot of people they God guys they
care about that stuff too oh for sure
yeah getting bigger getting ripped yeah
you know being skinnier you know stuff
like that
yeah normal I would say I think
especially when you're in front of a
camera you can notice like I notice if I
even gained like three pound I mean is
that a lot if I can't like even three
pounds like you can see yeah so you know
I feel sad and then I'll be like okay
I'm not eating for the next three days
wait so do you guys like struggle with
the way that you look in the mirror ever
I don't oh not really not me safe for me
I yeah I would I would say like there's
days where like man I don't want to take
a picture today you know or like in and
then there's times when all like lose
weight and I feel not because I feel
like skinny is beautiful but like I just
feel like that's the right weight for me
like this is what my face should look
like or this is what my body should look
like you feel comfortable yeah yeah yeah
and then I'm it's not that I don't when
I'm bigger like I don't mind yeah but
it's just like this is like what it
should be for me for like what I want
right so yeah I mean I would say there's
definitely days where I'd be like I
don't want to take a picture today yeah
you were just talking about this today
uh with what you you said you do you you
were working out more and oh yeah just
like cuz you never work out I never work
out but like for me um
just noticing like when you look a
little bit more out of shape for me like
I just want to look skinnier mostly
because I know if I'm skinnier that
means I'm more fit
and it ought to be able to perform
better when I play sports right and see
it's like performance based yeah that is
true
yeah but I don't know is it about
halftime that's why yeah we're about
there shall we take a two-hour shishi
break yeah let's do it
all right so routine shishi break right
now and apparently this is a new thing
so what do you have prepared for us
you're gonna serenade us or perform
something where I have potential I don't
even know what she is where we take a
bathroom break and we are half time half
time break so what talent do you have
that you can perform in 30 seconds oh I
can sound like a pigeon okay for 30
seconds what 30 no you just go ahead I
don't know what a pigeon sounds like
about that is in Hawaii I've had friends
do that and then they have their uh flip
flop or slip via slipper loosely on
their foot and they slap it okay so like
the wings core yeah we didn't we this is
literally our first time asking someone
to do that so you do that we're gonna
just start asking halftime show all
right we'll be right back after our CC
break
[Music]
and we're back I got a question okay
have you ever fasted like a straight
fast with just water no I have not
I've read a lot about that and
apparently it's very good for you to do
that once in a while like a straight up
fast so I've never done that I've done a
juice fast but that's still like calorie
like 1,200 calories a day so I was never
actually 1200 calories of juice juice I
just pressed Juicery but like they're
beginners pack it was too sweet though
but it made me lose straight-up seven
pounds in three days but it was just
water weight yeah in wastage instead of
stuff like that mm-hmm yeah but I've
never done a water cleanse but yeah I've
heard like monks can do it up to like a
month like I don't know I just really
like chewing yeah I love food too but I
tried it for three days it was thinking
about food I will say that it did give
me a lot of clarity is weird okay how
did that happen I don't know that I mean
I hear that that's what happens when
you're on keto to my your brain
functions a little bit differently and
you do get like this weird kind of
energy that's not your like normal
physical energy we do you like this like
your it seemed like my brain was not
tired
it didn't seem tired yeah exactly I felt
pretty sharp actually when you don't
think about food then then your thoughts
and the things that you have to focus on
actually are very clear so I don't know
I noticed that for myself just want to
see if you when I was on keto though for
that month it was it was definitely not
the diet for me like I was constantly
thirsty drinking like hmm you're
supposed to be though right I almost
like that - I was super thirsty I
started getting these keto like flu
headaches did you get that - I'm out
right yeah so then my friend who wrote
like a book on keto he was like oh you
need to take like you put salt in your
hand and actually like eat it plus you
need all these supplements and I was
like what that's not my thing like I
just really like to be food is my
medicine medicine was my food so I just
decided that wasn't for me yeah I don't
think I did it the right way
we're like you check your key I just do
that I didn't want to prick my finger I
hate needles I cry still as an adult I
didn't even know you could do that but I
didn't yeah yeah you like you're
supposed to prick your finger check your
ketones and be like Oh am I in ketosis
or not yeah I didn't do it dad I did it
back before keto was keto before iya was
a thing like I did it wrong but it was
like before it was a fad I would say
back in like 2010 so then you're doing
like Atkins basically kind of but no
carb yeah like even down to like well
low-carb yeah down to like okay this has
one gram I'm not gonna eat it Wow yeah
because I didn't know I didn't know
anything there was no real information
out there I just knew that by starving
yourself with carbs your energy will
come from your fat that's all I knew I
didn't know anything else and that's not
quite the right way to do it but it it
works I mean you lose weight you just
don't feel great no you don't you know
any time you take out an entire food
group you're probably gonna lose weight
from the initial shock anyway right
and then you'll plateau yes uh-huh
uh-huh yeah yeah so I was wondering when
like what got you into the fitness thing
like were you when you were young where
you always make into sports and were you
very active and is that what kind of
triggered that or was it was it
something else okay so my dad trained me
and my sister in tennis when we were
really young so I started playing tennis
when I was like five or six
he's a USTA coach and oh man it was like
Asian dad yelling at you on the court
situation but he he was a good coach I
suppose because I made varsity my
freshman year as team captain from
sophomore to senior year but I hated
tennis so much because it had always
been about it being for my dad for
winning for the team so I didn't
discover Fitness until I was 16 because
when I was 16 I wanted to do a pageant I
wanted to do the Miss Teen Chinatown
pageant and I wanted to you know look
good for it and like you know when
you're a teenager is 16 and it's like
2002 like I didn't know anything about
fitness but I saw an infomercial for
Mari Winsor Pilates and I asked my
parents to find me a DVD because it
looked really cool like these women just
lifting their leg I was like that's
really fun you bought it for me and then
I did those videos real
justly and fell in love with like home
fitness and it's crazy because now girls
do my videos just like that on YouTube
in their bedroom so when I was 16 I
discovered Pilates I ended up getting
certified as a sophomore in college and
then I started teaching just on the side
and then I didn't start my youtube
channel until after college and really
it was just I was moving from LA to
Boston for my very first job and my
students at 24 hour fitness are like Oh
Cassie who else is gonna teach us this
because my format is pop pilates pilates
- pop music it's kind of like a dance on
the mat no one else was teaching that
and so I said okay I'm gonna record this
10-minute video put it on his website
called YouTube it's just for you guys
like 40 people then I left and that's
how the YouTube channel got started
because I wanted to continue teaching
from a distance which is crazy because
that's exactly what I'm doing right now
except the world yeah that is crazy
you've done in person I've seen pictures
of like you with like hundreds of people
like in person yes like this the dance
routines and stuff that's insane it's
crazy my biggest one was Singapore and
we were on the Empress LAN and we're all
doing like plie squats and I could
barely see to the horizon but I later
read that there were three to four
thousand people they had a plie
squatting with me and I was like in
Singapore where it's like 90 degrees
with like a hundred percent humidity
Singaporeans are so like perfect like
they were all on beat I don't know how
but yeah I mean everything about them is
perfect it's like school for that
everything by the book yeah well a
couple of questions because you said you
graduated college right yeah but what
did you graduate biology so I majored in
biology and minored in business and then
you are also like fashion buying at some
point yeah that's right so I had always
wanted to be a fashion designer I've
drawn dresses ever since I was a little
girl but when I told my dad and my mom
that he wanted to become a fashion
designer
they were like you were definitely not
doing that because you're gonna be poor
and have no friends and
I don't know all the other mean stuff
you just see well you won't be
successful ever so I decided to not do
it he said you should be a doctor
because you're doing well in bio and
chem right now so just go do that and so
I did that but my heart was just not
into it my soul was gone and so I always
drew things on the side and while I was
teaching Pilates in college I I had to
hold my yoga mat my CD my keys
everything was all over the place like
this and so I decided to design a yoga
bag for myself and when my student saw
it they really wanted to buy it then I
found a local manufacturer to make some
of these bags and before I left for
Boston I remember sending out a few bags
to some magazines but at this time you
know every bag that you make is like
gold because it's all you have about
eight months into my new job as a as
training to become a fashion buyer so I
really was like no I'm not doing this
whole biology thing my parents were so
mad at me because I dropped out of
organic chemistry last minute to make
sure I could not make it in time for my
MCAT I had to sabotage myself because I
was such an obedient child that I just
went through with everything that they
said I wanted to be perfect and so I
really had to sabotage myself anyway so
eight months into my fashion buying job
my sister is texting me and her fingers
pointing to something on on in the text
and I noticed that it's my yoga bag in
shape magazine and so I took it as a
sign to quit my job and go for this 100%
because you never know if you're gonna
make it if you don't give it your all
right and so I quit my job
I bought a ticket to China on Friday and
left on Sunday went to the Canton Fair I
found a manufacturer and then let the
bags develop I came back to Boston and
pretty much just kept making youtube
videos cuz now I had no job and I was
teaching like at 6:00 a.m. 12 p.m. and
as 6:00 a.m. like every day and it was
weird 12 times a week barely making any
money and just trying to hustle Wow
so yeah that is a you don't I don't know
if people realize how rare that is and
crazy and risky yeah especially because
it seems like your childhood seemed to
be almost like a like a very your
stereotype like the tiny you for Chinese
Chinese being
okaywell Asian parents say become a
doctor don't do this other nonsense and
you decide to walk away from that
pissing them off in the process yeah and
going all in but everything's good now
with the family they don't like that
you're you know it's one of those things
where it's like never enough okay so
like even even if it's like I think they
are proud of me because it's this whole
landscape they don't even understand but
it's always more like well why can't you
sell more you know just like those
little questions here and there like
yeah you know it doesn't make a follow
up question to that yes a lot of people
you know they constantly want to know
from their idols or people that they
look up to what made you make the jump
because you've made several different
jumps what gave you the courage or what
was the signs and what allowed you to
persevere through the hard times like
especially when the only thing paying
your bills was doing Pilates and you see
you had it rough yeah what made me take
the leap was that if no one was gonna
believe in me I needed to believe in
myself and if I were gonna fail I wanted
to fail hard and know that and be like
okay we're good with that I don't want
to ever regret that I never tried and so
I'm always willing to take the risk on
myself and you know back then as a
college kid I just wanted to follow my
passion whatever that meant but
following my passion follow my gut has
gotten me to where I am today because I
know what feels right and what doesn't
and my whole motto is do more what makes
you happy do less of what doesn't and so
following that has allowed me to get
here do you think though uh because a
lot of people like yeah nice but uh you
did in a way your parents instilled a
lot of hard work ethics into you it
sounds like just because even with
talking about your 90 day you're just
like yeah I studied all this stuff I
know yeah and just everything you've
talked about so far it just seems you
extensively done research you take notes
and you put work into it right so it
requires a lot of that as well
maybe if you want to speak on that
yeah I mean clearly it's not like follow
my heart la-dee-da everything's gonna be
fine you need to have a plan
you know like plan a plan B and but when
but but I do believe that when you go
for something you have to go all-in it's
kind of like I don't know have you guys
ever Rock climbed or you know whatever
okay dude doing something we're pretty
much if you don't go all-in you're gonna
fall off you have to just make the leap
and so for me that's what I needed to do
in real life to see if it was gonna work
or not and I don't know maybe it is
something innate maybe it is well not
maybe definitely my parents trained me
to be a very studious person a very
disciplined person but also I'm a high
achiever and I like progress I like
results and I like it and that a I mean
like that's just who I am it stressed me
out throughout school but I really liked
it and I liked reaching my goal this
time it brings me a lot of joy so yeah I
mean you just got to be smart about it
cuz like it's not like I went for my
dreams and invested all my money or
their very little that I had that time
into these bags I didn't know what's
gonna happen I was still teaching I was
still hustling I was still I was doing
like Craigslist jobs like I think if it
were back then I probably would have
been driving ubers and delivering post
mates like I would have just like done
everything and been very humble about it
until I could get where I wanted to be
right mm-hmm what do you tell yourself
like do you ever think about what could
potentially go wrong and do you try to
convince yourself like if it goes wrong
then this will happen or are you just
more like kind of stubborn when it comes
to those types of you know scenarios in
your head and you're like I will never
let that happen well things are always
gonna happen I'm so many terrible and
things have gone wrong in my life but I
immediately switch into problem-solving
mode there's no time to be sad about it
it's like how do we fix this now so you
just got to be ready anyway if you're
not ready just start thinking really
hard how are you gonna fix this because
I think the great thing about problems
is it makes me my most creative right
true absolutely that's interesting you
say that you in the beginning that you
were very sensitive and emotional person
but it's
your very logic base when it comes to
work that's a thing when it comes to
work I'm super logic base and super pom
solving but when it comes to people
judging my character I become like this
like really soft thing that just melts
and dies that's so interesting to me cuz
it's usually it's more almost one or the
other but it's kind of both yeah so like
I think back to school and I feel like I
had a hard time socially because I don't
know like I I my high achieving self
made it hard for people to like me
I guess I don't know but it definitely
wasn't cool
it definitely wasn't cool and I always
struggled in the social scene and I
think that's where that whole the
comments affect me so much thing comes
from because that's a social thing yeah
but work-wise I've always been like I
don't care I'm just gonna go for it I'm
gonna do it whatever and that's
something you're confident I'm very
confident in my skills but when it comes
to social stuff what about the social
stuff were you kind of uneasy about like
is it was it hard to make friends was it
regarding to regarding dating or was it
like interacting with teachers like was
it okay teachers have always been fine
because like stood friends yeah I mean
like I don't know I I just see I'm even
struggling with it now I just like I
don't know okay I'll tell you about one
time so I I ran for a student government
freshman year of high school and um and
here's the thing I'm not well liked but
I am well known back in that scene
because of all the things that I did and
all the clubs I was in or whatever but
when I was in student government which
is super clicky and super popular kids I
remember we were making a float for
homecoming and I was in charge of the
budget obviously and so we got Walmart
and trying to buy hairspray to like
spray down thing to make them stick up
these like tissue papers and so I'm like
okay we should buy the generic brand
because it's cheaper than this like
Tresemme or something like that and the
kids like they videotaped me and then
they sent that video around it's telling
everyone that I was cheap
like I don't just like stuff like that
happening scars me and like I still
remember that so I don't know what that
is but I just have always struggled
socially so do you now buy the more
expensive okay like home goods Marshalls
TV but I want saving money you know when
it's time to buy a luxury you you can
splurge but like be smart when you can
be smart mm-hmm so we have some
questions from fans here oh wow okay yep
we got one here from Marianne she asks
would you ever consider running a
marathon no easy answer I ran a half
marathon that's still freezing
I hate running like I hate it like I'll
do it but I do not enjoy it in any
aspect my legs hurt my mind's numb I
just like really don't like it yeah so
no do you like it though no see I don't
like sports either because I don't like
being competitive physically like that I
guess like internally I'm like semi
competitive just based on my work stuff
but not like that it overtakes my life
but that's why I do really didn't like
playing tennis because it's always about
winning or losing and I just hated that
I don't mind competing against myself
but competing against other people's
stresses me out so what are other ways
you compete against yourself oh you know
just like okay it just works for example
like the 90-day journey like I want to
hit this number how do I get there how
do I get there faster like what kind you
like that kind of stuff or like you know
I lifted this much yesterday how much
can I squat today like that kind of
stuff but yeah when in computer why
don't you want to like I mean like you
were you valedictorian no were you
striving to be of course yeah that's the
best is that be stuff SATs GPA I have no
idea yeah we weren't close clearly yeah
not even close
oh wow wouldn't it because I would have
assumed you're just incredibly
competitive yeah I think I I don't know
why I said that a lot of things about
you baby yeah I think I am
but I don't like you don't like making
other people lose basically no no and I
don't like losing you do like board
games or stuff like that
let them out a little bit not too much
not in Portuguese I think it has to do
with like work and stuff like that work
or like beating sales from last year and
you know stuff like that
okay yeah I'm just confirming with the
gentleman that back because he sat up
straight when we started like talking
about you being competitive
you got another question here from
Potter freak tips on always staying
motivated when working out okay you get
this a lot oh yeah important one here's
the thing you're not motivated if you
don't like what you're doing so like
pick a workout that's fun so I love
dancing I love Pilates like when I go to
my workout it feels like a treat not a
chore so that's number one
secondly maybe have an accountability
partner like a friend a sister boyfriend
whoever do it with you so now it becomes
like a date so that makes it fun again
it's all about finding the joy in
working out and that to me is the secret
and also finding something that you can
constantly get better at something that
you can increase your skill in because
it makes it exciting to come back me
like oh can I do this handstand am I a
little straighter did I run like 1
second faster than last time
like I think that's incredible yeah
having having being able to see
improvement yes is is very addicting
yeah it is progress is addictive but to
counter that a lot of people don't
improve very quickly and they get bored
or they get there just not patient or
you know I think that's also evil yeah
most people if they don't stop seeing
results they just quit right so then it
happens a lot for a lot of people it
does and that's why I love doing all
sorts of workouts so sometimes we were
like oh why do you do yoga and Pilates
and dancing and all this other stuff
it's because I like to it would be so
boring if I just did one thing all the
time but I think you just gonna find
that level for you that makes it
exciting and interesting so whether
that's the right variety or increasing
your skill level just find that thing
that keeps you
coming back mm-hmm yeah okay well we got
one more here from Daniella she asks if
I want to get in better shape not just
losing weight should I focus more on
workouts or on eating so in my
experience she waits you wonder she
better shape better workout right not
just losing weight just better shamp by
working out or eating okay so I guess we
don't know what she means by shape like
physical shape or just like healthy fit
shape I'm assuming she means like a
six-pack okay leaner so if we're talking
about leaner you know I think when
people say that abs are made in the
kitchen have you guys heard that it's
because all of us have a six-pack is no
it's covered by a layer of fat so in
order to get rid of that fat it's gonna
be a lot of cardio a lot of hit workouts
and then of course um a creating that
calorie deficit so that you can start
losing the fat on your body for me and
my experience especially on this 90-day
journey a lot of it was food because
I've always been working out I'll enjoy
working out but the food I had always
been overeating so focusing on the food
I do a lot of lean protein along with
vegetables cauliflower everything that's
how I replace my rice with and that's
helped a lot I know I know I know
cauliflower is great though I take a
cauliflower cauliflower polka yesterday
for sweet Finn oh my god you have to try
it you have to actually I mean I would
try it
but I've tried the cauliflower rice and
from where uh well I mean I've had
pre-made ones I okay and you I mean the
thing is if you want right it's not
right it's not it's it's something it's
definitely something you know I will
replace rice dish in Clarke rice no
you're right it's just cauliflower just
cut yum nice
minced cauliflower it's not bad as a I
like it I think I think cauliflower rice
helped me on my journey yeah yeah yeah
no I love rice but I can really easily
overeat that and it bloats me mm-hmm
unfortunately as an Asian yeah yeah so
basically saying having a
better diet a diet is more important to
get apps and it is to get well I mean
everyone has abs to get rid of the layer
of fat it's not just working on it's
your diet it's it yeah it's both
it's totally both because ironically
though couldn't you just not workout and
just starve yourself and you would get
abs but you'd probably die but I mean
like over time you see your abs right
like that's like starving people right
there and you'll see ribs you know so
that's like it's like that's not our you
know what I mean theoretically yes what
about African children though because it
comes it starts to eat the muscle there
well that's what I was trying to see you
starve yourself okay you're canceled no
just kidding anyway yeah I think I've
heard that before though yeah you need
to I've I mean I know for a fact that
you don't lose that you can work out all
you want but if you're eating bad it
doesn't really it no it totally counters
it yeah it's so much easier to just eat
a thousand extra calories and to burn a
thousand extra calories just how it is
I was always like had the issue of like
I think I'm I don't know if you
mentioned or not I don't know if we're
similar like I've always had like this
issue where I I like quantity of food
like you said you like to eat a lot yeah
like I would rather go to a place that
has like a twenty dollar like 16 out
like a big steak then to go to like a
fancy place that's like a filet mignon
Kobe beef it's like this big like the
size of like a scallop I agree with you
100%
I love volume I want to fill my belly I
think it's a issue that I like the
feeling of feeling full me too
that's why it's dangerous though guys
don't you think because I know I know I
can stop like a lot of times I'll go to
dinner have a appetizers and be like I'm
good but I'll keep going because you're
so high achieving you just keep going
you know I don't like to waste either
he's also the Asian in you right now you
guys are going with the generic brand
what when the filet mignon is name brand
what we want to save money that's what
I'm saving
okay when you go to buffets uh-huh what
did your parents used to tell you how to
eat go to the get the expensive stuff
yeah
don't touch the rice crab legs only yeah
yeah yeah they would yell at me if I
want to talk but I still get rice like a
buffet that's how much I like rice it's
it's not it's a baby rice is amazing
I love brown rice though like I
naturally like brown rice is chewy and
good
do you like brown or white white but I
could eat I eat rice Mexican rice even
forbidden rice cool well um we learned a
lot learn a lot good yeah we learned
that everyone has ABS deep down
[Laughter]
different ways to achieve it and you
lost 16 pounds and it's harder for girls
to lose weight - it is it is and we
naturally just have more fat in our
bodies yeah yeah well congratulations
again and thank you for being here one
day after your big was it called that
was coincidence that's awesome glad to
be on here and like I told you before
this like Ryan I I watched all your
videos like back in the day and when you
were with d-trix making that Christmas
one the Christmas song decorate the
decoration literally my favorite video
of all time my sister Ashley every
Christmas so we're gonna play at this
Christmas yes funny and we like you're
the person watching I'm the one giving
you those views on Christmas ones are
like the seasonal ones always do bit
like they actually get more views over
time some videos people don't go back to
them but like those they do we could
David like that's he's the music dude
it's done didn't do that one but he's
the music dude yeah
yeah so thank you for having me on your
podcast
thank you really people don't know but
just another show you let us practice
our horrible BGA moves at your studio
thank you for that really practicing
again you want to plug anything yeah
what's going on like you have any
whatever your socials your murder play
your bio gates my bio gates um let's see
when is this coming out soon yeah well
when people are watching this yeah I
don't know if you guys want to get
started on some type of a workout plan
just go to my blog blog like on there's
like free workout calendars that is a
great place to get started if you need
to get motivated that's all your socials
I still just Blogilates everywhere BL o
GI la tes except by lo cakes yeah except
for it tick tock someone took my name
but I also don't need to talk so I don't
know awesome
okay well with that being said yeah you
could fight I was getting to it a top
appeal on Twitter and ad off the pill
podcast on Instagram and the way that we
always end this essentially we just blow
into the mic oh okay so in three two one
[Music]
[Applause]
we always say that but breathe have you
turned it down