hey guys so I know I haven't done a dear
Ryan video in a while so let's just get
right into it
dear Ryan can you say em without
touching your lips and mm and and tell
me and and and that's cheating can I use
my teeth mmm technically my lips aren't
touch okay that's cheating and mmm this
is so frustrating okay you can you it's
it's impossible it's not possible thanks
for making me a little unity well I say
a lot of you at home just did that so
don't even judge me how stupid I look
because you probably look just as stupid
but more handsome
do you Ryan can you do emoji impressions
I actually have never tried that before
so I'm not sure I mean I'll do as many
as I can
yeah this last one is kind of racist
anyway that's pretty much all the emoji
impressions I can do I try to do as many
as I could with the oh I get it because
I'm Asian haha good one man and now
you're calling me a girl I'm not even
wearing a red dress what is this a it's
not your best insult like steer you know
what I'm not gonna take this kind of
insults from emoji I have no reason to
get mad I'm not even making a fist now
what is that supposed to read what the
hell just stop just stop it this is my
video and this is my idea there's no way
that somebody like you
dear Ryan can you do the stitch voice
again it's actually really simple all
you have to do is make the awesome like
you're at the dentist like ah and then
while you're doing that move your tongue
back yes oh it's like you're gargling
like you're closing off your throat so
you don't swallow your mouthwash so make
a dentist sound I don't know why I'm
doing all these dental hygienic
references so you're gonna make the
sound like you're at the dentist by
closing off your throats that you don't
swallow the mouthwash and he's pouring
in your mouth not that they do that once
you can make that sound that claw
awesome you just add in words ounce
bottle bottle of the fun awful tonight
dear Ryan can you be a CS gamer you mean
CS like counter-strike no I don't have
time to be playing video games because
video games are a waste of time
and for anyone that plays you make
carnage that cartridge is such an old
game that I don't figure what the hell
do you Ryan what does a transformer
sport sound like that's a good question
actually
what do your fart sound like sounds like
a fork that's auto-tune fart with
auto-tune what does that sound like wait
a second do that again is exactly what
dubstep sounds like a forceout a really
long one this time all right
oh hey what happened what was that sorry
that sounds like trap music yeah I know
I sharted deer right can you step on a
leg oh I don't know why people make such
a big deal about stepping on Legos it's
not hard to do people just over
exaggerate watch it ya know it doesn't
hurt that much I mean people really do
over exaggerate I mean it kinda hurts
but that money goes really doesn't hurt
anyone they stepped on me son thank you
like humans promise you father my
revenge
Legos just because it doesn't hurt you
don't mean it don't hurt nobody else doe
do you're right you can mathematically
prove that 9 plus 10 equals 21
[Music]
how does 9 plus 10 equal 21 well the
obvious answer is 19 but I don't know
where to go from there
wait a second remember just now when you
said the obvious answer was 19 and then
I said wait a second yeah that just
happened 19 wait a second
19 seconds 1 remember 19 seconds into
this video I was doing the dear Ryan
where I had to say the letter M without
touching lips yeah so well it's
impossible to say the letter M with one
lip you need tulips
speaking of tulips tulips are a flower
flowers have petals and petals like gas
pedals or in automobiles and automobiles
what transformers turn into transformers
what are you getting in remember the
Transformers dear Ryan we just did yeah
when you press down on the gas pedal it
releases gas from its exhaust that's
basically a Transformers bar and if you
remember a Transformers part is
equivalent to what dubstep but if a
transformer pushes too hard and forces
out a fart he won't just fart dubstep
he'll shark shut out what Ryan trap
music which means this whole equation
it's just one big trap
[Applause]
well well well looks like you figured it
out who are you oh you don't remember
maybe this will help huh is this a
picture of you laying down that is my
dead father the one you stepped on and
killed and now I'm here to avenge him
like killing you No
no place you humans think stepping on
one of us hurts Oh No let's see how you
like it when a bunch of us steps on you
[Music]
what wasn't that bad did it hurt at all
actually
my turn so thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one little F if you want
to see bloopers and behind-the-scenes of
us jumping on Legos click the one on the
right or if you want to see the last
view ryan video click the one in the
bottom
wattles bottom or you could just type in
dear Ryan there's like a whole bunch
some other ones that's probably a little
bit better than this one haha