I try I try I try I always seem to fall
short sometimes I just feel like given
up starting or with something completely
new even with friends by my side
constantly giving me second third
chances I still seems like I'm getting
nowhere whoever it is whatever you
believe in he/she/it the maker of this
world has got to be sick and demented
knowing how badly people wanted you're
putting up damn near impossible walls
and obstacles at every level of this
journey dude it's just candy crush Kenna
grip oh yeah hey you play fruit ninja
right yeah so this is just a game right
yes like playing them fruits watermelons
oranges apples I mean
let this be a lesson to you
your precipice a candy don't you ever
underestimate the candy crush again for
also I'm gonna find two more people just
like you sugar crush yes and once you
play a game long enough you start to
lose yourself it's like you're in a
whole different world from everyone else
the only other people they can see the
world the way you do are people with the
same problems same issues
now I understand Sudha in the beginning
it's fine go in and out of these worlds
as you please
the thing is longer you stay in this
world more likely you are to be
imprisoned by him so we meet again at
Richardson Richard just call me dick
addiction
you
listen to me I need more hacking doing
this Ryan
you
what
and yet that light
oh I can't D why don't they drive
is it normal right and prove it to me
I've always had a candy crush God go
live on you don't do for farm to one
seems like it's game over no lies left
no friends to send you it oh yeah cuz it
seems like I have more lives right here
the dollar I could have five more lives
right now
of course I'm not going to not gonna
stay on real money in a free game right
I don't like the game town much looks
like you guys can use some help
who are you it's a me Mario