what is the most salad what fruit salad
or potatoes come up with this what is
the most salad I wonder why the rainbow
became the sign of game Oh
much of my spicy chicken deluxe meal is
going towards already we mixed it up so
this is a special episode because it's
our 20th episode and it's a special one
because I wanted to send this seat cuz I
never get to play with this stuff
that wasn't good cuz that was the one I
meant to press that's why you don't get
to sit in there well you know what I'm
actually watching the levels which is
something you don't do okay you you win
you win you don't have that one yes we
are mixing things up today and we are
changing the podcast up yep so welcome
back to another episode of off the pill
podcast my name is Ryan Higa you're
still know I'm Ryan Higa Jesse you but
you're just taking the role and then
your name is sitting in the whole seat
like the audio listeners don't know I
don't care I'm Ryan so essentially I'm
in control of the moderator seat where I
can do this if I want this is not gonna
be a good pun I think I want to do I
wish you were you guys were just always
here so I could just be this person
anyway um but we're on off the bill
block yes my name is Paco I'm here
joined here with special guests David
joy for the third time
hello good to be back there are times a
charm thanks for your third
ferm I guess yet they're not gonna hate
you this time I hope not a second time
they didn't get that much hate did it
with that much cables as double nodes
the first time he got hated on a lot
people hate me hated me it actually
affected you like in real life and we
talked about him the second time he did
second time you didn't get hate I didn't
get hate I was forgiven I think people
realize you're different dude you know
no interesting little weird little but
oh you got to do the read and then no no
and then in the audio / moderator seat
we have Ryan Higa
ooh okay ah glad now it's your duty Oh
different this week's off the pill is
sponsored by Skillshare a Skillshare is
an online learning community for
creators with more than 25,000 classes
in design business and more you'll
discover countless ways to fuel your
curiosity creativity and career take
classes in social media marketing mobile
photography creative writing or even
illustration whether you're looking to
discover a new passion start a side
hustle or gain new professional skills
Skillshare is there to keep you learning
thriving and reaching those new goals
also you guys just took or looked at a
kosher class recently right yep you
morsel for David but yeah yeah I we
looked at how to make apps
not really yeah UX design as the class
that we took and basically what UX is a
user experience and what that is is it
kind of you know it teaches you how to
you know create the flow of like it for
example if you hit this button it does
this or if you do this swipe it takes
you to this page and that whole
experience of using a product is what
user experiences
alright so kind of like the psychology
behind you dinner way mm-hmm and that
sounds like a lot of smart people stuff
I don't David knows that world I don't
and I still understood it it's pretty
simple
so it's explained well Skillshare breaks
it down for dummies even like Ryan see
this not even part of the read or we are
giving the
a good ya know it's it's pretty easy
it's broken down yeah broken out so well
even a dummy like Ryan Higa can get it
join the millions of students already
learning on Skillshare today with a
special offer just for our listeners get
two months of Skillshare for free that's
right Skillshare is offering off the
bill listeners two months of unlimited
access to over 25,000 classes for free
to sign up go to Skillshare comm slash
Giga again go to Skillshare comm slash
Higa for your two months do your radio
voice yeah but we still need to alright
wait do it again in a bit
but we did it guys yeah yeah yeah you
don't sound enthusiastic oh no I was
great I was very impressed you sound sad
these are something going on in your
life right now I know exactly why
David's this way why is because your
soul David is so like hesitant review on
the podcast now since he's since the
first podcast so he's afraid of things I
mean that's gonna get him like I'm a bad
comment I'm afraid of people
I know Internet you've changed you
afraid of internet people Internet could
you imagine what the world would be like
if Olson and the internet was gone now
what the world would be like at the
internet lism yeah if it suddenly just
disappeared I think life would be great
and it wouldn't be great how so is it
because like you couldn't just watch any
movie I mean out driving I can't I
wouldn't be able to listen off the pill
podcast disgusting you're disgusting you
know what though really like
realistically I think a lot of people
would be to like become depressed I
really think like people are super
addicted to the Internet I think I am
right I think most of us are but there's
some people especially kids growing up
who only know the Internet life who are
they would be lost I think it would be
like where's my memes how do how do I
know what to say or think who do I copy
now you know not to change the subject
but ninja milk I am I'm a big fan like
congratulations in paying me for this
but ninja moe I was super excited for
because it's actually really good I
bought two cases I know to support I
appreciate it yeah no no we sent you
something I appreciate ya ninja Mel calm
in jammu calm a lot of people bought
actually yeah and I'm Michael over 2000
cases or ordered sweet yeah so I mean I
could say oh we sold tens of thousands
of cans but it doesn't sounds good when
you say the cases yeah so I mean it's
it's doing well I mean it is yeah that's
great but yeah you know we could do
better
yeah thanks for bringing that up I
wasn't going to well actually but it's a
lot a lot of people's concern was that
oh there's milk in it you know so do I
have to shake it or like Emily be
lactose intolerant oh not to shake it
yeah we know where people keep asking me
that because I guess they think it's
milk I mean there is milk in it but it's
not don't shake it yeah you should you
don't have to shake it you know like I
mean like I think you guys are somewhat
lactose intolerant right and then dude
when I eat cheese cakes bro the next day
the toilet is my best friend do my
cheeks are making out with that toilet
room
she cakes cheek cake dude but you don't
you drink you drink a couple cans yeah
diarrhea
yeah I drink a couple like and I don't
have diarrhea I just have caffeine
headaches that's the thing that I like
isn't caffeine a from this not from
coffee you get caffeine headaches a
little bit yeah from coffee I don't get
that I think you don't drink enough
water no I drink a lot I actually carry
a jug with me and I made sure to drink
like at least half of the jug so I'm
pretty healthy person except for the
fact that I eat like fried foods every
day and sheet cakes and cheat cakes you
know you know just like janae Aiko says
dude eat the cheek cakes like groceries
but just to sorry we change the subject
three times in this short segment but to
change it up again because we are doing
something different I would like to
announce and this is our 20th episode
we're gonna change up this podcast a
little bit and even more so thanks to
people like Skillshare people who
sponsored this so we can finally afford
we're opening up another podcast Natalie
yeah oh I was waiting for it is that
play
that doesn't fit hold on you're about to
get me opening up another podcast in LA
[Music]
so why are you guys opening uh what I
mean it was always kind of the plan if
once we could afford it things to
sponsors and stuff but because most of
our I mean I thought I could get guests
out here everyone we know is in LA
there's very few hot here and yeah I
think I want to change that up a little
bit and also this is supposed to be
temporary this room is very small yeah
looks big on camera though it does
surprisingly but it's it's not yeah I
can't wait for all the equipment to
leave so I can finally move in what yeah
this is my room in your part of the
house yeah anyway speaking of changes
though what we wanted to do is try out
these new segments kind of like shows I
guess within the podcast kind of
inspired off you know what you like
radio stations to do right they have
like a little like sometimes they do
pranks and sometimes they do like no
games and stuff so we have a few little
games that we wanted to try out who
knows if you guys don't like it we
probably won't do it but we have fun
doing it so we're gonna try out this new
game that we made up called don't dudes
the bit where we supposed to say we
didn't actually plan this out we just
made it up before before this like in
the kitchen so I say clearly three to
one should make yeah I think let's cut
to a graphic right sorry well we'll
improve it Paco explain the rules for
dumb dude dumb dude's debate it's hard
to say true not that different debate is
about basically you have two options of
a either goofy topic or more serious and
two dumb dudes have to debate it one
person gets to pick which side they
and then the other person has the
leftover side no matter if you believe
in that or not you must support it with
any sort of logic or just do your best
logic best yeah but wait should it be
like you get to choose which side you
want or should like someone else I know
whoever's like the middle - I can is
I'll just try I don't want to do this
right I want to watch YouTube you're
gonna have to do this guy's already we
can be okay we already do this I give
you guys Lee can I give you as a topic
okay I'm dudes debate all right let's
just start one because okay here we go
so I'm gonna start off with should dance
be considered a sport I want Paco to say
that it should not be okay I believe it
Ryan to say already I want Ryan to see
you know wait wait no I want Ryan to
believe yeah say that you do support it
okay okay you don't sir Paco doesn't
support it
Ryan supports it and I wish I had more
time to think about this who should be
considered this sport maybe Paco can go
first then they should not be a sport
there's no ball involved okay start with
something okay it's fine but there's a
lot of sports that don't have a ball
involved like well unless you're gonna
make a joke wrestling is a sport women's
wrestling is a sport I agree so but you
know
so you're saying every sport needs to
have a ball involved well swimming more
likely it's a sport there's water polo
and if you can water polo yeah but
swimming in it and therefore it requires
balls but swimming itself that's a sport
yeah yeah yeah your arguments invalid
I'm talking about most sports most
sports need balls alright okay we're
gonna move on to dance dance is more of
an art - it's more of an expression you
can dance with balls no yes you can't
dance with balls but even if you could
dance the balls how are you supposed to
score it like I think what makes a sport
if you're doing a school okay so tell me
this then tell me this when people do
ballerina or when they do uh like those
talent shows and they hold up numbers
yeah they were symbols well regardless
they do that right hmm that's a score
but it's also it's based off
technicalities also losing Kelly I'm
using all the a letís mmm that's what
dance is most fatality cuz I'm going to
kill it with this topic right here go
ahead
it's known that even in those words
judges are biased only for all sports
judges are biased don't Reaser bias - in
basketball yeah but it's very difficult
when there's a actual physical score
that you can see progressing throughout
the game I don't know tomorrow but I
don't know if I said I don't know we set
a time it we probably should do that in
the future because I don't we could go
on for days based on what we just talked
about who won this debate in your
opinion I'm or the time I'm gonna base
it off of passion which is which doesn't
really mean anything well I like passion
passion I think for this particular
round I'm gonna give it to Paco you have
three points yeah okay the points don't
matter just like in yes okay I got
another one okay how about this one
first of all wait all the dancers are
gonna handle a hate on no but that's but
that's the point is you don't have to
actually believe it but you have to
argue it they're trying to make it
delicious they're trying to make it in
the Olympics you do believe it huh I
mean cuz I'm I kind of went out of the
dance community so it's really up to
them actually you have yeah he used to
be a dancer No thank you he's a great
dancer no way I was in the top 16 of
freestyle session humblebrag
anywhere was was are you better than I
gave you something no no Eric was like
talking the world yeah there's an animal
an actual animal I've seen him eat it's
disgusting next dumb dude debates dumped
next dumb dudes debate question what's
better dogs or cats mmm
what do you do you have a preference
yeah what do you have a preference I
have a preference what do you I well
clearly your dog you know but what's
your record
I'll take cats okay all right guy that
makes a head this job easy okay go ahead
right dad we should do that we should
get to pick if you really want to argue
the other side are way more dope in what
way do cats are way more cool down there
they're low maintenance you don't kind
of walk them you literally can just
throw
anywhere anywhere and they'll just be
like walk up super slow take care of
that eat it boom okay good
sure also you know they teach you
real-life interactions and that
brain-dead like dogs dogs will just come
up to you and show you love no matter
what okay
sometimes a Catholic I don't really want
to talk to you that's like how humans
are man it teaches you you know the ebb
and flow did you hang of relation you
think having cats is a learning
experience that's why people get pets
people don't get pets because they they
want to learn about life they get pets
well you can learn that from dogs as
well but you get pets because for well
for one you know you can't use a what is
it blind blind eye cat there's no blind
eye cat so there's actually real uses
for dogs right there's actually uses for
dogs you can also use dogs to smell out
drugs cash can do that there's real uses
and then there's also like you said the
loving side the reason the most people
get dogs because they want love cats
don't give you that love cats can give
you lay don't you know what they give
you a bunch of fur balls everywhere
whoa have you ever had a cat in your
house yes it's crazy
Roku does the same thing he does nobody
imagine what imagine roku times three
four times four that's how much fur cats
leave are on all over the page is that a
fact
they leave way trust me i had it he had
a cat but there's ultra hyper allergenic
cats really so they don't shed yeah you
have to groom them
well baby hypo they don't there's
cats and don't oh you get those
really bald ones but be real dude yeah a
little bald looking cat I know people
there's a whole thing for people that
really like that be real would you want
a cat like that
no I win no you want a dog eats babies
there are small dogs too right are there
I haven't seen any that look like those
cats but there are okay I'll give you
this there are blogs that I kill people
then there are cats who kill people very
true but let's say that you know you
need those dogs to kill people let's say
they're helping protect people like
those canines that work for the police
you might need that too are you there
are they trained to kill I thought
they're just trained to me well they are
trained and they're trainable you can't
train a cat to do that you can train a
tiger can you Siegfried and Roy believe
we got yeah what this debate is over and
you wanted the cats I think it's dope I
think it's over no disrespect to any cat
owners out there
I am personally am a fan of dogs but
it's a lot of I know for others that it
might be offended I like cats man cats
are cool I like cats - I also like dogs
but I like dogs more I think I like cats
is because they're more just like just
super chill about a lot of things so you
like them because they're easy to take
care of because you're lazy well no I I
would want a dog - yeah but he had to
pick yeah would you like this is this
outside of the debate which if you had
to pick would you rather have a dog okay
I think you would want a cat because
it's easier to take care not to say I
would want a dog I think I know because
you would want a dog but like I think
you would enjoy a cat because it's so
easy yeah but then I would fit but and I
want a dog because like you said they
just blindly give love yeah that's all I
want man all people want different pets
yes we take the best part yeah if a cat
starts you know I'm not all cats like my
cat was actually like wasn't my cat my
brothers cat was actually like really
loving cuz it grew up with three other
dogs I think that's why but it would
come to you let you pet it but I've seen
cats that just you go to reach for it
and just runs away or they claw you yeah
they claw you thank you I got again
there's there's some dogs that do that
but most times not yeah well that's that
concludes these I thought we already
concluded we will yeah I guess it
concludes the the topic of dogs and cats
I think the winner of this debate I'm
unit I'm gonna go with Ryan all right
how many points you get cheers for you
ready folks don't matter there's one
more oh we got another one yeah I got
one more I got one more for you if you
guys are if you guys are open to it if
you want to hear you do this maybe yeah
all right sure or a three-way
I love three ways
well there goes our money story skill
oh yeah go ahead
skill shadow just go share what did you
really have another one though yeah I
did I did um what is what is the most
salad
what fruit salad or potato salad come up
with this what is the most salad I don't
even know right right uh try to argue it
this is hard this is a hard one are they
so this just because we don't have any
rules in this game
let's all just argue this right now okay
someone pick it doesn't matter because
this is your random one did you make
this up no found online yeah what is
salad what is the more so it is most
salad yeah fruit salad or potato so what
about macaroni salad sure that could be
one of all the options to salad what is
the fruits what I'm trusting sure a bowl
over fruit and then and then potato
salad is I tell you the Mayo and potato
yeah not just that there's other
ingredients what is more salad they're
both equally not salads yeah but you
have to pick one I'm gonna go with
potato okay I'll explain why I would go
with potato as well but all right I'll
go fruit then yeah then I think the
variety of a fruit salad is too much
when you think of your traditional salad
it's it's all green and it's all lettuce
for the most part as a lie and a half
we'll go ahead what else you got I think
there needs to be a vein you ever heard
of a chef's salad that thing is all over
the place never has every piece of
culture everywhere they got ham
they got egg they got cheese they got
olives they got dressing pick whatever
dressing you the lon whatever chef you
want dude he can bake what and he like
you want balsamic vinaigrette with ranch
that's a weird combination but you can
have that chef's salad all right mmm so
that's a lot of mixture
what about fruit so we got fruits from
around the world different things things
to spice up your taste buds all right
what are you gonna get oh is that
watermelon is that cantaloupe or is that
a turkey in terms of water you when you
think salad I'm being real technically
you're thinking real like when people
think salads right you think lettuce and
or whatever like there's different stuff
in it and dressing okay they're dressing
for fruits
yeah I don't know I'm asking I don't
know I mean no need for salad I don't
think there are yeah it's just fruits
together right bunch of different potato
salad I mean potato salad has a dressing
in itself already right well let's
define what a salad is like that most
people think about it's just lettuce and
all there's a lot of things it's lettuce
right there's no lettuce you could and
you could add other things
ya know but the main ingredient it's one
main ingredients your point yeah it's
one main ingredient not a bunch of rent
equally among both is is there a potato
in most salads no is there there fruit
in most sell it yes
tomatoes tomatoes is what there are
tomatoes so there's we're already
invading the salad we're pretty much
half the salad Moses a dumb one this is
a real argument that people looked up
yeah salad we're already also present
their song called berry vinaigrette dude
that's a dressing true and we put the
dressing on the salad we already put the
fruity sweet sup with the salad that's
the salad baby I think there needs to be
one main ingredient in his salad potato
salad is potato normal salad is lettuce
macaroni salad is macaroni nobody puts a
salad there's macaroni as well there's
more macaroni than there's potatoes so
the so if I have to choose between
potato salad in a fruit salad I would go
with potato salad because there's one
main ingredient
you can't moderate and pick for your own
side dude I'm moderating this one I
thought no I thought we were all
debating yes you're gonna debate
I moderate this and I say you guys are
equally dumb we're even talking about
this I think it's a stupid one I think
this is stupider than the other stupid
ones that we have this is the dumbest
one I mean why the segment's because I
don't I don't get it yeah we're dumb
guys dumb dudes debate damn one of those
dumb dudes do two dumb debates that's a
lot of dumb dudes do tend to play just
don't do to dumb debates while
doo-dooing we could we use the outro
thing to cut off cut us off at any point
so but also uh if you guys have any
other suggestions for dumb dudes
debate leave them in the comments below
or if you wants to stop doing this show
within the podcast please say bit
outside of that we'll keep it in the
kitchen where we normally do anyway save
save save on the show yeah let's get
back to just being us yeah like that
that was justice being us though that
kind of we'd already do like kinda way
we just formed it into a show um but
it's fun it's fun to do stuff like that
is pretty fun yeah we do do that though
yeah I kind of feel lost now I don't
know what to talk about I think we
should be fighting over something that's
mom we talked a little bit about the
podcast movement to LA yes so we're it's
gonna be um can I say it it's at your
house whose house your house oh is it's
at what yeah I'm gonna put it in your
house I don't have a house there where
am i yes well once I get all the stuff
they're like you know put it in my house
yeah we're gonna have a podcast in your
house specifically your bed I would have
it in my house but I don't have a house
there I go I guess it's at my house now
yep we're gonna have a podcast at
David's house I'll be out there a little
bit more and we're gonna get some
already have a lot of people who are
willing to be on the show name have to
do it you don't have to do when I go out
there a whole tour of people's podcast
so I always say like alright when I come
to LA then
through the pot there's so many I have
to do are you doing them all in one day
I don't think this possible is only
traffic right it's not possible these
podcasts are like hour to two hours long
there's some podcast though that I'm
like a little intimidated by like what
like Ethan's podcast mmm
83 yeah they get their fans are very
like they're vicious harsh they will
destroy you yeah that's why I'm like I
don't I feel like David on here like I
feel like I have to be that's why I mean
to you because I'm getting you ready oh
is that why you're harsh critiques yeah
I'm definitely shaving for that one
definitely I don't want people make fun
of me you know what they're does but
there's not much controversy from your
side thank mean they don't they don't
they usually have guests that are
controversial in essence not always but
the comments are just kind of harsh on
that podcast yeah another one somebody
keeps asking me they're like you know
life it's not somebody people keep
asking me like oh what Paquette like
what podcast would you want to do and I
don't want to do the ones that I listen
to because it's like man that's
intimidating you know like Paula Rogan
Joe Rogan I would never do that I would
I mean that would be an honor but no
it's great what I've heard about his
podcast like he's had like like famous
people on it Mike Tyson like but he only
interviews people that he's interested
in yeah yeah
so could you imagine if you asked like
hey I want to be on the podcast he's
like I'm not interested in you I would
now I hate you hard no not at all I
would make no real sense cuz I'd be like
what would we talk about his pockets are
so like he's like scientists on you know
like what am I gonna contribute
Oh Joe I'm just not talking as myself
I'll wake up and then I write Oh Joe I
was just picturing myself on Joe's
podcast oh he's gonna hear me yeah yeah
[Laughter]
laughing so hard I could almost take a
shishi break let's take yeah yeah it is
actually
I'm done that was a long segment we did
with the whole yeah it's funny
I liked it JC time bye and we're back
Oh at you're gonna read read read read
yeah mmm and you crumpled up the paper
great I was just so hype you go for it
for it but again guys this episode is
brought to you by Skillshare again
Skillshare is an online community class
where you can learn things and it's free
for the first two months so if you're
not learning things for the first free
two months then you're being a dummy
don't be a dummy social media makes you
dumb use social media to make you
smarter broken out so well even a dummy
like Ryan Higa can get it join the
millions of students already learning on
Skillshare today with a special offer
just for our listeners Skillshare comm
/e go boom that was very good good you
tied it in somehow having way too much
fun with that mission I actually have
been trying really hard not to use them
don't know if you guys know because well
people won't know because it cuts to you
guys when you're talking about almost
like
I'm like waiting for the right moment
cuz I want to I want to use it but I'm
not going to hold him back thank you we
appreciate that Brian he get to see
better do you guys hear about that
straight parade straight pride straight
pride pride pride pride parade straight
Pride Parade you sure about it yeah yeah
I saw it artic with Justin this morning
actually and I thought it was a joke but
it's not
I realized it wasn't you know as it was
opposed by a lot of my gay friends and
they were very upset I don't really know
what it was about I thought it was just
like people trolling I assume is people
trolling right nope knowing well I know
it's a real thing but they're trolling
like they're obviously like what what
are you gonna be proud about like
hugging you
I mean can you be pride later prideful
of that like oh I'm so straight yeah but
where the
isn't that the majority of people do use
more straight people and it's more
socially acceptable that's the whole
point of having gay pride right its Gay
Pride Month it is yeah so your birthday
month it is today
mm-hmm birthday happy birthday Ryan dude
too bad you weren't gay because then
we'd be like happy birthday and it's
yeah it's same time a month yeah that'd
be great
oh sure birthday dude eve all like like
gay people this month can say happy
birthday that's a that's a night one
dude you really kind of run far with
this joke no I really wish some was like
happy birthday did that be amazing I
would go to a birthday party just come
out dude just come out of the closet or
you know who'd want to go to it's so bad
we know just come on cause Gary dude
straight straight Pride Parade is not
gonna be it's one of the gay pride
parade if you think about it what is
that even do you even look into this are
we just talking about nothing what do
you do I'm like well I mean so what is a
Gay Pride per well gay pride parade is a
place where like homosexuals go and they
celebrate and their diversity and raise
awareness and they have colorful Flags
and way too much glitter and maybe you
know a lot of touching and high-fiving I
would assume straight pride parades have
to be the opposite of that what would
that look what is the opposite black and
white flags that's it welcome to shades
of grey different yeah it would be the
the gay pride parade flag but just like
without any color like you put a black
and white filter on it I wonder why the
rainbow became the sign of gay yeah
that's good one as you know in Hawaii we
are our like uh-1 or like our college
team is closing the ring we wore the
rainbow where the Rainbow Warriors we
were just the rainbows at Fir oh yeah we
were the rainbow were just a rainbow and
then it became because it's white
there's a lot of rainbows right makes
sense and then it just became this like
gay symbol and well now we're just the
four years really the Warriors but you
still got people throwing Rainbow
Warriors that's where we were yeah so
maybe Hawaii's homophobic hmm or were
the Rainbow Warriors so
hawaii's fighting for gay pride could be
that's here yeah yeah well I just I
don't know I don't see what the rainbow
has to do with gay yeah I'm just I'm
just curious ya know there's probably a
reason that's a great question I I don't
I don't even know ya what do you think
it means that you think it means like
just accepting every color yeah more of
a race or like it could be like a
diversity thing you know like I like
roses
rainbows should be like for I'm against
racism because I like yes color
absolutely versus so so what would the
gate we're like changing the simple
about what would the gate like if we had
to make a new flag right that represents
like I think for yeah well I'm not a
racist straight men make a flag but
we're using logic like we're literally
saying I accept every color and it makes
sense right if you're not racist yeah so
how would you wouldn't you want to with
the same colors yeah I mean that's true
actually like I'd like a maybe like a
pink and a red versus or like a yellow
in a orange like pink pink something
blue so no like yeah traditional not be
were gonna say oh so you're assigning
colors to maybe that's why they didn't
you so they could stay away from that
hmm and that was PC this out the week
damn you didn't do like a synchronized
in do anything do it go be seeing it
softly he's a singer so you like
imitates really well mm-hmm but um my
topic at her I'm actually really I like
kind of can you look that up real quick
cuz I'm actually really curious what the
how did the rainbow become a symbol of
gay yeah it is right like it is it's I'm
not like just
otherwise they all just like got
together and just real smart about their
branding yeah
you know what I found the answer here
what says the rainbow flag was
popularized as a symbol of the gay
community by San Francisco artist
Gilbert Baker in 1978 and know that no
because he actually has a collaboration
with Nike for their shoes coming out
okay
the be true selection guy okay so some
guy did that but why like why what does
it mean the different colors are often
associated with diversity
yeah it's like a community
but actually have literal meanings oh
look into those literal meanings I think
you think URIs mother said I am I was
wondering yeah what does it have to do
it just became a common like common
knowledge if the run was a success eh
mm-hmm right the lgbtq probably one in
78 sorry red life orange healing yellow
sunlight green nature blue harmony peace
and purple violet spirit it sounds like
you're just naming things that sound
like the color yeah so what does that do
with a movement though you know what we
should probably add 74 head no word
Baker did come on the show because well
we could yeah you know if he comes on
though ask him if we can get some those
be true shoes though they're pretty
clean dude they weren't she's really
nice be true what is it he true I
believe that's what's called be true
it's a collection that he does with Nike
and I think I think every year they're
having a release during this month
they're dope how do you guys feel about
this is kinda edgy oh honey how do you
guys feel about when you would I mean
just I'm only bringing this up because
it's Gay Pride Month yeah how do you
guys feel about people telling you not
to eat at chick-fil-a oh man wait you
gotta go there with me
bro I don't I know you guys love I love
chick-fil-a too but there's some
articles that I read and I'm like and I
feel so guilty
well let me sum is I don't more recently
like how do I make up for that so that I
can still hey you know more recently I
heard that chick will actually donated a
lot of money like to the you know
there's that big shooting in the club
and yeah long time ago but they did well
they do
they did donate argue that that's kind
of a PR thing right cuz I mean they had
that reputation right the whole the
whole drama there for people who don't
know it's because they're a Christian
company and I guess in the what what is
the whole drama there there's a lot of
drama there but I'm not exactly sure
what incidents it was that they
supported Christian organizations that
support anti-gay laws right something
like that probably I that too and also
just like the way that they said
traditional traditional marriages right
so the
so I understand that and obviously like
if I'm you know I've been in a situation
where I was we were trying to figure out
what to eat and I was with a gay guy and
he like we all decided let's go
chick-fil-a he really really felt
strongly so we didn't right yeah and I
don't mind that but and I think that's
right and I think that's fine that we
still wanted it but like we didn't go
because out of respect but is it still
wrong because I read articles that make
you just feel like a novel person is it
still wrong to go to chick-fil-a on your
own because you're supporting something
that doesn't support like your friends
are like you know I've read articles
that make me stay I see they're like I
don't go there all the time but like I
like I like the food you know like I
can't I'm not gonna pretend like I don't
but am i supporting something by going
there do I'm saying like yeah for sure
it was kind of like the whole like thing
we talked about me being not being
vegetarian even though I feel bad for
you know how all animals are slaughtered
and stuff it's it's a selfishness yeah
the vegetarian one is a little bit more
understanding that's because Gabe Gay
Pride Month it's a little hard to say
that but I'm not gonna I'm gonna be
honest like I like their products yeah I
mean I was gonna come in agreeance with
that like when you tie it into the whole
like vegan or vegetarian thing but
that's what I'm trying to say it's like
I read those articles like last year
when that happened and like I was like
yeah this makes sense I'm just not gonna
eat there I don't need to but then I you
know I used sometimes a whole year goes
by I know you kind of crave sometimes
and yeah I know I went there and I have
gay friends and I have respect them and
I understand it you feel like I'm not
trying to sit like I'll still support
them but like I don't I don't know there
are also a lot of agree with the
correlation yeah there are also a lot of
gay people who do still go to
chick-fil-a I know there are but I'm
talking about the huge amount of people
who will be really mad at me even saying
this ball so I'm a question I have a
question how much of my spicy chicken
deluxe meal is going towards gay hate
how much if you could get an yeah of how
much hate you're contributing what would
that affect you what if it was fractions
of
penny oh but it's still that's the
principle right is the principle it's a
principle but what if there was a dollar
amount do you think that would make
people gonna be like oh maybe I
shouldn't oh sure
you know do this or would you think
people are like oh it's fractions of a
penny you know or like what they could
do right hear me out
you have if I know what the value is
right they find out what that fraction
of a penny is right yeah and you say
they offer you hey would you like to add
pay an extra dollar to support gay gay
rights and equality it would never do
this but they say okay I'm going to
chick-fil-a I'm gonna donate $1 to
support equal rights for gay people
that's just to make myself feel better
dude what make you that would be I think
a organisation really cool with that cuz
in there getting something not they
would have never got it like yeah out of
guilt in their movement like they're
like you know I like Salvation Army yeah
whatever yeah they're outside they're
ringing the bells or people who are like
save the whales they have you sign a
petition so like people ask you like how
many times have you had chick-fil-a this
year and then you tell oh yeah so you
can do that and then you don't have that
guilt exactly now I think organizations
should think about it because there's a
lot of people like me I think who really
like their products and don't wanna you
know yeah upset that community yeah and
then you be like well this everybody
wins
mm-hmm they get my money and you get my
money and I get my food those delicious
I don't know what I really went well I
think we're gonna get I like chick-fil-a
I I love I know you I think they're
really the service is great you know
it's it's hard yeah they're one of the
nicest like the workers yeah the best
you know I know there's a bunch of
towards the towards the like the
co-founders and yet a company but the
people who work there are literally like
have you ever been there they're like
the nicest they're trained to be though
yeah they're supposed to be that way
yeah what's they have to say something
all the time
they even oh they say my pleasure my
pleasure instead of like you're welcome
because they're there to serve people
and and have
yeah no faster there's like really like
small things like that that just make
you feel like oh nice nice P some people
in relationships don't even hear that
yeah I think I think everyone should be
able to eat wherever they choose to
whatever the organization believes
because it's its food but it doesn't
mean you don't leave in it right it you
are supporting it is what the articles
yeah I write are saying but you know
I've also seen like in because I go to
the the chick-fil-a in Hollywood I see a
lot of gay people there too I do too I
even saw a before they're all gay Pia is
here's the thing like nobody really
knows what the companies generally stand
for in general like for example we don't
know if the manufacturer of this table
right now is like a racist a racist or
if there's a person who you know some
supports gay marriage or doesn't support
we don't know these things for majority
of the products that we use in this
world I guess the the question is like
if you're if you know that they do that
is it bad to support even if it is a
great product you know and I think
people should still be able I mean
people should just make that choice for
themselves you know and shouldn't judge
if someone else
I have chooses to like but there's gonna
be there that's exactly the point there
a lot of people are being very much so
judged especially gay people then they
should they're like oh yeah that like
how dare you yeah like this is going
against what you are and I mean it's it
was actually the article is more
targeted towards gay people who go to
chick-fil-a and people who support equal
rights like the act like active people
who still go there yeah
and they made a very compelling are I
don't know what where that article was
from yeah there's it there was a couple
because it's you know gay pride ones but
I mean look if me if I found out that
McDonald's promotes Wars or like putting
sends money to terrorists it'd be really
hard for me to not eat filet-o-fish when
I'm craving it but when you say supports
you know Wars and stuff like we'd have
to see what exactly have they done yeah
like is it
oh they support like like nobody's gonna
support I support war you know there has
to have some like even when you're when
they're supporting their religion yeah
and it just so happens that their
religion has that clause and you know
like it's not like there's trying to
support I just don't like gay people
or a certain type of people it's because
it's in the religions whatever they
believe I don't think any like
McDonald's be like hey I support war
unless it's like in the religion or
simply did right right but what I'm
saying is it's not like they're just
supporting that for that reason I don't
think anybody does things just for the
fact of like hate right it's because of
what they it might be hateful but I
don't think they intentionally do things
to like be hateful yeah I don't think
it's more often I think the the
protection of their own beliefs and
values or their rights type of thing or
their like it's a lot of times like oh
like people just being selfish because
they're worried about oh how is this
gonna affect me you know so a lot of
times like when a smaller minority group
who's been oppressed when they're like
trying to raise awareness or ask for
equality a lot of times the higher
higher groups in quotes you know will be
worried because they're like oh well our
privileges or our lifestyle have to
change you know and in the it's in the
same way we're like if this is gonna be
a stretch of a metaphor but in the same
way with divorce how women wall is if
they're married to a successful in rich
man and when they get divorced the the
money that they get paid they get paid a
lot more because they're used to the
lifestyle you know
that's what they say the argument is
used to the lifestyle so a lot of times
that in that same aspect the the people
who are in power they're worried like oh
well I have to adjust my lifestyle you
know and how am I good how am I gonna be
used to this new movement this new wave
so that was our topic on chick-fil-a
happy I just thought it was interesting
you know I thought guilty I'm sorry I
have to say I'm sorry no support eat
right you want yeah I support equal
rights but I don't I don't feel like
even if I if they have enough money
right those foundations what do they
really what can they really do I guess
they can change laws that's what they
can do
but I don't really know I don't know
what
like I don't know enough I don't know
the truth I'm just hearing one
perspective to person like I mean I'm
hearing the perspective of gay people
yeah who are mad at me for going there
not me specifically but us I don't know
I think there will be a lot of gay
people who are okay with you going to
chick Floyd because there's a lot but I
mean there's a very huge majority and
articles like that cuz I read it and I
was like I can go there by the time I
finished reading it I was like oh man
people this is compelling like I I don't
need to go there and then throughout the
year I was like there all the time don't
worship the place no it's just a chicken
sandwich come on
I know just a simple some people are
just saying would like to get upset I
get it
I get I get their reasoning I get their
reasoning going just get it to a topic
that's not gonna get us in trouble
should we go to check for this okay
let's get let's change topic this wasn't
a heart I know I know but you know what
I'm laughs I like talking about this
because it's interesting it is other
people relate to it no no yeah because
it's a cop it's a it's a thought that
people have people only may not voice it
because they're worried like oh if I say
this does it make me a bad person
I think it's a common thought to have
like Oh will I offend people see what
they're having is what I think too is
like a lot of people might have that
thought but once they read that article
and they see the majority they see what
most people find like what's the easiest
way to not upset people there they trick
themselves to being like I'm not gonna
think twice if this is right there's no
right or wrong like this is what's right
I'm saying that it isn't or it is I'm
just saying people there's a lot of
people I think who don't even think
twice they just follow what's exactly
like if that was a less common opinion I
think it would be the opposite like if
people like to go with what's working
and what gets you
I guess less hate some people like
getting more hate I don't know where I'm
going with that
hhor-- pinion i think it what's
beautiful is that Lyman has it of their
own have their own beliefs values and
you're trying to not get hate comments
you're trying to do all right I eat a
chick flick all the time I actually went
there last week did you really I did
yeah Wow
you know what you should do those but it
doesn't make me a bad horse what about
this what about this yeah kind of going
back to what we said maybe there's a
sale you donate load that who will say
that you are a bad person for going last
week you know what those people are
whacked how about if not let's
compromise okay it's it's Gay Pride
Month I will not go there for the month
of June mmm I don't even go every month
so that's not even how about this how
about someone how about someone in the
gay community create something better
than chick-fil-a and all yes exactly
that's difficult all I care about is
having a good chicken set is true and if
it tastes good I'm gonna go or what they
chick-fil-a should do well I guess their
whole thing is like based on religion in
principle they should just bring in like
a gay CEO but he would they would never
do that yeah Wow so hateful something
that would not get us into trouble for a
change
you're right over there oh sorry I'm
dying I think I'm actually getting sick
for the first time in two years
you got sick in tweet just the first
time in getting ready not me getting
sick in his first time in two years are
you the type of person that gets sick
once you get sick you're sick for like
three weeks straight I don't know
because I haven't been sick for two
years so you don't remember three years
ago no I don't remember I hardly
remember things from last week do you
even remember what you ate yesterday I
know David a chick-fil-a a week ago well
I know a Barbie was just rotted sorry
I died yeah I probably ate chili I don't
know what day but who cares you know so
how am I supposed to remember the last
time you guys eight years ago yeah why
are we talking about it's not
interesting I'm Jamil calm thanks David
go to ninja milf calm
[Music]
all right let's talk about something
that's not gonna get us into trouble for
a change
I think let's just change it up
something little light you know a spicy
edge oh my god oh stop bringing the
chicken references that's in this light
something happen they do not get
something that's not gonna get us into
trouble let's go what don't you guys do
this week I mean that's went to chick oh
my god I'm sorry just kidding I know I
know I'm sorry
good I didn't do anything today's my
birthday and I'm so I'm doing this like
this is my my dream yeah like this is
what I wanted I really wanted this but
um yeah I didn't do anything I didn't I
actually forgot it was my birthday
mmm up until yesterday I forgot that it
was coming up and then what are we doing
tonight for your birthday nothing
what who's gonna keep this going for
another five hours we're gonna go
somewhere we're gonna do something all
right yeah hey you know what though like
in all honesty I'm not being like oh I
don't need the attention guy I really
don't want to do anything is that okay
no we know that you don't what's my
birthday I get to pick to do nothing we
want to do something I do for you do it
for your boy your for your friend all
right so I want what I really want for
my birth is for you guys to go out with
you all right and send me your Instagram
stories okay well do something what do
you I don't know we'll figure it out
yeah what'd you do this week though
let's do something so great okay this is
something don't don't know so you see
the dogs you can't tell it to a cat they
won't understand no all right let's
let's do something so crazy so that the
next podcast should be like all right
guys we really regret remember that last
podcast something went down yeah let's
start the podcast with that okay I see
if you were here last podcast we
shouldn't have ended it that way because
something went down
went down David actually lost the finger
alright now we gonna make that hat like
you're giving a narrative like I did
that's the baby wait is this a thing oh
yeah oh yeah yeah it's all a childish
sorry I didn't even think of that
because my mind isn't dirty mine is it
is bob was natural I'm the natural dirty
person I think we're good dude I hope
that's what he did this week do we
really care because because I know let
me finish I know what he's gonna be
Sarah T the ongoing joke what did you do
today yeah what did you do this oh I'm
sorry not today what do you do this week
I just worked
oh that's nice okay I didn't think he
was gonna say that yeah did a little bit
of work on the app stuff mmm it's called
taco mm-hmm and then I went chick flick
I'm done all right
add off the pill podcast where I add off
the pill on Twitter ad off the pill
podcast on Instagram what I did is you
Paco nope
don't you dare what you dare don't you
dare we are done I went to KFC they're
not Christian are they I don't know
there actually I went to churches
churches chicken churches chicken they
got good chicken I actually never been
there they got good chickens I went to
Popeyes also all right number one
chicken spot
chick-fil-a oh I'm done I'm done