if you don't believe in God then you
will go to hell when you die based on
your science religion you don't have to
agree with other people but you
shouldn't be slamming them for not
believing in what you believe
I think Krisha is definitely on a bad
rep it has also been misrepresented Joey
clapping clap do this spent a long time
kind of clap welcome back to another
episode of off the pill podcast oh I
forgot we've been playing the song I
don't know if you know where that is but
[Music]
sure
anyway today Paco is gone so we have
will in the moderator see we got David
Choi in the house welcome back to Vegas
David thanks for having me here okay you
can quickly get the thing now it's been
a while huh for you
what do you mean that was good I mean
yeah it wasn't bad it just said it's
been a while
welcome back David thanks welcome back
we'll get more recently more recently
welcome back we're doing welcome back me
we're back in Las Vegas as you can see
and um this is kind of a last-minute one
it's a last-minute podcast because I
have to go to Japan it's a cool name my
brother get married in Japan destination
weddings you know how come you never
bring your brother Kyle he doesn't want
to do it
have you ever had any episode with him
no Kyle on the episode no I mean he has
a very heavy pidgin accent too which is
fine because we're trying to get max all
the way on here next time let's do it
yeah some titles yeah no but he acts
I understand I understand you understand
talks to me yeah yeah and if we get max
on that's what we might need some
subtitles I don't need it can you
understand everything max says I can I
don't think I've ever heard him talk on
UFC what do you mean
max for Lily that don't know max
Holloway is the featherweight champion
of the world and he also started the kik
challenge like the back kicking at the
bottom I don't think it's charter I
don't think he started it he made it
famous we know he did know he did it he
gave credit to someone else
oh that's why he tagged John Mayer he
was one of the first big people to make
it big - he kind of made he didn't
create it but he made the bottle as he
called bottle Autobahn cap challenge the
bottle cap challenged essentially he's
the UH he's a fighter from Hawaii and
we're talking to some folks to get him
on the show yeah he has a heavy pidgin
accent so yeah so I mean can you are you
gonna document the wedding of your your
best thing about vlogging some mm-hmm
why I think I mean I probably want to
meet Kyle or see him he's been in videos
before
but he's not I mean like he hasn't
really talked much it's cuz he's a bit
heavy accent pidgin accent and I don't
know if he can disguise it or not I like
him he's a cool guy okay
anyway what what has been going on area
51 that happened yes since we were back
in Vegas
we didn't go actually raka raka went did
you see that no he actually went out and
he made it in the news like his pictures
there with him dressed up with his face
all painted and I think he was with that
girl that I don't know who he was with
someone I think it might have been that
Riley real point porn girl Riley yeah I
don't need disrespectful adult
entertainer yep yeah I think he was with
her I mean I don't know I could be wrong
I could be just like saying the wrong
thing but how come you guys didn't go
you guys live out here it's actually far
from here isn't it I said alarm for it
and it went off and I slept in on
accident so basically for those that
don't know nothing happened
really right yeah what he actually
stormed it right that's what I heard and
then I also heard that there was a
concert called alien fest that took
place there as well uh-huh I don't know
anyone that went and people that were
asking me or like yeah you live a year
ago and I thought they were joking and I
was like laughing and they're like no
are you gonna go it's like oh there's
million there was so many there was
millions of people signed up for it and
I think like I don't know what the
numbers are maybe look up how much
people actually went but it wasn't I saw
a picture and there wasn't that many
people well the cards good it was a
decent turnout but I mean nobody's
stormed it obviously it's a joke but I
thought there would be at least one or
two dummies that just rush maybe I'm
sure maybe there was mmm I hope not yeah
it says here that there are only
hundreds of people The Guardian says
that 75 people were at the gate whoa
that's it no there was more than that
right I don't know the Guardian picture
of something else then according to the
Guardian the gate is located on the
washboard dirt roads and is a rugged
journey but about 150 people managed to
get within selfie distance whoa one
person was arrested at the raid
also someone did do it and that charge
was for public urination so nobody
actually went in right right
damn do you guys believe in aliens
aliens I think that's different I mean
if you believe it that they exist do you
believe they exist well I think so I
think it's kind of almost silly to not
think they exist have you ever seen one
no I've never had any kind of experience
which is kind of interesting to think
about because if I've never had a
personal experience usually that's what
I judge like my opinions on things for
but for aliens I think in terms of how
many numbers of universes there are
right it's kind of it would be nearly
impossible for me how do you define an
alien though like extra I think there's
some there's other things that we don't
know about if they count as aliens then
yeah like the ones that you see you know
like the the ones with the big eyes and
the pointy 'f Chan or whatever they
called the greys yeah the stereotypical
alien do you believe that those types of
beings may have existed or do exist so
any form of intelligent life that looks
kind of like what we yeah mainstream
media from outside of the earth yeah I
think it's very possible I mean I think
a lot of people claim things from what
they've seen well obviously we have
learned a lot from movies and stuff like
that mm-hmm
and again that could be coming from just
someone's imagination or it could be
coming from real accounts because it has
been real cosmic who knows if they're
telling the truth or not mm-hmm but I
think that if it's very possible that
these aliens are just humans that
evolved to that point mmm and they're
actually like like I said I mean it I
like from the future right they're the
future versions of us essentially I mean
this is this just one theory there's so
many yeah I don't know enough we should
have like a segment if we start talking
about this stuff we all pull out tinfoil
hats the chocolate kiss on his head but
yet I think it's possible that's also
think it's possible that we are living
in a simulation I mean you've heard that
I've heard this before
because there's no weight I mean the
thing is there's with that theory
there's no way you can say yes or no
that it's true or not there's no way you
can tell that we know yeah and even if
you did know well who cares what can you
do about it right you know there's
nothing if we are in a simulation right
now there's doesn't it doesn't matter
like it's nothing we can do about it
right yeah so what's like the
correlation between I mean there is a
correlation in some theories between
aliens and simulation theory right for
the universe something some aliens and
simulation well I was thinking that I
mean this is I don't even know if I've
heard this theory I just thought mm-hmm
about it that aliens essentially they're
higher levels of and I'm just seeing
aliens and abroad you know intelligent
being yeah there's some there's a
there's a level that we don't understand
a level of intelligence essentially that
if they were at that level we wouldn't
be able to comprehend it anyway and
that's like us being us like they
created it's a simulation and then we're
in it right it's like like if we were to
turn on the Sims and create a world for
the Sims
right and they're living in that little
world they would never know we existed
controlling them right or it's like you
can't explain to an ant what a
automobile is right right you can't
explain math recently I don't know where
I saw this but someone was talking about
describing different dimensions or yeah
third dimension of fourth to me I don't
know what it's called but it's an ant
like if it an ant or on a table and
there was like an object on the table
and you were to take it away it would
have just disappeared to the end but
really we just moved it under the table
or something like that I don't know what
I'm talking about
I'm just butchering that but yeah I
think I think it's possible but I think
what I mean I'm gonna try to come at it
from a different angle but I think an
ant in animals are very different to
come I find it tough to compare animals
to human beings because you know animals
are instinctual like they they act on
instincts right you you throw a bone and
they're gonna run after it right but
humans we have a soul I believe we have
a soul and and I think that we have a
choice we have freewill to make a
decision like I can decide to slap you
and I don't think that
there's a I don't think we're I mean I
can I can entertain the thought of
having a living in a parallel universe
but because we have this free will in a
choice to make and in emotions right
which can drive us in and move us in
different ways and we can also create
that's what makes us different than
animals is we actually can create pieces
of art and different things I think
we're much more intelligent beings
much more you know we have more more
depth and like you know I have a choice
to like slap you right right now I could
throw something at you or whatever I
want to do but to say we're in a
parallel universe in and it's like The
Sims where you know we would control
this character but I don't think there's
something controlling the way that you
know like my decisions that I make how
do you know how do you know everything
you just thought right now wasn't
controlled by some higher intelligence
that's programming you or programmed you
to essentially think this in this way I
think that I would like to see Ides of
yeah what people believe yeah I mean
yeah for sure you can choose some people
believe you know I mean just to be to
clarify you're Christian I'm a Christian
and I I believe we were created by a
create tour that you know in in in the
creator's image so the Christians
believe that God is the creator of the
universe you know it's just the
beginning the beginning of time yep
right I mean there are Christians that
do believe in the Big Bang right that
was the beginning of what happened I
mean Christians you'd be stupid to not
believe in science right science is not
the complete opposite of religion
science is in a way its own religion
it's a yeah it's definitely theories
there's theories and there's facts
within science but I think that you know
I believe we were created because the
question that and you know III if I'm
being honest I do struggle with it
sometimes in regards to were we really
created right and but I have to go back
in time and nobody was ever there right
you could have been a million years ago
it could have been this is anybody argue
about we're not argue about we talk
about I'll talk about a lot because
we're into this kind of stuff but you
know if you look at the Big Bang it's
basically to dust
particles coming at each other and then
hitting each other and then turning into
something but for two particles to move
there needs to be a force right so if
there's a force like whose builds that
momentum or that gives that push for
that particle to even be there in the
first week where that particle come from
is it energy like was the universe
always there like why why is there
energy moving you know there needs to be
something that pushes that so it's tough
for me to believe that it so I always
have to question what came before that
so you're saying you believe that
there's something behind the curtain
even at the very beginning of where
science starts yeah yeah it's like if
though if you're saying if the particles
that collided is that's the Big Bang
Theory right yeah and that's what
created the universe universe universe
yeah what area was it in before that for
one and then who created the particles
we create the force right and what I'm
saying is and like you said there's no
way to really know for a fact yeah and I
think with scientists who there's the
whole point of science is doubt right
like they always doubt and they're
trying to learn more by doing
experiments and after X many times they
come up with a theory right of doing the
same thing over and over but they're
still always doubt so there's no exact
nobody has the exact 100% answer that's
always say there's no 100% right um but
you're saying from your perspective that
well I mean you struggle with it because
you're very logical yeah but what do you
what are your thoughts on that then my
thought is that my lot like if I'm being
extremely logical or you're a very
Christian person we can talk about that
tightly I think my because I'm also very
logical to and try to be as realistic as
possible I do think that I think that it
makes logical sense for me that there
was something whether it be a God of the
Bible or God of whatever it was or some
sort of energy or you know whatever it
was I mean we could say that some people
could say that there were aliens before
us right that created Earth but at the
same time it's like okay then where the
aliens come from was did they have their
own form of a Big Bang yeah but what I
mean what I mean is like I mean
essentially we're the whole simulation
thing we're talking about is
almost the same theory it's just we're
renaming it in a we're like masking it
because really the aliens are God in
this scenario in the simulation you
created the simulation right right God
created the particles or whatever you're
trying to say right the Big Bang or
whatever I don't I don't know the I
don't know the Bible well well enough to
compare it yeah but essentially is it in
your head possible that God is just an
alien or someone in the future or some
higher level of intelligence I think
it's um rated this you know yes actually
I think it's something worth discussing
and like talking about yeah but isn't it
in your in Christianity yeah almost like
sinful to be thinking in that way no no
God God didn't give us a brain to think
like in a box you know he I think when
God was the creator like there are a set
of rules to live by that help govern
human beings because govern because
human beings by nature are sinful
creatures right like if we act on
instinct if I if I really acted on
instinct I would if someone cut me off
on the street I'd want to punch them
right but but we have these rules and
regulations to govern us as human beings
so that we can choose to make a good
decision choose to be a good person we
can choose to do these things but it's
ultimately the choice that we have so
with that being said we're allowed to
think about these other things there are
a lot of philosophers you know even you
know Einstein questioned this a lot too
right so I think it's it's very powerful
this this whole concept of free will
that we can think whatever we want to
think we can behave however we want to
behave we can you know dream whatever we
want to dream we could debate whatever
we want to debate and I think that's
healthy to either reaffirm your faith or
if you don't if you don't believe if you
don't agree with some of the things then
you know you can you can you can make
that decision I think that's the freedom
that is given within this this religion
if it's if it is I mean I'm just at this
point kind of talked about some of this
stuff but
just for the sake of argument sure if if
based essentially if God created
everyone right and he knows everything
about that person what they're gonna do
in their future is that really free will
though if God you know how everybody
says oh gods this is God's path or well
I don't know what they say some sayings
like that
if God's created you yeah God's will
whether you made mistakes in your past
and you corrected them like you're on
this certain path that God created for
you right God created that path is that
really free will because he's like in a
simulation if you compute and you put
these certain you put in a code for this
character this character is gonna think
like this he's gonna believe in free
will
he's gonna believe I'm gonna make these
mistakes I'm gonna learn from these
mistakes I'm gonna believe that God that
God created this is that still
considered free well I don't know if
that made sense
well actually I know you're asking and
and I think it's a question that a lot
of you know people of many faiths think
about and you know they could struggle
with it or they'll have their own answer
or feel peace what do you think so what
I think is for me you know this is this
is definitely something that I've I've
thought about and I am still on a
journey right - it's as of learning in
and all that but I think the way that I
see it is if we understood everything
every sort of abstract abstract concept
then we wouldn't be God I mean if we
sorry would be God it would be we would
be God if we understood every single
abstract concept right but because God
let's let's just say if God did exist
mm-hmm
God would not be a great it wouldn't he
wouldn't be a god if he thought on our
level right if he thought in the way
that we thought then yeah it does it
just doesn't make sense right he
wouldn't be a God God needs to be an
all-powerful all-knowing all-loving and
cut so I mean like with that admitting
that the admitting that we don't think
on that level yeah how do we know that
we got it right how do we know that so
essentially if we're nothing on that
level we don't
we're just thinking in terms of what
humans know and what we've learned over
time from a book yep right and
essentially like we don't know for sure
we don't but but what do we know that
we're that how do Christians know right
so that's something called faith so I
think faith applies not only in
Christianity but I think faith can apply
in your lives just your daily lives
whether you're a Christian or not right
you have faith that when you drive from
home to the grocery store that that car
coming against you on the other side
with just the line dividing you isn't
gonna turn in crash into you and kill
you sure right you have faith that
you're gonna get to that destination and
I think in the same way you know
Christians have to operate in that way
right I think like I said God gives you
a choice you can follow you know and
learn more about me right mean like God
God wants you to learn about him so
that's why he gave us you know the word
so you can read through it sorry I don't
mean to sound like I'm preaching though
no I mean I think it's I think that's
why it's interesting because ya see your
perspective yeah so it's more like he
gives you the choice it's like you know
God's not God doesn't like condemn
people Jesus doesn't condemn people but
it's more like you make certain
decisions and there are consequences so
for example I get he's a just Scott so
you know if I'm gonna live a life of
like killing people
obviously there's repercussions right
like not just human-made laws but just
like the universal law or whatever you
know the law that that you know if you
if you operate within Christianity then
there's there's judgement right so if
you kill people for a living that be a
murderer but or a assassin yeah but you
know if you go around and and and live
that kind of life there are
repercussions right you go to jail you
don't like you your life will be ruined
so um what God's saying if you live a
life of faith in you you take that step
in learning about me and living the way
that that I teach then you'll be in line
with like what I want in your life right
now like you asked before if God knows
what you're going to do next
Yeah right is that free will does that I
mean for me personally I asked myself
that I'm like no I think I have free
will because I can make decisions and
and I can do whatever I want like like I
said like I can go out and treat someone
horribly or I can actually treat them
nice so I have that choice but I think
it's you don't have that choice though
because it's not like God's moving me
like a puppet no break what I'm saying
is with that theory yeah you just said
you had that choice but you're gonna
choose to be nice right because that's
what you believe in your brain is right
yeah
and God made you that way Yeah right so
isn't he really just controlling so if
he made you that way and you think that
way and you've chose to do the right
thing all the people that God made that
chose to do the bad thing he created
them to so why would he essentially if
this is if everybody's on god's path why
would God create these other paths I
don't think everybody is on God's path I
think everyone has a choice to live
along you know what what God teaches
versus making a decision to say I know
how do you know this how do you know
that that's do you I mean do you know I
don't but I own that's my feeling are
the other do you feel you have a choice
well what I feel is that I think I
personally think that the Bible I mean I
don't think I've always wondered like I
yeah the Bible itself is where you're
learning everything that you're talking
about right now correct sure that's
where all of Christianity we're just
Christianity not all religion correct
all of Christianity on the one I'm most
familiar with and I've been to church a
few times but I don't really know it and
grow up in it all of Christianity's
everything you know pastors everything
they know and so on comes from this book
and the book like you said is not
written by God right God didn't write it
guidance did himself did not write it
but he humans did pointed yeah but you
know how did you learn that you learned
that from the Bible something that
humans wrote so all that information
everything that you know about God
everything even the creation of the
Bible is from other humans it's not from
God himself he didn't even in the Bible
it says to go I didn't write the God God
inspired
so that's what Christians actly what I'm
saying so if humans aren't smart enough
just like ants not like if humans aren't
smart enough to think on God's level how
do we know that the Bible got it right
completely maybe it's close absolutely
not know I and I don't know all of the
answers but I can give you like my take
on what I've kind of learned and it's
that first off there are a lot of
scholars the brightest minds atheists
and non a theists who study the Bible
and look into in really deeply
understand it because it's such a
fascinating book just historically
historically a lot of these artifacts
that are in the Bible there's they're
digging up and it matches exactly where
it is in the Bible so so factually it's
accurate compared to some other you know
what things what things are matching up
what do you mean like you know an
example like you know just artifacts or
effects of like you know different like
clay pots and things like that that that
were invented during a certain time
period it matches along with the by I
can't be like super accurate fit but I
I've like looked into it but I think
it's it says something that there are
you know very highly intelligent people
who who go to you know dedicate their
entire lives and learning about this
this book right this historical book and
it's it's I think at least factually for
me that that is something that's pretty
interesting as a logical person right
it's like oh why would if this was a
bogus book why are there so many
scholars studying this and in teaching
it and continuously you know digging
things up in learning about it so that's
number one
well on that you know if that's one
reason to believe that this has some
validity to it yeah then what do you
think about other religions and all that
there's tons of people believe in
Buddhism who believe in every other
every other religion even Scientology
why do you think if so many people
believe in that not that that's like a
minor example but yeah and we all know
that's I mean but that's my point it's
like
yeah just because a lot of people
believe in it doesn't mean that you know
just like science right if that's
considered if we consider that a
religion and sure or a belief huh why
does somebody believe in it because
they're taught it from a very young age
so it becomes fact it's not a belief
it's fact
yeah and they show you instances just
like in the Bible there's things that
match up they show you instances with
with experiments and say like oh this is
what gravity is and this is because this
has been explained and it we can prove
it right in the Bible it's kind of like
the same thing maybe not as many proofs
but we also grew up in a grew up in a
society that teaches you science is fact
right and some people grew up in
Christianity like yourself and that's
fact for you as well
but you know what I'm saying what do you
think about other religions just because
a lot of people believe in it doesn't
mean that it's necessarily you know I
mean for you i'ma be asking ya know for
sure I my my whole stance on this is
like everyone is free to believe in
whatever they want I don't mean to make
that sound like a cop-out answer but you
know I'm still figuring out Christianity
I don't claim to know everything but the
more that I do dive into it the more
that I do feel that more connected to it
and I do think that it it becomes more
more real to me and it makes more sense
the deeper I go into it so that's it
into each their own right like I don't
want judge someone because they they are
a different religion you know or whether
there be Islam or Buddhists or whatever
right or Catholic like I think everyone
whatever makes them feel the way they
you know it brings peace into their
lives then yeah you know what do it as
long as you're not hurting people right
you can believe in whatever you want and
I really believe in the freedom thing
like I think you have a choice everybody
has a choice but it's which choice are
you gonna make right it applies to
everything in life whether it's religion
or your job or your education or how you
decide to treat people so I think that's
like the most important thing for me
well just for the record - I'm not
trying to say
I'm anti you're really an time you see
things that I think about yeah and I've
always been afraid I talk to this with
Jeremy for a long time Jeremy Jeremy Lin
yeah super Christian and I've talked to
you know he's even asked his pastors and
stuff and there's always it always comes
back down to you just have to have faith
which there's nothing wrong with that
but I mean I think it goes to show that
there's no hundred percent and I think
it's it's good for people be open-minded
enough to admit that like even even like
scientists I think you shouldn't say
there's no way
christiana like even if it's point zero
zero zero zero zero one percent that
Christianity our God is real right - in
atheists there's no 100% cuz you don't
know we're not on that level even if you
believe in science and your aliens
there's no way that we would know yeah
absolutely i I totally agree with you I
don't think anything is a hundred
percent but you know there are people
who will say that and believe so
strongly in their own religions and in
science right yeah I don't think that's
helpful yeah I think people should be
open-minded in and learn about other you
know thoughts and beliefs before you
know casting any sort of judgement and I
think you know something like your
spiritual walk whatever it may be
whichever religion that's a very
personal thing and I think even like
talking about it right now I'm sure
there's no Z on Traverse it's gonna be
controversy me hate agree so that's like
that's what that's why we're having this
you know conversation so I mean I
obviously know your beliefs right and
you're more confident yours and I I'm
still I'm still learning myself agnostic
yeah that's not agnostic as you believe
in something yeah but you're not exactly
sure not sure what yeah yeah I mean the
closest thing would be Christianity
because you know might have my family's
Buddhist house Christian but I've only
been to like church it you know cuz I'm
Arden and you and I've only been to you
know Christian churches but I don't
really I I just don't know you know and
that's why I ask because I'm curious
yeah it's it's fascinating like the
deeper you get into it I mean you listen
to some of the people who make
case for creation creation there's
there's creationist scientists and
there's like non creationist scientists
and that it's pretty interesting to kind
of see how they discuss things and you
know there are Christian scientists say
our earth is like ten thousand years old
or something
I I don't really know I'm not a
scientist so I can't even verify any of
that but whether I don't believe it's
true
I feel like it the earth is a little
older than that but some of them make a
case and they debate it amongst other
scientists they you know they talk about
carbon dating and how the traditional
way of carbon dating is actually
inaccurate some people argue that and
then some people I don't know I can't I
can't even comment on I don't know what
I'm talking about the science part
because let's see what the reason is
because and I think why it's become such
a I don't know I people have become so
arrogant about it I feel like more
people more and more obviously just I
feel like Christianity is still huge
obviously right but it was bigger when
we were younger for some reason I just
feel like more people now say okay
science is fact cuz we grew up with that
right and a lot of people don't
necessarily I don't know maybe I'm wrong
I I think the majority or for science
now as opposed to like twenty years ago
when we were growing up I actually feel
like it's growing you think so yeah at
least from my perspective maybe it's in
your groups do you think that has to do
with the progress of science maybe maybe
or like people who are becoming famous
aren't just like you know back in our
day growing up it was like every athlete
thanks God everyone gives credit to God
now it's like no deGrasse Tyson and Joe
Rogan and like people who have alternate
alternate theories that aren't just
Christian based right even like saying
the Pledge of Allegiance and people
having an issue with that it's like that
it's just a different time nobody would
ever come out 20 years ago and be like
my son or daughter does not have to say
to God in the Pledge of Allegiance right
yeah
but now that's an issue I I also think
that today in today's time like within
the past you know a few years or
whatever I think Christian has
definitely gotten a bad rep and it has
also been misrepresented and I think the
people who comment on
the religion itself are commenting about
the people the minority the the people
who are in in you know power in churches
and whatnot and the leaders but the
religion itself if you actually research
it it's like with anything right like
people can hear about like rumors about
you but if they don't really know you as
a person right
they won't truly understand where you
come from in in it's like the media the
media paints a certain types of type of
picture and I think a lot of people have
done that to Christianity but mostly you
know the Christians I know they're not
they're not like that it's it's just
like a you know in every religion in
every belief system there's always you
know bad people in it and there's also a
lot of good people so it's it's with any
anything like I think it's like I said
it's a personal thing so if one is
interested they should dive deep and
learn more as much as they can on their
own and I think this is something that a
Christian would say is just research and
read the Bible and then for yourself
and then just see what what happens you
know like and then maybe you'll
experience something maybe you'll feel
something and in maybe that's something
that we can hold on to I guess and see
where that goes I don't know like to
each their own but it's I think
Christianity has definitely gotten a bad
bad rep definitely in recent times
especially with like you know gay people
and the rise of like equal rights and
stuff like that it's I mean it's
associated with it I feel like it's kind
of chilled out a little bit yeah but it
was pretty bad to be like it was like
almost like a negative thing to be
Christian for a little bit yeah at least
on social media it maybe he's just in my
circle yeah you know like Christianity
if you go deep into it it's it's all
about love like God is love like and I
know that sounds hokey pokey but like
it's it that is the message so I think
if if people actually look into it and
really dive dive into it like they'll
that's what they'll learn not but not
from what everybody else is saying
here's the here's the other thing
other question I have for you I don't
know in the Bible is it wrong to doubt
Christianity and is it wrong to think
and believe in other religions because I
heard that it is um like I said God
gives you the choice yeah and will you
go to hell if you die believing in
another religion or if you die doubting
there's a god man according to the Bible
you gotta ask me this tough question I
know a controversial question no but I
mean like no I'm asking you specific
yeah yeah be personal come on the by
Bashar it you've learned from your
pastors your own reading yeah do you
believe that the Bible is saying
Christianity is saying if you don't
believe in our religion or if you don't
if you don't believe in God then you
will go to hell when you die the short
answer is that the in Christianity if
you do not believe that Jesus Christ is
your Creator and and is the Messiah the
one who died for your sins then yes
you'll not go to heaven at all Jannetty
right
that's what krishna teachers now if
you're asking about my beliefs that is
definitely something that I struggle
with something that I think about a lot
if I'm being really honest and I think
it's not just me I think a lot of
Christians thinking that way I would say
most probably thinking that way and
they've they've thought about this sort
of thing and struggled with in their own
mind right and I like to think about
both sides like you know there are those
who are very firm like if you're not a
Christian you're gonna go to hell right
yeah and and that's one way of
expressing that with what they've
learned the other is more like like me
in the middle like I don't know I just
don't know right if I can would an all
loving God send people to hell right or
allow people to make a decision that's
that's what I'm saying a good decision
to go to hell freeze those people that
went to hell too yeah so and like the
other lot like side of me if I if I play
devil's f do P if God is a just God
right is there such thing as can you can
you feel love without hate can you feel
it can you hate without love right
it's maybe that sort of thing maybe like
those are like the ideas that I think
about in my head yeah or the concepts
that really confuse me to be honest but
I'd really I can't answer that it's hard
because yeah it sounds evil for me to
answer it that way that's what I'm
saying though like and that's that's why
I bring it up yeah because these are
things that I think a lot of people
question yeah and like I said it doesn't
doesn't go anywhere that's why I'm
perfectly fine with anyone believe me
into anything but the people that
believe so hardcore and one thing right
like that's the people that I think need
to be a little bit more open-minded I
mean I'm not telling you absolutely to
not believe in what you believe because
everyone has that right and I'm just I
don't think you should get scrutiny I'm
defending myself I think you should be
scrutinized for questioning those things
I don't think there's anything in the
Bible that you know I'm gonna get
screwed and so are you feel like being
Christian I'm sorry guys I'm sorry for
everybody and then there's gonna be
people like me who get all the
Christians they're like oh my God he's
so but that's a he's so anti-crime not
trying to disprove make you sound anti
anything I know but you know how people
twist words and stuff like that anyway I
just thought it was interesting and I
don't know we never talked about
religion I know it's a very it's super
contra not but we're just having a
discussion I don't think there's
anything wrong I've had this discussion
with pastors and they don't maybe they
do hate me after I haven't talked to
them since but I think it's interesting
yeah to come from a perspective of
someone who's never been didn't grow up
in the church essentially I don't know
well we did kind of left you out there I
don't know if you have anything to
contribute there which one from what
topic or what was it just like um I was
just letting you yes you're having like
a really good back and forth now just
asking a lot of questions that I'd I
guess don't really have answers it would
be we should just bring on a pastor and
a scientist on the Shane show oh yeah
they'll be amazing all right but we do
talk about this outside of the podcast
we do and we have but not necessarily um
in this much detail yeah I talked about
it
yeah I don't know you're not very
religious are you wait what are you a
question
what was it oh just your thoughts about
yeah what are you yeah yeah on the
entire subject yeah just in general this
kind of it's not really like a science
versus religion to be yeah it's just me
coming from I'm not even on one side I
just thought I don't know enough to know
that's my that's where I'm coming from
I mean without trying like without I
mean you guys said so many different
points that I agree with so I dupes I'd
rather not like repeat those but yeah my
I'm kind of similar in your sense that I
didn't grow up be like in a household
that had religion very structured
religion like I think both of my parents
were mostly Christian or Catholic or
some form of that and we never went to
church but I think me like growing up my
parents did a good job of instilling
like morals and stuff like that without
religion and then it was kind of up to
me and I was kind of fortunate enough to
be able to have friends in different
religions and they could kind of imprint
positive messages on me you know I mean
like I had someone who was Sikh I had a
friend that was Christian and so you
know like it's stuff like love thy
neighbor and like you know the positive
messages I feel like I was fortunate to
absorb without that's why I don't really
feel that I can even speak unlike a lot
of stuff because I never read the Bible
like I don't you know I was just asking
questions because if there's an answer
I'm willing to listen yeah for sure and
it's not me the things I asked for some
sounds like I'm trying to just poke a
hole in your theory but really that's
just how I learned no question things I
think that my point of view being that
like that how I grew up I was kind of
just under the impression of just be
open-minded like like you were saying or
you want people have been open-minded
that's kind of what I grew up as it was
like I was just open-minded to so many
different things around because I was
fortunate to go to like a school and a
place I had a lot of different kids with
a lot of different ethnicities and
religions and so I don't know I mean
that's I think that's a pretty unique
like I'm not sure like a lot of people
didn't have that experience and so when
it comes to like me commenting on even
asking of like I don't know about
what was the one that yes David that
said I don't know I'm it's just like I
don't feel like maybe I have the
experience to talk on that specifically
so ya know I think like I said
spirituality in in what you believe is
really like I said a personal thing is
yes something that we all have we all go
through it because we're all gonna die
right like true like I don't know about
you like how do you feel about like
after you die like what is what is like
well I want
I hope happen yeah maybe talk about what
you hope could potentially happen or
what you think is actually gonna happen
or I see it I have a struggle between
kind of like you or you have like a
logical way of thinking about it and
there is a part of me that you know it
could be that the light just go out and
there's it's not like bad or good it's
just your existence is no longer right
the neurons in your brain no longer fire
and that's it it's like you don't have
any pain you don't have any suffering
you don't have positive emotions you
have negative emotions but then there's
a side of me who's been influenced from
the society and culture and religions so
like that where I think okay well what I
would hope to happen was that you know
maybe there is like some form of heaven
and then it's positive and you show up
and maybe there's some form of judgment
but it might not be based on whatever
religion is maybe it might use I hope
that it's just based on what type of
person you are right so if there's
something that judges you that go okay
how did you live your life did you kill
people did you help people
what was your intentions behind doing
this what was your intentions behind
doing that and then you get judged on
okay if you're a good person you're in
this good place right that's kind of
what I hope happens rather than maybe
being specifically narrowed into one
religion because I don't know you know
there's always that question of like how
one thing that I remember questioning
when I was younger was that for people
who don't have an experienced
Christianity if they're on the
completely opposite side of the
continent and they've never even met
someone who's Christian or know anything
about it how did they get into heaven if
they can't if they've never been
experienced with it that was one thing
that I struggled with I was like a child
because I felt like
you know what let's say how do you
answer that and then so that that's just
kind of like me bridging the gap in like
my hopes which is like okay well I hope
it's just like okay live a good life be
a good person help people and you'll be
rewarded in the end you know I mean
regardless of what you believe
specifically in structured religions so
cuz even like you think about it like
this like even babies that pass away or
like kids that didn't have a chance to
get into like how they cannot accept
Jesus right because it can't comprehend
it mm-hmm they've never had time to
learn it do they go to hell that's the
rest of things yes go to hell if they
die as a baby
you go to hell because you can't accept
Jesus you can't comprehend it I don't I
don't know what the answer is to that
trust me isn't sound right trust me
every Christian has probably thought
about this already let's be an answer
for it there are some answers in
theories but ultimately they are
theories because we're not God and we
don't know I think God is a fair God if
there if there's a God is God it would
be a fair God a God of love and but if
but a just God as well so you know it's
like a it's like a father figure
right the father figure you're not gonna
you want it you're gonna discipline your
child if you want them to grow up right
right you're not gonna just let them do
whatever they want I think in the same
way like sorry what was it mayn't over
again sorry like if you're saying
I mean well babies you yeah people
haven't heard so whatever judgment that
they're going to receive that's really
up to God it's not up to us to really
determine because there's a story in the
Bible of like this you know when Jesus
was crucified there were two people next
to him they were both robbers in one of
them you know was a criminal like he was
being hung there because it was a
criminal and you know he asked you know
one of them was like ridiculing Jesus
and then the other one was like hey
don't really kill him he's a good he was
a good man and and Jesus basically told
the guy who like defended him I'd say
I'm gonna see you in heaven like mmm
it's so it's like
you have that choice like like I said it
comes down to that in and if I'm being
honest like would I say that my choice
in diving deep deeper into this religion
is out of fear in the beginning yes it
was a little bit I didn't want to go to
hell right but the more that I learn
about it the more that I find that it's
less about heaven and hell it's more
about feeling peace and in every
circumstance whether it's good or bad
it's a learning experience and it's also
learning more about this being that's
out here or here or wherever it is right
just here that created like why am I
here like that's the big question I have
for myself is what am I supposed to be
doing you know I just met a guy who sold
a company in China for like nine hundred
million dollars he's like yeah I spent
six months just spending money and I was
I got really depressed it's like what am
what did he do now now he's like
starting like an education
yeah he's and stuff because he wants to
help people so that's what he found out
in those six months like now that I have
reached the goal right I've talked about
this before too like once you get to a
certain level of you know what you
always thought you wanted and you get
that then you start to think about oh
well that's not enough yeah so happy
exactly so what the Bible teaches is
that like just be grateful in every
circumstance right whether things are
good or whether things are bad because
that's the only way to remain truly
fulfilled in life because none of these
material things will ever bring you joy
now are they are they there too for you
to enjoy yes of course but and there's
nothing in the Bible that tells you you
can't enjoy things right but it's more
about your along the journey what how
does this religion play a part in your
life and like I said if Buddhism is what
gets you through life or Catholicism or
if you're if you're Islam like yeah if
that's what it is then then go for it
but to each their own
well that was turned into a very
controversial I don't know if it's
controversial actually yeah it's just a
topic that you know it's gonna trigger
some people yeah I mean hard list yeah
my intention is not to offend anybody
like I said in terms of Christianity I'm
still on this journey I'm still learning
right and I do time to time look into
other religions to just researching and
seeing what you're gonna get you don't
have to put a disclaimer you're gonna
get the heat I know it's all my yeah I'm
okay yeah you'd be fine you're just you
didn't say anything really controversial
yeah so anyway we're gonna take a quick
break and we'll be back and we're back
and we're back and we're back so on a
less serious topic I mean yeah I know it
was very interesting yeah no I mean I
don't say a lot of people but I do think
there is a correlation that people have
with being uncomfortable talking about
religion and especially with people that
have different views you know and not to
say that ours are different but I don't
know I think it's cool to hear different
perspectives
you know engine milk get your ninja milk
thanks today thanks ninja melt dot-com
get it actually get it on Walmart
Walmart calm cuz we sent them a bunch so
we got to so those out actually this has
been sold out in a lot of places so
thank you for people who bought on
Walmart it's amazing um it's delicious
we're trying to get it to actual stores
like like 7-eleven trying to but it's
gonna be its again it's it's us trying
to prove that we can sell and we have
been so thank you guys for that but it's
you guys some work to in order to
convince them I've had multiple people
and I actually like it when they ask me
like what's your unlike unbiased opinion
right and it's I mean legitimately it's
it's delicious it's good it isn't make
you feel super wired like does it make
you feel jittery
but it gives you like for me at least
the amount of caffeine that like amount
a cup of coffee which is perfect you
know doesn't make it it's like not as
acidic you know some sometimes energy
drinks can be super acidic that's kind
of the goal shouldn't go for yeah smooth
the number one complaint I get is that
oh why can't you make a dairy-free
option right right honestly I don't know
if I can legally say this but like I've
been told from other people cuz I can't
say personally from the brands
perspective uh-huh that they are lactose
intolerant they drank a can and they
were fine yeah that's what I was told
for Mike my brother his which i'ma call
his fiancee's super like lactose
intolerant yeah she can drink it
brothers the same way my mom too
I don't know why maybe I am maybe that's
why I'm gassy all the time cuz I
shouldn't be eating like cheese and
stuff like that do you think it could be
because the milk is not American milk
it's European milk maybe it's just
bitten it's just a small amount it's
such a tiny amount of milk that I don't
know I don't know I don't want to get in
trouble by saying that but I have heard
I haven't heard complains that people
who drank it that are lactose intolerant
having like bad really bad breakdowns or
whatever whatever it's called flare-ups
tolerance I don't know I don't know I
don't know why we're doing turning into
a commercial but yeah walmart.com go and
slash ninja milk I don't know if that's
right I don't know if it's on there yeah
yeah it's on Walmart site and if not
then you can go to Ninja calm I'm
curious to all the listeners on off the
pill what is your what are you what are
your religious beliefs and what do you
believe in you brought it back comment
in comment below no cuz I'm curious oh
yeah because this is this is a topic
that's I know it's controversial but
it's also very fun for me to talk about
because it's is it did we say anything
controversial though and I don't even
know if I would I mean I get what you're
saying when you say it's controversial
but is it no I get what he's saying but
I don't know I don't think it is we
didn't say like one or the other like oh
this is what you should believe in yeah
I think there is asking questions true
unless that's wrong which I don't think
in today's society it is wrong today's
questions I have doubt and not believe
and like you were saying it's like
questions you would ask a pastor yeah
and in my dating game effective I would
I would say that's what that's for is
like you know going to your pastor and
having any conflicts yeah exactly
and so I don't know and even attached
themselves they questioned everything to
just the same things at all
intellectuals question they have to
question themselves otherwise they would
be hypocrites right yeah I hope I'm
teaching this this religion but they
believe in it so much that they they are
so convinced because of how much they
have learned and experienced that they
feel compelled to teach it but they
don't know the answers either nobody
knows all the answers everything
otherwise we'd be good so I mean with
that belief technically technically like
what we're saying is as much as I grew
up and I believe the theory of science
right does that make sense
yeah I think science is a theory in in
general right it's not like we said
there's no hundred percent yeah it's
very fact its fact there's scientific
fact but it's still scientific fact not
mmm-hmm
you know I'm saying I mean I think a
fact is a fact well though I've seen
theories and facts within science yeah
yeah but that we're just arguing almost
just the words behind it right yeah it's
not like but you know what I mean right
there's no hundred percent we kind of
discussed that like should I forgot who
said it but anyway with science like
let's say all of a sudden for all of
time that we remember if you drop pick
up an apple and drop it gravity because
of gravity it'll fall right it'll fall
and hit the floor for how many years
have we believed in gravity or have we
documented this what if one day for
whatever reason someone picks up an
apple drops it and it doesn't hit the
floor then all of a sudden what gravity
is not a thing is there an explanation
for that or is or we didn't completely
understand it it's not a long enough
period of time that humans have been
able to I guess investigate into science
I think I know your your sirness
I think I'm really confusing myself I
think in terms of like gravity and stuff
yeah I think the formulas have been
proven they've been proven because it
happens every single time you plug in
every it works out every single time
right I'm just saying hypothetically
yeah but there's no infinite calculator
that shows the what am I trying to say
so you use the result like let's say a
hundred million billion years from now
someone drops an apple and it doesn't
fall and it disproves the theory of
gravity that means gravity was never a
hundred percent fact and who's gonna say
that it will in a hundred billion years
maybe it might change maybe it never
really was there may be something else
that we don't know that we didn't
discover is actually causing this
phenomena that's all I'm saying I know
it sounds super out there but I'm just
giving that perspective of like that is
a tiniest even if I don't if even if I'm
0.001 percent believing that there's a
possibility absolutely and I think like
I mean and you know what I think that I
might be wrong maybe a scientist can
come tell me but like I think life is
about believing in what you've
experienced yeah and I mean if we think
like that about everything in life then
you can't live it's like it just becomes
a choice is because I kind of I I've
seen things far enough to understand
I've learned what explains this reason
why things fall to the ground I mean
wasn't Einstein wrong about gravity
initially I could be your thing at the
wrong person I think I think I'm kind of
following what you're saying yeah let's
get a scientists on I really do want to
get I've always want to get had my
physics teacher back in Hawaii oh and
actually about biology teacher that I
really like but there's two teachers
that I've always wanted to have on the
podcast when I would make that happen
because they're both teachers in Hawaii
to two of them I like and I just wanted
I don't have a bunch of random questions
like this that I would just like to
answer
same thing for with a pastor I would
like to ask
but I would want to find like someone
who feels like a pro like they're a pro
at what they do and they know everything
yeah I'd love to just like question him
that would be a lot of fun all right
well if you're a really really
knowledgeable pastor out there or
science teacher don't want to be on the
show and you have some credibility we're
looking said it would be fun
yeah send us a tweet if you guys are any
of those people ad off the pill on
Twitter and at off the pill podcast and
Instagram so I mean we'd have to vet
them though because what if they're like
Justice I don't want some crazy person
I don't know I'm open to I think we
should start expanding to not just our
friend group but people that are just
like interesting thought leaders yeah
yeah you guys could also recommend who
you guys want us to reach out to as well
we're always looking for new people
ideally people who are willing to come
to Vegas my we'll do it in LA - yep
anyway yeah this this went in a
direction I wasn't expecting we started
off with area 51 I made our way to
aliens aliens controlling a simulation
simulation first I guess science versus
religion yep I wasn't planning on that
but uh that's the way the cookie
crumbled so and it crumbled all right I
had fun yeah it was fun thanks for uh
thanks for having me here in Vegas Mario
just picturing the comments thank you
for your honest assessment we will get a
real a pastor in in a scientist one day
so like we said hit us up we are open to
the idea I think would be interesting
and and if this is the most boring
podcast ever we're sorry but I was
interested that's why we stuck on the
same topic basically the whole time but
with that being said remember follow us
at off the pill on Twitter at off the
pill podcast and Instagram and pretty
much that's it yeah this the same way in
3 2 1
so religion let's talk about it