Here I am
boy d-trix in the world I'm cheese I
heard you got Christmas laughs OH
catching clothes wrapped in boys I got
all those Christmas gifts and puffiness
under mistletoe cookies and milk slow
and ball got a really big bag everybody
must be looking at me cuz I got swag
rainbow colored lights on the house I
got that heart full of happiness and
Cheer I got that candy cane Chocolate
Rain unicorns and silly game Layton play
champagnes my brain every little thing
that got in though the popping bottles
of eggnog singing Christmas carols with
my dad I'm the best prior have retail
black bubble ring hello
like catching ghosts wrapped in bows I
got all of those Christmas gifts
perky lips under mistletoe cookies and
go slow and ball really bad everybody
must be looking at me cuz I got less lag
I got a tummy ache am eating all them
cookies but guess what I got more
cookies on a plate by the tree Santa's
gonna be hungry but if he's ever late
I'm gonna decorate the house i decorate
the tree I decorate my homies i decorate
I decorate my car i decorate his hair i
decorate the trash
i decorate decorations dashing clothes
wrapped in bows I got Christmas gifts
and perky lips under mistletoe cookies
and milk flow and balls got a really big
bag everybody must be looking at me slit
I got this way