so I was so creepy in high school this
is my energy drink that I've been
working on for three years I don't know
why I didn't talk about it what are you
talking about Oh messed up things that
we talk oh are you talking time to clap
clappy clap clappy clap and welcome back
to another episode of off the pill
podcast we have Paco in the moderator
seat and we have a first time actually a
first time for Dana Dana Benson is here
everybody I think we should that's when
we should use the cheers like when we
get introduced you know like a bit well
Dean is here the first time there's
something nice about having a and then
introduce yourself oh and then me I
thought oh we have a we have another
read today we have a sponsor read nice
it's been a while man we need to need to
get more of these we can keep the show
going
it is Skillshare again this episode of
off the pill podcast is brought to you
by Skillshare Skillshare is an online
learning community with thousands of
amazing classes covering dozens of
creative and entrepreneurial skills you
can take classes in everything from
photography and creative writing to
design productivity and more so whether
you're returning to a long time passion
project challenge yourself to get
outside your comfort zone or simply
exploring something new Skillshare as
classes for you and also like I
mentioned lesson they have classes like
like weird things to like learning how
to lucid dream and doing all those kind
of you know it's that it they have a lot
of stuff it's a good advanced version of
YouTube and YouTube tutorials but anyway
what you get out of this promotion is
you can join the millions of students
already learning on Skillshare today
with a special offer just for off the
pill podcast listeners go to Skillshare
comm slash chica sign up to get two
months free of unlimited access of
thousands of classes again skill sure
comm slash EAGA the link is in the
nice Thank You Skillshare for keeping us
alive and then uh yeah guys go ahead go
go to Skillshare because it makes us
look good and they're like hey you know
let's keep giving Ryan money yeah you
guys are all coming here for once okay
they have really cool classes they do
and she's not being paid to say that we
were yeah we should all take a
Skillshare class like a different one
and then just talk about what we learned
I forgot to open it before the show as
Ella Skillshare class on how to open up
cans without white noise that's it that
would be a heart actually eating snacks
in class especially chance true always
caught Oh is there a way there is no any
nice crunch
no anyway you would have to like like
suck on the chip for a long time no but
even opening the bag oh yeah you can't
do that everyone had that scene in Big
Daddy mm-hmm and when he's like trying
to eat um well that's he trying to eat I
don't know some kind of chips but that's
such a relatable thing you can't open a
bag of chips without making a lot of
noise yeah whenever I do that instantly
wherever I am in the house dogs every
single time I remember in school
whenever I had to open up a bag of chips
I'd always just be like I'd have to
cough yeah because it was loud you know
so it Gregg does with farting and farts
at the same time huh yeah he does holes
yeah well he coughs loudly so you don't
hear his fart yeah but you can clearly
hear his part and a burp is like it's
extra long wait what do you mean
sometimes he'll do the Burt Burt the
barb the barb the but that's a good name
for it the barb the burp I was other one
cough combo that is that's a lot yeah
just died a lot of emotions going on
ones I've definitely farted and sneeze
at the same time I once threw up and
diarrhea at myself at the same time ha
so where did it go
yes because when I was a kid you know I
had the flu
uh-huh and so I just like spread my legs
open over the toilet and just like try
the puke through the hole didn't it yeah
I definitely got all over me oh yeah oh
yeah well that's just unfortunate where
else actually where else is gonna go
unless you have a trash can next to you
so what about you Dana since we have a
girl in the room today and we're
starting off with very hot oh how should
I say manly topics is that sexist to say
no most girls don't let's see not that
easy huh yeah how about what this what
are your thoughts on girls are like
girls no Boop well I mean that's I don't
know I don't think that's a know that it
is girl I mean it's a joke yeah it is
but a lot of girls like don't you talk
about they're poop-shaped
yeah those are poop shamed I agree yeah
but you agreed that girls don't poop are
you agree that it's a common joke yeah I
think but I think some girls take it too
far you know where they're actually like
I don't want to talk about this great I
don't poop you know we should start it
your movement I mean I there was that
video I gave you about how girls should
be like allowed to fart hashtag me poop
yeah and then bite what you're gonna get
you're gonna get you for that Bob no I
mean like Dana's pretty as much as Deena
is cuz you're always you're the only
girl in or hpc and you're around guys
all the time farting and burping and and
you're pretty open to it like you don't
think it's I mean whether you do or not
you're just around it right yeah yeah
you have a choice but even before rhpc
she's kind of been around all guys just
the dance crew all Steph boys like I was
always around like 15 to 17 guys all the
time so maybe I'm immune to it because
I'm maybe I guess oh no but you grew up
with all I mean not grew up but like all
your friend group was mostly guys um and
then now with rhpc you're surrounded by
guys all the time who are pretty gross I
would say I mean in compared to the
average yeah person I think very open
with farting and some but like being the
only girl you don't really like when
that stuff happens it's not
you go ill or like you're just so immune
to it but you yourself don't do it yet
so I think that's what we're talking
about like how it's not okay for girls
to express themselves that way I think
with us it's okay
what do you mean like with us like many
girls did that we'd be like no he's like
we would kind of encourage it yeah well
yeah I'd be like cuz it's you it's
different yeah would you do it with me
do what fart if you farted yeah I think
we would be all laughing we'd be like I
think we'd be grossed out I think we
need like yeah I think it depends on
your friend group I don't know okay so I
permission so if that happens actually
we encourage it not just permission we
want you to fire in front of us
yeah actually have you ever have you
heard ardan fart yes does she fart on
you ha no I I mean I don't do you do
that like the people we don't really do
that yeah dude
really yeah mm no she hasn't done that
no yes arned I heard I've heard it and
she was extremely embarrassed how about
now
what if she farts she still is yes no
she still is embarrassed but like I mean
I don't see why like I've heard her poop
before I've heard I've heard some salvos
I'm sure Greg actually has Greg hurt I'm
sure he's heard you fought oh yeah do
you do it like no not on right so I
think similar to that cuz you I mean you
guys are basically like how long have
you and Greg been together it'll be
maybe 15 years holy moly older than a
lot of that's like people watching yeah
more than half our life they've been
together since high school right yeah
lasted my last year of high school right
that is uh you're basically married in
some states I think yeah common law
common law
well um speaking of Greg what is it like
living with Greg that's a common thing
that I mean not just I mean we don't
even know yeah oh yeah I mean you kind
of know you lived it
yeah but I mean like the it's it's an
interesting relationship cuz you guys
have been together so long you live
together but you also work together a
lot uh-huh we do everything together
it's good it's tricky but do you ever
get like man I just need my own space
oh all the time does he that's yeah well
that's why their house has like five
different rooms yeah yeah we each have
our own offices for when yep those times
happen because they do yeah I think what
helps is that like early on in our
relationship too after a few years of
dating we were like Co partnering a damn
studio we had the dance crew so we were
both kind of like in the creative
director position so we always worked
together and then we both taught
multiple dance classes together and I
feel like it we kind of got used to
doing everything together so we
understand each other's chemistry and
how we work right but with this line
it's like with what we're doing now with
working with you and stuff it gets a
little tricky knowing the fact that it's
kind of like unpredictable of what you
throw at us basically and since we both
have different strengths and visions
that we could either show off we do tend
to bump heads a lot creatively and that
kind of affects the relationship because
if you have a tricky day where you want
something to happen your way and you
know he thinks otherwise
before compromising it's like you can't
go home and complain you're like let
yeah stress out on your boyfriend who
caused you the stress to begin with so
we don't have that but we do understand
that okay
we're compromising a little bit more
efficiently now where we both kind of
understand how to work around each other
and our visions but it's tricky but also
rewarding because it's when you know
when we come out with something that's
really cool that we both were a part of
we could say that we also did this while
in a relationship or it's something that
we created together and that yeah that's
awesome I was wondering about that
because it's got to be like for you I
feel like it's tough because or maybe
weak there's a side that we don't
see but you're the temp person that I've
never once heard you mad really actually
I think a little annoyed but I've never
heard you complain or mad like I don't
know if you have no no I've never seen
her Greg get mad at her actually but
I've never seen like maybe when you guys
are home do you ever get like and show
that I'm sure you have to write every
normal person does that otherwise you're
a social path you know but you've never
when we're around you've never done that
yeah no I think it's hard did how do I
say this when I'm around you guys it's
like it's always a like a positive
environment so it's kind of hard if
something frustrates me like I won't let
it get to me right um I think a lot of
the time too is because your frustration
will probably happen before we even get
together because you're designing props
and you're designing costumes and you're
designing sets and that's something not
necessarily we're around and then as
soon as you're done being stressed out
that's when we all meet up and then
you're like I have nothing to be upset
about I've seen like moments were like
you know if I mean even if it is a
positive environment I mean there's it's
stressful situations we're running out
of sunlight or if like we've got to film
something in a limited amount of time
we're not moving fast enough you know
like there's there's definitely times
where everybody gets frustrated and I've
seen Greg get frustrated stressed and
you guys kind of whether it's like
something you disagree on and Greg get a
little upset but you won't you just kind
of go with the flow okay like very
passive mmm-hmm I think oh yeah when he
kind of gets in that position I know to
just kind of follow his word because I
trust that you know I don't I don't want
to confront him in that time or I think
he kind of gets into a director mode so
I'm like okay let me do this for you
because I think at that time when were
filming and it something like that
happens I just kind of trust him or I
just trust and that he knows what he's
gonna be doing and I'll help support
that because sometimes he'll be kind of
in a panic or trying to figure out what
he needs
you are kind of overwhelmed so then
that's when I become like what can I do
for you type thing because I know that
you know if it turns into something more
complicated than at home it'll be a
different story
right right with a real fighting
physical fight brings out the bat that's
why maybe that's why I'm reserved
because I know that hmm we'll figure it
out later
yeah not worth not worth bringing it
into the working environment because it
could bring everybody else down and true
that is true I can make things harder
mm-hmm okay
well that's just something I wondered
about yeah but we kind of jumped right
into it like we we went to what you do
like we need to get to know how they met
and stuff let's go quite a lot to go
order man okay just need to be CoreLogic
I wanted to be hi mom does she listen to
oh what's your dad I think they do yeah
that's cute okay well watch time baby
yeah but yeah so you how about talk
about how you and Gregg met cuz Gregg
was looked way different and was way
different back then he did and you're
kind of an emo girl like a goth girl oh
you're a hot topic model you're talking
about her high school days and when they
first met in South that's why oh haha I
still really love Hot Topic yeah your
outfit looks straight out of Hot Topic
is that yeah I mean you you've always
had a unique I went out I don't say
hipster but like you have like a unique
sense of fat you're a fashion person
mm-hmm I think it's fun yeah
um are we getting into how we met yeah
okay he's gonna ignore my question
formally right how we met formally oh
yeah cuz you guys think you guys met
yeah yeah we'll talk about that we'll
talk about that our story time mm-hmm
look at that she's all giddy still she's
still got butterflies thinking about him
that's disgusting
Oh Gail stop um we met it was my first
year in high school and it was my first
homecoming and he was actually the blind
date of my best friend at the time so we
met we had our homecoming dinner at the
mall food court and then Greg shows up
and that's how we formally met and I
just remember during the dance like my
friend didn't want to dance with him
Greg was kind of a Wallflower that
entire night and he went to a different
high school the first two years before
he switched over to mine so he would
come to every dance like our friends
would take turns bidding him in you know
when you fill out an application for
someone from another school to attend
the dance right so he would always be
there and dance with him so I feel like
he I kind of wanted to talk to him more
and more and then after summer break
like he started attending school just
two years later though right here is
this yeah show your age real quick
graduated 15 years ago right yeah mm
four or five ish 2005 um so you
basically for for two years you're just
like man this is really weird guy that
just keeps hanging around our friends
but doesn't ever dance yeah and then you
were attracted to that yeah all right
guys no you know it's a bag of Dana he's
just gotta be a you know hang around
don't really get involved be a
Wallflower but like every time every
time it would come around he would
always be like that silly guy and he had
an afro at the time which is hard to
believe now he had a big afro and he
would wear like ginormous hoop earrings
mismatched clothes like he was always so
quirky but he was super shy at the time
so I feel like that's what kind of made
me interested and I was like I was too
shy to ask him to dance but it was so
repetitive like they would bring him and
I always had that curiosity like I want
to get to know him more but he went to
our school and then started dancing in
our dance classes and then that
friendship builds because we always had
yo mutual friends and
and from there it kind of took off
through dance and yeah just hanging out
who talked who hit up who first was it
ever like oh hey I think you're cute or
is it always just like just talking and
flirting and then yeah actually um it
was pretty random cuz we would hang out
and then all of a sudden he would kind
of send me little messages on MySpace
after school so that was a thing after
school you'd go home and check your
myspace and he would just be like hey I
hope you had a good day you're so cool
cool that is so like I remember that
yeah yeah but the thing was hey I
actually had a crush for a son one of
his friends so it's one of the step boys
er um a little bit before like one of
the step boys close friends like right
outside of the group like a brother a
cousin yeah so I was so creepy in high
school
explain that okay I don't know I
actually don't know this story that
neither do I did you do I mean you're
still kind of creepy now bleh
so I would if I liked a boy I would just
kind of like follow him around or just
kind of so that boy I liked I see you
building up your courage I've never
heard about this go ahead okay let's say
this psycho Dana yes I don't know if I
still have it it's probably deep in my
closet but that boy that I liked he
stepped on a plate but you said I don't
know if I still have it but that boy is
in my closet
here's some scary okay I'm sorry I
didn't mean to interrupt sorry data yeah
way cooler no go ahead
he like he stepped on a plate at lunch a
paper plate it was laying on the floor
and he left like a shoe print on it
and like right when he walked away I
took the plate and I was kind of joking
off to my friends because they knew that
we all kind of liked him he was he was a
cutie so I took the plate and I like put
clear tape on it to laminate it and
preserve it and I kept it I may have had
him sign it like I think they all kind
of knew that I was crushing pretty hard
right um and I think he knew it too so
it would kind of be more of a playful
thing like watch I'll do this type thing
that's so creepy it is but back then you
didn't think um so I did that and I
would like draw a cartoon version of him
on my planner but the thing was when I
started showing more interest in Greg
like I drew a doodle of Greg next to the
guy with afro and the hoop earrings and
I think Greg and I spend more time
together like in dance class that really
brought us together
and that's when things started like
actually happening I feel like with the
first guy was crushing out it was more
playful like trying to joke around cuz
he was super cute yeah Greg was always a
person that I was very interested in
he's such a unique character yeah we can
all agree on that
um I know someone I peaked on Twitter
and someone asked like what made you
fall in love with him and stuff and our
shadow think like on my drive here
stooping to the good-good when he went
to our school he was on like the
audio/video audio/video audio/video team
and he would do the morning
announcements so he would read the lunch
the daily lunch that would be you know
on the TV they would roll they still had
the TVs that they would roll in play the
morning announcements he would read
lunch or any news and
but he had the afro and the big earrings
and like everybody saw him as this
character I was like oh he's so cool and
that's why that's when you fell in love
is that what you were saying you don't
know but that was like the moment you
just thought that was he was so cool
he's such a cool character yeah and I
think yeah yeah you can tell I I've
always been drawn to things that are
unique and I guess you can kind of tell
that yeah yeah
and then you yourself are very unique in
terms of how you would dress and like I
mean did that's what you take pride in
different and doing things differently
stalking people yeah did Greg know about
this like back then yeah he was aware of
it it sounds like a plot to an 80 summer
flick I don't know why yeah you see you
like we explained that story and then
making doodles of the guy you're like a
girl in an anime that's like the main
Kerala
with the bad character and was like
really handsome and then she ends up
falling in love with the guy who's like
the clown yeah the guy who would have
always have like the swirly eyes yeah
every time we see it's the true love
yeah I get beat up all downstairs while
you actually sick you saved you would
follow guys around that you liked and
then saved their footprints yeah
but the thing was I think everybody kind
of jokingly knew I was like that or I
kind of made that character for myself
I'm a joke yeah but I feel like Greg
kind of he made it seem like there was
no need for me to do that anymore
right because after we started like
talking like a couple months into our
relationship
he went from having an afro to doing
like the rat tail things yeah so when he
asked me to homecoming or some other
dance
he had like a ring container thank what
do you call that a ring bell ring boxes
yeah yeah I don't know so he waited for
me at lunch and all of our friends were
there and he had this box and he
presented it to me and it was the lock
of his rat tail
I have to do anything for that I didn't
have to creep behind you it's scissors
or anything like that's mine and I have
like I have like three at least for
those of you that don't know what that
is that's when your hair is like what is
it like a single strand of mullet yeah
it it's a baby mullet or like a baby boy
a baby mullet
pretty much I used to have that he
didn't cut them off and you guys are
freaks you guys are pretty that's pretty
strange but it's like that's why it's
funny and unique yeah yeah you're funny
Dana I didn't know I did not know I
bought that creepy side of you but
that's funny they call the call do you
still do that do you feel like this
mustache hairs like you shave off his
mustache and present that to you my god
every year on your anniversary that's a
great idea
I'm sure there's people who can relate
those like very I mean it seems like
Anatomy right I don't know why I think
Adam a I'm just picturing you like a
girl literally fault like stalking
someone that they like but usually like
a anime thing cuz in an anime that's
cute
if you do that in like a lifetime story
it's it's a murderer it depends on what
platform you're in yeah in anime it's
like oh it's so funny it's cute and then
you know but in real life oh it happened
in real life yeah I'm glad your don't
agree yeah yeah okay I did not know that
to be honest yeah oh yeah and then um
informally you know we have a hunch that
you met someone before mm-hmm
because we went to the same elementary
school and middle school and I don't
know if you guys had like like rainy day
Fridays but you would have designated
days where mixed grades would come
together and the last two hours of the
school day you can go to a room that's
watching a movie or you can go into a
room that's all coloring or toys and
stuff like that I loved it it was so
much fun
high school in elementary school and
I remember going into the toy room and
just like a little a little 10 boy
asking to play with me and we we did the
you know what a marble run is is where
you build
yep-yep contraption you roll the marble
but we both remember playing with that
that was our go-to thing and I told him
like I remember specifically this one
time that I played with a little boy who
is tan yes are you all you remember
maybe a little bit of shadow already he
was born with a hairy kid yeah really I
did not know that yeah so we did that
and I feel like while we were talking it
was a random story but I want to say
that we both kind of got that feeling
that it was fate because I also had that
experience with another friend in
preschool and I never I have totally
forgot about it and I met up with a
friend near the end of high school and
we became best friends and then there
was this one time where we were talking
about do you remember playing with a
girl in preschool like blocks and so a
similar story and a couple of months
later a couple weeks later he comes with
a picture of us playing on the floor
he's like this is yeah so it was weird
and it was a very similar feeling huh
yeah maybe you were just following him
this whole time
that's cool I mean that's classic
clothes do you remember anything from
preschool I do I do
why do you not I heart I don't remember
too much just like embarrassing moments
like peeing in my cot or like cutting my
own hair yeah stuff like that peeing in
your cut yeah go ahead
yeah like a small bed you know oh you
used to peel on in the bed yeah last
week too had to change the sheets
so whatever dude grown man is a grown
man has grown men you know just shows
that my body's working yeah I just I
remember
not being a good kid I used to get in
trouble a lot as a preschooler yeah used
to beat up girls
no I didn't I was one time and it wasn't
be dying it's just we're not getting
into that one hitter quitter yeah okay
whatever
no but you know it's funny too cuz in
preschool I don't know my mom told me
this but I do remember giving attitude
or like being really annoyed with the
ladies that ran in the place and I just
wouldn't get along with it listen to
them I wouldn't get along with them I
wouldn't listen to them but I was told
that when when there was a guy there
I would like like him and listen to him
Sallis I was your sexist I was dude
you're gonna get for that hashtag
no I mean yeah I mean that's that's what
I was told I mean I don't recall being
sexist but I guess I didn't like I don't
know that's all I remember
Wow well we went to your grandma's house
at one time and you showed us that
picture where you couldn't sit still and
like this totally looks like something
so it's it's a picture of me as like a 3
or 4 year old and my hands like this and
like it raising up into the picture and
that's cuz the ladies were holding my
arms I wouldn't want to take the picture
and I look really pissed and I guess
they took a bunch of shots and that's
the only one they could use do we have
that we have to show that that's you'd
have to go back home I don't know who
did that I don't know but yep that's all
I remember so you were a crazy stalker I
was a sexist and you were a poo poo pee
pee boy yeah but that being said poopy
and pee it's time for our shisha break
we'll be right back
[Music]
I brought she's knocking huh I brought
you something I just remembered oh wait
this is part of the show I guess so okay
could include let's clap what you have
it on you right now it's right outside
well then that's not clap okay oh you go
get it okay all right let's talk crap
about as she's leaving dude Dana is a
stalker dude this is a creep bruh good
thing good thing Dana found Greg because
she might have been a murderer so you
could he probably would have murdered
Greg if Greg didn't like her and then
kill Brandon oh I think she would have
choked him with his own rat - I think
she would have just followed him Dana's
money that's how it begins
mmm that's how it begins I can't think
of anything like would I ever follow
somebody if I like them enough I know
when I was younger like used to follow
people - uh a little bit but not like
her extent definitely not when she saved
the foot yeah I've never done that
no but else she said it was part of a
she's back she's oh she's back you said
it was part of a joke though but it
wasn't really really wasn't what what is
this Dana it was her friends just being
accepting of her creepiness sorry Dana's
just snuck back in and what is that Wow
[Laughter]
it does open I think it's a what what
Hills or a doodad container but Greg and
I were out um a store that sells
containers uh-huh yeah they have that at
the register
yeah well what are the odds then that's
kind of cool they're selling our merch
well thank you it's a giant build
everything of a place to put this in the
podcast oh yeah I hope I brought a stand
[Music]
that was good time it's like yeah those
are really nice nice okay well first
before we get back into I got I got to
do this go share read again the second
half of this go share read I don't think
they didn't complain about last time but
I didn't have to read it exactly if so
I'm just gonna say again this off the
pill episode is brought to you by
Skillshare Scotia is an online learning
community with thousands of amazing
classes and without having to read all
this just as explained in my own words
Skillshare basically is this site you
can go to and learn a bunch of cool
things you've seen it Dana mm-hmm
actually I don't think you've ever even
went on it I have or you have gone on it
I want to learn you can learn a bunch of
like you can be a teacher on it on there
for one and basically you can learn
things like how to make your Instagram
better like how to how to turn it into a
business or even learn how to like I
said lucid dream you can learn a bunch
of weird style Adobe Illustrator on
there yeah they have a bunch of like
things you could learn and actually like
I don't know the things that people go
to college for but you can learn it on
there and it's different from YouTube in
that I think it's like screened so it's
like a very like premium version of like
a YouTube tutorial like a better version
and a professional version of that so go
to CEO share and remember if you go to
skill share and you do sign up you can
get two months free unlimited access
with thousands of classes just go to
skill sure comm slash ego make sure you
guys use that so they know like we sent
you and yeah just look good this week we
aren't doing can Oh balls or purple
elephant if you a real one just not yeah
but again shout Skillshare thank you
guys for keeping us afloat keeping this
podcast going yeah otherwise we'd have
to quit I mean we there's a bit I mean
there's just been we there's only thing
we've been keeping up with there's just
been a lot of things going on lately you
know I mean you can kind of talk about
it it's everywhere it's literally right
here yeah I were I'd rank it in the last
podcast as well but he did there's a lot
of comments like oh yeah I didn't talk
about it last time and I'm making a
video for it but by now my launch party
happened and this is my energy drink
that I've been working on for three
years I don't know why I didn't talk
about it but I've been working on it for
a while these guys on you but yeah it
just came out and we just had our launch
party on Friday so
fun right we're filming this before the
launch party cuz it's in LA so we're not
gonna be without you know we're filming
this in advance but yeah we're the
launch party is happening at by the time
this video comes out it has happened so
hopefully there's no drama
but yeah in jammu comm check it out it's
it's different it's yummy oh thank you
it's all right yeah I wanted to hear non
everybody I mean I gave it to like
friends I gave it to like you know
family and stuff and everybody's like
very positive but I wanted to hear like
you know there's gonna be people who
don't like it like anybody like you just
like rep you know the Red Bull like I
like the taste of it but like initially
when I first drank it I wasn't a fan
I'll tell you what people are gonna say
about yours it's too sour milk is weird
doesn't taste like milk though the
closest thing in terms of the thing is
when you hear about it you probably
think oh that's gross an energy drink
like milk and it's white - right but
what I wanted I wanted it to be white I
wanted to be different and the the
inspiration was kind of like those like
I don't know what those things are
called like after you eat Korean
barbecue you know like those kind of
drinks I can in Asia we have a lot a lot
of it yoku little big things uh yeah I
mean I there's nothing yeah kind of like
that like the yogurt yeah Kyle pico from
Japan yeah like this there's not there's
a lot of that in Asia and I really like
those drinks there's no energy drinks
but you know I wanted to bring that here
and nobody really nobody in the u.s.
wanted to do it so we we work out of the
Netherlands that's our production nobody
want to do it and there's good reason
it's a big risk but you know that's
ninja milk and Anna and I are drinking
it Cheers he's not supportive thanks
Dana this is what it sounds like so good
ninja muqaam where were we sorry I
wasn't going to add mode well I mean
it's the second half yeah yeah we have a
lot of those yeah we're interested okay
what do we have here first
Nelly from Nelly which prop costume was
the most difficult to create proper
costume most difficult for people who
don't know Dana does all the costumes in
props props
yeah oh um the BJ light sticks oh yeah
so that ii BG a video the light sticks
that light up yeah those were good yeah
Danny Dana and made those that was a
process because well you texted me the
idea mhm mhm and they were all hand-cut
from acrylic like we got a special saw
for it and I had no idea how to operate
it and it was a very big learning curve
and I tried so many things like I put
the stick on the flashlight and you
wanted both silver and gold and I'm
trying to figure out how to color it how
to do that yeah so the light sticks
ended up being clear but I spray-painted
them like half or six gold six silver
and I just didn't like the way it looked
you couldn't really see it glow as much
afterwards so the day before we sent you
to LA with them I had a big bottle of
nail polish remover and I was like hand
removing all of the spray paint out of
all the crevices and everything just
like undoing there was two days of work
and on top of that we were working on
the Star Wars video at the same time
because we we filmed that a few days and
then you had to leave to do the BGA
stuff so then we were like picking up
while you were away but I feel like the
fact that we were doing two projects at
once and it was a lot of back and forth
so that was the hardest problem and the
Star Wars one had a lot of costumes -
mm-hmm so I was just at all at the same
time but yeah difficult to wise that was
that's I mean it look legit thanks yeah
I mean that couldn't have been easy it's
hard - yeah cut a straight line from
acrylic yeah I think that was actual
like a blood sweat and tears project
because it was overwhelming we were
working on multiple videos at the time I
was trying to learn how to use this saw
and the acrylic it's kind of sharp so I
definitely got in
several times you actually got cut it's
got like sharp ends when you after you
pull it through there's a little chars
that come off or if you're trying to
like smoothing edges and you you catch a
little bit yeah
all right but it was fun I think I
really like learned or I felt
accomplished like I taught myself how to
do this actually why don't you talk up
talk about how also you kind of got into
rhpc cuz that was like unexpected right
yep yeah okay more story time yeah fun
fact like I met you before Greg met you
II do you remember how we met is that is
the third grade dude you're the kid no
it was at your house right my house so
you were living in North Hollywood at
the time with Doc yep yep and well Dom
kind of grew up around my family a lot
so it was no surprise that he would
spend holidays at my parents house so
when he came back for Thanksgiving he
brought you along with him
so we met you at my parents house on
Thanksgiving no staying there hey you're
back yeah you were staying at yeah you
were staying with us and that also was
when agents of secret stuff came out too
so we spent Thanksgiving watching agent
to secret stuff with all my and then the
day after was our Thanksgiving party
uh-huh and you dressed me up I tell was
the beginning of her career she dressed
me out she thought of because so
basically you guys have these these
parties these Thanksgiving parties where
they all dress up and like you know
there's Pilgrims and Dana basically I
didn't have a costume because I didn't
know I'm gonna be you know most people
don't dress up as anything she made me a
pilgrim with within a day mm-hmm oh I
miss those parties yeah when we were
living back at home we would have these
themed parties and for Thanksgiving we
would throw like yeah costumes in a bag
and for Thanksgiving it was you could
either draw a pilgrim or an Indian and
there was like two teams and we would
have a whole like Thanksgiving Olympics
yeah
feast and like competitions and relay
races and it's so much fun but we were
all on the pilgrim side me you and Dom
so I had my costume others need to get
our line races so within 24 hours of
meeting you I was already dressing you
yeah and that was and that's when we
first met yeah yeah but the actual thing
that brought it all together was if you
want to talk more about it because what
you actually design was amazing
which one the the cloud thing right oh
that's right so even before I moved out
here I was still doing stuff for you
guys cuz that's when you would got
brought Greg on yeah and I would come
out to visit him and it just so happened
to be like oh you're gonna be in town
you could help us with his stuff so I
was visiting with some friends and I
helped you guys make a cloud video for
the 10-million the lamp clouds mm-hmm
that was a lot of fun so I helped out
with that for that week and then I went
home and then I came back a second time
and that's when we did the tea time room
mm-hmm
well originally because I mean people
don't know I'm sure that you went to
college for interior design yeah and I
mean even when you first came out here
it wasn't from my impression I I just
thought you were you're coming here to
do that it was this was gonna be like a
short term like oh so you don't have
anything else yeah you want to just come
help us out you know just kind of casual
yeah and then I just found like wow this
is like so much so much value in terms
of what you can do it's so little yeah I
think that's your gift in terms of like
it's it's very difficult to be creative
with not much and ain't even Greg to
like both of you are very similar in
that you can make something pretty legit
with not much mm-hm and that's big for
me because it saves me a lot of money so
I'm gonna buy the real like I don't
gonna buy actual clothes sticks okay hey
Dana do you think and the thing is I'll
always be like do you think you guys
could make this and I've never heard no
yeah like it's always like what okay
like even if it's really difficult and
then Greg will be like yeah I think Dan
I think we'll figure it out yeah but
it's never like no even though it should
sometimes probably be a no really yeah
like uh if when you're like oh can you
help if I have to help them with props
when you asked me to help them I know
it's like a bigger project sometimes
I'll go over there and I'll start
helping them I'm like how are they doing
this and they're like yeah we should
have said no it's like going at it
they're so creative it's crazy like
you're the epic snort snort epic snort
no video like you called me and you
talked to me about it and you wanted
like this frozen castle and multi-levels
and stuff and greg was editing another
video at the time but I had you on
speakerphone and I hung up and Greg and
I looked at each other I know I need I
need people to do listen tell me no
because I go to big things we do it I
think that's almost fun in the
Challenger you know we make something
work it might not always be
three-dimensional I guess it gets to a
certain degree yeah yeah but it's part
of the fun yeah I mean it's it's
definitely it's definitely I know
sometimes I'm just asking but like I
already know you're just you're not
gonna say no sometimes I tell great to
like just tell me this is not realistic
I can dumb it down more but Ryan's like
that really pretty girl it like you know
and then you guys are like the boyfriend
and Ron's like can I have this and then
you even though he knows like he
shouldn't be getting it you guys like
you know anything for you babe it's like
that's oh no I'm going with this analogy
all right I'm just saying they're
they'll do anything for you because they
appreciate you so much mmm that's some
way you've found a way to make that but
not that's not if I was dating you I'd
say no find a much better guy so what
when you first were bringing her on you
thought a short term what you hated long
term um yeah what just kept like she
just kept help at first she was just
helping for free like she was just like
oh I I'm I'm sure Dana will help make
that it was always just like Dan just
helping and then we were like okay well
if she's gonna be
doing this you know delicious bring her
on for a little bit because at the time
I was still thinking you were still
looking for that you know interior
design kind of job I don't even know one
of those like shows like those problems
well yeah well I have my bachelor's in
interior design and my concentration in
interior architecture so I did it all
you know like the Cod and the model
making and stuff but I feel like what
I'm doing for you now or the more
hands-on stuff is kind of more relatable
to what I was working on when I was at
home because my previous job was like
more civil stuff and it kind of became
into something that I haven't tapped
into and it I had no intention of going
further in that but with what we're
doing I use a lot of my model making
skills and you know learning what
materials to use and what works as well
as aesthetics and making sure things
look cohesive and all the little crafty
tedious things basically right but yeah
when I came out here it was fun helping
you guys and I did have a couple clients
from back home that I was doing like a
broad staff for us I would send them
like CAD sketches and stuff and then I
did a couple of jobs for interior design
out here for my previous job yeah that's
literally what your expertise is mm-hmm
because she designed the for people who
watched second channel the tea time room
and that was like I mean we I wasn't
expecting that like something so
professional but I mean that's it was
around that time I would say yeah all
this - with Sean we actually have a
video of that was supposed to go of the
making of this room I don't know where
that video is I think it's going Sean's
computer somewhere somewhere yeah
there's there's a video of them making
this room yeah and you helped there was
a segment where I guess you can't see it
now but the the Rhino that's above you
you helped me I did it was part of the
video yeah it never came out it's still
one day it might one day
there's a lot of videos that are like
one day one day there's some videos
though that that haven't we I haven't
posted that I know it'll be the right
time it just used to marinate like fan
ball has to marinate I'm telling you
don't just trust me dude I know these
don't work work a Dana so I mean we kind
of already discuss some other things
like how you and Greg fell in love and
stuff boring and also you know like the
props that you guys made boring um and
then I guess he stopped insulting her so
much people already think you hate her
like a lot of people from the other
videos thing you know say oh yeah you're
here to defend your side here and yeah
you can let's talk about that how paco
is like really mean to you i know in a
joking way but sometimes it's like even
for us were like cringing oh yeah i mean
to everybody you are but it's a
different amount but we're sexist we
here's a least sexist because you treat
Dana how you treat us exactly all
feminists yeah I get opportunity disses
coming all around your but some things
you say to her you can't get away with
oh sorry I didn't mean to interrupt
talk about your side of the story I
guess Paco is a feminist and I was I'm a
three at best tell him tell him what he
said we to update people yeah I've been
wanting to explain my side of the story
because when talk were told that story
about how one of our friends asked
Monica if she's on the team or not or if
she's yeah with us and you said what did
she say like she's too good-looking
like she's Monica's too good-looking to
be see and you said that I said but it
was actually well that's a story she'll
be about better context basically we
were like oh yeah what is Monica in the
group and I was like what no Monica
stood up to attracted to be in the group
and then someone is like what about Dana
and I forgot that like you know Dana's
like part of it but you just got to
commit to the joke
like what Dana's like a three at best
and then I said afford okay way better
now you defend yourself
so it was Monica that said after you
said she's sooo good looking to be in
the group Monica goes oh so it was
Monica that said that and then I went
yeah yeah you're right
she just wanted to clarify but it's even
more sad because she's just like she's
not like offended she's just like yeah
that's even more offensive you hurt her
you don't you don't care about that
stuff but it's just like the way that I
don't know this is some things you don't
I don't know maybe I am a sexist person
I'd I don't treat girls the same way I
wouldn't say that to a girl I think
friends to like self-deprecation is like
our security blaze automatically it's
more of like a light-hearted thing I
don't know if I would say it to anyone
in the group oh you're like a three at
best maybe only you actually because you
would say that to me yeah I don't said
to Greg or will or any of them that's
also be up for me I think I'm in a
position that I can say that you say
messed up things all the time yeah
because you guys like do mess up things
to me so this is our dynamic what are
you talking about are you talking I
don't I don't yeah I don't know we don't
say those kind of things to you you
don't we give you helpful advice but
that's because that's just how we talk
there's example the relationship is Dana
I don't talk like that to Dana
but Greg really or any of us just you
that's okay that's what makes you
interesting all right let's just do it
one last I mean the only really good
question that's left is like what would
you be doing if you weren't working with
rhpc we just talked about what you went
into and then how she got that what
would you be doing oh that's true um
well it's not like I don't have time I I
would like to do something fun on the
side too cuz there are times where
you know you're writing Gregg's editing
all the graphics and thumbnails are made
and I do have a little bit of time I
would like to do I would like to do
something fun and crafty maybe like
greeting cards or I've been practicing
calligraphy yeah I think that would be
fun something artistic that I can
control or create a fun product either
that or like musical theatre would be
fun yeah you do like to you're good
singer and well actually I didn't know
about they that's it a really
interesting thing
Dana's greeting cards or birthday I
don't know maybe those kind of things
yeah yeah and would you write like the
things in it to like funny ones or like
just sure or lame custom you know oh
yeah yeah
here if as soon as Ryan fires all of us
start a patreon okay and then you know
different tiers and then people can
order your stuff hmm should I start one
know when I fire me again thank you sure
we're still here I've always wanted to
do I mean I have no artistic side but I
always want to make the jokes cuz I used
to like reading the the comedic ones
like you know there's so many of them
that are just like lame puns yeah I'll
be great at Liam policy very close but
then but then I couldn't do the art
because it's poorly draw you have the
puns and you attempt to doodle it it's
much more entertaining looking at your
stuff than like looking at one of ours
and having it look good oh yeah I agree
him have some house do the art because
even with manga like the people that
will write or have ideas they aren't
necessarily always the artists right so
you know where she's making a joke that
it would look like a little kid drew
yeah that's how I you I love that you
love it cuz you're good at drawing the
rest of us normal people you can't draw
or like people don't stalk yeah this is
crap like the thing that you made for
Shaun before he left like it was oh my
god it was delightful like I tried
really hard I shouldn't and I think
that's what I would rather appreciate it
well thanks for the little ego boost
inna but I it's just that was off the
pill pod where can they follow us you
can follow us at off the pill on twitter
and at off the pill podcast on Instagram
and be sure to check out Dana she's on
Instagram and Twitter and all that stuff
and just we put up her graphic radio
follow her well and check over her check
yeah in the beginning get at Dana
usiness
my name again Danis well okay well Dana
was the guest Dana's the only one I
guess what yeah yeah that's alright how
about this if you guys are real ones
everybody in the comments but Dana is a
ten a solid ten oh you don't have to I'm
not that yeah yeah thank you guys again
for tuning Todd's pill podcast I'll talk
to you next podcast
she has never made it to the end you can
tell I know
yeah I know she's different for girls
fart in it that it's gonna be our do
whatever so does this
Ryan is a sexist the title 15