hey guys so recently I did the ice
bucket challenge on my second channel
higatv I'm sure all of you know by now
but for those of you that don't it's a
charitable challenge where you either
donate $100 to an als charity or you
dump a bucket of ice-cold water in your
head and you donate $10 instead and
basically in my video I did the ice
bucket challenge and I donated $100 plus
whatever that video earns is going to be
going to the ALS Association so if you
can't afford to donate the hundred
dollars or the ten dollars you can
actually just go and view that video and
technically I think you'd be donating
like a cent or like a fraction of a cent
or something but anyway as always people
in this world love to find the negative
and everything especially when it
becomes popular it happens all the time
once something becomes really popular
people have a tendency to just hated all
of a sudden think about it remember when
planking first came on and it was like
the coolest funniest thing you could do
and then all of a sudden everybody else
are you doing it and it became the
lamest thing ever or like Justin Bieber
when he was a little kid on YouTube
everyone thought he was like this the
most talented cutest little kid ever but
once he got signed and made it big he
had more haters than anyone now he's
kind of generating his own haters
because of his actions but initially it
wasn't his fault or even like when we
all used to pee on each other for fun
and then r.kelly did it and then it was
no longer cool anymore so that's why we
stopped right that's that's why we
stopped doing that right basically these
people love things but a few people know
about them but once they become popular
it switches come on what kind of person
does that sound like to you get it I'm
stirring my hips hipster jokes are oh
yeah sorry
back to the topic in my mind the ice
bucket challenge was and still is a
positive thing yet now that it's
catching on it's like the worst thing
you can do right now these people are
saying things like people were only
doing this for attention now uh yeah
that's kind of the point to gain
attention to raise awareness
who cares if they're doing it for
attention they're still contributing to
the viral trend more than you have I'm
not gonna lie if I didn't see so many my
friends do it and so many of you didn't
tag me I would have never known what it
was I didn't even know what ALS was
until I heard about this challenge yeah
so it might be something stupid to do
but it did bring awareness people who do
the ice bucket challenge are greedy
because they don't want to donate the
hundred dollars well first let me ask
all the people who are saying things
like this how much did you donate what
have you done for an als charity what
have you done for any charity I mean if
you donated $100 or more you have every
right to say that but keep in mind that
not everyone who does this challenge is
as fortunate enough as you to be able to
donate that much and
sometimes by doing the ice bucket
challenge you're actually donating more
than $100 because of although awareness
and attention it brings secondly if one
of these videos get a million views
that's like a TV show commercial do you
even know how much those costs I don't
know but I'm sure it's at least in the
thousands which is a very generous
donation people shouldn't be doing this
because the ice bucket challenge is a
waste of water meanwhile in Africa this
is probably the biggest and most legit
argument that people have with this
challenge and yeah I'm not even gonna
argue here you do waste water in this
challenge but if you're fortunate enough
to have a computer or have internet
access and you're able to watch these
videos I'm pretty sure that you've
wasted water before and it wasn't even
for charity I'm like 99% sure that every
single person watching this video and
myself are able to waste like a little
bit of water every single day and we do
it whether we want to or not but don't
pretend like you grew up in a
third-world country you've never wasted
food water or anything before if you're
complaining about wasting a little water
for charity then you better be peeing
and pooping in your shower every single
night because flushing the toilet waste
way more water than the ice bucket
challenge and that's not even for
charity but ya know wasting water for
your comfort is much more important than
charity in fact if you're that concerned
over water you shouldn't even be
showering every single night you should
only be showering when you absolutely
have to or like if you're really sweaty
and also you better be getting dirty and
sweaty by accident from natural causes
because guess what if you're working out
you're also wasting water
you're burning unnecessary calories
which causes your body heat to rise and
because of homeostasis you start to
sweat and because of that sweat you get
thirsty and because you're thirsty now
you have to drink water that's your
fault so for all you lazy people out
there that don't work out thank you for
saving the planet and also for all the
people wondering why the ice bucket
challenge why did this challenge start
with ice water instead of just donating
the sad truth is nobody would have
watched let alone share a video of
someone just donating and trying to
raise awareness by talking about it the
ice bucket challenge is when made it
shareable I made it a trend I was taking
those other challenge videos that people
just watch for entertainment purposes
and making it charitable that's right
again for charity nobody got mad about
the waste of cinnamon for the cinnamon
challenge certain world countries need
spices too with all that being said to
anyone who's actually done the ice
bucket challenge and donated despite all
the negativity you might be getting now
I still believe this is a wonderful
trend and a great cause and thank you so
much for doing it and continuing to
spread this campaign I still support it
100% if you're in a place that's in a
drought or some days that water is
scarce
I I completely understand your concern
for saving water but rather than hating
in the comment section which does
nothing but bring negativity why not
just find a solution compromise I mean
they're still
you can do the challenge without wasting
water my friend Jeremy Lin just did it
by throwing himself into the ocean and
if you're still really that concerned
over saving a bucket of water I'm going
to help you out right now by starting
this new campaign called the save water
pee in the shower campaign every single
time you have to pee you pee right into
the drain of your shower but you don't
wash it down into the end of the night
when you take a shower so it all washes
together at once that's like three to
four flushes a day you'll be saving
depending on how much you pee or I
suppose you can do it the other way
around and pee into a toilet all day and
then when you finally flush at the end
of the night you just get in there and
start watching yourself there's a lot of
different solutions rather than
spreading negativity or on the ice
bucket challenge let's be positive let
us find a solution together and keep it
growing let us save water together let
us spread positivity together let us pee
in the shower together
let us that way we can do both continue
to raise funds and awareness for ALS and
save water in the grossest way together
this message brought to you by the save
water penis shower Association I got it
what if we combine the two and pee into
a bucket all day and do the pee bucket
challenge and pour it all that is
disgusting r.kelly nobody wants to do
that I mean we're not doing it right
beeps man PN n buckets before it was
cool so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see last week's
video click the one on the left if you
want to see our ice bucket challenge
video click the one on the right and
remember every single cent of that video
earns goes to the ALS Association so
thank you so much for watching and make
sure you click the donate pretty much