dear Ryan can you do Epic Meal Time
first we open the fridge grab the
package open the package there's no
bacon strips in there no bacon strips in
there no in bacon strips in here open
the microwave put it in close the door
two minutes for ultimate thawing act
it's about to get epic up in here epic
up in here epic to pick up there open
the door like a bomb step down like a
boss take a gander at the world like a
bomb but run off like an assistant there
I saw this bear spill some table all
over that bear mother and Spartan fight
the game is tied you're down by three
last-second shot blocked by yourself
empty parking lot nope blocked folder
flop run around the block running
running at a time running in slow-mo
microwave not much time then epic
clean up the mess paper towels for day
two so leave a question in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
it it looks good like silhouette yeah
yeah