dear Ryan can you do the chubby bunny
challenge chubby bunny
don't be buggin tell boo-boom boo-boom
[Music]
you know it's people like you why I'm
self-conscious top employer dear Ryan do
you slap shot in the face
hey Shawn yeah the hell nobody slaps aw
ah
dear Ryan can you find evil
[Music]
it's right there
dear Ryan can you go Kyle tipping you
good Greg good awesome five right now
we're gonna go cow-tipping I think we
got one right over there it's a cross
hey cow I got a tip for you why don't
you lose some weight fatty I'm gonna
crawl dear Ryan do you have an evil twin
[Music]
seems like you're right professor hope
the world is not ready for colors yet
which is why there can only be one wait
you know gun this little time why don't
you just use that from the star that
goodbye Ryan looks like I twitter.com
slash so real right here
hands up get your hands up both of you
wait what were you doing just shoot it
how do I know which one of you is the
real Ryan what why don't you why don't
you ask us something only the real Ryan
would know all right wait when's my
birthday
easy June 6 1998 as mine seriously
you're doing this I don't know you're
looking kind of fake right now buddy
next question well what's the square
root of 9 times 2 divided by 6 how does
that even help us differentiate who's
the real one man just one strike two
buddy that leaves you with square root
of 9 times 2 it divided by 6 more
chances this is ridiculous right last
question that only the real Ryan Eagle
would know is there ever gonna be a
cheap Apple product that doesn't break
down when a new one comes out no real
Ryan and I said yes it's called the I
doubt it wait a second I was going to
say the same answer huh how did you know
to shoot him
[Music]
professor hope he looks exactly like me
of course he's the face
what are you an idiot come on let's go
take me home it's a good thing we ended
this I almost had to use my pokemons
come on swirlix let's go home
no what you guys I'm comfortable with
how I look so leave a question in the
comments below and you could be
responsible for the next video looks
like you're right professor
[Music]
nobody slapshot ah it's just all in his
eye and you'll be fine oh he'll nobody
slapshot
[Music]
[Laughter]