hello and welcome today I'm gonna be
teaching you how to beat make up but
before we do that you see these wrinkles
see these bags we don't need either of
these anymore
we're doing makeup dear Ryan can you be
a makeup girl first of all you're
probably wondering who is this matching
makeup man he's no Michelle Phan and
you're right I'm not Michelle Phan nor
am i Michelle's Ben or Michelle's then
my name is lots of lots of fun I'm not
gonna be teaching you how to be makeup I
said that already
first things first every make a group
person thing knows that the first thing
you do first is cleanse your face done
the next first step is to powder your
entire face unfortunately for me I had
no powder so I had to walk through the
store but fortunately for me I met a guy
along the way so I didn't have to go all
the way no what's up man you want to buy
some of this so now you got it one's a
little bit more pricey than usual but
that's the price you pay when you order
top-quality makeup brands like Mac now
that you have everything you need you
must now powder your entire face like so
done and finally you're ready for the
last stage your I people like to use
land came and Sephora but what I like to
use is the French Creole a and knowledge
you have your eyes thing what you want
to do is gently and delicately color on
your eyes as fast as you can like this
finishing touches done and now that your
look is complete remember kids if it's
not Mac its crack good luck day so leave
a question in the comments below and you
could be responsible for the next video
a lot more than that
Labour's Shane
so I didn't have to go all the way whoa