hey guys I am about to head to the
Philippines in a couple of days so I'm
like really we're like rushing to make
get this video done I apologize if
there's been like a little delay I'll
try and post this out there when I'm in
the Philippines but I have no idea why
I'm gonna have time to do that based on
our schedule out there I'm in the
Philippines I'm going to the Philippines
or I just came back from the Philippines
so mob hi
ma boo bye okay what am i doing welcome
back to another dear Ryan that's not how
I start this I need a dear Ryan theme
song somebody make me a dear Ryan theme
song I should make my own dear Ryan
theme song it's dear Ryan there's
something a Michael Jackson song
oh dear Ryan can you show us your judo
techniques so for those of you that
haven't watched my drop my life and for
those of you that don't know since I was
five years old I did judo my whole life
going up when I did judo everybody's
like why lunge take karate or like
Taekwondo judo was never a popular sport
only up until recently since the rise of
like Ronda Rousey's Steudle be even been
considered like a legit sport I feel
like Sean and I are actually both black
belts in judo crazy right doesn't mean
we're any good at it but we both have
our black belt we may have colored our
white belts with sharpies black belts
nonetheless call sean fujiyoshi
no yo I'm doing a dear Ryan right now
can I um can I throw you I guess like
judo throws okay all right all right
here we go I guess
the Saline I get the assaulter Gotti the
og got him
Gucci Martha that's my noggin which you
Martha OG got the Ouchi gari Co Nagi of
course was a really advanced llamar
motor got to me the Sony boom box the
hole got to me and last but not least
the og Gotti also to Gotti you gosh I
guess you go to Gotti Ronda Rousey Gotti
see you got your techniques like this
you ain't got to be afraid of anyone not
even Ronda Rousey that's right Rhonda
I'm calling you all publicly I'll take
you out anytime anyplace anywhere you
want to go to dinner I'll take you out
to dinner anytime anyplace anywhere
my treat what I thought maybe even go to
a bar after I actually own a bar I'd
love to have you and it's called the arm
bar I'd break your arm oh you're dead
quick yeah mom water got to me dear Ryan
can you do the human piano get it it's a
human piano human piano dear Ryan how
did you get that scar in your own people
are always asking me about I feel like
I've explained it before but I look
through my videos and I don't think I
actually have so I'm gonna do this one
this scar look how big this scar is
right here and a scar right here
actually I was getting attacked by
ninjas one day and I'm not even gonna
bother this is a true story a story I'm
necessarily proud of when I was 6 years
old I was in the first grade I remember
I was riding my bike with a bunch of my
neighborhood friends you know at the
time there was this stunt daredevil guy
called Evel Knievel you guys don't know
who he is he did a bunch of crazy stunts
on his motorcycle and basically I wanted
to be him I thought that was like the
coolest thing in the world there was a
few of my neighborhood friends and we're
all riding our bike on my street there's
this gigantic ditch she about a six foot
six and a half foot drop and I don't
know where I rode my bike straight
towards the ditch tried to lift up the
handlebars try and do a backflip and
land but it did not quite go that way so
instead I did kind of like a half
backflip and halfway through towards the
end I was like oh my god I'm gonna fall
instead of bailing I turned sideways and
basically I landed exactly on this arm
and completely broke my arm
I got it casted and apparently I don't
know something went wrong with the
casting so the time I was high school
kept having these wrist issues like
every time I just bent it a little it
started to hurt when I got x-ray Tyria
they realized that you know from that
first injury an arm got messed up what
they had to do this because his mom was
longer what they had to do is they had
to cut all the way through the bone and
take out a chunk of bone to make this
bone shorter that's why there's big
slices there and then what they did is
they went in and they attached a metal
rod to the two bones so that the bones
would heal properly and then they put
another metal rod in here you know I had
metal in my arm for like a like two
years some metal actually still in there
but actually really self-conscious about
this I used to always like wanna wear
long sleeve shirts nothing you can do
about it's like it couldn't it could be
worse you could have a scar and your
frickin nose dear Ryan go to hell and
kill yourself wait you want me to go to
hell first and then kill myself it
doesn't make any sense do you even do
that as if you're in hell you're already
dead can you even kill yourself in hell
there's no way you can go to hell if
you're still alive that doesn't make any
sense unless oh my god this is hell
Jesse though dear I make a freestyle rap
um I don't know how to do that my
rapping is basically fifth-grader poetry
I just look for words that rhyme as fast
as I can and then I just even if it
doesn't make sense I'll just say it
that's how I freestyle but I'm just
gonna go for it ah yo I'm sitting right
here doing this dear Ryan call me MGM
cuz I'm a straight lyin to you when I
say that I'm making this up I got all of
the lyrics written out on the back of
this Cup I'm just kidding there's
nothing really on there in fact I
already did this dear Ryan I don't even
know why it's still here I'll tell you
why cuz I'm lazy I'm a bit crazy when I
open my eyes big you got some flowers I
got daisies that made no sense a penny
for your thoughts
cuz I need to buy time now dot dot dot
okay
okay now I know how this rap is gonna
end I'm just gonna keep rhyming words
that all end with n like abbreviation
and condensation on a scale from 1 to 10
IGN rates a 10 out of 10 and for all
y'all that don't think I'm really
rapping for all y'all out there that
don't think I'm really freestyling
you're right I'm not I got all the
lyrics on the back of this cop oh my god
that was so bad okay I was I was I was
freestyling but that I I'm not good I'm
sorry I'm sorry guys
to all the real rappers all
there that was such an insult I'm sorry
guys dear riot can you make dubstep with
your dog you guys have no idea how
difficult it is to work with Marley it
doesn't even sound like dubstep dubstep
sounds more like so leave your questions
in the comments below and you could be
responsible for the next video
you're almost there there we go
thomas up