my Ryan Higa and each week are we taking
a different celebrity with me to survive
in the wild Marshawn Lynch Channing
Tatum Nick Jonas Courtney Cox even
President Obama himself have all said
now to being on the show so instead we
have local celebrities sean fujiyoshi
best known for his work in those viral
how to be videos back in 2007 with his
super cool best friend who is smart and
funny and can most definitely do it all
he still don't think you got all the
greg did Sean to be pushed to his limits
do you think we should get behind this
shall we like to be tested like he's
never been tested before I hear some
quick trivia for you if it's about 65
degrees for googly right now and the Sun
setting in the east where would you find
Kanye West Kanye yeah at home no no no
he would be in the north like its
daughter what and you'll see a side of
him that the world has never seen
oh come on really kind of guy take a
piece seriously this is do this why no I
don't know it's what's happening right
now i ryan told me he's gonna meet me
here with like some kind of helicopter
or something because that's what barrow
does on his show but no no I was just
with him like ten minutes ago so kind of
just like a whole big waste of time you
know I guess we'll see what he has in
mind
right now with the shortage in the all
the mountains hide you think where to
pull it up with his location right now
oh all right I'm here at the spot and I
have no idea where he is all right here
we go
like they say in French adios amigos ah
here we go
how you doing Sean that's it yeah what's
that you're not even gonna wear like a
fake parachute I'm not even gonna wear a
fake pair of shoes really crocks crikey
mate
it's not even the same accent Sean and I
have a long boring uneventful walk ahead
of us before we reach our first stop so
it's a good thing we have multiple
angles beautiful shots of nature and
very important life-changing questions
to feel that time hey you know the
survival shows where they cuts a bunch
of shots of and angles of people walking
and whatnot yeah why well don't you
think like in that one wide shot that
they have don't you have a one like wait
where's all the cameramen you know do
you think with all the different angles
and whatnot you'd see like a few people
here and there and hey look we're at the
end of the wide if we can just walk in
silence now yes you're right you could
catch Johnny boy yes
so we've been out here for about three
or four minutes now and I think I'm
about ready to go home now all right
Sean here's our first challenge what we
got to keep heading in this direction so
what we're gonna need to do is climb
this cliff right here make it to the top
and push forward he's there hiss that's
so dangerous I'm not gonna climb that
Sean we have to climb this you just told
me that we're gonna go on looks like a
little hike I didn't think we're gonna
do anything crazy like this can't we
just like walk around it I mean if you
want to hike another 20 miles that way
and spend another day out here I suppose
we could do that but if you don't want
to do that we have to climb this cliff
this is crazy Sean I've been a survival
expert for about four five maybe even
six minutes now I'm not gonna let
anything bad happen to you you have
nothing to worry about
would you trust me no oh well then we
are in quite the cucumber dipped in
vinegar aren't we that's a pickle by the
way you know what a pickle is the
ancient natives had pickles god I really
don't want to spend another day with you
fine yeah let's do it
oh all right Johnny boy that's a spirit
climbing a cliff is no easy task it's
incredibly dangerous and should not be
attempted without a professional however
if it's your first time rock climbing
you'll have beginner's luck and bad
should be enough all right I guess all
that's left to do is to just go in and
climb this mountain then shouldn't we
like for a rope or something up there to
like give us support in case we fall you
know what gonna be a survival expert
yourself good cat Sean I almost forgot
about this all right so whenever you're
climbing a cliff or a mountain or any
kind of really dangerous Heights where
you could possibly fall what you want to
do especially if you have a bunch of
rope like so pull it up like this bunch
it up just like that and then you're
just gonna what but yeah just like that
and and then you should be good to go
because the last thing you want when
you're climbing a cliff is using any
kind of rope you don't want to mess with
it and then all of a sudden you get all
tangled and then you know you might
mistake it for some kind of snake and
you're like oh no snake let me let go of
this club yeah I'm about a hundred
percent sure that he's never climbed
anything ever in his life but what are
my options
I either I'm this cliff and possibly die
or not climb the cliff and have to spend
another day with him so
yeah I think I'd rather risk dying so
John has no idea but uh I've actually
never climbed a cliff before I mean I
didn't lie I have Rock climbed but it
was one of those cliffs with the
colorful rocks and the people voiced you
up and stuff so it's a little bit safer
but I've never actually climbed a cliff
even with that rock wall I only made it
about a quarter of the way up then I got
scared
I do have an uncle named cliff though
there's that all right so I'm gonna go
up there first just remember whatever
you do do not look down and do not panic
that's one of the biggest mistakes
people make in the wild so just follow
after me let me go up here we go never
you're rock climbing you must always be
patient and take it one step at a time
make one wrong move and it could all be
over I was a really close one Oh almost
fell on all the way back Oh Oh God
you okay I look down I don't like
Heights I should have looked down what
do i do John I know I should have done
this Sean Hill but you're not even that
high right now he can just walk right
back down you're not even at the steep
part okay I just hurry up just calm down
just calm down okay come here help okay
that's a hug me it's okay okay we'll
just slide slide down the hill okay
we're here right here okay okay just
give me a minute okay all right a new
plan I just thought of it
since the Rope is still up there you
know actually only one of us needs to go
up there Andy and once you get up there
you can help pull the other person up
with the rope okay sounds good
right so when you get up there what I
want you to do with me yeah why do I
have to go up because I'm heavier what
you're not even that much heavier than
me and even if you were how is it better
for the lighter person to pull up the
heavier person science look I'll tell
you what okay as you're going up
whichever way you go I'll be right below
you so just in case you fall I'll be
right there to take off my bag and throw
it on the ground so you have something
to fall on and you'll be fine sound good
I guess let's just get this over with
all right let's do this good luck my new
plan seems to be working almost
perfectly
it seems Shawn historian to fatigue as
he approaches the talk well I have to
think fast and come up with a back-up
plan just in case you get stuck
[Music]
oh oh oh my god I made it thank God
yes well that was awesome Sean I was
absolutely phenomenal how'd you get up
here yeah you're just down there oh yeah
see things so funny you're gonna laugh
at this so at the end that I thought
you're gonna fall I went to go gather
some leaves and you know brush and some
rocks for you to fall on and in the
process on the side of the mountain I
found this trail that comes all the way
to the top this is not funny we didn't
need to climb at all
yeah funny hey you have to check this
out this view is amazing
get over here Sean and I enjoy a moment
of nature I realized that it's the
perfect time for a deep and emotional
part of the show
I got father would have loved to see
this right now all right yeah before he
passed he's to always take us camping
and fishing and he just loved everything
about nature so I really wish he could
have been here yeah I know I can
definitely relate to that you know I've
always wanted to bring my own father as
well he's the he's the same way as a
grandfather and you know recently he
passed so sorry no it's it's fine it's
it is what it is but I just I really
wish that one day he could really just
be out here with me
see this Hey I think he already is what
what you're not my father
no not me I meant like his spirit its
spirit what are you that's not funny you
trying to say that my father's dead what
you just said he passed yeah I asked him
to come out here and he said thanks son
but I'll have to pass I would spend an
entire day with you in the wild for your
stupid little show but I'd much rather
be dead than do that something like that
I don't know I'm not a good impression -
so he has a weird accident but my point
is is that he's not dead it's a really
messed up thing to say actually your
comedy is a little bit too dark for me
anyway we better get moving before it
actually gets dark out we don't want to
end up like your grandfather right right
you get it cuz you're because if when he
gets dark the predator might attack us
anyway my dad um yes I get it
no I don't think you get it because you
didn't want laughing isn't funny - okay
then
so we're mad sometimes in the wild
things can get a little frustrating and
I'm starting to suspect that Sean's
getting a little irritable mean yeah I'm
pretty annoyed I mean aren't you guys
Sean's irritable nurses probably due to
the hunger settling in if we don't find
nutrients for him soon he may catch a
bad case of the hangers and literally
starve to death
all right so we're actually really close
to the extraction point we just got to
climb one more Hill but if we're gonna
make it all that way we have to find
some food in nutrients for Sean before
he starts to death what I'm not even
starving I'm not even hungry but luckily
for him I know exactly where to look and
I'm not gonna let that happen so come on
ate like two hours ago before we started
this and you're in the wild you have to
be resourceful and know where to look it
may take some time but you have to be
persistent and keep your cool can expect
food to just magically fall out of a
tree check this out
right here and that is how you do it see
a lot of people don't think to look up
in the tree for food but it's actually
very common for people to just get a
bucket of chicken bring it out to the
forest and then just sit no oh what's
wrong no why who the F one of them has
no skin who the greedy but just comes in
here
he's all the skin illegal you know the
driest late pointless pointless what
kind of rock really upset I guess that's
just like his pet peeve or something I
don't know maybe the dude just really
loves fried chicken skin I mean it's
common sense it's common courtesy basic
manners you know like if you're gonna if
you're gonna leave a bucket of chicken
on a branch and a tree in the middle
than the matter Mountains tell me all
the skin or just the skin or at least
leave some gravy or something why ask me
hey you're right yeah no I'm I'm good
now so I'm I listen I am so sorry about
that showing off no no it's fine that's
a totally reasonable way to react to not
having chicken skin on your chicken no
no no I know it's a natural reaction
that everybody anybody would have but I
should know better than to overreact you
never want to over act in the wild
that's one of the basic rules never lose
your cool and I did so for that I'm
sorry
what come on now what we really don't
have to we got to do this Shawn
if you want to go home let's just get
this over with come on I'll bring it in
fine
hey hey what what are you doing I had to
be sure sure of what you didn't take the
skins and you didn't and now I can trust
you for life come on let's go
the Nevada mountains are incredibly
dangerous but with the right technique
and knowledge and maintaining your cool
your pressive ear choppers right over
this hill this is the end
Shawn really really impressed me today
and he's definitely under my respect not
because of the bravery he showed or the
endurance that he had the entire trip
but because he didn't take the skins and
in the end that's all that really
matters isn't it
I'm ready I can't believe we made it
well you guys got an extra battery or a
charger what's all of this where's the
helicopter oh yeah you know about that I
don't think you know this but you know
the very beginning with the whole
helicopter dropping me off yeah we faked
that yeah I know yeah there was no
actual helicopter there's no helicopter
wait so you're telling me that we're
gonna have yeah we gotta walk back