is Ryan Higa and I'm going to be
surviving all by myself in the Arctic
with nothing but the clothes on my back
and chest in arms and pretty much all my
clothes while teaching you the necessary
tips and techniques to survive in the
freezing Arctic with nothing but the
clothes on my back right now we're in
the Arctic this is no place for fun and
games hold on you don't know what are
you lost out here the Arctic terrain is
completely unforgiving if you get lost
out here you'll be sorry the Arctic
terrain won't forgive you because of the
unforgiving this do not want to get lost
out here trust me if you do up
whoa one of the toughest parts of the
Arctic is actually just just walking
around because of all the snow you're
gonna need something to help you not
sink into the snow while you're walking
right now I'm going to teach you how to
make your own homemade snow shoes we're
after get this big ski off when you're
lost in the wild you have to be
resourceful and make do with what you
have so let's make your snowshoes what
you want to do first close your two
daily tennis racquets from your jacket
I place them beneath your feet this is
gonna be like the base of your shoe and
actually gonna need something to tie the
rackets to your shoes you're gonna take
the laces from your big ski and well
unfortunately for me it seems this big
he has no shoelaces and you definitely
don't want to use the shoelaces from
your actual shoe because that'll make
your shoes look weird and you definitely
want that in the Arctic so what you're
gonna want to do from here is put the
two extra shoelaces you can't run in
your jacket and use these to tie the
rackets to your shoe like so this
technique may look very complicating and
difficult to understand and it is
all right now you made your snowshoes
nice and snug
time to get moving because we got a lot
of ground to cover let's go
the ancient natives traveled great
distances with their snowshoes some say
they even went as far as going to thee
and that's about enough for today you
don't ever want to dehydrate yourself in
a snowy terrain like this one
well the biggest parts of survival if
not the biggest staying hydrated
contrary to most belief in other
survival shows when you're thirsty and
desperate you never want to drink your
own pee
because it's sterile and absolutely
disgusting what you want to do is just
eat some snow from the ground it might
sound crazy
the ancient natives really believed that
snow acted is a good substitute for
water when in desperate times eating
snow in a terrain like this may bring
your body temperature to an unsafely low
level that's a good thing because then
you won't sweat and you won't dehydrate
again don't want to do is just eat
random snow because it might be dirty to
be safe always look for the yellow snow
like this one right here chances are
this is someone's pea and as you know
pea is very safe to drink because it's
sterile so what we're gonna do here is
just scoop a little bit out from the
middle and uh - okay that's not penal
never drink from an open carton because
it may have mono I'll have to find
shelter soon because night is coming and
it's only gonna get colder from here the
cool way to tell how much time you have
left before nightfall is by knowing the
temperature see the ancient natives
didn't have watches like you and I so
what they would do is use temperature as
a measurement of time the colder it gets
the later it is basically the technique
they use is actually pretty simple what
you do is you pull out your cell phone
and what you're gonna do here just find
the weather app it's already it's not
really moving because of my gloves -
you're getting really it's pretty
difficult right now my gloves are making
it nearly impossible to open the weather
app and I can't take off my gloves
because my hands are cold and the last
thing you want in the Arctic is to be
uncomfortable you're still unable to
open your weather app because your
gloves what you want to do then is pull
out your daily jacket thermometer and
basically use a thermometer as a sort of
stylus or writing tool so you can open
your weather app the ancient natives
this technique from the Nintendo DS as
you can see yeah almost no problems at
all it's working phenomenally
phenomenally is a big word there you go
as you can see it actually this is the
coldest I've ever seen it before it's
negative 1 degrees Celsius at for you
Americans I believe that anywhere
between 20 to 75 degrees for googly
that's really cold so we really need to
get moving but as a day drags on I find
neither food nor shelter my feet are
starting to bark my nipples meta parting
and I'm going to think I bit off a
little more than I could chew this time
you know being out here all this time
and it's only been like 30 minutes but
I'm starting to feel like giving up it's
hard to lose hope but then I remember
well my grandfather's only son of my
dad's side always told me son it's an
ice box you open it get what you want
close it I'll stop poisoning electricity
and after all this time I never really
understood what he was talking about
until right now he was talking about
here he was talking about the Arctic how
I should never give up I should
persevere how I need to never back down
and just never give up get out of here
buddy get out of here get it out of here
yeah
thank you guys so much for watching if
you want to see the cabin trip we took
in order to film this video click the
one on the left you want to see the last
dude verse while take the one on the
right if you want to see Greg the guy
with the mustache attempt this very
first backflip in the snow we'll just
wait to the end of this video in five
four three two one
I started to come too soon okay now it's
okay there we just don't think just
believe just talk into it like a little
ball go oh oh oh oh my goo closer close
it looser cool okay oh oh my god Tina