hey guys so I feel like I tell you guys
the same thing every single month but I
am once again sync with um just kidding
is probably just Ebola fever bola Ebola
fever hold up speaking of Ebola it might
the only one that before you found out
what it was you pictured about like a
snake and that's probably because it
sounds like ball like a ball constrictor
or like boy the k-pop star yep
ten seconds in already off topic as you
can probably see it's gonna be one of
those videos not even because of my ADHD
this time it's because I'm a little
delirious from the medication but I'm
still gonna make the video anyway I'm
sorry I really shouldn't be making any
bullet jokes but honestly I really did
think like legitimately thought that I
had it like about a week ago about a
week ago did that come on I'm not gonna
lie to you guys a couple weeks ago I got
back from out of country and I got
really sick I was getting really bad
headaches and nausea and like stomach
aches and for some reason I just kept
sneezing and coughing up blood all the
time I wasn't gonna reverse vampire I
was just like spitting out blood it was
bad but it turns out it was just a
really bad sinus infection but at the
time I thought I was dying so naturally
I was a little paranoid and it didn't
help that everybody on Facebook and
Twitter was talking about how Ebola is
gonna have an outbreak and stuff like
that so just like any other paranoid
person I did what you're not supposed to
do and I just googled my symptoms and
guess what pops up not Ebola but some
other random illnesses that don't really
matter because they're not in the news
right now but when I googled Ebola guess
what happened guess what I saw under the
symptoms list did not match up with my
symptoms completely probably not even
half but I knew for sure that I had
Ebola keep in mind I was very delirious
and sick and super jet lag so I honestly
did believe that I had and just like
anyone else who believe they're infected
with a deadly virus I did exactly what
you would think to do in that scenario
not go to the doctor and make a video
about it instead hence this but
fortunately as you can tell I got a lot
better but just the scare of thinking
that you might have Ebola or anything
else that's deadly makes you think a lot
deeper and that's exactly what I did it
actually helped me come up with a new
model to live by I used to be all about
that Yolo life Yolo right you only live
once Oh live life to the fullest it's a
good message but come on we all know you
all know this out nobody says that
anymore and so news I probably said it
more times in this video so far than
people have said it today in the world
now here's a brain
Newmont straight out of a sick person's
head it's called it's none other than
welcome to this is gonna well this I'm
trying to think of a epic way to
announce what the word is but it's
already in the title you guys know it
it's Ebola its bolo it's Ebola everybody
only lives once right it's a completely
new and unique motto okay it's literally
saying the same thing but the meaning is
completely opposite of Yolo everybody
only lives once so be careful don't live
life to the fullest that's dangerous
live life to the safest nothing that
Yolo nonsense Yolo will get you killed
but Ebola will keep you alive meet
Johnny he's about to embark on an
average trip to the market but when
Shawnee reaches for his seat belt the
seat belt gets stuck frustrated and over
it Shaunie is about to make the biggest
mistake of his life
Yolo
and now little Shaunie is a little gonee
if only Shaunie took the smarter route
and said he bore loans too dangerous to
drive it out seatbelt the meteor would
have missed him and you'd still be alive
today
now meet Derek Derek is at a party where
he's being peer pressured to drink
marijuana drugs and come on deck our
cookies are doing it but what Derek
doesn't know is that he's about to make
the biggest mistake of his life
Yolo Derek more like dead Rick
if only Derek made the right choice and
said nah man the drug lord who had his
marijuana drugs stolen would not have
sent his pet rhinoceros after Derek and
he'd still be alive today
moving on this is morally he's a dog so
he can't even say the word Yolo which is
why Marley is more living last but not
least meet Ryan he just got back on a
trip overseas and got so sick that he
actually thinks he has Ebola
Ryan is debating if he should make a
video of all his experience or go to the
doctor should probably go the doctor but
what Ryan doesn't know is that he's
about to make the biggest mistake of his
life
all right all right I'm sorry to
interrupt this has to stop mr. narrator
guy it makes no sense anymore how is me
making this video deciding not to the
doctor I'm making this video the worst
mistake of my life if I'm still alive
right now I'm doing it and nothing has
even happened
[Music]
see if Ryan never made this video he'd
still be alive today what are you doing
using up my endcard time I have to tell
them what videos to click on next so you
think I could join you for this MCOR I
don't know man is kind of a solo thing
but I guess y'all alright wait so should
we start doing that oh yeah to see last
week's video click the window left