yeah I'm about to lay down all the dirt
you know the facts that I gained over
the past 10 years 12 years actually yeah
cuz I just want to cut this beef with a
fork and knife right now first off let
me get off my chest I'm not what you all
thought righteous time's up and I'm
gonna raise my wrists expose all of
those that I met since oh six so you
thought you were safe or under with the
click post another picks and the clips
looking violent side man mullet crying
man how about I let the world know but
the kiss side that I've mad nobody knows
about the time in Cosmo just my team to
meet your side the hell would I know
that you pay for it oh every trinket the
bottle and selfish and duffle and
charitable that we're moving on where to
look and pause I was appalled when I saw
all the controversy
[Music]
oh you react when I like the fact that
Ben and Rafi are related but you didn't
know it's about time everybody knows
smushy minded up shots fired get your
mind blown who died who's that who a
magic mustache three points were for one
and a five nine
that's right I'm talking about pieman
and Singapore mb/s become award night
here side with a nice smile and the blue
eyes gonna be more time to earth even 55
for high won't kind of like when I met
rice for the first time even I was
surprised for my own eyes or the
distract and the fig facts are a
mismatch you in that bad to the truth
bride maybe I'm lying
maybe I'm the bad guy superwoman got
permission bird even Lily now it's your
time silly come in for my feelings
because you know I'm swimming but your
whole life shouldn't be killing your
image concealing but I think I'm gonna
keep it moving like every to Purdue and
they get grounded and they groovin
algorithms and they proven Hollywood's
in the future find the rhythm the
moochers gender to me into with the
realest genuine youtubers speaking of
which I think the most really composed
honest innocence yeah now you're double
it and you get the merit wins
I can't expose anymore from my own
experience but who knows I know Franco
and his new show keepin it real old G
Timothy's ill again
what a journey can't believe when from
peeping on the stream now you're on my
TV but to me most importantly get
integrity especially a comedy a dying
breed bastards roots icicle she
whoopsies my name out it was probably
just a misfit for my rhymes scuttling
personally running how to track this and
many left got a rabbit past channel M&M
agree upon diversion super saiyan when a
witness and they gotta read the
differences there get some official with
the lyric really efficient exposing
[Music]
works
your grenade oh yeah it probably would
not I'll figure it out I'll just have a
drama almost have my Twitter hacked I
never would've thought
[Music]
it's up next and there's so much stuff
to say like that one time one day get
exposed at the whole world no seeing the
course with me everybody get up let's go
I'm just oh never never mind then
[Applause]
[Music]