hey guys so for those of you that don't
know I've been making YouTube videos for
about eight years now and a lot has
changed since then both good and bad but
today I'm gonna be talking about one of
the bad ones because I'm a pretty
pessimistic person I'm pretty negative
some people see the glass half full some
people see the glass half-empty for me
I'm so negative I don't even see the
glass anymore oh no wait it's still have
full mmm I just realize what this looks
like the letter C anyway I'm gonna be
talking about one of the bad changes
that I've noticed that is definitely on
the rise on YouTube which happens to be
yeah you guessed it it's in the title
easily but hold people I mean but butter
hurt be easily butthurt people in the
they're hurt what beep-beep-beep-beep
ooh but hurt people people who are
easily offended and reacted an overly
dramatic fashion usually starting with
the word Wow here's some examples of
easily butthurt people tune I love Nicki
Minaj she's Bom look she's alright you
don't think she's Bom I mean she's not
really my type I kind of more into girls
that actually wear clothes Wow man I
can't believe you're just lucky I'm not
into slut-shaming she's just not that's
not my preference lust shaming is a big
problem because it's all over the news
no I didn't mean that
you are me made in China hey Derrick
you're Chinese right Wow
oh are you serious what I'm Taiwanese
man there's a big difference oh I'm
sorry man I didn't realize no you didn't
you're right
one here funny joke sure alright what do
you call that Asian person I don't know
what a chunk good okay I don't want fur
you know alright what do you call a
school bus full of white people Twinkie
wow dude what I can't believe you just
said that well I thought because you
made a racist no my father was killed by
a tweet you get the point
don't get me wrong easily butthurt
people have always existed they're also
known as overly sensitive people I'm
sure you know exactly what kind of
people I'm talking about and maybe it's
just me but I feel like over the years
people have gotten more and more easily
butthurt over everything especially on
YouTube YouTube used to be a place where
you could upload whatever you wanted we
uploaded things that we are passionate
about we could say whatever you wanted
to say it was like the opposite of
television it was freedom but over the
years I notice that YouTube is becoming
more and more like television where you
have to be really careful with what you
say because everything you say is gonna
be used against you and it's
fend something we can't say or do
anything on YouTube anymore without a
bunch of people being so dramatic thing
is I don't even think these people are
actually offended half the time I think
they believe that it's supposed to
offend them so they act that way but
really doesn't even bother them or maybe
they just say these things so people
agree with them for example I posted a
video a couple weeks ago and there's a
joke in it that mentions Ebola and the
thing is if there wasn't so much news
and articles about Ebola right now
nobody would have cared about that joke
at least majority of the people wouldn't
have been offended but because it's a
turning topic and scary to people it's
all of a sudden so offensive and for
those of you who haven't seen that video
this is what the joke looked like if a
girl that small were to kill me how what
the hell do there
Ebola now you really have seven days no
why I even told you and from that little
mention of Ebola I got so many upset
comments saying things like that is so
offensive people are dying from Ebola
now it's not a joke yeah making fun of a
deadly virus is so funny you're such a
bad example for kids see I understand
when you first see this how you could
think it's offensive cuz it's a serious
topic in a comedy video think about it
does that really offend you or do you
just think it should first of all it's
one joke in a fictional scene on a
comedy video on YouTube and even if it
did does that joke honestly hurt you or
offend you in any way because if it does
I apologize sincerely I did not mean to
offend you in any way it wasn't meant to
be offensive but if you really do get
offended that easily you should probably
stay off the internet because you're
gonna have a bad time Ebola is not
something new it's been around for a
long time just because something is all
of a sudden in the news it doesn't make
it any less or more deadly than it was
before I made that same joke a year ago
I'm pretty sure nobody would have cared
because it wasn't a trending topic there
or if I were to switch out the word
Ebola with something else that's deadly
like arsenic people wouldn't have even
mentioned it and injecting arsenic is
just as deadly if not more deadly you
would even have seven days to live you
died that day and last if mentioning
Ebola in a YouTube video is a bad
example for kids just because it's a
deadly virus and what about children
shows like Tom and Jerry that entire
children's show is about a cat trying to
murder a mouse but I guess attempted
murder is not that bad right because
it's not in the news but it is or what
about Pokemon that's a bunch of people
who are capturing wild animals and
keeping them captive in a little ball
raising them until they're strong enough
to fight other animal sounds like animal
cruelty to me or even spongebob there's
not much violence in that one but it's
very sexually inappropriate for kids
come on they live in bikini bottom and
there's somebody named Sandy Cheeks in
bikini bottom and also there's a mr.
Krabs in bikini bottom don't even get me
started on Squidward's nose
childhood ruined and like I said these
are all children's shows Burt
and me because I watch them occasionally
sometimes okay I watch them all the time
so well you easily butthurt people out
there the next time you feel like
something is offensive to you asked
yourself this does this really bother
you does it actually offend you or are
you just thinking that because you feel
like you should be offended even though
you're really not and also because you
want to make a point to the rest of your
butthurt friends can thumbs up your
comment because if that's the case
you're one of the main reasons why
YouTube is becoming a butthurt place and
it's a real pain in the ass pun not
intended but intended seriously let me
just go back to the fun YouTube
community that it once was I know that
was a long time ago about eight years I
was like 15 or 16 I'm getting old now
I'm 24 I'm about to die wow that is
really offensive what you just said
you're 24 and you're about to die that's
really offensive to everyone older than
it was a joke that is not something you
should joke about you should never never
joke about that
Never Say Never
oh so now you're supporting guns and old
outdated Justin Beiber references that's
even more offensive than before you
support Justin and he supports weed
which means you support drugs how are
you even here I just shot you that
wasn't even me you racist just because
I'm Asian we all look alike I mean you
do look like we all do you're both
technically media because everything
revolves around you the whole world
revolves around you you probably don't
even care about the starving kids in
Africa because you're all in the first
rogue country where you even have to
care about what everything what's up I
didn't even shoot you that time but I
did let me guess I said something
offensive to you now what no those guys
were just being irritating they were
getting butthurt over every little thing
thank you that is what I've been trying
to save this whole time thank God
someone is finally wise okay you know
what I was cool with everything else but
the moment you bring religion into this
that's the moment you know what I give
up I'm not even gonna talk this time wow
you're not gonna talk to me just because
I'm a girl that's the most sexist thing
I ever alright is there anyone left or
can I please just get back to the video
Jesus crap what did you just say I said
Jebus like with a B like JB JB so you do
support Justin Bieber and his drum house
I do not support him I was just you just
say to him you're no he's a guy for sure
you sexist what do you hate girls so
much and I don't I love girls I love
y'all to death Wow more death jokes good
job Ryan
there he bowl arsenic naughty book
wasn't people I could have been Ebola
maybe not what was it arsenic
well now you really have seven days or
seven seconds depending on which one it
was I don't know is there syringes next
to me but which one is it is it Ebola or
art sick oh I guess it was our snake I
guess this joke was in good taste after
all good taste just like this Twinkie
I just wanted to apologize about Magican
wait a second
by making this video doesn't it mean
you're about her person because you're
butter from the butter people no because
it wasn't all about the butthurt people
it was about the Twinkies too
[Music]
so thank you guys so much for watching
if you want to see the last week we do
we throw it on the left if you want to
see bloopers and behind-the-scenes into
another right remember you don't you
don't want to do any of those you can
just sing along with me ready five six
seven eight
[Music]