Yeah right can you make everyday
trickshot video like trick shots you
were doing your everyday life does that
even mean I'm doing my everyday life no
I think they mean to make trick shots
out of stuff you do everyday okay but
like what kind of everyday things
what about bottom flips what those are
trick shots bottle full but that's not
an everyday thing plus we already did
that yeah a long time ago it's not even
a thing anymore plus you guys know how
much I hate when we do overdone trap
what look if we're trying to do an
everyday trickshot video let's at least
figure out what you do every day and
then try to make trick shots out of that
what kind of everyday things I don't
know just make a list of what you did
before we came here all right
today started off like any other day
[Music]
[Applause]
Yeah right can you make a everyday
trickshot video and that's about it it's
just another average day am I supposed
to make trick shots out of any of that
really what you expect us to believe
that's what you did this morning that's
what you do every day yeah what part of
that is so hard to believe
oh I don't know how about like the
toothbrush part where you throw it
behind your back without looking in
Atlantan a tiny cog yeah I do it every
day or bouncing the paper plate off a
fridge into the truck I would just toss
it straight in but because of the angle
you kind of and really growing away your
alarm clock what about you honestly
expect us to believe that that's what
you do every morning yeah that's what I
have all those expensive but you know
what you gotta do look all I'm trying to
say is that it sounds a little
unrealistic I'm realistic Wow
okay so what are you trying to say on I
just told you that seems a little
unrealistic so you're calling me a liar
we're not same parts of your story
sounds a realist so you're saying I'm
fake now I'm not going you a fake per se
you're not a person what you listen here
all right and I would never ever ever
stoop so low as to faking a trick shot
video
know what
see it's all real whoops
[Music]
Oh
[Laughter]
[Applause]