oh dude what the hell so hard you block
this oh yeah Oh
nibs McGee
all right Shawn your first hit him as
hard as you can
great give him a karate chop right in
its neck all right you kick a - groin
you're gonna squeeze it it's harder you
guys why don't we just all attack him at
the same time
Ryan I'm gonna make You Gino you talking
like that I've never told anything I
love you had to tell you before I
Ryan I'm not gonna make it you talk like
that I never told you I left the soda
can in the freezer
left a can of soda in the freezer you
don't take it out it's gonna explode
what who cares about that you've just
been shot I don't understand if you
don't take it out it's gonna go
everything I don't care about the
freezer I don't care about a stupid can
of coke yes I care about you cold from
them because I love you what what are
you doing Ryan this isn't funny I know
you're still alive I can feel your pulse
you know what even if you do live
through this don't expect me to be
around anymore and I hope that stupid
coat does explode in your freezer you
jerk gee just bright damn it Charlie is
the blue one or the red one just caught
red blue white black which one anyone
cut the white oh yeah it can't be the
white one Charlie then cut the blue one
it's not the blue one either red telling
you Charlie it's not the red and it has
to be the black one Oh what the hell man
what that is racist what I think just
because it's the black one that's the
one that needs to be cut what are you
talking about that was the last one I
told you to cut you should hear yourself
right now you sound like a racist
basketball coach listen we are running
out of time just cut the quiet line this
was your choice not mine
you did it you did it
damn it Charlie is the blue one or the
red one could any of them just flip it
over flip it over okay now take out the
batteries
all right the batteries out it's no
climb down right well look for an outlet
around got it plugged in yes okay so
unplug it still cutting down Charlie
damn it
all right listen okay I want you to just
cut all the wires at once but wires or
what makes it work if you cut them all
at once it'll probably mess something up
are you crazy I'm not gonna do that
I'm just Yolo okay okay so now that the
alarm clock is off what what do you want
me to do with the bomb
get up against the wall turn around
yeah oh you know expected a lot of wine
it was too easy
so easy that I can pour myself a cup of
delicious tea I can enjoy this cup of
tea carefree without even being worried
about being interrupted mid-sentence it
was too easy so easy that I can pour
myself a cup of delicious tea I can
enjoy this cup of tea carefree without
even being interrupted mid-set wipe
yourself off man you did without even
being interrupted mid scent like
yourself off man who day are you
supposed to say that after you shoot
it's just in rift flow again I get to
lead the weapon to reference but that's
supposed to happen long live the king
okay well that would actually did happen
before the kill but my King doesn't
really have nothing to tea huh more like
teehee okay so now that the alarm clock
is off what what do you want me to do
with the bomb too easy
see huh more like so thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see the behind the scenes in bloopers
click the one on the left if you want to
see the last expectations vs. reality I
think it was like relationships or
something like the one on the right and
that's all there is to clicked today so
yeah