hey guys I recently got pulled over for
the first time in a long time for going
six miles per hour over the speed limit
true story when it comes to being pulled
over I'm either really lucky or really
good at getting out of getting a ticket
I've been pulled over a total of four
times now and each time I got off with a
warning this last time was probably the
stupidest reason I've ever gotten pulled
over but I have to admit the first three
times I kind of deserved it the first
time I got pulled over it was because I
just didn't completely stop at a stop
sign okay something that didn't really
stop at all at the stop sign I kind of
drifted what Tokyo Drift was big at the
time yo all right I mean the second time
I kind of ran a red light and I come on
it was an emergency I had to poop there
should be a special light for that there
should be a brown light well I mean I
guess sometimes green does work yo all
right and the third time I mean it was
even a big deal I just kind of stole the
Toyota oh my god go go go we wasn't even
chasing I stole this Toyota
Yolo I deserve a ticket right now for
saying Yolo three times in one video for
now anyway I've had a lot of reasons to
hate the police just like everyone else
I'm not going to because could you
imagine how much it already sucks to be
a policeman I mean everyone hates on the
net cake wrappers for example they're
one of the most influential people in
this world and yet they're always
hitting on the police in their song
especially for whatever reason at the
end of a verse right before the chorus
[Music]
but I'm not a rapper clearly back to the
top like I was saying before I got
pulled over a few nights ago and gotten
that up with a warning once again I know
so many people who still get tickets for
stupid reasons like this so like I said
either you're really unlucky or you're
probably just doing it wrong so I'm
gonna be giving you guys some tips on
how not to get tickets these are the top
three things that you shouldn't do when
you get pulled over don't ever try to
convince him that he's wrong or you made
a mistake
do you know why I pulled you over dope
actually I really don't because I'm very
sure I was waiting 35 do not make any
excuses unless if it's an emergency like
your cat is flying do you know why I
pulled you over me I mean it's not my
fault I couldn't see the speed limit
sign I was going way too fast it was all
blurry you know and no matter what we do
not undermine him or trying to be a jerk
to him do you know why I pulled you over
um cuz it's a slow day for you you had
nothing better to do you used to be
popular in high school and you had all
the power in the world and all of a
sudden with high school ended you had no
power so you decide to become a police
man and pull people over for no good
reason what you want to do is show
complete respect this is pretty close to
what it looked like when I got pulled
over do you know why I pulled you over I
am so sorry officer it was completely
irresponsible of me and I should not
have been going that fast I sincerely
apologize well you don't seem to be an
[ __ ] so I'm gonna let you off with a
warning this time just be a little bit
more cautious yes yes no yes yes of
course yes thank you so much sir thank
you
oh and of course if that method doesn't
work it also helps to have a big rack as
well do you know why I put you all up
there oh wow yeah that's quite a big
rack you have they're all yours here you
go thank you this is exactly what I
needed without police there would be so
much crime so much injustice so many
murders well I mean there already are a
lot of murders
I mean it's especially with all the
shootings lately and please do not start
another gun control debate in the
comments do you really want to know the
answer to keeping our people safe the
answer has been right in front of us the
whole time
hide your kids hide your wife I actually
named my Wi-Fi options education hide
your wife oh yeah this is John and I
dated Marcel Mia morphine you don't have
the hand Anna
we're pretty much like best friends now
so overall just remember the best way to
get out of getting a ticket is by not
getting in one at all and keep in mind
that all the laws make complete sense
and are here for a reason and if there's
just one thing that you can take from
this video or one thing that you can
remember just remember this statement do
you know why I pulled you over I am so
sorry officer it was completely
irresponsible of me and I should not
have been going that fast I sincerely
apologize I appreciate that but I'm
sorry I'm still gonna have to write you
with here here's my Rach nice try
somebody I already got one earlier when
I pulled over the up about this and you
are good to go have a nice day
everything is easier with a big rack