hey guys so this video is gonna suck
just letting you know so I was supposed
to film today and hopefully post the
video by tomorrow which we all know is
Friday okay so that joke got old fast
that was supposed to be like you know
like a fast you know like it like a fast
car
some like Dobb lurry thank science
anyway so as I was saying until I saw
rudely interrupted my hai itself I was
gonna film today but I needed a costume
and that costume was gonna be delivered
to me but sadly that didn't happen I
don't want to point any fingers or name
names names so let's just call this
company FedEx I paid for the X extra
money just so they could overnight it to
me and three days later I still don't
have it which honestly wouldn't have
been that bad if they would at least let
me know but no I tracked it and it said
it was coming so I waited I waited by
the window like like a dog were a badass
dog I need to woke up extra early just
so that I could receive the box myself
because apparently if you don't answer
the door they're just gonna leave your
package underneath your welcome mat no
matter how big the packages and I'm
sorry I don't want to sound like a
complainer but I'm just fed up with
FedEx next time I'm just gonna use a
different delivery service like UPS but
really the real reason why this upset me
so much is because I've been trying to
post videos more frequently for you guys
and I put so much time into planning and
making sure this video would go out by
this weekend but sadly you're stuck with
this crap sorry but I promise you as
soon as you get my costume I will film
edit and post the video as soon as
possible for those of you who want to
know what the video is gonna be about
well
it has nothing to do with that clip I
just got interrupted again hi shadow
what if he what if he never comes Oh
gents
be patient he's coming are you sure
shadow are you sure I hope so
are you guys like date
ho sassy you're such a [ __ ] but yes