hey guys so it just passed that I cannot
open notice this very overused trend
that's all I saw about Wednesday
seriously can get it it's funny when
it's a joke but they were seriously a
lot of people who really think that
they're forever alone I don't what is
this
and these people are actually sat there
same and I don't think that's a
legitimate reason to be sad no one needs
a wiper in our girlfriend to be happy
and just a heads up by telling people
only you are you're actually repetitive
everything that you want self-pity is
not attractive to most people just smile
be happy maybe your next Valentine's Day
it could look like mine yeah I know
you're turned on right now you're a
little cold but you're gonna be heating
up because I'm gonna be on you all night
you ready cuz together we're gonna
create something beautiful you think I'm
making a joke but that's pretty much how
my Valentine's night was I even tweeted
it Twitter blasts anyway I am sick of
this trend and I want no part of it no
part of it nope you already know I'm
gonna do it so
I don't know how to say this but I I
love you thank you
[Applause]
hey honey did you miss us all here you
go 20 bucks
thanks for appreciating it hey make sure
you pay me back though
you wanna boom you want a boo you want
the bull you want the boat no forever no
boom one day I'm gonna be a tree yeah
probably not forever a stone
[Music]
oh yeah just keep lying down freaking
camper forever intro who are you forever
alone
mom dad bus where are you guys
it may not mean nothing to y'all forever
bye drink um yeah so I have ADHD as you
probably can see for every butterfly
my point is that yes we all want to find
that one person that we fall in love
with and I really do have nothing
against the forever alone - I'm just
saying if you're actually sad about
being single don't go posting it all
over the internet for everybody to see
that's not gonna work and if you're in
your teen years and younger I know a
boyfriend or girlfriend might seem like
the most important thing in the world
right now but trust me it's not I'm 21
I've been a teenager for like ten years
I know so stop worrying about being
alone just smile at it like - in school
there's a lot more fish in the sea
and remember the world is your oyster
and one day you're gonna find your pearl
unless if your oyster has no pearl then
in that case you would have to get
another waster which means you need
another world yeah it's not looking good
for you