I don't want to go too into detail but
like I hate it I'm like learning from
this this guy I don't even know like I
met him through VGA and I'm like why are
you telling me what to do man I think
that's what having a kid does it really
makes you think about who you are
I've been ready are you sure right I'm
not ready welcome back to another
episode of off the pill podcast I
thought you didn't do the interest song
no you said you didn't want to use that
interest we have mr. justin chon in the
house GP GP you know in the first song
that was just there's that I mean you
guys are hearing on it but like it's
just me and David in the background here
BGA chanting it's just me and David haha
I did like 50 times to try to get
different times all across you know we
don't have real fans doing that from do
one day bring you back
I didn't an intro Paco is also in the
thing there he goes yeah that's the
perfect sound for you yeah I got it um
yeah I went all out of order you know
why because we are back in Vegas and it
is um we haven't done a podcast here in
like three episodes but we are back
because Justin is in town I'm here how's
it going man it's going good it's been a
while since you've been out here too and
yeah it last time was the last fight you
came here the last game was for what or
which fight all right a conor mcgregor's
might have been it might may weather
gregory was it was that fight was that
fight remember feeling really sort of
like disappointed mmm
anyways you look like you're from the
90s with that hat on thank you I
appreciate you look like a custodian
from the night I know with that haircut
answer you know I'm trying guys look I'm
going for you want to explain because I
don't know people couldn't I don't know
if people know or not but you're hella
buff right now uh-huh
and you're doing you said you're doing
it for a role yeah I'm about to the
you talk about yeah yeah yeah I'm
playing I'm gonna be playing a
korean-american adoptee that's getting
deported
deported and he lives in the south this
is the film that you wrote and you're
directing yeah
ending your action acting and you were
working with the studio a big studio
yeah about who you're working with yeah
I mean the main the main studio is macro
there's a co-financed here for the film
but macro made sorry to bother you mud
bound they made two of Denzel
Washington's films fences and Roman
Esquire they made yeah you know they
made they they made up this film called
the land you know they do a lot of like
super you know ethnic driven films so
they're like a good partner for this but
yeah it's about like you know with like
deportation and stuff these days you
know we have the dreamers and daca but
like part of it that people aren't
talking about is people who were adopted
here internationally from like the 70s
and 80s are getting deported people who
are adopted here by why you what do you
mean by US citizens so you adopted
meaning like they flew them like ship
them over yeah like you know when you
adopt baby from Africa or China or Korea
oh I don't know about that I mean I know
people do it but ya know see do you know
any like real house aren't illegal at
that point as I'm saying that's why it's
really messed up you say that is hat so
there you go but they're getting
deported well yeah what's happening is
that that that they get brought to this
country you know and this is there's a
child Citizenship Act of 2000 so anyone
adopted after that gets automatically
granted citizenship huh but anyone
before that is detected so if they got
adopted here and the parents didn't file
like the proper paperwork yeah now like
with the current administration himself
ice is so aggressive that they are using
loopholes to deport people like that
have no connection to their homeland and
like you know they were like brought
here as kids and you know International
Adoption a lot of money is exchanged and
right it's uh it's
it's really bad it's really sad dude
that's hella sad yeah what year was this
after their okay after 2000 I think is
when when they you bring so a baby from
a different country they're protected
but anyone before which is just a stupid
loophole yeah yeah so like you know
people from as your movie is about
though yeah well it's about a guy who is
dealing with that and he's uh you know
korean-american in and grew up in in the
south and yeah so like you know he's
just trying to get us left he's starting
to like really get his life together and
then bad stuff happens it and then he
has to deal with the possibility of
getting deported
okay well I mean just going back because
I didn't really for people who don't
know who you are
justin chon is an actor you've probably
seen him in stuff a bunch of things
you've been acting for I don't know how
long for like 18 years 19 18 years and I
mean he's you're not really acting as
much you're doing more like directing
and stuff but you were in like a ton of
show like yeah I remember you from the
Nickelodeon show it was that just Jordan
Jordan is just Jordan is just Jordan
that part now is that was like the theme
song in the beginning I mean I wasn't a
big fan of remember I agen dude on it I
feel like I feel like you know you know
your audience that's listening right now
like the age range they probably watch
oh they're actually older than really I
mean yeah cuz it's podcast so yeah
people don't really care yeah I
while you were in Twilight was in
Twilight all of them right yeah yeah but
I'm like a very small part of it I'm
just yeah you're a human dude so is Anna
Kendrick yeah we're in 21 21 and over
and over not 21 not the card movie yeah
oh yay 21 and over yeah wait miles miles
teller and Skylar Astin
here in a bunch of stuff man yeah I mean
like I said you were in things that I
just remember because you're there
wasn't many Asian people around and you
were just like Oh Asian do it on
Nickelodeon that's pretty cool
and then obviously Twilight right but I
know you know that was fun wasn't it
crazy all the people who would played
those like
like like eight like the human rolls
kind of blew up right well Anna Anna
Kendrick's huge yeah but yeah like when
you go back and watching you know like
Dan that is such a can't believe she
played that insignificant role yeah talk
about Twilight and how when you told me
about it ah how you thought oh my god
this film well I don't know if you want
to say what you want to say oh no I
think we could talk about it now I mean
I talk about it then because I think
people would really want to know but
first let me let me so let me explain
something is when I was gonna do
Twilight I was just getting off of like
like children's television like
Nickelodeon and doing a bunch of stuff
for Disney and stuff you know and I I
always wanted to be like an Asian Sean
Penn you know I wanted to be a serious
actor so I was planning to really stay
away from anything that's kind of like
you know I wanted to try to find serious
roles you do some indie films that are
and then my agent called me and said
there's this movie and it's and I think
you should go out for it's about it's
about a family of vampires and I hose
like hell no can you cuss on this yeah
you can guess I was just like [ __ ] no
man I don't want to go for that and he
was like well dude like you don't have a
job you should probably like there's not
a lot of options for you cuz you know at
that time you know it wasn't as open as
it is now yeah so a ginger yeah so like
the roles are limited so I was just like
okay well who's uh who's directing it
and she he was like Catherine Hardwicke
I was like oh and she did a movie called
thirteen and Lords of Dogtown that I was
loved resume yeah she she did like indie
films I really loved and then I was like
well who's a main star like it's in he
was like well this girl named Kristen
Stewart I was like oh because I had seen
a film called into the wild yeah and she
has a pardon that she's just so amazing
in it and I was like I would love to
work with her and then and uh and that's
why I auditioned and and I auditioned
like I don't know six seven times and
what I mean
because it was yeah because it was
during the writers strike yeah so they
couldn't rewrite stuff like so we had to
do a lot of improv
so you go in and and because they
couldn't write new stuff we had to go
and and improvise a lot of scenes with
the other sort of potential cast members
and then uh yeah I showed up I was like
okay well I'm really excited to work
with these people but the film itself I
don't give a [ __ ] you know like it's
like you know um and you know like the
books it's based off books and stuff but
you know I was really excited to work
with the people involved but like the
actual story I was like well you know
it's it's just an opportunity and right
and and but the other thing is it's I
don't think they wanted me oh really cuz
I was Asian
I think Catherine Erik your key right
yeah is that isn't that well I don't
know is that a asian character in the
book
no but they don't specify his ethnicity
just that he has black hair and like I
think like nasty pimply scan or
something I don't know but uh but um
Catherine I think came out recently
saying like she had a prob she had
problems casting minorities yeah but
yeah I don't think they really wanted me
because you know was Washington forks
Washington they didn't feel like but uh
there yeah so catherine fought for me
and that i am proud of you know anytime
I can get rolled it isn't meant for me I
was really proud of that so um but you
know and and the fact that I'm the only
Asian in that entire series is is pretty
cool yeah like it's like another fun
fact is like that for those people who
don't know you actually did YouTube I
did yeah I did because um because of you
guys
hmm he's you and Kevin you did it a lot
I mean they consistently you were
consistent for a little bit I did it for
like a like a maybe like half a year
yeah your intro is I love doing thanks
but um it's I think he would understand
how hard work it is how much right how
much hard work and I was like dude this
is like from not for me hard work hard
work your other it's a real career it's
real it's its own career and like I
can't do it part-time yeah I thought I
can maybe like just kind of do it like
when I have free time but it's not the
case like it has to be a full-time game
you know and I was just too busy like
acting and and doing other stuff and
just way bigger things no no it's not
that like I know like YouTube is even
bigger than like I think if you're on a
network television show uh-huh
no one knows who you are Yeah right like
I was just on a show for ABC
nobody has ever recognized me from that
like no one's ever said oh yeah you're
that guy for that ABC show but like
people recognize me from your YouTube
videos
yeah yeah well I think it depends on
like the size of what your project right
cuz you were in I mean like people
obviously don't you from Twilight
because the fan base was so big yeah
right once you talk about how you turn
down pitch perfect yeah go and this is
all interesting yeah this is all things
that I have never talked about I know
that's all yeah and I think it's so
interesting yeah because it's an inside
world too like a star's life yeah yeah
well it's not a start yeah I mean so
it's to a certain degree yeah but uh
yeah I had just finished shooting 21 and
over and skylar astin was in 21 and over
with me and we both got cast in pitch
perfect so I went straight over from
from Seattle to I think it was Baton
Rouge or Shreveport Louisiana so I went
from one hotel to another and I was like
man I just I wasn't um you know I
thought I wanted to do it and I showed
up and and you know and I was there
who's who's you know I love and and Nona
for a long time so like I I was really
stoked and then but then um you know we
uh got there and I was I saw the reality
of what it was what it was it's like a
musical mm-hmm
and you didn't want to do it and I was
just like what you sing to like what so
like so like yeah the audition was like
you had to sing a song and and whatever
and and you know I sent a tape in and
and I also do think that Skylar put in a
good word because he got cast as lead
he's like hey you need to cast this guy
so I showed up and then so weird then I
myself in like dance rehearsal for like
80 hours a day and then we and then we
were also doing like singing rehearsal
and like and I was just sitting there
like in and we're sitting in like a
circle we're all picking out parts and I
was just trying to do like a falsetto
and I was like dude this is not I feel
like a phony I just don't feel like I
belong here cuz Han because what you
didn't feel feel like your vocals are on
point with them or like why like yeah I
just I just didn't like it yeah and I
just felt like really kind of stupid
personal experience is like you know and
every day at the end of the day we would
kind of show the director the
choreography and stuff and you got to
get in it you gotta be like beginning
like doing the whole dance I gotta
commit because you guys someone's not
committed to me and and you know I think
I also talked about I get I I know I
could talk about this but like because
we've hashed it out personally is
there's an actor named Okarche and he's
uh he's in everything now he's he's
gonna be in Britney runs a marathon he's
he would paid Mindy Kaling's younger
brother in the Mindy project he's in
Mulan he's he's in like a film with Ryan
Reynolds right now he's a huge Indian
American actor okay and I didn't like
him and like we we got we were at it
like me and him were like and he was
like anyway like I don't wanna go ten
guys in pitch perfect yeah he's in pitch
perfect he plays the riding that guy and
me and him didn't get long yeah you know
I don't want to go too into detail but
like I hated him right and he I don't
think he liked me either and that was
another reason I was like dude and it
just like as a week went by I was like I
don't I want to get out I don't I don't
want to do this and also like 21 and
over was talking about doing a reshoot
in China because they got some Chinese
money so we had to shoot part of the
movie in China yeah and and then also
keV wanted me to do some stupid movie
with him
yeah and I was like which is probably
the dumbest thing I ever did is I gave
up pitch-perfect to go do Kevin G
YouTube movie that's that's friendship
though that's not very well that's
pretty loyal perfectness and you knew I
mean it was you had a big budget I mean
yeah I knew it was gonna be yeah and I
in its music and stuff and it's
entertaining I knew it was gonna be good
it's just at that time and sometimes in
life you have to do what's best for your
soul not for your bank account yeah damn
that's deep so yeah so I was just like
you know what I'd rather go chill in
Hawaii and and and I'm glad I did I mean
it changed my life you know like spent
that much time in Hawaii and and
Hawaii's like a second home to me so
like I'm glad I did that but like you
know um also you know I like I was like
so just partied out
I was drinking so much and all that
stuff and I was just like I was just
kind of done and and Hawaii I was like a
little bit relaxing and and then I had
to I went from like being in a hotel and
to sharing a bed with Kevin in like an
apartment in Hawaii KevJumba for people
who don't yeah
I was yummy were you shooting hang loose
mmm okay with Dante right yeah yeah I
love Dante Basco you know Rufio but yeah
you know since then you know like if I
could just indulge you guys in the
conflict between me Okarche we test it
for a a NBC show for a TV show we you go
what happens you have to go test for a
show like for like the the executives
and and so I made it to the final round
and then I was just waiting in the room
to go test and then the elevator opens
and it was a car SH and we hadn't seen
each other since pitch-perfect in the
elevator open and he looked at me he's
like ah [ __ ] and I was like I was like
what the [ __ ]
and I just like turn this like and then
and then we were just like you know you
have to test a few times yet to test
network in the studio and then by the
the same third day like a conscious I
can I talk to you I was like yeah cool
man and we went into like an empty room
while we're waiting to like going to
audition and he's like man and I will
give it to him like use the bigger man
he like apologized first and and we
pieced it out and
maybe you hate him so much like why did
you guys hate each other so I don't know
man I just like I mean we're both
different people ya know and I can't
like speak on his behalf because it's
you know I I know what's going on in his
life but like I was just I was also a
different person yeah and I you know I
just we just didn't get along
you know sometimes you know when you
meet somebody for the first time they
rub you the wrong way and you you just
yeah you just don't vibe with somebody I
feel like and here's the thing is
sometimes you don't vibe because
actually you're a lot more similar than
you'd like to admit mm-hmm you know and
you see I think you see parts of
yourself in somebody that you don't like
but you're actually like you're actually
like hating on yourself but then you
eats your insecurities that make you
kind of hone in on that and start to
like you know let it bother you but but
I don't know a car she's a sweetheart
he's a really amazing guy and and yeah
we're totally cool now and we've we've
hung out a bunch of time since then so
like you know I think sometimes that
kind of conflict helps you actually
become closer I don't know that's I mean
you want to talk about pitch perfect
this stuff is like Opie we're gonna clip
it and just send it you like these
different actors okay well I mean I did
want to because I think that's
interesting and yeah super it's an
inside look that a lot of people don't
get to see definitely yeah um but yeah I
mean now you're doing like I said you
were did acting for I don't know how
long I mean you're still acting but
really your claim to fame currently is
you're directing because you've been
directing films and writing them and
recently you've had two films make it
into Sundance back-to-back your last two
films both made it into Sundance and one
and one of them won an award
yeah yeah right that's huge I don't know
people know that but getting into
Sundance is like super prestigious and
it's it's you know named some other
movies that Frio station the drumming
one replies flash you know really tough
to get into Sundance and your last two
in a row with it you directly got in
there so right now you're kind of like a
I mean you're kind of like like Cott
right now in that world directing
inde sort of like anyway did you also
write those as well I really you you
wrote direct acted and acted in in the
first movie GU yeah and then I wasn't in
that my most recent film is purple
mm-hmm
so what's wrong with that when right now
miss purple so I went to Sundance with
that this January and it comes on
theatres September 6 in LA at the Newark
in Santa Monica and then and then it'll
expand in New York in two landmark
theaters and then and then um after that
it'll expand to most major cities you
know um I think it's gonna be through
Landmark Theaters but yeah you know it's
about a strange brother and sister who
grew up in like a gentrifying Koreatown
in Los Angeles and and their dad is is
close to passing away he's he's
terminally ill and and the daughter has
stuck around to care for him and they're
live in hospice nurse quits so she's
forced to have to contact her brother
who and begs him to help help him help
her take care of him because she has to
make money and work and pay for stuff
and what she does what she does for work
is she's a karaoke hostess and you know
if you're from LA or you're Korean you
might be familiar with like the told me
culture it's like you know you go to
Kurt you know karaoke room and girls
come in they're like kind of like
hostesses and they come and hang out
with guides for money so it kind of
explores that world in a way but but
it's really about a brother and sisters
relationship I have a younger sister and
our our relationship has been pretty
complicated over the years and you know
I'm dealing with our parents and and
kind of divvying up responsibilities and
I think the the brother-sister
relationship specifically is pretty
particular because it's like one's a guy
and what's a girl and and I haven't seen
that really sort of explored in film you
know there's only a few films that that
talk about I mean like you know you can
count on
the savages skeleton twins but that's
about it
you know I mean I feel like age of 17
kind of touched on it because like you
know the you know the girl is dealing
with all this stuff and then you find
out the brother you know there was all
these stuff that he was holding him but
like it wasn't like a main sort of thing
this is like the main meal is like their
relationship but it's also empower
empowering story like she she needs to I
think she lives in a very lonely
solitude existence of a world and part
of her journey is to understand that
there's a world outside of hers and
that's why there was a Chicano whole
Chicano storyline that weaves through
the story and and things that kind of
bring her out of her comfort zone and by
the end you know I think she starts to
realize and learn how maybe she can live
a healthier life but when this is come
out this comes out September 16 Ola in
November 6 in LA and then New York you
said New York the next weekend and then
other it'll be in San Francisco Seattle
like it'll be in most major cities ok
yeah it's called miss purple yeah and I
was curious as to a your writing process
and how you get into that because the
whole brother-sister relationship like
you're obviously drawing from that
experience and uh maybe like with Kuk
and stuff if you want to talk about that
because uh it shows like different
ingress intricacies I think it was
during the the riots right yeah it's
takes place during that 90 to LA riots
yeah and then your next one is with kind
of like deportation and I'm not sure if
you have any actual experience with it
but maybe like you can kind of take us
through this story of all three yeah
well you know I think I have a there's a
reason or purpose for the art that I
make I mean I feel like most people on
the internet know me to be an idiot but
I think it is it you know as a filmmaker
i i i my purpose really solely is to
there's a few thing
actually the first and foremost is I am
trying to bring empathy to our community
as Asian Americans so like if somebody
that's outside of our community watches
a film they maybe understand how we
operator or can can empathize for us a
little bit more so that's a first
criteria second criteria is you know we
have crazy rich Asians black panther and
and all these sort of uh you know miss
Bala these films that are strictly you
know cast and include people of that
ethnicity which is great but I'm also
interested in my art exploring how we
coexist and interconnect and all that
stuff so those are two things that that
that drive me in terms of what I want to
say is for the writing process you know
everything I do has to be it needs to be
coming from a very personal place the
one I'm about to do I read a few news
articles about people who were getting
deported and just really I just every
time I read a story like that I would
start crying like crazy because it's
really sad and it's like some of these
people have to leave their families
behind and you know me being like a new
dad and having a one and a half year old
like I couldn't even imagine that and
also like just for somebody like that to
be abandoned by the parents and given up
for adoption and then a lot of these
people go through the foster care system
because even their adopted parents
sometimes don't want them and then you
know fast forward like two decades
finding out that the us the place you
could call home doesn't want you and is
kicking you out I think that's a very
it's like it's like getting pretty much
kicked in the ass yeah your whole life
yeah it's pretty my heart goes out to
them so like you know giving a platform
to a community that doesn't have a voice
I think is a worthwhile endeavor so you
know that those are some reasons why I
make the art that I do and and and you
know I want to be like sort of the
counter-programming we have like the
Justin Lin's and the James wands and and
you know John choose and and they're
doing amazing working they're really
great in that studio of like big-time
studio system I think I'm really great
at drama and you know and I in comedy
and stuff but like much more intimate in
real kind of stories so I'm like the
counter-programming to that and I think
I I just make a nice balance I think
it's really interesting that you um I
mean a lot of people say that right a
lot of artists will say I'm all about
like the art and not anything else not
like the fame not I just want to make
art yeah but you were presented with
some huge opportunities to work with
like hundred like really really finance
films like big studios you you were I
mean you were offered basically you
could have went that route yeah you
could have went the route of B being the
next director of a Marvel film or
something but instead you chose I mean
that doesn't appeal to you well money
doesn't drive me that's the biggest
thing is is uh I've seen what money like
in Fame and all that I've seen people
have it right and we all know that that
doesn't make you happy I mean it's not
it can't you can be happy with money and
fame if you're sort of internal
compasses right but if it's just that's
the only thing you're looking for you're
gonna find yourself very very empty
so money doesn't drive me it's I think
money is a great sort of indicator if
you're doing great work there's a money
I think follows Talent right so I don't
focus on that
I don't focus on the biggest opportunity
or the biggest career move I fee I focus
on what feels right to me and and
artistically and and spiritually and you
know um what makes sense for my family I
think if you do one of those huge movies
you won't see your family for like three
years you're like constantly working and
and you're having to answer someone
that's the other thing that I really
really value is autonomy like I really
value being the master of my own life
mm-hmm and not having to answer to like
people telling me what I have to do or
how I need to do it so
with art so I value that so like you
know those kind of opportunities I'm
very flattered but as of right now I
think there's a there's a lot of work to
be done that I feel is important that I
need to do first I'm not saying I'll
never do it you know like yeah be really
fun to do like a big million yeah a
hundred million dollar movie but you
know my my babies like really young and
I don't miss out babies like really my
babies like little a baby hahaha
my baby's a baby and I never get that
time back with her yeah so you know I
work from home like I do like my editor
Reynolds who's also from Hawaii Reynolds
Barney and uh his name is actual
Reynolds Barney roasting here I know I
love him though but like he's over at my
house we're editing in uh in my office
and like I do that purpose and I and I
stay home as much as I can to be with my
baby but if I was doing studio film
I really doubt they're gonna let me edit
from my home and of course yeah so
they're gonna make me edit from the Edit
Bay they're gonna come in and out to
look at the progress and everything and
but uh you know I do that so I can
astronaut like for now at least you know
when when my kid doesn't want me around
then maybe yeah that's maybe when I'll
go do like a bigger film and just bounce
and and do that whole thing but right
now I think like there are some stories
that I think can change people's opinion
you know in a different way and I tell
stories about people who aren't the
point zero one percent you know like my
stories aren't really like fantastical
they're like a realistic look at our
lives you know like it's a lot of my
films are about the working-class you
know they're not about like super rich
people they're they're just about like
normal people like us you know and and I
also think that's valuable yeah well
with that being said we'll come back and
we'll talk about another film that we
had in mind yeah yeah but before we get
there we have to take a quick shishi
break and we are out
[Music]
and we're back and we're back back gtfo
gtfo that's um so what were we talking
about our new upcoming yes oh you were
talking about how you like do more real
things mm-hmm and never me and Justin
caught with ideas because it's usually
stemming from me it's really dumb like
really
we have really dumb eyes but I like that
too yeah it's a it's it's a nice break
right yeah you've got to have your meal
but you also have to have your dessert
yeah I think that's something that I
really like about you is that you don't
try to like you know get stuck in like
one cubicle like you have a lot of
different facets to in one cube yeah
yeah you have many different phases to
your keep allotted little cubes yeah
you're really you're cute
cube he yep
but know that I think that's what's
really cool about you is that you know
there's so many different sides to you
that there are some people who are gonna
be like I don't think Justin's are
dumbass like he's really serious you
know I really like dose types of people
thanks.thanks yeah I don't like you but
it's okay no thanks yeah I mean I think
about I take it all back man no yeah
thanks man no III think like I think man
I just I just want to live a full life
mm-hmm you know and I think it's life is
there's too many things experience them
to just be one thing you know and I feel
like that's what you guys are doing like
with this podcast and right you guys try
not new stuff and like you could just be
doing the same old but like yeah there's
too much cool stuff to do that to just
be like the serious guy or the funny guy
or that's why I love when I see you know
comedians do like dramas and stuff yeah
I love like when Jim Carrey did The
Truman Show or Eternal Sunshine you know
and I also like when when
really serious guys that do like stupid
comedies like when Matt Damon did that
one film with Greg Kinnear I think it's
stuck on you where they play Siamese
like stuff like that you know I love
when they do stuff like that but I think
that um I think there's so many ways we
can like express ourselves why limited
to just yeah the same old boring
[ __ ] so let's talk about how you you
guys are gonna explore yourself in this
new dumb idea that you have this dumb
idea um I mean it's been a long time
like still saying we're gonna do it but
we just never do it but we are trying to
write a BG a movie for people who I
don't know if you don't know what that
is it's just our fake kpop band that we
had started off as one video a joke
and it just ended like really well it
did a huge international reach yeah it
it I remember the first one because it's
literally singing dongs idea which means
I have to take a [ __ ] right yeah yeah
I died initially is just me and David
right we just I recorded it's just my
voice really and then we're like okay
well we need a band and I was like okay
what Asians do I know that can be a part
is obviously Justin's one right because
I know he can sing too if we I mean we
didn't you didn't really need to sing
but and then I got feel because I know
he likes to dance and then Jun I kind of
just met but I knew he was into kpop
yeah it was just super helpful to have
him he's like the identity of kpop yes
he's literate like beep that's his life
he literally is doing still like on his
by himself he's doing like carried on
with BJ by himself he's literally like
the last video was about him leaving the
group and start doing it because he's
the star yeah and and he's it's
happening yeah it's real life you know
actually I've gone to some general
meetings with like some studio people
yeah and they bring it up they break up
beat you here yeah they go like so hey
what is this dude yeah some like a few
particular we're like hey so Thomas it's
like what is this BGA thing and I starts
are laughing why did you watch that
because these are like old white men you
know and I'm like wow
why though it cuz they do they have kids
is that I don't know oh I didn't ask I
was just typing justin chon yeah but
then they love it they're just like no
it's like so fun and they love it but um
but I think we also like that's that's
something that you did was sort of like
with the whole YouTube you bridge use
help bridge the gap because it started
off such a little thing and you you and
some other people like really blew it up
into something that's like more now it's
mainstream like YouTube is not like it's
not a niche thing it's more actually
more big than we were talking about that
like TV shows or whatever it is so the
point of where networks are adapting to
like kind of the YouTube formula
ya know it's all about streaming and
videos on demand yeah so I feel like
it's just as legitimate you know I
remember I will actually be on Twilight
explaining to them I was like yeah I'm
doing this YouTube thing and they're
like why would you do that why would you
waste your time yeah and I was like no
no no you don't understand like this can
be you know reach a lot of people and
it's it's the new thing that's that I
feel it's gonna be huge and and I end
you know watching how you guys were
operating I don't think they were seeing
that yet and everybody was catching up
but now it's it's it's legitimate more
legitimate than anything you know but um
I don't mind I don't mind doing some VGA
[ __ ] yeah
yeah well we were working on another so
we have another song that still needs to
be we wrote it out David and I and and
it needs to be recorded still I do you
guys have auditions
um rappers like you need a Filipino
rapper and it would have to fit this
storyline oh you don't need anybody who
was it that keeps asking me like there's
it was funny cuz like like I said it was
so casual the way I was like HS and you
want to do this like kpop video yeah it
wasn't gonna be a big deal similar like
filling them I was just like but then
like people like man why like why don't
you pick me like other like Asian
friends I have yeah like jealous it like
like even like Wes I think wanted to do
it at some point I don't know if you
actually want to he sit like here's just
like why did you ya ask me
yeah or like anyways would've been good
yeah he looks very like he has that look
too yeah you know where sis like slick
undercover sort of like sexy yeah you
know like I could see how like
mysterious yet mysterious west from
waffle production yeah yeah what he's
the one that the girls like right from
wrong he's like the mysterious quiet one
but like he has style and like and
you're kind of like Oh style but he also
seems like a guy that would take care of
his girlfriend yeah really nice dude
yeah I like but that is also like has
like them brooding like like male sort
of like energy but then also sensitive
yeah and then we have Phil shotsfired
combo well I mean speaking if there's
any BGA fans watching they're gonna be
shocked cuz I mean if they only know you
from BGA yeah like you said they
probably think you're an idiot and I'm
sure they probably think you're an asset
like you hate like you really do hate
Jun yeah and we've got to keep that
going my god you really does hate you
[ __ ] June yeah that down but that in the
calculation one of the Twitter questions
is from tuned do you remember me tell
him tell him he should go watch a
picture telling him right now oh hey
June you should watch Pixar's Coco I
don't remember you who are like what is
what's his name username June curry on
so June like why the [ __ ] do you have
curry in your name like what is that
about
I don't know why he wants to be like
Korean that's why Oh curry on [ __ ] Beach
is a real thing guys we're not playing
characters it's written so that they're
all very exaggerated versions of
ourselves David David's question to you
is are you secretly in love with June
curry on a man sexuality it should be
fluid
so I I'm not I wouldn't be ashamed of
Robin this is going you know that space
between the ball that's why you want to
pull his hair but I know I think I come
from a place he comes from uh straight
yeah I think I sexual frustration yeah
funny the hall that natural like that
relation like the first script you
weren't really I'm trying to remember
how it started you weren't we weren't
mean - you weren't mean to June yeah I
think it's a sieve all just happened
like on Sarah
yeah like it just became an ongoing you
know what I think it was so I think it's
because he was like the the slave driver
we had to learn that stupid dance the
first the first video and I we like
actually had to rehearse yeah yeah and
I'm like I'm like learning from this
this guy I don't even know like I met
him through VGA and I'm like why are you
telling me what to do man and I think
that it's like that secret frustration
evolved from that mmm-hmm and that was
like oh but he's kind of cute but why
tell me what to do I felt bad for June a
lot because we are all so bad and like
not really taking the dance part
seriously and he was so serious about it
yeah yeah yeah I mean I told him from
the start like um cuz he choreographed
the first one and then he had a friend
helping us with the second one and I was
like I saw the second I was like dude
this is too hard man like but I gotta
say the dancing and the first one's way
better mm-hmm
it was actually easier yeah it was
easier but look did you notice how much
we cut out of the dancing on yeah yeah
but the dance our dancing was better in
the first one mm-hmm
yeah second one was barely even dancing
boobies were so lazy were like nah man
is they just cut a lot and a lot of it
was just us like messing around like
your that shot that was all like yeah
that was the other thing Jun directed
the second one yeah and he was really he
was really making me frustrated
also his directing style man because he
just takes too long with everything I'm
like hurry
part of the story lines like June comes
back he's like I've heard your podcast
like I've heard your I heard the punk
and you know I super deep dude right my
name is June curry on and I have her I
mean I I don't actually I don't want
your video to get D monetize I was I'm
gonna stop yes too late but no no no but
you know he's very talented
yes very talented he you know he did a
great job with that music it looked
really great and he's a he's a good
dancer is a good is amazing violinist
yeah his his his skills on the strings
is like uncanny just a really amazing on
that violin but that you know you know I
violin the bow is made of horse horse
tail really so he's really good like
he's connected to animals and yeah and
connected to the earth yeah so uh he's
really good with the wood in his neck
yeah we gotta get Jun on the podcast but
then bring Justin back and not and not
tell June yeah Justin will just be there
yeah do this no no no you know you know
what needs to happen is you need to set
him up like make him to get real
comfortable and then start having them
kind of like talk a little bit of [ __ ]
yeah and then I should be like I show up
in the door with like headphones on and
be like I've been listening to you I
don't think is so nice I don't think he
would hit talk to you even if like you'd
be like oh yeah yeah Justin sometimes
said some things to me yeah I think I
don't think Jun would would do that yeah
yeah it's funny how that just it just
became a thing it became it became a
thing and it's people's favourite
relationship it's either you love the
the love-hate relationship between you
and Jun or you just love David for being
David yeah David's funny too in it yeah
we we hope to continue it on in a in
movie form at some point but what I want
to talk about right now is Paco stand-up
career know
yeah I want to get I want to talk I want
to talk about
Paco's stand-up comedy career we for the
viewers at home Paco and Ryan were in LA
further apart there they're doing the
podcast in LA and the plans yeah and we
went out for some drinks and then we
came back and we forced Paco to do a
stand-up stand-up act for us and we all
like critiqued him let's preface this
like Paco never let me I would say like
yeah oh he's like I'm gonna do an open
mic and like he would never tell me
where it was yeah I was like dude you
need critics that like you need people
to tell you like when it's not good and
also for sure yeah also we need to
preface that we know nothing about
stand-up comedy or we are like our
opinions are valid in any way we just
wanted to like give honest feedback of
how like it's just normal people yeah
like if we like it or not that's all
like and another thing that I would put
in is that you guys come from a
standpoint of like storytelling no like
you guys do really well at storytelling
so in that aspect because my jokes
aren't just like oh these are one-liners
you know where it does come from a place
of oh there's some reality to this so
that's why I was like you know I do feel
comfortable but also because I really do
look up to you yeah but we were just we
just wanted to we just wanted to get a
little taste
yeah of the Paco Jim and after I did my
set they destroyed me for like a good 30
minutes but I that's why I respect you
more now because you you really took in
stride you didn't let it like you know
be personal and and you know that's hard
to do like it's hard to take criticism
you know we were too but we're just
speaking from like a non professional
stamp or just how we took it yeah yeah
but uh but uh you know I think that
right now Paco should do it well I mean
I think I think how this could be
relative to a lot of people is that yeah
I mean I think people need to loop if
you're gonna try and do something you
have to like commit to it and then be
open to the criticism I think yeah I
think it's really tough to do no but
there's a reason why and you understand
why I didn't want you guys like I'm okay
with performing at open mics and like
bars coffee shop some people I have no
idea who they are you know because that
like in the end when I do stand-up
comedy it's gonna be for people like
that
starting off it's gonna be for people
who have no idea or Who I am with you
guys it's a lot more personal because of
the relationship that we have like the
audience is seen Justin will [ __ ] on me
all day and I'm cool with it and it's
fun and then Ryan will do that too and
I'm cool with it too but when it comes
like oh this is something that you know
I'm trying to work on this graph and
stand up enough and then to have like to
think oh are they just gonna [ __ ] on
that too
you know yeah yeah I see what you mean I
see um so that's why I was very much so
like Auto III would only want to invite
you and only have you there when I get
to a point like I'm comfortable I work
on this hundreds of times you know I
made this set good enough for I'm
confident that I can get you to laugh
yeah yeah well you feel proud yeah yeah
but in the meantime tonight I think you
have to you know when people come over
to Ryan's house I think you know just
the people know people are coming over
to my house I think you know I would say
I respect that that you took criticism
very well yeah and I think that's that's
important for a lot of people it's it's
tough man in any zone
especially if it's your job yeah you
know if you just work and something you
take pride in something you love and
someone comes and criticizes you I mean
it comes from a place of us trying to
help right yeah yeah but even then
that's tough man but that's a path to
progress that's a path to mastery ax is
you have to you know be open to not
being awesome you know and at least I
can speak for myself is like I know like
I'm like a novice and just starting out
as a director and writer all that stuff
and I need to I need to always be open
and get wrekt all the time the more
times I get wrecked the better I'll get
because if I learn from it
what's some negative criticism you've
got in for like [ __ ] like [ __ ]
specifically you know someone review
said like you know it was kind of messy
and but if you but they also talked
about like you know you could tell there
was a raw artists passion behind it
that that it kind of makes up for it but
but I have to admit yeah there's parts
that are pretty rough and the way I shot
it was super
low budget and and scrappy so like I
don't have time or or you know the
resources to make it super polished but
I look at it now and and taking that
sort of note from the reviews and and
you know I generally don't read the
reviews it's more like you know asked
like peers you know when especially when
I'm when I'm editing and I'm getting to
stage where it's getting kind of close
to locking the the film so I could send
it off to like sound and color and all
that stuff
I'll have we'll work on it and then at
night I'll always have at least one
screening and I'll I now invite the the
scariest people that I that I admire or
whatever and I'll have them watching and
give me notes and sometimes it's really
I'm like you know and and a lot of times
are right and and always it always it's
always a note behind the note so they
might say like this section just doesn't
it's kind of just like bad it sucks and
then it's like I have to really go back
and then be like okay instead of being
like [ __ ] you you don't know what you're
talking about just really think about it
and get the note behind the note and
maybe it's he's saying it just felt slow
or or maybe the editing wasn't crisp
enough and it wasn't engaging enough and
or like maybe he's saying it was bad
because he wasn't clear on the the the
protagonist sort of how they were
feeling in the moment and that's
something I have to decipher afterward
but like for me to be like he doesn't
know what he thought like that part's
not bad like it's sometimes people their
notes aren't you know because they're
talking in the moment they haven't had
time to process for a long time what
they're saying so that's like an example
you know and that has you know when I'm
in the editing phase I'm constantly and
then you know and then sometimes like
you also but here's the other thing Paco
is like sometimes you also have to stick
to your guns sometimes you go no that's
just my style or that's how I express
myself you have to know when something
is you know very sort of integral to who
you are and in some stuff that's just
more of a practical technical thing that
you need to improve upon you know so
like people
were ragging on sort of some of my music
choices in that saying it was to all
over the place but I like that because
I'm not one thing and they're like well
there's too many tonal shifts in my
films and I'm like frankly I don't give
a [ __ ] about that specific thing that
they're talking about and that's
something that I I want to hold on to
but yeah I don't know what kind of
wrapping it up cuz time is uh but I just
wanted to throw in one more Twitter
question because you are actually the
first father guest oh yeah we haven't
had any guests that has ever thought
about even had kids
except for your mom yes yeah but so
because you are kind of seen it again as
a crazy person you know you're doing so
many things um how is it has having a
kid like changed your view on a lot of
things or even life yeah it has that's
the the simple answer but um I think
having a kid can go two ways you can
just live your life and kind of be
irresponsible or if forces you be really
you know we're talking my self-aware and
introspective it forces you to examine
who you are as a human because now you
have this child that's coming to the
world and and you have to you know you
have to determine who you're gonna be
and who the person that they're gonna
call dad and so it's made me have to
take a second look at the type of art
that I'm making right so if you notice
the art that I'm making is I mean
speaking of which like how are you gonna
explain to her BG hey yeah but you know
that's you know it's it's fun though you
know yeah it's fun but like in terms of
you know feature films they all have a
purpose and and I can stand confidently
and it would on two feet in front of her
and say yeah I did that for this reason
I was trying to give these people a
voice and then sometimes it's okay to be
like I really truly believe that
sometimes the answer can be like we
needed money mm-hmm we everybody needs
money to survive so I needed to take
that job because we our family needed
the money
but um it really but at the same time
I've become kinder I've become more
compassionate I become more sympathetic
and empathetic towards people I'm not
quick to judge I try not to be I try not
to be as judgmental because all that
sort of and also I try not to speak
really negatively about other people
like it's all changed when you had a
baby yeah yeah yeah well it's not
overnight but CLE is is true then that
does change you once you have a kid yeah
but it's your own personal decision if
you want to change or not um but you
know I don't want to bring em hmm
you know I think you've seen me change
over the years
yeah we're talking last night and I
think before I was a much more
aggressive and you know I look at myself
now
and I think I I'm not as aggressive in
the sense that I somebody's like I'm not
used before I'd be like oh yeah screw
that guy you know if that guy hey Doug I
don't do that as much because I don't
want to bring that energy home and I
think that's what the baby does and in
terms of work some people go in the
direction of like I need to make more
money to give my kid what they need and
then there's the other option which is
like no no all that stuff doesn't matter
I think what's more important is helping
molding her to be somebody that you
think will be a great member of society
what's more important is well yeah you
can either try and make more money too
to try to give your kids what you think
they need and then but that my
philosophy is to spend more time with
them and try to you know give them a
strong foundation you can't make your
kid become anything they're gonna be who
they're gonna be and I only my job is to
kind of give them the tools or what I
think is is productive and constructive
for them to go out in the world and it's
on them but but I think that's what
having a kid does it really makes you
think about even who you are and you be
just become you have to become more
selfless because a kid
they can't care for themselves you have
to care for them so in that way I think
I've become it's less I become less
egotistical you know I think being a
creative and an actor is that one of the
most narcissistic endeavors the one can
take on because you're just thinking
constantly about yourself and how you
come across and and having a kid really
takes you outside of that and it's less
about like your own sort of hang-ups and
ego which i think is a beautiful thing
so you guys should have kids yeah so I
guess when I go pick one up or we can do
one together
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay well I mean that's that's a good
way to end off of us so Paco and I are
gonna go get kids yeah again just to
wrap up Justin your film is purple comes
out when September 6 at the Newark in
Santa Monica it'll expand to other
theaters in Los Angeles and in
California San Francisco Irvine and and
then but then the next weekend after
September 6 the following weekend was at
the September 12th it'll be in New York
it to landmark theaters in the city and
and it'll expand out to most major
cities after that miss purple is purple
Guk is still on Netflix Netflix but uh
you know Netflix is pretty messed up
they do something I'm not gonna go there
they do something that's called a pan
and scan we shot that film anamorphic
which is like yeah what they do is a pan
scan they just they pan and scan it and
they scan it and they cut off the ends
and they really and they decide when to
pan so like for example there's that
shot with the two brothers arguing and
she's in the middle it's cut off at the
ends and they decide when to pan to each
so I didn't know that watch it on watch
it on Netflix but if you want to see the
true aspect ratio buy it on iTunes
yeah support home support or pirate it
whatever yes that's
yeah that thank you again Justin for
being here you can follow us at off the
pill podcast on instagram at off the
pill on twitter leave us your questions
and stuff like that there where else can
they find you though my instant I
usually mostly use Instagram but you
barely use it yeah follow me on
Instagram yeah but no no I I use it in
between projects but what I'm really
focused on like filming I know because I
didn't concentrate but you could just
follow with me at justin chon on
instagram and and you know if you want
to slide into my DMS now take I'll take
a look
you're probably because they follow you
on Instagram it'll be a good way to get
a reminder like oh this is coming out
yeah yeah yeah and I do I do like post
stuff about the process you know like
I'll post stuff when I'm in in the Edit
or on set so if you're interested in
filmmaking at all like yeah that's a
good follow yeah behind the scenes stuff
also if you want to see cute pictures of
my kid yeah
Papa babies of a babies all right well
how we normally end it we just breathe
into the mic and three two one