ever since she saved arendelle it's been
Elsa this Elsa that I was forgotten
everybody loved her more and why not I
mean she's the queen Who am I
she possesses ice powers what do I have
she has let it go I have a stupid song
about building a snowman I've always
been one step behind but no more no
longer will I live in her shadow
oh hey Elsa you're kind of blocking my
light do you think you could okay I'll
just move then no longer will I be given
the cold shoulder so after you're done
playing winter mall do you think I could
use the computer to do my ah okay you
know what I don't need it
no longer will I be the second choice
for kids to dress up as on Halloween
canteen no longer well Elsa reign as
Queen
oh no where are you going to see the
fire wizard what are you crazy
kinda I love crazy for things in
arendelle are about to change like Green
Princess Anna has left orange ale and
what well I mean she's missing and owed
Charlie won't you just let it go what
let her go there it is wait how do you
know he's not gonna just kill us the
moment we step in there cuz I have
something you once but my queen it seems
she plans to start a war a war in
arendelle well that'll surely be the
first time in forever my dear I know
that accent
mushrooms oh please my queen
this is serious it seems she has gone to
the fire wishing to become stronger in
every way well good for her she needed
it I mean she was quite the fixer-upper
look could you just tell us what you
want us to do in case she returns oh
don't worry little Charlie if Ana indeed
returns with the intent to start a war
with arendelle I will personally show
her a whole new world isn't that from
Aladdin that's not even your song I what
but what I meant was if she returns I
will welcome her to the circle of life I
mean I think I think that's Lion King I
mean she will drown under the sea nope
still not your song I will
hakuna her Tatas you know what I got it
I got it this time it's honorable turns
I will welcome her with love for love is
an open door
so you want us to leave the doors open
even though she's trying to start a war
with us I feel like that's a bad plan
you Charlie just go get the troops
[Applause]
fire
inside
this is
Oh Elsa you ready to build that snowman
yet
[Applause]
Katara charming
no you have to yell my name chairman
it's Olaf
[Applause]
stop
[Music]
some people are worth melting for