[Music]
I don't want to play the ball
you're the coach I just don't care
[Applause]
[Music]
why'd you go in myself
really really really
[Music]
yeah
so sir why don't you burn my toes
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
darkness deep inside my soul speaks to
my mind
[Music]
right my poetry
won't know what is me
[Music]
I know you want the best for me I'm
sorry girl I was being so mean
[Music]
I'm sorry to
but there is one last day
both of you I love you get the
[Music]
pink lies thank you so much for watching
I'm supposed to tell you guys like which
one to click on and what they say but
they already have text and tell you so I
don't know what I'm here for
well there's so many options what are
you trying to tell me that's from how to
be more