I was sick and tired of having terrible
days I've tried other dating websites
before and could never find a match
honestly I was about to give up never in
a million years that I think I'd ever
find him well with give up and settle
calm back in all and today hands down
the best dates I've ever had they sent
me more matches than I could ever need
they showed me the way and it's finally
found his spirit give up in SOCOM we
believe there's someone in the world
that is perfect for you and we're here
to help you get over the fact that
you're never gonna meet that person
we hate each other so much I can't even
look at him cuz I hate his face
we're not even gay and we both are with
our highly advanced matchmaking system
known as the personality attitude
placement enrollment research by
algorithmic groupings also known as
popular bog we will find you a near
perfect match within second I searched
gamer and girl and got a 50% match that
I did after a most charming Oh those
into this shy and quiet type and that's
exactly what I got type in how smart
successful good-looking a man other
dating site and still never found first
john davison settle calm perfect match
ITEC in black girls with my preference
but I'm not gonna lie I'm not the best
speller so I wasn't surprised when I
showed up to my first date and saw
nothing but a black grill I'm not picky
I test for the hottest mastery in fun
our love will continue to burn brighter
than it nothing wrong black man she's
still smoking people used to tell me
there should be violins playing for me
at all times because I was such a sad
person that's why I went on to give up
and settle and ask for someone cheerful
optimistic violin free almost a perfect
match I got a chair full of domestic
violence for me clothes II know we all
know there's a lot of fish in the sea
but there's also a lot of people on land
you don't have to resort to fish yet
just sign up to give up and sell calm
and find the settling soul mate you
never even knew you wanted we promise
you you will not regret it unless you do
it's completely free money back
guarantee so what have you got to lose
sign up give it a try you might get a
virus give up and SOCOM we'll see you
there
see for yourself and find your perfect
match today it's fast it's fun it's not
a real sight give up and settle calm
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see last week's
video click the one on the left if you
want to see bloopers and behind the
scenes click the one on the right and if
you want to go to give up instead o comm
click the one on the bottom and find
your perfect match today
[Music]