hey guys so just to let you guys know
this video is gonna be a little weird
and it's gonna feel kind of rushed and
yeah I don't have a lot of time to
explain it so I'm just gonna get
straight to the point sean is moving
away normally this would be the part
where I would cut to like some kind of
sad skit or do some kind of joke or
something like that but like I said we
have no time he's moving away in two
days so just for some backstory sounds
not fighting with anybody in the group
or anything he's literally just moving
to California to be with his girlfriend
and I don't know if you guys know her
now but sean has an engineering degree
and that's one of his other passions and
he's gonna pursue that but we never
really knew when exactly we didn't have
like an exact day so we thought that
when you told us you know when he's
gonna be moving out we could have enough
time to plan this surprise you know
party or surprise performance for him
kinda gives us two days to come you know
come up with an idea and then pull it
all off he's gonna be tough I'm like I
was saying it's feeling kind of rushed
right now so I can't spend much more
time here the guys actually just came
over so we can start planning that
secretly planning this video because
Sean still packing so we it kind of
gives us two days to come up with an
idea and then pull it all off
it's gonna be tough Sean this video is
for you we got to just get to it right
now we're doing the planning stages for
Sean's we don't know what it is gonna be
just to reiterate I just got back from
Hawaii right now as I was getting back
just texted me and said he's actually
gonna be moving this week versus at the
end of the month we did Northern
California I won't say where it
specifically Sacramento so we can get
started let's figure out just make a
list of what Sean likes first thing that
comes to mind when I say shop fujiyoshi
he likes Hawaiian food a lot of spam
okay okay famous bowls do the cookies
and cream
I know get back to the house Sean he
likes putting stuff together yes Sean he
does like she's always on a Rubik's Cube
yeah I love puzzles yeah no fishy you
like swinging it's a necklace thing that
you got oh wait what one thing that you
really like some Crocs
when as Sean ever wore prop that's why
but hey you know I mean I don't I don't
know just do that on your own time enemy
you know the best just like Hawaiian
music yeah yeah reggae you should make
him a ho lion song okay papi how you
decided to it okay like a music yeah
might be about this yeah that's possible
we might be able to edit it together
dude we got two days it's easier than
doing a live all dressed up like we're
gonna be Hawaiian singers and rappers I
think he would laugh I think we should I
think everybody should know it's like a
it's a message to Sean I mean it must be
hard we'll just be like background
sounds and like ad-libs and stuff yeah
how we're gonna get him here without him
knowing you has to know something's up
leaving that day do you have like a
super old screen I have a bunch well I
should make a really bad one so he's
like what the hell and then he's like
really good does not want to film it
nobody comes it'll be more you know take
me can get really bad so really happy
okay so we'll just send them this is
horrible script um to be there on Friday
will arrive a few hours early to set up
the whole surprise me video and all that
stuff yeah okay operation on three three
I'm looking for beats on like royalty
free music
we're not musicians I just typed in
Hawaiian and reggae Sean's favorite
music
I honestly it could we could use any of
these but I think it should be something
more happy my type in Hawaiian anything
comes up there's like so stereotypical
like listening I can't sing to this or
it is like on SpongeBob
not like Hawaiian cops that brought us
what you gonna do bro whoa whoa doing
Maria na na hai in the studio right now
and as you can see
check out my studio you got the little
laptop setup right here got the mic and
then mount proof right here some sound
proofing machine the sound proofing
honestly don't know how to use most of
this stuff I just know how to plug it in
and then hit record so usually I make
all the songs with myself I do all the
voices and they kind of just like lips
but since this is a special thing for
Sean we're going to do is have
everybody's voice on it I'll probably do
most of it but like I definitely want to
have everyone in it
so hope you guys are ready I am singing
can't make me Derek you're a senior bro
I can tell I'm ready
stop this one here goes up to avoid
moving away movies in me meets this
culture of operation it is it really is
or is it appreciation culture
appreciation over from Hawaii yeah I
grew up minnows this is part of what the
culture I grew up please culture
appreciation not appropriation
appreciation we appreciate cuz we grew
up with the culture through several to
do nine one six
we got an itch
first I was perfect
Shawn Shawn Hado wait Shawn every fire
that we love you
we're gonna miss you making me his notes
I'd never done my brothers I think I can
work with this day to day - Lian er stop
my bad hopefully
all right let's wrap on the music video
Thank You ap I don't have Sean to film
yeah I remember him
[Music]
it is game time Sean's coming in about
two and a half maybe less than that yeah
we have a full video to edit room to set
up all the cameras are set oh yeah
food to setup we have guests to arrive
not enough time I'm scared if anyone
else leaves no one else to get into
video Sean this ends with you almost
finished rehearsing well pretty much
done rehearsing we did one run through
[Applause]
and it's you I'm 58 so people won't look
out we're good Tina looking out
literally it could be any second and
ready its go ahead of Ziggler still
editing I knew it we had time sorry on
my way I forgot to pack a couple more
things be there ace ASAP I guess you
have time to edit courage I had a
feeling about one for sure
[Music]
oh I see and flip the switch
over the past two old days the rest of
us here at our HPC have been observing
studies compiling data on a favorite
things from hobbies to show to smooth
all in order to create the ultimate most
epic most amazing celebration we've gone
through countless gift ideas from all
new fishing equipment to a trip to
Disneyland to just straight-up giving
you a suitcase full of cash but nothing
seemed right until it finally hit us why
don't we give Shawn the best gift he's
never asked for a poorly made snob
Ian Rush lions laughs reggae music video
record by all of his best friends and
also Paco and so we did welcome charge
the beginning of the ultimate
probably somewhat disappointed
celebration
[Music]
[Applause]
now we barely posted let me do this I
just might some kinda game but the rest
of us in Irish PC would like to see ya
we love you we gonna miss you and if
you're feeling lonely you can take this
is to show our appreciation
[Applause]
[Music]
and give your final salutations what's
up Shawn so I am pretty bummed that
you're moving but I'm excited to see
what's in store for your future one
thing that I'm gonna miss about you is
your ability to solve puzzles and
problems and stuff like that and I
remember specifically you actually
enjoyed the process of solving the
puzzle so what we decided to gift for
you was a Rubik's Cube buzz but we know
it's really easy for you to solve this
this is not an ordinary rubik's cube
plus all we did was we colored when the
yellow squares white so you'll
technically never be able to complete it
you'll just have the fun of trying to
solve it for the rest of your life and
if you get bored of this one we got you
this super easy one that you'll be able
to figure it out now good luck have fun
Shawn what's up bro you're leaving it's
gonna be different not having you around
you're like basically my right-hand man
when it comes to filming editing you
know getting stuff done with with Ryan
and the videos and all that so it's
gonna be a little different me and you
were always kind of like you know
sidekicks I guess we would even dress
the same sometimes don't shoot you know
we would like resting clothes they like
the same church for some reason we're
always wearing hats for some reason
backwards hats especially so we decided
to get you a hat actually make you a hat
because it's not just ordinary hat as
you can see it's backwards but it's
always backwards yeah buddy
anyway I'm gonna miss you bro I'm gonna
miss having my right-hand man
but you know I'm sure we'll keep in
touch and we have one out there bro I'm
gonna miss you peace hey shine I just
wanted to say thank you so much for
being literally the first friend I made
and an excellent roommate for when I
first moved to Las Vegas anyway as you
know and as you all know you're the
sweatiest member of rhpc but I've never
seen this much before and I know you and
Ryan talk about this all the time on how
wish there was some sort of shirt that
me armpits were lighter than everything
else so that when you get sweaty it'll
all be the same color
well now you have one so enjoy we're
gonna miss you good luck in all you do
and keep in touch Shawn I can't believe
you're leaving dude it's so crazy we
have so many memories together you've
always looked out for me and I
appreciated that you know we're excited
for you and we're trying to think as a
group you know what does someone need
when they're moving furniture I know you
love building stuff I know you have an
engineering background so since you're
one of my close friends I decided to
break all of it for you that way you
could have fun putting it back together
there might be some missing screws maybe
some splinters and pointed edges sound
like a ghetto IKEA but I think you'll
have fun and that's what matters
enjoy hey what a song it's your favorite
arts PC member Paco I know you're
leaving and I'm happy for you man cuz
not only do you get to start a new life
but I get more active parts so yeah no
seriously I'm very happy that you know
you're able to make this move I mean it
takes a lot to be able to move past a
comfortable stage and move on to another
part of your life and I notice you know
you always have that necklace on and you
also have like one word on there so I
thought you know in this new state to
your life you need a new necklace and
bigger is better so I got you a big
necklace yeah
you can probably put the word like
hard-working or popco you know cuz I'm
someone who inspires you a lot and I
know that you always want to remember me
because I'm the best and also the guys
thought this would be kind of wack but I
know you're gonna like it good
yeah I got you some Crocs too ready
definitely engineer appropriate attire
you're gonna look fresh building
building all right peace dude like this
dire urge to start this video by saying
hey guys but that's not the point
what up John I'm just gonna start this
off by saying that I feel very weird
obviously I feel sad that you're leaving
but the same time I'm really happy for
you but it is weird I'm not gonna lie
it's weird that you're not here right
now like at this shoot that we're
shooting today you know how it is when
we're missing someone from shoots it
feels weird but I guess we'll just have
to get used to that but anyway I'm just
gonna start us off by saying that I am
very thankful for everything that you've
done you know not just for rhpc not just
like filming and stuff like that
obviously I'm thankful for that stuff
but just as for me personally as a
friend I'm extremely thankful we've
known each other since I was five and
you were four I think it's rare to have
friends that last this long I think in
our late 20s both of us damn world but
it's pretty rare that we're still able
to maintain this friendship and for me
personally growing up especially like
her on middle school high school time
your friendship meant so much to we're
making YouTube videos we're making those
lip sync videos we were dressing up as
girls and you know publicly putting this
stuff out there YouTube back then was
not what it is now this is like oh 506
when you know we were the weird kids
people didn't look at they looked at us
weird this wasn't a normal thing and you
were right there with me and I really
appreciate that I had somebody by my
side obviously we had Tim and our other
friends as well but we were a small
tight-knit group and you're always there
by my side sharing the weird burden but
anyway I'm not trying to make this all
overly dramatic or emotion or anything
so I'm just gonna go on to your final
gift as you can see it's right here are
the things I feel like we've always had
in common is that we've always watched
anime final gift is themed anime without
further ado a beautiful piece of artwork
that I person
the art on the bring a little closer see
whole CSU as you can see your finally if
is something I worked really hard on I
don't know if you're right
you recognize this or not but this is
when we did the anime shoot so that's
why I was talking about anime and how
you know personally I think this
something you can hang up on your wall
and when you move any fine you already
know this is not the real thing
Oh reveal what the real one right now
take a look anyway all jokes aside again
I just want to say I appreciate
everything you've done for not just me
but the entire crew and oh there is one
last thing I know I said I didn't want
to make this you know all cheesy and
dramatic but there is one thing that
I've always been wanting to ask you and
you know it's it's kind of awkward for
me to ask you like this I just know I'm
just gonna add let's just go back to the
song I didn't wanna make this song
emotional there's one last thing I need
to know before you
the one night was live with the right
side
I just need to know can you see
[Applause]
this is to show our shuttle speciation
when Tirpitz and give your final
salutations like we said before
another real
they poeple with
that's not a joke take my keys take him
with you oh yeah and by the way if you
haven't caught on yet Shawn we're not
actually filming that really horrible
script I sent to you that was just to
get you here instead what we're gonna do
is actually throw you a little party so
if you take a look behind you it's done
[Applause]
[Music]
hey guys I don't really know what to say
to be on everything is kind of a shock
to me I came in thinking that we're just
doing a regular video but man it got me
it's all hitting me right now and I'll
be moving to California with my
girlfriend and yeah this might be it
god I'm not used to being on this side
of the camera you know usually it's Ryan
on this side but the rhpc
thank you guys for everything you guys
are my family always have been ever
since I moved here I'm gonna miss you
guys thank you for all of the awesome
experiences all the laughs and stress
with all the videos that we've been
through I only wish the best things for
you guys I'll be supporting you all the
way getting emotional yeah I didn't
think I was gonna get this emotional do
this but Ryan thank you for bringing me
back in and for letting me help you for
all these years even back in high school
just like how you said that you're my
closest friend and changed my life in a
very positive way back in high school
and I really appreciate it I probably
wouldn't be the person that I am today
or be able to experience everything that
I have experienced if it wasn't for you
so thank you from the bottom of my heart
you're definitely my longest and closest
friend still
keep doing what you do and I believe in
you guys and again to all the lamps out
there thank you guys so much for all of
the support and for following me and for
supporting everything that I do I hope
that you guys will continue to support
rgbc and me as well and our future
endeavors and yeah I guess that's it
that being said yes all I can give is uh
these guys