let me guess he broke up with you for no
reason again yeah I just don't
understand why he would dump me like I
not ready for this seriously
well I mean I guess this is the first
time you ever got dumped twice in one
day I hate guys why can't guys be more
like girls wait what why can't guys be
more like girls are you kidding me girls
are the one who well first off kpop
stars secondly girls are the ones that
should be more like guys you actually
think well the WNBA yeah but you
actually think that relationships would
be better if girls were more like guys
yeah you're completely wrong well then I
guess we both know what needs to be done
all war that has been going on for ages
a war so brutal that even the gods
themselves have just get to it
guys versus girls
you shall not pass
[Music]
okay first off guys are shallow oh right
this again all guys care about is boobs
ass and tits boobs and tits are the same
thing but now hotter girl looks you know
there's way more to us than our exterior
yeah I admit guys can be a little
shallow sometime told ya but don't
pretend like girls aren't just as
shallow
oh please there's no way okay then tell
me white girls go crazy over guys with
nice bodies you don't do that can you
really look me in the eye and tell me
that the reason why so many girls love
Taylor Lautner is because of his acting
uh yeah the reason why so many girls
love Taylor Lautner okay fine so we like
hot bodies big deal but looks aren't as
big a big deal to girls as they are to
guys yeah but you girls are the reason
for that how was this our fault you
pretend like you guys don't care about
looks yet what do you do every single
morning you put on makeup sometimes
throughout the entire day you get your
hair done or did is some might say and
you care about it so much and you don't
even let us guys crack a window in the
car
not to mention shopping what about it
girls love to go shopping because
they're into buying materialistic things
that make them look good whether it's a
dress or shoes or nail pain it's polish
that - oh yeah and don't girl see that
the one thing a guy should never do is
call the girl fat obviously but you can
call guys fat and they usually don't
care but if you call a girl fat they get
extremely hurt you know why because
girls care that much more about their
physical appearance therefore proving
that girls are more shallow than guys
[Music]
all right here's one go for it in a
relationship the girl usually cares way
more than the guy since when okay well
let's start small remember when I got my
haircut earlier this week what why are
you moving oh here sit here fix it with
a comb not your hands and what does your
hair look so weird today anyway well at
least I noticed it was different right
[Music]
[Applause]
and you know it was one example and like
I said shallow mad because I didn't
notice your haircut it's not about the
haircuts the fact that you didn't care
enough to notice a difference just like
that one time you came over
hey what up G my dog just died it was a
hit and run oh so sorry
see I was thoughtful I cared just to
finish the flashback hey yeah do you
have any more hot pockets in the freezer
no yeah you're right that so insensitive
I should just go check myself mighty
fans you didn't have any left so it was
kinda even you just stopped using those
examples we're talking about
relationships not us ah okay fine well
when it comes to relationships break up
show a lot about how much people care
it's true and once again girls care more
that is press pause Buress you mean
preposterous you know what I meant
oh yeah look there's no easy way to say
this but I don't think it's working out
huh what a huge relief alright then just
disregard that last text
[Music]
you can't use that that never happened
it's just an example it happens to girls
all the time
text breakup I've never even heard of
that this one's made up well let's just
see you takes a break-up harder the guy
or the girl maybe I should call back I
need to call her back I'll have all my
hot pockets there and after some time
passes let's see who really cared about
the relationship hello
étoile going to the club tonight you
want to come oh man my girl just broke
up oh sorry to hear that man
so bar that sounds good look maybe I
didn't notice a haircut or two and maybe
I wasn't as caring as I should have been
when I accidentally ran over your dog
wait wait but it's only because we get
along so well you like a homie I've just
always treated you like one of the guys
I guess sometimes I forget that you're a
girl too
gee thanks look I get it guys have been
asking to you in the past but think of
all the guys who choose to date you know
not all guys are like that and
hypothetically speaking if we were to
ever for whatever reason be in a real
relationship together I wouldn't I could
never do something like that to someone
I care about so much because that would
just be prosperous look gee I know
you've been looking everywhere and I
don't understand why you can't seem to
find a guy they can see how amazingly
rare you are but maybe
maybe you've just been looking in the
wrong place yeah sure
some guys do you care
oh yeah you just admitted it guys care
for that does make you look better
I guess when it comes to relationships
guys have the event
[Music]
yeah that was really weird yeah you're
right it's not do that you know I think
we should just stick to being friends
what a relief
disregard that last night so thank you
guys so much for watching if you want to
see the behind the scenes and bloopers
click the one on the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right if you want to see Bob Marley
and by Bob Marley and me my dog Marley
bobbing to music click the one on the
bottom hey wait
yeah that was a misleading