and then I think out that one we would
we would eat first what guys it's a joke
nah David's cannibals leave it in the
conscience don't you ever wonder like
why don't we eat dogs and cats oh we got
a clapper claps clapping claps and
welcome back to another episode of off
the pill podcast Oh normally Park was
here he plays this it's fine today we
have we have will with okay I'm new here
yeah will I and was back and we have
David who's who's also come back he was
on a second episode I believe and then I
got kicked out yeah he got he got soul
David David in me up after that have a
so he's like dude people hate me that's
what she said people did hate me cuz I
was so passionate about Apple you well
there was that and they said and I
talked over you yeah I apologize
well I mean I don't think you have to
apologize at the time the funny thing is
like even for me like there's a lot of
things I didn't notice I did until we
started doing this yeah yeah it's true
because no when we normally converse
it's like we are pretty much talking
like over each other all the time but
you don't really notice it until you
watch it on film being on yeah being in
front of a camera it's very different
than in person mm-hmm right yeah but but
the thing is like I think a lot of
people don't realize like they're like
so irritated that you kept staying on
that and seeing not like you know maybe
you had your point of view and it seemed
like you weren't you you were trying to
prove your point I was trying to prove
my point and we just kept clashing yeah
and we talking over each other and I was
also low-key trolling just a little bit
you were trolling in the beginning
especially but I think you know well now
you know that people don't like it you
won't like the troll I'm sorry guys I'm
a naturally I'm gonna comment but you
left I wrote I forgot what I wrote like
I apologize I won't do it again or
something like that
dude you should do it I should just what
I should do it again no
you will probably me they're like damn
why is David back on the podcast we
don't know that David's actually
incredibly funny but he's what do you
call that it's just dry like dry humor I
have dry humor people think I'm an
[ __ ]
but it's swear look it's so funny like
how do you explain that like most people
like when you first meet David it's like
you almost have to do a disclaimer I
feel like cuz you're so blunt and like
I'm honest I like to be honest very
honest yeah um but I mean it in a I'm
honest in a nice I try to be nice yeah
you got mean em I mean I don't think you
know but you do say things out most
people be like ooh he really said that
mean it's true but it's things that
people are thinking I just say it
because I feel like if it's better no
he's like yeah better to say than to
just hide it and pretend that you're not
really thinking it that's true
I guess that's I mean with sometimes I
do assume as well that people are
thinking something and I say it and then
I may be wrong what like I didn't we'd
roll one again but I mean I just felt
like I should have brought that up
because thank you last time there was so
much negativity and I think people
misunderstood you mm-hmm and you were
hotted it I mean you you were like
actually kind of down from that for a
little bit I was a little like you know
cuz I have it so I don't know if your
your audience knows I I actually also
make youtube videos I feel like some
people don't even know that they
probably end up just I mean they know
they're like well David makes a lot of
the songs he makes all the BGA songs he
Huichol a black cuz David actually
started before me making music and then
you also dislike MIT little like blogs
and blogs yeah those youtuber youtuber
I'm one of the earliest actually I
talked about on the junior podcast how
he saw you first and you kind of
inspired him hmm
but you're like you're like grandfather
YouTube you're like a year before me old
guy yeah old man almost I got some white
hairs here as you can see but
traditionally because your brand is so
clean and your musics like really nice
and it's like weird love like love music
and hates what it is thanks guys people
have always been from what I seen like
you've I've gotten way more hate than
you've ever gotten throughout your
career
I think until it's because you have
2,000 those had I've ever gotten on
YouTube but fun huh but yeah this cuz
you had a larger I think like the bigger
your audience gets its its but I think
for the most part you'd get a lot of
great comments because you put so much
oh yeah I I want to bring this up
because I've been watching all the
podcasts very closely you you know the
the one that Arden was on the last
episode she mentioned how much you work
to two episodes ago or two episodes yeah
yeah that is absolutely true
I mean for some of the listeners are you
bringing that up I mean no because I
think like the success that you've had
on YouTube it's because of your work
ethic you know just for the listeners I
know I come me I come out to Ryan's
house probably once every like once a
month once a month then once every two
months and you know he wakes up he
starts writing and then we eat some
lunch and then he goes back to writing
he does that almost every day if he's
not shooting you know I I as a friend
want him to have a good life as well so
I try to you know I'll be like hey look
let's go out to let's get some food
outside of your home instead of post
mating it you're just adding on to what
Arden said about me I am I have to slit
a loser that just doesn't leave a loser
but yes it's true Ryan does not leave
his home Wow
it's hard but you know what your success
is deserved well-deserved because you do
put so much time and energy to create
content for your fans I think it's it's
a it's that's why that's why you know
you make great content well thanks well
said I think you you tried to shift the
focus away from your feelings as we were
talking about how you felt when you got
all that hate for the first time and it
also because it also once brings up
something me and will we're talking
about earlier yeah how did that I mean I
only really the first time you got that
much hate I like fell board yelling at
you
yeah comments I was triggered I was
definitely triggered triggered or what
you said because there's a difference
hmm sure thank you felt misunderstood so
he was a little mad triggers called
misunderstood okay yeah I felt that peep
like you know the Internet's very quick
to judging you know I consider myself a
pretty nice person in general and when a
nice person is getting hate you just
feel like it's unfair I feel like why
why me yeah yeah I do
did I kick a dog but the interesting
thing is that you're so used to and
analytical about being on YouTube and
understanding how you know even if it's
a bunch of people it's still a minority
and people would dislike me you're I was
surprised that most times you would just
kind of shrug that off because you
understand like hates gonna happen yeah
but I've never seen it happen to you
that much it's because I've been gone
from YouTube for so long and I forgot
what it feels like to get hate to get
hate let alone that much hate that much
hate yeah yeah do you see it from their
perspective yeah I agree with a lot of
those colors you know so when you say
why me it's like okay yeah I mean I'll
admit my faults and things that I've
done wrong in the past like you know
honestly I didn't even notice it me
neither watched it back and I was like
oh he is kind of doing that after I saw
the comments I was like oh I didn't even
really notice it because that's just how
we talk yeah me and David we don't like
argue but we go we believe in something
we're not so hard we're not gonna just
agree with you to make you feel good
yeah I think that's dishonest I agree I
think we're both like that yeah
very blunt yeah and I disagree with
everything you just said right now okay
there's the troll David coming up and
all that brings me to what we what we
were talking about almost like well we
just saw the Kevin Hart thing on Joe
Rogan he just did this thing you want to
bring that up because I thought that was
super interesting what we're not yeah I
think I just saw today was a on the Joe
Rogan podcast he had Kevin Hart and
Kevin Hart had a super insightful
explanation and like point of view from
to talk about I don't wanna say it's
like being affected by the comments
right you know if he has videos online
or whatever and he was basically just
saying
I mean he was kind of bagging on people
that you know comment mean comments
essentially yeah in saying you know how
do you have so little time or so much
time so excuse me so much time to sit
there and like formulate thoughts and
then sit there and type something
negative it what's the purpose what's
the purpose like and especially for
someone like Kevin Hart who never stops
working and he's always doing something
you know his point of view was like
really really smart and I really felt it
honestly yeah I mean I mean you want to
talk about like what he was saying cuz I
think it applies to like you know what
David was saying too but the thing is he
gets I think he gets it on such a such a
bigger level than any of us right it's
like you have to like figure it out at
some point or you're gonna go crazy like
cuz if you had that every day you would
have to figure out how to deal with that
or else you'd probably like be depressed
and kill yourself or you wouldn't make
videos altogether like you would be so
sad and mad all the time you would ruin
your life you would have to figure out
how to deal with that I mean yeah that's
basically what I took from it was just
kind of looking at their perspective of
like okay it's probably someone who
maybe it's a little negative or not
doesn't just has a ton of time and
they're not really working hard on
something for on their own side you know
that's kind of what I took from it and
to I mean especially for someone like
you to you're a very busy person to it's
like you know I mean yes you got stuff
to do positive things I focus on and
yeah I just felt like he had such a
smart like articulate 'iv is that the
word heal it responds yeah like his
thought about it in such a I don't know
such a smart way I mean I did something
similar to we've kind of I mean I've not
really addressed it in I mean I've said
it in vlogs before but it's not I didn't
make a whole video about it but I mean
that the reason behind someone leaving
something so negative is because I mean
the reason why anyone does anything is
for themselves you know like you always
do it because you think it's gonna be
make you better not a better person just
make you feel better or it's it's you
that's the reason why everyone does
everything you want to feel so yourself
you can yeah yeah so it's even if you
make someone mad it'll make you laugh or
maybe they're doing it because they want
they feel so bad about themselves that
want other people to feel that pain yeah
that's what I think because I've felt
that before I felt like I wanted to
leave like a negative comment somewhere
just because I'm if I was like that
person I know that I would be getting
these comments and no one's leaving it
you know like I know if like I said that
I know I would get these responses
negative responses and it makes me want
to be like man I should get no one
saying the negative thing that I know
that would be said if I said it right
you know just because they're not
popular whatever it is so I mean there
there's it there I understand it not
that I would do it and I don't because
obviously I I think mature past that but
I can see if I was a kid that didn't
really do YouTube and I was like upset
with my life and I mean it doesn't mean
it I'm anonymous nobody knows nobody's
gonna know right I would write some ID
probably because I would feel bad for
I'll be a troll there's power behind you
know having the Internet in front of you
right yeah being unseen and like you
said I mean what I wonder from you guys
perspective is should people be allowed
to have but like write bad comments and
be trolls yeah what do you mean yes yeah
freedom of speech yeah I think there's
nothing I mean I don't honestly think
you people need to understand I think
you know what the difference is is I
grew up playing games and I know you did
- yeah and it's so filthy like it's like
the worst things you'll ever hear people
who say to you like way worse than some
of the click some comments you read that
you become almost like for me it's like
well that's ridiculous is a joke yeah
does even hurt me it's so bad that it's
a joke the ones that really do hurt is
when it's not necessarily hurt but like
when it's a critique and it's actually
well thought out and it's like man
that's kind of true there's truth that's
where it kind of hurts and I guess
that's when you get triggered more
because it's well thought they like
analyze who you are as a person they got
deep inside and then they're like oh
wait whoa but in a way I don't think
that's bad either I think that's good
yeah sometimes I would agree like I like
I mean I don't like it but nobody likes
it but I like critiques constructive
calm yeah like I like that's how I
learned like I disagree with Joe Rogan
he always says don't read the comments
he tells all his guests like why you
guys read the comic don't read tweets
don't read the comments I disagree with
that I think I've learned throughout all
the years and and tried to improve
because of the comments earning like it
not taking everything at face value yeah
is his perspective is like hey if you're
gonna get offended by the comments it's
gonna change your comedy and I
understand that but you just have to
know what to listen to him what not to
get what he's coming where he's coming
from
but he always instructs his guests like
and you know people get affected by that
to not read the comments and I don't
really I don't know I don't agree with
that completely
so I saw recently that there was a and I
need to talk about this because we just
flew on it there was a thing about
Southwest and how was it there well they
got their shares got downgraded or
something like that because of the
recent um was that crash to Ethiopian
Airlines yeah the new so the Boeing jet
is apparently is the second crash of
that same type of jet in the same in
like fought like less than half a year I
know
and the reason I'm thinking about it is
because remember that we just will and I
just took a flight to go actually to
record with David and we had the crazy I
was one of the craziest flights I've
ever been on where I felt like it fell
like we were on a roller coaster you
know when you'd that feeling when you
yeah Mike right yeah and it was like if
they like that for a good like sometimes
at like five second at a time it's like
we're calling like the seat wasn't like
we weren't touching the seat it felt
like obviously we were right for like 15
minutes I would say yeah long constant
yeah honson like up and down but there
was like some moments where that drop
feeling it didn't seem like we were
dropping but it you had that feeling of
like being in the air for like five
seconds at a time I was like this is the
craziest thing this is not normal where
people are sitting out in the plane was
some people some kids screaming and like
there's some people screaming but it was
a they did warn us and it was super
windy so I'm gonna attribute it to that
you know and ideologically I'm thinking
I don't normally get bothered by that
stuff yeah me neither yeah we know the
statistics too like I know that it's
like actually don't know the statistics
but I know it's like million one in a
midlife ten million or something like
that the chance that you're gonna crash
right right it's super slim but you
think about it every time you fly I'm
sure right I think about it not every
time I think about every time I fly I
mean I don't I don't really think even
for like a slight second like yeah yeah
slight second I'll be like I could down
this flight but whatever I've had a I've
had a flight where now is like
I wouldn't even like depressed I was
just like really not having a good day I
was like I don't even care if it crashes
that's really I really had that damn I
was having a very bad day I think it was
like girl problems you know what girls
but I had that feeling I remember
thinking and the project won't even care
if it crashes so tough like that
the bumpy thing like yeah I said it was
super windy I think there is something
specific to like our region though that
because I think flying in and out of
like Vegas is pretty notoriously bad
right and it's something to do with like
the temperature different Hills yeah and
we like go over like the hills into
California or wherever it's never been
that bad no that was crazy I was bad and
and then I read this article and I was
like okay this is the second one in six
and it's the same kind of jet right a
Boeing was a Boeing seven was it I don't
know you know you know what it is that
those jets it's a very common one it's a
second crash in five or six months or
something like that and what they're
seeing is they're stopping production on
those jets right now and they're saying
it because those crashes were attributed
to all investigators suspect faulty data
feeding into the aircraft's automated
flight says that's crazy
yeah so like who knows like I mean I
don't know if I can be talking about
this guy wants protects protects but I
saw this article yeah and I mean would
you fly south I mean like that's what I
fly I'm already flying on it I know this
way you know what it's not even about
the airline because all airlines have
Boeing's
Boeing airplanes what's that specific
one I guess yeah no but the the that
specific airplane is sold to Southwest
yeah yeah you know like all these photos
each airline have the same pretty much
exactly the same I don't know I think
they have the exact same planes but like
for example the Boeing 737 most airlines
use the 737 mm yeah I think that's what
it was I think that's the that's the
plane they're talking about but like if
they're having that I mean I never
really like even if there are is a plane
crashes okay well okay ten million more
flights and it won't happen you know
another 10 million or whatever that
number is but the fact that has happened
and they're acknowledging there's an
actual problem I feel this is the first
time I actually feel like Dan this is
risky
yeah and it's such a short period of
time five or six months too
plane crash just an outlier yeah just
makes me feel uneasy I know all the
people who are about to have a flight
coming up sorry yeah let's say you have
a bike coming up behind Jesus look good
luck - thanks guys hmm but on a brighter
note I don't know that's my wine Ted so
I wanted to crash one time and all these
other crashes r.i.p to other people
there's killed like the whole I think
everyone on board like over 100
something people wow it's really sad and
scary nightmare seriously yeah
that's your worst nice you know I when
I'm on the plane there are times are
nice you know I've been on like probably
hundreds of planes in there are a lot of
moments where I'm just thinking what
what do I do if it crashes into the
ocean I've thought - that's a forest
what if I'm the only one alive I don't
know why I think like I'm the only one
alive because I guess if you're dead you
wouldn't be thinking about it but like
yeah you wouldn't even be in that
situation right you wouldn't matter
right but if you're alive then it
doesn't matter because you could still
survive tried and III definitely think
about that I get really deep like all
the smokes in in the cargo so I got to
like crawl out of the plane and then
what if I like scraped my knee on a seat
bleeding I'm in the forest you guys do
this like this is this is true I'm not
saying this for because it's funny
whenever I'm like waiting for my flight
and people are like lining up and you
see who's on your flight you guys look
around I look around yeah and I'm like
and I think like if we get started like
if we're like on loss yeah you know I
want that on my tonight yeah I'm like
see this guy I know he looks just where
I think about that oh you do everyone
does that and then I think oh that one
we would we would eat first what you go
in that far I'm uh I think you're making
a joke man
I know everyone's gonna think I'm
seriously like a couple no see I didn't
even know you were joking
that's joking okay well I'm joking good
guys it's a joke
nah David's cannibals leaving in the
college it's I feel like you should
strive to be that guy here for now
everyone's gonna write David David's a
cannibal in the comments but you know
why I just told them - why is that gonna
hurt you
is that gonna hurt your feelings well
it's better
saying that I'm okay David's a
cannonball that better get a cannon
cannonball cannibal how about a can of
balls hey I like that one the best
you know what I accept that one more
than cannibalism because cannibalism is
is very you think just I mean like if
you were in that situation it's not
is it wrong to eat someone if you're I
mean if you're surviving like it's kind
of illegal
I would assume I in some states don't
know the laws on it but I would assume
is like I mean if someone had already
died right I would assume it's probably
illegal yeah I would assume so as well
I would hope so yeah please don't eat me
but I give you were if you were say you
were surviving on an island and they're
like how did you survive in like
honestly this guy passed away and we
hate him way to jail for that you know
what it's I don't think it's illegal
because I remember no I read an article
I think I was on Vice where a guy had to
get his foot amputated and he did a
tasting for his friends this is a real
thing this is real like yeah she like I
think he cooked he probably cooked it on
like the stove and this is disgusting
tapas is disgusting by he going but like
he it's on Vice you could look it up
chopped it off and he did a tasting for
his friends and I think he made like he
saw them skewers yeah yeah of course
oh I think they had to sign something
and people ate it his own foot his foot
well it was your own property right he
ate his own foot and I said it's not
illegal and his friends ate his foot
it's not illegal well he had them sign
something maybe that's the legal
document maybe yeah alright so man okay
well now we know okay you're we're sorry
David you can be accountable if you want
you know what Ryan if you had Danah
balls if you hadn't of like a little
tasting event I probably would try a
little piece of your you try my foot as
a friend I would do it why would I'm
doing you a favor
you're not eating my foot like would you
will would you eat his foot take a taste
no I wouldn't maybe smell it you know
what would I eat it I'd probably smell
it first you know what you know it's
funny though like I saw that this this
meme it was kind of like where do you
draw the line it's like a picture of
like a dog a cat a cow and he was like a
vegan thing like well yeah you shouldn't
be eating any animals and like where do
you why do we draw the line at like cats
and dogs and domesticated animals
basically like domesticated animal is
yes and then yeah they would live in a
house and you know with human beings you
right so like dogs and cats and like I
forget what what else is there like a
lizard lizard fish parakeet no parrot
fish there on the safe side specific
birds other side of the line there's
cats and dogs hamsters yeah and then
well it made me wonder yeah I mean me
wonder like I get we have pets right but
like don't you ever wonder like why
don't we eat dogs and cats and like I
mean like is there there's there actual
reason why that happened over time like
and then why do we eat cows like do you
know I mean that's gonna be like a good
sound bite right there why don't want
eat dogs and cats exactly I didn't want
to say that but yeah you know I think
it's more racist stupid racist unlike
how much time throughout like history
we've spent with them and so over time
you know through the domestication of
dogs and stuff yeah since we've spent so
much time with them they've left kind of
the realm of our food if that sounds you
know if that's okay to say into the
realm of helping us I think you know
companion companions I always thought it
was because they show love like dogs get
have like loving like they don't attack
us or cows love do they though dude cows
are freaking cute
they like jump in the air and they
wiggle and they'll cuddle with you do
you have a cow no B never seen like
those videos of like them like being
super cute I lived by a pasture and they
were just smelly and I would feed them
like tea leaves and stuff and I would
keep my distance because they're like
drooling and slimy and there's like
thousands of flies on them I think I
mean I don't want to sound too I don't
know I would assume most animals can
show compassion in one way or at least
we can interpret it in compassion and
then also right they probably learned
that over time I'm sure right like
yeah I think definitely domesticated
animals have Early's dogs specifically
have learned and what to do to kind of
make us evil and evolve that way I think
so yeah so a dog who wags its tail
that's been bred more than a dog that
doesn't and so that's what has
essentially became like oh they're happy
what I mean is like at what point in
time did they say oh these guys are you
know let's keep this one as a companion
this one's to this wolf that's kind of
like a dog is not good like this is not
a good animal too we can still eat that
wolf
that's exactly won't kill this dog why
we have the dogs just because there was
someone that made a decision saying yeah
this dog didn't bite me but maybe it's
because I thought did maybe it's because
dogs they tried it eating them and they
didn't taste good yes I was gonna say
that that's probably that's probably a
big part of it too but there are places
in the world where people still do eat
canine like yes so then my next question
is Asia would you guys eat I mean you
would clearly try dog and cat I don't I
would try I would say what your women
before I would try what other cat you
really is I don't catch that yeah I
don't really believe you there I'm just
like would try I would try it I would
try because I'm just a very curious
person and look if if in the past if a
hundred years ago people you know
humankind survived because they were
eating dogs and cats or whatever animal
for that matter if that was something
that kept them nourished and gave him
energy to to live life and to procreate
then you know what I got a respect that
and I mean if an alien came down here
and said well you guys eat these large
disgusting animals why do you eat a pig
that eats its own poop like why are you
eating the these dirty dirty animals you
know an alien could come down and say
that and we wouldn't have a good answer
for it I mean we could say it tastes
good but I mean I've never tried dog or
cat so I can't say if it tastes good if
we try and it's really good you know it
could be a meow do you think you'd be
able to try it um I think if I was in a
dire situation I would but I wouldn't
want to just for the fact of saying that
if you know people know that I ate a dog
yeah and I have dogs yeah and I think
that three of us we love dogs I mean I'm
a huge dog lover I like dogs more than
people sometimes and like but I would
try it out of respect to those who have
it's like if it's a part of their
culture or whatever I would just try it
but I wouldn't feel good about it
because I love dogs I think they're one
of the best you know things that the
world has to offer
human beings I don't think I could as
much as I kind of want to side on with
what you're saying is like you're
starving well that's completely
different I think I think I had like
that like that the options obviously if
we're a trip or whatever and it was to
not disrespect someone or something I'd
have to I don't know I'd have to
respectfully decline in the most
respectable way that's okay it would
yeah yeah I think that's anything that's
kind of I think most people wouldn't say
that but it's different too because some
people think I'm sure there's people
places in the world where some people
think how do you eat cows or how do you
eat this you know and there it's on the
same side they have either like a
religious reason or more some really a
reason like of morality right and so I
don't know
Who am I to say that they're strong and
is that culture you know you know
actually though when I hear about like
like and see videos of like when those
videos trying to make you a vegan yeah
yeah yeah like the I think I I agree
with a lot of their points sure but I
think I'm too selfish to give up
something I love that much that's a
super honest thing to say I'd know I
like I agree I'm like this is messed up
what they're doing to these animals but
like because I'm not seeing it every day
I think that's why like it makes me feel
bad right but then I don't change and I
think that's selfish but like that's
also part of my upbringing like I wasn't
taught this
had I been taught this from when I was a
little kid yeah I think it would be
different I think I would have grew up
differently I don't know I don't know
how you guys feel about that but I feel
like that's like I agree actually with a
lot of what vegans I know you don't
necessarily think the same way but I
agree with a lot of like thought what do
you call those big those far that I
don't know III think it's okay to eat
meat
right I don't think it's okay to do what
they do to get that me but I know that
it's necessary to keep humans alive yes
and no I would I mean if you look at you
think don't you think it is necessary in
terms of like the food there's already
people starving and if you were to get
rid of that yeah I think it's more so at
least the way I look at it is just the
way that it's there I think there is a
morally sound way to like yes yeah yeah
agreed and there are tons it comes to
people to do it yeah but yeah once you
start getting at this mass scale a lot
of those things that I value they the
importance of them goes down and so I
mean when I comes in like me my own
personal opinion on it I don't really
buy like those you know the the wrapped
meats in the store because I really want
to have at least some sense of like okay
I know where this steak is coming from
alright know like what the conditions
are you know and I think that you know
you have a choice and you're absolutely
you're exercising the choice and I think
the markets if enough people make the
same decision that as you do they say I
don't want this like mass-produced
whatever meat I want this meat that was
you know where the animals were treated
better right I think if more if a lot of
people request that the market will
adjust to it you know before people
didn't care about organic stuff now they
do because people are requesting it and
also it's in terms of like the right way
of treating animals you know to turn
them into food I think any way you do it
I mean there are better ways and then
you know yeah it's not but it's always
yes it's always gonna be brutal at the
end of the day because you're killing an
animal sure you look at the animal
kingdom you know a tiger you know
attacks a deer it's gruesome it's it is
oh no and in that's just the circle of
life and you know we need to eat yeah
and but the difference is though that
the deer has an opportunity to get away
right yeah the deer isn't isn't you're
not putting the deer in a cage and then
sending a tiger into the K
sure so I mean not that the deer will
get away I'm just saying like it's a
little different because their whole
life I think that's what people are
that's the inhumane part about it it's
like like if they didn't have brains or
thought or feelings or anything I think
it'd be fine for people yeah it was just
a slab of meat that grows bigger with no
consciousness but I think a lot of you
know the hardcore vegans you know PETA
they don't even want you to even kill
any animal no yeah I know I know but I
don't I don't necessarily agree with
that but I do agree with it
I mean slaughterhouses and stuff like
that I mean you see that they're not
going through pain and production yeah
so there's better ways you could
probably do that and that's not as
natural but I also understand I've seen
the argument on the other side like what
people would starve yeah I don't know if
that's true but I mean I could pay I
understand yeah it could be
we don't really so the funny thing is
that people get so upset and triggered
over things like this right and that's
why I'm trying to be a little careful
but in all reality and I thought about
this before all these like issues we
have with if you really break bring it
back to its foundation and I always
think like this is I know it's not good
but if you really bring everything back
in like if there was war if there if
there was chaos if there was an alien
abduction abduction alien invasion and
we're so we're trying to survive
nobody's gonna care like if your people
are starving we're just fortunate we're
in a fortunate enough place in life to
worry about these little miniscule
things not saying that it's miniscule
right but like if like [ __ ] was going
down right and everyone's trying to
survive and it's every man for themself
right there's chaos world is ending we
would not those same people would not be
like hey we can't I don't think I don't
think so I don't think they'd be focused
on surviving yeah yessuh cumin need they
could still be vegan yeah but they
wouldn't be like hey you shouldn't do
that mm-hmm you know yeah we live in a
society where were we have the luxury of
making just like you know decisions of
first world problem decisions like you
know oh I don't like the color of this
whatever like organic first GMO yeah
yours like give to give the people and
walking dead like GMOs you know like in
that world
GMO genetically modified you know that
option of having food like constant food
coming in right and then raising cattle
and then putting it I mean
cages and stuff so that they can get
food you wouldn't say like oh my gosh
you're immoral you'd be like they're
trying to survive Yeah right but that's
I mean we're in a place where we're
lucky enough we don't need that that's
why we can complain about it yeah I mean
everyone's gotta eat
and everyone's gotta pee so on that you
should pick it up shishi break you
halfway
yep all right I guess well you wanna
send us off
[Music]
okay what do you wanna say no I didn't
say let's like singer oh yeah do it
she jingle I caught JR did not gonna
believe you're a singer junior chairs
was like this she-she-she brain let's go
on she she and we're you can do it sorry
I've seen enough episodes where I know
what you say and we're back see she
should break you guys don't know how to
do it I'm still practicing yeah I still
I'm still learning kids I said I'm
Stewart I'm stunned to a stupid to know
hmm what do kids add that that following
in there to us stupid I'm to us stupid
to us
I actually I don't know if they actually
talk like that yeah I've been around
kids in a while hey it's Jackie Chan's
birthday is it was it was this we just
passed weekend yeah 65 dude they're
making another rush hour what no way
yeah they all right unless that's the
age of 65 yeah can you even still do
stunts well I saw a picture of him and
Chris Tucker mm-hm and they're like did
they did some kind of pose and I read a
posting they're doing another rush hour
for I think like I don't know I don't
know this true I maybe look it up bro I
love Jackie Chan
you know what he's he's I mean as an
Asian American he's he really was one of
the guys who paved the way to making
Asians the Asian stereotype of martial
large stronger than ever yeah so it says
how it says all these assault no I bet
no but it's all seriousness he I think
he really paved the way for you know
people to really you know see that there
are some Asian American actors that can
have a successful film oh yeah he also
bridge the gap between you know he
played his part in bridging the gap
between asian-americans and the black
community through Chris Tucker in that
movie and his movies were funny they
were a great wall they were it was just
so many like and it was I love Jackie
Chan movies immensely yeah some of my
favorite so Chris Tucker said a fourth
film was definitely possible possibility
they didn't say they're doing it it's
not in pre-production they're working on
a few things for the script so they are
working on something but he said Jackie
Chan wants to do it he wants to do it
and the studio wants to do it so it's
gonna happen
Oh most likely that's awesome dude that
is awesome a lot of respect for 65 year
old to do stunts like that and he
doesn't own stunts that's also like who
does that anymore yes Tom Cruise but
yeah that's true that is true do you
guys have a favorite Jackie Chan movie
that you remember from childhood that
you could like watch at any point rush
hour rush hour rush hour is over ones
like which ones I mean I know there's a
lot drunken master rush hour was my
favorite I was so fun imal in the Bronx
I don't remember
Meals on Wheels hello you guys give this
up no these are all his movies when he
was really young you guys never watched
rumble in the Bronx no how old are you
dude dude the Bronx is so good fake
Asians fake Asian fake fictions honestly
go back and watch Rommel rocks it's
really good I will never watch drunken
master uh I thought that was Bruce Lee
no dude
legend of the drunken master he's like
this I didn't see that his dad is like a
kung-fu master and then he like learns
his other stuff I think I saw Jackie
Chan later in his career like when he
was doing funny things not just action
no they were funny oh really they were
really funny he's always been every
movie he's always but like this little
sense of cute what
humor is what I was in say in comedy I
was combining those two words and then
just in crazy crazy amount of stunts in
action but I would go back and watch I
was ever
really good I would say my favorite
meeting think of that the movies no
Jackie Chan I didn't bring it up oh yeah
want me to oh you just thought you just
just thought of it as topical can I just
out a driveway you know yeah so makes
you feel kind of old yourself to think
like wow this guy's been around that
long
yes still doing things oh you know what
he played the UM using karate kid' the
new one I didn't actually see that one
was it good
yeah that would jeans Oh like when Jaden
Smith yeah mm-hmm wait sorry I was
thinking at Cobra Kai that's good we're
all on three different what happened
during this you see all right sink each
other ready hands in yeah we're back in
sync to shi shi and we're back because
you guys said it wrong that's why sorry
we got distracted during the shi shi
break because one of my fish has a
bubble by its blood dude congratulations
Ryan thanks man
so what am I have a guppy I have a lot
of copies but they're in this big tank
and one of them is giving birth and I
never I never see it I never see it
happening and I finally there's like a
little bubble there so it's like the sac
thing coming out and we were just
waiting for it and it's not happening
but at the same time you don't want to
miss it I don't want to miss it because
you've never seen every single other
yeah I just see the babies if you see
the babies I'm like when does this
happen as the first time I'm seeing it
happening we're here how to do rate this
podcast you're missing your grand rifice
you're making that your grin my grand
grand fish grandkids you know what
though I'm not I'd still eat fish there
you go and I love fish
boom I love fish yeah I'd still eat it
you ate it last night
I did we have sushi you know sorry to
the vegan people they probably could
either only fix meat or fish what would
you pick for us your life boom go sheet
meat yeah because then I would have to
eat I think you would pick fish no I
just well I mean other than sushi like
what you don't know I know but doesn't
meet is like burgers and like steak
that's true and like covers a much wider
like there's more possible yeah but fish
is healthier for you yeah what would you
choose I don't know that meat guy I do
like me but I do like I mean eating fish
is I feel like it's good for you people
it is cultures that eat a lot of fish
are usually pretty live longer
but the fish that we have now there's
too much mercury in it you think so
for sure like there's a lot of fish in
every ocean or is it only specific
oceans how do you know I'm not an expert
but I know that when people eat too much
fish yeah they they get mercury
poisoning mmm it happens a lot you know
in the same way that like I was saying
like I don't get to see the negative
parts of like you know like the
slaughtering of animals all the time so
I kind of you kind of don't think about
it yeah and you kind of like it's kind
of selfish but at the same time you it's
understandable like if you don't see
something that often you're not gonna be
thinking about it all the time your
disconnect yeah
so I also heard like back when there was
a tsunami in Japan that you know all
that radioactive material went into the
water and it was constantly spreading
further and further and further I
remember like there's said so many years
from now every fish that's important
from there that you're eating is gonna
be in fact like not in fact radio a
creation and I remember hearing like
okay this is already happening and I've
been eating fish I haven't changed I
haven't changed because I haven't but if
I read an article like today I'll
probably like oh maybe I won't eat sushi
today but I'll probably eat it like in
the week yeah it's the same concept it's
like we just forget and like I mean I do
at least that's the power of media I
mean they can you know when you're yeah
you can change corporation like that you
just told people hey this is this is a
story we want to put out we want to put
an emphasis on the fact that we're
cleaning it up you know the radiation in
the in the ocean as opposed to them
coming up with the story this radiation
is starting to affect everyone's fish
yeah like that's that's the power that
like big corporations have yeah and a
separate no but it's related to what
you're talking about earlier is people
don't really care about the lives of
fish which is kind of crazy yeah yeah in
terms of like when we were tank talking
about drawing the line right animals and
mammals like they're very heavily they
have emotions they have feelings
blah blah blah and that kind of stuff
right yep fish I don't it's very rare to
have someone I feel like defend fish in
that way because like when I started
fishing that was one thing I was like
how do I dispose of the fish like in a
in a moral way right
and like some people say like hit it
over the head right and it'll just knock
its lights out and whether or not that's
you know well or insane however some
people just throw it in a bucket and
let's let it suffocate I think was water
don't scream or make noise that's yeah I
think that's what it can can't relate to
it as much and they're also in the water
so we don't see them all the time right
as imagine if you if you were to catch a
cow right by shoving a hook through its
through its mouth and like hooked onto
its mouth and it was like going crazy
and screaming you'd be like damn this is
hard to watch
yeah with a fish just like oh it's
flopping around cute you know like oh
you caught a fish yay it's no actually
when I see fish and see the blood coming
out actually I still kind of like feel
bad for oh I do too that knows like when
I started fishing I kind of was like I
need to figure out a way of like how to
morally dispose after I catch anyone II
want to eat it right yeah I mean if we
were to ask the fish what do you think
the fish would say what if the fish said
you know actually the best thing for me
is you probably should cut off my fin
first I prefer like it's like it's like
asking someone you know like imagine if
the fish could talk yeah what if there
is a way to morally do it at the fish
nose that's the least painful that'd be
like someone asking you I'm gonna eat
you what how do you want me to kill you
yeah or is it like brain what if this is
right what if by hitting it in the head
what your being with your act what if
you're stimulating something in the fish
or like knocking it out but they can
still feel mm-hmm yeah that's scary well
regardless I mean it's I mean I think
it's it people don't feel a certain way
about fish for that exact reason though
still right or maybe it's a cold-blooded
thing cuz people don't care as much
about reptiles Ulua true yeah get um
cold blood get on and we're cold blooded
damn we gonna wish just grab the fish by
the sleeves never your eye that was a
comment you said earlier I'm cold
yeah we're cold-blooded yeah well I
should have brought that up in the
beginning one of my favorite comments I
read on one of the last podcast I don't
remember it specifically but it said
something along the lines of how I
always wear a sweater right
I like wearing sweaters but and I'm look
cozy and warm and then he pan over a
Ryan sure he's like look sweaty and the
comment was like I just am so confused
on what the temperature is in this room
yeah people thought we might be either
in different rooms or how big is this
room like it's not that big once I let
me say is it's cold it is cold here Ryan
can handle the cold like a champion like
it'll be love that's super cold outside
he's like wearing a t-shirt I'm like
you're definitely cool he's like no I'm
not I'm sweating yeah always like oh
what are you trying to be tough no I
love the code and people like oh where
are you from like Hawaii and like what
that doesn't make sense and here's my
explanation for that and you grow up in
Hawaii at least for me I grew up it's so
hot there right and there's no a/c all
the sweating yeah like all the time most
of the time it's hot and it's the most
uncomfortable thing that it's so like
humid people in Singapore you guys can
probably relate except you guys are rich
enough to have AC I didn't have AC it
was horrible the only time it felt great
is when you walked into like
supermarkets or like places that were
cold and it was such a luxury I had one
friend who had AC and they were like
rich and I was always like so excited to
go to their house cuz it was so nice to
just step in there and ever since then I
guess I grew up just appreciating the
cold yeah was it a do you think growing
up was it a thing of money to have an AC
or was it just the homes like maybe when
your parents bought homes back in the
day maybe it was just like people didn't
think they needed AC is because it was
like cool like I mean we were we were
like not rich we were like I would say
like middle-class we weren't poor we
were a middle class I would say and they
still would my parents to say like
that's a waste of money yeah and I
actually ended up I ended up getting
them AC yeah but my mom was like I don't
we don't need that room so it's just in
the living room and in my bedroom so
when I go back check the ones that are
on the wall but it's it's I don't know
yeah it was still considered I think it
expensive it's like a waste of money so
example but it's sobering it was a
luxury yeah and I think that's why I
love the cold yeah and also I sweat easy
you know what shawne's the same way and
he's from Hawaii he is I'm onto
something
damn hey if there are any Hawaiians out
there do you like the cold I mean I
think I think that's I mean that's why
people think oh you're from Hawaii you
should like the warmth ya know I think
like people who grow up in like really
cold like Minnesota right you you would
like the warmth because you hate the
code there right yeah that's why a lot
of people when they move if they move
from the Midwest or something or
somewhere where it's really cold they
have harsh winters they moved like
California they're like oh my god the
weather I mean it is nice but you
Singaporeans are like me cuz it's so hot
they just love the cold but the thing is
they have a/c you might be onto
something here I might be
could you imagine not having AC in Las
Vegas we would probably be dead you die
do you really think about it if if [ __ ]
went down right and electricity got cut
out
I think we're dead we were just talking
about that yeah what would happen like
we would I mean during the summer it
hits like 115 degrees 120 sometimes and
we're in the middle of the desert like
if there was like a apocalypse right and
we're all locked in here we we'd be dead
during the summer what would you do
there's nothing like how would we
survive you would have to find just some
shade or some water or something that's
what they did back then yeah I mean they
people didn't want to live and didn't
live in the desert back then we got
tricked into living out here people do I
mean that's how we're that's how
humanity you know came living with us
today well they had to live through it I
mean I mean they went through it but
they're not like hey let's settle right
here and it all shows the human spirit
I wonder how fast we could adjust our
that we have like a kid who was born
into a climate and then it raised their
whole life but if if all of a sudden
everything just like all our luxuries
got shut off
I wonder how fast we would adjust to
like our environment and would we evolve
as humans would the the next generation
of kids be have like really hot skin oh
and their well their body temperatures
would be at naturally at 105 Oh
instead of 98.6 I don't know damn we'll
never know I don't know why I brought
that up oh you know why I brought that
up that's because we were listening to a
book called CD games and that was I was
pretty um highly recommend it was a long
drive it was really cool it was super
interesting it was good but if you would
have saw us
from an outside perspective like three
guys just sitting there listening to
this book that sounds like a British
lecture from like a college you'd be
like oh let's get doing we do for fun we
were like genuinely into it no I mean I
thought it was super super intriguing
that was really cool and I and then made
me think like when people listen to this
podcast they're not really getting that
much right like we're just talking about
like I learned a lot what did you learn
lean one thing you learned from this
podcast see maybe we need to start like
going at school reading more yeah become
scholars you know we should do is listen
to more like educational stuff and then
will regurgitate in a dumb way for dumb
people because I don't like listening to
smart people talk it gets boring you
know because I'm not smart my first
lesson today two plus two equals four I
mean when I say dumb I mean like thanks
for coming to my TED talk when I said no
I don't mean like we don't think I just
mean we're not necessarily Harvard grads
yeah you know like yeah duh you dropped
out right so yeah I got accepted to USC
and I was gonna go for music business
right and then that was a time I got
signed to a publishing deal for at a
company called warner/chappell music and
I ate so I chose that and I dropped out
because I wanted to pursue YouTube mhm
and will dropped out as well you did
yeah we are three dumb dummies and then
we're the bird themed boys anyone's
listening to right now we will do our
best to get more educational things and
dumb it down for you naturally I thought
you guys are dumb it's cuz we're dumb we
are dumb yeah but we'll make it fun try
it so what do we learn from sapiens that
humans are strong that's not oh you mean
the the book yeah I feel like I learned
actually a lot I nearly thought about
how there was multiple species of like
quote-unquote humans that one yeah I
think that one yeah and then what we are
today is Homo sapiens but there was like
the Neander
dolls or Neanderthals that's how you
pronounced it yeah and like all these
other ones and we know ones that
survived yeah we don't really know I
don't think how we became the last ones
to survive there he was definitely pecks
predators yeah he was saying that could
have been like we could have hope
extinguished that or iPhone in time Oh
was that because and this is the this is
the only thing I really took a not that
I to only took away this but I thought
it was so interesting that how he was
saying we've evolved so that our brains
are bigger than like Apes right and the
reason the reason why we're so weak is
because our brains are so big and it
requires so much energy we compared to
the the chimpanzees and the Apes they're
exactly yeah
yeah and he was saying that um and what
what made us talk he didn't say this
this is or us you know hearing that and
going on you know how they draw aliens
and they show aliens like your
stereotypical alien has a gigantic head
and a smaller body right and you know
you know that's your stereotypical alien
a small body gigantic head at least
that's what we hear it if you think
about it what if they're just the
evolved versions of humans because I
mean there's a conspiracy theory already
that that's what it is
yeah aliens are just super evolved
humans as you see time it's like my
favorite yeah it's like battle of the
minds as opposed to physical story right
which is like what animals have - it's
all based off of speed and strength
right right with human beings we've come
to evolve to become a society where we
don't need to actually physically fight
yeah because we're smart
these are dominant we have we learn that
our brains make us the most powerful
thing because we can shoot we invented
guns we can shoot an ape whereas if we
didn't have if we're going one-on-one in
the physical battle that hate would tear
us apart yeah but because of our brains
is the most powerful gift that's but
that also is why we're so physically
weak there's no thing that's as strong
as an ape and as smart as a human
because it would be too much energy to
repower that brain yeah something like
that yeah so what if so aliens you know
what that means
well kick some alien ass physically but
then they'd probably have super guns and
then super shoot us
yeah I mean for all we know they're
already we're already in they're gone
we're in their world that they created
that's like her dummy Homo Sapien way
they got super gonna shoot us you know
what we're bringing we're gonna listen
to more and we will update you guys I
think it's been like yeah I really think
oh but you're leaving hey you got to
come back I'll be back someday yeah you
gotta breathe we gotta get more negative
yes guys leave some negative comments
for David please was it David cannibal
cannibal I'm just a sack of canned balls
you didn't have to take it there but
alright sorry guys I really think we
should we should learn more so that we
can be we gotta get better at this we
got to have you got to help educate our
listeners yeah I realize I feel like uh
as we do the podcast I realize that
being able to like conversate and watch
it back it's pretty crazy like how you
say like I feel like Paco naturally is a
good comping a conversation and speaking
and something that I loves to talk he
loves to talk and I feel like it's it's
hard it's a hard to generate entertainer
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's is that's why
I mean that's out of everybody in noir
hpc I was like he needs to be on it cuz
this is his gift yes not necessarily
like oh I'll write a skit for him sure
he'll do it he's he would want to do it
his own way but when he's just being him
like that's best yeah not when he's like
not trying to make you laugh it's funny
to me and you can see it through the
podcasts because that's essentially what
I think he would love to hear us saying
this type of thing forward
he ain't gonna watch this you think you
need to watch this he I don't think you
I mean if he does he knows that we're
ending since he probably would have
skipped it like the ending alright miss
you Paco you're a great person
yeah he's well he comes back tomorrow
from Japan yeah or not tomorrow I guess
when this comes out he just came back
yep um I guess yeah what that being said
and wrap this up but I do think man I
wish and we brought this up earlier what
huh
the whole alien thing because I think
that's we're on to something I think so
too
and I don't think we're the first one
because I've seen something similar I
just don't remember the videos and you
can continue this in the next episode I
know
off the pill I like to use topics with
David because David I know he thinks
about these he's more skeptical than I
am
yeah and he brings like that a nice side
of that I mean I'm pretty skeptical too
though but I like to have fun with it
we'll talk about it next time with David
then yeah yeah sounds good
okay well thanks again for tweens to the
thanks again for tuning in to the off
the pill podcast remember our twitter is
at off the pill instagram is at off the
pill podcast we still can't like you do
you know people there right like could
we just get both of them to say off to
peel podcasts off the pill we'll look
into it I mean I you could look into it
I don't really know people there I I
need to step my Instagram game up well
you do it I've been good yeah and
actually you've been good to you leave
you do stories and stuff I do stories
sometimes we didn't do viewer questions
this this week did it well do is this my
favorite part I know sorry guys
having said you know how to end this yup
3 2 people hate this part I feel like we
want to ask him deep purple elephants
now we should leave a new code today
yeah well you know what we'll just put
the David David is a cannibal David in
it is a can of balls like that that I
mean they probably if you didn't make it
that far you probably won't whatever
cannonball saw that piece
[Laughter]