damn bill I like disgusting right now
well still November I can't shave it
I can't shave it hey guys so as you can
tell this is not our normal video
because I'm not at my desk and there's
no bed behind me so actually this is a
kind of a tradition are we going through
something nice for people all dressed up
as a ninja
no no why I started dressing up as a
ninja that doesn't really add anything
to it but it's fun so this year unlike
the past couple times we did this we are
actually not only gonna be giving out
food we're gonna be giving out a bunch
of blankets and warm clothes and I'm not
telling you guys this to make you guys
think like oh I'm such a good person or
like we're such good people it's
actually the opposite I'm actually very
selfish if you think about it not doing
it to help other people I'm doing it to
make me feel good so it's incredibly
selfish just so happens that this
selfish thing that I'm doing has a
byproduct that is makes others feel good
I don't know what I just said anyway I
am going to go and be selfish now but
being that we have a lot more things to
give out this year I might need a little
bit of help which as you know only means
one thing
cookie butcher no jutsu yeah your own
man just gonna kick it to the slightly
no flips page I forgot to put on my mask
smoke sock pretty thing
alright guys got a big night ahead of us
hands in selfish on three one two three
wait wait for me I got the camera it
always happens
see nothing it was just us