are you tired of living the same old
comfortable life don't you want to go in
an adventure and discover some new
hidden secret surprises isn't it about
time to add some style to your life
well when the Brier lines you'll never
live the same old comfortable life again
because it's impossible to get
comfortable you'll discover surprise
after surprise the moment you show up
thanks to our hidden fees and in terms
of adding style to your life we make
sure that every single one of our
customers are fashionably late thanks to
delays hi I'm Ryan Higa and here at a
dry airlines we've always believed that
your experience flying did not just be
good not just great not even just an
all-around amazing experience so that's
what we do
our motto here at ever I airlines has
always been just that even though you
paid for this flight we don't work for
you we're gonna be as rude and
condescending as we want gonna like a DJ
you know push a couple buttons have a
couple sips before you know it we're
there pay me so we got this game right
it's kind of like the mini Olympics but
with bets you take a luggage but a
half's add that little red sticker on it
rather than placing it down nice sleep
we shall put it on to the plane and if
we hear anything broken or anything in
pieces and you lose
oh it's for fun but it also makes us be
careful with everyone's frag Lea stuff
one of my pet peeves are when people ask
for things but we take customer service
very seriously here so immediately after
we're finished doing what we're doing
like gossiping and taking a nap or
eating our food will not the customers
food the good food we go over to the
customer and politely say what sometimes
we like to do this thing up here we turn
the entertainment system all the way
down so when the passengers put their
headphones on they turn it up they can't
even hear anything and then out of
nowhere I pick up the PA and
you're the spit out oh but even with our
incredible staff the fry airlines
wouldn't be what it is today without the
help of all of you our loyal @vy
Airlines members show up to almost every
single flight from the parents who
ignore their screaming kids member who
the angry business man shouting on his
cell phone for the whole plane to hear
for the guy who didn't learn shapes as a
kid to the armrest hugger the leg
spreader a guy who sits window but has
to pee every 20 minutes the overly
friendly guy who talks the whole flight
despite seeing you trying to sleep even
the guy who was constantly farting
thinking we don't know it's him and even
though we have funnier to write Airlines
we always take your safety very
seriously with our newly updated on a
safety demonstration video hello and
welcome to a Wright Airlines this is
your safety demonstration video which
none of you are actually going to listen
to but we're going to do it anyway so
that you don't sue us there are four
emergency exits on this aircraft in the
unlikely event of surviving a plane
crash and life vest is located in a
pouch underneath your seat but so is a
luggage of the guy sitting behind you so
you probably won't have access to it in
the event of a change in air pressure
and oxygen masks will automatically
appear in front of you if you don't
already know how to put on a mask and
breathe chances are you're not going to
survive anyway if you are traveling with
a child or someone who requires
assistance be sure to apply your mask
first because your life is more
important hashtag priority we remind you
that this is a non-smoking flight as
compared to all the other smokey flights
that you've taken you will find this and
all other safety information in the card
located between the vomit bag with gum
in it and our dirty complimentary
magazine that's held together by
children's boogers located underneath
the tray table that we don't clean if
you have any other questions please
hesitate to ask the flight attendant
it's a real father to the conversation
that we're having in the back thank you
and have a safe flight is what you
should be saying to us but letting you
join us today you're welcome
so what are you waiting for book your
flight with a Verizon a still don't
believe us we'll check out these
satisfied customers showing us their
thumbs
[Music]
yeah we may be a little dirty delayed
expensive annoyed careless all around
just awful but like we always say here
to fry your alliance dry airlines just
steal