do you really want your life looking
like this cleaning up after others
flipping burgers for a living
unclogging toilets living in this black
and white world well luckily there's a
way you can change all that the bright
University you'll learn the necessary
skills and knowledge to be the best most
educated overqualified mess cleaning
burger flipping toilet unclogging
scholar with a degree and you'll be in
color headed by university we want you
we want you we want you we want you to
pay us you will not not regret it only I
could go back hands-down the best
decision my parents ever forced me to
make everyone knows that the reason you
go to college is for money college means
a degree a degree in the job the job
whatever I can guarantee that we might
get you to the degree part if you put in
the work cuz really you're doing all the
work not us I never been so stressed out
in my life I never thought I'd ever wish
to be back in high school again
yeah maybe books are about a thousand
dollars a year Norma meal plans at
another equation forty five but the
experience is quality education and
friends are gonna be making along the
way priceless
I finally got my degree in communication
and I only owe like $100,000 with
financial aid scholarships and the two
part-time jobs I had a lot of tending
over I can pay back my loans in 20 years
instead of 30 might as well call me
Johnny some definitely in debt chances
are you will need a loan to be able to
afford a bra but don't worry you don't
have to pay it back until right after
you graduate that's a lot of time
because if you thought you were gonna
graduate in a couple of years
they're completely forgetting about the
prereqs out of Ryan not only can you
choose to learn things that have nothing
to do with your major but you have to
learn things have nothing to do with
your major you want to be a dentist if
Ryan university offers dentistry 101
right after you complete English 1 & 2
calculus 205 2 years of foreign language
the history of rock and roll and women's
studies because of the dentists you
never know when you're gonna get a
four-word rock and roll star asking you
to calculate an equation while you're
cleaning his teeth or her teeth
if Wray University may be a little
pricey so let's be real you're not gonna
be successful with them where else are
you going to learn the necessary skills
and knowledge for a job other than a
professor or book or hands-on internship
or the job itself or Google or even
YouTube how to video
exactly Noli so what are you waiting for
pay your application fee so you can
apply today before you know it you could
be just like me like me me like me like
me paying tuition at a variety if we
accept you that is so choose a bright
University because really in our society
why university because everyone else is
doing it thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the left if you
want to see more honest commercials
click the one on the right if you want
to see a half animated horse with a
super slow-mo face of Shawn while he's
dancing around in a club dancing to a
bunch of techno music click the one on
the bottom yeah it kind of made that up
alright click one of them I don't know
which one's the best one but do you
probably do it's probably the previous
video k bite