hey guys so a few days ago there was an
eight point nine earthquake in Japan
followed by a tsunami which pretty much
destroyed the place and I know I never
make serious videos and the reason for
that is because whenever I do I get all
this hate rain this is not why I
subscribed or this isn't funny it wasn't
supposed to be this is more important
than comedy or YouTube in general I've
been trying to think of ways to help
support Japan and encourage others to
support as well so what I'm going to be
doing today is I'm gonna go outside for
an hour holding this sign long if you
love Japan and for every hunk that I get
I will be donating $10 to the Red Cross
Disaster Relief Fund for Japan I'm about
to grab a couple friends with me right
now to help me film and uh let's do it
so right now we're on the street and uh
we've done our signage as you can see
let me donating money marzipan for every
home that we get so honest let's get
this started
yeah
and that's 30 bucks you can see we have
a lot of support here in a la bunch of
nice people support too bad I'll show
your love
that was like amen let's go okay let's
just say that was 25
so what is that one honker is that like
50s in public to start yes so we're
finally back because the sun's going
down thank you to my friends kept jumbo
Chester C picture Kim at Mike song for
helping me out as you can see there's a
lot of support here in LA and I hope
wherever you are you can support as well
I'm going to be donating the $600 right
now so that you guys can see it
here's the screenshot and if you have at
least $10 or more to spare please go to
Red Cross org and make your own donation
and with that being said I just want to
say that my heart goes out to all of you
who are affected by the earthquake and
to everybody in Japan you saw it
yourself in this video there are people
in LA all around the world we're going
to support you and keep supporting you
into things get better la is a very
supportive place I had no idea I love
you
honk if you love Japan man I'll give you
love you