oh hello I didn't see you there welcome
to how to act like your favorite actor
and I can assure you that if you follow
all these tips and techniques you'll be
acting in a long time and you'll be able
to do things like this happy haha sad
confused what transition
[Music]
nor attack like Robert Pattinson also
known as Edward from the Twilight movie
all you have to do is talk real quietly
and sound like you're in pain it's like
a drug to me more pain than that it's
like a drug to me even more it's like a
drug to me you just had spoiled milk in
the morning and somebody punched you in
the stomach and now you have to hold in
your pain it's like a drug to me you're
like my own personal brand of heroin I
don't know why Kristen Stewart gets so
much hate for being a bad actor in order
to be a great actor the character you're
playing has to be consistent and Kristen
Stewart is the master of consistency oh
my god it's shocking oh my god I'm so
happy oh my god that's terrible
oh my god I'm a ninja are oh my god oh
my god see they're all the same so
people may give her a 1 out of 10 for
acting but I give her a consist 10 out
of 10 how do you feel about that Kristen
oh my god that's shocking
Nora talk like Alan Rickman also known
as Professor Snape from the Harry Potter
movies all you have to do is make the
stitch boys from lilo and stitch how
long long spine Allah and once you got
that done all you have to do is make
your voice deeper and talk with your
teeth closed all I can teach you to be a
witch the month I can teach you to eat
ensnare the senses I can teach you or
just the patent expunge the Bob I can
teach you to sound like Squidward
I want to control you everybody knows
the accent but in order to sound like
Arnold all you have to do is make the
Kermit the Frog voice Kermit the Frog
here and then sound like you're throwing
up listen to me
[Music]
Janardan act like Jim Carrey all you
have to do is flex every single muscle
in your body and have really sharp quick
movements well alrighty then a lot of
people say that tearin' Lautner is a bad
actor but he's not he just has a
different style of acting called
distracting all you have to do is have a
nice body and take off your shirt to
distract people from your bad acting oh
my god you're bleeding
[Music]
Thanks got some blood on the counter too
you mind passing me oh you know what
don't worry here ok shoot spill the
beverage do you might hand me that trash
where do you keep getting all those
shirts for look I don't know how you're
doing this shirt magic but the bleeding
is not stopping so you can you just call
an ambulance or some oh yeah sure you
don't need to take your shirt off just
to call it oh yeah you guys have any
more shirts I'm running low
just act really sassy and sarcastic and
do that stuttering thing where you don't
really finish your sentence so you you
don't want me to okay yet get just grab
it man
yeah throw up your arms and always be
angry I don't know okay
undress the monkey over here huh Jeff
large is a great actor what makes people
really love her is that she's really
down to earth and she doesn't care what
people think she's silly she's clumsy
she puts her pants on one leg at a time
just like everybody else after they take
nudes too far hey Jen do you think you
put that fort down why what are you
calling me fat what does it even matter
how much I weigh I don't want little
girls watching this to see Katniss as
this anorexic supermodel character you
don't have to be that skinny and
beautiful just to be a really strong
independent woman okay that's fine but
this is Hunger Games you supposed to be
starving in this scene and not eating oh
my god I'm so embarrassed I'm so sorry
guys I am only human after okay it's
okay here I'm gonna put this away here
well all you have to do is talk like
you're in very deep thought all the time
so that everything you say even if it
doesn't make sense
sounds like it's very deep and dramatic
sometimes you got to go back to actually
move forward I don't mean that like some
fancy metaphor I mean literally when you
crash into one of those big old green
tube things in Mario car
gotta press B in reverse a little and
then you can keep going and even though
I know all that still have so many
unanswered questions like they named the
tree after the palm of the palm after
the tree did Delilah ever tell that guy
what it was like in New York City of
course the greatest question of all what
is the meaning of life cereal
I mean don't taste that good not the
healthiest cereal round is just there
yet life is still a cereal because life
is still surreal
[Music]
or attack like Samuel Jackson all you
have to do is talk like you're in a club
or at a concert or anyplace that's
really loud where you have to shout why
are you stopping mr. Cruz you want to be
a part of this game yes coach and I'ma
ask you one last time mr. Cruz what is
in your wallet
well hey you got a hearing problem mr.
Cruz I said what is in your wallet
I don't know cash wallets and mr. Cruz
that's the whole jabal pusher I got
pictures let's make that a thousand some
gum ten thousand push-ups mr. Kruger huh
I am credit card okay and what kind of
card is that ain't that hard mr. Cruz
what kind of car do you have mr. Cruz
what is in your wallet
heesu get your ass back on the ground
and give me a hundred thousand five
hundred thousand with a capital one
[Music]
acting like leonardo dicaprio is really
difficult because of all the different
characters he plays however there's one
similar role that he plays every single
year and in order to act like that all
you have to do is start nodding your
head press your lips together and begin
clapping and the Oscar for Best Actor
goes to Matthew McConaughey
[Applause]
normally when you're scared or
frightened of something you move really
quickly but every horror movie actor
knows that's the complete opposite of
what you want to do Norma attack like a
horror movie actor all you have to do is
move in slow motion when something
frightens you
[Music]
oh it's just you Marley
it's just shoes
[Music]
Oh God I'm just gonna go kill someone
else already you're so damn slow God
sure went down the street to the beer
house every drama movie actor knows that
if you want to look really sad look out
a window you don't actually have to know
anything for this one you don't even
need to know your line just come on with
a combination of the scariest and most
dangerous things you can think of and
then have an editor put it in for you
with really good effects so you're
saying the Machine fell in mouths
volcano and it's gonna erupt at any
second yes and I'm afraid this time it's
not just gonna be molten lava erupting
what else is there lasers
Laser volcano only on sci-fi so you're
saying all the animals had been sucked
into the sky yes and I'm afraid this
time when the storm hits it's not just
gonna be rain what do you mean it's
literally gonna rain cats and dogs
the rain of cats and dogs only on sci-fi
so you're saying a tornado that's
forming in the ocean is heading towards
us yes and I'm afraid this tornado is so
big that it's gonna suck up man-eating
sharks so it won't just be a normal
tornado it's gonna be a sharknado only
wait if a tornado is forming in the
ocean isn't that just a hurricane no I
mean tornadoes can form over water too
right not sure I know hurricanes do and
should we just call it shark hurricane
yeah but that doesn't sound as good as
sharknado yeah but I mean just to be
safe I think we're thinking too much
into it yeah this is the sci-fi Network
we don't have to know real science for
this right sci-fi or science may not be
accurate but at least we have good
effects so I know what you're saying I
was nothing like all those actors Act in
fact that wasn't even good acting that's
because you're used to seeing these
people in movies and if we were to put
all the stuff you just saw in the form
of a movie see how perfect the acting
actually was sometimes you got to go
back to actually move forward even
though I know all that still have so
many unanswered questions what does it
even matter
no okay well dress the monkey yes coach
oh my god that's terrible it's like a
drug - what do you need like a drug to
me what else is there
shining shimmering splendid to me you
have you darted up
[Music]
cuz life is still Saraya okay yeah that
still sucked so thank you guys again so
much for watching if you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click the
one the left if you want to see the
previous video click the one on the
right or if you want to see another
video just like this one it's called
hottest thing like your favorite artist
pick the one on the bottom that one will
teach you just as much as this one
probably not that much