muster up hey guys and Happy New Year so
this is the first video of the year I
know I'm a little bit late but as usual
I went back home to Hawaii for the
holidays and I had a lot of time to
really reflect on myself like most
people do around New Year's and I
realized that I need to make some
changes most of you guys already know
I've been doing YouTube for such a long
time and during that time I would say
95% of the content was always relatively
clean I mean not like Disney Channel
clean but I've never shown like drugs
and alcohol or anything too sexual I
haven't even cursed on this channel
without getting bleep at least recently
I'm gonna done something when I was
younger I mean I can't even see the S
word and they say that on TV now you
know the word see what I'm talking about
it's a bunch of bull this is what
happens when I try to curse here not
even my choice son of one holy Oh
surprise mother I guess I can curse see
what I have to go through it's time for
a change you see this this is why I get
censored this is P G mo that's what I am
on right now it's on look at Justin
Bieber Miley Cyrus even Selena Gomez
they all switched off their PG switch I
went from clean innocent stars to these
drug using bucket peeing sexy sexual sex
superstars and at first everyone thought
including myself well that they're just
ruining their career and now they're
doing better than ever because that is
what people want which is why it is my
time to break for you by the end of this
video I'm gonna be switching this off
for good I'm gonna kill myself I don't
know why I did this no more mr. nice
Ryan no more clean innocent videos it's
time it's time to get a little edgy
huh
guess it doesn't work oh you thought
this was gonna be a vlog that's
something the old Ryan Higa would do
well guess what the old Ryan Higa he's
dead this is the new and improved Ryan
Higa the head you Ryan Higa ready by the
time you finish this video this switch
it's going off for good welcome to how
to be a average welcome to how to be
edge I'm rich yeah I introduced myself
twice but that's the first lesson of
being edge you ain't afraid of the rule
edgy people will do its normal we don't
do what society tells us to do I mean
look at me
look what I'm wearing right now see this
jacket the zipper don't go straight at
the middle like every single other
jacket it goes a little to the right
why cuz society that's why [ __ ] no hook
you my pants rip no big deal right there
just repent well guess what
these pants are ripped on purpose [ __ ]
I know you guys can't see it right now I
had some bad know who my cereal today
and now I got diarrhea
I guess what color underwear I still
chose to wear that's right Oh kind of
pulled that too hard
wait now if you really want to be edgy
just wearing it edgy clothes nothing cuz
you can change but if you really commit
like oh I did that's the sign of a true
rigid person see my hair color not even
my real hair color I've dyed it well I
mean I sprayed it but it's not gonna
come off until I shower later [ __ ] and
these piercings yeah they might not be
real but they're still don't leave a
really dark red mark when I take them
off later
I'm most importantly if you want to be
edging you gotta have tats rather sleep
thank you every edgy person you can
think of as tats and I know you guys
think you know what I'm gonna say but no
these tats these are real these are real
temporary tattoos and they're all edging
these are tattoos that nobody gives but
this Chinese character right here it's
in Japanese I can't even read Korean
tell me how many people are brave enough
to get something like that
how about this one a lot of people get
this tattoo because they love their mom
but I got this one from when I punched
my mom in the heart pinch or even all of
these so Angie the story behind these
tasks didn't even happen yet it's the
story of when I got a copyright claim in
Disney don't show me
all right now as you look the part and
dress the part here's the final step
before you can turn this stop lay off
and start saying words like well you got
to do is act the part is Angie people we
know on the edge all the time like right
now I'm literally sitting at the edge of
my seat when I sleep I sleep at the edge
of the bed and my bed is at the edge of
the room which is at the edge of my
house which is located at the edge of
Las Vegas at the edge of no matter the
edge of the USA the USA as we all know
is on the edge of bankruptcy
we don't care cuz edgy people we take
risks forget the consequences just Nike
adjust trial the bump it just do it or
watch the law to wear your seat belt
when you're at the wheel my arm around
it like it's no big deal
fish Oh mom made spaghetti tonight still
wear a shirt that's white energy kinda
oh you have to wait an hour after you
eat to go swim I just wait 45 minutes
and jump in and see all the videos you
pull they sit walk them all it cost
extra
how much extra a dollar eighty okay no
then okay yeah maybe that last one
wasn't that edgy but if you were to
continue the scene oh do you want let it
what does that cost more to know ya
veggies all right
you know all the steps you gotta look
the part you want to dress the part you
know how to act the part you know what
time it is time to go ahead you Reggie
forever and now for the very first time
I will be debuting the very first
uncensored cursed word on this channel
and it goes a little something like this
okay yeah this video was a vlog that
didn't actually really happen I wouldn't
actually break a real laptop anyway for
all of you that actually thought that I
was serious for a second I'm not really
Reggie there is no Reggie I'm not gonna
change for all the people that thought I
was serious look the truth is I am
getting older and usually with people in
the entertainment industry as they get
older they intentionally trying to get
edgy or so that they can appeal to an
older audience and honestly I just I
don't want to do that look if my stuff
gets edged ear over time because I'm
getting older that's fine but I'm not
gonna force it just to appeal to a new
audience I'm not getting edgy I'm not
really changing my image in fact because
I know there's already gonna be a lot of
you who didn't get the sarcasm in this
video all those bleeps you heard in this
video that you thought you were offended
by weren't actually curse words I
actually didn't even curse once throw up
filming this entire video this is what
it really sounded like without all the
bleeps you know the word I it's a bunch
of bull will son of a never wholly curse
oh oh this surprise mother channel
because coz if society that's why and
start saying words like I did yeah you
see I wasn't cursing at all and if you
put all those bleep sections together
it's actually a message that I created
to help assure you guys that I'm not
really changing if you didn't already
catch it this is what it says I will
never hurt this channel because if I did
I did that [ __ ] would be crazy I'm sorry
I had to do it I had to man now for all
of you that still want to complain
please see my video since this [ __ ]
makes no sense have a good night house
see you next year I'm just kidding I'll
see you guys this year I'll see you guys
probably next week a bike so thank you
guys again so much for watching you can
see bloopers and guide the scene since
on the left you want the previous video
which was last year to on the right and
again don't worry guys I'm not gonna be
swearing all the time like I'm not gonna
ever say the words again oh oh [ __ ] see
it's still bleep