hey guys sorry I didn't post a video
last week if you follow my newly made
snapchat you know that I was in Hawaii
for a wedding and no I'm not saying that
just to plug my snapchat I hate it when
people are constantly promoting their
own real line so yeah I was in Hawaii
for a wedding I know why I'm so dark
right now so I apologize for not posting
and also I'm sick but anyway today I'm
gonna be talking to you guys about
having to break bad news to people it's
literally one of the hardest things that
you have to do in life yet it's
something that we all have to do I
honestly think it's harder to deliver
bad news to someone than it is to
actually receive it and if you've been
in that situation you know exactly what
I'm talking about a king bad news to
people just sucks it's one of the worst
feelings ever this is why I came up with
this video to not just help you myself
as well here's some tips and techniques
to make it a little easier and you guys
the next time you have to break bad news
to someone take a look first up we got
probably the most common technique that
people use the good news and bad news
technique if you have to deliver bad
news to people got to give them some
good news as well to cheer moms no
matter how bad the bad news is there's
always good news
you just have to find it I got some good
news and bad news
what do in here first give me the bad
news well you know how I just left to go
get us lattes from Starbucks yeah whoa
in the parking lot I kinda hit a kid
what are you serious and I fled the
scene but they definitely have your
license plate on file and they're
probably on the way here now kidding me
right now they're still good news so
could there possibly be any good news I
got the lattes Oh
oh yeah that's right they spilled when I
hit that kid the bigger picture now
there's different levels of bad news
obviously some are worse than others for
this technique all you have to do is
give fake terrible news right before you
give the actual bad news so I comparison
the actual bad news is not that bad hey
G yeah they're not making a frozen - oh
that's X and also I kind of ran over
your dog on the way here what oh wait
before you get mad they are making a
frozen to it are still dead though the
cliched technique one of the worst ways
you can break bad news to someone is by
just surprising them with this technique
you're gonna give them a warning that
bad news is coming so that they can
mentally prepare for it all you have to
do is start your conversation off with a
very cliche line such as yeah there's a
there's no easy way to say this
I do it to Billie and do with the boot
indubitably
in dub it - what does that work
indubitably yeah that it means I you
know to be without a doubt or for sure I
know what it means boo why are you
trying to say oh because your
girlfriend's cheating on you
what are you sure indubitably it duped
and there really is no easy way to say
that word the good news bad news and
even worse news technique sometimes when
you have really really bad news you
don't want to overwhelm the person so
you're gonna want to break it up into
pieces with this technique you give it
to them in part so instead of giving
them extremely awful news you just give
them bad news and even worse news like
we mentioned earlier it doesn't hurt to
sprinkle little good news in there
wasn't a sprinkle I don't know what that
was so I have some good news some bad
news and some even worse news I wish I'd
ear first the good news I guess it the
good news is that your son is still
alive so oh my god still alive what
happened well that's the bad news do you
want to know that now or I thought you
wanted a good reason right tell me what
happened okay well the bad news is your
son has been hit by a car in the
Starbucks parking lot why didn't you
tell me that immediately well you asked
for the good news first not the bad
thing he's still alive without even
knowing isn't good news you have even
heard the even worse news
how could it be worse well the even
worse news is that I lied about the good
news huh he's dead just have fun with it
now if you still can't figure out how to
use these techniques I made it even
easier asked a bunch of you on Twitter
for some of the worst news that you ever
had to break and judging by those tweets
I came up with some of the most common
situations that people find themselves
in when they have to break bad news here
are some pre-made examples that you guys
can use when you're in that situation
like when grandmas tests come in she got
your grandmother's test results back and
well she passed so she's going to be
okay no but you just said she passed and
she got an 8 8 plus wait a
which passed away the worst news you
could possibly break in a wedding and
you Dana do you take Gregory to be your
husband again and by the power invested
in me I now pronounce you man and wife
let me now kiss the bride wait I have
something to say I have terrible news
there's no easy way to say this so Oh
the Wi-Fi is down when she refuses to
give starwars a chance what are you
doing you know how I love Star Wars and
I believe in the force yes and ever
since we've been married I've been
trying to get you to finally watch it so
not going to right which is why I
believe this belongs to you what is that
what may divorce be with you you get her
to break the bad news for you can't just
do the same move over and over it's open
Hey I really am though when it's the
highlight of his day
the park is closed today when you're the
boss
sir what are you doing I'm gonna light
this ring around you on fire
why cuz I'm firing you what okay
obviously these are jokes I took it a
little too far you're not gonna light
someone on fire this video actually
started off kind of realistic and then I
had too much fun with it sorry guys but
anyways truth is there is no easy way to
break bad news to some best way you can
do it is by just getting straight to the
point don't beat around the bush it's
like ripping off a band-aid you just do
it one time really fast you get it over
with you also hope that you're not hairy
because that hurts marks look I have to
get back to work in ten minutes what is
it it'd be quicker I promise okay well
then what's up so I have some bad news
what is that your newspaper you got wet
outside so it's pretty bad news now I'm
scared for you for a second I thought it
you really meant that means well to be
honest I actually do have more bad news
from your neighbors lawns I don't know
do you want to give this to them or okay
now listen there is something I need to
tell you and it's it's pretty upsetting
I'm betting what is it I just told you
it's up sitting there kind of slouching
you really should sit up cuz your back
it's not good for your back you know
okay but anyway the real reason why I
called you out here is because well your
parents it's it's not looking good and
my parents what do you mean it's not
looking good your parents they they've
definitely seen better days
what happened just your parents it's
just a bit messy just tell me what
happened what is it you find it's your
hair my hair what does this have to do
with my parents you talking about it
your hair is everything to do with your
appearance I think it's your ear could
also be your posture you're kind of
slouching again you went back to doing
limited tell you something up sitting
again so you remember to you know are
you kidding me are you serious I mean
that's two different answers it's no and
yes cuz no I'm not kidding you and yes I
am serious you are still slouch is this
supposed to be funny to you is this
supposed to be a joke Breaking Bad News
is not supposed to be funny well I know
that it's under drama watch it thriller
light suspense
yeah Breaking Bad I know it's not a
comedy it's not supposed to be funny
it's like a serious show and you do know
there's a the show is over right so
there's no new episodes so it wouldn't
be under the new cat
don't you get it what where are you
going I'm going back to work I'm so over
this you made me worry for nothing you
made it seem like you were going to give
me bad news and you did it I mean
technically I did give me bad news
remember your neighbors bad news -
goodbye okay fine
gee just just wait okay just I really do
have something important to tell you
where to God Ryan if this is a no it's
not it's not okay
it really isn't look I'm sorry I guess I
just made all these jokes because I I
just I don't know how to break bad news
to people and I just hate seeing people
get upset especially people actually
care about it's part of life Ryan
everyone has to do it I know I can take
it you just have to be honest with me
and stop with the joking around okay
well earlier in the video it wasn't a
joke I lied something really happened to
my parents
oh no no not that are you really
cheating on me no of course not
then what is it well there's good news
and bad news the good news is I already
talked to your boss and he said you
don't have to go back in today given the
circumstances okay what are the
circumstances well that's the bad news
um you know those bad news papers from
earlier what about them they weren't
actually soggy from the rain outside huh
he's firing you right so thank you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers and behind-the-scenes
click on the left if you want to see the
previous video click the one on the
right and if not then you don't have to
do anything just log onto your phone go
on snapchat and check out real