hey guys as most of you know I've been
single for a long time now and as much
as I say it's fine to be single I'm not
gonna lie sometimes I missed especially
when 90% of my closest friends have
girlfriends hey I don't have a
girlfriend I'm not lesbian prove it then
kiss me
gross no lesbian anyway I'm sure a lot
you guys out there can relate when
you're single and all your friends are
in a relationship just makes you want
one even more even if it's unintentional
everytime you see them together it kind
of feel like they're just rubbing it in
your face that you're single Hey
[Music]
Wow okay you guys are just gonna call me
a loser to my floss no we're just
singing now what get it cuz your sing L
a little bit it's all you single people
out there you know what I mean right I
realize that part of the reason why I'm
single is because I have no game
whatsoever and also I spend pretty much
all my time in my room by myself alone
making videos could be part of the
reason why and again I know a lot of you
guys are the same and I took it upon
myself I made it a mission after years
of studying women and men and
relationships and Gophers I don't I
don't know why I don't know I discovered
and created the best techniques and
pickup lines ever invented that will get
you any girl so for all you fellow
losers out there I'm standing up for you
gonna help you I'm gonna teach you I'm
gonna teach you 100 percent effective
techniques I don't know if they're good
or bad yet but they're 100 percent
effective that will get you any girl you
want the first thing you have to master
in order to get girls are the three C's
cool courage confidence when I see a
pretty girl I turn into a complete loser
I don't turn into a loser Mike my inner
loser comes out that's where the first
seat comes in cool you have to play it
cool don't freak out ii see courage one
of the hardest steps when you see a
pretty girl is to go over an approach
her and i'm not gonna lie i used to
chicken out a lot but this is when
courage comes in don't make her away
just need to instantly build up the
courage and just walk right up to her
and once you got those two down all you
need is a third seat
confidence don't ever show that you're
nervous never show weakness yeah yeah
this face is nice I thought come over
here and say that right just be
confident when you're confident anything
you say will work so be alright so maybe
you can't say anything in fact here's a
list of things that you should probably
never say because they don't work trust
me
whoa you got some big feet ass up girl
I like your stubble oh hey we cut the
same Adam's apple hi I'm Ryan Higa wow
this is amazing I could not ask for a
better situation do you think you would
like to maybe introduce me to your
friend I don't know I thought they'd
think it was funny so now you guys got
the three C's down all that's left is
what you have to say tell me what that
was there are a lot of different girls
in this one that's why I created pickup
lines for every single type of girl such
as hot girl pickup lines for hot girls
guys are always trying to come up with
newer smarter pickup lines so it's
actually more original to a hot girl to
give her a lame and obvious one key
point just be different if other guys
are trying too hard do the opposite hey
could I have your number cuz I seem to
have lost mine sure what is this phone
number well how is this supposed to help
me find mine oh my god did you fart what
nope cuz you just blew me away I haven't
heard that one since the third grade
second nevermind it was me
hey I just met you and this is crazy but
here's my number so what aren't you
gonna finish the song that's a song hmm
here's my number here you know this one
nerdy pick-up lines a lot of the coolest
girls are nerd girls that are smart and
into technology and video games all you
have to do here is just play on their
level um excuse me do you haven't I'm an
iOS 6 or later iPhone that I could
borrow I just really need Google Maps
being that I'm completely lost in your
eyes right now hey are you busy tonight
cuz I think you should come over to my
place yeah you know we can have a lamb
party play some counter-strike we're all
obviously be the Counter Terrorist
because you're obviously the terrorist
already wait why you're looking bombed
tonight girl
your difference between you and me about
12 inches that's almost the size of my
feet which are about nine and you know
the difference between your feet and my
feet I said earlier 12 inches which we
all know is the length of a foot and if
I were to take my foot and take a 1 foot
step towards you you know what the
difference between you and me would be
then um zrl know you didn't count the
length of my foot it's like something
like negative 9 my foot would be on your
foot because I'm coming on to you
straight to the point pick up lines some
girls don't like to play games just get
straight to the point
hey what's up girl let me put my opinion
v real quick your pee yeah my pee no my
my D oh okay thanks for letting me put
my pet deer in your van how can I ever
repay you
kiss me straight to the point
insulting at first but aren't really
pick-up lines just make it seem like
you're insulting her at first when you
really aren't that way the next line
will sound amazing ha you must have a
lot of Big Mac meals from mcdonalds
honks scuse me
yeah cuz out of all the girls here
you're number one somewhat racist people
blind sometimes there's gonna be a
language barrier you just have to adapt
do you like the anime one piece you
don't have to speak like that
I speak English you anime one piece hey
Justin Bieber fan pick-up line did you
find out she's a hardcore believer hey
do you like Justin Bieber oh my god I
love Mike
chances are she's underage walk away oh
really cheesy pickup lines these are
specifically meant for girls who think
that pickup lines are cheese I don't
know they don't even know what cheesy
means yet look I know this might seem a
little out of the blue and I know you're
probably fed up with a bunch of guys
coming up to you so I'll keep this brief
I think it would be a good idea if we
were to prom around together unless of
course you prefer to provolone oh my
gosh you're the cutest man a picture
with you have my parmesan and some girls
just hate pickup lines in general
because they hate when guys are
predictable and give them the same old
thing these pickup lines are a little
less predictable and they kind of do the
opposite um
did it hurt what when I fell from heaven
yeah I hear that one before what no when
your ex-boyfriend broke up with you a
month ago yeah and your new boyfriend
broke up with you tonight huh I don't
through hey are you from Tennessee why
cuz I'm the only 10 you see no you're
like a six still above average if I
could rearrange the alphabet I would put
what you and I together
no I mean I would use those letters but
it would be
you are a BITC and h it's overall in
conclusion I think you know how to pick
up girls last thing you have to do is
simple just go for it
oh that's alright and before you know it
you'll go from this your the this face
is nice if I come over here and say that
hi to this hey you like Justin Bieber
he's all right I guess in that case did
it hurt you know when your ex-boyfriend
broke up with you no it's a mutual
breakup oh well I'm well are you from
Tennessee cuz you're on five maybe six
tops well if I could rearrange the other
really you can't so look I'm doing my
best art I'm trying my heart Oh trying
just be yourself
look I just I just like you a lot I saw
you from across the club earlier and I
know you're so pretty and I just I
didn't know what to do or say and I just
froze you know once I got the courage to
come over here I just I started saying
all these pick-up lines from this
dumbass video I watched earlier and huh
just take it easy if you have to watch a
video to be something you're not
girls I'm gonna see right through that
just be yourself
you're right I think you could start
over yeah sure hi I'm Ryan Higa
how could this make it any worse hey you
[Music]
just just felt left out oh just see you
guys later
I don't know whether whether DJ stopped
by