I just finally made like six six figures
from dancing so much there ain't nothing
atop that what do you consider I think
psychology is a young a young
thank you emotional approaches and
welcome back to another episode of off
the pill podcast I'm right you go we
have David Choi in the moderators seat
and Paco right next to me and today we
have a very special guest his name is
Dietrich's Dominick I should say Dominic
d-trix Sandoval currently on TV right
now hmm
okay hello how much longer is it gonna
go for your I mean you're on you've got
that much longer
So You Think You Can Dance judge that's
huge yes thank you thank you is I mean
oppressions say it say it you know no
it's it's incredible because that's like
where I started my entire career and now
I'm back on as a judge judging people in
their lives there mm-hmm nice I mean
this is like I mean I know you already
judged ABDC America's Best Dance Crew
but this is I mean that's not to have to
put that down I'll just tell you know a
lot this this is this is also great
Randy Jackson's watcher now he's like no
come on let's be real I mean that show
has been going before a BDC and it's
still going on it's a it's a sixteen to
you is it a bigger deal uh yeah I think
so just cuz it's right it is it's it's I
mean it's a not to say that a VDC wasn't
yeah but it's fun dude it's like it's
kind of crazy I feel like I shouldn't be
there I'm like uh I don't know it's like
every time I want like I'm there and I'm
judging them I I just remember their
position uh-huh so it's like almost
sound like when you're reliving a moment
it's pretty it's pretty cool
it's way easier and you get paid more on
that side and you do the other side are
you allowed to say that what I hope the
judges would get paid more than the
contestants you know true
mmm yeah we just can't say how much it
was like 11,000 all right that's good to
know
yeah not that much right I mean is it
per episode or just in total I
forever for less your life eleven grand
for the rest of your life you can't do
any other job are you gonna continue
doing that or it's not like a one season
thing yeah its contraction rush was but
for four seasons uh if they continue oh
but that show's been on for how long now
which is like I said if they continue 16
sweet 16 and so if you guys are bored
you guys should go there Monday nights
9 p.m. CET 9 p.m. making that face PT et
those of you that don't know because I
didn't introduce Dom you start off as a
dancer right and we met while you were
on Quest Crew which is the ABDC winner
America's Best Dance Crew winner every
was like who people how America's Best
Dance Crew oh right Oh
older people new generation doesn't
really know what that is okay what they
know so you think so you think you can
dance right
yeah let's still on anyway Don's are off
as a dancer turn youtuber turn into a
television star turned into podcaster
soon if you're doing a bunch of stuff
but I met Dom almost 10 years ago yeah
we should talk about that in 2010 I'll
be official yeah and you were in agents
of secret stuff for our fans who did you
originally have that because right off
like you made like agencies agents of
secret stuff you literally asked me on
the spot and I didn't take you serious
yeah but when you were writing you had
to have had someone no I just thought it
was a funny character it was like the
bad guy who's like kind of crazy and had
it's not like the guy you just hate it's
like you know he has jokes and stuff
like when we first met the day after you
asked me you're like eh you wondering
why my film agent secret stuff and I
literally thought you were playing I was
like come on man you playing I don't
remember asking you I mean I listen like
it was like being in a video alright I
remember asking me that how do you think
became that I mean I know we wanted you
to do it but I don't remember that how
it happened but yeah I mean and then you
did it
yeah then we became friends yeah my
youtube career yep because of this man
Paco
yeah that's why he started no I started
YouTube because of you man
did did you hell yeah I think as you had
some dance stuff up already uh no I
literally I mean I think like real
yeah as in like a dance room my mom no
you're the one that inspired me and I
have my story but apparently you don't
agree with it but what is the story yeah
I'd love to hear okay so this is out
went in my head okay he's gonna say no
it didn't go that way doesn't even know
what the story let's hear it let's see
how much like we hang out that I
actually take it serious and then you
just forget maybe alright alright I saw
the beginning what are your stories 2009
alright
Los Angeles I stay North Hollywood sorry
to be exact not 2009-2010 time losing my
my my story
anyways Ryan goes hey dude you real are
about doing YouTube and mind you at this
point I just finally made like six six
figures from dancing so much there ain't
nothing atop that right I was like I
love this like this this is something I
think I could do and he's like you
should do YouTube and I was like that's
something I don't think I would want to
do you know cuz your boy is making some
money and he goes is that the real
reason why I was like what's a big part
of it like you know I'm able to make my
op dance he goes alright what I'm gonna
do is I'm going to show you my month of
December is 2009 his month of December
he's like I'm not showing you this to
boast I'm showing you this because this
could be your future and I was like wow
why is your voice so deep and he's like
and he's like here check it out and I
was like oh he showed me is it like 300
racks first 2009 he's only don't ever
say that to anybody
that's true okay fine I was like 289 but
but he was like he I was like oh uh
camp
let me get camera I started making
videos and I ended up instead just doing
for the man I'm falling in love with the
craft and that's the story yeah you're
right I don't agree I don't remember any
of that
I remember Greg brought up like when
you're asking about camera gear and he's
like telling you stuff is like why you
know is good camera gear for ya the
Canon 7d he was big
yeah he was jealous because at the time
it's like riot like whatever Ryan said I
was like yes I will do it like you're
you know the master you're teaching me
and he was like you should get a camera
I used this one so I just got a canon 17
I didn't know how to turned on but uh
you know Greg was really envy of that
cuz he wanted a camera that was his
dream it was his dream
Gregg the guy with the moustache one who
edits for us he that was his dream
camera and couldn't afford it and then
you come in with no experience you buy
his dream camera and that's why he was
salty yeah
jealousy party for one Greg Wow you made
a lot of use with that camera
you started YouTube and you created like
a huge channel oh yeah but big part of
that's cuz of Ryan he just would like
the videos back then and then my channel
exploded and yeah thanks Ryan you did
your own thing I mean you did your own
thing and you built your kind of built
your following but you also had that you
were still in the dance community like
heavily in the dance community and
that's why you've got your TV show but
not your show but you judged on
America's Best Dance Crew yeah and I
remember when they brought me in they're
like oh we're bringing you in for a to
be judgement makers Best Dance Crew
because like we feel like your digital
following is a huge you know outlet and
I was like again that's because of right
Ryan
Brian's basically my Jesus Christ he
saved me and I Bernie Goetz smited my
career you're gonna get smited anyway
what I find amazing what I find amazing
is that you know you're you're a dancer
right that's what you start off as and
you're still known as a dancer you're
still in that community that you created
such a like a successful career centered
around dancing and that's something that
there's so many dancers in the world
that wish they were in your position it
can build what you've built for yourself
like what how did you do that like what
kind of mentality do you need to have or
work ethic to build a career off dancing
of all things uh it's a real question
isn't it yep I have low expectations
like I think I grew up at such like a
bot like a I got a low standard as far
as like quality of life I don't know
everybody's perspective is different but
like I grew up not really having
anything and the idea of like like a job
of like a dream job at that time
probably something like a claims
adjuster or something something that
like is equal to like what my families
are doing just we grew up in a low
standard so I felt like because of that
if I just keep like trying to surpass
that then who knows what can happen so
it's almost like I'm kind of climbing
this ladder of like what the is
happening with my life and I'm just
still going just because I didn't expect
to get this when you say sorry sorry to
interrupt you but when you say low
standard what is it that you didn't grow
up with money or you just didn't have
standards so the truth comes out all
right David you just just trying to get
into the trunk dig deeper Gashi alright
so I was born in Sacramento California
alright and my mom grew up in my mom at
the time was on welfare well thanks Dave
and she was like you know paper Subway's
characters I never established this bond
feeling the Holy Spirit so let me speak
mofo go so anyway so anyway I think like
to be honest yeah my mom did grow up
like we just grew up strict on funds and
I was just like the we just didn't have
a lot and I just felt like dance was one
of the one things that I think any
especially a b-boy at that time like we
just got all types of hate from you know
everything cuz there was no literally
like overall way to make money off of
breaking and then they came off the show
called So You Think and danced in 2005
and then like literally just taking that
opportunity and essentially just always
showing up to opportunities even if I
felt like I wasn't ready I think was the
one thing that helped develop everything
I have you know that and Ryan Higa see
that I mean I do remember telling you to
do YouTube and the reason was because of
your personality it wasn't I mean like
obviously people there's dancers right
and dancers I mean you know the biggest
you can get to a certain degree without
having you know branding behind it is
like a backup dancer to like a really
famous Justin Bieber or somebody right
well I don't know I may be teaching but
you kind of went with that route you
went with your success with dancing but
you used it to create Dietrich's the
personality you know I mean and I think
that
isn't that what you were trying to teach
with your passionate project mmm
passionate yeah cuz it's more than just
okay become a great dancer right yeah I
think it's like overall what is the
question like I mean I think is it is it
just what was it was more of a question
it was more of a statement of like why
you are where you are is because you
didn't just follow the road of just
becoming a great dancer and then you
know teaching or becoming a backup
dancer like you you
the reason why they picked you up is
because you built your personality yeah
and I think overall it's like a big part
of it was growth I think I think I've
always been obsessed with this is like a
really answer but like since the very
beginning and to go to also answer you
Ryan your statement which wasn't a
question but to kind of go back to just
answer both those things is I was
obsessed with growth of like learning
about whatever I was doing or if I
started something new the growth of that
and then what that just became I guess
the more you grow you just are able to
offer more stuff to this world and then
if you're decent enough people just pay
you to do that's kind of the goal
yeah is it fair to say that you are
obsessed with becoming better at
whatever you try to do oh hell yeah just
because I thought I constantly think I
suck and I feel like it's just uh that's
part of anyway like I think any creative
they just you know always I just feel
like I'm just obsessed with knowledge
knife like I just need to keep getting
better and you feel like that you did
that with dance - I'm still doing it
with that look at all these young cuz
there's so many young kids online is my
father killing like these little
eight-year-old kids right I know when
you see them what do you what do you
feel um
feelings for natal when you see these no
okay so like what do you how do you
react so I I work with a lot of these
younger kids too especially like the
ones that are moving out of here because
they're so dope on I I feel like the
beautiful thing about them is that they
haven't gone through enough life stuff
to realize the restrictions and fears
that life can teaches you to be afraid
to fail you know I'm saying so they're
gonna learn how to they're gonna start
something see the standard at an early
age and then just go after that and then
I
for me it's inspiring I feel like it's
like it's really really dope to see
these kids picking up stuff and being
freaking masters at it hella hella early
[ __ ] and then and then you feel like
you need to become better than them no
where are you go
no because we were talking about how you
are obsessed with growth and when you
see young kids who are surpassing your
skill sets or whatever yeah you wish you
had when you were that age not only they
surpass their skill sets over here David
I still get I still get down so get down
in my day when I watch you dad you're a
master you're a master of your craft
there's not a lot of people in this
world who can move like you that sounds
weird but like we do a replay of this
we're talking and and like I'm just
wondering from you know your perspective
as a master of your craft doing it for
like over a decade and have you know
your judge on shows like when you see it
like do you feel like a little bit of
competitiveness with these young kids
like not that you're gonna directly
compete with them but you know like for
me example as a musician when I see
these young kids I'm like damn I wish I
was as good as them I still feel that
now you want to talk about it I guess
for me not really just because uh for me
I get excited about the the future of
the generation if anything I always like
to help out on the the that the
dancers don't know about like how to
monetize it on how to create a life
longevity lifestyle of it or if you're a
young kid a big part of it is you have
all the movement and I'm pop I know you
can vouch for this - is these kids
haven't gone through enough like life
emotional to like really understand
why you're dancing yet does that meaning
to the motion because you got to go
through some crazy to be able to
like express dance in a way that people
can translate it that don't understand
dance right so for me with dances I
always try to make dance secondary to
whatever I'm doing meaning like what is
the message I'm trying to to say or what
is it that I can get the average person
at home that doesn't care about Dan's to
want to watch that or showcase that to
other people I don't
about dance so with these young dancers
it's like they have all the amazing
facilities and they'll destroy me at my
craft physically but when it comes to
emotion and be able to tell story that's
what I would love to help out for them
because I feel like if I was that age
and someone help me with that it should
be like you're able to like almost get
it even faster does that make sense so
it's like the why but so how do you
teach like you said they don't have the
experience how you teach someone like
that well what do you do would he tell
them well I I said it was about like
experiencing emotional you gotta hurt
yeah yeah I just I beat the out of
them you spoke to both my ninja milk oh
my god
emotionally ruining the moment oh my god
there's so many cheap references no
one's gonna get but what I'm saying is I
could kind of relate because in music
you know Dave's trying to speak [ __ ]
go for it go like you could tell if
someone's singing from a place of
experience versus something that they
just are just singing for example for
example you say to me you made that song
up right that's original
yeah so you guys if you guys want to
play that you're gonna have to pay me
royalties royalties well I mean really
nice attitude
this is B you know this speaks to you're
funded really interesting your person is
it your personality type though and I
and I think I've told you about this too
is like and I think this is also what
makes you great is that you you do
always want to get better and that's why
you got really good at dance and then
you find something else that you really
want to be good at like singing like you
were trying to take you're never really
sang before but you've been taking like
classes for like eight months right oh
yeah yes yes yes I mean with everything
you do if you get into something you get
obsessed I get obsessed for example like
our friendship right mmm I'm obsessed
with bringing back what we had
you know I feel like Ryan I feel like
since the ytf days you know it wasn't it
wasn't it wasn't you know it was you
know but I feel like I want like our
planet it was turning into a beautiful
tree in the forest of great friendships
and I feel like we was blossoming and
then like if you were the water and I
was the Sun it's like I want to be a
better son for your water and I feel
like we can build our tree a friendship
again so with that being said I study a
lot about friendships and stuff and
wanting to grow those things and Dom
doesn't drink
he's never drank before in his life he
doesn't do drugs he's very clean have
you ever done drugs before Ryan
introduced me to adderall so yeah yeah
so you just brought up ytf very quickly
there's no punch to that phrase I'm
sorry what what did you have fun at ytf
like can you tell us about your
experiences I had a blast ytf I think we
all did it in some certain point it just
ended kind of funky you know that I
don't know
no I thought why can't was great I think
it was like we had an awesome run and it
was like the first of its kind and again
I got a praise Ryan because essentially
Ryan put his brand his own personal
brand aside for six friends I'm pretty
sure I like everybody did but I think
everybody did everybody did to an extent
but the Ryan was like the the one that
like literally birthed a lot of our Kurt
our pushes and careers on YouTube and
thanks man
well I mean keV already had a career you
guys had careers it's just we together
it helped everyone including myself yeah
like that was like that was like what
are they called team ten before that
existed right I mean we didn't do that
we had I thought people like did that
though to a certain degree like we lived
in the same building the haunted
building where everybody lives now in
North Hollywood you thought I'm sorry I
never thought it was there's a couple
weird things dude there's weird
in that building people who live there
or room you heard other stories I mean
our room and then Kevin Victor's room
why didn't Kevin Victor were haunting
there oh well there's there's there's a
lot of people living there now but
anyway we kind of did that there's
certain degree I don't think there was
other groups before us no it would be
cool I thought it was dope yeah yeah I
thought it was the idea was there would
you guys ever bring it back
whitey yeah that's not my I mean I've
been down uh right I don't even know
what that means like oh why every means
yesterday today forever I mean like just
like what like touring I don't want to I
don't want a tour what if we made a show
we could do a show I could do one you
don't have to do it but what if we made
a show oh yeah was that the original
[ __ ] season why we've made whites yeah
yeah the whole goal was to that we
didn't have to do it later
like we don't have to keep doing these
shows cuz we're gonna get old eventually
yeah we didn't really do that we didn't
follow through so that was why Tia did
you guys what did you watch ytf Parker
come here let's say nothing I'm letting
you guys kind of just like talk and
everything you guys have a lot going on
I don't want to interrupt the flow just
okay stop stop Paco's pursuing a career
in comedy so yeah stand up so he's right
he's right no I've got good ones
let me read your nose I don't ever start
with knock-knock okay I take that as a
challenge but Dom you have an Emmy you
want an Emmy like you're you're one of
the very few you just won an Emmy Award
it's kind of like any award they kind of
just sit there and develop dust okay but
did you ever dream of even winning one
of these like did you actually see
yourself no no definitely not so yeah
that was in 2016 that yeah question won
an Emmy in hail no like I've I don't
even think that we thought that was
possible when we were doing that show to
be completely honest so no I never
thought that that's crazy
where is it what do you do do you like
collecting yes yeah I don't know like I
don't know you guys feel about awards
but I feel like awards are like the one
thing that it's like it doesn't matter
how like basic or how amazing it is they
all kind of do the same thing and click
dust I mean I maybe I was able to charge
a little bit more for teaching but I
don't know yeah it's just a resume thing
right I guess that's the incredibly
that's a real award yeah that's not like
you're getting like some randoms like oh
we feel bad for the Asians and the
Oscars that up so let's give these
Asians dudes and award yeah but it's
still like people still think it's that
it's still connected
it's an Emmy you know you're right I'm
so much better than you guys you are in
that respect for sure do people know
you're Asian you're happy people know
your fans know oh you know right yeah I
think so you're half Filipino 68.7% - oh
you took a test yeah and uh the one
where I did my own math and looking at
my family um so uh yeah but I think it's
about that but the rest is uh etiqa
Etica is Ryan's jokes can you tell us
more about passionnate yeah so I started
a company called passion 8 is that a
play on passionate oh my good
you're pretty yeah it is thank you
you're the first one ever point that out
but I didn't I was just wondering no
because it might not have been yeah
passionate is basically uh passionate I
created a company to essentially help
the next generation of dancers or any
dancers that feel like they want to get
like the level up of their careers not
just like physically but mentally so
they can have the same type of outcome
that I feel like I was lucky and
grateful enough to have that I didn't
expect I was gonna have so yeah get
passionate calm slash that's it I think
it's the passion is calm just a slash
I'm gonna talk about some of the recent
projects that you did cuz you're working
with is it Logan
Oh bigger logistics we should roll clip
of that right now I don't and we're
barraged no let's use my video
right okay even then it's like someone
okay who is this person
oh dude who is this person oh my god you
know really I don't know so you know
you're talking about earlier this kid
that like changing the game and dance
like so she's like literally to me she's
well she's 16 now but I've noticed and
she was started probably like nine or
something but we did this show called
roller roller dance season to last
season and she was on the team that that
I was able to choreograph that one and
her name is Logan she was on the lab and
I was a girl
yeah Logan's a girl B girl logistics is
there be a people name and she's like
completely blown up like crazy over this
last year not just like industry wise
but asked like like B girl wise and like
all styles dance wise but what was your
question Paco was just like what you've
been doing with project late because I
know that you guys just did a video
together right yeah we just did a video
who you are by oh that was her oh yeah
that what you see it yeah oh yeah you
commented yeah thanks dude yeah thank
you uh again a big part of it was
because it was her and I wrote the idea
down and I pitched it to her and I was
like this is not gonna happen unless
it's you because when I was creating I
just kept picturing her and she was down
to trust me that piece and boom I for me
I think it's the best piece I've ever we
I've ever got to create up and to date
and again odd to say big part of it
because she is so amazing if you haven't
seen it then you can go check it out
I know that was meaningful to you
because you're the one who introduced me
to Jessie J right oh really that song
yeah that's that specifically that song
before she became Jessie J the the pop
artist she was yeah see - yeah we used
to listen to that same song it was a
youtube video it wasn't even like she's
on stage it wasn't even like a produce
thing and she was seeing who you are and
like you would listen to that over and
over and over to the point that I like
memorized it right so I knew that if
you're gonna be something good you're
gonna what you memorize the song good
well I mean I memorize about knowing do
it anything I would rather be the part
where she yells out big okay anyway we
were watching I knew it meant a lot to
you because you never really did well
you've done some stuff to it but you
never really had the fact that you were
gonna showcase
song it had to have meant a lot to you
yeah how you felt about it
yeah it's a beautiful song and the piece
was about I think like young girls that
struggle with what to post on Instagram
if like people do this all the time in
general not just young girls but I feel
like young girls that I have heard about
especially from her like in the lab like
that's big that people struggle with was
like as a young girl like what do I
produce that will maintain my like
self-love and like putting that at risk
for the idea of getting more likes for
more followers so I felt like if I was
able to tell a story that can help them
with that I'll be able to change lives
and Logan made it came to life so yeah
and I thought it'd be weird cuz I've
always want to do that piece but I feel
like if I play the young girl it would
be better and wouldn't wouldn't take
away from the song yeah and Trixie was
she was booked yeah okay well well
that's your girl character yeah I don't
know yeah so you you're kind of on
hiatus right from posting YouTube videos
yeah obviously you're doing a lot of
other things passionnate and then you're
judging so you think indents often do
you shoot once a week
Oh once a week once a week so it's not
that I doing in between those being lazy
no you're not lazy uh working on music
okay so you're doing stuff yeah but it's
just taking forever what does that mean
like suck it seems no I've been
working on music like the last almost
year now mm-hmm and because I I've
always wanted to a musical like a film
musicals that to you before so I figured
I'd learn how to at least do basic
so I can write it for not even me for
other people mhm
but that's like a longevity dream you've
been taking lessons too vocal vocal
lessons right yeah cuz I went to uh this
guy I'm David Choi once and I was like
yo David can't remember singing he's
like I don't do that I play piano I was
like you already say that no he didn't
oh I know you did go to him though yeah
one point oh yeah
well we're actually supposed to work on
more stuff together but that was again
my fault I'm not ready yet
David I want to be at your standard I'm
ready for you whenever you're ready
I'm ready now I was waiting for the
punch timing right downtime hard time
all right so you're working to music
yeah you're working on well obviously
you're doing the show you're doing are
you still doing passion 8 yeah we're
doing a next summer we'll end up being
the next one we do okay we're gonna like
pry something on clinic then a clinic I
just thought of like a meeting or
something oh no I mean like a bath you
know basketball clinic you like going oh
yeah yeah for like a week and then do
something in yeah it's just uh it's like
a weekend long thing and I think we're
gonna happen yeah yeah it's kind of cold
mmm cuz my day 3 everybody's weird yeah
it's a good way to turn people off
though I'm gonna go in there no but I
kind of like it takes a while to find
the right people that come and take the
experience too because a big part of it
is just like not just feel submitting
but it's like having the right people
that really want that because it's like
we go and really deep as far as like the
dance ability itself the psychology the
business aspect of it and I think it's
just it's it's for everybody essentially
ever all types of dancers like any but
more importantly like if people really
want to live off this craft and I think
this is probably the best live off the
craft of dances the best uh I guess
clinic you can like you could take to
really have that outcome now and what
better place then to learn from a master
who's pioneered his own career you're so
sweet thank you man I guess you think
that of me but I I don't really think
that I'm still learning it's it's a fact
um always learning though oh yeah right
that's kind of it like I mean gets to be
a pioneer like you've mastered music but
you're still learning about it right
he's like no like God for a while yeah
it's those are true words of a master
Ryan you've mastered the art of comedy
and YouTube videos no I haven't really
yes really
so there's the rest of us all say that
maybe 2005 to 2010 YouTube comedy
specifically mm maybe I mastered that
you've also mastered the art of being
humble that is an art well you know what
we will be right back because
I need to take a shishi break so that's
P for all the people I don't know a just
to remember and we're back gives any
brands for this this nope
okay this brand this episode this
episode of aw off the pill is brought to
you by a ninja milk and you can get your
local ninja milk online we're gonna
leave a link in the description box
below
go get them right now they're hot I mean
they're cold but there's they're hot you
know all right we'll work on I didn't
even ask him to do that but thank you
you're welcome
alright I'm going to ask my for my check
now mm-hmm
I will send it to you and I will send
you some cases to the right address what
was the address again it's one two eight
one two five four - OH five four
you're making it harder on yourself
right now they're continuing 27 that's
my social security number
what if that is someone's real it
definitely is why they might be one of
the first people ever like Jesus's
cousin so we recently had Bethenny on
the podcast mota bethany mota you know
what she's hot friend she's hot
yes she is a thirties she what she said
I didn't watch them so as a Storify you
guys met she's definitely yeah - because
I didn't know she she's my better 2/3
but so obviously because Beth is you
know famous in her own right a lot of
the questions are about Beth oh come and
because obviously the other episode -
right we talked about you as well
a lot of number remember what you
made for her on her birthday
of course you'd remember oh yeah
the bedroom yeah the childhood room
that's creepy
it is now that we say it like this like
if I were to show you guys the room it
wouldn't be
as creepy there was a thoughtful idea
okay there's a reason for that
this is your chance to explain your side
because we feel like in our relationship
where our best selves when we're coming
from a place of playing and like having
like a fearless type of like attitude
and state and we feel like that those
times were always when we were kids so
we always try to maintain like a
childish like playful type of
relationship so I decided to make her
childhood room so if she ever felt like
she needed to relive it or you know be
in that state or if is that time of the
month she can go inside the room she can
go inside Rule three she can go inside
of her room and just like okay I
remember what it was like my friend I
mean it was a good the thought was there
right yeah and I actually I'm very proud
of him I'm very proud of the guy still
there yeah yeah it's at your house yeah
it's at my place I just took one of the
rooms and made her her room and she she
still uses it for storage but it's I
yeah its storage it's actually like well
thought out though like when you showed
us to that room it was like wow there's
a lot of thought put into this you did a
lot of research watch I you saw it yeah
that's how I found out yeah oh yeah it's
really quick it took me a while it's
cool it was cool you had to like uh you
have to look for a tv/vcr
two-in-one right they used to have that
by the way for you guys watching this
not knowing these have TVs adviye
like a v8 like a VHS player mm-hmm a VCR
and a DVD player and I had a fight and
it took forever and I was like the one
thing I was like this is gonna be hard
to get mm-hmm but yeah we found it
Facebook marketplace do you guys ever
argue about little things about like do
you guys ever argue or is it just yeah
we're not Jesus Christ dating Jesus
Christ no I mean but you guys have
probably still argue what do you guys
disagree about like um well you know
it's like a common one and maybe she'll
say something else but if I could common
thing we disagree about is how we're not
enough for the other person like you're
your own self yeah like we feel like oh
wow we argue over the idea that I'm not
for her and then she argues over the day
she's not enough for me we always want
to be better for that person so as more
like an internal argument that's out
ternal it's almost healthy don't shoot I
mean it's better to have that that yeah
right oh yeah placing blame and like and
I can do better
oh yeah yeah I used to place babe babe
babe
hashtag no well I used to place blame a
lot but I feel like that's why my past
relationships didn't work out you know
speaking of which Ryan I feel like I
feel like we came to a place in our
relationship where I was blaming you a
lot for the paint and I realized it was
really just inside of me and I just want
to say I'm so sorry callbacks write that
down I call back but whether or not it
stays in the video it's up to you but
just call back writing anything um but
yeah I think it's healthy to argue in
any relationship I think it's like it's
gonna happen but I think more
importantly to know how it goes after
that and if you guys can grow from it is
where the importance is do you guys hang
out a lot yes every every day or every
day yeah are both busy people so yeah
we're busy like singing and like but
she's good I don't think is it because I
heard her sing yeah it's beautiful right
it's just really good she's super good
yeah uh and then she'll be like I'm not
good not like and then you think like oh
I suck I hurt you I'm really yeah
so I'm like damn I must really suck cuz
you don't think what did she say what
did she think about or what'd she say to
you about your singing she usually does
this and I think that means you she
likes it makes a face no like I think
she's very supportive but I'm like I
mean I'm still new to it right mhm but I
I think she's very supportive overall
just to listen to it all day it's
probably really annoying for it's like I
imagine if she was just practicing her
dancing she's like babe like oh you
be supportive wait hold on so as a
dancer when someone's practicing in
front of you and they're not very good
does that annoy you
no oh I
actually the thing with me is like I
want to help the person I get better but
I think that's what the problem is like
we're singing I like I want her to help
me but she doesn't would you like her to
I will babe how many learn how to sing
better did you ever ask her did help you
yeah oh yeah
and what she usually say then
[Music]
I can do that I'd like my ATD is bad uh
where did that go
I usually ask her to help me but I think
she's like always like she probably
started of hearing me she honestly just
feels like she's not good enough to help
me to be honest really yeah we
completely honest but I can listen to
her I got to get better what do you like
most about her I'm sure there are a lot
of things but yeah I was deep things
right away but I authentically move she
like inside her moral value I think I
was it brought me to her initially to is
like this her to amount of self-love
that she had for herself I felt like oh
man that's cool that's like that's like
a really cliche in deep but um I love
the fact that she yeah I just turns me
on that she that she's confident in
herself yeah yeah she has like not in a
boastful way but she just sounds like
this like she wants to be a better
person constantly and I felt like with
my past relationships I've liked in
relationships in general in order to be
best for that person you can't gotta be
your best self I almost like it to be
selfish to be selfless type of thing so
that yeah I think I think that
and she's bomb you see her oh look at
your boy get another the young the young
but thank you baby it's great no I I
mean you obviously really really love
her and and when she was talking about
you really loves you
I see you guys is a great beautiful
couple
oh wow thanks I guess a question that I
have since you know you came up from
hard times and and at where you are now
maybe you can give advice to you know
your past self or even like other kids
who are in this area that aren't maybe
able to get into passionate and they
just you know they're looking for like
advice from somebody who's made it out
of hard times oh yeah my past self I'd
probably say continue
a little bit of gingivitis
self-deprecation write that down don't
touch my paper yeah and I think to the
just the person out there that feels
like it's kind of like really really
tough which I believe it's it's tough
for everybody is just different types of
how tough is I think the ability to play
and look at everything as an opportunity
instead of an obligation really helps a
lot I think with that growth and if you
become obsessive about something like a
craft and it takes you away from like
whatever pain could be I keep investing
in that and then also be okay with a
pain you know because I fly gets the key
ingredient to be able to to heal it to
be to be honest so I feel like if I had
background music it would help a lot
more sorry this is all we have hey y'all
these guys are down well I'm here to let
you guys know that the only great thing
about down is that you know what up is
alright because without down there is no
up its life was just always about up
there never be down and you would never
understand that up it's just it's just
up there you have nothing to judge it on
so you got to thank the Downs especially
if you're thanking us now make sure your
thumbs up this video characters you you
believe they're like losing is important
oh hell yeah for me at least I don't
know I mean I'm all you guys have done
great things in your life in your
careers for me I've been I thought the
one thing that's made my whole life
possible is the idea of losing and
failing so without it again I don't
think you would really understand what
the other side is it's kind of like
heaven right they describe heaven as
this place of like perfection and then
you really think about perfect and if
this this world was perfect how would
you know what it is without having the
opposite right so there's like a beauty
to the not being perfect cuz everything
was perfect then inhale it be perfectly
dark
so then he's like oh I don't know how to
judge it so I'm just there right so it's
kind of like that I just look at
everything is like oh the beauty behind
the up is or one thing is the opposite
of it because you would never know what
that is
deep hashtag deep do you believe there
is a heaven
I believe this is heaven especially
sitting with three angels that's right
even you Paco or an angel write that
down
[ __ ] I'm sorry no it'll be good
awesome
you're giving him a mall right now use
all of it yeah you want to get into
these already this is like weird for me
because I usually want to ask like you
guys questions go for it's Karma do you
guys think there's a heaven do you think
there's a heaven David I believe there's
a heaven yeah yeah I believe in some I
mean form of it I believe in the
afterlife
oh yeah I do too I do too I agree you
too even some something I don't know
what that's called but I think there's
something you're like agnostic yeah not
not what's the other one where you don't
know stick believes in if there's
something there's a being yeah I know
which one I would say agnostic what does
the one not not atheist yeah so agnostic
about you Paco um I don't know man it's
weird
he's a pastor's kid yeah oh you lost
your virginity early didn't you know at
the age of 26 actually that's early for
me oh wow the our question for you then
was the expectation in standard at which
your childhood was was that like did you
feel like you always had to live up to
like what a pastor's son is supposed to
be uh in a way yeah actually learn more
of how to act well I'm staying away from
you maybe you should go into some
Twitter questions oh go for it that's a
good
that's a good transition there's a fan
you if Z Wayne says asks would you
rather know how you died or when you die
and why neither I mean you don't want to
know no cuz I'm excited for the surprise
but Jordan oh you're dead but if I had
to choose one oh wait wait I'm art is
this the premise that I'm dead already
sure okay I'd rather know oh no when
you're alive yeah like right now okay
would you rather know like right now how
you die or when like you're gonna let's
say it's like I'm gonna die in three
months versus I'm going to die by a car
crash which if I had to choose one I
guess when yeah I think I would use that
more mm-hmm cuz you could do stuff yeah
what would you do depends on the time so
if I would you still be judging say the
mean dance it depends do I make it that
long like give me a date and I'll take
three months left it's always do you
know subjective time yeah three months
left yeah I was on a lot of time I was
still judge mm-hmm and I would still
finish this podcast a we made it on the
list honesty so sweet yeah okay I mean I
I mean that's not really the question I
just kind of took you somewhere else but
I mean that's interesting
no that's what you guys do I don't want
to know when for sure when right yeah
it's more beneficial you can use that
yeah I would probably dude I don't know
what I would want to do actually mmm it
depends on the time I feel like mm-hmm
what feels like you're gonna die at 178
you Mike oh a long time yeah that's
true okay oh shoot what would you do
close you do pao cashews what if I had
only what I would choose time as well
time yeah David I would choose time ya
know so we're all the same bore yeah hmm
mmm okay well on to the next question
from uh betters unite I wonder I think
she's our fan
do you and Beth ever play pranks on each
other no but I feel like I feel like uh
no we don't but maybe I want to start
now hmm I like you prank garden a lot
you prank garden a lot no not really
like when you post up on your Instagram
we kind of like it's not really a prank
or she's kind of a dick yeah it's so
funny
mm-hmm so that's kind of like a prank
yeah I guess so but it's like she's she
knows about it yeah yeah oh he fakes
pranks Frank it's not a prank
it's just truth I'm a fake all right no
no no next question CP Valerie what's
your favorite and least favorite about
making choreography the favorite part
would probably just be able to produce a
message I've like a lot of people that
can help a lot of people Oh Shay but
it's so real honest um let's see and the
worst part is probably like the
self-doubt maybe that comes with making
stuff like like especially if you're so
protective over like if you have a good
reason why and you're like you become
like a little bit like man asked me like
perfect and perfect so I don't have that
as much anymore it feels like um but
yeah I would say those two things do you
feel like when you're creating
choreography for yourself versus other
people do you feel more of that pressure
on when you're performing it or when
someone else is performing it I feel
more pressure if it's for me then I do
for the other person because for me the
other person is actually a lot easier
and I get to see it where like with me
it's like I feel like I can't see myself
doing it and I already feel whack so
much like the pressures like for me
would be just a hire to make it because
it's just like also my ability sucks
it's gonna create around the what do you
mean like right now like I'm not just
good at dancing as I used to be as far
as like what I can do not ladies
creating creating choreography yeah go
away that's in your head right uh yeah
but it is for yourself it's like I feel
like I'm more limited on what I can say
with my body worth other people
well usually people I choose it's like
they have more to say and I can get the
message in my head that I want the world
to know through their their uh their
bodies like AB yeah there's a lot larger
than yours yeah yeah yeah so um I guess
this is a question that I have since
we're talking about choreography and
kind of your art yeah I'll do here I'll
do your solos thank you um but also if
you could only choose one
I guess creative aspect and outlet what
would you pick because you're you're
actually so multi-talented you mean like
it's annoying like crafts well you said
you think you're into singing right now
yeah but then you I know but you you
dance and you pretty much like I mean
like you said you're always learning but
you conquered it I mean you've hit the
tier right like I'm like the top tier of
what a dancer could be like what's the
higher
what's higher than what you've done
become the judge on the biggest dance
show
there's something really higher than
that right I don't know maybe all right
I think so I mean well what I'm asking
is if you're at that tier right like the
highest here in my perspective it's
almost not as fun right because with
singing it's more interesting because
there's so much new things to learn and
I feel like you just like learning so I
guess went back to POC was question kind
of went off track um what is what would
you pick I mean would it still be dance
oh uh if I had to choose right now
yeah it probably choreographing because
I feel like if it was like one thing
that I can help more people with it
would probably be choreographing pieces
then making music or making people laugh
does that make sense so cuz I feel like
right now the the choreographer I kind
of just fell into being a choreographer
there's nothing that I really took
serious but I felt it I kind of to be
honest easy and I feel like because it's
so easy it's not as fun because I want
to feel struggle when I make stuff does
that make does that make sense so
choreographing like I feel like I would
help more people out that way so I'd
probably coat that okay well oh that was
a good answer yes that's great like you
need that struggle that sorry that you
don't feel like you've conquered it
because once you've conquered it then
you're like I'm done yeah and I feel
like I mean there's still like a
struggle in creating and core
but it's it's a lot I think it's because
I've been around it so long I've been
doing it so long I mean it Ryan's kind
of similar like probably like you know
what you have to do and you know what
you need to do and it's where is there
like growth in it or like at one point
in time and again I think you can
constantly grow but you gotta want and
do that type of things so that's what I
love singing because you know when
you're this bad then you can just have
you just keep going wing and then you
know one day you won't be as bad that's
better
wasn't getting better it is better than
what I remember yes it's a lot better I
have a question I'm so you know as a
dancer you need to be in shape you do
you do you feel like dancers should
workout do yoga that type of stuff or is
dancing enough would you say yeah Paco
it's not like it used to be when we were
dancing like you'd be a little too lazy
to eat the dancers now are crazy
man like they're I like running every
morning they're their diets are freaking
Stern their training mind and body
learning from some of the greatest
people all over the world and a big part
of it too is that they have the standard
after their palm because of the phone
but I would recommend that especially if
you're like going for it now
no like no matter what dance taught you
got to be like if every yeah I mean it's
in the Olympics now people are
definitely already big crazy break know
there yet dance actually ballroom and
breaking b-boying and breaking is now in
the Olympics junior and adult divisions
that's crazy right that's pretty crazy
so ain't like week they can't have our
dyes that they use do you know the spam
musubi is in the tuna hotdogs for $2 20
cents a am/pm ain't gonna work no more
like that unless you're b-boy Morris but
that is cut you know that's like in
every sport right like over the years
every sport they get better and better
like someone just broke some kid just
broke Michael Phelps his records right
yeah a bunch of his records and like kid
yes I'm cool or something yeah something
like that and then like you know compare
basketball now versus like 50 years ago
Oh Naz is like you're about to say Oh
Braun or Michael Jordan who is that okay
well that's I'm going even further but
like it's it's a whole nother level of
like athleticism sprinting you know
people used to run marathons in like an
hour
like slower I don't know what the real
I'm making that up yeah I know yeah like
over time people are getting better and
better at stuff and at what point I mean
there's so there's the aspect that you
have to offer is that there's it's not
just physical right yeah in terms of
like I mean I think it's gonna like
improve what I ask is what we what David
and I talked about with music of how
like David loves real quote unquote real
music you love you love like EDM and
stuff like that too but like like
there's a difference between like the
art of music and then the like formula
yeah like the formula basically so what
do you consider good I think psychology
is 80% and I think physical ability is
actually 20 so these so you're saying
these kids have the physical yeah I
think a lot of kids and then like well
logistics is the one that's where it's
like she's very stern on growth of mind
and I think any something be always
coming out right now is that there have
a strong balance between mental growth
on top of physical growth and I think
with any craft you could tell the
difference when someone's like like
LeBron James I I think it's like a big
part obviously to his physical but his
mind is like super like brilliant and
he's able to take advantage of both
those things because I think also to
your body is secondary to your mind I
think your mind is the center point to
operating your body so I think just
taking advantage of your brain I think
was a huge part for me at least wife
like I have a lot of received a lot of
outcome for a lot of things that I felt
like I maybe didn't really deserve
compared the person that was physically
what you used to say all the time like
oh I'm not the best breaker
not even close that's choreographer but
you were smart enough to combine the two
and use it and use your personality to
create the success you have yeah yeah
yeah yeah you're aware of that that's
what you did right yeah I guess that's
yeah yeah I think the mind is very very
important um again I don't know how you
feel David but to while you're on that
subject do you feel like if some
not in a good mental state or maybe they
just broke up with someone do you feel
like when they dance it's different than
if they were in a happy relationship uh
it's definitely be different it's just
whether or not other people will enjoy
it or if they'll enjoy it but I do
believe it it is different I also
believe that that type of pain used
correctly it will end up being something
really brilliant mmm because there's
like a sense of like emotional high and
I think with any high emotion it's a lot
easier to create with those types of
things
just because it's like you need to get
it out no it's almost like a must yeah
that's good advice again anything you
want to plug out there other than your
TV show that you're currently on So You
Think You Can Dance since I eat EAP well
is it 9 p.m. or 9 p.m. Mondays on Fox
mmhmm et/pt
there you go check out Dom he's a
judgment that show it's huge show and
what else your YouTube your Instagram
well he hasn't been doing are you gonna
are you gonna post again soon I posed
the last Sunday oh you are you gonna go
I honestly did it that's Instagram you
watch there Thanks I do instagram.com /d
t RI X they got rid of those go yeah
they hooked you boy out nice ok yeah
there's perfect well with that being
said you can follow us at off the pill
on Twitter at off the pill podcast on
Instagram and basically how we end this
is we just breathe into the mic in 3 2 1
she's a bunch of summer-rae boys than
that - there's some resourcefulness