how much does your violin cost no it's
like it's like about the price of like a
mercedes-benz I can see me I have no
reason to hate Justin that was just I
forced that one but I know you know you
try to defend yourself right now but
you're mean junior arrow knows the real
truth clap claps yeah welcome back to
another episode of off the pill podcast
Oh was scary a little bit a little bit
scary a little bit late today we are
doing fire with a very special guest mr.
Joon sung on say it again sit of
sessions on John's song we're here with
Joon Korean that's his other name and we
also have David in the moderator seat
[Music]
Paco here in exit well he's a joke so
we're with Joon today many of you may
know him from BGA we just had Justin a
couple episodes ago a few episodes ago
or you might know him as the violin
player or more recently as a real k-pop
star not a joke like BGA let's talk
about how you just released a new album
a real elect legit kpop songs right yeah
what how recent was that uh it came out
last week
oh well actually I don't know when this
is coming out but or it came out
recently you had Alan that came out
recently that's available for streaming
platforms and everything yeah Spotify
what's it what's the name of the album
supervised called limbo so June limbo
okay and the music video actually looks
really it looks legit like where did you
do that key that was in Korea so I went
all do it you got real kpop like
cinematographers and stuff cuz it allege
it
yeah they shoot a lot of like a Jerry
peak k-pop group stuff I don't know if I
don't like them for our stuff oh I mean
we can really for sure
yeah they look really good well I mean
no fancy you did the other one and those
look good but I think part of it is cuz
you had real dancers right yeah where we
were holding you back
no I think in Korea the film crews just
generally know how to shoot kpop stuff
very key
whereas out here it's like they're not
really used to how to shoot the dance to
make it look more kpop I guess that was
you you did that yeah I tried
so you've choreographed all of that and
everything no no no the recent one I had
a choreographer do the dance so what
what did you do then for that music
video I think so
the whole album and the project I kind
of oversaw the whole project and like
making the creative choices on like
style concept all that and then the
music video I guess technically all I
did was um I coordinated getting I was
kind of like a producer for a music
video um I didn't really direct it but I
still I kind of co-directed it I guess
and then I flew to Korea for just one
weekend to shoot it and then came back
does that happen very often were not
necessarily a company will hire people
to do it but an individual will I don't
think it happens that often cuz one it
involves like a ridiculous budget and to
like I guess the artist is supposed to
be focusing on being an artist and not
really handling all the little things
that make a production of production but
since I don't have a company nothing I
just kind of did it all yes right so I
mean for people who don't know Jun is
also a youtuber well you started it on
YouTube before all this yeah
and Jun has one point four million
subscribers 143 million total views but
a lot of those views and stuff were even
before you got into kpop it was a lot of
had to do with you I mean you're known
as the violinist right you used to do
violin covers of of k-pop songs but
after when when when did you get into
this whole like was it before BGA or
after BGA when you really started to I
don't know basically become a kpop star
well yeah I started off of youtube just
doing like pop songs like American top
40s covers on the violin it was kind of
an excuse for me to start the kind of
like keep playing the violin so I
started that when I was a freshman in
college and then kpop I think I just
started when somebody gave me a
recommendation to cover kpop song and I
was in a dance crew in college so I kind
of put those two together to do like
violin kpop dance covers and I was
already into that I guess before BG I
think that's partially the reason why
Phil I think I fell David reached out to
me to be part of BGA and after BGA I
think yeah because I didn't know you
before that no I don't think so I think
that's when we first yeah and when
you're the only guy in the group that
actually like looks like a kpop person I
try it speaks well - yeah yeah I'm full
Korean so you're though so you can hear
when cuz apparently I didn't know but
apparently David's Korean isn't perfect
so you can hear that he's not good at
Korean no he's completely fluent Oh mom
are you yeah born in Kuwait you're not
like that great did you hear that um
side there those lyrics I wasn't born in
Korea I was born in America I suck at
Korean thank you very much but harden
has said you're Korean isn't always
great right no it's not
like we had to sometimes you'll have to
ask your friend when we're writing like
lyrics and stuff like like how do you
say this I asked Jun yeah
do you say C I have no walk I wouldn't
have known yeah like I mean I can't tell
that's we were talking about this
earlier when we're recording those songs
because me and Phil we can't speak like
any of it it's just making sounds to us
like I can't I mean I I couldn't have
known that you aren't great at speaking
Korean I suck
do you really know I'm really bad I was
not forced to speak Korean with my
parents growing up I wish they forced me
but they tried at one point and I was
like alright if they were like if you
don't speak to us in Korean we're not
gonna respond to you and I was like
alright fine I'm just not gonna talk to
you then it's holy backfire yeah but
what they did force you to do was play
instruments right yes yes how did you
know that because you're a musician oh
yeah true so yeah so I grew up playing
violin and piano I play a lot of played
since I was five
violent both instruments actually I hate
it so much
piano and violin both I hated both I
hate I hated practicing what about you
did you hate violin oh there was a time
when I really didn't want to practice in
the beginning when you start a fifth
grade fifth grade did you hate it in the
in the beginning it was kind of like um
well actually in the beginning I liked
it it was actually more out of spite
because I'm my best friend played the
violin and like you know when you're
young you have like playdates and stuff
like that people come over and we play
video games the one that he would always
for some reason bring his violin and
then kind of like the first 10 minutes
of our like hangout session is him
showing me like him playing violin like
hey I practiced and he would kind of
like kind of show off I guess right
sounds like I was like I'm kind of
jealous I told my mom I was like hey I
want to play the violin that's how I
started really person if you're watching
we know what you're like we know what
you guys are good friends anymore hey
Harrison look why I'm asking because you
said you were born in Korea Yeah right
South Korea and and not North you're
born in South Korea and when did you
come here
well where did you grow up in New Jersey
okay so he's he's still in Jersey no
he's an SF right now yeah we're he's
like my first friend in America because
I didn't have friends cuz I couldn't
speak English so oh really yeah well
what what grade I guess I moved when I
was third grade so I came in third grade
I was I was great at math class that was
the only class that I was like I went up
to the board and I did all the math
problems and then every other closets
every other class was pretty rough for
me really did you get bullied I didn't
get believed because I was in the ESL
program like pasta foreign kids program
so even if he did get bullied he
couldn't understand why I pushed in
stuff is like yes yes yes well it's
crazy you don't know I mean like I guess
you grew up lancaster agree with it what
ages at 7 like 9 finish oh really
yeah oh okay well I'm still kind of
surprising you have no accent whatsoever
no I'm really I mean I don't hear it I
hear seriously you're talking quick I
got a question here about your
instrument cuz you know that's your main
weapon of choice right in the violin I'm
wondering how
much does your violin cost it's pretty
to personal doing no it's like it's like
about the price of like mercedes-benz
like SUV I would say that's that's a lie
you're not even joking no I'm not even
joking do you
you own it yeah I own it I have
insurance on it it's like it's a I
forgot what it's called like when you
get something really expensive like
jewelry you right yeah yeah so you get
it appraised right yeah so my Valens
appraising and stuff like that cuz I
could be wrong but there there are
actually violins out there that are very
expensive and are rented out to people
right yeah yeah I think um there's
violence that can range up to like a
couple million and stuff that is stupid
yeah it's crazy for a piece of wood no I
mean like okay would you be if you if I
were to have a million dollar violin
somewhat not me like some who can play
it and mercedes-benz while it which is
150 grit know how much I don't want to
how much is a I would say like around 50
50 grand violin and a cheap violin but
not like it's like around 100 hundred
bucks 200 if we were if they were all
were to play the same thing you would be
able to tell which is which actually it
might be kind of hard to tell the
difference between the Mercedes Benz and
the million dollar one but definitely
like the cheap cheap ones like the
factory made ones they're like the ones
that are like in like music shops like
for example like an instrument you get
at like sat match for example or
something like that is not probably not
that one I can tell the difference
between that and like my violin or like
a couple million dollar fine or
something hmm did you did you have - is
it like a payment thing or like how does
that usually work like you have to go
into a back alley or you go into yeah
you have to bring like a suitcase and
everything it's pretty pretty shady you
know it's hard to tell when you're being
sarcastic
yeah this is second language okay I
don't
what is the has anyone ever it's a
Stradivarius
yeah have you uh as anyone ever lets you
play it I've only touched the
Stradivarius
once I don't know what is this word what
is that it's the name of the person who
made the violin oh ah you haven't
touched him no no the violin that he
made I touched hundreds of years ago
right he was yeah couple hundred years
ago I think there's only two hundreds
treads in the whole world are we talking
about the Mercedes Ben no this is this
is the million dollar Oh God these are
the ones that are in museums and so how
can you even play them like what if you
dropped it like oh then the one that you
have Oh mine yeah that's like 50 grand
like what if there isn't do you
lose like 20 that's 20 grand already
like you don't think we do like crash
your car yeah you fix it so like I think
David can speak from experience but like
um people fix it it's like piece of wood
and then it's still worth the same like
my violin for example it's like almost
like 300 years old mine and then there's
like a section on the bottom of the vial
and it's completely shattered and
reglued so it's been older than America
1776 so I mean like okay so if you if it
was really me 300 years ago and you're
saying there's a bunch of these right
even older than that that are worth more
it's kind of like wine and get it's
worth more as time goes on
mm-hmm do you know the previous owners
like how did you how did it get into
your hands I actually don't know the
previous owners but it was made in
Germany for example and I mean not for
example it was made in Germany I got it
from my violin person in New York he
does a lot of like professional
violinist like um probably don't know
but like Midori caught them like these
people are um Midori is green Japanese
oh really yeah a lot of names for anime
sorry I didn't mean oh no that's but
then on the he he has a lot of those
like really expensive islands and like
cheaper ones I don't know where he got
it from but I got it from him in New
York
yeah can I thought will be could you pay
for it sorry well my parents didn't you
my grandpa my grandpa grandma helped out
a lot on Lawrence to like an investment
it's kind of I mean if you keep it like
no I'm thinking about it like it's like
gold right you just keep in
violet you should get a bunch of
violations hold on to it that's a coin
that's always Bitcoin it wasn't a
mercedes-benz you a SUV cost when I got
it Oh what was that the Passat because
of inflation that's probably partially
that too but then another thing is um
violins like the more you play it the
more the sound develops as in the sound
that my violin made when I first got it
and now it's completely this wow that's
the opposite of a car yeah I guess we
can drive it the worse it is oh so do
you
yeah that's kind of interesting yeah so
you could just have like a farm right a
violinist buy a bunch and just have them
play all day and in you're making money
yeah yeah right yes it's appreciate
that's yeah but like I mean like how did
pottery if you're reselling it like how
can you prove like okay this is played
for like a thousand hours since I got it
so it's worth that much more I think it
really depends on like the professionals
opinion like I'm not in the right so
like I can't really decide what it costs
is but I bring it back to the guy he
fixes it up for like a week comes back
and he's like probably like cool so they
do but they realize oh you played this
so X amount but they can hear it as a
sound and stuff like see how much the
sound is and it's more and stuff like
that they can they have like yeah it's a
combination of like the sound it's the
combination of looking through the
sometimes like the person who made it
will put like a signature inside the
violin too and you can kind of
authenticate that but how do you know
how much it's been played as I'm saying
you can't really tell that but you can
kind of like measure look at the wood
and there's a lot of different factors
that are involved with that so I think
it's because my parents own a music
store my mom is a restores she does that
she does that for a loose take your
thing to him and then see how much more
since you've been playing it actually
what you should do is just start the
farm man like start the pile there's a
good business you know I know you
actually bring up a good point because
actually some of the more expensive
instruments that my mom has she actually
has people play it she should make it
worth more
yeah because it opens out even more yeah
you know like a violin sitting in a
museum like for several years will sound
pretty bad I don't think the average
person knows like I didn't know anything
I didn't know violence cost that much
for one
now I'm starting to think every violin
I've ever seen how much was that really
warlike Lindsey sterling her violins
can't be worth that much right I think
when it's when you put electric when
it's an electric violin which is what
she usually plays those it's worth less
worth less yeah because there's that it
doesn't really depend on the wood and
stuff it's more technology that makes it
so much so you're almost like a kpop
Lindsey Stirling in a way yeah I dance I
play violin yeah yeah and I guess a
transition into that because we need to
talk about kpop I kind of want to know
and touch up on I guess your your
history in your past and how you kind of
got into kpop and how you're like trying
to integrate it into your YouTube
channel and did you even audition for
like did you even audition for like you
know actual k-pop groups yeah I I
addition once in college and then once I
got um I guess notified from some
company when I moved out to LA right
after college but um
kpop was just always something I
listened to because my sister's really
big kpop em she still is and a shout out
to her but Harrison gets one thank you
which Macaulay a kpop I just got into
cuz somebody recommended me like praying
playing a k-pop song and I danced in
college so kind of combined it to and I
made a cover people liked it and then I
started listening to kpop I started in
doing dude really there's ghosts here
well I want to know like this I try to
just move on dude can we cut real quick
for real let's cut hook with this ghost
in here man that what is happening yes
damn maybe we should show this is scary
haunted edition
[Music]
dude we're all a little freaked out that
was really weird it could be a
coincidence it's never happened before
my house this is so dude do we ever
announce this is at your house this
podcast this podcast is in this L a
podcast is at David's house and there's
there's girls here now we know David you
have to live here anyway if more weird
things happen I mean we're going through
the footage when you go through the
footage crazy-eyed even though that
first thing fell to be honest for our
listeners there's two large bangs you
heard actually you might have heard some
voices because it's being recorded I
don't know a couple of our painting
things fell like right back to back and
they didn't fall all day so like I don't
know
yeah it's really weird uh-huh anyway
getting back on top every time so Julie
actually has a good point
do you believe in ghosts cuz you you
said just now you were like oh man I got
like goosebumps no I got a lot of
goosebumps um I don't I don't I don't
want to believe in ghosts I think it's a
mentality thing where if you don't
believe it and you're strong but you do
if you're strong so it's really
interesting to me because there's I've
heard a lot of stories about the kpop
industry especially as of late right
there's some articles going around like
about how little they get paid actually
for how much they're bringing in I don't
know what's true I've heard some stories
but since you've been kind of in that
world not that you're you you went down
that industry route are those there is
there truth to those rumors of what like
how poorly they're treated like or I
mean David knows too you know a lot of
people in that industry yeah I've heard
I've definitely heard some stories yeah
you know I think I think something
important to note is that we only know
of like SM yg JYP like a lot of these
big big hit now at BTS we know these big
groups big companies but there's like
hundreds of entertainment companies on
in Korea and there's like thousands and
thousands of kids that are trainees that
may never even get to debut even if they
like they might be a trainee for 10
years and they might not get chosen to
debut so there's so many people in that
industry that it's kind of like hard to
say like this one example like is the
same for all of it but I think there is
a lot of truth in those stories don't
just exist for no reason I feel like no
no that's like that's something I never
really like have like a strong opinion
on well I only know because I mean we
know some people in that industry and
I've heard stories not to say that I
know it's true or not but since you guys
are more I mean you know more than I do
I mean I've heard things were like they
force you know the trainees or whatever
to essentially like they they force him
to get like plastic surgery for
sometimes and they force them to even
like do sexual things with people like
kind of [ __ ] them out yeah
but so you know that that so it is true
that's true so you know from personal
experience yeah actually yeah I know
someone should I even say this story I
won't say names I don't say names but I
will say that I know someone who was
spilled of that industry I'm trying to
be very careful be careful this person
offered services quote-unquote services
to somebody I know who is wealthy for
basically hinting at if you pay me I
will do I will sleep with you and
they're in the kit in their campus
recital
yes and you know them personally and
they told you this know the rich person
the rigid person told me this I so it is
true then because I've heard that and
I'm not I didn't hear it from David I've
heard it from someone completely
unrelated so it is truth that stuff
happens and I also heard that not only
do they do that
they do it for a reason because
if you ever go against the label but the
label does is they basically use it as
as blackmail so if you ever go against
them they'll release that information
and they'll have some kind of like sex
tape or some kind of scandal to cut
basically just ruin your reputation in
Korea yeah right and it's way worse
there yeah in Korea if you have a sex
tape your your career is over
right whereas in America it's just it's
just begun Jun any you got a black male
Jun
we've already becomes the big star so I
mean like I guess since you kind of
almost got into that world I'm kind of
curious actually because there is there
or there are a lot of benefits to going
down that route right like you you get
instant exposure well not I guess like
you said it's not for everyone yeah but
I think I think if you debut so again
it's like if you're a trainee it doesn't
you don't really get the benefits except
like the resources but once you debut I
think like in the big three like SM ji
Pyg I think definitely um you get that
instant exposure literally overnight
fame like if you if ji p posts a teaser
for a new group they're instantly famous
overnight kind of thing and they do a
lot of press marketing as well as again
like financially they help with all the
resources training music video budget
all that kind of stuff like you seem
like the kpop music videos they're like
pretty insane scale wise so I think
there's a lot of benefits in that and
but also a lot of downsides as you
mentioned right and doing it
independently I think it's a lot more
fun in my opinion because I get to
control everything and I think that's
more important to me then I guess like
being famous like that quick very easily
I guess yeah so for all those young kids
out there who look at k-pop stars and
aspire to be like them how do you become
a kpop star
I don't be Korean or Asian actually know
they're expanding yeah there's a Thai
there's a lot of like um like half
Korean people there's a lot of Chinese a
lot of Thai and yeah that's it's not
it's not limited to being Korean I think
I think it's if you have what it takes
like talent
wise as well as you have the passion I
think the most important thing is the
passion to do it because it's not just
about you being good at something you
have to like looking like a kpop idol
right because there's that like image
static k-pop idol has when you're on
stage f2l you look really pretty really
cute really like cool or like sexy or
whatever it is you kind of have to like
fit in that world you have to have what
it takes and I think that's the thing
that makes somebody a k-pop idol or
artist more so than the music or the
talent cuz that like you just changed a
kpop song to English it becomes American
pop it's not right I don't think I never
thought kpop was at genre kpop is like a
whole package just pop in Korean yeah
and you just have to have the image the
dancing the production all that package
that's what makes it there's actually a
lot of controversy about that too right
isn't there like a what is that the
award show is announcing a kpop category
and BTS fans are really upset because
they're they feel like they're putting
they created that category just so that
they're not competing against other pop
artists and because BTS is huge right
now so I forget I can't even remember
what award is something big I don't know
if it's like Grammys or didn't I know
there there is a there was a lot of
contrary recently they announced it and
there was a bunch of like BTS people who
are really upset and and it is that's I
I mean I get it but it's kind of like
why wouldn't they be allowed in the pop
category yeah you know it's still pop
and there is English in it like I don't
know it's lose the MTV MTV VMA Awards oh
that's nothing what are they getting mad
over speaking about being cancelled
right and stuff like that like don't you
think like if you ever were to make it
like the goal is to make it big right
like if you ever were to make it big
don't you think aren't you worried that
these like we just talked about all dark
and dirty these labels play aren't you
worried that that you're like going
against the grain and you're like
sitting example for people like they do
you must I mean you you will be on their
target list like they don't want people
to create themselves on their own they
want you to be like hey we need this
label to make it
aren't you afraid at some point they're
gonna target you or maybe it had they
reached out to you already to try and
get you under them mmm no I mean I do
get like like some like it's like no
name entertainment labels sometimes
reach out to me here and there but um I
don't think gun like a target one
because like I think I'm still starting
and I'm still kind of discovering myself
and this music career side of things but
I think the beauty is that my YouTube
channel has me for like the past eight
nine years mm-hmm and you can see the
full history of me right and I think
that's something that's very nice to
have like almost like a portfolio for
myself and I think people looking to be
in the kpop industry like there's one
part that they have to think about what
do they have to lose for me a big choice
of not joining a label was because I had
too much to lose because I had that
whole like I guess like um portfolio of
me being a YouTube violinist that if I
did sign to label for example they'd
probably like make me get rid of my
youtube channel maybe get rid of my
Instagram anything so like wow I have a
fresh new plate that's how they would
that's how they like their I donate
right so they can write everything for
them and they interesting kind of things
is that that's one thing I think is a
little bit different because in like the
American industry for example like they
won't do that like the artist has full
control right and I think that's always
how I should be um but in but kpop I
think is just completely different the
culture is different and what they're
looking for in k-pop idols and how that
markets how that sells it's completely
different from like Justin Bieber for
example it's a totally different image
so I think it works for that end but for
me I don't think I need to like
necessarily keep myself tight to kpop
mm-hmm necessarily because I'm it just
made sense for my demographic to do kpop
right now but I would consider myself
more of a korean-american artist rather
than a kpop artist interested it kind of
sounds like the packaging for Korea is
really about inorganic you know like
everything is oh it's almost like
plastic surgery which is something
that's widely accepted they're like they
wanted everything to look clean-cut well
produced we're in the more Western
westernized the entertainment it's kinda
just like be edgy be original make your
own stuff but still have like
hints a formula there yeah yeah for sure
yeah so I what are you looking since you
said that you know this is what you want
to do for now what is your your next
goals because after uh
I guess this kpop days is over for you
whenever well this mini album was like
kind of me just really trying to getting
get it out of my system like I have a
physical CD I have a music video I have
a lot of like I I featured an actual
k-pop idol and one of these songs and
then um so it's just something that I
really wanted to get out of my system
because I never was able to do it and
finally I got to do it so honestly right
now I'm kind of just like I don't know
what I really want to do I kind of want
to see where this album goes yeah as
well as work on music that's not maybe
not in Korean I'm just like and I want
to kind of bring the violin back because
I think I kind of pushed that away on
purpose because I wanted to like really
focus on like original like singing
rapping that kind of stuff but I want to
bring the violin back and see how can I
can incorporate that in my future
content so so you'd be open to
continuing this if this blows up for you
and does like really well yeah I mean I
don't think it necessarily needs to blow
up but I think I want to follow it
because it's still a passion for me like
music is still a big passion but maybe
kind of seeing where that might lead me
with like my film side of stuff - yeah
soundtrack stuff maybe is the YouTube
enough to kind of sustain a career for
you I would say I took a really big
hiatus like two years no violin playing
no violin covers and like content on
YouTube for a while and like YouTube is
kind of it's very important that you
know like you have that consistency on
YouTube to maintain that number so all
the fans watching my content right now
on my channel are were originally there
for the violin content not for the k-pop
content so I would say I'm I've
rebranded my YouTube it's almost like
starting on your YouTube channel so I'm
right now not now I don't think so but
um I think hopefully eventually yeah
because it's because I know there's a
lot of musicians out there that you know
it's it's difficult to do music
full-time right you know you're lucky
you're one of the lucky ones if you're
able to so you know when it comes to
making money
I know YouTube pays
percentage of ad revenue and then you
know you sell merch do you have a
patreon do you do you do live shows like
is that kind of where do you make money
as well or Randle's yeah I think right
now it shows shows were the biggest like
last year for example I did a lot of
like university shows with like my
violin content and then moving forward I
think I have like a physical album CD
that came out that was actually mostly
again kind of getting it out of my
system like I can say I have like a
legit k-pop album I was like little
photo cards and stuff like that so
that's one merch possibly like more like
t-shirt merch merch I think is always an
option moving forward but um for now
it's still more of a passion project I
would say
so for fans you want to support you what
are the top two revenue generators for
you where they can support and help you
you know get to a full-time position
mm-hmm I would have to say just stream
it and like 10 million 30 million just
keep streaming hit that refresh button
or you could start the violin farm or do
violin from you I'm telling you man
that's a good business
it sounds like telling you I don't know
what the numbers are actually but it
sounds like it could be a good business
it's a good return it just takes a long
time hounds like it could be a good
business on this horrible transition
let's go into some some questions we got
from Twitter yeah that sounds good
sorry I'm reading like these are so good
I mean speaking about like kpop and BG a
[Music]
splendid you'll ask do you hate Justin
did we just did we talk about that about
how like the last podcast Justin was we
were talking talking how much about
you oh yeah I mean did you get - did you
get to listen to that well I got I got
notified by some hey Justin said some
mean things about you
fandom my fans are like and then
somebody took it actually really
seriously did they somebody actually got
hurt
oh really they're like they're like I
can't believe Dee talked about you I was
like no it's a joke I'm pretty sure it
was a joke if I went I watched I watched
it to the point when puck was that like
there's no way Jun will make it through
this point in the past I show you uh and
he's like well I can leave now yeah I
was there and I would I just made fun of
my youtube username Jun Korean yep no
biking shirt didn't know that it was it
Curry on was Korean
yeah I appreciate a lot of people that's
like the Malay actually did I didn't
realize till later on whenever you know
how you do Q&A here and there sometimes
right like that's the number one
question I get like every single time no
matter how many times I explain it like
an AM screen name back when they I am
used to be a thing mm-hmm carry it over
to my google gmail account that carried
over to my YouTube account and then
that's juice so now we know where to
email you basically yeah pretty much
sure you guys fighting
but do you hate Justin use mmm no I
don't I I have no reason to hate Justin
maybe after the podcast episode maybe
we're calling me out like that's I
already said that like we were like oh
we're gonna get Jun to like talk show
but that sounds like I don't think Jun
would do that even even if it was real
yeah let's just hear you what would you
be your bestest is this your your yeah
let's come back now that you're in front
of Mike yeah Justin's right here and I'm
Justin and I just said fu June or you
look like a catfish oh my god you're way
leaner than I am Wow
we need AC Paris in the side-by-side his
whiskers right now well I mean he got a
beard I saw I was watching the podcast
without thinking it on the back last
night
oh wait no it was so AG but it was such
a deep
that's a major dislike at fish it's like
he was waiting to see a real place
because we have the back of the dead
yeah like I have no reason to hate
Justin that was just I forced that one
but no defend yourself right now but
you're mean Junior everyone knows the
real truth but to be fair Justin was a
pretty mean to you as well no but that's
like I mean that so that became a thing
on the first shoot I think after a
little bit and naturally progressed and
in the second one I started writing it
in because it just naturally progressed
it's like it's a realist in the young
boy you see the Otis yeah yes the oldest
and the youngest and it's like a natural
like it's funny you think the
relationship works but it's really like
that in real life too
yeah it's a it's carried on it's yeah
it's not it's not an on-screen thing
it's just naturally like yeah he'll do
it even if the cameras were off right
now Justin's voice in my head as soon as
said catfish like that high-pitched
voice I don't I don't think he sounds
like that very good impersonation in
person but you know what I'm saying he
did say that he he would make love to
you
and I did I I don't know if you believe
that he would but it wasn't a sarcastic
he did say that he did say that I mean
he he twee he said he would grab you by
the hair
we don't have we're not trying to
demonetized here yeah but he'll say
things like that
yeah and he won't say just kidding mm
even though we know just so you know
it's a love-hate relationships all of
hate relation but anyway so we have a
few more I want to know this but I don't
know I don't know where this one came
from have you ever had any rude
encounters from famous k-pop idols rude
encounters or maybe a wholesome
encounters I want to hear the rude ones
yeah
give me the rude ones cuz I'm sure
you've come across a bunch since you go
to kcon and you do all those like you
know you're kind of in that industry no
yeah
at kcon I do this thing I do a lot of
things where I'm IMC because I'm
bilingual um so they have these things
called fan engagements where they come
on stay
age they answer like Twitter questions
like this like kind of like this setting
a gonna interview but I take the
questions I asked him in Korean I
translate it for an audience and stuff
like that I won't say a groups name
because I don't want to like cause kpop
yeah I don't say names actually you
could that's terrifying people but then
there was this one specific member of
this girl group that was just completely
different on stage and how she was
offstage like the second she got
offstage she like called for a manager
got like where's my water where's my
water like a diva I could not not just a
diva there like a diva but it's super
like like a really [ __ ] diva like to
the point where like on stage she was
like I really have the second she came
down her smile just disappeared her face
just completely changed right so I don't
think it was rude to me I think people
dealing with her honored right would
feel that she's very rude all the time
but maybe she was having a bad day or
something but that's the bad one what's
your name what does it rhyme with Oh
drink the the kpop fans woman is that
the girl group like Pink's oh no I did
not say that
no no but that's like one of the biggest
girl groups right yeah it was them it
was them we're just gonna start it well
figure out which one June said okay so I
mean well that kind of goes back to what
we were talking about though like it's
very artificial right not nothing
everybody is like that but to a certain
degree like they have to be like the
cutesy personality on stage if not it's
that's there's a reason why they're all
they act very similar yeah and it's it's
kinda you understand that right yeah
following like a formula and stuff like
that like I have like for example for me
like I have to say nice things about
Justin to have that facade of me being
the nice member of the behave exactly
the scenes are just making out kind of
going off of that what is the weirdest
fan encounter you've had that I've had
um cuz I mean this is a question we
usually ask like the girls cuz usually
their stores are pretty wild it's always
stalkers yeah but have you had any weird
ones I'm sure mmm
I think it was I forget if it was that a
Kate Connor so I'm no it was at one of
the cake cons most of my experience has
come from kcon because that's one of the
kpop fans come there was one fan that
literally followed me everywhere knew
which hotel I was in so there's a
stalker story hmm yeah but this one was
weird cuz I'm like I don't know how she
knew but then like the next like one
like I saw her at the hotel in the lobby
and she made eye contact then I like you
know like when you see a person then
they recognize you and like and stuff
like that so I was like oh it's a fan
stuff like that we took a picture she
asked for a picture and then and then
the next morning I woke up I was getting
ready to go to the convention I walked
out of my room and she was in the
hallway and she was just sitting in the
corner of the hallway she's something
she's like oh shoot I'm sorry and she's
like that's a bunch of stuff but I was
honestly like really creeped out to say
anything or like comprehend what was
happening but then that happened to date
three days in a row dude yeah she was
scary stuff like that so that was a
slightly creepy the third day she's just
sitting outside your door oh that was so
she just the reason why these things you
know she was here the whole time
okay well then yeah that's like a
stalker story you know seems like we
have one more question and it says well
that's kind of we kind of answered that
already
tell us about it's not through BGA stuff
other questions Jun do you remember when
I met you in the lobby in your hotel I
got one go ahead that your fans might
want to know about unless they already
know mm-hmm are you single am i single
[Music]
yeah how long have you been in your
relationship or is that private
information no it's been a little over
three years now Wow
yeah actually like a month after three
years girl we know right yeah we met
yeah she's actually our stylist Noir
who's it kind of and she was on
some of your videos right yeah she's
singing oh wow do you guys plan on
collaborating more or mmm yeah maybe
like honestly like now that I'm kind of
getting into the singing rapping stuff
like that it would be really nice to
have a song together I think would be
really nice but um she's reliving -
right yeah she's phone and griemann how
does she feel about all of this success
that you're experiencing right now well
she's kind of like my reality check
always as in like she'll humble you
humble me maybe a little too much in
what ways though like what it was like
what I can't imagine you being cocky or
I mean yeah that's like generally I
don't but like for example like when
you're in a relationship or like with
family or something you kind of want
that like like them to kind of credit
you or just like crazy a little bit you
know like kind of like that child in me
that I want like my girlfriend to watch
my video and be like oh my god you look
so good and stuff like that for example
like she'd compliment but at the same
time humbled me at the same time she's
look at my most recent music video for
example she would watch it and she'd be
like who is that guy he's so
good-looking
it's like a compliment but yeah so she
is compliment think she is appreciating
but at the same time she knows to like
make sure it doesn't get to my head and
stuff got it got it do you think it
makes some of your fans jealous that you
have it you're taken you think her um
yeah I think initially like we've been
public for a while but um I guess some
people still don't know even though I
post pictures with her all the time and
stuff like that but um there are
instances when people do get jealous and
are really mean to her on her Instagram
for example people like make fake a
constant like you really mean on our
Instagram well isn't it normally like
the kpop like people bands like people
what they don't have relationships right
no that's like a big like if you have a
girlfriend boyfriend than your career
and isn't there a thing to like I don't
know because I just read bja comments
isn't anything like that there's usually
a couple guys that like you and Justin
who do have some kind of bromance thing
going on
yeah the group there's always one right
yeah yeah how many how many not that I
don't know that you would know how many
of those actual like bands either how
many how many gay people are in the kpop
industry do you think
personally I think there is plenty
really there's a lot but you're right
it's not accepted in Korea it's accepted
like out here like people like kpop fans
prefer that yeah it seems like it
because they would rather have two
members dating each other than them
dating different girls right because
they don't want to like ruin the facade
yeah they want that fantasy of being
able to be with them at one point but if
I'm not able to get you then I'd rather
have right David be with you for example
doing this that's kind of I just had an
image in my head
yeah well people trust me have images of
you and Justin so I have the next one
the next skit we're gonna write is just
like softcore porn well do you monetize
yeah yeah do you have anything did you
like to plug though yeah so my my my new
mini albums out it's called limbo ask
three songs I worked a lot I worked
really working the Alishan and where can
they get it you can get it you can
listen stream it on Spotify it's on
iTunes on everything you can just search
Jun limbo it's on my channel watching
Korean on YouTube my music videos out my
music video for my third songs coming
out pretty soon too and yeah awesome
well make sure you guys go check it out
is actually very legit especially if you
like BGA stuff it's it's up there man
the quality is really good
that being said make sure you guys
follow us at off the pill on twitter at
off the pill podcast on instagram and
june you're well we we can pop up your
thing yeah you can curry on her young
for yeah june korean yeah but that means
ed i guess we'll just you know how we
out for this we'll just breathe into the
mic in three two one
[Music]
you know that Mike price smells like so
many different people so like curry I
cleaned it carry on he cleans like curry
on crayons yeah