warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact recreate a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears I'm pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised put them in a hat
and if we draw at the player concert
then decides how many points is worth
based on how sharing of a dare it is if
the player passes another player can
take the steal the first player to get
ten points to do something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name basically write your
name on a ball of aluminum foil yes you
may have seen her in ages of secret
stuff or on TV on Teen Wolf this is
orange okay my name is basically we all
write down one of our own
there never has the least pledged in
another game I suppose good news for a
person to them isn't able to stop this
no the hardest
[Music]
this is a lot of paper next time we take
a poop you're gonna be like a printer
[Music]
bringing the mayonnaise is a liquor
company
you just ate that much of me I give you
like one point on the rim that's a good
three-pointer because this toilets nasty
welcome to the hello boxwood how's it
smell take a big whiff first papers
coming up see what happens when you
don't watch the show
yeah ah to play marriage
a 1 and that's good to do - you got a
Dipsy
[Music]
put it in here and you squeeze it
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's pink
for blush 2.5 2.5 thank you it's pretty
messed up
all right good job very kinda say Gina
just ball off a step up to the crown do
it I believe in myself I paid five
points in I'll give you four this is
gonna hurt
and I think about it oh yeah oh yeah not
good company
dude this is so helpful so I have bowl
around to this kind of Cove in a little
bit now eagle I think I bend my knees so
that issue me or did check away the step
I condemn my knees so maybe I'll take a
three three where the three I still feel
it in my chest all right fall on the
spiders this is a one flip what's a fun
I don't know how about a fry hand string
and you land and crush a turd with your
feet so there's a little cushion yeah
okay cobble thing okay and plant your
feet yeah it's Dookie oh my goodness
that makes fun whose knees or one of us
choice how about you getting your first
try is 4.1 any kind of clip but you have
to land like a car wheel or clip or
whatever it's called and just let's
stick it yes
good job or you have them all right by
one now she's had four point one eye is
a click the first to your right to that
one another on top of each other and the
person who draws this is on the bottom
also you that's not can you change it
what are we talking right on you and you
have to hold them up in a push-up
position and put something on your face
the longer you hold it the more points
you get what's underneath my face and
I'll plate full blast you suffer greater
stunts where every ten seconds you hold
Gregg up get a point for every 10 sec
make maximum fun that's gonna be tired
okay fresh we all need to add one thing
because I think it's already hard I'm
gonna start simple just some ketchup oh
that's a lot yeah that's the expired one
carpet cleaner that's a big piece oh you
just made this instantly more difficult
she just added the poo that she stepped
in in two years so not only are you
getting you're getting can you land and
crush a turd with your feet payback at
least one of you to rest but this is a
vase that's so disgusting dude every 10
second is an extra point maximum five
points this is Greg mess up his feet oh
wow Wow
[Applause]
good job Airbender Oh
for that I would give you the win you
guys think the same there the judge got
and you want to win that's what you have
to do I would say you're in the chair
you know the chair how many eggs are
thrown at me
until what person two per person and
then do two at the end maybe new clothes
I'm gonna do this
do it this is the third idea we lost to
a guest I don't care and are you quinoa
fans room you like do I look at our team
differently I respect you more but
you're in terms of guys all your
girlfriend's like oh and the final touch
here we go
just receive you know safety first yeah
yeah yeah Josh to the mystique because
he doesn't get out of his point yet
all right we got seven eggs my name's
Derek and Greg will do two each and then
Josh would do one number one right here
come dare this for that plate nice
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know how you're gonna take this
back to California but oh yeah also sign
the ball off the ball and yeah we're
going to bed peace bye I dare you guys
Derek
Ryan hello hello Oh big news again so
much for watching if you want to see the
previous video click the 111 you want to
see the previous I dare you do click the
one on the right thank you so much to
our d for being in this stupid I dare
you thing which actually makes her look
pretty girl she's she's pretty girls
your girl's growth there you stepped in
poo and your eggs all over you you're
discussing any lick the toilet sink
[Music]