warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised we take your dares
put them in a hat and if we draw it the
player console then decides how many
points is worth based on how daring of a
charity if the player passes and whether
player can take the skills first player
to get 10 points do something amazingly
not amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name you basically write
your name on a ball of aluminum foil
jenna Marbles I'm Jana Michaels and I'm
ready to do dance and her boyfriend
Julian
fidelia's and let's go get some legs
right now we our own
let's go roll a dice stick that number
of ice cubes in your underwear
oh all right how many points is that
word I say okay
yeah all right that's gonna be really
tough you're in a dress oh he dies for
this during a dress underwear my
underwear or we'll just go face the
other way put it in ice nice job tonight
I do to lick the gaps between someone's
toes oh I say welcome Eric with yes run
in that dirt real quick
three points get wet your tongue should
be like a peninsula that's a great know
your four and a half three okay get Greg
they're taking something cold out of
your freezer this is frozen chicken
nuggets well this is really hard
that's secrete hard that's like ice one
chicken nugget 14.4 points for once you
guys yeah
oh dude you want some frozen mustard
with that oh dude don't bring chickenpox
oh that's the one that they give all
your points to the person to your right
if you have no you basically just what
if you break break your fingers this is
like jaggedy to come on instead of doing
this you put the back of your hand and
lean against it and drag it to this line
this way you're just bricks dude I was
like really
oh you went to I way more than you
there's more pressure than about Huracan
fingers yeah open
I have negative one I do you to put a
bar of soap in a sock and hit the person
on your right on their stomach what wait
so who's there is this someone does it
to you one so nice and fresh that little
thing gentlemen anything how far do you
want like this if you hit a boob at your
boob it's gone yeah I'd say all three
points in a head-to and a half I dare
you to drink water that was used to
watch Frank's hair yeah legs nice look a
little sweaty too though well there's
definitely sweat in there points for
this
take mine Josiah born born born born to
sign for identity
I think great you get at least a half
way yeah
I dare you to act like a dog until it's
your turn
that's how about this you have this good
somewhere the DARS bus and take a inhale
at least like five seconds long don't
have to hear you inhale for five seconds
you're just getting to know you I never
thought I'd see they'll give him what
points that's weird dude I need a good
fiber come on let's go right there you
break a piece of wood with your head
there's one plank right there hey Ryan
hope you can trace through this right
yeah that's a sweet spot nice so there
it is so how many points am I getting
we're judging after then oh dude missing
hair dan this is like sorry good sounds
like you shape your watch a really dirty
sock with boiler to water Tori left and
then put it on and put it in your mouth
five points yes points oh you could do
it for four to three what she's trying
to wake up this deal
put that in your mouth I'm impressed
and a little grossed out damn and it's
your turn to yeah I dare you to do a
push-up with someone how about we make
it John it should be that with like
people on you and then you have to have
a dog poop right here oh come on
you're stealing this sometimes gauge the
weight yeah and the poop he's like
coming up now poop right there watch the
poop with your nose how one person then
one person was the heaviest Ryan to do
right
when this poop is running place you get
like ten percent stronger you get not I
dare you to lay in the bed and get body
slams oh I got it I'll lay down and you
do one of those jump things you're doing
all your videos and land on me oh yeah
what is that word I say that's three
points that's good that's like a three
you do it Derek oh my god he's gonna
jump on you dear you to roll on grass
I've just been cut with your shirt off
or you run but if you hug that sago palm
323i hug this is gonna be holy sword to
like doing this is sharp my one passes
damn for real do a damn Derek Derek
pillow in the face for time yeah I just
open one of them three points it is a
pillow that was really soft you know
this is for Dragonball going to use all
your muscles and use it just shut your
eyes and wait
if you're blindfolded and you put stuff
in there that's a challenge we're gonna
put things in Julian's Melbury each one
gets one point for just attempting it
for each one he gets correct correctly
guesses exactly what it is
exactly exactly what it is he gets an
extra point for ties so technically he
could win if he just gets he has to
correct yes three points he wins yep so
I'll go first
ready open your mouth you see no I can't
see any Patsy nearly all right open your
mouth or Shu will show you later
next person
yep she finger wait Jenna said Jenna
yeah knows my face which dog peach this
is for the win if you get this you
deserve to win are we doing this
that was not poop was it no more in that
going there like classy at the end or
something is that an unused tampon did
you see what the first one rag is our
loser so he's gonna be pulling from the
loser cup someone slaps the bottom of
your foot that's part of their foot dude
yeah
it's part of their job only do you get
decide the ball of a move but you also
win your very own hardly do that orchid
so thank you guys so much for watching
if you want to see the previous I dare
you video click the one on the left if
you want to see the last video we did
with jenna Marbles click the one on the
right and be sure you leave your dares
in the comment section below because
we're gonna screenshot them and it might
be responsible for the next I dare you
video video video