hey guys so if you're watching a TV my
second channel and you know that I have
a series on their code I dare you where
we take a bunch of your dares that you
guys were in the comments and make a
game on it I know I don't normally do
this show on this channel but this is a
very special episode because we have two
very special guests that you might have
heard of what are the first people who
are big on YouTube mr. KevJumba and of
course NBA star Jeremy Lin who you might
know from the insanity back in the day
he's like really good at baseball or
dota or soccer or something oh sorry
football with that being said these are
all real dares but please do not try any
of this at home just do it somewhere
else no I'm just kidding please just
don't do it okay please don't do it
yeah just don't do it you're here this
whole time no warning the following
video contains stupid and dangerous
activities and I attempt to reenact
recreate a reincarnate and the following
stunts tears and pretty much anything
that's performed in this video your
discretion is advised do your best if
you don't get it
[Applause]
we take your dares put them in a hat and
if we draw it the player console then
decides how many points is worth based
on how daring of iterative if the player
passes another player can take the steel
the first player to get ten points is
something amazingly not amazing as well
as their name in the Hall of Fame no
just kidding they get the ball of man
you basically write your name on a ball
of aluminum foil I am ready for I dare
you I dare you to blind for yourself and
the other members pick five things for
you to kiss all right what are we saying
points are saws this work into tens if
you mind this is not a crazy hard I
would say three that's it's easy one
let's do it two points to watch let's go
find something live from the kiss guys
lives are one
[Music]
all right go in oh yeah yeah for lasting
yeah this is a person huh you guys do it
I can see you great do it you gotta do
it two points I dare you to put chilli
chilli or pepper up your nose water for
40 seconds oh I don't know that's no
spicy smell that first what is this why
don't we give it a point based on
burning my nose just like smelling it
okay ordered a spicy Oh suck it in baby
[Applause]
burning but I'll mash it into the stems
I'll give you another point oh I can't I
can't I can't take a bite out of him
give another point till one for the
devil three points I dare you to get
slapped on the stomach two times from
each person oh he said yeah you got the
one on you got
like we're talking like oh and that's
one good lorry
oh let's see what we find
[Music]
[Laughter]
I dare you to let all people throw a
food at you I got just some really old
hard rice we got some really old it's
like a shotgun do a video with KevJumba
that's like ten that's like super rare I
dare to eat a spoonful of mustard I'll
do a soup spoon for to soup for to build
up and you fill it up you gotta take the
steel take the steel
[Music]
Oh Jerri standing us won't have arrows
good to throw a tennis ball as hard as
they can
as hard as we can but I'm done so we're
gonna change it to basketball onyx for
the obvious reason I'm not good at
basketball tennis balls we're gonna go
an order of like the least painful this
one's like a foam ball this is rubber
ball this one's kind of hard like this
[Laughter]
that sounded pretty solid oh yeah I dare
you to wear a dress any dress for the
rest of the game like a pretty little
princess cookie on your forehead slide
it down your face in your mouth without
touching oh that's all I say you get
point of view get it so it ran fine a
delicious cookie we found a delicious
daughter laughter point three point if
you get it if you get my hard over the
nose that's like tough landscape I'm
looking in the reflection it's good to
get shot with a paintball what's on a
shirt Oh
yeah you have a paintball gun do I pass
it and Shawn's gonna steal it if I'm
scared this is for the width this is
worth the wind I in my appeal again
we're gonna put a disclaimer but do not
try this at home
[Music]
all right so we're about to do probably
the stupidest thing we've ever done on a
dare safety first right to do this to my
where John got a face mask no space and
this is the dare that you guys came up
with your idea it's pretty good a shot
[Music]
Shawn is the winner for today we're
gonna do science prize right we figured
out Shawn's prize Jeremy had a really
good idea winners it's a trophy you have
to add a layer to so every week the ball
should get bigger until it's you know
pretty decent-sized first layer Shawn
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right so thank you guys again so
much for watching our very first episode
of I dare you on this channel to see
more emphasis of I dare you on my second
channel you get TV click the one on the
left you want to see the previous video
click the one on the right and again
thank you so much to KevJumba and Jeremy
Lin for being down to be a part of one
of the stupidest games ever invented
damn jumper I like Jeremy doesn't have a
slogan at all he did some pretty Lynn
st. it's pretty interesting but I'll see
you do
Janna orange okay just gonna force it
through my face are you through lean
lynn hing Mui
this is rolling for a long time it does
not need to be rolling cut not okay cut