warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact recreate a
reincarnated the following stunts tears
and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised
why should we talk about different
colored trees seasons are changing we
take your dares put them in a hat and if
we draw at the player's heart so then
decides how many points is worth based
on holidaying of a dare it is if the
player passes another player can take
the steal the first player to get ten
points is something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name you basically write
your name on a ball of aluminum foil
JJ you may have seen them before maybe
especially in the news and the dramas in
the drama alert no I'm ksi I'm the
gayest guys mini-vince
I'm gonna win because this is the first
time that somebody's ever requested to
do a night air you nobody wants to do an
idea you actually reached so now we get
everybody to send the foil ball because
we have this new trophy
[Music]
all right the other half to the spirits
alright so basically just make up your
own dare the loser has to pick out of
the loser Cup who goes first
I see whoever has the most chapped lips
I dare you to drop as many utensils on
your foot as you can do that depends if
he draws blood I guess we could decide
how much points after we see in the
object in the head so we're basically
offering JJ to up his points to three
points but sila gets a slap is put with
the spoon instead of dropping it this is
the best
[Applause]
hi Ryan sir let's go
I dare you to put clothes pins on your
nipples and let the person to your right
pull them off he's gonna keep these on
to nipple or simply at our nipple for a
whole round we can always flick them off
at the end of the round when he comes
back to him with fries here if he
doesn't make it one point it's a little
uncomfortable triplet to over time it's
gonna hurt that's I mean it's toreador I
dare you to duct tape or glue your
thighs together to the rest of the game
oh just be like this what about the
peanin you gotta cool like that is your
pants yeah yeah british points points
are more valuable then you to balance on
your back on a yoga ball and then
someone has to hit your face with a
pillow hard for a very specific going to
be using a spoon instead of a pillow
nice wouldn't score this like takes you
back to your childhood days and doing my
job
[Music]
[Laughter]
lick the bottom of a foot I always got
the grossest four to just lick them
biggest but Yoda told you no okay you
had a big toe let's get it
I dare you to get punched in the gut by
someone wearing boxers wouldn't be to
make it more interesting somehow okay
I'd say you can all kick me in the
stomach and my knees so you let Jesus go
oh it's really hard kicks and you feel
like it's a good kick you don't know how
it's gonna be
well up the points
[Music]
so are we all pulling wire guess so
yeah alone it's not low sense it's not
too bad Oh fire what are you doing oh
why did that hurt so much you get and I
dare you beard or mustache put glue or
honey on your face and everyone cut off
their own hair and stick it to your face
anywhere alright so they're crazy but
we're gonna make a mystery hair mustache
it's gonna be right here so you're gonna
be smelling it the whole time we're not
saying where it's coming from
I'm gonna pass this one this is the
whole game yes the game they're trying
to say they're trying to do it for less
than what is it - I said - I mean if
you're gonna do it gladly give this to
you I need what I can get yeah I get the
other side too so it's even you know
yeah
[Laughter]
I am putting you know that I enjoy just
really suck their rule mm-hmm and real
oh there you go good just don't tell me
what I dare you to licorice to our
dreams or eat it three for your man I
can't eat hair the list too hard
[Music]
[Applause]
I think I need to go home and you go
freaking confess some sins I dare you to
drench your back with water and let
everyone flat hand slap you on your back
water make it worse
yeah yeah so much worse yeah Wayne Bruce
well I mean depends on how hard that's
gonna bruise all for sure man I dare you
run as fast as you can on the treadmill
while posting a selfie and a description
on Instagram how fast is your turn old
lady 11:10 that's fast
selphie description and then post you
know wholesale offer anything you don't
make the posts well there's Expo nears
that's fine I suppose
you got to put something
[Applause]
there's no way there's no way no way I
don't think so if he does it you get to
if he doesn't he get one yeah yeah
oh my gosh doing this I don't get I
don't mr. gray
No
I dare you to put some dirty socks in
your mouth do I got some crazy stuff I
don't know when we hiking trip and we
just got back yesterday
hey I'm watching it close oh I got some
hiking socks for you
I'll make a brew of it like hot water a
tea bag tea tea bag with this and we
could put whatever spices and then you
do the tea bag before you pass this Oh
[Laughter]
roasted anchovies oh we put some pickles
in it some Chi in there yeah yeah that's
a piece yup right there there you go
there you go
this is gonna be nasty let's go don't
get it's not changing to you good oh
that's changing colors have a lot of
liquid to be honest Oh mother it's the
fact that there is a sale 1.50
[Applause]
[Music]
this is like a historic episode I dare
you that the person to your left text
anyone whatever they want that could be
interesting yeah technically we're gonna
dare someone to tweet something and
Simon said he would do it for you give
him the phone 51.5 he has a girlfriend
they're gonna make like a year
anniversary in a week he's gonna tweet
out that he's just holding a ring that
age me an engagement ring and we're
gonna let the internet run wild and the
rules are he can't explain it at all at
all until this video comes out okay you
ready we're tied now technically steal
anything all right
I dare you in a soccer kick a rock all
right so we changed it because instead
of kicking a rock which could
potentially break your foot we're gonna
kick a cactus and since they're
basically just gonna keep trying to
steal each other's points we decided
people with the top points with me and
Gregg don't have a chance basically
whoever kicks the cactus the furthest
wins since you end of the seamount
points you guys can get normal but since
you're behind ya kick with your left
foot
whatever goes first - you can pick I
come with you
Mike's ready let's father though right
it hurts
oh yeah adrenalin enough oh god you guys
are crazy
alright you came to the furthest but we
talked about it yeah so I said like like
this is probably the most competitive
one so I'm down for like a three-way win
with these guys I'd be honored to share
that title with them first time at first
time swim through poi and underwear then
make out with fish you'd rather kick a
cactus oh really it's fish
[Laughter]
[Music]