warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact recreate a
reincarnated of following stunts tears
and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video your discretion
is advised
these dogs that were little treasures
thanks with Dawson I said golden
retriever but a dachshund body look like
Harley but they're golden what up ah we
take your dares put them in a hat and if
we draw at the playground so then
decides how many points is Worth based
on how daring of a dare it is if the
player passes another player can take
the steal the first player to get ten
points did something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name basically write your
name on a ball of aluminum foil it's
pretty late go back another episode of I
dare you we have a very special guest
miss Lindsey Stirling whoa hey guys I'm
going to be sterling I'm super nervous
to do this new experience for me but
normally I'm playing the violin and
dancing anything serious
yeah so we're going to do the loser Cup
right now person police amount of points
not to boot from that back into the
video what one of them remembers he
yelled along is okay
a third conga three two one oh my god
right yes
I dare you to go blind for the rest of
the video why am I getting for this I'll
get a negative point oh she's going -
Morgan's no your voter is all the points
you have
Blonsky three points alright promise I
can't see anything
okay the water bottles at the one scene
on your right my ribbons are one of
balloons will yeah yeah we all throw up
water balloon by Sean spoon is filled
with something gross
oh it goes like a water bottle yeah
hahaha you get wet it's not gonna hurt
I don't see like a three Oh
get them wet though you miss no dude we
got a extra one we got excellent Oh
we'll give a real easy three-point I
dared a belly flop onto a bunch of leggo
le flop but you got to do like your
knees you just fall straight into a
bunch later oh dear knees like my face
Stewart's my belly
well anything yeah yeah he's falling I'm
sure hands will catch you or no you have
to
oh it's like a two-pointer that was
about it gets falling on us oh I don't
know what where you would would you
don't break your teeth you're happy
I like barely put my house and I don't
feel dude and I have job that's even
better is that it would be better it
might help you I surrender how many
points okay 202 deducting my head for a
sec hey I'll do it this is only two
points I might have to get a haircut
after this age I was his worst less than
Shawn like a baby look like I'm sorry
yeah you fine - oh my girl I'll show you
from The Times like a beanie it's so hot
where is a crown it's a cool oh yeah I
know what the end would you like I know
oh we should have in the sugar HK - and
us you and you sure gonna hurt on the
way out okay King Rama I need to start
so angry boy alright then she's off to
smash a banana in your face peel a
banana oh that's a big deal I mean it's
kind of humiliating - okay would you
hold it it'll break so if you break it
in half
there's a whole stomach you doesn't
mourn Nana warns okay but or the
I'll do it I'll come up with the dares
boobies customizes and we could be lying
hello he spins in a circle by the pool
and then he has to take five big steps
for whichever way he's clean
is for you okay this is a little bit
more dangerous so we put him right here
on this rock wall and yes the rock wall
yeah how much boys this is your jam how
about four points if he gets across in
20 seconds it up a little bit so we
positioned Shawn he's right there you
can't see anything and what he has to do
is walk across to this platform he has
30 seconds and if he doesn't make it or
falls in the pool doesn't make it
whenever he gets three points just for
attempting here he makes it there in 30
seconds you get four points
yeah the timer three two one
oh my gosh even the time up into five
seconds do great oh hey Sean is good oh
all right I'll give it or fibrous root
of I eat it
you're a you're on right there oh you're
doing so well
oh it's literally got more and more
dramatic he was like oh you stumbled oh
he's going back oh my gosh I've been
come with more points
put chopsticks and your domes and table
hook they're looking at in the game
recliner yeah I'm gonna give a and
testify to falls all you 103 tissues in
10 second three in three a CUDA I said
Wow let me just how many tissues three
points per but he's way to them paper
yeah or anything you the nickel is two
points two points one at three point
three great slider if somebody sizes
inaudible oh I say it with this knife
and just do one tissue Oh
some green ones oh I'm glad I can't see
it already
you spit out all right - what - so gross
Oh
oh my god is it is it salty you so hard
to swallow you could chew that you can't
swallow every well I'm not doing the
Heimlich okay oh I see the green yeah Oh
doing I do it apart Jonah this is salty
Josh shirt eating my boogers I okayed a
brown chasing anything
no you're tasting it all right doggie I
ask pieces go Josh disgusting my date
ahead butter whipped cream pie yeah
right did you sit down smack him with
two thorns whoa that's a real five right
we got some cool whip right okay buckle
is ready here we go this is worse oh man
everything oh my god it's everywhere
looks all right
oh my god but your whole one - hey Oh
votes so wrong
you guys are brutal - points yeah we
could give an extra half it is hey good
day different I gotta first one was like
an explosion
so how you got my ear hi in Higa sweet
one full from the loser cup the group
picks three items from the fridge and
they squirt them in the losers face you
know why you only baby bad this is karma
that's what that is
it's my shoes for a mystery item in my
face
they're like oh that's funky we're
changing it I instead of just scoring it
in Lindsey space what we're going to be
doing is great food makeover three
breathing you read the whole tree house
okay so stuff from France it's called
flow bar and which you can apply on the
cheap sipping tea zone nice French
yellow plastic yellow message alright so
what we're gonna do here is apply this
to the eyebrows oh it does great you're
going to why do you like the smell
mustard I don't think very many people
like give me a statue must so the next
item we have is from so we're going to
have this
look you Joshin hey yo song cheeks
and the jigsaw you may go
am i symmetrical that's the most
important thing doing oh yeah oh good
job so gross oh hey just going can tell
just go buy something right there oh my
god wanna sink you know what's up and I
look so scary
I mean we're well I think you look
pretty good Otis taste so bad I'm just
blotting just kind of big favorite big
boys to make sure I know what you're
talking about
all I know is oh yeah don't worry you
look at your makeup looks good your
makeup look good yeah yeah yeah like a
four-point slaps or do you want like a
two points less we ain't giving you a
three different days two points you
gonna get some soft slaps but you don't
win but when you get some hard stuff but
you to him win one two oh gosh yeah one
two three hey your solo that's coming
baby
Oh
Oh nearly done I go look at the mirror
Hey so Sean just won so I find you to
take this off oh this is sort oh oh my
god Oh
weird that came up so sterling surprise
is actually on the wine violin okay so
great there's also available and signed
the ball blaming I'm just so smashing
Thunder I dare you this room you have
two losers
what a mess for then we have to do the
same thing yep in a round on his little
board while each person slaps w wet
towel with a little Oh like a Dana space
so thank you guys again so much for
watching and thank you to Lindsey
Stirling for being a part of our crazy
show which I know wasn't easy for her
but she did pretty good uh make sure you
guys go check out her channel she does
some amazing content you've probably
already seen it because all our stuff
goes viral but yeah and oh yeah and
leave your dares leave more dares cuz
we're running out of dares leave us more
dares the conversation below thank you
goodbye oh I gotta breathe