warning the following video contains
stupid and dangerous activities do not
attempt to reenact we create a
reincarnate and the following stunts
tears and pretty much anything that's
performed in this video if your
discretion is advised and if we draw it
the players once within decides how many
points is worth based on how daring of
authority if the player passes another
player can take this deal the first
player to get 10 points with something
amazingly not amazing as well as their
name in the Hall of Fame no just kidding
they get the ball of name basically
write your name on a ball of aluminum
foil I don't even have the person to
your right or left your choice to give
you a titty twister up and we do left
and right nice Oh for 10 seconds right
we have three more second
I dare you to wear something for the
rest of the guys I dare you to launch a
road ban face oh this is like a good one
point if you come out like an inch to
two points it's like three dancer yeah
if you go to like the planes about to
break that's like a four fiber this is
one that's about one and a half to two
almost a - yeah dude I'm going
that's like three two thousand five two
five oh hey you got one is that high -
boy five I'll take it you wear bangs in
the dress what they've heard like medium
boys play the rest of the game with your
pants inside out
everything is flip-flop wear socks on
your hands underwear outside of your
pain and your being there's your hands
backwards that's a good 2.5 I'll do that
one that's the same as this yeah all
game I'm just gonna flip it do it very
nice got the socks on the hands go great
jump on a chair with a blindfold on ooh
and the spinning chair you just want to
spin it and jump and hold take your
Bible off you get one spin to try and do
exam time okay yeah I'm gonna do this
trowel right and then you put your Bible
on can't do it again and then go jump
Sandeen hold it baby
great great great
sorry
finish your 1/1000 tied damn nice that
was hella good yeah over this you it I
give you a fork now that's good
good job let's go
I dare you to put butter and someone
tummy and lick it gross to put the
butter in the bellybutton
that's a point yeah so how do we fight
for that I see that you're going in the
belly button that's another point right
there well you see where we're going
when her mouth doesn't actually touch
that's true that's like it's actually
getting jiggling that way yeah it's
gonna pull out all the gunk 3.5 min yet
three four papi that's a good Claire you
say
who's next
let's proud Higgins crying for a little
bit too
it was like the last day today to lick a
dog the big question is where because
there's some 10 pointers zero point I
dunno 10 point I was a pause pretty good
that's like not to girls you know that's
later they've been walking around them
more say in this house oh yeah a small
dog [ __ ] I smell like Fritos three
points over four paws three point four
ball okay I'll do four balls I'm
straight-up opinion he's welcome we have
squirt here sorry buddy smells like
straight-up Friedel's right yummy I'll
let you guys know oh there's so much
there's other stuff dude this is I dare
you to wax off your leg hairs oh not
right now right now we got like some
super sticky tape so Ryan wanted to do
this suggested but now he regrets it you
don't want you oh damn you got something
it this is a good one point first strip
and you get up to three strips hey you
want a 2.5 dirt house up you gotta pull
it off slow oh is it a fast like there's
five okay three three points all right
y'all the air pockets isn't a straight a
massage yeah I'm professional across
that's a wide one slow one faster
ow dude is getting hairy
Oh oh man that wasn't that got like no
hair you're gonna do a great - damn that
was unexpected that was way more than I
thought was gonna happen okay that was
definitely worth three the first was
like yeah wow I can't feel it right I
dated drop a big book on your foot
we don't own books that are big because
we don't read we did a stack of books
and we're thinking what is like neatly
like this right k2 is like maybe like
above the waist yeah and three is like
shoulders oh my gosh damn above the head
and two Wi-Fi right there i 2.7 go -
tired
- yeah good job will hi Greg let's go
Brent Glick a car tire oh I'll do the
outside this way right there I dare you
to make a condom water balloon and slap
someone in the face yes that someone is
me pointless slap this is for the win
for the win one person I am we all take
all of our each just oh oh - what oh
just to make sure that looks good when
it's square like that my Shawn three two
one
oh my gosh Oh
it's time to throw will it pop I feel
like I'm gonna miss this is constricting
my shoulders yes can flexible stop don't
do it three two one one popped one
bounced often just said bounced off
definitely miss it good job bro
I dare you winning John is our winner
today about hair you loser dare which is
let's go let's go loses go to subway and
buy the worst sandwich possible dang
take a marker and draw a gangster tattoo
around the backyard
illegitimate take a marker and draw a
gangster tattoo
you know I'm disarmed - got this in now
in the East Bay la Maya by an artist
named Eric watch that turns into a snake
with the mouth open I just love tea time
and a Hello Kitty eating yang a burger
and it soon love the tribal work and the
Crone cuz Dragon Ball Z school because
there are those who dare rebuff Desai's
John's prized - Shawn - everyone
you in
what so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see the last I
dare you video click the what in the
well the one in the middle because
that's the only option click that 1v1
see Lindsey Stirling do I dare you but I
also remember to leave your dares in the
comment section below we created though