why are you dressed like this was real
honest we haven't done it in so long so
we look cool so we go a little less hole
it doesn't work welcome back to another
episode of we take your dares put them
in a hat and if we draw at the fair
concert then decides how many points is
worth based on how jamming of Adara t if
the player passes another player can
take the steal the first player to get
10 points with something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of pain no just kidding I get the
ball of name basically write your name
on a follow up a little alright so the
person with the least amount of points
has to do the lose there and we're about
to write it right now
hi stare nice there how do we decide who
goes first we make up in the most a beer
and the hardest with a fork no not that
again
Oh Oh hard to grab I'm gonna win that's
what he said about parcours hat throw
egg on a car outside and go lick it of
you must swallow what does that mean oh
that's wrong that is more girls there's
not here but we're thinking about
changing it from the car to this dirty
trash can because it's dirty you're
changing it to a trash can
but we're gonna bump up let's say 300
the shells in there to squish it extra
point for I don't want that I don't yeah
that's too many points Seto I'll do all
that for three
so please agree to the three yes all
right Greg I'll let you do the honors
bro can you break this egg for me I
wondered why you squashes filling no I
think you said three for the show sorry
I've messed up the egg crack oh two
points for the whole thing that's one
point what though
Derrick didn't get it pakka got a point
come on that come up boys you know what
this is your game this game is about
being gross you're when I'm a disgusting
person I know okay I dared to let other
players choose an item for you to brush
your teeth with Oh Paco found a broom
and we're debating what to put on top
yeah you don't have to eat it but this
is now I know you don't like Mayo so two
boys to do that with mail go on three
point what's 30 put like leg hair and
stuff on there such a three point okay
I'll do it alright let's make it then I
hate me oh dude how much you get a nice
100 its on expensive how much - so much
hair you come into it but just go quick
I say for five seconds already got one
[Applause]
that man AZ fresh smile I got manual in
my lips they're not gonna be chapping
let's go
I dare you to pick your nose with a hot
needle yeah we got some extra extra hot
so we're gonna test it out to see what
how many points is worth got tobits I
hate spicy stuff so that's barely in the
dirt no it's in there I could feel the
tingle right now so well how many point
is that word I'll say two points two
points for will around yeah go oh this
sorry just one point now one when it
gets back to you I dare you to faceplant
on five different things let me ask you
this what kind of point value are
looking another four three or four when
you face nine is this like a scorpion
FaceTime my scorpion face man you know
like wonder legs like kick up over their
head
oh the stepwise one what what is a
basement to you then then a why just put
my face on the ground right on that
being putting your face on the ground
face mine is like this that's a face
yeah yeah we got some flour and then we
got some vacuum dirt look at the season
song
[Laughter]
I'll juice do boy okay I got a measure
[Music]
[Laughter]
chuggers much hot sauce hot sauce as you
can okay we got here we got Tabasco
Louisiana hot side sriracha how much is
this worth I need to how do I know we
should do we should have salted the rim
with some hot cheetos it's not too late
something to Roger oh I smell it there's
like a tomato shot hurt just like when
done wrong - oh that was burnt yeah bill
we have with Legos and where then do it
head spin
Oh rizzoli goes that upstairs where you
adjusted it because Derrick is a
breakdancer we're gonna let Derek's
breakdance the 20 seconds he's gonna
have to put on socks and gloves filled
with Lego so we get a show let's do it
go how many points is this
oh we just like after receiving boom 5 6
7 star
[Applause]
[Laughter]
look at all these cuts to all three
points right there
three point five go paint it wax the top
of your hand yeah I don't want to do
that you're knocking Siri I don't think
we even need to wax it would you die for
that
[Laughter]
welcome to the barbershop I'm Derek I'm
going George Costanza all right this is
great this is crazy dude do you look
like a samurai yeah this is the final I
think we need a loser dare let's just
finish you with this this is like way
better than
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah I'm taking turn on the ACS is hot
[Music]
[Laughter]
then any with the guys and I came here
to visit Erika how you doing I think
it's time for me to get Erika what you
think why did you do it take it we're
you the only one that did that or
somebody else did it I'm the only one
why who that cuz you guys filmed I dare
you huh yeah did you at least win oh I
have one YouTube does things