w volunteered to do this I know we got
the shows dear Ryan parcours we haven't
got up our cars in years that's been
like it once
welcome back to another episode of I
dare you we take your dares put them in
a hat and if we draw out the player
comes with any pens how many points is
Worth based on how daring of adair it is
if the player passes another player can
take this deal but first there to get
ten points when something amazingly not
amazing as well as their name in the
Hall of Fame no just kidding they get
the ball of name basically write your
name on a ball of aluminum foil it's
pretty late alright today we've got a
very special guest on you guys may know
him as rice ball your time hey guys yo
sup guys its rice co I've been training
my whole life for this and I would
rather die and leave this household
loser
yeah we can arrange that now it is time
for us to do the loser dare present the
least amount of points has to do the
loser dares so we're all gonna make up
our own hunter Dara put in the loser cup
and if you have the least points you got
a draw from the loser Cup
alright let's do it I decided this first
whoever has the most obnoxious underwear
obnoxious brightest underwear cochon
solo I'm nauseous I'm glad oh you're
about what you got bro it it's just red
I don't know but his is pretty bright
rock paper scissors scissors why did you
say it what I got rock
I think you want Greg go ahead I hope
nobody is scissors the other one I want
there it goes forever your stare the day
I dare the fill underwear with eggs kick
bristle II in crotch Wow that's the kick
briskly how how many points is I think I
don't have to write this after I see
this
I say move in um um you'll get three
okay we're gonna do this escalation
style first person kicks you set the
tone next person in school harder harder
and then Greg goes last he goes the
hardest you ready yeah
whoa kid I'm in stroking oh okay oh
that's a judo kick right that's right
judo Oh whose is grape to the hakka
first ring Bucky oh my god let me scare
pause oh go to the side don't care I'm
sure yeah was that my pot once am I
gonna get three and a half all right
I'll take the three now I just go Frank
Rick I messed up more than that yeah my
ankle hurts for sure I dare you to put
your legs through your shirt arm holes
the rest of the game the only one this
all dressed up tuned I don't like that
one round one point was the max I said
max three so one point initially next
round another one next I'll turn around
sure all right dad quick fashion show
good job
I dare you to put yogurt under hood
let's go look in the fridge so we don't
have yogurt so we're gonna use this
Jesus what is this season soybean paste
we're gonna be a stylist for today what
do you think this is worth how take like
three or something I'm down for a three
degree dew point that's sorry that's it
nice all day go kind of hard with oh oh
oh that's a jail this is feels pretty
good everybody get some my leaves over
there so it all nice I'm like this oh my
god that's due on the other side a
Chinese restaurant all right
made a lake in between someone's toes Oh
trusty it was worse I'll give you a
treat threes a good base just got like
one time you gotta make like a couple a
couple laps
one two oh how many then I guess three
dammit yeah Oh God look at that dude
what if I throw up on his foot extra
point that's right right yeah Oh
all right it's so salty it's so salty
why I was crazy I was crazy have
everyone make a big wet lump of toilet
paper and everyone throws it at you
rabbit sweat that's like deeper but we
slap it on you I've always make like a
cat all the mass yeah so is this one
around our full game I'll steal it from
you oh if you're chicken I'll do it oh
do lesson three yeah
no bet if it's a whole game I'll do
three oh don't give it to him Sean you
already got three Oh jam Peru boy oh
sorry
there you go oh yeah this isn't sticky
there yeah that'll help that don't Anya
let's go Derek I dare you to spin 10
times and jump from your couch from your
kitchen counter wait what I think they
think we're at the other house I'll let
the spinning jumping [ __ ] should we
make it first and engage the points yeah
let me get a little risky I'm down okay
let's see someone get some matches some
gasoline all right what we're gonna do
is we have Derek spin many times on this
platform up here and he has to walk all
the way from that platform while all new
across - right here let's do this if he
does this was it three give me more
points in that rocket hi
all right four points if you fall in
that's a fail but you still get to point
all right County one yo this kind of
scary - you didn't I mean the bad I know
I could've just fun all right forget it
faster Hey 19:20 go all gonna holla dude
of course the fool Oh
haha with danders whole egg in my porno
good job Derek I dare you to slap
someone in the but as far as you can
with wooden spoon it should be we
slapped we should 1.4 hit and we all
need to pick our one thing whatever we
want how many do you want for this point
per slats all right Piper's already we
all pick something let's go alright
that wasn't fun too bad Jimmy darrock
one okay okay two three Greg take the
pain going on with that right right okay
look at this oh one more sore minor is
yours is like like a whip yeah two
different pains Oh turn-ons
let's go
I know Drinkwater an issue of any person
who's playing Oh drama jerk Roxanna taco
has been wearing it for his whole life
I'm down I'm down
oh I'll take your shoes shoes in this ah
this is work psycho for I do it for
three men oh four three two Jackie Jo no
not do it for two minutes
oh you're not coming to live Yuri
hustled in orders crossed in there oh
nasty you go please go view not he's
good there you two belly flop into a
puddle puddle and cement kind of tough
puddle of Legos Legos we lift him up we
grab a limb off the ground
hey long as my head is safe I'm we're
dropping what is this worth was this
worth three three I'm going more than
five let's do it this what I've enjoyed
looking forward oh my god this is gonna
hurt go to higher for give me a fourth
car one two three that's also horror
what happens all right who dropped it is
the guy with the mask you can see I
can't see
let's go Johnny I know you jump and then
split you do that Oh jump then split
makes it bend my butthole let's make him
bend down standing up of oxygen I'll
just form so prove it let's get on down
one point you're at two point four
points one two go what do we that's a
one okay you guys oh man damn whoa okay
I'll give you two years to get into here
oh do ya right go you need help I'll do
my poly
keep it going dude your help pleasure
every no I'll give you I'll give you a
three off
good job job let's go Derek I dare you
to get punched by the person on your
left in the stomach and slapped by the
person on your left in the face how many
points like a three for a pretty decent
for a basic punching slap your do it
yeah I was at you two in there oh yeah
for four points punch in the stomach
slap in the face sat in the face okay
look I'll kick it oh yeah you did a
tallboy oh great you should do you know
how to do that the toilet okay
oh whoa all right let's go there oh yeah
I'm Vinny poker
I quit dude all right great
data link Ryan's ear
what like in his ear or like that but
you're 2.2 be in my ear that's gonna be
infected what if you think is there
whatever you put is this part of us here
in your money oh just this patch right
here you have to suck it if the little
cleans a little it's clean I can get
half a point yeah point just to them
something you're here
alright title 2 points for Greg okay
won't go oh I don't think you're honey
you're getting it out briea suck harder
bro use your tongue
oh yeah I mean it's kind of coming out
oh yeah clean is coming up Oh
honey you're good yeah good job Greg
okay
what's over there just stick your foot
out and I'd like all your toes behind
voices this much look at the bike let's
go look at the road how much is worth
right so three 300 yeah I'm gonna go
good I heard a crunch let's go Ryan I
dare you the loser did the loser dear
losers do it do it this is basically
doing losing to win that can steal it
for the win if it's something to steal I
will check it first right ready right oh
this is my own everyone gets to drop the
time and play button on you know choose
weird different spot no we just measured
this in a BTS video it's about ten
pounds three points to get hit with the
diamond play button even though we
decide this for the win right here you
win one have you watched since second
Channel hey number one
oh dude that looks alright on the phone
to see oh that wasn't a bad ready Danis
bought 40
so this is a contraption that we made
that could swing from A to B and then it
goes this is three two one oh hey you
won though
yeah here you go bro here's your prize
yes first time one I dare you on here
first channel one first time I dare you
know that being said Shawn has the least
amount points so he's gotta do the loser
Dario Shawn rice gum jump off the
balcony into the pool
belly flop holy walk not impossible I
don't know if I can reach from the
balcony but we could go from the one
like a ladder something oh I do have a
letter all right how do I get past it
alright this is the loser Darrin Biggest
Loser 3 - why
getting read now hmm
hey job Sean oh that's just an excuse of
shorter ABS yeah wraps with that being
said Ryan get to sign the foil ball for
very first time we do that we already
know what the surprise is you win your
own surprise go heavy this is let's drop
this on my foot
ha ha ha thank you again so much for my
stuff oh thanks for trying to naughty
guy touching Nixon