yes true a new dance it's really popular
outings company was that the last I dare
even get here with Miranda was here last
one wasn't uh not accurate no it was a
noir story
yeah you know that um she tweeted out
the Jeremy's a college Jeremy wasn't
into Christianity more into [ __ ] is it
her tweets her photos she's cool yeah
came out it literally came out we take
your dares put them in a hat and if we
draw at the fair culture then decides
how many points is Worth based on how
daring of adara tees if the player
passes another player can take the steal
but first there to get ten points when
something amazingly not amazing as well
as their name in the Hall of Fame
no just kidding hey get the ball of name
basically write your name on a ball of
aluminum foil it's pretty late welcome
back another I dare you you have two
very special guests featuring members of
BGA mr. David Choi didn't ruin your
night you say yo-yo too and of course we
have Justin Sean my name is Justin and
welcome to I there you now wave into the
loser cup we all read our own dares and
basically the person's the least amount
of points has to do it so you don't want
to make something too crazy bad because
you might be the loser so we're all
going to just like take a paper take a
pen right write down any dare you want
so now we're all are those are Darren
saying we gotta figure out who was first
I want to decide this
whoever can pull the most nose hairs out
and just know you're good at that that's
why you're not right I
whoever can pluck the most hairs
wherever on your body knives I'm done
whoever can plug the most hair from
anywhere on your body gets a go first so
where you go first and get the sonic I
got one
Gate chimes OH next your hair extensions
Oh classic does it count double you said
hair anywhere I suggest adjusted we
earned it oh I dare you to work diving
goggles filled up with water for the
rest of the games they're like below the
idol so it's like a little it's kind of
annoying you get a point to do it
already
at a point when you comes back to your
turn and if you saw all right okay calm
down that's good
they're never coming sadist mark on your
face after I know okay let's do it
you'll be too much that's good that's
good that works that works all right
Justin then it's okay Gary to put Legos
in your shoes socks and walk up the
stairs
all right you go up and down the stairs
there you go jump uh-huh let's go see
what his games like real quick right so
this is like one point just to do this
stair but for the jump this is one point
five two points two point five three
points I'll do it this is a bag of
jewels oh goodness oh it's in there
that's gonna hurt dude don't like check
this out there's so much to Scott about
dig
Oh got it you got it great cat banshee
oh not that bad ha ha ha that's a high
jump this is it all right hot this is
hot
dude that's right oh my gosh Oh
ain't nobody no blood all right that's a
three-pointer oh I dare you to lick a
whole window frame all right like what
like a widow forget dirty hunter does
this cuz he's some like diseases let's
see disease
I could see it this is a [ __ ] 4.5 more
you gotta make sure your tongue is clean
yeah yep the old 4.5 4 d 1 I'll look it
for Forks alright let's go David
that is so gross sugar nasty can't
believe I did that I gave you to wax
your armpits Oh
so since we don't have wax we're just
gonna use the man Jay's ass don't you
like this yes and hate as much as we
whip it is that new for the both for
sure let's do it this is gonna hurt this
is gonna hurt No oh my god this country
so bad your dream I'm different to one
just like RIPTA like did even blow it
out okay oh you're like boys oh wow
this one's a lot more sweaty you got
nervous yeah too
was it look good that's good Cody Clark
[ __ ] so this is worth three points it's
a 14 answer to be sure though your
eyebrows this time I dare you to eat
fruit any fruit with any sauce in your
fridge do you have fruit I don't think
so unleashing that we got it all funny I
don't notice a sauce on it
bang thing sauce what is big tank that's
BTS dude that's our arrival yeah Banksy
dog Oh
manis and onions how about you mix the
garlic with the mayonnaise and then put
it in the nest so anything I should add
some more stuff while you're at it give
it to me oh that's not what's too much
dude watch me win and the final radius
that was extra plummet just for a little
bit this Jew boy who got more how many
points you would use for three now
people don't agree this is all right
I'll do it for three I'll do for 2.75 to
it for two and you have it I'll do it
for to learn to cute this on them yes
yeah it's bad for you who you don't
taste it if you throw up it doesn't
count
Hey oh yeah
I dare you to duct-tape your whole head
leaving only your eyes and mouth what is
it I'll do it I'll seal it you do it
what is it worth it's a full mass but
for how long and then arrested again
yeah it says a whole game like I
wouldn't do any more not with the
eyebrows eyebrows don't go back fast
yeah it takes like three months how do
you know - shave my sister's eyebrows
before I just want want this protected
and I want to be able to breathe that's
a good point
I'll do it oh my god he's gonna be on
your hair - dude I know baby joy is so
cute you look like yeah yeah I think
it's at 6:03 point on route 5 I'll take
it better than three let's go Greg I
dare you to dip him with snow and
something more like Nutella than
something bad like inspired mayo and
lick it lick someone's toe which stuff
yeah
let's do it please what's gonna be on
the tofu cream whipped cream is easy
bigger like oh and lick it all off as I
can leave stuff for we have to eat the
whipped cream yeah I got past
I don't before yes this is up from
January 30th it's expired by like four
months we're about to get super intimate
right can we just turn on some music
remove I know we only known each other
for three months cry-baby
I think we really need to take our
relationship to the next level there's
some less walls no lick the crevice huh
that's where all the dry blood is
I dare to add four points to your score
you're welcome dad poor but we get to
choose what you do oh we make it uh how
about we have you bend over and we all
we fall with you with the cops they'll
be escalation to yeah
small hit bigger hit figures hit and
then Justin goes last widows horsing
yeah let's do it I don't think you know
how much is gonna hurt
three two one two one oh that's not even
that bad don't want that to look I gots
to make up for it one two oh god this
hurts me more than a demon that doesn't
story impersonation of a turkey smashing
egg on your head from a person of your
choice so I stand like a firing line I
have to jump in the way of it
hey throw up an egg as high as you can
and you have to try and get it to land
on your head if you miss it in the
points no I'll do it
for this Friday hi I'm afraid my break
that's that's good go try go first yeah
ready oh I got it all the hard one Oh
where's you kid
that's high I'll do this for
ah sorry that's too far yeah the points
do do look like party impressive oh boy
get a wet willy in a wedgie okay let's
be real it's not that bad it's got to
either be a super wet willy oh that's
super when I feel like it's got to be
super wet like we're doing something
that big I'm not gonna win so I'm not
going to pass all right you know what
you do since were the leaders we should
just dare each other because of this
wedgie thing we're gonna connect it with
the rope and we're gonna run opposite
direction we're gonna see who gets the
worst wedgie I'm always all flues and we
both win is this possible in this game
uh we gotta get all right that's scary
huh oh my god McDonald's in the kitchen
new one bring Frankie for the council
has pumpkin and we decided that we're
going on two winners this year
you just have to run the someone's
underwear either rips I live in your
ripoff though the or we see it high
enough to we can see cheap cheaper blood
sugar let's do this judges would tell
you as they already wanna get his mask
off delegate you're doing the end yes
right the college smoking I'm taking it
on dude I need help he's part of it dude
it is hurts way more than last night's
all's good optimum Paul Colligan
oh you got the trawler y'all he'll tell
me time oh my god it hurts so much slow
one hair at a time you guys go ahead
you see a moment it's late now have a
headache you finally got it all gave me
out oh there's so much hair right let's
go find everyone else oh my gosh what we
got here is a double daisy chain
where'd you rig let's do this EGA time
guys got a run already three two one oh
cool these are you not hurt right now
here we have two winners that being said
we have a loser dare which I believe
Greg it's time to pull from the cup all
right so loser there loser eats one hair
from each person good luck well I mean I
got here for you right here who has his
hair just as long so we just need one
from joy got one that's it and there's
gonna you gotta eat it dude that's true
of extension here's your diesel it's
like that little darling oh and there's
always hair in your mom yeah that's like
Mr braces to know all right well this is
never happened before but I guess you're
gonna do the prize for two people well
first of all we'll do you guys need to
sign the ball lane
Oh God now it's time for your prize
all right so I went again day care so
much for tuning I dare you um we'll see
you guys next time thank you so much
adjusting chart and datatype check out
the channel links coming soon good I'm
really your ajussi yo yo yo it's so good
MIRR Ballinger sale yeah bro Natsume
congedo uh hey gotta get model nega-chin
go up so y'all we are