No
I got bling
all right horses our unicorn
stopping on a bed of the prettiest
flowers pulling on the roots with
ultimate power don't care what you think
don't care about you this is our road
dog this is how I do I'm stronger faster
than all you haters a blow right by you
on my scooter skater you better my feet
right nobody care you can't catch me cuz
I'm the gingerbread man
flowers stop down for hours so strong so
bad haters you make my grass don't even
know people try to make me cry but I'll
never cry maybe
are you a girl scout
hamish at the door
I know right horses our unicorns our car
lucky ass
oh I'm hard on the streets we just like
that I'm the son of a beach people call
me animal but I can be three a beaver
can suck up a lot of
see I do the dishes every day the water
burns my hands but I'll never show the
pain my hands with my hands hurt I will
be okay I'm trying to hold it in but I
really wanna stir
I got bling
are you a Girl Scout knowledge at the
door
is our unicorn
getting it a get it anymore
Oh
car
the concrete
I don't run I just
do the Riverdance on the dashboard
our into the rich and steel from the
boards
our car
8:24
beso me Savio señores
I'm a bard when I walk through your door