I'm a dream star
i'ma inky water be I don't hang with the
geez I just said with the seas when I
skipped on the streets other people JC a
super bad I seems today wanna be me I
run with scissors I break the rules I
dream and I Drive I'll order in schools
I'm a hardcore thief
I still don't share I don't need to
bring my rep cause I feel prepare look
at that hot chick looking this way I
don't want a girl with these she gotta
have a what I don't want no pussycat
just to clear the fog I do what I want
I just chill with my dog I stand like a
rooster with my cheese stuff hey I just
uh put my shoulders not for therefore
dandruff aches but I'd like to eat draw
draw especially when I'm sick I take
some Tylenol and after then I feel
better I'm a dream store I'm not ain't
you wanna be I don't hang with the
cheese and just go with the Seas when I
sit on the streets other people say she
a super bad I think today wanna be me I
run with scissors I break the rules I
dreaming I Drive I'll order in school
I'm a hardcore D I still below chair I
don't need to build my life cuz I just
build repair falling on some breaking
inch rims cuz I'm bad I applied for the
7 in the 45 somebody makes me mad I love
to play Monopoly I love the police every
single feature I'm in I hold my anxiety
I pillows but my dog I pillow fight like
hat
I'm pillow fighting the carpet I pillow
[ __ ] his lap I feel like my house I feel
a [ __ ] this tree I feeling like the wall
I pillow front myself I'm a chainsaw
I'm my age you wanna be I don't hang
with the keys and just go with the Seas
when I skipped on the streets other
people say she a super bad I seems today
wanna be me who are you
all my things thought you
what ice cream where you at I'm home
dude I'm 39
it's party that was me David Jonah great
question a scrapper dr. Seuss who's your
daddy
my mom give you write that you write
that son I don't have a son but if I did
you would write that yeah oh hey so my
drink stalls you bastards