hey guys so I watch a lot of scary
movies now and honestly I used to hate
them when I was younger but then I
started making videos and realize how
fake they are now I actually enjoy them
but I'm not gonna lie in the back of my
mind whenever I'm watching horror movies
I want to get scared but you know I'm
thinking of all these other random
scenarios of how the movie could have
went instead just like every single
October I go on a horror movie watching
spring horror not horror hold or Moodle
but majority of the time I can't just
ruin the movie for myself instead of
just sitting there and falling into the
story of the movie I'm always looking
for other things like how do they make
that how did they do that effect make
those costumes mother how long that
person interested in makeup I bet this
is what's gonna happen I still don't
know what the Fox says the thing that
ruins it the most for me is that when
I'm watching these movies I'm always
thinking of other scenarios of how the
movie could have won and because I've
been watching so many horror movies
lately I've been jotting all these ideas
down on my phone and that's why this
video is created so for all of you who
watch horror movie thank me I'm sorry I
don't mean to ruin the movie for you
guys well on the bright side for all of
you people who hate scary movies and
can't watch them hopefully you can watch
this video and it'll ruin the horror
movies for you the same way it does for
me so with that being said this is what
horror movies would be like if they
weren't scary
[Music]
never get rid of me you'll be free
judge me
sorry kind of skate a little bit in the
bed wait do that again she's beating by
water do you know that could have been
avoided for just use water
[Music]
hold on this is taking too long
I have a really good idea what remember
that one trend we're gonna do hey hey
what's up it's your boy the priests and
we got the demon right here volunteered
to do the ALS ice bucket challenge so
here we go
[Music]
Oh hurt huh
this is Texas everybody has a gun it's
time to upgrade man they say after you
watch this tape someone calls your house
and says seven days then a little girl
crawls out of your TV and kills you
seven days later it'll be really honest
with you this entire legend sounds
really outdated you said I have to watch
this tape how am I gonna do that I don't
even have a VCR nobody watches tapes
anymore this little girl needs to
upgrade to like a DVD or at least like a
blu-ray and you said somebody's gonna
call my house nobody can call my house I
don't have a landline if anything she
would have to call like my cellphone out
and I'm not gonna answer some random
phone number and he said she's gonna
crawl to my TV nobody watches TV anymore
maybe she crawled out of my laptop and
that's like a 15 inch screen shoot at
the cross and she would have to be
really small if a girl that small were
to kill me Wow what the hell do there
Ebola now you really have seven days no
I even told you
[Music]
you're a perfect guys I'm telling you
she's gonna be perfect for the base but
they should pitch perfect material Shawn
that is d what'd I tell you press a nice
dubstep routine r1 five six seven eight
I don't know put this I don't believe
your son is actually in a coma I don't
understand we move and these things keep
happening why did they keep following us
because it's not the house that's
haunted it's your son
there we go what you heard him there's
nothing we could have done
he was insidious but now he's outside
his booth spirit of the realm are there
any of you with us right now says he
can you show us a sign that you're here
maybe was here was the wind okay you
show us another sign that you're here
because why do they keep coming to me
think it think it likes you what no he
doesn't know that for sure mom man the
chocolate the roses it does like you
I like he's blushing
and that was the first time we met I
couldn't take my eyes off her because
well and we're never on her but even
though I couldn't see her I knew I had
to see her again
[Music]
you're even more beautiful than I could
have ever imagined
[Music]
Oh a crazy nightmare thank God it's over
though
or is it oh yeah this is really starting
to get crazy
it's perfect material
yeah they got weird fast and that last
one about the Ouija board that was just
based off the trailer that they're
playing on the TV all the time now on
the I said on the TV that sound like a
six year old man they play it on the TV
right it's getting even weirder I'm just
gonna start while in my head I'm not a
head on behind but thank you guys again
so much for watching I hope you guys
have a very happy and safe Halloween and
for once in my youtube life I'm not on
an October on a Halloween related video
I'm not gonna put up one of those scary
loud images you know that scares the
crap on you guys in three two one
like I said I'm not gonna do it for once
which is weird
it's actually even more scary I think
that I'm not doing that because it's
like what is he gonna do you know the
thing guys so much for watching if you
wanna see please he wears it behind the
scenes click the one in the left if you
want to see last week's video click the
one on the right and if you want see
anything else is Halloween related and
he's probably there's no place else to
click so just click one of those huh huh
I remember uh shut up Derek