all right patient zero six nine ryan
higa
time is 8 45 a.m introductory session
begins now
all right ryan why don't we start off by
you telling me why are you here
okay um
[Music]
okay before we jump inside the mind
of ryan higa which is a roller coaster
what the hell was that anyway um like i
was saying
we are going inside the mind of ryan
higa
and let me tell you it is quite the
roller coaster
okay seriously is that really necessary
because like this is going to be really
long if we have to cut to a visual every
single time i say the word rollercoaster
fine you know what i'm just not going to
say it we are going inside the mind of
ryan higa
and it is going to be a you what you
know what it's going to be
so buckle up prepare yourselves
because this documentary is going to be
really
freaking stupid
oh okay and now you guys don't cut to
anything now that i'm done talking you
don't cut to anything okay yeah well
would you ran out of
nice visuals of stupid things to cut to
so all of a sudden you're just gonna
leave it on me
okay okay whoever's editing this you're
just a little bit
hey guys hey guys hey guys
hey guys hey guys
and i think we're all set you guys good
yeah camera a rolling camera b
rolling
um okay uh why don't you just uh
introduce yourself
and just say who you are what you do and
why you're here two which camera uh just
this one right here camera hey hello
my name is matthew j williams i'm a
clinical psychologist
and i'm here to assist in the evaluation
of
of you no uh you're coming with me
to evaluate ryan hika okay yeah and
that's not you in this case
no i'm raining austin remember we just
met
i'm sorry can we stop for a second and
just understand how this is gonna
possibly work if
i'm evaluating two i mean i sent you the
chain documentaries to to watch right
that's what
no i watch those but those are still
like he's one person but you're reign
and ryan i'm no i'm just right look
we're just gonna
can we just keep this moving because uh
there's gonna be a lot of stuff that we
have to get through and i
really don't want it to drag the one
thing shane's actually really good at is
keeping his videos
nice and short so okay
all right i'm psyched
because i'm a psychologist so
good um okay so it is uh
day two and don't don't let the fact
that we're wearing the same clothes as
yesterday throw you off uh which is a
little stink
um we are currently heading over to
ryan's house
um but since we have a little bit of a
drive uh what we're gonna do is call one
of his closest friends
and kind of do an interview i guess kind
of you know what shane does and then um
just to get a better idea of you know
what we're really dealing with here
so and okay here we go it is ready
okay hello
hey is this uh is this regina speaking
i am her well first off thank you so
much for
taking the time to talk with us what i
was just saying uh thank you so much for
taking the time to do this with us
what are you talking about i didn't take
anything nope we're just saying thank
you for taking the time
who the hell is that guy i don't want to
talk to you tell me the other way
there we go much better sick now what
were you saying
uh well we're just calling because um we
know that you're really close to ryan
higa and we wanted to know
a little bit about him so you are close
to him is that correct
uh no that's not it it's not correct so
you you're not close in uh no he lives
all the way at his house i don't live in
his house i can form my own house what
are you trying to say you stack that
what i'm saying is you i mean you do
know things about him though right
duh like things that no one else knows i
know lots of things about him that
nobody knows but they're all secrets
they're secrets are there any
anything that you can tell us that
nobody knows then yeah
all his secrets okay
like what exactly um let me think a
little bit oh
i know i got a good one go ahead so this
one time we were all in a
shoot and ryan was sitting in this chair
and i was right behind him because i was
counting on the gross white hairs he was
starting to get
and nobody knows this but then he put up
his phone and i could totally see his
phone screen and i saw that when he
actually opened his phone his passcode
is actually 169 no no regina we can't
that's not the kind of secrets we're
looking for we can't share that in our
documentary why not nobody knows it it's
a good one i'm sure it is a great secret
but maybe something a little less
private than that oh
okay well nobody knows this one but
ever since ryan moved to his new house
everything
changed everything what do you mean by
that exactly
well there's just so many different
things like
his furniture and the paintings on the
wall
and i can tell you right now that the
carpets are completely different from
the enterprise i'll tell you that
those are things people already know but
just by watching his videos i know you
said less private yeah okay but maybe
something a little more private than
that then
fine i didn't want to talk about this
one but when he moved something else
changed as well
okay and i know for a fact that nobody
knows about this except for his closest
friends but
when he moved he also got a new address
and that address oh okay you know what
just forget it all right
what we can use any of that what do you
want me to say those are the biggest
juiciest secrets i have about him what
do you want me talking about the boring
ones like the fact that he's only five
eight even though he claims he's five
nine or
that he got a piano in his house even
though he doesn't know how to play it or
how about the fact that he
has a big drinking problem and nobody
really knows about it except for his
closest friend
wait wait hold on back up what do you
want me to do back up hold on
you just said ryan has a big drinking
problem uh yeah why
oh sure are you that that's completely
true yeah cause that's a really big
accusation to make so we gotta make sure
you get out of my face i wanna see you
again turn it up either way
getting back to what you were talking
about you were saying he actually does
have a very big drinking problem yes
how many times do i have to tell you
guys it's a big drinking problem okay
i've seen it with my own eyes and ears
that's very bad why else do you think he
has all those wet spots on his shirt and
why
i don't like to wear socks to his house
anymore because every time i go there
there's little puddles all over the
place and i like to step in it and it
gets all wet and my socks get whispered
wait what does that have to do with his
drinking problem because he's always
spilling what are you stupid
like i don't know what his problem is
but it's not that hard to drink things
i've been doing this since i was like
five years old so that's
what you meant when you said he has a
big drinking problem that he spills a
little
oh my god yes how many times i gotta
tell you that the same thing i don't
want to talk to you anymore you're gonna
make me repair myself
wow um right
i cannot believe we
have so much good stuff already dude
this documentary 100 went viral
we might we might even be on drama alert
this one right here yeah i think this is
good yeah this is good
all right thank you i'm pretty sure this
is the right
spot um oh you know what actually
one more thing before we actually get in
there i told him i was only bringing my
film crew
so do not let him know what you actually
do because we don't want it to become
defensive
right okay right yeah so if he asked
just tell me like
you're my assistant or make something up
whatever you do just do not let him know
that you're actually a colonial psycho
psycho psychiatrist
clinical psychologist
hey guys hey ryan um good to finally
meet you in person good to meet you as
well man
oh and this is my good friend matt he is
a clinical psycho
it's like patient um
okay um cool well do you guys wanna
head in there and get this thing started
you know what we'll meet you in there
because we're actually gonna go move the
car real quick because we parked in the
sun
right and uh it's we don't know how long
this interview's gonna take and you know
we don't want the ride home to be all
hot you know so
we're gonna go do that we'll meet you i
thought you guys said you ubered here
yep okay well um take your guys time i
mean i will be in there and
i'll see you in there whenever you're
ready sounds good
[Music]
sir what are you doing oh my god oh my
god oh my god look at this
look what i literally just got chills
what are you talking about chills don't
have goosebumps or anything to indicate
you have
okay you know what you can't see a
feeling but did you see what i just felt
just now when i saw what i felt
what does that even mean i think we're
dealing with something
a lot worse than what we thought okay we
literally just met him and he seems
completely normal to me okay you don't
think it's weird that he just
snuck up on us almost as if he was
planning for us to be right in this spot
no we told him we were going to be heard
a specific time and we did just that so
no it's completely okay what about the
aggressive behavior the way he just
shoved his hand out at us show like oh
i'm the dominant he shook
your hand he shook your hand that's
completely normal getting chose again
just thinking about his face did you not
see the way he smiles like a psychotic
person his mouth gets all whiter his
eyes are squinty and no no just stop
okay
i know you want this documentary to be
all entertaining and dramatic but
you can't fake it okay you can't all
that's happened so far is we've shown up
at a specific time which we gave him
we met him you shook his hand and that's
it by the way if you think his face is
suspicious that means your face is
suspicious because guess what you've got
the same face
same face
wow that is
the most racist thing i've heard all
week
what i i'm very disappointed okay that's
not how i meant it in any way seriously
man
it's 2019. grow up
no it's not
so i was thinking we could do the
interview here if that's good for you
guys yeah
that's um that looks great i think we
well there's
we should take this college because can
i get you guys something to drink water
red bull
yeah i'll have a water please thank you
sure rain i'll take a v8 splash
i don't think i have that oh okay then
i'm i'm good thanks
okay what kind of person doesn't have
the splash in their fridge
the normal kind well i think it's pretty
normal to have v8 splash like pretty
stocked up
nobody drinks fade splash literally
nobody well maybe they would
you know if this was like they wanted to
be like a sponsor for this documentary
you know what i'm saying
are you trying to wink trying to get a
sponsor
thank you all right so um how do we
start this off do you want me to
introduce myself or don't even think of
it like that this is just gonna be a
very
casual normal conversation just between
friends
think of it like uh just hanging out
okay cool um
so first off i guess uh is there any
history of mental illness in your family
i'm sorry mentally illness like any
crazies in the family like i don't know
your parents you brother sister cousins
you i don't know not that i'm aware of
no
no huh how interesting what's that
supposed to mean
i'm sorry um ryan would you mind giving
me a moment with rain please
sure why
what are you doing what who starts off a
conversation asking about mental illness
how would you have started it then i
don't know talk about the weather talk
right
who cares about the weather okay i
thought we were here to find out if he
was one of those like crazy stuff
social sociopaths
okay and i'm not gonna be able to
evaluate him if he's uncomfortable and
he doesn't open up to us do you
understand that
so you got a pretty nice house
thanks man fine yes he does seem a
little uncomfortable yeah i think so so
you know maybe just chill out with the
questions a little bit you're right fine
you're right
you're right i will i will chill at the
very least bring it up a little bit more
casually fine okay i will if it comes up
i'm gonna run with it though
okay that's it that's exactly it and i
got it okay okay we're good
okay here yes
let's just come on let's just do this so
sorry about that
oh no problem uh you guys good we're
good
we are good um speaking of good though
the weather has been quite good what
didn't you guys say
i mean for me personally it's been a
little cold but i guess if you're into
40 degree temperatures yeah it's been
kind of nice
that's funny uh speaking of cold
though have you guys ever been to the
grocery store now that place is freezing
let me tell you
god i mean it definitely can be
sometimes such a weird
place the grocery store don't you think
like why do they still have a magazine
aisle right
what is this 2015 do people really need
magazines
like let alone a new issue every single
month right
what are you doing like what do they do
with the old issues when the new ones
come out
what are they doing i'm sorry is this
like some kind of comedy bit you're
working on no no just
casual conversation you know i just you
guys never wondered what happens to the
old issues when the new ones come off
no i i can't say that i have i imagine
they recycle them
oh well um i guess since we are on the
topic of both
old and new issues what are yours
exactly
what okay seriously you need to stop
what it came up naturally this time okay
i don't even know if the rest of this
interview is even salvageable at this
point but if you want to grab anything
else at all you let me do the rest of
the talking
understand fine fine but all i'm trying
to do
is warn you okay he he really knows how
to steer
a conversation it's like
that gas stove or is that electric um
i'm pretty sure it's gas yeah he is
incredibly
manipulative and when i look into his
eyes i see
this darkness you know the part that's
supposed to be colored in the middle
there's this little circle of darkness
that's just his eyes that's how eyes are
shaved and colorized yeah i think he's
one of those things
what things i think he's anemic that's
really
that it is exactly what it is see he
already got tired
i think that's what happened
let me do i have to go pee too
number one you're in the bathroom
so okay i'm sorry
hey are you gonna wait for me
you're gonna okay i'll be number one
that's it
sorry about that again yeah we had some
camera issues to work out and
you know it was just getting really
messed up look guys
i know what's going on okay you guys
don't have to be so sneaky about it like
i will be completely honest and answer
all your questions
as long as you guys do the same for me
because if not why are we doing this
right
there's no point that sounds fair to me
totally um but we were
being honest there really was a problem
with the cameras that we had to fix
right well this like weird error message
popped up on the uh
viewfinder screen on the camera saying
that the lens aperture lens aperture was
corrupted by the shutter speed exposure
on the memory card white balance iso
okay that's not even remotely true there
were no camera issues no it really said
that the lens
aperture lens aperture well then why did
it pop up on the screen
i oh my god look i am so sorry okay you
know what guys let's just
i think we should stop while we're ahead
okay if you want us to leave i
completely understand i think we should
go
you know what no no hold on hold on i'm
actually really curious now um
rain could ask you a question
okay um why are you here
what why i mean do this documentary
no no rain why are you really here
why am i i just told you to do the
document to interview
rain documentary why are you here like
why am i
what do you mean like why am i like
physically right here or like why
am i doing this documentary in the first
place
um you know i don't normally mean i i'm
not why
what do you do i don't what what just
tell me why you're here this is
um just tell me why you're here i you
know the shame
stuff really seemed to brings you here
um are you hearing i'm only here
because i feel broken okay is that what
you want to hear me say
fine i'm saying it i feel broken
i'm broken i mean i mean i've been doing
this for over 12 years you know it's a
long time
it really is um
and i know i don't normally you know
jump on trends and just do
things because it works um but
you know i'm just so i'm just so tired
you know
so tired you're tired
and so you compromised your own values
and basically made a subpar documentary
piggybacking off the success of shane
dawson's series just
because you thought it would be easy
views but documentaries only succeed
when people know they're real
and now you're realizing that you
haven't been real
for a very long time have you i
i don't know i mean i i don't know um
but you do
because you're finally looking at
yourself and seeing the real you
the you that was hiding behind all the
other personas you've created over the
years to hide behind personas like
what are you even i don't know what
you're talking about i think maybe
we should take a little break right now
this is a good spot see there's the
happy funny version of you that uses
comedy as a defense mechanism to show
that nothing really affects you
then there's the most normal persona the
one that you use to show that everything
is just fine in your life despite
everything going on in your head
there's the silly obnoxious one one that
thinks they're smarter than everyone
oblivious
to the fact that everyone sees right
through them and how incredibly dumb
they really are and there's just so many
others that people don't really see or
know about but you've created
all of them for the exact same purpose
to hide and protect the real one
the broken one the one that nobody
really knows or gets to see
including you because in order to see
him
you have to really look at yourself and
you were always just so
afraid to do that now weren't you rain
or should i say
ryan
this whole time okay you know all you've
done is change your hair that's
literally all you've done is put your
bangs down over your forehead
nothing's changed you know what i'm ryan
i'm i'm finished
this was supposed to be a documentary
okay not some sort of ridiculous drama
it's not a drama
really oh it's not a drama well whatever
it is it doesn't make any sense at all i
mean who are you right now
are you rain are you ryan and if so are
you still ryan yeah that makes zero
sense
that makes no sense you said you wanted
to see inside the mind of ryan higo
nobody said that place made any sense
what no i didn't want to do any of this
this is all stupid okay this was his
idea reigns or writing whatever the
point is it wasn't my idea i wanted no
part of this and who do you think you
are
exactly what yeah who do you think you
you know what this is stupid i'm done
stop cut cameras i'm done with this okay
i'm done with this nonsense we're doing
not doing this anymore
i'm gone and i already tell you that
you're inside the mind of ryan higa
nonsense is sense he he
okay that makes no sense and he told me
that don't you get it yet matt
we're all ryan me reign regina
the uber driver the cameraman the sound
guy makes you think you're so special
what makes you think you're not ryan as
well because it's obvious you guys look
the same
i don't that would be the second most
racist thing i've heard all week if it
wasn't coming from myself
oh sometimes personas look different but
like i said they're all created for the
same purpose okay
okay well tell me uh if i'm a persona
ryan and you've named every person of
ryan that exists
tell me which persona am i why don't you
take a look right there
and find out for yourself oh my god
no no no no this doesn't why am i what
this doesn't make any sense
the persona with the drinking problem
what no no
no no this doesn't make any sense like i
said that's because you're in the mind
ryan higa i know stop saying that
and why are you here tell us why are you
here right why are you doing
right why
what brings you here
all right patient zero six nine ryan
higa
time is 8 45 a.m introductory session
begins now
all right ryan why don't we start off by
you telling me why are you here
okay um
well i i tend to spill a lot when i
drink things
and i kind of always just wondered sorry
one second
camera is kind of functioning
lens apertures corrupted come on again
[Music]
hello
what the hell is this gross