you don't know me all right if you know
me when's the first time we met internet
icon nope that is it no what I'm doing
this because I respect Ryan and and I'm
also like friends with Paco I don't know
about France I don't know say friends we
are rolling let's get the clapper claps
go okay welcome back to another exciting
edition of off the pill podcast today we
have a very special guest mr. kevin wu
kevjumba I was I was expecting my
applause yeah on your way up and we have
the moderator Paco like me more than
they like you the competition starts I
knew me and Paco would just be you know
I knew that too I thought you guys are
like we're gonna get into each other's a
bit to each other's skin and is that
what the under each other I'm gonna skin
a little bit brighter hey now we went
too far yeah we're trying to keep my way
too early way too far I know yes we're
trying to make money yeah go let's do
you want to throw away front year you
know your responsibility I don't even
get paid for doing this yeah you really
he's not going to any Maya yeah you
don't get paid this is like bullying me
right now what Wow yeah this is Paco's
like fantasy right now Paco when yous in
high school at ninth grade you had
dreams of we're the same age yes you
dumb it just the way you acted
you know noon that you're like younger
everyone everyone always thinks that I'm
like still 23 22 well you guys can we
grow up that's why can we are getting
look at your schools bro did you
actually curl me nah this is all natural
okay this is real style you know why
this is real stuff - hey hey are you
watching the audio levels cuz I don't
think you are
I kind of am okay I think we're good all
right well we peak it's like part of the
extreme it wasn't it it was pretty a big
part of it just that yeah it was uh
we're celebrating you know POC will be
held in our friendship I'm gonna be the
bigger man here yeah Paco you let's
let's let's be clean
you are way bigger you're like seven
foot three like way older - yeah well
birthday yeah 28 when's your birthday -
12 years older oh you guys are pretty
climbing but we're like basically
brothers yeah okay in closeness we're
six days apart right six days apart yeah
six days apart whoa we celebrated our
25th birthday together here in Vegas
actually I've heard a lot of stories of
others yeah we have yeah we heard the
doll actually that somebody made for us
the voodoo doll back in the day best
listeners can't see but Kevin's holding
up a best crew doll made by one of our
friends
that's 21st birthday and I'm giving it
back to him because I was holding it for
a long time on this podcast you can't
see me holding it up but that's what I'm
doing and I look like John Cho but I'm
wearing a breast crew outfit remember
when we first got those like I do on the
way to this shoot like the shoot the
poreotics yes that was the first time we
just because we didn't have an outfit
initially right the first one yeah we we
went to hmm to buy the outfit it was the
day of the shoot we just like what do we
wear you yeah and black in yellow was
really pop
their song at the time Wiz Khalifa and
we saw these ridiculous black and yellow
outfits yep and we just on the globe go
create our characters through the
outfits yeah I think we have no sponsors
for this one right so for this episode
was sponsored by Jim oh yeah yeah Jim
milk I mean we're gonna have some
sponsors but when they heard calf
Jumbo's going back they're like we're
gonna hold back on this one did they
yeah yeah okay that's again this episode
is literally you guys just bickering
you guys are like like sisters well you
know he gets jealous when you know
Ryan's friends are here and you guys and
you know and you know what too though I
knew this is gonna happen because
personality-wise that's a lie
oh man this is just like a roast session
I don't get jealous and when his friends
come over just you
I think it's cool it's cool I think it's
cool you know you sound real jealous
right do what was that what I saw
what do you mean I saw Dan show us yeah
this is me excited about today okay so
let's get into it before you guys start
fighting again let's start with the
easiest question that and the most
common thing that we got online since we
announced that you're gonna be here oh
no is there gonna be a broad question
it's it's not it we gotta go are
specific okay let's go into specifics
then okay and you know what I'm not even
ask you that until later let's talk
about something really current yeah
let's talk a little bit about how we
started talking again recently and that
is about the playoffs you asked a ball
player yes
so I told Ryan I've been watching my
basketball and I said you know you flirt
with the idea of talking about sports on
your podcast so not just basketball I
know you're a fan of wrestling I am but
I'm not a fan of watching it of watching
wrestling yeah you're only okay I like
to wrestle right I don't like watching
wrestling but you like I like like watch
yeah yeah okay I mixed I sorry yeah you
like watching and then a you like
watching NBA yeah and there you know
sports kind of niche your fans that
don't watch it don't really relate when
you're talking about correct they don't
usually relate yeah yeah so not a lot of
them at least right so when you tweet
about it you talk about it there's like
crickets you
most people I would say especially on
Twitter that's not the audience for it
there's some people especially because I
came out as a Spurs fan a while ago so I
have a bunch of like certain followers
that are Spurs fans that respond but
other than that it's like nobody cares
oh yeah Kauai just hit that game winner
in Game seven
I could tweet it but nobody on my feet
would carry would care if I tagged like
Raptors and Canadians or something like
there's no nobody would care I mean what
you wanted me to talk about that here
and I told you that I don't think most
people care about that stuff here I at
least so I'm convinced that people would
care maybe not Paco but but playoffs are
coming because it's so big everyone's
talking about it like yeah regular
layout sir I don't think people care
right like yeah you know there's 82
games in the regular season that's a lot
of games yeah and sometimes they play
back-to-back and to be honest I check it
every day even during the regular season
I said oh I'm a big fan and and I guess
you know Ryan's also a big fan um but
the conversation was more like you know
people might not track the stats or as
much or like follow certain teams
because not every city as a team yeah
and you know YouTube is global luckily
NBA is becoming a little bit more global
but what I want to say is like sports in
itself can be relatable maybe not sure
the data or or certain players
franchises but just the what you can
learn from sports how sports can inspire
you you know to work hard and so it's
more of a reflection of like our culture
our you know our daily life and how we
can succeed right paka
yeah I just don't like that you said can
inspire you and you looked at me and
then said to work harder you try to pick
a fight again I'm sharing eye contact
and it just so happened that I wanted to
give you some inspiration I knew this
was gonna happen
I just Michael I know you work hard I
don't know what it is when he puts his
mind to something he gets it done it's
just getting him to put his mind into
something yeah but does he put his mind
on a lot of too many
things is better not really I'm I have
an addictive personality so if I really
like something then I just go hundred
percent into it that's good yeah I mean
it's good if there's no gets bored
easily
yeah jump he jumps into different things
like he'll be into basketball one week
or maybe more than a week then you'll be
into stand-up or whatever it is yeah you
don't know me alright if you know me
when's the first time we met internet
icon nope that is a no what are you why
yeah movie man uh-oh my name is continue
with your sports analogy it was getting
somewhere good it sounds like you're
being most sarcastic no it's um we're
good
it was getting somewhere good I mean
what I said what I need what I said
about it but you know I get what you're
saying
I just think like even like when I'm if
it were like me and Paco and we'll right
we're I mean the most regular people on
it unless the guess is somebody like you
they don't even watch basketball it's
hard to like even bring it up and talk
about it when even though I as much as I
like it it's like they probably didn't
see any of the games or really know
who's on whose team right I mean you
don't really know I mean I know only
like the stars names none of them yeah
but you know when in the playoffs like
when Kauai hit that yeah did you know
that everybody move memes pape up for me
yeah means like when Damien hit that
that three-pointer up from like 35 feet
I mean people are gonna see that yeah
and you can talk about that but you know
in the playoffs there's more of those
happy accidents where people are like
hidden big shots and the pressures on
that's the thing about sports it's
competitive there's high stakes you know
these these players go through crazy
amounts of pressure they're playing back
you know on Monday Wednesday
friday-sunday like they're playing four
games a week and it's just like you're
seeing people at the top of their game
go at it and like whether it's be sports
regular sports you know you watch movies
TV like you're getting the top athletes
or performers and they're just there in
the moment and it's it's transcendent of
just
oh I'm not a basketball fan like you can
respect and appreciate yeah you know
seeing like transcendent performers like
Kawhi Leonard yeah for instance because
like no matter what you do to be like
the top 1% of what you do requires a lot
of hard work and dedication and you know
a lot of hours people don't see right at
like a few seconds of glory yeah that
they all do see ya so I guess trying a
segue into that you know you were one of
the top 1% of youtubers thrown amount of
time yeah but like you know I mean you
still had a very solid foothold in the
YouTube game you know like a well-known
amongst a lot of creators and fans and I
guess you know out of nowhere it kind of
you kind of just like fell off the face
of the earth were yeah you like
disappeared I didn't know that yeah
there's people were starting to put your
name right next to the like you know
Bigfoot and Loch Ness monster Jumba
that's when you started acting right
right so it it went through many stages
of like you know from you to to wanting
to do acting yeah and then transitioning
from like you know I'm gonna take a
break from this career chase and and
just focus on you know family and in my
life so from when you were like at the
top of your game cuz you didn't it's not
like you became all like although some
Kev's irrelevant and he's gonna stop it
was when you were still getting tons of
views you were still very popular you
just want to go a different direction I
would say so and and um and this goes
back this is gonna be like you know a
friend moment for us - but you were
doing YouTube and you like we had
private conversations where you're like
yo I'm committed to YouTube like this is
my bread and butter like I don't need to
do the whole LA thing I don't need to do
movies I don't need to act
I just love YouTube and I was like and
that's that's amazing like well I I
wanna like see like like what's you know
on the other side right like I I had so
much enjoyment on YouTube
but I I felt like I felt a sense of like
harmony
some may not be the best word but it
felt like that you were gonna be able to
walk that path and because I was like
your quote/unquote brother like best
friend at the time I was like or one of
your best friends I know you know so I
was like yo I I get to still like
experience it through you so like if I
don't do that at least I like I know
that you get to live that life and I
could still like connect with you and be
like dude what's it like and so I was
able to like confidently go this other
direction right Adie I mean I didn't
know that but I mean I thought I'm at
the time like I remembered that we
talked about it and you did seem a
little like oh no you were just kind of
tired of being kept in a box like kind
of like you had this persona on line
right you you I mean you had a surgeon
persona I mean the same way I did up
until very recently where you felt like
you couldn't say certain things and you
couldn't act a certain way and then you
kind of wanted to get away from that
from what I remember
at least I I mean there was a there was
some of that um I felt like I had
YouTube I was making videos trying to do
it with other things that I was
interested in I was in LA so there was
there was a lot of influences right like
meeting older actors and getting their
perspective and and just seeing you know
I'm I grew up in Houston as an Asian
American which we'll have a conversation
about because you guys are from Hawaii
but I was always a minority and I was
always like told I can't do things like
you know I played soccer so I was always
the only Asian kid and I was I tried out
for club my first year and I was on the
e team that's the so they have a b c d e
so E is like Division three or four it's
like the lowest division and I didn't
even like there were so many kids I
tried out so there did they're basically
just grouping kids and like you know
that they had their favorite so they put
them on a and B but I was on the e team
Mike and I was like dude I don't even
think they saw me play uh-huh and I was
like the only Asian kid at the trial and
you know fast forward six years I'm on
the eighteen
like I'm on the a-team I've built a
relationship with trainers that are
world class like well not world clap but
they played professionally and they're
now training and they were like kept
mentoring me and eventually I became on
a team and it was just through you know
like proving that I'm not just you know
the scrawny asian kid like that needs to
be a class but but going into like
entertainment doing YouTube like a lot
of my videos were about being Asian
American and stereotypes and and and you
know I grew up in a culture where we
were you know especially Asian men like
do you masculine you know so so I think
wanting to like like as a youtuber like
my audience was growing up as well I was
growing up and just wanting to have a
presence on on a more traditional
platform so that like people who are
like Oh Asian Americans don't belong in
Hollywood or Asian Americans don't
belong on TV or if you're gonna be on TV
you're just gonna happy the quirky best
friend or like the token Asian and I was
like I'm I'm not cool with that I'm not
cool with that but but that's that's all
that's a that's a whole nother I mean
that's fine I mean that shows it's just
interesting cuz you you saw that issue
right and then you just said you know
what I'm just gonna go do it and that's
something that I've always kind of
admired about you is when you set your
money you're kind of like hit that's why
you guys fight a lot you guys are very
similar when you really set your mind
something you just do it put us in this
you're like him with but with work ethic
no honestly I'll let Paco speak okay
I'll correct and Paco is people who is
naturally he's like like we talked about
this before like in sports and stuff
he's naturally gifted
yeah like wow you were on the e team I
was already a team and I was out
practicing what I do like scrawny agent
down there dude yeah I was crying he was
huge
he had the arms but what I was saying is
that I mean that's what you've always
been like when you want to go into
acting you went full-on into acting I
did I loved it and you know we did like
I said we could do a whole park
about like you know just like the craft
of YouTube and the craft of Paco being
podcast host and entertaining himself
like there's a there was a there was a
process to it that I I I really enjoyed
huh and I mean like it would be cool to
like talk about that on another podcast
cuz then you could come back and then
you know bring the view yeah I mean
you're you're welcome back yeah sure
you will be like honestly no it'll help
I mean whenever we have guests it's
interesting and people want people have
been asking for you you know that's
great no I mean obviously you're welcome
and after this time after this podcast
maybe you can try out this YouTube thing
you know I mean you kind of cool got it
still it's being and I told you earlier
I think you should do a podcast I mean
you have like a radio voice and you're
really good at interviewing people I
mean you're naturally a host so like I
mean you could essentially be yeah be
fun what me and POC would do but in one
I'll just take Paco's job you could do
that I don't need that ik my own I mean
I I mean he's good but he doesn't you
know keep up on friends and he's not as
funny as I am his haircut is wack we're
not coming after your lame-ass job right
but this is a dope podcast I'm just
talking about specifically you're wrong
[Laughter]
actually that is something that uh Ryan
was talking about was like the
challenges above you because you're so
charismatic and on camera you're just
like a really likable and relatable
person and I think that's something that
a lot of people enjoyed and so to get
out of that shell when you went into
acting everything did that prove to be
something that seems to be a huge
obstacle because you were so used to
just you know being you on camera that
if someone saw you in a different light
or in a different role they're like
that's kind of like being typecast yeah
that's not that i nodi I feel you
that's a good question Paco you did your
research like that's awesome I always do
my research that's why you ain't taking
my job that's true that's sure no so I
think
with with that with acting right like
the format is a little bit longer so if
you like play all your cards you know
people are gonna like lose interest
after a while so you kind of have to
like internalize a lot of those like you
know the charisma or you know people
don't want like charismatic characters
on screen like you they do like in the
right moments but like not all the time
whereas YouTube you have to be turned on
all the time and it's yeah it's the
thing that I was talking about was with
I was like with Ryan earlier I was like
you know I think maybe Kevin just came
at a point where maybe it was a little
too early because now they are hiring
people who are just like charismatic in
just themselves like Kevin Hart or ken
Jeong or the rock you know yeah this is
these people who are truly themselves
where if you you know try to do your
right with you right if you came at the
right time it might have been just like
you know so like Ken Jeong Kevin Hart I
would put them in the comedian category
yeah I mean you're funny too you know
sometimes I know he knows dude you have
to tell him yeah we're talking about
like putting them in categories of the
actor yeah Union but and the rock is I
would say he's an actor and he's been
doing like dramatic and they're all
really super high level talent eeeh 1%
like you're talking about but just the
category you know like yeah like a
communion needs to all as well always
just like more so bring a certain energy
right so I mean speaking on that is
there any just cuz I'm sure people gonna
ask what do you what are your plans like
what do you want to do next
Wow man okay so people are gonna ask
yeah sure yeah
no I came on this cuz we were gonna you
know get deep and talk about anything
that the fans want to hear and you guys
want to hear so the question being like
what do I want to do next
um I I've enjoyed I I would say I've
enjoyed having a more private private
life definitely last you know half
decade it's been it's been really tough
really challenging
so if I if I tried to like maintain
YouTube and like do a career at the same
time I think I think I wouldn't have I
wouldn't be here right now you know I
would probably just like given up and
there were times where I like felt like
giving up and and so just to answer your
question in a broad way like I'm just
kind of cultivating myself and then I
feel like at some point there will be a
period where I'm like I would love to
reconnect with with the people that I
collaborated with that we're part of
this community of creators and also with
with audience subscribers viewers that
supported me and grew up with me like
that's the ultimate goal right but I
want to be at a good place before I I do
that right I make that connection with
them so is that like that sounds like a
comeback yeah
I'm not calling it a comeback I'm just
saying I'm trying to work on myself
yeah but eventually I mean you'd like to
reach back out to that audience right
well I'm not gonna sit here and be like
eventually I'm just gonna like like just
chill at home like I don't care about
them no like I eventually would love to
be in that position right but you know I
do like setup maybe I set a pretty high
bar like I you know cuz I I see you know
this we can I can change the topic but
you you see a lot of youtubers that that
they represent something like being an
influencer and I like I just read The
New Yorker article with the makeup you
guys know I mean you're the trending
curator of the yeah yeah yeah so like
that's a that's like a case study for
like you have celebrity you have status
you have millions and millions and
millions of influence and followers but
like are you saying the right things are
you being the right person and I feel
like there are there are really good
role models out there that I can like
support and channel my counter my energy
for and
until I can like look at myself and be
like okay I can I can be that role model
to on that on that very big public level
maybe not anything as close as like the
heyday you know back in what 2010 to
2012 but like even I had a small level
like yeah what I would love to do that
night
I do do that you know I'm coming on here
to talk to you and yeah my family feels
like I've been present you know but it's
just maybe the the audience on that saw
me on YouTube there's like there's
definitely like an absence there and
it's it sounds it so it's almost like a
relationship type of thing where it's
this what it sounds like to me at least
where you're like you know you're not
ready to come back to YouTube just yet
you know you're trying to find yourself
be securing yourself and everything and
when everything I right yeah right you
know it's definitely relationship just
like our relationship yeah our you know
we see each other once every three years
yeah and was just but you know I'm
dipping this is like me dipping my toes
in and like I said I'm doing this
because I respect Ryan and and I'm also
like friends with Paco I don't know
about France I don't know say friends
but no I just I came on here you know I
couldn't turn down an invitation to be
on the show and I actually was like
watching the show from back home in
Houston and was like man be pretty funny
to reconnect with Ryan and just talk
about MBA which is what I requested Paco
request that I feel more might like
Rocky's shirt yes why isn't this the
conversation because you guys lost okay
well you still we got a problem
um just just to get a little I know you
didn't want to get back into it a little
bit but wait you're gonna you're not
gonna let me I mean we got a lot of that
but go ahead when you're a true fan you
never lose its a growing period yeah you
don't lose weight you are on the team
what's that boy
very touchy subject for him this just
happened yeah but this I hey don't make
me what am i doing right I don't even
know what I'm doing but don't make don't
open Pandora's box breath what there's
nothing you your shirt says clutch city
but it's automatic that y'all gonna lose
Oh word yeah what's up I come with the
bars too boy oh we're gonna talking
about that you guys actually made music
together and some really I know you know
it's all plan fire you has been really
like successful songs and I kind of want
to know before we go into the shishi
break how was the collaboration process
on that I mean I think it though it
stemmed from the joke of being like hey
can we get away with doing something
like make a love song almost about
something while being douchey mm-hmm the
joke was being douchey yeah essentially
but then us getting away with it giving
a a reason to do it being that were nice
guys because we don't I mean we wanted
to play the nice guys we didn't want to
be actual douches so it was a way for us
to do those jokes without having to I
guess be real douches because it's not
funny if you're actually being a douche
right yeah it's yeah it was like a so it
was Ryan myself and also Chester yeah
and he wanted to do a song like you use
it he's a musician so he was like like
pitching us song ideas all the time I
feel like and it was great his
creativity was very motivating and and
then he kind of had this hook he was
like mm and he would just sing it and
then and then like when it finally
clicked for him for him I give a lot of
yeah I do give credit to Chester for
coming up with that kind of hook and
then and then because we did shed it
tear like it was a lot of circumstances
that went into it and Ryan has a
specific humor where he likes to like be
hardcore and like but then like there's
some heart to it so it was a it was a
good combination and and shout out to
Wong foo cuz like they they started like
the Asian being nice guys thing and we
was just like a lot of things coming
into play and and yeah I wish we were
able to like incorporate more of the
community in that but we ended up going
and shooting the video like the same we
pounded it right I mean we'd happen
really fast we thought it was a
your video but we didn't think it was
gonna be like No yeah zero zero budget I
mean but back then though like everyone
yeah and then if you got like even a
decent amount of you see because this we
knew I was gonna get some views because
it was bigger bigger production for us
at the time of YouTube nobody was really
making like that kind of content we knew
that if we put that out and get more
views back then if you got that kind of
views and likes and favorites you would
be on the front page so they just
exponentially just boosts everything so
I mean it was I mean we you posted that
version of your channel I posted in mind
it was bound to it was a little easier
to understand the algorithm we knew the
algorithm yeah we like you interests you
were like really methodical about when
to post how to post how to get the
viewers in and it just yeah I just
really exploded and yeah time for a
quick shisha break yeah sure all right
shishi break and we'll be back and we're
back nice Thank You barato
thank you I haven't heard that
compliment before because you got a
high-pitched voice actually Kevin I know
I wish I had both of your voices really
because yes like oh sorry I'm just
punching in the face like voice where
it's like but like in a good way you
know I mean you have a bass voice but it
because your nostrils are so big word
that the sound just escapes all three or
Phasis at the same time fake news that's
not how science works per sign I should
just make out hurt and neither do you
I can smell Kevin and plant from there
man Kevin went to UC anxious yeah but he
didn't graduate yeah but he could
actually I did graduate did you really I
got a diploma this month actually oh and
that was not UC Davis right
yes dude I forgot to ask you about using
Community College I don't know actually
why are you you lie to your life you lie
more than Trump your fake news well
until one my own you actually did not
know you were still except that I like
you that's the only I didn't know that
you were still going to school though up
until now I was I know I am I'm done
yeah you are done now and it took him
ten years congratulations it did take me
ten years on and on yeah and what did
you what's your degree in so it's it's
psychology I finished my last is that
even a real degree and a half online uh
and like I had done so many courses like
I would take you know riding courses
I've done I've hopped major so many
times and then it was just more product
of like what's what's like what's the
most convenient for me
and it was again psychology yeah it was
I'm not saying psychology is like
convenient it's a very complex and high
level like science but for me at the
time I like wasn't always at at home and
I didn't wasn't able to travel to campus
like well every week so I just didn't
online degree Pam yeah but only those
last few years most of my degree was in
class but just the last two years was
online got it
well I mean like I was saying though
kept got into UC Davis what you get into
so I got into a lot of trouble uh you
know you know I also got it actually I
didn't even make it to you H you didn't
make the UA more like everyone in Hawaii
that's like their fallback like I want
to laugh but I'd feel no we're gonna
we're gonna offend all the people who
didn't I know I don't know what it
really means to very common in Hawaii
you know 2.8 GPA did you just get in
yeah okay I didn't get that do you still
have dreams like about like high school
or like maybe not passing a class or no
no no do you I do
yeah I still have dreams when I'm like
in school like I'm like
I've dreams where I'm retaking middle
school and those are like are you a kid
dreams I'm no that's nightmare mortal
yeah it's more like an Asian nightmare
yeah okay but it's like because what I
feel like I could probably start like a
an a group on this yeah I I think well
we're your parents those I mean I've met
your parents but were they scary
typically like strict like Asian parents
you know they you know regardless of
them personally yeah it was just like
it's a cultural thing it was you I don't
you want it to be know me yeah strictly
were you a good student no oh
how'd you get into UC David that's a
pretty guys YouTube when I don't like my
extracurricular stuff like soccer you to
right right right
got it yeah my grades were I don't think
I was top fifty percent but I went to a
very competitive high school i
shouldn'ta liek that oh yeah I didn't I
didn't my grades weren't good
you shouldn't have leaked what I wasn't
even like in the top fifty percent of my
high school that's fly mints I I mean
and then look where you are
em I guess so still got your degree
right you went on this crazy adventure
of eat that is YouTube now licking ya
know you're in movies you did a bunch of
stuff and you didn't its you didn't need
to get straight A's
right you could still do things right
and my parents still love me there you
go yeah it's all your kids out there are
your kids out there doing really poorly
in school we're not encouraging you to
do that yeah but it's it's possible to
make it better do well for parents yep
for yourself but actually you know
talking about your relationship with
your parents and going into it the same
I like it when ya going NACO talks a lot
sounds like a dude no go ahead
but going so the question that comes
from Twitter and it's a from Tony stank
south Tony what's the best slash funny
memory you have while filming a video
with your dad because you said your
relationship with them wasn't so
stereotypically Asian
you know so I didn't say that well were
they wearing I said I was talking about
the strictness of you know it was a
stereotypically agent oh really
okay yeah so then I guess if you could
explain you know because the
relationship with your dad was very
public and it's very like you know smile
that part was not so I guess what was
your favorite memory and what was that
like - I'm trying to think of a specific
memory but like I mean one comes to mind
when when we did like what we hate about
each other and Mike there's this one
joke I like could not stop laughing and
he was just talking about my like bad
eating habits and like where I would
like not close my mouth I would eat
loudly and the way he said it was like
he used the example of like you know
when you eat noodles he's like my dad
but you can watch the video he's like
like a noodle when you eat the noodle
and I was like at first I didn't know
what he was saying but what and then he
just kept saying second noodles and I
was like yeah that one that one comes to
mind yeah I mean he's like like you said
it seemed like he was having fun and he
did it I mean I don't I don't really
know I mean it seemed like he enjoyed
that attention right yeah yeah so I
didn't have to like pay him back her
mm-hmm you know give him residual checks
I'm sure he wasn't asking for him yeah
but yeah and that's that was that's
unique to him and he just like I'm
grateful for that we got this might be a
little personal too but you have talked
about it publicly and everything but uh
Eddie ass please tell us like what
happened with the accident and like what
do you been up to recently you know and
I know we can go like a full podcast
about uh-huh because I'm sure yeah that
in itself yeah cause a lot of
realization in your life right but if
you could give us a spark note version
you know the thing that I used a lot in
high school okay yeah so you know
shout-out to Eddie for you know asking
the question and for Paco to segue it by
saying it's just a little personal you
know he's just like oh it's not that
person yeah you know it's it isn't
it's nice to sparknotes through trauma
it is yeah it's it's uh you know just
get so like quick glance over it you
know we don't have to go into it you
know I mean if you're a relative out
there well you talked about it yeah you
want me I got you I'm you're gonna base
you're gonna make him knock oh it was
bad it was it hurt a lot and I was sad
and my parents were sad and I had a like
walk a long way back to get back to
health I mean you I mean this is where
where did this happen um it happened in
NorCal just so people okay yeah by
myself I was by myself - and you said
you still I mean it still hurts you
today uh well yeah yeah I I still have
residual pain from but talking you want
to go and talk about pain no no no I
mean you can we're asking about your
story so you know we want to hear more
from you I know I know what I need
empathy if we're going to talk about it
yeah I mean I mean yeah I mean it it
sounds like something that you know that
you have to deal with a lot consistently
and it's always something that but I
guess because of the pain it's allowed
you to grow you know obstacles in your
life for the things that either cause
you to change and adapt for the better
or you either like let this toxicity
like just fester in you and you just
like are matted like situations around
you and you know but it seems like you
took it in like kind of like made it
into a positive
I would say I'm living with living with
it yeah sure
I wouldn't like put this like
inspirational ideal twist on it and say
it's like been a positive experience for
me but it's definitely been it's
definitely been an obstacle and and part
of overcoming those things is is gonna
make you stronger but but I'm not too
focused on on the end result of like
coming out of this like stronger and
like ready to like teach the world how
to deal with you know this kind of thing
that would be like
that would be like down the line but
right now I'm just just trying to like
live a normal life what do you have to
say on the matter Ryan well I mean I
don't think we should keep you don't
want us talk about we don't have to keep
on that so yeah I just think it would
take up longer than Ian that's why I
said so we can wear em back you're more
than welcome to come back yeah multiple
top possible you have me back on the
show we got to see how the views are
come back ever you might come back as
the moderator I don't know yeah yeah so
like right now you know like there's a
little bit like you know dissing between
us it's like friendly competition or
whatever but when you were near the you
know the top of YouTube and stuff and
you and Ryan were kind of like like best
friends side-by-side did you view him as
competition though in a way cuz I was
like you're a very competitive person I
am but Lydon I love humble people and
Ryan's one of those and so like I think
before I met him like there was a lot of
YouTube like like oh they're both Asian
and they're comedians and and they
should like who's better but like once I
met Ryan that like that did like
evaporate it was like literally gone a
lot of a lot of people kind of like our
fans would make us have some kind of
beef big day would have beef and I
compared you know I mean you've seen it
you've seen the comments people just
naturally because there wasn't many
Asian I mean there was agents but me
Kevin I where we were at the top at the
time so naturally people are gonna
compare us because we're both Asians and
we do comedy or yeah you're doing vlogs
I started doing vlogs more skits you did
some see what you did skits to you did
like that vlog skit vlog and Ryan are
also very different yeah and my
completely there was such a big need for
like Asian American like there was
enough pie I would say for like the both
of us like it wasn't like we're both
fighting for the same audience it was
like he's bringing something to unique
I'm bringing something unique and let's
let's just like write write write or die
together was the first time we met at
YouTube live to write that was the first
time we did that's where I
so we talked to David because that's
where I met David - you know what I tell
them that like the the shirt thing when
I was like awaiting you like we were
gonna go to the event and I like made it
like a backhanded comment about what
your way I know you remember it I
remember vaguely but I was like you
remember it more I do oh you're gonna
wear that okay yeah you tell it and then
I'll give my side on yeah I was just
like you know I saw Ryan as you know
like influenced a big big deal
and I was like you know you're about to
see like all these people in person for
the first time like I've been to YouTube
events but yeah that was my first event
it's overwhelming and there's like you
take hundreds of pictures or you're
meeting lots of people you know you're
meeting not just like viewers
subscribers you're also meeting other
youtubers that you follow and like or
maybe look up to and not to but you were
you were just so humble that you you're
like I'm just gonna wear a grey
undershirt and like some jeans and let's
just go and I was like dude you're
behind you like are you gonna wear you
know I do remember like coming like
we're about to go okay and then I
remember coasting oh you're gonna wear
that I think the timing was like almost
the most self-conscious things I always
say about keV is he'll say things and
even if it's like whether it's funny or
if people get offended a lot of times
it's not to be mean it's literally just
blunt just honesty hmm
I think a lot of times you say things
even though or it's overly sarcastically
what do you guys would have been doing
all day and then you'll be like oh no I
meant all of it but people will really
believe that but they were I realize
that you're joking but like I didn't I
had just met him that day other than
what I've seen online so I took that
personally
oh yeah and I remembered everything you
told me that yeah numerous times this is
like 2010 was that 2010 yeah so like
what
other stories do you guys have like fun
time between each other it's a lot what
can you share cuz I'm sure there's a lot
of like r-rated stories man you guys
were in ytf together sure which was a
first probably the first big like super
group on YouTube hopefully at the time
it was unique so I mean like what what
stories do you guys have that like just
some idea or just anything but just
between YouTube that you guys can
remember that it's always just like what
are you looking for like I mean are you
looking for what are you willing to
share basically lived in the same
building where not all of the youtubers
live in LA and North Hollywood there's
so many of them that moved in there by
the way into that building specifically
youtubers yeah Wow we were the first
though I know we were nobody else is
around
anyway we basically lived in the same
building so we'd I mean there's so many
we saw each other almost every day for
like years so I mean it's hard to say
one specific thing I was your favorite
consistent thing then about each other
are it consistent yeah I mean we we
lived next to the dance community too so
like you know obviously my roommate was
Victor his was d-trix we were next to em
else to do like a crew from Houston that
I'm fond of so real crew was like Ryan
post post they were all like we were in
the same circle and then you had the
acoustic singers like junior who was
here the two weeks ago
just so many talented people so like the
consistent thing was like just being
awed by like and our place was like the
kind of hangout spot for just all these
people to like just kick back jam
sessions were crazy like we would just
like turn on the camera and do like the
spam freestyle or and then like behind
the camera like people are like just
like haven't liked playing beer pong or
something you know so like we were just
having fun but it was also like kind of
productive because like us being
together like was like good for our
community and just like sharing talent
and so I was like that was consistently
pretty cool yeah yeah I will say like we
I mean I got spoiled by that like we
were surrounded by like the
dancers in the world the top some of the
top singers you know and they would just
be like we had a regular party you just
be like making up songs on the spot
while people dance to it yeah yes the
most amazing like choreo you see me lox
and freestyle rapping and it's just like
all this talent and we would happen all
the time that I just didn't appreciate
it as much because I'd like the least
yeah we had no talent on my gym tour we
had to make skits because we were like
we just announce people's names like
here's another good person at what they
do and we're just like we would slow jam
sessions and we just be filling up space
yeah like anyone could have been us yeah
but we got to witness it and we did not
film that a lot of times the best cover
you weren't even filled yeah and we did
not carry our responsibilities well
that's the only thing that's all
contributed was like sharing it yeah
dang people are gonna be upset and my
other we just you know I remember that
though is because when jr. came back and
he sang just for a little bit like we
didn't ask jam or anything yeah I was
just like damn this is so good I'm like
a show yeah and I forgot how like I took
this for granted because they used to be
there all the time and sing guys to it
yeah we had just yeah I kind of wish it
was like you know I want to go back to
those one of those parties we're like
there's just so much talent where and
then there's me and Kev just just
watching just truth just like nodding
our heads and yeah oh man
yeah fort or weird that's why we were
the hosts and we tried to do pest crew
skits and do whatever we could to fill
time because we didn't just filling time
yeah basically throwing shirts that's
how we're gonna feel that's how lame you
want to do patottie but the show was
good thanks yeah the rest of the members
they were all talented Jeff and I were
just just along for the ride we were
there basically for the meeting greet
that's it all right well we gotta do our
tags at off the pill podcasts on Twitter
at off the wait the other way around at
off the pill on Twitter at off the pill
podcast on Instagram yeah and then do
you have anything that you want to plug
your upcoming channel your doesn't
I love you mom they're not I know
actually my dad I'll tell him to watch
it just so he can hear so love you dad
and I love you dad
yeah homies shot to Houston personal
shout-out to two people that still like
me me on the street and my mic still
care about me you know that's shout to
you guys like I wish I knew our names
impossible right Oh didn't even get to
talk about it maybe next time when it's
over but I was we I was gonna bring up
like I don't know I was gonna talk more
about basketball but shout-out to Jeremy
- yeah he's doing layoffs yes life he'll
still me sorry I said killing it too
premature he's I mean he's practicing
with them and we don't know what happens
behind the doors yeah like he's he's
practicing with quiet he's probably
guard guarding Hawaiian practice so that
Kauai can't hit that game yeah he's
welcome you're welcome
and his defense is way better yeah why
was you yeah I saw your name on that
shot yeah
yes so again thank you to Kevin we are
pretty much oh we have no other things
to plug yeah
just exhale on the mic all right that
being said heard about this thank you
for getting to off the pill podcasts I
guess we'll see you next time but also
Kevin will be back we'll see that's a
lot of pressure on I know we're making
we're making sure so that there's
comments that are always gonna be like
drink it you just want them to subscribe
so that you you might not even bring you
back but I'm gonna bring you back
people aren't subscribed of this podcast
all right in three two one
[Music]
I know there was like a right way to do
this there's no right way