hey guys so halloween is coming up fast
if you're one of those lazy
procrastinators that don't have a
Halloween costume yet or at least an
idea I made this video just for you and
for myself because I also don't have a
costume or an idea yet or if you're
anything like me and you just don't like
dressing up I know I know party pooper
poop but I mean come on you in a
dressing up too if you had to dress up
as much as I do throughout the year I
just notice that I did not do my hair
well I already shot the beginnings I'm
not gonna do it now see what I mean and
that's why I came up with a bunch of
costume ideas that require little to no
effort or money to get done maybe I'll
be the best costume idea at the time it
takes to get done to possibility of
getting a chuckle out of it ratio is
pretty good I mean some people are lucky
they have certain features that allows
them to come up with even better costume
ideas but even less effort like my
friend Greg for example I'm not sure
what it is but there's something about
his look that just allows him to be so
many different things like Mario Luigi
Captain Crunch the monopoly man Colonel
Sanders Tom Tucker Bob hercule the
Pringles guy haha
I look like all of them because of a
mustache good what no you're like them
because they're all drawings and
drawings are beautiful pictures and
pictures are worth a thousand words and
a thousand words aren't even enough
words for me to help you picture the
value of your picture in my life which
drew me to you when I picture you as a
drawing huh you really do think that I
would have never thought that John's
because your mustache as I was saying I
know there's a lot of people who love
dressing up but I'm not one of them and
we all know if you show up to a
Halloween party not dressed up there's
always that one guy or girl that always
judges you wait what even dressed up why
even here sorry so for all my fellow
lazy dresser uppers here some of my best
last-minute lazy Halloween costume ideas
that are just enough to get by let's
start off simple all the following ideas
I'm not even gonna explain how to do
them because they should be pretty
self-explanatory
take a look lazy Halloween costume ideas
50 shades of grey
Nickelback Miley Cyrus Facebook k-pop
star one direction One Direction fans
unicorn Adele screwed over Russian
Sponge Bob my name is spongeboob
counter-strike Halo Reach
minecraft feeling under the weather
this feels nice Iron Man Batman Aquaman
Thor Wonder Woman the flash Wolverine
Cyclops Superman would you like soup or
Green Lantern The Hulk you wouldn't like
me when I'm angry
rah next we have a bunch of costumes
that are even lazier than the ones you
just saw these are for all the people
that are so lazy that when you go to the
party you can be even lazier just do
costumes that have anything to do with
relaxing or sitting or chairs chairman
of the board New York City sitcom Saturn
Saturday taking the set a baby sitter
baby sitter for a babysitter guy with a
broken leg wheelchair with a broken leg
pretty wrapping drink fessor a a snail
Skrillex Wow oh my god yes Steven Hauk
I'm in love with Siri Siri heart I am
cheating on Steven Oh Roman Cheerios
make haste
oh no I'm next bunch of for people who
want to go even lazier than that they're
for people who don't even want to sit
down at the party sitting can get tiring
taking a step further Jim Carrey I feel
like standing lay a pregnant chicken
Himalayan eggs a guy in therapy looking
for the remote in the couch tourism of
Emily Rose the pringle guy that got laid
off by Pringles and now it works for me
now these are for the laziest of lazy
you don't even have to show up to the
party and when people start giving you
crap for not showing up you can still
say you were there you just showed up as
Invisible Girl a legitimate ghost is a
lie people who still watch American Idol
want details girlfriend a bad joke a bad
joke following a bad joke
everyone on MySpace and last but not
least a hot girl that doesn't look at
Halloween has a chance to dress
and show off her body there are none I'm
just kidding girl I know not all of you
guys dress like that on Halloween
unfortunately right guys
I'm sorry I had to go close the window
crickets were trying to get in anyway
thank you guys so much for watching if
you didn't take one idea from this video
I hope it at least sparked an idea in
their head or at the very least remind
you to start looking for a cost I hope
you guys have a wonderful Halloween and
for all you lazy dresses that wait what
what is this yeah you like it
these are some Halloween costumes you
could be with no effort Harold kept John
Messiah
Justin John Glenn from Walking Dead
every bad guy in the movie Pearl Harbor
Remiel and Mulan how to tell a bad
driver
Wow you're just being hurtful now wait
what I was just trying to give you
suggestions earlier but you're just
being racist how would you like it if I
was racist to you know I wasn't nice you
like you were my friend great but I
thought you were my friend you're trying
to make a Filipino accent because I'm
Filipino no you are not my friend go I'm
go branch from the same go let go let go
we don't tell me you're trying to sing
Bruno's
seriously once you pop the fun don't
stop Gracie stupid I'm out of here later