hey guys and welcome back to another
episode of I dare you that's not what
we're filming dear Ryan this is what I
meant to say before we get into the dear
Ryan's though I just want to do a quick
shout out and thank you to every single
person that downloaded the teja and I
know I didn't say much about it on this
channel but on the TV I released a video
announcing it and got over a hundred
thousand pound loads in one day it was
like number 10 in the App Store for
iPhone user and for Android it was like
number three or something crazy like
that there's one thing you guys so much
I'm still posting daily so for all of
you who haven't gotten they happy yeah
make sure you guys check it out I'll put
the link for iPhone and Android in the
description box below but with that
being said here's another idea why do I
keep saying that there's another dear
Ryan here we go you're right show us how
you would confess to someone you like
I'm just gonna be completely honest the
last time I think I literally told
somebody that I liked them was probably
in high school and I'm really
embarrassed but I'm it's it's in the
past I I did it over aim if you guys
don't know what that means it's an
instant messenger kind of like MSN
Messenger not that you guys would know
what that is it's like facebook
Messenger it was for AOL you guys don't
know what a o L is what am I talking
about anyway I did it over the internet
and I'm really embarrassed about it
because you should say that kind of
thing in person to someone kind of like
how I would do it now something like
this hey could I talk to you about
something listen this is awkward I I
know we've been friends and just friends
for a really long time now but I can't I
just can't hold it back anymore I think
it's time you know well I do Ryan can
you parody the Big Bang Theory okay let
me first say that I actually really
really like this show when it first came
up I absolutely loved the first two
seasons but then I started to notice how
much they use the left truck if you ever
do get around to watching that show or
if you already do then try and count how
many times they use a laugh track every
episode what irritates me the most is
that they do it on parts that are not
even intended to be funny but yeah you
still laugh because you hear other
people laughing
Sheldon what are you doing
my my spot it feels different for some
reason did you change it
Sheldon it's a couch it's not gonna
change that's just not true it off a
chemical compound can change is surely a
physical sitting device can go through a
physical changes well you know that's
not what I'm talking about Sheldon I
never know what you're talking about
oh that's just rude is it yes this is
what what see what I mean I just hate
when shows put in laugh tracks to make
it feel like you should be laughing even
though nothing funny happening it's like
come on like where did all the
intelligent comedy go and what it was
with all this immature forced comedy Oh
like you can do better
yeah as a matter of fact I probably
could then go ahead okay um the Big Bang
Theory more like the big fart theory get
it big fart theory because the shows
things you know not that's known as a
big fought theory I get it now dear Ryan
can you use Internet Explorer yeah sure
let me just get my time machine
[Applause]
dear Ryan you do a Higa bros episode
please only Ryan and Kyle for those of
you that don't know Kyle is my brother
who are always like shocked that I have
a brother cuz they never see him in
videos but like it's not that I don't
want him to be my brother just never
hasn't wanted to be in videos with me
when we were growing up and I would like
to be filming stuff he would always be
more into video game and even when he
would play video games and I would be
like hey can i play with you he would
usually say no because I wasn't good
enough and it didn't matter what game it
was like whether it was Connor striker
Starcraft or Street Fighter or just
playing cards I just wanted to play a
game with my brother
any game I never could do you want final
deep I have to turn key you never come
out anymore
you stay indoors playing sing up
[Music]
zombie mode ya see my childhood wasn't
easy tough streets of Hilo Hawaii took a
lot out of you when the Nintendo was the
only man right can't you see I'm filming
right now go away Kyle dear Ryan can you
be on our Elsa from frozen who from what
dear Ryan can you teach us some lie
facts I made a video about extremely
lazy people and how those people are
actually the smartest people because
they come up with solutions to solve
problem well that's exactly what life
hacks are so basically I just took a
bunch of things that I can relate to the
most and I came up with solutions in the
same way here's some of my facts that I
can relate to I hope you guys do as well
the diet life hack are you one of those
people that likes to start diets but
always ends up giving up on them well
this life hack is really easy all you
have to do is buy a bunch of mirrors and
attach it to all your unhealthy food
with a little note that says you and
you'll probably never break your diet
again the phone finder now if you're
like me and you're always losing your
phone this one's perfect for you all you
got to do is attach a cord to your phone
and make that cord attached to some kind
of base and put that base on a wall
there you have it you'll never lose it
again unless you lose your house before
it filter now I know this one doesn't
just relate to me have you ever had one
of those days where your farts are just
rancid and I'm talking like really bad
like when they come out and they're
super hot I don't know why I made this
motion that is disgusting my right hand
is a fart if those farts like in a
cartoon above character will smell them
they'd have x over their eyes oh dude
this is gonna be bad
oh my well no more smelly farts thanks
to my life I make all the fart Hilton
all you got to do is get a fabric
softener and tape it to your underwear
right above where you know what is and
the next time you part it'll smell like
fresh laundry love Silver's
I miss how are you guys I've been
freestyling this whole video it makes no
sense that's again when does my videos
make sense when do my videos make sense
is what I meant to say okay in all
seriousness I know that you guys want
real life hacks and I actually do have
one real life and I know you guys
probably have already heard about this
because I've seen posts about it but I
have been doing this since middle school
before the internet even existed that's
not true it existed but it was slow and
I had dial-up then and there was no post
about this at the time so I invented
this life hack that's not sure I learned
it from my mom she probably learned it
from other people basically it's called
the shower steam ironing thing I don't
know why it's not even that hard but I
hate doing it I hate ironing my clothes
so have you ever seen me in public
there's a 50% chance that my clothes are
wrinkled or I use this life and
basically all you got to do is take a
hot shower and bring whatever clothes it
is with you into the shower with you you
just gotta hang it somewhere where the
steam is hitting it but not the water
now once you're done with your shower
all the steams have gotten rid of all
your wrinkles and if not you can use my
backup life hack to get all the wrinkles
off all you have to do a shower mom can
you iron this wasn't even funny so sick
I'll be stupid poorly made immature
jokes and take no thought at all it's
all just literature because we think
it's funny it's not funny just make me
so mad that sometimes I just
[Music]
now that it's gone a little that's a
smart deal hey thanks man I hope you put
your fart filter on right now what oh
yeah that's you know mattracks not even
in the once I said not even once so
leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video thank you guys again so
much for watching you want to see
bloopers and behind the scenes click no
on the left if you want to see the
previous video click the one on the
right and also just a quick announcement
to all my labs in Beijing I'm actually
gonna be there on May 28th for the
Lenovo tech world event they said
they're gonna be showcasing not only
just my life hacks and I just did which
I think are still the best life hacks
I've ever seen also some of your life
hacks as well all you got to do is
hashtag I hacked light on Twitter
Instagram and they might pull your and
we're gonna be showcasing all the best
one and if you don't want to do that you
can just continue singing along to this
song with me dad that's not the right
song