I hit rank three third in the third
thirty North America Oh playing
exhausting night Catarina and everyone
was just like who is this guy people a
lot of people see you with that do
normal day and I just tell them all I do
is I need sleep TFT I may look back on
this and think this is probably the or
maybe could be one of the best times
moments shall we
clap yeah let's do this yep just give us
a little welcome back to another episode
about the pill podcast
hey there yeah we got a little bit music
we got David in the moderator seat
pocket right here I'm Ryan and we have
very special guests and I guess you
could say oh gee even huh in the gaming
world we got SCARA also known as William
sorrow first okay yeah yeah I mean you
don't mind that people know you're no
okay
yeah people know but like no one calls
me William the people I live with no
coming the only person who calls me no
my mom doesn't call me William
my mom come no my mom calls me Jimmy
because okay talk about this first
my full name is William Jimmy Lee okay
okay
Jimmy I never liked William growing up
cuz I was like William is like it's like
a stupid name oh yeah
I like ya Jimmy and so like I would just
go by that about I told my close friend
just call me Jimmy my mom my dad call me
Jimmy you know and so like my really
really close friends my relatives call
me Jimmy my like clothes like housemates
call me SCARA no one calls me William
unless it's like like IRS tax purposes
like that right government calls me
William no one else when you get in
trouble yes exactly yeah but so your
housemates I mean obviously you live
with a bunch of other gamers we should
introduce you first for people who don't
know SCARA is originally you started
doing playing league right you were like
professional eSports I was as a
professional league of Legends player
for two or three years then I
transitioned to being a coach for six
months and then afterwards I would and
in between I was I've been a streamer
for about seven to nine years Wow
I'd have to really double check because
I didn't start streaming on Twitch I
started Amy on Xfire and exactly you it
was like it's such a stuffed program you
had a cap of 50 people so like if you
hit your cap people have to wait in a
queue so people at someone left to watch
the stream and so I used to stream water
Warcraft Arena on Xfire to Kappa 50
people like way back when and then you
always filled out your cap
yeah yeah I was actually really good and
the funniest thing is like I was I was
like one of the top rate players on my
battlegroup I could never get ranked one
and the reason I could never get ranked
one
it's cuz hospice team was so good she's
just like actually just beat the [ __ ]
out of my team until we got like the
moralize we hate her quit the game I was
like I see was like her team is way too
good like oh he had like yeah she was a
really good druid she had a really great
warrior she had a really great warlock
and they had like literally like some of
the best players in our battle group on
the team it'll she's actually building
an impostor and and the funny thing is
now you're doing your streaming TFT yes
which is team fight tactics yes it is I
don't know it's like a game bride game
just kinda yeah yeah it's a strategy
game right okay
actually the best I found the best way
to describe it it's a deck building game
it's a building it's a strategical deck
building game with I guess gambling
elements it's got to be one of the more
I mean I don't know if it's I haven't
checked recently but is it more popular
than fortnight yet on Twitch hell no for
days but it still it's one of the bigger
ones right I will the tribute it to
something like it's like hearthstone you
know okay and so it's something that
like there was a lot of crazy around
there before and unless it's probably
it's died down by now and unless they do
something big like it's probably this
day like at a good level for like a
couple years right and that's so
interesting you put all this time into
learning this like skill and this art
and it could you you have to adjust
right like you can't just play the same
game well League I guess I play League
for like 7 years actually so I never
thought I'd switch and then just
randomly like I went in to play this
game okay I actually got was getting
tired of League for the first time in
seven years Wow
so I started playing dota Auto chess I'm
like I'm in my stream I actually had
these where I played more all the chests
that played League of Legends and this
is the five months following TFTs launch
and then one day I got a invite from Rai
games super 8 dat like we need we want
you to come in and test our game I'm
just like okay mm-hmm they even say it
was a game you like we need you to test
something confidential but through Mike
did a great provide that new was a game
so much I woulda died and they were
making their own daugther auto chest
which is the the first iteration of the
genre uh-huh and it turns out that like
as I was trying to escape ride games
like the clutches of Riot Games to play
other different games they just dragged
me back in so then I became like one of
the faces 40ft
and like a lot of my success is
attributed to me jumping on the
bandwagon first right right so they were
very supportive of your career then you
say or I mean yeah right like I was a I
was a streamer for illegal edges that
became a top seaman for the new game
like I was actually like I okay I was I
was almost a consultant for them at some
point I felt because it's like when we
we they have like a chat room with all
the the alpha testers and we talk a lot
about the game but even then like I at
some point had to figure out if the game
was worth like all any on and what ended
up happening was when they first invited
me to that meeting and like everyone
else else ended up leaving I sat down
with the devs for like two hours after
hours like we're literally eating in the
dinner room i sat down for two hours and
talked to them not just about the game
like the future they gave my talk to
what's your distribution plan like
what's your like how are you guys gonna
make money what's the future of your
game what's expansion look like Wow
everything I heard about from talking
with them I was like these guys that are
intelligent they know what they want to
do they can enact change quickly and
like I really like these guys and so I
all end on the premise that I like the
people working on it more than the
premise of I like the company or like
anything about the game get interesting
because the first the first iteration of
the game we got was like yeah potential
but it's like man honestly it was it
wasn't as good and even now I should
credit you yeah you pretty much helped
develop it like I do anything about the
game I was just saying the like I I
talked him about some but like a lot of
stuff I talked to him about they already
need to do so like it's not like I was
there to be like oh you know I made any
part of the game successful I'm just
saying they're like I thought them a
little bit about stuff here and there in
a way it's almost like you guys both
affirmed like this is what we because it
does really yeah you confirmed yeah yeah
but we're talking about a lot about you
know what you're currently doing yeah
let's go into your past a little bit
because it's actually it's it's a niche
you have interesting stories you do a
really ok I hate my hit me with my just
references they you guys know each other
from yeah we've known each other for a
while now because that's sighs I mean
clearly you know something I don't know
we don't know her like me and David's so
yes I I've met Paco
four years ago four years ago I saw I
started offline TV which is like a group
of how do I even see like a gamer yeah
this is actually a gamer house but like
streamers house and we didn't fail it's
like there's so many like there's been
like a lot of streamers yes yeah that
been growing up and that like we were
the ones that are able to kind of
succeed in a formula I have no idea how
like essentially I brought together a
lot of people that wanted it's so funny
actually at the origin story was like I
had a version me and like no manager
Chris and I had an Excel document I was
like in this dock me I'd the people I
wanted to work with like in the house
and so like like pokies name was on
there which it we eventually got her
toast is on there but I was like oh
toast wasn't even on there it was so
early I didn't Lilly Picchu one of the
people who live live was a lives with us
is on there and I was like there's
nobody can get her she's too big so I
like crossed her out and like we didn't
even try to get her like the first the
first couple people we got but like we
end up grabbing a lot of content
creators it's been I think about two and
a half years since we started all of us
are doing pretty well like it's been
pretty successful and where was I going
with this
there's oh yeah I met him because pocket
tiger came over a long time ago and I
think me before that actual house yeah
was even like created it was one you
know the base unit that's why it was
grabbing food a couple of oh yeah so so
I use are I still have a friend sorry
they used to name Orlando and then I met
him through Orlando and then what's so
funny when we're starting off off off
off line we were just like how do we
make cool stuff and then he drove over
to try to help us do school stuff we
still have he was one of the first
people to film our very first skit ever
Wow and that was the reason why we don't
do skits anymore because we're just
awful actors actually like the worst
footage I really want to see I don't
even know how to find it like I'm pretty
sure it's hidden somewhere like we our
first ever skin was done with pakhi Oh
that's when we learned that streamers
are not actors or actresses and that we
probably do a little bit better with
improv and like set scenarios than just
like hey let's read off lines oh [ __ ] we
can't read off lines well I mean it's
kind of a we do I mean we have lines but
we'll improv it yeah a lot of times you
can tell you that huh I said see what
makes you feel comfortable
yeah yeah okay so basically you guys met
but before that story in it because like
you have to tell me the story from that
point because I am not even sure I
remember the first time I met you it was
at Korean barbecue okay but we kind of
just talked about because I was very
curious to like your backstory and how
you kind of got into league how you
became a team with Dignitas all that
stuff okay guys are like you oh boy like
you you want my life story from what I
got was just interesting because it was
a gamble you know in a way alright so I
was playing League of Legends like like
the first season started League of
Legends was it had no support right I
came from a game called heroes of
newerth
I I switched to League of Legends
because all my friends quit and my
brother was like hey you got come play
with me and my friends like dota I
picked up cuz he wasn't playing it his
friends League
what were your professional at that time
or you were just an amateur I wasn't
anything right I think the best that
place was I was top 100 on the Hawn
ladder
he wasn't the earth ladder but some that
like I was not a professional player or
anything I did well in world Warcraft
but like I didn't consider myself
professional right and so I just jumped
to League of Legends and the I remember
first three games at played I had
averaged 30 kills a game and I was like
this game is so easy like I can't new
this is a children's game this game is
dumb I hated the game when I first
started and then like onwards and
onwards onwards and I ended up getting
into it and I went to the very top I
remember I got no this because I was
ranked 3 in the month it took me to
level 230 rank came out and when rank
came out I hit rank 3 third in the 30
North America Oh playing exhausting
night Catarina and everyone was just
like who is this guy because all the top
players are from beta and so no one knew
who I was
except for one person who would become
my future teammate locust
locus knew me because he said play World
of Warcraft on my server and he
remembered that I was a top PvP on that
server and I made the Kinect that way
and then we started a team together so
it's like you know that six degrees of
separation it's like in eSports it's
actually like I know one person they
know everyone else then that's how it
was this seven years ago crazy it's not
even that long it is but if you think
about it how much things have changed
like you said you guys just formed a
team and then look where you are like
seven years isn't that long for how far
in eSports I think six months is a long
time he used to be so crazy that in the
first two seasons people people were
like what's your long-term plan now it's
like that's a joke right so so in in
normal businesses from what I understand
dr. pan plans like a ten year plan you
know short-term is one year long term is
ten years and then that's it
in eSports long year long term is one
year and short term is one week and so I
couldn't tell you at any given moment in
like like at some periods during the
last five years a lot of periods well
that was doing the week after mm-hmm and
I even even now like two months ago if
you had asked me are you gonna quit
legal and she's like hell no - I love
legal legends and then EFT comes out you
know I blow up plain TFT and now I'm
like an entire I'm like a strategy gamer
now and it's just it's really strange
because I that's no we're way I expected
to go and like mice like my success I'm
trying really hard not to take it for
granted
trying to work really hard on it but
like it just came out of nowhere I like
to think that like especially in eSports
a lot of opportunities will come up
randomly and it's just like your hard
work will dictate your your luck if I
need these and then then it's just up to
you to pursue them like then it's up to
your hard work to maintain like the
success you know do you think any person
just like any any single person could
train and play as much as you play a
certain game and become as good as you
are or do you think some people just
think differently and help as good as me
are you wear dresses I think I person
think there's a there's like this it's I
always wondered cuz I know like half
would she didn't play that game at all
and like all of a sudden
hold at the top at these well especially
it comes to ha fou I think there's a
skill sets of people excel it so like if
you're an FPS gamer yeah really good
reaction time right uh uh really good
like I guess like muscle movement you
know when it comes to that kind of stuff
FPS skills will translate in between FPS
games right so Ashley if you want the
best skill set you should be an FPS
gamer because there's always there's
always a need for that skill set
strategy gamers are like you know maybe
they they don't think quickly but they
think like well like overall um they are
maybe slow mechanically they don't have
much mechanics but they're very good at
being able to understand and piece
together different pieces to make like a
whole picture right uh and so those are
skill sets about that way a lot of
strategy gamers have people like this
guys toast ha food dog very very like
very good at excelling like and knowing
like the value of things and like the
odds of stuff happening you know and so
everyone just has different skill sets
when you grow up you learn to learn
these skill sets from a lotta different
things you know and it doesn't have to
be games like let's say you were I don't
know like you're playing you're a
badminton player and you have really
good like hand-eye coordination because
you play a lot of tennis you play a lot
of batmanning you need that high
hand-eye coordination to play that skill
to play that a high level and then you
can translate some of that's going to
play in fps
right and so a lot of people who are
really really talented just play games
all their lives ok well that's
interesting to me I've always wondered
that and well I mean like if I were to
ask you like you said it's a certain
skill so do you think if you were to
just just start playing a lot and just
trained your ass off you could become a
first person shooter player um I always
tell people is that yes that I could
become good but do you think you become
like where you are I could not be
legendary at the game oh but I
but like because the amount of hours
that have to put in especially at this
point in my life is very it's like I
don't have enough timing right but if I
did I'd have to literally switch
everything into doing that so I guess at
some level you have to have confidence
in your ability to succeed right so for
me I always think if I put enough hours
into something I'll be good at it mhm
and that's just the confidence I have in
myself right but I don't ever think I
will be like a super good at something
so like I might put in thousand hours
playing overwatch like more than that
let's let's say I put a whole year to
play over
in playing Call of Duty and playing apex
and csgo how good would I be at FPS
games well if I actually trained and
practiced I did a lot of like ain't
ballestas stuff in queue has an actual
regimented schedule I'd probably make
like global we'd actually I believe that
but right now if you look at my school
you've laugh at me if I said that like
actually like if I play FPS games you
look at my skill you buckle this guy's
never played held a gun before ever I
just this guy in real life more than
like online it's really bad
like I think I'd probably be able to hit
like that you enjoy it though like if
you're not I mean my little enjoye being
bad at something but I enjoy improving
at something so like if I if there was a
game that really like caught my
interests legalize just comes out with
an FPS game and I'm just I just want to
be [ __ ] good like I it kills me to be
bad at the game I would put in the hours
oh there's not something yet I'm like I
want to do that and for me I I just see
better use of my time like for instance
like people a lot a lot of people see
you with idea I'm a normal day and I
just tell them all I do is I eat sleep
tf2 you mm-hmm and read that sounds like
a merch idea but like for the first
three weeks of TFT launch which it's
been about a month enough in month in
three weeks in I would plate TFT for 12
hours
Wow I'll wake up shower TFT for 12 hours
maybe go to the gym
I've personal trainer for like three
this week whatever maybe go there and
come back after TFT goes out for three
hours I would need a record a video
about TFT now take an hour about two
hours so like literally I like 3 a.m. or
like 1:00 a.m. I'm recording a video in
the middle of the night to put on
YouTube to like fight to right answer
the occasional guys because obviously if
I'm blowing up on TNT
I'm I capitalize on the success smart um
or I would walk into toast room and I
would talk to him about the day I'm
talking be like hey you know like what
do you think it's good what you think
it's bad I would if he's not available
even if I'm eating I'm bringing up TFT
streams I'm watching dog I'm watching
Hoff watching like hyped I'm watching
say I'm watching all these really good
players I would absorb information even
if I'm not playing so like I would say
the first like three weeks I was putting
in like 16-hour days there sounds like
you enjoy it oh yeah I really enjoy and
right now like I would say my motivation
for the game is lower than when it would
start
for sure I'm streaming like only like
six hours why is that um too easy
no I'm actually struggling a lot right I
think I'm trying to take it easy because
um let's talk about that actually oh
yeah currently I'm doing a challenge I
started the year I wanted to do Ustream
for every single day this year and so
365 days of streaming and when I first
started challenge it's because I saw
coke carnage pretty people don't know
coke are huge variety stream like really
really big rice Jimmer he's been
streaming on Twitch like since forever
he is really dedicated audience he
averages like you know seven eight
thousand play anything like JRPGs
doesn't matter he has the world record
for longest time consecutively streaming
on Twitch can you guess what it is 164
days I don't know I don't know I mean if
he's 32 days it's six years what no it's
five and a half years its way every
single day it's 2,000 days so like you
that's like what uh okay he he streamed
through his first child and he stopped
in a second and he made a video about it
and that was his schedule he was
consistently streaming every single day
that's how he got blew up bigger that's
how he blew up he he was more amazing
though he was more consistent than early
morning talk shows he was there every
day of the week more consistent in your
family members he was there for you you
like kind of stuff and I saw that
challenge I was like I'm gonna try doing
that let's start easy let's start at 365
so I go through it
honestly [ __ ] joke like the first
hundred fifty days I was like this isn't
even that challenge I just do this
normally you know and then recently like
with TFT popping off I realized that
it's really when you get new viewers you
have to be really careful especially it
comes to strategy games because there's
a lot of back seating and ones that we
actually taxi it would be like oh you
could alright yeah yeah I see that
and so yeah when it happens in TFT I
have a lot of new viewers coming in
they're just like super toxic super
aggressive and like I can't get like a
good flow going for my game for my
gameplay because like I'm trying to be
entertaining I'm trying to be uplifting
and I'll lose a game
and maybe it you know honestly like the
best players will play sait sometimes
literally the best players I watch
because it just happens but uh if I ever
do that or I have a bad day where I just
don't play very well like it becomes
super toxic to the point where like I
can't play because that on top like I
become like super snappy like I on
average ban ten people a day right now
and before when I was out when I was a
virgin like 2.5 viewers I was I never
abandoned person I been one every two
days right it's like just the sudden the
influx of the popularity plus the type
of game I play it's really back to see
the book because even you play to the
right odds if everything's results based
like right so like they see that like oh
you could've gone for that and they see
this oh you could have done this but
it's like even if I made the right play
I could like it could work out that for
me like oh you should have done this why
didn't you do that right and so it's
really straining I think the last couple
days for me doing this challenge not
having a rest day as well as doing this
I've been streaming a lot less hours
I've been trying to take more time off
still doing like what six hours a day
but like I went from streaming 240 hours
a month every month that's select that's
crazy like a hundred and eighty but what
is doing that is you feel the burn out
like did you feel like you had to at
some point then I think maybe I was a
little more snappish at people like
because the thing about the most
important train has a stream where's
patience hmm I would say like cuz this
is seeing patients because you didn't
get a lot of dumb ask questions like
people coming it's like like new players
it's not a book oh you all answer to say
50 questions 50 times a day
so it's like you have to pay the other
have the patience of a saint or a
teacher to be able to do what I do
especially if you're like i market
myself or and I'm marking myself like
maybe Brant I don't even like saying
that word it feels too like artificial
like I'm I'm being like you just lots of
friendly it's just more yeah yeah I so I
a lot of people see me I was like it the
educational guy like the teacher to
professor whatever and like when they
come to my starting how do I do this how
do I do this how do I do that but like a
lot of times I'm just like yo like that
way you ask me right there like you
could Google that like that's just
really easy question it's like it's like
you can know but you're asking me
instead and you want me to
you the answer you already know it
sometimes when like that combined with
people were being dicks yeah because I
have a lot of new people like I think
before cuz I was I was averaging like
what 2.5 thousand three thousand viewers
which is like you know that's a success
story anyway that's a lot but I go from
that to going to doing like thirteen
thousand nine to thirteen thousand
literally I quadrupled quintupled my
viewership the success comes with some
growing pains oh sure
and I didn't see the problems with my
stream challenge and like the other
stuff before but after now I'm just like
oh [ __ ] like I have to be really really
careful because like I'll get like like
really annoyed a lot quicker like all
this the mental fatigue tends to build
up and so for me as a defense mechanism
I'm like I try out the back d backlash
or like travel yes be upset or snap back
at my viewers as much I ban a lot more
people every day but that's just the
nature of the game I guess and then I I
take I'm streaming a little bit less you
know I I started reading fantasy fiction
to try like balance out my might be my
thing but like if you have to like if
you saw my pie chart of what I do for a
day it's still like TFT what should we
call it
like streaming YouTube videos like
sponsorships and then like now you just
add in reading right except for reading
it's like instead of it's like it used
to be I read like in about an hour to a
day on normal I just like reading mm-hmm
and now I read like four hours a day I
had a day where I slept at 4:30 cuz I I
turned out my stream I got in my bed so
I really 11:30 and it at 4:30 a.m. Wow
and I woke up I read some more and I'll
say huh that's nice it's really nice how
many hours of sleep do you generally get
oh it's generally it's like 6 to 8 hours
probably probably more along the 6 or 7
honestly I I think I used to be like I
used to be a cutie slip 14 you know 14
straight are you serious yeah I don't
think I tried really I mean maybe I
didn't sleep for like 24 hours I might
really I feel like as a kiss so easy
asleep a long time like you like yeah I
thought like 10 was like a long yeah 10
to 12 is long 14 that's fine but like
that's a one thing I have seen about
getting older is you tend to sleep a
little bit less yeah true but that
that's like oh the worst thing is I'm
the oldest person my friend group or
likes to anyone I mean almost oh yeah
I'm definitely always in the house huh
I'm turning 30 this year okay and it
scares me on the big three the big 3-0
I'm just like [ __ ] guys everyone
everyone looks really young to me I'm
like god you're like a baby that [ __ ]
wearing diapers around the house it's
just a number man no no no I know it's a
big deal yeah I like see around people
I'm just like oh you just got the eSport
you're a professional player that's nice
to meet you oh you're 16 mm you're half
my age you could have Yackey you could
have been their dad yeah you know it's
just it's just it's really interesting
age wise I think on average like
everyone's getting older in the scene
but you stop people coming in they're
really really young you're just like oh
my god yeah you know we can't go Praja
age 17 what was I at 17 you know doing
stupid [ __ ] well-well be right back but
we're gonna take a quick she break and
yeah what continue talking about this
with some Twitter questions
[Music]
and we're back okay do I go right into
Twitter questions or should we welcome I
actually had a question I'm answering
the in the gaming world and this just
recently became a thing and I'm sure you
have thoughts on this ninja joining
mixer mixers Microsoft's new streaming
platform competing directly with twitch
for those listeners who don't know okay
so I told them in the break I was like
I've already talked a lot like II this
is pretty much like this car a podcast
at this point so if you guys want
talking like please oh no this is the
point that's why we get to bring in
different people because it's a whole
world we don't what David and I don't
know
okay so it's actually very interesting
to us okay it's super interesting so
back to SCARA podcast let me talk to you
about my feelings about ninja is
actually like okay so ninja moved him to
mixer and obviously he's not gonna say
it's for the money but it's for the
money of course whether he said those he
wanted to go back to his roots
but matter what its roots work was
twitch that's what yeah his roots was
actually halo so he's moving about for
money but also cuz like Microsoft backs
what should we call it
mixer mhm and then what ends up
happening is I think keys would be able
to get like early access to Halo and
that's gonna be like a big pull for both
himself and tharixer for him as a
streamer
he was the superstar streamer and well
you have to know about twitch and I
don't think anyone ever really talks
about this no streamer ever stays on top
so the number one streaming on Twitch
never stays for more than a year every
single year like clockwork it moves out
actually the longest first place
streaming on twitch was cutie pie I
think it at one and a half years really
and then like after him it's like and he
was a league of Legends dreamer also
your former team yeah yes so wait is it
happening is like he was the first and
then it went to
[Music]
I've been like dr. disrespect and then
like ninja and then shroud and then tea
foo people who's number one thief is
number one right now oh I didn't know
that I guess huge he's like he's like
ninja but like uh-huh old ninja like but
old ninja hit the highest highs of any
person that right hit the 900k
viewership mark collab with Drake has
his own merchant Walmart this guy's like
household name good branding end up
happening was I would say he kind of
fell off no one stays on top right yeah
kinda fell off and then you got the
superstar offer from mixer I'm assuming
and why not take it the but it's like
it's only can only be good for him in my
opinion like he moves off they think of
it what happens worst-case scenario he
fails to you it's like a two three-year
contract right I'm sure it's a two-year
contract he got paid a shitload of money
for it and then the marketing when he
returns can you imagine twitches the man
returns yeah and they just a silhouette
of him and a poster it [ __ ] pays on
Billboard's everywhere it's like so
you're laying on his strategy yeah
exactly like like so like worst-case
scenario he got himself a bag of like a
huge paycheck he comes back after like
troubling times and people welcomed him
back busy still them right now the most
fall person on twitch.tv Wow still and
and that's like the future right you're
predicting that and that's poorly if it
does well you know it's all good because
he's a superstar who who changed a
platform he's got that draw he's got
that power to be able to make like it
just elevates his brand so much to say
he can go anywhere and make people come
to you or at him right but also say this
okay so there's actually recently a
couple of drama between twitch in ninja
yeah sure time heals everything you know
so maybe that can happen in the future
but right now there was an issue with
his channel about promoting other
streamers and how there was Russian porn
oh yeah okay so so like twitch has been
really all right let me preface this by
saying imagine you're a CEO of twitch do
you care about like the they're like
random like tea sir there's a bit alive
terms of service violations or like kind
of gray area BS that's been happening
here and there
for the last year like oh this girl got
banned for doing for like doing
something dis girl thing in there for
throwing her cat you know stuff like
that and what you as a CEO care about
like these small things these small
infractions probably not right you're
you're trying to figure out like okay
like how do i how do I work with Amazon
to create like a superior product how do
we make sure our ROI is good like what's
are not q3 plan like [ __ ] like that you
know it assume you have somebody else
yeah right and so it's probably and even
in the general sphere it's probably not
that important honestly it's like the
really really super hardcore Twitter
fans it's like I just [ __ ] up y'all
got these like POS things all this stuff
recently like they try to promote the
stupid stuff where they use ninjas
channel as like a beta test to promote
other streamers like if you're offline
the one of the biggest a what a next
which employee tweeted that what are the
biggest problems with twitch right now
is that if a streamer is online offline
and you go to a stream you will not and
you're a fan of him you may not watch
another streamer so they're trying to
make sure that funnel doesn't just I
some people out they want try to make it
easy access for you to go it instantly
to another streamer that they're
promoting so obviously they tried to
bait a product on ninja that was kind of
weird still probably what would have
been okay but someone was streaming porn
on the 49 channel on the under the four
night tag and got that got recommended
cuz they would recommend the all four
night streamers because obviously me
just fans or fortnight fans they would
recommend their category and so ninja
obviously doesn't like his brand
promoting porn it's kind of [ __ ] so
he like had a Twitter video about it hey
you know this is stupid [ __ ] oh yeah
yeah yeah and then the CEO apologized
they kind of reverted to his channel all
this stuff in the end it's like this is
only good thing this is only good for a
danger like that's I see like ninja
walks away clean he is on this new
platform and I think success or failure
will be based on who switches mm-hmm
I'm very honest I tell my chat look do
you that mixer comes at me with like a
10 million dollars I'm out the door you
know yeah I even like 5 million I'm out
the door see you guys that we did it for
has a podcast we were just talking about
this were like yeah Skaar what about 1
million 1 million not really well what
about 2 and I'm just like whoa it's like
I don't like this job for them right
let's work our way down yeah but I think
it's really interesting and generally
almost everyone I talk to it it says
that mixer needs more people to drive
over like ideally didn't want five of
the top ten shops right well you can't
just have one yeah yeah well maybe you
can I'm like yeah but like it's like
it's like PewDiePie for D life right and
right yeah do you know any other
streamer sister you want do you live no
you know any streamers to stream my
mixer no but do you know people would be
heard of mixer yeah do you know people
who stream on Twitch yes yep bunch of
random people I'm sure so like there's
no draw there if it's just one we got
like five superstars you can do it
mm-hmm
I've seen some extra streamers the
number one streamer on mixer that wasn't
Ninja was a 24/7 uh radio station so
they got some ways to go before I'm
pretty sure that's illegal as well by
the way
but like I'm like always positive that's
not allowed but uh the other fridge have
you ever met ninja or played games with
him no never he plays fortnight he's
he's at the first-person shooter yeah
yes I'm not an FPS guy he's also like
remember what everyone that's on me is a
really cool guy really chill guy but
like my worlds don't intersect like
right I don't leave the house so so I
get difficult for me to meet people when
like I don't go anywhere
um so that's probably the hardest thing
but yeah I would consider an agent to be
like very close like a C or B level like
a superstar like just in general oh yeah
yeah like shays he's like amazing Bob
he's in like mainstream yeah yeah yeah
like commercial yeah I'm like I I don't
always say this phrase I'm pseudo famous
so you may know of me if you're like my
specific demographic you're like yeah
you're 18 to 28 living in Southern
California who's also predominantly
Asian and you really like bubble tea and
you hang on a k-town it's like
like then I'm famous no like nothing
you're giving yourself man I think
anyone who plays or yeah we go get food
you get stopped hey those people I told
you are you really what I mean like okay
so I think what you're saying is true
and you mate you make a good case you
should take that clip and send it to
mixer I think what if you were to just
like get a few of other big streamers
for other ones put it put together a
pitch and send it to them if they hey
give us fifty million dollars BAM okay
it'll be more I mean so like already all
that stuff my agency's I'm sure talking
to other are like it's already happening
like yeah I already know how could your
self we know one of the platforms are
talking to you right it's right it's not
mixing oh it's not mixing yeah yeah so
it's someone else but like for me it's
like I wouldn't do that work myself I
like this I like to think they're like
that's why I have agents debris media
doesn't mean to say yes or no yeah and I
wanna focus on just the stuff I'm good
at you know I like playing League of
Legends like playing PFT I want to
create content I don't want to get
bogged down by political like politics
stuff or I don't wanna get bogged down
by like things I don't like like mm-hmm
a lot of times people when you talk to
corporate people it's like so how did
you feel about your brand like what do
you think your brand outreach your
growth and like they start using these
buzzwords I'm just like I know what you
mean I can understand the English
language but the more you talk like this
the more I don't want to listen right so
like I tried I think a lot of our
success as a household and a lot of
streamer success is the ability to stay
authentic to their mm-hmm - they're like
brand I'm going to use one of those
terms I'm sorry okay sure but like a lot
of their success and I think a success
of a lot of content creators has been
awesome to City and being able to
capture that has been really difficult
for a lot of people you know I'm sure
you've run into problems where it's like
is this you know Ryan material is this
something I'm proud of
sure and maybe you've released things
that have been successful that you don't
like all the time
it's I mean it does take it's it's a
matter of like your own self right leg
yes you think people like you said you
could do really well but if you're not
happy with it then yeah okay well I mean
a lot of people don't think that way
though you know but maybe it's different
for streaming I mean works on YouTube to
not be authentic and still be able to
get away with it but maybe it's
streaming you have to be streaming cuz
they see you so closely and like right
if you're a good actor you're in
Hollywood you're not streaming be like
for them to see six hours of your life
you can't act you can't act and fake it
that long yeah exactly like you will
slip up you know right well YouTube yeah
cut out all the parts like I could be
like a completely like PG person if you
just ignore ignore me cussing like every
you know five or ten minutes right so
yeah I agree like anything you chopped
up and at it you can make me look like I
say you can make me look like the devil
it doesn't really matter but on you
streaming yep nope no possible so you
said you a lot of people see you as like
a teacher do you think your appeal to
and why you're so popular is because
you're good at the game or because they
just genuinely like you okay Oh
aside from very very very rare cases I
think if you're trying to make a name
for yourself you have to be good at the
game okay like you being good at the
game is a draw for people to come and
watch you there are exceptions you you
should be entertaining you should be
consistent you like all this stuff
you should have presence you should be
able to like I don't know like all this
stuff but I think if you're not good at
video games why would people watch what
what what I mean is you're like there's
there's being good at games and there's
being like you like in the top
percentile no I think you need to be the
top percent oh okay well there any other
cases where like they're just maybe
really good-looking or they're just a
nice personality or like the show maybe
you can have success that's not at the
top level if that's the case if you want
to be like a 10,000 plus streamer and
you cannot suck ass at your video game
they are known to play especially if
you're not variety streamer 10,000 plus
dollars
which I think there's only handful I
think people will average 10,000 is less
than 50 or like less than 60 if you want
to be and a lot of those channels are
like like tournament channels you know
so individual wise it might be less than
like 40 right but if you're one of those
people and you're and you're no for
streaming one game or one type of game
so you're not a variety streamer cuz
people who watch variety streamers like
lyric are there for different reasons
like they like his personality I don't
know how good of a gamer is how
completely awesome I'm not watching
streaming up to tell uh he oh I could
say very confidently is not superstar
level like that's super good like a lot
of the other streamers read no for one
game like League of Legends or one game
like apex legends or like for a night
they have to be good that he had you're
it's even ninja you know who was at the
very top of his game he won the first
pro-am like he the all the tournaments
he was the winner so people could he
wasn't the best player I can confidently
say he has no way in hell but he he won
all the tournaments he was good enough
to where he could say he was elite
status and a part of what made his
appeal drop ended last year he didn't
qualify for a world championship this
year I heard is really bad right and
like as of you are like you don't want
to watch someone who does who's not good
enough to qualify you know there's so
many other people I can watch why would
I bother about with a bother so for yeah
I think there's an argument to be said
with that though like with a basketball
like LeBron he didn't make the playoffs
when people start watching him just how
much do you bring to the table when it
comes to video games like if you're not
playing you want to watch someone who's
good you know he's either good or
entertaining and it's very rare to find
the full package the full package player
who's like good entertaining streams a
long time yeah yeah all this stuff so uh
I think if you're especially a exclusive
streamer streamer that streams one game
you have to be good to break the DIF I
figure mark if you're not who you can't
compete I'm a hundred percent serious
you have to be not just good elite if I
wasn't challenger or a grandmaster like
I was at the very top I would I would
lose several thousand of my viewers
guaranteed actually my viewership has
gone down because I'm not even higher
rasili yes oh wow it's that like oh
relation is interesting I didn't know
that
I thought they were just there I mean
like I know like you said if you're good
at the game you bring in viewers but I
thought after they get to know you you
know um a lot of people um hardcore fans
a lot of people like the game so they'll
just watch the very top person on the
section which is white which is uh
discovery system is awful so like
YouTube has the algorithm which everyone
hates and despises but it's phenomenally
well well done like it is the most
successful algorithm to finding stuff
that you will watch right in like of
anything I know mm-hmm even if it's
complete [ __ ] I hate it hahaha but
uh twitches is terrible which is what
just a numbers based on numbers you get
so like if you're not in the first page
you're not gonna get discovered
who's gonna discover you like why would
I watch people always ask me how do you
be a good streamer and I'm just like
have a reason for me with a watch like
what's your niche you know most people
anisha's they have to start out being
good and then they can work from there
like if you could say you're the best X
in the world people will watch mm-hmm
but that's it like unless you have that
kind of draw no one will ever discover
you it's kind of like a resume in a way
then yeah yeah to some extent you could
be like hey I graduated first to
Stanford but like instead first to
Stanford like I'm the number one like
challenger player in Brazil or something
like that you know mm-hmm Wow well
that's good to know for all the kids who
want to become streamers oh you're not
you got to be the best in the world it's
like start practicing that's some real
advice though I think but I I appreciate
it some people are just like I can do it
you want to know what's [ __ ] crazy
the difference between you play see well
I like the first tournament or not it's
a difference becoming up or down mm if I
lost three games in a row on stream in
the first four three weeks i streamed
PFT I will lose 2,000 viewers three
games already have it done to us like a
math it's no it's like I watch other
streamers and most players most people
come in will watch to the end of your
game and leave anyways but people will
not watch a loser does it worry you then
that I mean so no I mean because your
current viewers [ __ ] and while you're
doing so well right now is because
you're doing so well at the TFT does
ever worry you that like all of a sudden
new game comes out and no one cares
about TFT OH
which I mean like the or you don't have
to switch but if people aren't
interested in it oh absolutely but like
I think at that level like you don't
want to worry about too much like for me
it's like focus on yourself and focus on
the grind and try to make the best
product like I'm confident enough with
for me as a person that I will excel
regardless what happens like if you're
gonna ask are are you gonna be
successful ten years from now hell yeah
20 years from hell yeah
thirty years from now I'm probably dead
but if I'm not probably still in success
can mean a lot of different things but
like mm-hmm I think personally I always
I'm confident of my ability um and my
skill set to find success regarding in
any yeah okay well that's a good answer
then well this this is basically just
like how to become a very successful
streamer podcaster been really good this
is very helpful advice like thank you
thank you for letting us be on I don't
want to stream anymore so we got some
Twitter questions yes some of the fans
out there very easy and simple one HMU
Cesar asks how often do you wear suits
never pretty much never steal on the at
the LCS analyst desk I've been on the
last couple days and I were sued to Kiwi
kids wedding he just got married he's my
old teammate you can actually name off
the occasion so those are the three
times I've worn a suit this year oh is
that so that's a guy inside I think it's
just like they saw me recently a suit
like a now it's okay I spend most of my
paycheck for the LCS desk on that I
don't see myself I want to treat myself
like I don't spend money on anything I
really only spend it on food which I
love and that's it skaara actually
bought me my first suit oh yeah we went
to some random bootleg place and like
they were slightly giving deals for sure
for suits I'm like baka you go one let's
so I can get yeah well you didn't need
what I just looked about yeah
I see really nice person but yeah it's
like that's all that's all I have have
feels like I just got to see recently
and then they're interested so I've
spent money on that and then recently I
got a mechanical keyboard custom-made
for myself it's super nice I can't rave
enough about this like I want everything
I own to be custom like ideally cuz iPad
okay I don't know if it's like we use
mentality by like saying they're like I
got this and I'm the only one who owns
it no that's I mean it's cool I feel
like everything right now I was like oh
you get a participation award and I'm
just like I don't want a participation
award I want the only one give it to me
like and so like you're at that level
where you can get I commissioned a
friend Nathan to build one for me and I
got like I think I got I delved into a
world of mechanical keyboards by the way
stupidly expensive like pretty much all
the stuff you want is like sold out yet
to buy them I like their secondhand
party websites or through people they
they move up like two times in price and
it costs like one to two grand to get
your final board if you want it done
well so I have like a one to two grand
board it's super nice and I'm gladly
easy for like the next decade and I only
the only two things I spent money on for
like the entire year I'm not even
kidding
question number two from Twitter from
Griffin Hatake does living in a house
with other streamers caused unnecessary
tension and frustration and how do you
deal with feeling irritated with each
other the mess mess is you make messes
you make and deciding which is very
specific who has more break this down a
bit I mean living with other even like
creator streamers whatever you want to
call it I'm sure there are frustrations
right oh yeah absolutely even living
with living a roommate right but but
more specifically its you guys all share
something together is it do you find
that more I guess they're saying
frustrating but do you find helps okay
all remember I talked a lot about my
problems with recently about like I've
streaming every day yeah and all that
stuff and part of the reason why I feel
like I am not doing as well as the first
couple weeks this is toast recently left
the Canada
his family again and I think him leaving
motivated like he motivated me to to be
better at TFT because me and him nice
like bounce off energy like it was kind
of like a friendly competition yes
because like he's a top one streamer I'm
like number four and I was always
looking up to him and like I bet I'm
gonna beat him I wasn't like do this
better I'm gonna do this better and like
I'm sure he sees that like because I'm
hustling he has to hustle as well but
like ever since he left like I've had
like more like problems in terms of like
my focus and my motivation and like all
this [ __ ] comes up it's like I know it's
still a lot more when he just left
recently and it feels like like you know
he helped me out a lot but not just him
like it's very motivating to live with
people who are successful equally minded
I am true the frustrations come in like
terms of like I guess privacy like
personal space is not that good I think
you want more and more of your own
personal life as you go grow older like
right it's really I I see very few
people who do where that's not the case
usually you enjoy company of others like
and you're like early 20s and select
your late 20s but like once you get your
late 20s honestly you looking for a
relationship you're looking for like -
like really settle down and I think that
we talk about this a lot we tried to
make off on a business and I think
they're like for the most part like in
the end we weren't sure we what we had
big dreams like we went off fine to be
like a maybe a household name all this
stuff but then we realized that like
while we're trying to go for so business
oriented stuff between friends not sure
how long is this gonna like even stay
together or us to stay together as a
group currently like we may there's a
chance that we plan to like just disband
at the end at the end of like the
current lease because just because like
not because we hate each other but
because it's it's like that time a
little house said it's hard to push
through the plateau in a way i pushing
through a plateau it's like I feel like
there's a time when people know that you
should move on or that you you want to
move on and while we're having a great
time together and we're being very
successful like I think bring us
together has made everyone more
successful right and we we're like
creating lifelong friendships and one of
the one of the words or
instead Lily used to say was that you
know what they said that it was the best
of times in in our last house she it was
during one of our like we were sitting
down like eating like talking she's like
you know you don't know the best of
times until they're gone and she said
that that could be us right now and I
thought I always think about that
because I'm just like that deep line
yeah I don't know like I really may
think I may look back on this and think
this is probably the or maybe could be
one of the best times of my life
mm-hmm I truly believe that that could
be the case and so I'm trying to just
not take you for granted I get again
right and do the best I can and not
really worry about where stuff ends you
know cuz it's gonna end at some point
I'll find it's gonna dissolve because we
decided not to like kind of taking new
members and not to like kind of expand
at least currently maybe that changes
the next couple of months who knows but
like we try they make it very very
exclusive and by doing so it's like well
if one person leaves like it's like you
know it's like a boy band you know you
just can't kick you out [ __ ] Justin
Timberlake and expect you know the rest
of the band to stay together mm-hmm
oh we're like a really shitty boyband
like you could bring in we're like we're
like S Club 7 do you remember that real
throwback like no one even remembers
them in life yeah but yeah like we're
like like that you guys are like you
guys are a family yeah yeah I actually
think of him as my family I'm not I'm
not super close to my uh my real family
anymore um I had to visit them next year
by the way I promise my fault my father
my grandparents my grandfather's last
wish before he dies he's 92 right now
it's the seam his his grandsons and so I
have I was like I will definitely go
just tell me what so I'm planning a trip
next year to see him before he dies
where did your family live my family's
all in China okay
also that is that's pretty tough all my
fit like my mom dad moved to China
my brother's studying in med school or
trying to go into med school over
Boston but he just came back from China
too so like I was the only person in the
country
for a long time actually talk about my
family do you know how my family a
little bit we thought about it that's
okay it's subject ever you're
comfortable okay I've talked about this
like I guess maybe three friends I'm
knob is that super public because I feel
like it's just a little bit awkward
talked about okay um so my family does
pretty well in China I would say uh my
aunt owns the four largest hospitals in
Sean high also very well uh yes so
fairly well uh like I learned a lot of
interesting things my grandfather or one
of my grandfather's yeah one of my
grandfather's did train ten thousand
people for the Beijing opening Olympics
Wow he was one of the eight generals in
the Chinese art I think it's called
general is where like there's eight
different people who controls at least
like ten thousand people I have no idea
it's really weird but like he retired
recently but he was the one who trained
the opening ceremony he's trained for
six months they cut down from ten
thousands like eight or seven and so
like yeah you saw the Beijing Olympic
ceremony when they ran across the screen
all that said my grandfather my
grandparents trained that my my dad's
younger brother is like one of the
number one contact lawyers in the
country or like and he graduated like
first in his class from MIT something
like that my my dad's like one of the
best offshore engineering platforms in
the country he got hired by Chinese
government and he wanted a number one
civilian award last year Wow which is
great for me because they could just get
they could just give me visas for free
it's actually excellent bunch of so like
actually like like my father's
generation I could I consider me like
like the generation of miracles you know
like kind of like you know talking about
you know they're like the generation of
miracles and like they see our
generation is like the failure
generation like they always what did
what do they think about your career
choice
oh they actually like I think most of
them like me cuz I'm like the most
successful although like everyone else
is like it's like you don't know where
do they get it though oh yeah yeah cuz
like it's like it's huge engine it's
legal X's and all the fan
Chai's places all this stuff they don't
sign with like Nike and [ __ ] like that
and any wild [ __ ] China but so like in
China in some countries you can have
money without power okay it's possible
or vice-versa in China it's not possible
if you have power you also have money
like it's and so like I would say my my
family is relatively powerful in in that
country uh-huh and I I'll talk about
that much because like I don't like to
ever have any kind of association with
them I don't want to feel like I can
always fall back on going to China sure
thing and to be honest I'm really like
cut off from my family like I I've very
rarely talked to them I'm like it's like
terrible when I feel people here people
have like oh yeah me and my mom like
call each other on a monthly basis I'm
like yeah me and my mom if she's like I
remember and like I don't miss her phone
call like maybe we'll talk like once
every six months my brother might talk
like once every like three months so
it's like I'm a really like very distant
relationship with my family I feel much
closer with my family in LA like my
roommates no they're pretty much my
second family
didn't I deal with my mic mic closely
related like blood ties but it's not
it's not because there's like animosity
no I'm just a terrible person like I
feel like I do really really badly like
you know I'm like the worst kind of
friend you can have because I will never
reach out and ask to do something and so
like if you don't interact with me on a
daily basis which I don't leave the
house mm-hmm
so you can't interact with me unless you
live with me I will like like I won't
reef refresh the friendship kind of that
deal because relationships and
friendships are like the same thing you
work at them for them to be better you
know if you don't work at them you're
not gonna develop good friendships and
like a lot of times like I'm a very bad
person at that and like that
that's true for like both like my
friendship relationships as well as like
my household like my my actual family
relationships now I try to get better at
it but like that's just let's say it's
one of my biggest weaknesses but you're
working on it yeah I mean when you like
you said you wanted more you've been
living with your family yeah you've been
living with these other
streamers but you do say you want your
own personal space and it's getting to a
time where you feel like you're at that
age where you want to have your own
space uh yeah I know like I think
especially when I live with offline
people I I feel like it's it's weird for
me to try to pursue a relationship
because I always it's actually really
funny because I think of them as like a
second family I always compare like if
I'm interested in girl I'm like what
would my my roommates think if I brought
her back and there I feel like they
wouldn't be like satisfied instantly not
interested like my traction level to
them doesn't matter as much as like how
but I think my roommates will judge me
for the person that hears well they
approve that closer yeah at least
sometimes I feel that way I talk to
other people our house well they feel
that way too like like they have to be
you like if I that's tough for the
person like I've been in like one
serious relationship and then like a
couple of things when I like talk to
people like I'm always just like would I
be comfortable bringing the back and the
answer is no which has been though a lot
of times like I don't bother I'm very
private about my relationships people in
my household don't know if anyone I'm
talking to anyone there's multiples
before we wrap it up yeah the first
thing that popped up when you brought up
that question of like how do you guys
diffuse issues is something is something
I always think about cuz you told it to
me and it was like I was having issues
at one point and you're like is there
anything you can do about it right now
and right away and I was like no and
you're like then why are you so focused
on it focus things that are immediate
and the things that you can toast with
oh dude okay so I we talked about Mikey
pie big a streamer legal legends
teammate one of the biggest things I
learned from him is to not give a [ __ ]
about stuff and I feel like he learned
that you grow older anyways like
predominately with him he only cares
about a couple things in life it's like
his friends his cats
Leisha and League of Legends that's it
lishus his wife
why it's not like they're married and
it's like he's live in the life like
he's got the girl
he's got the game he's got the cat you
know he's got he's got everything he
cares about that's all he cares about
he doesn't care about like he's like
image he like he wears these like white
shirts [ __ ] he actually moved up a brand
his mom bought him new white shirt so
like $20 but like like he's like he's
like flexing with his $20 Whitey's now
but for the most part for the most part
like he doesn't give a [ __ ] about
anything like he'll he'll blow money
away like he's had yes'm Gucci [ __ ]
sneakers he has got some nice [ __ ] but
he doesn't mainly as a joke you know
just cuz he can as opposed to something
he's actively interested right like I
learned to care a lot less about like my
appearance to others I learned to care a
lot about less about like what I wear
and I learned to keep focus on what I
really care about you know whether it's
like my stream whether it's my
relationships my friends my roommates
are it's helped me focus a lot in terms
of like what can I do to get stuff done
and just ignore everything else cuz I
think I think that's made me a lot less
like I guess stressed about a lot of
different things a lot of people come to
me with problems and I'm just like do
you want me to like actually solve them
for you or do you want me to like just
be a listening like person cuz like I'm
really bad at being able to do both at
once
so like I try to have them clarify
that's actually a really good question
to ask people because I found like I
always try to solve problems exactly
people don't want like this one a year
exactly you know that's actually very
important to learn yeah yeah be a good
good listener sometimes and so yeah I
think well thank you know everybody
listening to this well what that being
said do you have anything to plug yep
twitch stream or something like that you
know you can you can see you can find me
on like Twitter comm twitch that complex
Cara I have SCARA official mic well you
know what I have a YouTube I've all that
[ __ ] go to my Twitter you can find it
all there I don't have anything to plug
I'm trying to do this challenge thing
but I'm gonna I'm gonna finish it by the
way there's no way I'm stopping but like
I guess every 65 what do you what dare
you want uh it's to 23 oh so like oh you
started to begin at January first
stalking in at the very end of the year
the very dream to arity No okay so let's
treat it silly yeah like a pack awesome
believe I'm gonna be backseat saying
things and I don't know anything about I
guess I didn't play auto chest for a
little bit but I don't know that League
heroes are I just I don't want to
relearn it he's a dota player that I
played a lot of chess I was a king I was
one game away from Queen oh really so
[ __ ] piss I hit it that's not be I
was I was a pawn nine tonight I got
tonight nice you played the game I got
tonight
all right well again real quick real
quick
go ahead I didn't wanna I don't wanna do
a certain the very beginning I'm a huge
[ __ ] right here your fanboy like I've
watched a lot of you [ __ ] I'm not gonna
lie I'm retired earliest [ __ ] from ninja
that is prettier all the way to like I
watched a tinfoil ball recently I
watched I watched hey remember we talked
about videos that I do pretty hell but
you're not proud of does there's a
there's a bunch in there doing the water
walkie with like the shadows that took a
shitload of time that was crazy I
watched a live oh yeah okay like that
one oh yeah oh you're very you're very
inspiring person to watch I look at
YouTube I see a lot about the creator's
for like very good that like vlogging
and like very good at like honestly if I
was good at vlogging I probably I feel
like your skill set is very inspiring
person like it's very nice because I can
look at it I always like talk to Albert
whether people live in the house like
have you seen this like look how he does
this he's like wow this is really cool
I'm like awesome
well I appreciate that and we are gonna
check out your stream right when you get
home no please
oh sorry right before we go thank you
again for being here you can follow us
at off the pill on Twitter at off the
pill podcast on Instagram and usually
just how we end this we just breathe
into the mic in three two one
well that was like a load what you hear
that knows me