so like the part like is say for sure
that there's no scrip there's no paper
script on Terrace house never had a
girlfriend never kissed a girl and has
never changed since the show you know it
yeah the more people who wants me to die
I want to live more and the more people
who cost me that then I'm gonna you know
lose more weight alright clap claps
alright welcome back to another episode
of off the bill podcast
okay that's good today we got David in
the moderator seat Paco right here next
to me I'm Ryan and we have a very
special guest mr. Eden Kai in the house
I recognize him from uh Teddy's house it
the hawaii edition was it name of that
one Aloha State Aloha State let's see I
should know that we should know that why
I didn't watch it huh no but I did a
little bit of research so I knew that
anyway we met a few months ago and I
said I was a big fan it was a mind
blowing for me because I was a huge fan
of you yeah I I am so just for people
who don't know Terrace house is a it's a
Japanese reality show it's on Netflix
and Fuji TV in Japan three guys and
three girls living together and romance
or their life focus on their lifestyle
just think of like a wholesome Jersey
Shore or real world kind of thing honey
I don't know how to explain because I
never liked those show like reality
shows but that Terrace house was the
first one I could actually watch really
oh and I think it's because it doesn't
look like there's there's minor things I
don't know how what's so a big lievable
it is that could be a cools you into
like the normalities of it's not
dramatic like people fighting every day
every episode and well I don't know
maybe there's some truth behind those
lights or something goes yeah I think
that's interesting to hear because I
hear a lot of people from foreigners a
lot that they want to learn Japanese or
like they're learning the Japanese
culture and that's like the most people
who watch us like the show right well I
mean watching it just like the there's
things I didn't even happen ease I don't
even know because that's not my culture
no I'm Americanized so just like
watching that show and seeing like the
little things that get on peoples nerves
I guess or like the way that it's just
such a different maybe that's what's
appealing to me it was Japanese culture
and how's everyone's so polite and the
moment there's like you stray away from
that a little bit it's
offensive I mean depends what you do and
stuff but I think yeah well let's talk a
little bit about who you are
cuz you knows for some people who
haven't even seen this show they they
don't even know who you are in the first
place uh you know where are you from
you know you're a lot younger than we
are twenty-one yeah
born in 1998 some time flowing right and
you were on the show at the age of what
eighteen eighty I was a senior in high
school and where were you born and
raised I was born and raised in Tokyo
Japan
a place called hot tea oh gee and I
never went to international school just
a regular public school until seventh
grade and after that my entire family
moved to Hawaii about six and a half
years ago so went to a local high school
graduated so you can speak this well in
six and a half years well I'm still
learning my dad is from actually my dad
is japanese-american so he's uh who was
born and raised in Portland Oregon okay
so I understood what he was talking
about but I so my mom's from a normal
way too but spoke like Japanese to both
of them it's still like pretty
impressive that you're being able to
pick it up cuz I originally just hearing
you talk I thought you were American
raised that's a compliment in Hawaii
there's like no accent whatsoever
yeah well yeah you have the laid-back
kind of personality of a Hawaii person
as well well I mean I'm from oi you know
what I mean though cuz he's even better
than people from is great like in
American people probably think you speak
better English than the two of us Wow
maybe you just learn the right way well
that means you're really smart that
means you did well in school probably I
always follow my passions your position
we can talk about that so you actually
even on the show you were well you do a
lot of things but you were primarily
what oh cool a player I played the
ukulele acoustic guitar and I'm a
singer-songwriter currently and
now you're doing shows and stuff yes
going back and forth would you say most
your fans are like no you from terrorist
Isles
yes I think so but oh no what is your
fan base like because you know ever
since Netflix has acquired the rights to
terrorist house I'm sure that has got to
new like international fans yes it was
pretty mind-blowing for me too because I
did not know first that it's gonna be on
Netflix that I was like only for
Japanese TV but when I first noticed
that oh like an English comment I
posed and after it had like a lot of
stuff happen and it's I was happy you
know and bless and ever get to never
thought of like experiencing stuff like
this and I'd say a lot of people are
from Japan or in Japan your fan base fan
base yes but at the same time some
people are from US Canada Europe
Philippines Thailand Brazil I'm just
blessed
you're a worldwide sensation and
multi-talented I was kind of shocked how
many people like not just in Japan and
on like how many people watched Harris
house like it's a Japanese reality show
it doesn't make sense that all of us
would love it so much but it's it's huge
like I mean if you know you know a lot
of people don't watch it but the people
that do it's like they're super into it
I agree actually you know um a lot of
agent people lie doesn't matter if it if
the person is Japanese or Chinese or
Korean like a lot of agent people
basically watches the show which is
pretty mind-blowing to me too or if
anyone's dating Mazin they watch it
watch it like so like me my wife or my
husband I'm wondering like is there just
I'm sure there are I'm bothered song
really racist but is there like I wonder
if there's people who are just like what
in a white group that watches terror
cells I'm fine I feel like is that rare
like in the Midwest because it's not
Netflix so anyone can watch it right
it's not where I think but like most of
them aren't like Asian people both like
I do
receive some comments to like you know
that's non-asian so what's the puted and
do they just like because i know there's
some people just like japanese culture
exactly like whoever likes japanese
culture or you know who's interested
yeah to see what is it like in japan or
i'd like to live with japanese people
right
i will say this is to the audience
anyone listening right now or watching
it sounds i'm just gonna be completely
honest it sounds like the most boring
show in the world but then that's what i
thought initially watching one episode i
was like oh that was alright i guess
i'll watch another one oh I got addicted
I actually felt the same when I just
heard about the name before ello has
state only knew about the name I never
watched it and I could totally relate to
you cuz like that's what I thought yeah
the description right three guys three
girls living in a house yeah and and
nothing really like it's hard to say
nothing happens because when you
compared to American reality shows right
like Jersey Shore yeah it's more a world
that's so dramatic people are fighting
punching each other and stuffing and
then and then you watch this show and
everybody's so polite and nice to each
other then the cameras just set on a
tripod is like beautifully shot it's not
like extreme zoom ins and shaky cameras
to make everything look more hectic you
know it's very calm and relaxing and
it's like watch some people eating
dinner yeah it's a like you ma but it's
really a isn't it more so about like
your the the viewer is thinking about
like what they're thinking like what are
they thinking when they're silently
eating together what's going through
their mind right all the little nuances
of like human interaction I think that's
what's really right funny and
interesting and also having the
commentators right the what do you guys
call them I say well we say like studio
members or snowmen bah and stuff I love
them yeah they're super entertaining
that's what makes the show yeah no
offense but I mean like it oh for sure
no they they're the consistent people
that there's basically for those that
don't know you guys have a reality show
but in between the show there's
commentators commenting on every little
thing people say like people they don't
like they're celebrities right yes they
are like remember the guy with the
glasses yeah machaon yeah he's a
professor
comedian and I was so happy when I was
you know roasted I am well I mean he
told me that oh you skip bet like you
know drink all the bathtub water like
girls like Japanese Paco and I could be
like I do not or did I pass the word so
when the show is coming out it's
sometimes it's not finished why you guys
are still recording right like no you
see yourselves like as a show a film
that's the cringe your awkward part of
the show cuz we're gonna see ourselves
when that's released right inside the
house which we did so you know remember
the scene that oh like are you
interested on the you know anyone or a
boiler who's your like favorite like
from Aloha State mm-hmm and you know
blah blah blah blah and that scene is
out and right we watched it and it was
pre awkward well I was wondering cuz
there's I mean again spoiler alert
there's there's moments where you got
like in earlier episodes you guys all I
feel like in every season they always
talk about oh who are you interested in
you know and you're just like a private
conversation with the boys private
conversation with the girls but it you
know you're being filmed so like you
know that other person's gonna see it
right mmm don't I mean doesn't that
affect I mean I don't I don't know maybe
I feel like I would be affected by
knowing that that person's gonna see it
well I wasn't for me personally I didn't
know like that it'll be on that that
early first of all so I wasn't so I
don't know like maybe others like they
knew about it so you were you being like
completely just like oh these are my
honest feelings cuz you were very honest
by the time that they said yeah I'm out
here on his human being no but uh yeah I
wasn't I wasn't thinking about that at
all you're just being authentically you
I think so like the part is that you
know I could say for sure that I
is nervous a lot for the first couple
weeks cuz you know like living with
strangers and I was like the youngest
you know uh the other cast Eric and even
they're like you know 27 26 and that
time and they were like 10 years older
than me you know
so I was you know a little pressure like
and I was kind of you know scared they
couldn't like me or not and stuff but
you know once I kind of got used to it
and got close with them and stuff
everything is fine okay yeah did you um
I guess I don't know if you can talk
about this or not but like did was there
anything that you'd I know you can't
answer this I don't why I'm asking but
is there any way that you really didn't
get along with their it's got to be
annoying living with two other dudes in
the same room that's like it's not it's
not just housemates it's roommates right
and then three girls like right down the
hall I don't know if it's down the hall
but like in the same house you know it's
a beautiful house but there's got to be
some things that get that got you a lil
annoyed I don't know if you can say what
you can say I could say that right now I
love them all today for sure that the
whole purpose is you know we all have
different personalities everyone's
different and for a low estate what's
interesting is that there's people
that's Japanese Japanese from Japan but
there's also local people so there's
gonna be you know some culture
differences how they think different
yeah for sure
so yeah you know like might be tough
sometimes but they kind of you know get
that long I mean you've seen like Eric P
and L mean that scene to you yeah so
stuff like that and could you explain
what happens between this cuz I haven't
seen it so well Justin we were talking
about this earlier just like Japanese
culture in general is so different for
like what's acceptable and what isn't
you don't sometimes you don't even know
I think in that snare without spoiling
anything you don't even know that you're
being offensive to someone when you are
in a different culture because you
wouldn't it's not considered offensive
in their culture in your own culture or
like even you're originally from Japan
but if you you know used to the
environment that you're know been around
then you might say something offensive
right
because you just forget about it yeah
well so you're indirectly saying that
there are some people in there in the
house that may not have you may not have
liked what are you trying to fish out of
him right now I don't think you said
anything about that's though would you
say you're friends with everybody
mm-hmm and you're close to everybody
well um I'd say no cuz everyone lives in
a different place some people live in
Japan so who lives in Hawaii somebody
lives in LA or mainly New York yeah
so you know we're going our separate
ways but I'm totally cool with everyone
and I think everyone's cool like you
know we're on the most recent season as
well they brought you back yes
Tokyo 2019 2020 so you're in right now
only part 1 of the new season is out
there's another part are you can you say
if you're in that as well
we'll see yeah I have a question about
it's like because you know not everybody
has the opportunity to be on a reality
TV show right and you know I think a lot
of people do wonder about the camera
situation like how many cameras were
there it was it just like a bunch of
like webcams that were set everywhere or
I'm nervous or just like good quality
there yeah or just like DSLR cameras or
whatever is I think he said he can't you
can't say right behind the scenes stuff
okay well Avenger it depends I will say
there's a reason why we're wondering
because no one's allowed to say anything
on that show I feel like I tried to
google it before it's just because it
shot so differently that is I think
that's another attraction where people
are like how are they filming it with
and getting these like raw real motions
from people that's not over-the-top yeah
I mean I have a friend who was actually
a director for a reality TV show mm-hmm
and he told because I asked him some
questions about how reality TV shot and
some of the things that he mentioned
where it was that like he will like
everything's real but there would be
certain scenarios that he would kind of
create like yep
all can say hey this person kind of said
this thing about you and you know like I
I like I don't know normal in reality
shows that right uh no we got we did not
have that oh really
um yeah so like the park is say for sure
that there's no script there's no paper
to script
oh no it's Harris house hmm so but I
mean you know like how you guys like
there's a camera rolling someone walks
into a room and then all of a sudden
every like the cameras or the camera
rolling all that time that's a lot of
wasted footage you know I'm saying like
someone has to turn that camera on I
mean I know you can't answer that but
I'm just saying like that's what I
wondered about it's like how obviously
I'll weed the same yes yeah yeah I'm
like he walked into the room there's no
way like the cameraman is on a tripod
there's no way the cameras just there is
just waiting for him right yeah I was
like and if they're not filming the
whole time is that's high quality
footage there's no way they have that
much space hold all that footage anyway
we'll get all away from the behind the
scenes stuff no you can't talk about it
anyway but I mean in general I will say
I mean you kind of in a way blew up from
the show right I think everybody like
different levels right like Lauren
really blew up from the show do you like
she's like on a TV show now right I know
it's crazy yeah and then you're doing
shows all over the place which you
weren't necessarily doing before like
touring and yeah I mean I'm just blessed
and unlucky well you're skilled I mean
there's a reason why people were
impressed by you and it's also very like
on the show they were talking about it
like how'd your you have such a it's
like a what's that demeanor : very um
introverted I guess I don't know if
you're an introvert I'm just assuming
anyway you seem very like yeah sly it
but then when you play them clearly when
you play instruments you're like crazy
well I mean I'm happy to hear that uh
you know oh another thing um I never
really wore pajamas before but for sure
house and stuff I wanted to be polite
said that's why I decided to bring my
pajamas but never thought of like
receiving lots of like positive
feedbacks same for like the first
episode right yeah and same for my
personalities you know I was in
affecting to recede like no feedbacks
like that you know oh he he's acting
completely different way he plays a
guitar oh cool oh right I was like
really like never thought of that
yeah so it's it's I think the part
that's interesting for me or like other
cast members is that you're able to look
at yourself on the screen mmm from like
the third point of view right because
you're not used to just seeing your
everyday life because she'll definitely
learn a lot from it you know where
there's some things in in the show that
you wish they didn't cut out for they or
that they are you wish that you that
they did it did or they did yeah
probably you wish they did but I'm sure
they picked the best moments yeah like
they can't show everything yeah it's not
it's only sure for sure what in 45
minutes
in episode something like that oh well
they cut it out you probably can't say I
want it to be cut or like I wanted
things you wish shouldn't have made it
well back then definitely the scene when
I eat catfish alone good scene though
yeah nowadays it's super hilarious like
it's it's funny I love can you describe
the scene for those who haven't seen it
well I went out or you know that with a
the cast one of the cast members and
went to go watch some some fantastic
piece you know the movie and after
everyone yeah yes it's I was it was a
great movie anyways comment about the
movie but a movie with someone from the
show yeah from the show
yeah and after the movie you know it was
supposed to be a surprise and I
reservation like at the place a
restaurant a restaurant yep
and I asked her if you want to go eat
dinner and I Khloe got declined well
what was her excuse
she had grandparents dinner or something
like that I really hope she doesn't
watch this it's all in fact we're gonna
clip it in sent and tweeted to her
that's even better that's better
she said that she had to go to dinner
with her grandparents which is a lot it
was something like reasonable sure it
was just I mean but then you got to see
the behind the scene just which is what
I was talking about earlier of what like
she was saying well I think she really
didn't have to do I don't know if that's
true or not well I mean you know I think
family is important what I could say
family is important you know like you
don't know what's gonna happen like
anytime so I'm such a nice guy I think
it's a nice so you're too nice so she
had to go have dinner with her
grandparents and then and then you went
to dinner that you made a reservation
for two with you went alone and then you
ordered a catfish yes that was my first
catfish and you know I did not want when
I you know cancel the whole reservation
and why not I mean I feel like most
people would have done that but that's
why his he was so interesting on the
show you know cuz she actually went well
it was like you know pretty close for
the movie theaters so yeah why not you
know some stuff and then basically the
what was sad about it is he there's a
shot and he's just eating alone after
being rejected essentially and it was
just very sick it was like a very like
heartbreaking but man because
everybody's ruined for him you know but
let me ask you this did you enjoy the
catfish I tasted a bunch of emotions but
actually fun story on this trip in LA I
have any catfish for like three years
after that and recently a few days ago
actually ate catfish wow that's an and
then what happened it tasted a lot
better and now he's back ladies he's
back on the market the bats kiichi he's
gone I wouldn't know I think they moved
it or something right or it's gone like
that
have more anything from it but uh I
think one thing that I read online um
that they're talking about like you're a
virgin or something when you went on the
show yes what I mean the hope I think
that what you said initially coming on
with some or I mean it's
I never gone in a relationship yeah yes
so like complete then just like yeah
never had a girlfriend never kissed a
girl and has never changed since the
show you know it
Netflix popularity baby one I mean I'm
sure you've already said everything
without saying anything but I'm
definitely still bad on it you know so I
want to ask you Riley where I Ryan any
tips for for me like for dating advice
you're asking me yeah I mean I don't
know if I'm the best person like I'm not
known for picking up girls well I would
say right one I would say naturally your
your genuine kindness seems to be a gift
and I think if you're just more
confident with that you seem a lot more
confident already from the show at least
just talking to I mean you're talking to
us like it's nothing and they con the
show it seemed like you were struggling
to just talk to people initially but it
seemed to improve over time and I
haven't seen the new season with you in
it
I was gonna wait on to the next part
comes out and watch it all at once I can
binge it awesome but yeah I mean just
talking to you now is kind of shocked
before like because I hadn't met you
except for that one time and we barely
got to talk and I didn't know what to
expect to be honest I mean that's
another thing about those reality shows
like you get an idea of a person mm-hmm
but they're not always exactly like that
or maybe you've changed a lot I don't
know well I could totally say you know
I've been there a lot over 30 years but
you know things about a show reality
show is that what they show it's it is a
part of me but it's not everything of me
you know and there's always gonna be
like some fun parts with me and
hopefully I could you know show more of
that
my life journey is there anyone that you
feel like not necessarily acts but like
they know they're on camera so they're
acting differently from when the cameras
are off
you can't talk but yeah
what is your break no spice we do but
but I think before we go to the sushi
break you did bring your guitar here
yeah in case brought a guitar we should
add that as our she she we've never had
a live performance here
really we've never no never I think you
may be the first here let's see how we
can even record this properly yeah yeah
we would love to see music from you
that'd be amazing before she well let us
yeah take us away into our she she break
no be serious eating guy this is a you
know a clip of my new song that I work
with a cat McDowell and because of me
some Cola they're awesome and uh it's
the song top is called outside inside
and you know the time I get treated as
Japanese Japanese in Hawaii and a
foreigner as a foreigner in Japan I had
that a lot and I used to think about it
a lot but like the most importantly just
be you kind of song like the course goes
like song Canon soft kitty and intial
goes like
[Music]
Thanks I was really nervous and we're
back welcome back thanks for that that
song it was awesome I know thanks then
very quick actually it's such an honor
when did you learn to play when uh for
guitar I was I think it was 14 and I
started playing the collide from high
school
oh well that's kind of recent that's not
a easy thing to do where you found of
Jake Shimabukuro uh I know I said it
like that actually you know did not know
that and uh uh and look like after all
like I've searched it up after I started
playing though clothing and stuff and oh
my you know such a cool playstyle and
stuff and I got to meet him one time and
yeah he was super kind yeah yeah he's
awesome
yeah I never met him but everybody in
Hawaii knew about him just because he
was the guy who could play they were
clearly a little too fast because crazy
man slow down dude like I'm getting
nervous like yeah yeah it was pretty
crazy yeah so what else is going on I
mean you're here here in LA right now
doing what shows here or mainly creating
the EP right now and uh so this is your
third it's actually my first EP and then
what are these two things so those two
are albums my instrumental albums I made
it a while ago actually from high school
mm-hmm and I had couple albums from
Japan but you know it's unreal label
yeah and uh yeah things kind of changed
well you look very different I mean you
obviously a lot younger but you look
very different
you said you were thank you you would I
mean he lost a lot of weight I did I
lost about 35 pounds after
to tokyo serious thank you well I mean
that's a that's a lot like what what
sparked it like why all of a sudden well
you know I wanted to you know be a best
version of myself and I think you know
once I get the attention from the
viewers as how the show goes
you know I love the fans and stuff too
but you know I also try not like listen
to some people who gives out like
suggestions trying to be like little but
really I feel like we're in a time right
now where people want the opposite
they're all about body positivity and
silence yeah but I mean I I'm assuming
with all that positivity there's always
gonna be comments that are the opposite
right naturally trolling and yes and
that really affected you mm-hmm the
thing about this show is dad you know
people are gonna criticize see you
you know people everyone is different
you know everyone has a different
opinion so if I do this on the screen
people think how yourself like done dad
right and said you know there's like
everything going on everyone has an
opinion about you yes yes man I can't
see a lot of negative opinions about you
though again what what can I like what
like what I mean this is one thing where
it's just like you're too conservative
you know you're too kind
where you put other people before
yourself which is sometimes like are you
really living your best life at that
point are you mate are you really making
the right decisions for yourself or are
you living for the gratification of
others mm-hmm so a lot of times when you
hold yourself back like that people can
be frustrated because people uh you know
they want which is weird because they're
living through you in a way where
they're like oh you should have been
yourself this is where you should have
broke free they would have done yeah
exactly
so that's why I like those are the type
of criticisms or you know like when I
guess the awkward situations and like
being rejected like oh you got rejected
because of this I would've did that so I
mean yeah it's like those types of
things but it's not saying it's not
saying he's a bad person no I know I'm
saying
kind of surprised that that was the
thing they attacked you like I'm sure
that there is other reasons they
attacked you but I mean to say like hey
lose weight or like you're too fat or
whatever you weren't I mean like you on
the show you weren't that like you
weren't big I don't think you were
overweight yeah not it I don't think so
understand if you compare two Americans
Japanese in Japan it might be over
without where the comments came like
that those comments came from mostly
Japanese fans or is it from Americans as
well mostly from Japanese people
immediately you know like don't get me
wrong like everyone has you know people
yeah stuff but not a spoiler but before
part two is out I've received like a
tons of more comments like that then
when I was appearing on although his
state oh you the current season the
current season sees a lot of hate I did
mostly regarding your weight or
something else
everything everything like you know just
just straight-up die and stuff you know
like I mean after all all the stuff that
you know has happened for the past three
years and especially like this year I
think I have a like thicker skin I have
a stronger mental and well not always
but I'm trying like thinking you know
positively you know yeah the more people
who wants me to die I want to live more
and the more people who cost me fat then
I wanna you know lose more weight as
much as possible I mean not at the point
that I'm gonna like not you know have
like if he's just order something but uh
right you know just trying to be healthy
trying to be myself and I mean I don't
feel anything about it but like you know
for at that time it was pretty tough for
me that I couldn't share my emotions to
my fans are the crowd you know I just
get it act like nothing is going on but
you know that happens for everyone else
I think it does but I mean I think you
have to a certain degree you have an
image of like real real innocence and I
think I mean you even just sing and now
like you feel like you can't really
express yourself completely I feel like
I feel like you can like I think I think
I mean
I do like like in front of like my
friends or like you know but non-public
like face to face is that do you think
is that a Japanese culture thing culture
it's it's a long it's a long story like
well what uh what would happen if you
were to because you know in America
right like if you look on on YouTube and
a lot of these youtubers expressing
themselves expressing their I love it
like their depression and the things
their struggles and that they're going
through if you were to do that to a
Japanese audience
how will they generally react to
something like that don't wouldn't that
make this like feel a boo right is it
taboo or do they feel more like they
could relate to you and like oh I go
through that too and I want to support
you it really depends if it's like a fan
fan then you know gonna be like very
okay or you know like I want to relate
to you but like if it's like just other
everyone else then it'll be like like
don't give me that negative five I don't
want to I don't want to see that kind of
stuff right so it's it's not a it's
depends it depends on situations and
stuff that's what I know Japan is like I
mean traditionally like you don't like
even just like naturally me growing up
like we don't share you don't share your
feelings really you know with when
you're growing at least for me it's not
like we didn't have a loving home or
environment but if you're like I don't
know you I don't I never told my dad hey
I love you like you know like it's not
like in TV shows you don't really say
that at least in my household and all my
friends growing up around that time
maybe it's different now I think it's an
Asian thing yeah it is an Asian thing
yeah I think so maybe maybe not but I
feel like you're younger too but for me
um well the reason it started music is
you know to make people smile not only
kind of sounds cheesy but I want to you
know bring that positive vibes and what
I loved about you YouTube watching your
videos too
is it makes me smile like you know it
makes me positive overall and that's
what I want to do and I'm happy that
it's my job and you know effort like
this personal stuff instead I think it's
really no need to share that with people
but I only want to share something
that's happy with people right so you'd
like to bottle up that stuff in a way
which people say not to do but I mean I
think everybody does it to a certain
degree and I also think right now it's
almost
people at least in the US have been
going in the opposite direction and
creating more drama because that's what
has become like the thing right to share
your depression itself yeah which is I
mean I like I said I think the stigma
should go away and I'm glad that people
are sharing this stuff but I think
there's also people who are how do you
say like that it's being over there
taking advantage of the situation
yeah because it's almost like becoming
like I don't want to see a trend because
that sounds disrespectful but it's kind
of becoming that and I feel like if you
can't get away with that it's a very it
just it just sees I see the difference
in the cultures essentially if you were
to do that I could see why your Japanese
fans would be like no what are you
whining about like keep it to yourself
kind of thing I don't know if that's
true I'm just like I'm top of my head
maybe I mean sooner or later a might
just be like oh whatever just start
showing my emotions and stuff but I mean
for most of times I'm I'm pretty happy
all right I try to be positive kind of
guy so right you take the negative and
you use it too yeah like now I feel
better if I received those comments
because I get more you know motivation
you know talking about the catfish you
know like reject me more or exactly more
like one more rejection you know a lot
more haters so so that I could go like
you know I could motivate myself and be
a better person
well we all hate you here so oh thanks
this list 10 things we hate about Eden
and oh wow I know it's surprising only
10 there's way more to be hundred over
hundred we get some of this like the
Twitter questions I mean there's stuff I
know we can't you can't talk about but
it's kind of interesting oh oh sorry I
said one of the questions which I like
to because uh I'm curious you kind of
dodged this a little bit but what is
your love life look like now mmm are you
single ready to mingle
are you in a relationship are you
talking are you dodging this question
well uh
go let's party when it's out oh wow you
just told us you're in it then Wow
no I didn't say he's in it yeah okay
well I mean well let me ask you this
have you ever written a song about
someone that you loved or interest in or
a song for a girl at any point in your
life yes are all of your songs about
girls in your life yes no what can what
gives you the most inspiration though is
it like when you get heartbroken or do
you draw inspiration from other things
so when I create a song you know it
could be affection or not affection I
love to like create a little small short
story inside my brain I wanted the song
to start but like I wanted the song to
end at the same time and it could you
know come from like a personal
experience to you but like it also be
like some kind of location or like view
there's a really beautiful place called
China walls and for my lot of my
instrumental songs I used to go there
after high school as I went to high
school in Hawaii Kai my friends and you
know just chilled there and the sunsets
are super beautiful and that really
inspired me a lot of creating original
songs so it depends but hmm yeah what
kind of girls do you like like if you if
you're not in a relationship if you were
to get into one know what kind of girls
do you find yourself more attracted to I
I love well does it matter like a friend
or anything you know a person who's
really passionate about something you
know it really doesn't matter what it is
but as long as like they're really
passionate about it you know they're
chasing that dream or or just a little
thing you know um personalities and what
about personalities like girls were a
little more quiet
a little more
able to have a conversation outgoing
loud energy low energy outgoing for sure
I think cuz you know just love to
communicate with people nowadays and
nowadays not nowadays are for me I feel
like that's a skill you I mean I know
you can mentioned it on the show but is
that a skill that you learned from being
on the show because it seemed like over
the course of those episodes that you
were on it improved for you you seem to
really shy and then you slowly started
opening up but I feel definitely better
than before for sure but not at the
point that I'm satisfied so I'm still
there's more to go for me did you have a
lot of sorry you're saying go ahead like
when you were in junior high high school
elementary did you have a lot of friends
or did you hang out with like a few
people just a few and you're still
friends sometimes I mean that's that's a
weird answer we this is what I want to
say we hang out sometimes yeah cuz
you're busy when I whenever I'm in back
back in Japan yeah but you know it's the
thing about schools dad everyone kind of
goes like you know there are like
separate ways you know everyone lives in
a different location and I'm more
excited to meet new people for me who
has like a similar interest or a similar
passion well so you're in um sorry
you're in Japan how long again fortune
until 14 14 so what do you like better
like as you like where do you like
living better uh us why is that
I feel more being myself in a u.s.
meaning you can you just feel more
yourself because I I feel more open
about anything in the US and you don't
feel that in Japan no it's because of
the culture the society yeah I just say
this society the person if the person is
okay culture yeah
really you know something like if the
person is like older you have to be
super polite or you know if it's like
your boss you gotta be super flyed can't
be late or you know if you something
Slade
you gotta apologize and so all these
like you know Tim who are like me
manners and stuff and I'm not saying
it's bad at all it's really it's great
to be polite and stuff but sometimes you
know when you when you kind of get used
to the you know Aloha vibe right the
local vibe and whenever you're back in
Japan all the sudden you know it
sometimes it kind of its kind of too
much yeah no I mean I hundred percent
agree because I mean I only went there
for like I was there like a month ago
and I was only there for like a couple
weeks and I've been there maybe three or
four times not very long and every time
I go it's always like everyone is so
polite and so nice to you that like you
I feel brewed by just existing and not
following you know I mean like I'm own
America and like I
oh shoot was I supposed to like just
little things like I read on oh I didn't
read I saw a video too saying like how
to take trains and stuff like that I
didn't know how to how to do any of that
and then like just just rules and like I
didn't know but I was doing it I was
like talking on the train and I noticed
oh wait no one talks on the train I
don't I didn't know that was an
etiquette thing I don't know if that's
true or not but I mean no one talks to
each other on the train and I was just
big old English American accent just
talking to people no I mean it's just
like little things like that I didn't
even think about but like it's mmm
everyone is so polite and I feel like
it's not real I don't know if that's
true enough but I feel like nobody can
be sown Hatt likes put on a smile and
treat you so nicely all the time like
there has to be some pointed then though
it's just like I don't like you they're
really suppressing like their real
emotions yeah and I feel like I don't I
can't tell because everyone's so nice
but when you're there long enough you're
like this is kind of suspicious nice
they are so that's why they're mostly
honest on internet but I could I just
say you know there
really committed which is not a bad
thing at all but Japanese people like
their early commit only what they're
doing yeah but you know sometimes when
it kind of goes too much then you know
they're they get super exhausted or they
you know you know the situation like
they work too much yeah they all of a
sudden like blackout and stuff and
that's what's been going on a lot and
yeah so I think that's you know it's all
about the balance there's pros and cons
that reasons yes yes exactly like
Japanese people they have like like you
said one of the best work ethics but to
the point where sometimes like there is
exhaustion and I think Japan has one of
the highest suicide rates to which is it
an unfortunate fact but it does come
with the fact of being unable to express
emotionally where you're at right
because you're you know or and the
expression only a correlation yeah and
the expectation because yet to get into
high school you have to test right yes
and even then there are certain high
schools that are very good and if you
don't make into that it's looked down
it's not like a CT that he could just
take it over and over again if you just
mess you get away for another year and
there's such a huge pressure it's
heavily looked down on I I don't know
how much I could say about it but like
you know people now does its kind
different before people used to lay
judge from like what kind of school you
went like no matter like friendship or
work right you know he didn't get into a
good school the people who did look down
on the other people right so for me like
I never attended college you know
graduate high school yeah in gosh
trained into music so that what did they
see you as scum nowadays no but maybe
before like maybe you know traditional
people might think oh you never didn't
college like you know he's that smart
and stuff right but I'm happy that
there's you know a lot of people in
Japan who accepts me like of who I am
right well you said a lot of your like
half your fans are from Japan mm-hmm
anything is a little bit of the graces
of the media and being on terrace house
yeah you get that exemption because it's
like oh you didn't go to college but it
paid off because you
you were able to do these things well we
had that that was my the whole subject
of like you know what I when I was
thinking the entire time of Aloha state
whether or not I want to attend the
college or not I was planning to go
attend a music college mm-hmm and after
you know like we seen some life tips and
advice I talked about to everyone and
decided on the show you said mm-hmm and
I decided not to but you know like
there's no regret of whatever I have
done and mostly I really want to take to
take care or lie when I really want to
care about people who also cares about
me mm-hmm and I think that's the most
important thing okay sounds great
sorry kind of got too deep no no that's
great
so I noticed I watched some of your
performances and whatnot on on YouTube
oh thanks notice that your dad is a very
important part of your career I you know
I met you before this podcast you know
with your with your dad and we had a
great conversation and it seems like
he's very integrated into your your life
yes he has you know in fact the music
stuff actually came from like my parents
to like my music interest that kind of
makes sense see musicians or my dad used
to be a performer he used to work for
NHK for 18 years he did it
radio casting right yeah like voiceovers
and he used to be actor too
yeah you've done like a lot of stuff and
you know my parents loved music they I
think I remember like you put you play
like some like classical classical music
when I was like little but most likely I
was heavily influenced by a Michael
Jackson mm-hmm
because I was just blown away of like
how music could be powerful like how
much it could influence the entire crowd
or like you know
the whole entirely generation like you
know right so since then like I started
actually singing first before guitar I
knew clay but I was like stalking for
like 4 years when I was really into
playing the guitar so that's why during
terrace house and so I wrote that song
called monogatari one will be left or in
the forward before I left
yeah okay so before that song I haven't
sang for like four years
mm-hmm but yeah so for my parents so
your your full-time musician slash actor
would you say yes acting used to be not
used to be acting as my another passion
I'm passionate about I used to be a
child actor when I was around sex you're
a child actor when you were in Japan
yes Oh what-what were you in anything
that's a little bit good fine um like
just several commercials and maybe TV
dramas and so nice Oh like a reoccurring
actor yes yes Starro that so that's
basically where you got your start then
right well it was a while ago but after
since the terrace house I'm trying to
like you know I found out that's you
know it is my passion so I'm trying to
get back into it right and it's it's
definitely fun you know doesn't have to
a professional film movie kind of style
but it could be like you know a really
casual video and stuff I just um I I
want to like entertain people and you
know if there make them happy basically
so yeah how did you feel after being
rejected by Haruka Haruka is how you say
it then watching the fireworks by
yourself that sounds like a typical SADS
it's up to you and catfish moment I mean
I I don't know what you can say but that
part is clearly already out I read the
question and it's motive because I asked
I was like who is Haruka I didn't watch
dude I already know now so I mean like
what happened yeah
what happened you can talk about the
stuff that's already been out right sure
just tell us the scenario we want to
know about you you know learn about your
Torian situation but what is this well
this is all you know has happened okay I
went to the house and there's this girl
like alone and she looked like have
pretty heavy heavily weighed depress and
I asked her what happened and she liked
one of the guy who also lives in a house
but one of her roommates told him okay
that she likes you without even asking
her yeah exactly
stuff and he rejected her AHA man Wow
then I'm getting confused but yeah okay
no keep going I'm following
so she was she looked pretty depressed
and I just wanted her to feel better so
I'll be back in Japan next time on July
if you have time do you want to hang out
I go out with me kind of stuff and she
said yes and well I haven't like really
watched those episodes at that time and
came back from straight from Airport and
went on a dinner and you know start
talking stuff and I was like oh this
person is like really nice and kind and
after a few days or something later she
wanted to learn oh cool la so I saw her
oh cool all eh mm-hm
and I told her that I'm interested in
you like for like a third liked and you
want to like go as a date but she kind
of refused she told me that she only
sees me as a friend I'm sorry she said
that and I was like okay and at that
point I wasn't sure so earlier on we
were talking about the nice guy stuff
mm-hmm
lovely would the video - nice guy back
then and uh anyways I was you know for
that time I was kind of like starting to
hate myself for being a nice guy I'm a
typical nice guy oh you're so nice like
you know and
putting on like you know on a friend
zone all the time so I you know ended up
like talking about this to avian in
Tokyo but she told me that you know like
it's everyone likes your personality
whoever at liking appreciates your
personally really does appreciate and
you know there's not much people out
there is a place don't change that's way
she's she told me and told me and I was
wondering cuz I asked her to you know go
watch it fireworks together and she says
she was interested so but she wasn't
sure and well for me I wanted to go just
to clarify stuff up like I was I really
like moved on actually that time and you
know as a friend as a friend I wanted to
go but a day before you know the
fireworks she call me around like 11
p.m. or something and she declined it
like she's she told me that she can't
make it
she doesn't really feel like it feels
like it's a date so awkward
so I'm sorry in she hung that so Jen
Dallas and I ended up going there by
myself again like three years ago and
why did you go why did I go I love
fireworks oh it was huge it was like it
was in a place call me not to meet I was
like yeah yeah it's like it was so
beautiful and uh you know I think I
don't want is it avin as I say it avian
he and I think she's gave you good
advice don't change I think your
personality is very unique and I think
it's very it's almost I mean I don't
want to say too nice you are very nice
but I think it's a good thing and I
think like she said just just hold on to
that and wait until that right person
comes along that's gonna accept you as
because I don't think you need to be a
bad guy the point of nice guys the song
wasn't about not being a nice guy finish
last right but in the end you realize Oh
being a douchebag doesn't always work it
just works for certain people spend
years like me like the camel toe video
again person that one used the
instrumental Soulja Boy yeah yeah we
can't do that okay cool well I react
that that mark right now they weren't
that mark alright well thank you again
for being here was never you thanks for
having me such an honor it was a
personal interest of mine actually we've
got a lot of dirt a lot of stuff that we
probably can't see on camera but we'll
hear more dirt and release it after
thank you again you do you want to plug
your handles or anything what is it um
well we're gonna owe a tin Chi calm okay
getting Chi calm man I'm also gonna
start my merch store it's eating chi dot
store and I'm wearing this one right now
awesome cool that's that's that's it
cool awesome well you can find almost at
off the pillow on Twitter ad off the
pill podcast on Instagram with that
being said basically how we end this is
we just breathe into the mic so in three
two one
did I miss anything