hey guys so recently I've been getting a
lot of people tweeting me and emailing
me about this new thing called milky
apparently a lot of people don't know
about it yet but there's still a handful
of people online that are trying to make
milking happen if you've never heard of
milking before good as literally as dumb
as it sounds all that is is people going
to random places and pouring milk all
over their heads oh my god milk me what
is so funny about pouring milk on your
head it is not funny it's not okay it's
a little funny look guys the joke has
already been done it's not gonna be
funny once everybody starts doing it
just like planky this is just stupid
wasteful and plain offensive to cows and
vegans and I know making this video
about milk you might give it more
exposure but the last time I let a
stupid idea go on videoed planking
became famous people died there are so
many other trends that you could be
doing that are cooler smarter and less
wasteful than milky I mean I can come up
with a bunch just off the top of my head
like walling landing rockin all the
backing chairing the visible cheering
super invisible cherry standing or even
like fruit juice into a cup divine back
news with no skirt and pour over your
head while super invisible sharing I
could work too it's barely even funny
now and it's definitely not going to be
funny once everybody starts doing so I'm
begging you please don't let milking
start don't try to be a trendsetter or a
hipster at least not with this idea
don't do it just because no one else is
really doing it here don't help the
world become even stupider than it
already is okay okay hey Greg got milk
on my face Oh