hey guys so I recently realized that
I've been using the internet a lot more
than I used to I mean I use the internet
all whether it's YouTube Twitter
Facebook nothing better to do messing
time on the toilet I'm in an elevator
with someone else trying to avoid
awkward conversation as of course they
didn't mind when I'm in bed and you know
well I have a guy so of course I'm gonna
watch some Naruto I mean I'm on the
internet all the time and I discover
that there's so many annoying people
online well I mean there's a lot of
annoying people in this world but I mean
the Internet finally allows us to seal
I'll admit I have a lot of annoying
internet tricks as well for example I
can sometimes be one of those annoying
people that uses acronyms way too much
like lol lmao LMFAO everyday it may not
seem weird when I'm texting or typing
when you really think about it it would
sound really stupid in real life
hello kay man what are you doing it
mm-hm nothing just wanted to get some
food okay lol yeah
you want to come Kay lol so long where
do you want it off okay lol are you
really laughing a lot right now what G
lmao yes lol alright whatever I'm just
gonna pick you up in a little bit okay
ttyl : M parenthesis : d carrot
underscore carrot less than three STFU
okay there actually should be an
afternoon for the most annoying people
on the internet like my pony but at
least then we'll have something to write
to these people when they're being
annoying online and here's some of the
other annoying people I discovered on
the Internet take a look
the attention [ __ ] everyone has seen a
guy or girl like this these are the kind
of people without a pulse whatever it
takes to get people to give them
attention also known as people who fish
for compliments people keep saying out
of like Selena Gomez but whatever the
hater also known as the troll the heater
is the most common annoying person
online these people are so upset and
bored with their lives that they try to
make other people feel the same way
about their they always find a way to
take something positive and make it
negative something I finally met my
going lost ten pounds huh then why do
you look exactly the same
dentistry school was a pain but I
finally graduated dentistry school is
not even hard you can idiot get a real
job just got done with the Japan tsunami
relief fundraiser about to head over to
the Children's Hospital after the save
the planet and puppies convention well
so you only care about Japan you jerk
the over you sings person pretty much
anyone who says yo all right way cool
story bro had burnt oats that's what she
says shave my head right back from
legend wait for I god I cannot marry oh
my gosh I cannot I can bro I'm just dead
and of course last but not least here
right dear right do Ryan can you do
Gangnam style
the overly deep person if you don't know
something like this personally you've
probably seen at least one of these
pictures that they make these people
would take a picture of some beautiful
scenery and come up with a quote for it
that's just absolutely brilliant and
beautiful
[Music]
if you always say no you'll never say
yes the hashtag usually fought on
Instagram the hashtag you will take a
picture of something and just put away
too many hashtags on it's like they
treated like some kind of game to come
up with as many hashtags as you can
relating to the picture spring-break
trash sunny one time one times with
friends one times with friends in the
sand filter
look I understand if you made the meal
and you're proud but even if you ordered
something that looks absolutely amazing
you don't have to post a picture of
every single meal you're gonna eat hot
pockets make me happy the unrelated
captions girl these are the kind of
girls that would take pictures of stuff
but the caption that they write to
describe the picture has nothing to do
with it called looks like this patience
is a virtue sometimes your heart has to
let go just ate a hot pocket I don't
know if girls actually fall for this but
we've all seen those guys that try way
too hard to impress these guys will post
the corniest things to get girls to
think that they're the perfect guy Hey
ladies
do me a favor don't show me your boots
using your mind ix up information person
that makes post about the current
situation but doesn't want to talk about
it when you ask that person if you're
gonna pull something specifically meant
for one person can understand then send
them a freaking message where she's when
we're caring enough to ask you about it
tell us what you're talking about
the wannabe rapper those people that try
to act all hard and cool by posting
pictures of their money and and guns and
tattoos out on other gangsters 3 much
wannabe rappers the grammar nazi' I mean
the grammar nazi' has got to be one of
the most annoying people and yeah
actually grammar is spelled with an A
everyone on MySpace and last but not
least whether it's on Twitter Facebook
or even YouTube there's always that one
irritating guy who's always complaining
about others where's the cutaway oh stop
I'm coming I'm star
ABI now please stop