hey guys so today I'm gonna be talking
about the most annoying types of friends
and I know that sounds really bad
because you aren't calling your friends
annoying let's be real for a second
every single friend of yours probably
does at least one thing that annoys you
but you just look past it because well
if they're your friend either that or
you haven't been friends long enough to
see those traits come out or well you
don't have any friends you would know a
lot about that huh
what you act like you have friends what
are you talking about I have friends
yeah and that's why you're talking to me
right now you talked to me first that's
why I'm talking to you yeah but
technically I am you so you talked to
you first why are you here I'm annoying
right and I'm here to help you with this
video since you have no friends yeah but
you only have season two look if you're
gonna help can you at least wait till we
get to the examples I'm sorry I thought
we already started is this not the first
example is it's not the whiny annoying
vlogger friend anyway as I was saying
until I still rudely interrupted myself
I love my friends I'm sure you guys love
all of yours that's why we call them
friends but there's no such thing as a
friend that's never annoying there's
just friends that are significantly less
annoying than others and today we're
gonna be talking about those others here
are the most annoying types of friends
take a look
this is one of the most relatable common
ones there is the baler we all have that
one friend who says they're always down
to do stuff and then they make plans
with you and at the very last second
they tell you that they can't go or they
bail hence the baler hey Greg do you
want to go to the gym a little bit yeah
let me just get ready all right I'm good
you ready oh my bad dude I I can't go
anymore I can't make you have a doctor's
thing appointment conference the judger
just like it says in title this is the
friend that literally judges you for
everything that you do I see you and me
like seriously you're gonna wear that on
a date what's wrong with it I mean it's
cool I mean it looks a little
polka-dotty though you shouldn't have be
heating those those are so bad for you
wait are you liking her photo you just
met her that's so desperate the
passive-aggressive friend this is one of
the most annoying types of friends in my
opinion they never ever tell you exactly
what they want to say or what they want
to do it just hint at it so that you
don't believe the bad guy and they put
it on you all right so who's driving I
can't cuz my car's in the shop so I can
I can I I did drink a little so I mean
like if you don't mind riding a little
bit drunk it's fine oh I do have shoe
boxes in the back that's kind of taking
up some space so they'd probably be
really uncomfortable for three people
but it's cool because I can just throw
my shoes on in the trash I don't need
them I mean I don't need shoes I cannot
have this as lepers even though it's
really not safe for my workplace you
know as long as you just don't block my
rearview mirror because you know I can't
see at night and I can't drive
oh it's Dave I can't see during the day
very well okay fine I'll try to I can
drive no it's it's fine I mean I can
drive as long as you drive okay let's
just go sure if that's what you want to
do the liger again another common one I
mean these friends pretty much speak a
different language when it comes to time
just have to translate it for example
agar says that they're leaving soon it
means they haven't even started to get
rid of it when they say they're on my
way that means I'm on my way to get
ready but I'm still 30 minutes from
leaving when they say I'm here that
means they're five to ten minutes away
and then when the liger says I can't
seem to find you where are you that
means they literally just showed up at
that second the overly sensitive friend
this is the friend that takes every
little thing so personally that you get
to the point where you have to be
careful what you say around them and
what you do around them because you
don't want to offend them oh wow what
eft ITF TI thanks for the invite oh I
mean I was already with Derek and we
just
by this great food place oh so you guys
were already hanging out without me
that's cool now you don't mean my green
why because I'm Asian so I only Asian
food what amazing - Wow so you're saying
I'm unoriginal I didn't say that are you
calling me alive okay it's not a big
deal we'll just strive back to the same
Greek food place at the same exact meal
so you don't feel left out okay no I'm
good what what else do you want just
don't want to go why Artie the ditcher
when a hot girl or a guy comes along
this is the friend that just changes
after them they disappear and completely
seem to forget about you and your
friends the photographer I guess this
one isn't really annoying to a lot of
you guys but this is really annoying to
me this is the person that has to take a
picture of every single little thing
that you and your friends do to them
then needs to be broadcasted or it
didn't happen the cheap friend this is
the one friend in the group that never
pays for anything okay I'll be right
back I got a all right and your friend
over there said you guys are paying
together the overly competitive friend
this is the rent you never want to play
games with because they always get way
too competitive oh you just hit it just
hit the ball like are you serious no
let's go I mean like if you want to
handicap you can get help take it easy
man it's cool it's your turn go ahead
just go ahead you need the help so I
hope you need to play by the rules even
by your own your dumbass roses fine the
check out this video friend I need a
better title for though this is the one
friend that always wants to show you a
video that he or she thinks is so funny
or cool or awesome even though they're
not that funny or cool or awesome you
see that twist so good right right right
right
the overly honest friend and last but
not least you never want a lying friend
that's like one of the top things you
don't want in a friend but sometimes the
overly honest friend can actually be a
lot more annoying for example see that
twist so good right right right right
this video sucked oh because sometimes
it's better to lie to a friend than to
actually hurt them this video sucked oh
but I guess there's a good ending to it
and it doesn't end awkwardly and again I
didn't make this video to call friends
of mine nor do I think you should send
this to your annoying friends because
that'll probably result in you know you
having less friends it's actually the
opposite when I made this list I
actually realized that I do a lot of
these annoying trees I mean when you
watch this video I'm sure you guys
pinpoint in which one of your friends is
this and which one of your friends is
that but sometimes we forget to look at
ourselves you haven't already you should
rewatch this video and instead of
thinking about all your different
friends that these apply to think about
yourselves if there's something a friend
does that really annoys you chances are
you do something that really annoys that
friend as well because there's no such
thing as a perfect friend which also
means that you're not the perfect friend
either in order to preserve that
friendship we have to learn to just
accept these annoying traits and realize
that no friend yeah how would you know
you have no friends I have friends okay
just because I'm talking to an annoying
imaginary one it doesn't cause i'm not
imaginary what you still don't get it
get what you see how annoying I am too
yes you aren't incredibly annoying she's
why you named me annoying wrong I didn't
call you that you called yourself that
exactly I called myself that and I am
you
I'm gonna knowing all along you see that
twist so good right right right right
this video sucked oh but I guess there's
a good ending to it and says intend
awkwardly that's really bad for you
right
[Music]