in a world
there is traffic there stuff to get
everything to do with this video
[Music]
then was like team
you've got to wish come back
adventures I brought you all here beyond
theory I thought you were black I am
every time I look in the mirror all I
see is black and you all look back to
anyway why don't you all introduce
yourselves
hello my name is Tony starch also known
as iron man with the power to eliminate
any wrinkle I am do with the power to
give you or you option but you miss our
captain Canadian and I presume from
Canada hey hey guys I'm actually the
incredible anger-management Hulk
basically I'm the Hulk but I don't get
angry anymore since unless you know of
course I'm dead if I see like blood or
or like a dead body or or it maybe
someone texting while they're driving I
hate that so sorry who are you
I'm Hawkeye but you guys don't make the
spy kids you're not really super here
they're just like me except they don't
have a movie even spider-man had a movie
and he wasn't even invited but seriously
you guys should probably go so the
situation is there's a girl named Regina
and she's all tied up help I'm tied up
she's tired I'm tired and she's bleeding
I'm bleeding I'm not bleeding and you
must rescue her before she gets run over
so are we supposed to get there solvent
arranged
[Music]
moving at least paper our cab whoa whoa
good stuff the runners use a hammer
tires are bad the word captain in your
name doesn't mean you're the key or
maybe you should give me your iron and
I'll give you my hat so she stopped
argue he's not helping
listening tired or maybe we should see
what you guys did I'm the Hulk now you
don't look like a hope not even green or
big you just have a big mole on your
face oh yeah
if I wasn't a Hulk could I do this they
thought I wasn't in this movie
[Applause]
okay we don't start working together
we're not the real sustenance oh yeah oh
yeah
[Music]