really in a world completely deaf it's
called Earth no I mean yes but we live
in a world completely different world
from what you're used to
what do you mean the people they've
changed theirs the porters
ha
the camera horse and caption I look
terrible in this picture now people will
write nice things about me but what are
you doing taking off my shirt
why so I didn't take a picture of myself
so everything I'm not flexing but I
really is that's just gonna make you
look like a douche I know the wall
stammers it's fam and much much worse
it's been nearly four hours and my
blueberries aren't ready to harvest and
neither are my sheep what kind of world
is this oh it's not a world then what is
it you don't want to know oh it's a
world
called Facebook hey hey who are you I'm
Tom and this is my space actually no
this is my house
oh yeah the one to ask dad oh hey xanga