it's my birthday today or something No
oh I know what your breath Eddie it's
time it's time better watch this cave
just like this dress make me look fat
got your gift
what happened with Jasper was nothing
compared to what could have promised to
never put you there something like that
ever again
Oh how much could you possibly mean to
him if you just left near your money I
just can't help myself
you're so mouth-watering Mon
Oh dick run
penguin so now will you kiss me no
you're still some fan
now this how much could you possibly
mean to you wait how much could he
possibly mean to you Wayne how much
could you possibly meet a guy get much
better oh my goodness