here are you talking to
critics ring it's all 12 six times
better than saw tool why would anyone go
there and lavage Elise Lee knock them
out how like this three times better
than saw for you want a candy okay sure
almost as good as a seesaw I feel
and 2.4 times better than sulphide
I wanna play a game my and some 100k but
that's not the point I want to play a
game a game what kind of game is a game
about whether you live or die
because for the past ten years in a
board game oh my love monopoly just
putting it out there
what no Xbox no ps3 what are you talking
about Game Boy Advance we we were right
to pray single this is not that kind of
game oh okay as it was saying for the
past 10 years so let me just stop you
right there this is halo 3 you can count
me out okay I find halo 3 boring now I
think I hate you
and when I say halo 3 I mean all the
Halo games and any games similar so no
Counter Strike Call of Duty here's a war
maybe World of Warcraft you know I'm not
sure but listen this is serious I am NOT
talking about stupid first-person
shooter games nor am i talking about the
world of warcraft i am talking about a
game whether you live or die this is a
game about a life your life so like Sims
3 saw 12 coming soon let me go right now