[Music]
we don't understand I don't know
she looks like Chewbacca drugs she looks
like a Geisha that got ran over
I was following us around I don't know
but she's like everywhere she looks like
my ass and my ass is pretty white I
don't know but she followed us on the
way home today from school
you
[Applause]
and I'm pretty sure she was watching me
eat dinner
[Music]
I swear I saw her at the bathroom today
and look she's in all of our pictures
ready one two three
[Music]
[Applause]
the hell is she doing I don't know is
something wrong with her cuz it it is
that you
maybe she's [ __ ] or something and
she's handicapped it's someone Uncle
Fester
what do you want from us who are you
Who am I what is this and who is that
and who are you I'm Timmy Timmy mom
honey you forgot your life Loney salad
[Music]
you