I've defeated two Decepticons the
Megatron's the photons the icons the
Jamaican mimes but now they want revenge
they're coming they're everywhere
welcome you've got mail what the hook we
don't know exactly how many of them
there are but we do know one thing for
sure there's probably more than three
[Music]
hello get off you bought from me talk to
me you stupid umbrella Lewis Stephens
are you just gonna keep talking to that
lab all day shut up Megan what up doing
name is box anyway what are you
something a werewolf
whatever go back to Twilight Janu
doesn't matter who you are where you're
from why you're from there or who you
are all that matters is that we are all
going to die maybe
vroom vroom welcome
who said that I just want you to feel my
comfy cushions maybe take a look under
my hood check my oil
Transformers Revenge of the household
objects hey I'm a lamp dumbass