hey guys so if you follow me on Twitter
Facebook snapchat all my other social
medias you probably already know this
but the movie that I filmed a year ago
is finally coming out I'm gay also it's
coming out as in like you can watch it
online but anyway and just for those of
you that don't already know if you do
choose to watch it it's not gonna be
like one of my videos the one this movie
is not a comedy it's a thriller slash
horror and I only acted in it I didn't
write it or direct it or anything
because if I did I probably would ruin
this actually that thought alone kind of
got me thinking a lot of you guys are
always telling me that I should actually
direct real movies like mainstream
movies I'm telling you right now that is
a terrible idea
I would ruin your favorite movies and
not just because I will turn everything
into a joke but mainstream movies are
nothing like making these videos you
have crazy expensive budgets with huge
sets tons really good acting is just an
all-around huge gigantic professional
production crew what do I have I have
this
see we're even better just why I think
some of the most expensive movies ever
made and recreated them to show you guys
what they would look like on a low
budget and more importantly what they
would look like if I directed them
[Music]
yes Nana
emo Nala Simba Nala
Timon Pumbaa scars are not a cheetah
Anaru chamalla
multi tail don't man
damn I see Baba
[Music]
and maybe one never told you about your
father told me no you told me no your
father when it comes to 22 year old Luke
Skywalker Darth Vader you are the father
what and like I said that's what what
happened if you gave us these expensive
movies to make we'd make them better
obviously this wasn't serious at all one
day when I do make an actual legit movie
a legit feature film it's not gonna be
like these ridiculous skits that's gonna
be a lot worse but anyway I was writing
this video I got completely off-topic as
usual this video as opposed to be
telling you guys about the movie that I
did but once again I died I didn't do
that and actually the producers of the
movie wanted me to do a video promoting
you know this movie but I did this
instead you know why I'm not doing all
this promos I'm not some kind of sellout
okay that's just gonna use my YouTube
channel to promote things okay you know
I'm not gonna tell you guys that oh the
movie comes out today September the 16th
on Friday so you can get it online
anywhere you know I'm not I'm not gonna
say that that's some kind of promo [ __ ]
that's gonna subliminally try and tell
you to watch something that you guys
don't want to watch I would never do
that I stood up to those greedy
producers and I said look this is my
channel okay this is my channel and I
have morals I'm not just gonna go and
tell people that they can order this
movie right now tell me how I DICOM for
the simple price of $9.99 that's tell me
how I died icon for the simple price of
$9.99 No okay I am better than that I
told them I said is what I did I said
guys in all seriousness movie is out
that's all laughs that's all I needed to
say you have an hour and a half and ten
dollars to spare please go check it out
I actually think it's very good for
something again keep in mind it was a
low-budget I still think it turned out
really good if you want to know more
just click the link in the description
if not and you guys don't want to watch
it that is perfectly fine I will just
see you guys next week here on a brand
new episode of dogs marks on the next
episode of Dorothy
Bader has another son
[Applause]
[Music]