did you always look like this
why does it still look so dark oh you
know what there we go well now there's a
glare that's annoying see now you guys
can see why there's rings in my eyes all
the time yeah I recently got glasses
again I know it's been like seven years
since I got LASIK apparently LASIK
doesn't last forever so these things are
back I mean not that I used it a lot in
videos and a lot see me with glasses
that is because I used to be very
insecure about how I look now I don't
really care because I'm home and also
it's a different time you know the
glasses for whatever reason in the past
decade have become a lot more cool and I
think it's because you know enemies are
more popular because you know Anatomy is
they always have that really cocky
arrogant dude who's like looking at the
ground laughing to himself as he pushes
up his glasses so that he can look at
you and say something really smart or
cool
[Music]
and I still look pretty nerdy I don't
really like how I look low insecure
still hey guys hey guys hey guys see
obviously I haven't vlogged in a very
long time but you know I mean it's like
riding a bike you know once I start
doing it a little warming up it does all
comes flooding right back like I
remember Bieber fever
that was a thing less than three okay
yeah I kind of forgot how to start a
video naturally but I know this is not
it for real this time
hey guys so this is definitely the
longest break I've ever taken from not
posting videos on this channel in my
entire youtube career and I know I'm
always apologizing and making excuses to
you guys for why I'm not posting and
that does get annoying so this time for
I'm really not going I'm so sorry guys I
really just I've been going through a
lot of things over the past years one I
don't usually talk about relationship
stuff here on YouTube but just because I
made it public ironically last year I am
no longer dating anyone I'm not dating
mrs. Shay anymore I know some of you
have already figured it out because of
you know looking at our other social
medias but I never really said anything
here on YouTube and I felt like since I
did announce it publicly I should
probably let you guys know that as well
and don't worry it wasn't like a messy
breakup or anything like that it was a
very mutual I didn't I wasn't gonna make
a whole video about it I just thought I
should mention it to you guys because
it's been a while since I updated you on
anything and don't get me wrong that's
not the sole reason why I took this
break I mean it probably contributed to
it a little bit the real reason why I
had to take this break was because I
needed to reflect on my own life I mean
it is 2020 and the thing that I have
found was that I don't know how to break
this to you guys but I'm freakin old man
I mean I just realized that I am going
to be 30 freakin 30 and I know if this
doesn't make any sense but I never
thought I'd actually be 30 years old I
mean not at least until I was 50 that's
three decades oh two dogs could have
lived a full life and died in the same
amount of time that I've been around I'm
a two dog death hero and yet at the same
time how many times have I been caught a
good
I think about it kind of a lot I'm like
I mean well 29 Christmases in a row and
Counting nothing that's a big deal or
anything you stop stop taking my glasses
your glass is who the hell are you I'm
you but mature as a 30 year old that's
why I'm not insecure about wearing my
glasses and comparing myself to some
silly little anime cartoons oh okay I
guess I have a lot meaner in the future
I'm not trying to be mean
I just don't have a lot of time to get
you to where I'm at right now and why
exactly do you think I need your help
because I am a manifestation of
everything you thought you would be by
the time you're 30 oh really
yes married yep kids two of them YouTube
here and there but most of my time goes
into making actual movies and television
shows that is when I'm not enjoying my
beautiful toilet room toilet er what a
toilet aquarium it's a toilet surrounded
by a gigantic fish tank on all four
sides including the floor and the
ceiling so that it feels like you're in
a warm transparent box in the middle of
the ocean an ocean so big to the point
that it almost feels like you're in the
aquarium but for the fish I don't
remember wanting that by 30 but yes I
mean like how do you how do you even get
in there I think it doesn't matter
you're not gonna have any of those
things by the time you're 30 maybe not
ever at the rate that you're maturing
well I'm not gonna lie I think I was a
lot younger when I thought I would have
all of this by this age I literally
forgot about all those goals that's
exactly why I'm here to remind you of
everything that you ever wanted in life
so that maybe you can start making
changes and finally just grow up because
you know it's never too late to start
really you think I can make that big of
a change to my life this fast yes I do
you really think I can rent a movie or a
TV show in the next like three months
people have done it in less so I could
really have the toilet aquarium room
thing well that's kind of pushing it
timewise but I suppose if your movie
makes enough money I guess in terms of
marriage I mean we live in Vegas I could
get married today if I wanted to right
technically true but I think we still
want to make sure we find the right one
if I get married today I could start a
family like immediately I mean why wait
right yes I suppose you could you could
start thinking about having no not think
about it I just need to do it I mean I
don't want to be an old dad
has no energy to play with their kids so
I need to have both kids by the age of
30 I mean it is possible if you choose
to adopt kids oh I want my own blood
kids I want blood kids two of them I was
kind of hoping there would be two years
apart but I guess we could settle for
two months if I have the first one this
month had the next one in the next
couple months you know that's not
possible right I know it'll be difficult
but if I work really hard and I vote
Ryan think about what you're saying okay
you only have about what four months
left this kid has been going on so long
you might have even less than that
I mean like less than three I don't even
know why I bother
so anyway point I'm trying to make if it
isn't already clear I was not and I
guess I'm still not prepared to turn 30
and I guess I'm kind of having a midlife
crisis which means not only am i getting
old but I am already at my midlife at 29
years that means I'm only a little 58
and and that that is so much more time I
don't even know why I'm freaking out 29
years that's almost 30 years that's two
more dogs I can have back-to-back they
can live and die I'll still be around
for almost sorry all this time off as
you can see thinking about life and
death has made me a little well dork all
jokes aside I know age is just a number
it's not the most important thing in the
world the thing is I'm really starting
to notice differences in myself now that
I'm getting older and I didn't realize
it was happening until I took these few
months off to reflect now I know it's
already too late for me I've already
caught the old
but for you young whippersnappers out
there I'm gonna tell you guys about the
changes I've been noticing in myself so
that maybe maybe you guys can catch it
before it happens to you before you guys
catch the old I was gonna make a
coronavirus joke but I just found that
in bad taste is it our people so
sensitive these days I don't know man
I'm old now I don't I feel like I'm a I
just I feel like I have the right to
offend people because I'm just that age
now where like I just don't know better
because I'm old coronavirus too soon
okay yeah just cancel me just cancel me
already I want to turn off the camera
turn off the light again oh man dark
comedy early detection is everything and
one of the first things I started
noticing about myself is I've started
noticing and catching myself saying
things that I've heard all people say my
whole life the next level past
discovering that you're starting to say
things that old people say or the old
people sounds you start to make and
these are the real minuscule things you
might not have noticed throughout your
life I don't know when I started doing
this but I started doing them as well
[Music]
you know back in my day well okay you
know kids these days okay floored is a
tic-tac-toe large market what the flog
hurry up marking kids these days yeah I
don't know what flarg is I don't think
that's a thing the point I was trying to
make is that old people don't like to
curse so they replaced curse words with
other words I'm just I'm just gonna be
honest I just made that word up because
I didn't want to put anything close to a
swear word in here even put the beep
sound in because I don't want to get to
monetize seriously like YouTube doesn't
even want you to put those sensor beeps
anymore or it could flag it as like
age-restricted
I mean what's next you know I mean I
remember back in my day youtube did not
care about things like
know why I went so there now this next
one I've always been old in I guess it's
the kids lingo these days I was always
behind when he came to trends even like
five years ago I kinda knew memes I kind
of knew like what kids were saying these
days today I have no idea what the hell
kids are talking about when I say kids I
mean people that are still in their
early 20s because to me I can understand
them right that party last night was Mac
ya know cat dude yeah totally guys it
was so well lit at that party everywhere
lights on the ceilings and on the sides
there was like almost no shadows no caps
either right
just a couple hats like that I don't
know caps whatsoever yo was that growing
red though are you talking about
smashley no her name is not actually
smashley
right and you mean I usually doesn't
gonna nickname no it's it's good that
would be ridiculous if her real name was
smashley like it is in smash then what
does she like a Playstation came Smash
Bros ooh but she so bad and obese her
body mass index probably twice the
normal rate of like an average person at
that height right yeah oh no cat right
another old person thing I have been
getting new interests that are not
gaming or YouTube I've been more
interested in politics I have been
trying to read more books but probably
worst of all I have been kind of into
learning about the stock market I'm not
gonna lie I'm getting pretty good at it
[Music]
what are you trying to learn about
stocks yeah I just can't decide which
stock to buy what are you interested in
just the broth really the broth you know
I just can't decide between like chicken
or beef wish stock would you buy aren't
you a little bit old to be making these
kinds of corny Joe horn stock
and last but not least and probably the
most cliche way to spot someone who's
getting old we all know this one it's
about music everyone grows up with a
certain generation of music and for some
reason the the generation of music you
grow up with will always be the best no
matter what and the moment you feel that
music quote unquote these days aren't as
good as it used to be when you were
growing up chances are you've already
contracted deal and the thing is once
you're at this point you don't recover
from it it only gets worse and worse
newer music becomes more and more
unlistenable to you and not only do you
resort back to the music you grew up
with but you start having an
appreciation for the music from the
generation before you and the generation
before that and so on even before you
know it it happens you're just old and
the truly truly terrifying part about
all of this is that you stop caring that
you're old because really truly old
people they give zero flogs
[Music]
yeah no I must not be super old because
I I still care how bad I look in these
here you know these back you really just
don't want to grow up huh what are you
talking about it just did a whole video
showing you how old I'm getting look I'm
just gonna be straight up with you
because I care
this whole video is about you worrying
about getting old but when I look at you
all I see is a child thank you no it's
not a compliment okay look there's
nothing wrong with getting old everybody
ages alright the only thing that's sad
about you turning 30 isn't the fact that
you're acting older that you're changing
in any way it's the fact that you're not
you're exactly the same
there's been no growth from you in years
and I don't think you've even noticed
that no I have I mean I know I've been
five nine since high school I have grown
about 15 pounds since then though so
there's that see this is exactly what
I'm talking about you can't even go 30
seconds without making some kind of
stupid joke how do you expect to become
me if you're not willing to change look
no offense but I don't want to become me
I'm not trying to be you okay I might
not be the most mature person in the
world and I wear the same clothes that
I've been wearing for the past decade
and yeah I still think puns are one of
the funniest things ever created by God
is not a God creation got a disagree but
like you are everything I thought I
wanted to be by age 30 but now that
you're sitting right in front of me I
know now thank you
wait dumber than me man but what you're
what I thought 30 year old me was gonna
look like as a kid you're just an idea
from a kid version of me and I'm Way
smarter than kid me kidding me this is
ridiculous I don't even know what to say
roughly because you're dumb no it's
because I'm too intelligent to be
engaging with someone like you engage me
I'm just trying to marry you weirdo no
that's not what I meant just face it man
you're stupid you're the one who wants
app not just one but two biological kids
by the time you're 30 that's it for
months that's just not realistic well
with that attitude I guess look I know
exactly what
do all right I know that you're not that
dumb and I know you're not even in
denial you're just trolling because
that's the only way that you know how to
cope with something as important to your
life as this and it's not going your way
am i right
that's stupid another dumb thing to come
out of your mouth like cut the act
already man you're gonna be 30 seriously
you know damn well that it takes nine
months to have a baby and and that's
assuming you already have somebody who's
willing to have a baby with you which
you don't so just so you can finally
admit to yourself and hear it out loud
I'm telling you you're not gonna have
the life you thought you were gonna have
by age 30 you're not gonna be married
you're not gonna be done with YouTube
you're not gonna do anything really
significant for this world and most
importantly you're not gonna be done
making those silly awful puns basically
dad jokes despite the fact that you're
not gonna be a dad by the time you're 30
maybe not ever
it's time to face reality right it's
time to grow up
[Music]
right
I've wasted so much time I I know I
won't be married I know I probably won't
be done with you two but I won't do
anything significant for the world
really doing this it doesn't mean you
can't start trying now no I've already
accepted that the only thing I can't
accept because I know that if I change
right now I could have it
I will have my two kids and by the age
of thirty this is literally the only
thing you can't do nine months to have a
baby you say huh yes you already know
that well then I guess I'll just have to
have twins
that makes Margit dance