she's late again she lives so close what
could possibly take away you asking me
all these questions what do I look like
a teacher to you and I wasn't really
asking how am I supposed to know where
she is what do I look like a GPS no it
was a rhetorical question I was a red
Oracle question speak English what do I
look like some kind of Mathemagician I
wasn't asking you directly per se and
now you calling me a no per se
well I look like a to yo do I look
like some kind of cat what sky my
Himalayan British Shorthair Russian blue
what you just carry around labeled
pictures of cats with you all the time
okay oh yeah I'm Russian blue I guess I
don't russian blink think so Russian
blue you think I look like a Russian
blue
I'm still here too
yeah I could see that
sorry I'm late
what took you so long my same odd
morning routine you know her morning
routine it's almost night well I didn't
say it was a fast routine there's a lot
of stuff for us girls to do in the
morning don't you watch any of those
makeup girls to do all those my morning
routine videos and they basically just
show everybody what they do in the
morning um no why would anybody even
want to watch that cuz it's good hmm
anyway I think that's what we should do
today - what our morning routine so that
people can appreciate how much work it
is for us girls to look the way we do
all right if we're really gonna do this
who wants to go first or dizzle Regina
you want me to go you go first
I don't even worth of you what about me
you're not starting with You Hana T I
don't even know if we're gonna even do
yours this time what why not cuz I know
you're gonna troll us so you remember
the Halloween story a while back when it
was your turn all you said was I'm sorry
I was your help I stay home cool good
nice see what I mean because that's what
I did they won't cook right but that's
not a storm you know what Regina can you
just please go oh sure we just go my
morning routine goes a little something
like this so the first thing I do in the
morning is wake up I usually turn wake
up early like around 12:00 or 1:00 p.m.
but lately I've been waking up even
earlier like 11 a.m. from the cold
because my stupid boyfriend steals all
the blankets from me so I yell at him
and he just ignores me the whole time
and continues to sleep which makes me
really sad so I cry for about five to
ten minutes before I realized that wait
I don't have a boyfriend so I get over
it and that's when I hit to the bathroom
where the real fun begins I do all the
boring stuff first like turn on the
shower brush my teeth brush my hairs my
little push down stairs and by that time
the showers steamy enough for me to
write my name in it so that I can take a
picture for in stores and snappies then
comes the fun part my mega I always
start with my foundation which if you
don't know is pretty much just power so
any kind of powder works but personally
I use flour because I love flowers then
look and smell
beautiful and once I finished that I'd
do my lips I know most girls like using
these coloring sticks but I prefer to
lip tint which is a technique that's
really popular in other countries
outside of Nevada or basically all you
do is put some fruit punch or grape
juice whatever color you want in a bowl
and just dip your lips for two maybe
three or four hours and you're done and
ready to do your eyes now some people
call it eyeliner some say eyeshadow but
really it doesn't matter because they're
all the same thing and basically it's
just the coloring of your eyeball
section again I know most girls like to
cover their eyes with coloring sticks
but I'm really not like that typical
basic batch so I like to use the fancier
foreign brands like Crayola which stays
on pretty nicely or like sharp piece
which is actually waterproof and won't
come off when you swim cry or even scrub
for an hour and if you can't afford
those I found that you know those little
black balls that everybody gets every
Christmas works really well I believe
that brand is called shark wall or
something but that works too
and after that I'm pretty much done and
ready to get the day started
so I leave the bathroom and that's when
I always see my blankets on my bed move
so I go over there thinking wait maybe I
do have a boyfriend
but when I check and remove the covers
it's not my boyfriend at all it's me
under there I see myself sleeping and
that's when I realized I was asked you
projecting the whole time so then I just
wake myself up by pulling off the cover
so that I get really cold wake up and do
it all over again
ah so would you guys say that was long
ah thank you uh anyway um who's next our
diesel what let's hear your morning
routine hopefully it won't be as long as
we're jeana's though right why not you
trying to rush my routine what you
rushing me dawg you rush I gotta rush
like some kind of Russian to you huh
yeah like a Russian blue I don't get it
anyway like I was saying yeah go ahead
and just take your time no rush
good now where was I where was I oh I
don't think you even started I wasn't
asking you that was a red Oracle
question stupid anyway my morning starts
a little something like this I wake up
grab my phone first thing I do jump on
that clash of clans harvest gold elixir
build troops raid other building stuff
MECs candy crush it I guess stripes
again packets I get chocolates with the
sprinkles on top boom on to Bray dungeon
pad to the 12 hour mark and back to the
basics that jump right back on that
and repeat before I know it it's nice
then I just do it all over again
so that's your full routine the non rush
version mm-hmm well then I guess we're
done with this right what what I mean
all that's left is me and I don't have a
good made-up routine like you guys all I
have is a real one so what about me I
already told you we're not gonna let you
troll us again I'm not sure I you may
head just let him do it man yeah fine go
ahead then but I swear if you do that
cook rice joke one more time I'm sad
money routine not joke not joke at all
my routine goes a little something like
please every morning I wake up afraid
afraid for my life gunfire screams for I
know what I hear banging on door someone
trying to break in that's when I grab
the guns I keep under my pillow and
count down four three two one
I fire the moment that door opens before
I can even get a good look at who it is
as I'm about to leave her realized I
know this man he's my father
tears start coming down my face like a
waterfall being chased by the TLC and I
just wrote get in my car and head
straight to my psychologist in ten years
because I don't know who else to talk to
I tell him the whole story and he tells
me on today you shouldn't be sad cuz
your daddy didn't die I say what and
that's when he tells me on a tape I am
your dad and I don't know what to do I I
don't know if I should feel happy or
betrayed and I just closed my eyes and
black out when I hope and then I found
my psychologist my father dead I shot
him I hear sirens coming that's when I
get back in my car and start driving
again tears are coming down my face like
a kpop star in that movie ninja
assassins like rain and it blurs my
vision right as an old lady crossing the
street a slamming mob breaks I lose
control of the car and hit her - no hope
lady I get out run over to her to see
that she's barely alive then down next
to her not able to convey how sorry I am
when she stops me she tells me to come
closer and she whispers I forgive you
son and that's when I realized this
innocent old lady I killed wasn't not
dead to here started coming down my face
like that's enough hey I'm not done yeah
let him finish I want to hear the end so
what did your tears come down your face
like oh just like Bruce Lee favorite
drink oh let me guess like wah ha no
like Pepsi he liked Pepsi I heard that
too
is that really your morning routine the
routine you do every morn I so you're
saying that you pretty much murder three
different people that claim that they're
your father every single morning when
you get up
oh you mean
like with the song come on yes what did
you think a morning routine was I
thought you mean morning like when you
said because people die Oh morning with
Leki's are you using the sting no that's
not an easy mistake why would you even
think that that's what we're talking
about don't be mean to him dude his
father just died all three of us hi okay
fine I get it there's some kind of
language barrier of some sort and I
don't know why in your head for some
reason you have a country accent I think
his Canadian accent no it's not not even
close but that's fine because now you
know which morning I'm talking about
right the one where the Sun rises I okay
then can you please just tell us a real
answer are you gonna tell us sorry
yeah yeah I can't tell us that what your
morning routine what do you do in the
morning I wake up cook nice thank you
guys again so much for watching if you
want to see bloopers and behind the
scenes click on the left if you want to
see the previous video click the one on
the right and if you want to see last
skitzo video click the one in the bottom
that's a really good idea I think you
should click the one on the bottom
that's the best one ah autumn you didn't
just do what are you doing here