hey guys as many of you know I have a
dog named Marley and you may have seen
him in a few videos here and there but
recently I just got another puppy he's a
Corgi and I haven't thought of a name
for him yet so I've just been calling
him Marley the Corgi and he has such a
cute and lovable puppy but for some
reason ever since we got in my other dog
Marley has been acting up and misbehaved
for example I came home and I saw Marley
tearing up all of our trash in my living
room and he knows better he knows not to
do that or like now Marley is the only
one that sleeps in my bedroom because
he's potty-trained but ever since we got
the new dog I'll wake up and find a poop
on my floor and I don't even know how he
did it but he somehow managed to get
onto a table that's two feet taller than
him and knocked over a vase and cracked
it on our floor bad boy Marley so I
don't know he's just been acting like
crazy like crazy lately and and I'm even
like now look you just scratch he's
scratching on the door and I'm trying to
film I'm trying to film Harley I think
he's probably just jealous or the other
dog but I don't understand why because I
show him just as much attention
sometimes I just wonder like what is
going through his head no no no no I'm
not a kid I didn't even do anything this
time ah hey hey hey you I know you're
just a puppy and and maybe we got off on
the wrong paw but do you think you could
help me out of here got your dirty
little snout you filthy mutt um you
might have been the only dog before but
this is my house now well actually we're
both kind of just sharing why do you
think you're even locked up like you're
at the pound right now what do you mean
you actually believe that there would be
a treat lying in the middle of trash in
the living room floor for no reason at
all or don't you find it a little
strange that you've never sleep poop
before yet every morning you wake up and
there's magically another piece of poo
there and are you that stupid to believe
that a vase would magically fall off a
table when to deadly right next to you
you you were trying to frame me
no wali boy I was trying to kill you
you're evil yes Molly pop evil come on
Marley the Corgi let's go film a video
have to warn Ryan how do I get up well
maybe if I start digging I can get out
of here but no that's right I could just
push it over so as always saying I I
just don't I don't know what to do with
that dog like I'm really hoping that
it's just a phase that he's going
through right now I can't just like
return a dog because my other dog
doesn't like here it's like two brothers
and the older one is just at the younger
one as it's really damn it boy but now
Marley oh my god
Marley this whole time you were just you
were just you were trying to kill me and
Marty the Corgi bad boy what the hey but
in all seriousness I did get a new dog
as you can see any is still nameless if
you have any suggestions leave them in
the comments below and they will be much
appreciated but yeah that's about it so
make sure you subscribe to our channel
we post new videos every not as much as
we would like to think about more you
can buy my unicorn you buy my spider-man
I mean Vincent van Gogh painting yeah I
love Janice oh hey we already did that