hey guys first of all I wanted to thank
and congratulate all of my subscribers
we made it to the number one most
subscribed spot on YouTube and if you're
wondering why I'm congratulating you
guys it's because it's not just my
achievement it's yours as well because
without you guys I'd have no subscribers
you know what you guys make you know I
don't know where I'm going with this but
you know what I mean
anyway you're probably wondering why is
the title cloud ninja male preview
that's because I'm gonna be giving you a
preview of a short film that we've been
making first of all if you like how to
be ninja and the ninja glare you are
gonna love this film it's full of action
comedy and some scenes even have action
and comedy in one that's right now what
Shawn getting blown up
isn't that funny and action II but
there's also drama closer closer you
know I would but he's my like for an
aspirin and not to mention evil villains
Danny G ed your phone
yo yo yo it's a girl with Gina leave a
message after the cow got it but the
best thing about this film is that it is
100% created by us no company's nothing
and it stars your favorite sean
fujiyoshi Timmy knows I'm going to give
you the hardest pitch Taryn ah go
and the mute guy Bryson Murata why does
everybody be gone
so because you guys are all my love
subscribers I'm going to be putting on
an actual trailer and a link to show you
guys how you can watch it for free on my
next video so make sure you subscribe ah
just kidding but seriously and now that
that's done peace out losers that was
supposed to you know with the smoking