hey guys so I was hanging out with a
friend today I'm not gonna mention names
and he had a friend with him who I've
never met before and this person
inspired me to make this video yesterday
I'm gonna be talking about something I
really don't like arrogant people beep
beep beep beep move arrogant people
people who think they're far more
important than they really are some
similar or related words are conceited
ignorant douchey cocky [ __ ] jersey
shore' ish and not to mention the word
arrogant came from the word era which
originated from Robin who we all know
came from the hood arrogance is still
used all around the world today this is
not a word of the day I don't know why I
did that intro because I can anyway you
guys know the kind of people I'm talking
about right
do you know who I am I was on Disney
Channel that one time on that one show
that aired that one time on TV so I'm
pretty much a big deal
I'm the most irritating thing about them
is that they could be watching this
video right now and not know that we're
talking about it because they think
everybody loves me but in a way I guess
I do understand why people would act
like that because apparently now it's
cool to be an arrogant douche for
example celebrities like like Chris
Brown encourage arrogance in their music
could you imagine what his songs would
be like if they were modest yes yes that
look like a toupee I get what you get in
10 years in 11 years or imagine the Old
Spice guy
hello ladies look at your man now look
at me now look at your man now look at
me he's a little better
my point is unless you're Chris Brown or
somebody that can back it up there's no
reason you should act that way so this
is a wake up call to all you arrogant
people out there II don't like you
we don't care about how much money you
make unless you're giving it to us don't
care about how fast you can run a mile
unless you're getting a Taco Bell we
don't care about how big your house is
we don't care how much weight you can
bend we kind of care if you have a
Lamborghini though that's pretty cool
and we don't care who you know what you
do when you do it and why we just don't
care hey pop shot on 21 exit out
and that's when I realized making videos
putting them online expecting people to
watch and share my opinion well that's
just that's just modest as hell I'm
really good at saying I know modest