hey guys so I know for a lot of you the
title is probably a little confusing
because it's you know off the pill and
babies well it has nothing to do with
actually being off like a pregnancy pill
this is a really unfortunate coincidence
off the pill has a series of brands I
used to do like a long time ago some of
you guys might remember but I know that
there's a lot of you who are a little
newer and probably don't know what this
is because I haven't done this in like I
don't know over five years so basically
for those that don't know the off the
pill name came from the idea that those
were the days that I didn't take my ADHD
medication and basically I would just
rant about any random thing that came to
my mind although sometimes they're a
little too random where I would like go
a little too off-topic or I would just
cut away to these random skits or jokes
and usually it was just a really bad pun
so bad to the point where I had to
explain it that's what he said see what
I did there that's right it's gonna be
even better see what I did there
that was smashing but yeah that's why I
like this series because I could just be
me speaking my mind not sure other
people liked it as much as I did but
anyway the reason why I stopped doing
this series in these types of videos and
stuck more with you know scripted skits
and stuff was because well I I was a
huge coward because you know move
because like cows' words are like Moo
select coward sorry because sometimes
when I would do these videos and I was
just like freestyling I would say some
things that we're not too well thought
out I mean they were my honest opinions
but sometimes well a lot of times
they're very unpopular ones and honestly
I just got scared of making them as you
know people got more and more
politically correct I just don't want to
offend anyone well not anymore bring
them back because I'm smarter now I'm
better now I've evolved okay I'm no
longer some little timid Caterpie hiding
in his little Metapod I'm Butterfree now
sorry guys I also used to make a lot of
Pokemon references back then when it was
a little more relevant but honestly I
don't think people really appreciated
them anyway as I was saying before I
went completely off-topic as usual I'm
no longer afraid to do this series
anymore because I think I really have
gotten smarter you know I'm not gonna
say things that are just gonna offend
people I know how to give an opinion now
being a little bit more PC and most of
all I just know how to not
the majority of the masses by giving a
controversial opinion on something that
I really I hate babies okay there you
got it out of me okay obviously that's
an exaggeration I don't hate babies that
much I know I know it's like what Ryan's
baby hater okay you eat a baby you can't
believe your baby ain't looking you eat
a baby there so either see where all of
our hands up like this when we talk well
just scare me out real quick and this
isn't quite what I wanted to talk about
in this video but I just have to say
this babies are stereotypically one of
the most innocent things in the world
like if you were to make a list of the
most innocent things in the world it'd
probably be like babies and then like
puppies and trees puppies first babies
trees trees and because they're so
innocent it's really hard to be critical
of them but if you really break it down
and you really think about it babies
they they freaking suck figuratively and
literally like for one I'm not that very
old age right now where a bunch of my
friends and my classmates and peers
around my age are starting to have kids
and they'll go on their social media and
they'll post like these pictures of
their newborn babies like I'm talking
like right after their birth and right
like a caption like oh my gosh she's so
beautiful
oh he's changed my life for the better
you such a cute baby uh I sound like an
ass right now but almost at the point
hear me help everybody in the comments
are like Oh Congrats she's so beautiful
oMG she's so beautiful grats he's
adorable Oh cute so cute so coyote and
yes I'm not saying the babies aren't
cute I think a lot of babies not all but
I think a lot of babies are cute but you
guys I can't be the only one that thinks
that newborn babies are a little gross
looking they're all red and wrinkly
beady eyes gunk all over them yep and
now you can see why I stopped making
this series I mean this wasn't even the
point I want to talk about in this video
let's just get to that all right the
whole reason why I even started thinking
about babies is because last week I came
across this video about this new
movement I don't know if you guys heard
about it it's called babies babies
babies babies babies I don't know how
they pronounce it sounds more like a
disease to me than a movement whoo he's
got the babies and basically if you
haven't heard about this movement early
parents are starting to raise their kids
as these babies which basically means
that they're raising their kids with no
gender so they're not a boy or a girl
they just form a thick be baby I don't
know why they had to call it that it's
not like babies is a gendered word you
can still call them babies anyway so
basically these parents
raising these babies or babies I can as
a gender-neutral so basically they're
not telling them they're a boy or a girl
as they're growing up because they want
the baby to decide on its own which
gender it wants to be 100% sir is this a
real thing you can look it up and you
guys know I don't normally speak out
about you know more serious
controversial topics but that's the
thing when I first saw this video I
didn't think it was serious I literally
thought it was a joke and I'm sorry I
know this will offend a lot of people
especially the people who are already a
part of this this movement but I think
it's ridiculous I'm all for the
transgender community and the gay
community and the lesbian LGBTQ bar s
tuv god I don't know there's too many
letters now I'm all for people doing
whatever the hell they want to do as
long as it's not hurting other people to
be honest I think this one has gone a
step too far I think it is harming
people it's harming the baby these
babies are gonna be so confused maybe
not when they're worth their parents but
when they start to meet other babies and
those babies are like what do you mean
you're not a he or a she min these
parents are almost guaranteeing that
this kid is gonna get bullied when he
grows up she grows up they grow up
that's why they called it babies and the
thing is I like to think I'm a very
open-minded person I'm always open to
hearing new ideas this is like come on
you copy a little realistic here a baby
should not be able to make a decision as
important as that in fact a baby should
not be able to make any decisions at all
on other than which toy to play with and
even then we read aside which toys the
baby can choose from these babies are
freaking idiot there's a reason why we
don't treat them like a dog because if
we did I'm pretty sure that would be
considered abuse shut up
we're wait did he just he's been down
there for a while
yeah like four minutes now it's crazy
man Wow and I know you can argue that
these babies aren't actually making
decisions - they're a little bit older
like when they can talk whether that's
like age two or three I don't know when
babies start talking but I'm pretty sure
at that age they can still answer the
question are you a boy or a girl yes or
no or they can say boy or girl by that
and that's still way too young to be
deciding anything I mean even if there
were four years old or five I mean have
you ever talked to a five year old
before they're still really really dumb
hey good to see you again you do I see
you brought a little Timmy here with you
I did say hi like he's so shy at times
that once you get him going
what'd you do today Timmy well my mom
took me to the park and we went on the
swings yeah do we then I swing on the
swings and I swing did Oh
the swings it sounds like so much fun
and then I then I swing did 2 4 4 2
whole times Wow
two whole times this is awesome and then
after there were there was a green ball
and and the ball came by me and I could
kick the ball I kicked it and then it
was rolling on it and on the grass which
was green like the ball was green with
the grass and green ball was green and
it was green and it was green and then
he was greens to the ball green you
idiot okay obviously I'm going a little
over the top but you guys get the point
any rational person knows that little
kids let alone babies aren't developed
enough to make these kind of
life-changing decision
I mean if this movement is really about
the kids and about these babies and
giving them the power to choose why stop
at gender what's next why not let kids
choose their own name why did you get to
choose it up normal they want they just
ask the kid when they first start
talking what's your name why can't the
kid be named mama or Dada or Google or
gaga I guess it could be gaga
maybe that's why eighty gaga is a baby
now we know yes that does make you more
success and that's just the beginning
why do you get to dress your kid up when
you go out in public what if he wants to
run around naked you don't know or why
do you get to choose with the baby eat
shouldn't you just take it to the market
and let it point at what it wants why do
you put diapers on them why do you
potty-trained there why do you get to
decide where the baby can and can't go
approve that that is butter all
oppression because big bundles and
babies should be able to express their
buttholes wherever they go under where
am I going with this this slide mean my
meds
by the way you better not be picking up
carrying or touching your baby in any
way before it can speak because if it
can't speak it can't consent if it can
consent that's assault and also the baby
did not consent to be born so you
basically kicked it out of its home you
did that okay this is ridiculous that is
my point you don't need a baby's consent
no give babies those choices because we
know what's best for them because babies
and little kids are just useless loud
disease-carrying moochers that depend on
adults to take care of them and make
decisions for them because you're just
too stupid and then just physically
pathetic to be able to survive on their
own
Wow what is wrong with me I really do
hate kids you guys get the point you can
probably see why I enjoy this series and
why a lot of people get a little mad so
I'm sorry to other people within I
probably offended
obviously I'm half joking when I say
that I hate kids I don't actually hate
kids my points remain the same and don't
get me wrong I do love kids in fact I
want to have a kid one day I just don't
want to have a baby who knows you know
maybe all it takes is for me to just
mature a little and for me to experience
it myself
maybe there's something I'm missing
because I'm not there to experience it
myself maybe if I had a baby of my own
and I'd be so in love with it and
blinded by the potential of what could
be that I'd love every aspect of it even
the negative even as a newborn maybe if
it's my own kid I won't see the newborn
house like this dirty red gross looking
squishy thing and I'll see the true
beauty the potential of what could be
that the actual miracle of life yeah no
that's that's still gross that is come
on that is this girl's right I think
definitely as Davies