hey guys sorry I haven't been putting
out videos quite as frequently as I
would like to but I have a good reason I
didn't want to just kidding I've been
sick in fact I've been sick for a while
now
with Bieber fever no but really I was
sick justin bieber justin bieber justin
bieber Leave It to Beaver that's all I
hear that's all I see it's all I smell
he's everywhere
I totally have Bieber fever don't make
me beaver but ask you all right who just
be bird when you think Justin Bieber
it's either oh my god I love him or
somebody needs to tell this girl to shut
up this needs to stop stop worshipping
him like he's some kind of God cuz he's
not and stop hating on him like he's
Chris Brown he did nothing wrong
he's not even close he's not even
Kristin let alone Chris white maybe
Chris blue what was he talking about
oh stop worshipping him stop hating him
because beneath those boyish good looks
is an ugly kid just like you and me
sure he may promote his album his world
2.0 every single day and maybe he does
use a few made-up words with his own
name in it like Bieber blasts Bieber
fever or belieber only Pokemon see their
name over and over paper blast ha I mean
seriously what the he go who does that I
do that my voice crack which brings me
to my next point
I wonder what Justin Bieber's voice is
gonna sound like when he goes through
puberty baby baby baby oh that's right
it's gonna be even better see what I did
there
speaking about that song why was
Ludacris in it was I the only one that
found it a little weird I mean he goes
from roll-out to when I was 13 I had my
first love your Ludacris man when you
were 13 you bust your first cap see I
could pull off a cheesy line like that
when I was 13 I had a mouth of braces
there was all kind of food stuck in my
teeth cleaning it all cuz they were
stuck in the spaces but Justin still
used him whatever anyway this video is
not meant to be hateful in any way in
fact it's the complete opposite I
actually wanted to say that I respect
the fact that you actually keep YouTube
one of the biggest stars today and I
think that youtubers should always back
up other YouTube so Justin I have one
last thing to say to you
less than three less than three Bieber
blasts ha