so today I'm going to be talking about
that that then can in banking that Oh
dancing
what an odd intro hey guys so today I'm
going to be talking about dance and to
be honest the real reason is because I
can't dance I'm just not good at it
it takes me a really long time to learn
the newest dances I mean I only just now
learned how to shuffle okay so maybe I
still don't not a shuffle big deal I am
so sick and tired of people inventing
new dances because by the time I learned
the newest dads there's like three more
and I'm like what did this happen you
know what kind of dances I'm talking
about right you know like the dougie the
stanky leg the cat daddy ethical yeah
there's a reason why I had someone else
do those dances because if I did it it
would look something like this the cat
day I don't care what your mother said
you finish your food cat the to skipper
stanky leg salsa dancing and I mention
you get the point anyway today I'm gonna
be taking initiative and I'm gonna be
creating the next biggest dance
it's called top reigning Barbra
Streisand
you
I mean I'm just saying if you're like me
and you want to learn the next-biggest
dance before it's uncool top rating is
gonna be the next big thing it's gonna
be big it's gonna be huge gonna be
ginormous that's what she said no she
did it I did Oh
anyway together we might be able to make
top rating an actual den I'm competing
in a competition on facebook.com slash
Just Dance game so make sure you vote
for my dance because this is our chance
guys I'm standing up for all you
horribly untalented people who can't
dance good people so join me and
together together together we can make a
difference
why is there a camera up here hey so
send me a video response of your top
rating and you can look cool like this