warning the following video may not be
appropriate for lunch and the age of
three if you would like to speak to an
operator please hold remember that your
call it very important to us so please
enjoy the music while your party is
means to ii ii ii ii ii ii ii ii ii ii
ii viewer discretion is advised
farts f to the a to the R to the T to
the s fart F to the a to the R to the T
starch
hey guys so today I'm gonna be ranting
about parts I don't see why there's such
a big deal about farts when I fart
people are like oh stop farting that's
so disgusting that's only mature well
they're the immature ones because
farting is a natural process of life you
don't see me going up to people telling
them to stop breathing because their
breath is stink just stop breathing I
mean what's the difference sometimes I
meet people whose breath smells like
fart and sometimes it's worse so I don't
see why it's such a big deal everybody
farts except for girls girls never far
just kidding but seriously everybody in
the world farts people dogs cats hogs
lambs giraffes pillows bladder pies a
lot of busses let up horses cows at the
cup so why is it such a big deal because
we make it to be I like to answer my own
questions isn't that right yes anyway
for those of you who don't know there's
four major types of parts the first one
is loud and proud these cars are really
loud and they usually don't smell that
bad so they're perfect for birthday
parties next we have the silent but
violent these parts are freakin ninjas
they just right out without anybody
knowing and yet those are the stinkiest
ones next we have the queefs these are a
bunch of wannabe farts that come from
the vagina posers and last but not least
we have the shorts these parts are the
reason you should never force on a fart
because if you do you might end up
farting ouch anyway those are the major
types of parts personally I think parts
are nothing to be ashamed of but for
those of you who are here's some
techniques for you guys to hide your
farts raising the volume all you have to
do is make noise louder than your fart
well thank you all for coming here and
listening to me that was my project on
house synthesis hope you enjoyed it
next we have denial all you have to do
is deny deny deny
that wasn't me what was it you that and
last we have the blame just blame it on
someone else I think it was you what
these techniques are so good that even
celebrities use them
Craig that soldier boy that's all we
have for the chorus what goes next I
don't know a wrap I don't you figure it
out that's genius see how easy it is so
stop trying to hold in your farts is
healthier if you just let it out because
if you don't let out your farts all the
gas inside your body is gonna start to
build up if it starts to build up it's
gonna make you expand if you expand too
much you're gonna explode when you
explode your body parts are gonna go
flying everywhere dogs cats dragons
sheep they're all going to be eating all
you
remains but what happens when they were
not a remain Steve that's right they're
gonna go for your babies do you want to
be a baby killer because every time you
hold it apart your that much closer to
killing a baby so like I said in the
beginning of the round all you people
who try to hold in your farts and think
that farts are gross and immature think
of it like this I'm trying to save lives
what are you doing you're killing babies
prick