hey guys so I just watched that video
called Friday by Rebecca Black when I
was in a loss for words for words what
the hell with that the song is terrible
the lyrics are terrible and I became
tear Abel because the song is exactly
like the music I make I'm just like
Rebecca Black I can't sing so I oughta
to myself when I write lyrics I
basically just talk about what I do on a
daily basis and yes the crap I put out
gets a million views but dean army of
you she got more so unlike everyone else
I'm not gonna say that she's a failure
because she has over thirty five million
views in a month how many views do your
videos get I can't beat that nobody can
beat that unless you're one of these or
these huh or even haha Charlie Sheen
when you think about it the lyrics
aren't horrible ish she was just being
honest the whole time I love Fridays and
I do look forward to the weekend
especially if I get the party with the
kids from Kidz Bop party and party and
yeah and actually she was absolutely
right by my mathematics and today we're
Friday yesterday would be Thursday
tomorrow would be Saturday and
afterwards well let's just say you won't
need an umbrella because it's Sunday
shut up kids Bob nobody even likes you
but there was one line in the song that
tickled my mind a little bit
tickle tickle my mind she goes wee wee
wee
so inside Ted what is that some kind of
cheap shot at Asians just because we
don't know how to speaking the good
that's racist just like that girl I met
in the library last week I don't know
why I'm here I don't know how to read oh
you thought it was gonna be Alexandra
Wallace no not every race is going a
library is her you're being sexist or
Alexandra Waller RIS walrus oh that was
an otter
Oh ding-dong what the hell is that
supposed to mean
that's your language yes but that's a
completely different dialect and why do
I have subtitles I'm speaking fine Oh
ping pong Cheech and Chong y'all mean
shut up I don't even speak pennies
pennies yes
I'm Japanese he speaks pennies
oh and yes that was a library didn't you
see the book anyway to summarize the
music video is absolutely amazing if you
haven't seen it yet and that's okay
because right now I'm going to show you
a shorter and better version of how the
song should have went take a look
7:00 a.m. ni go back the same day