hey guys so today I'm gonna be talking
about weird people I know what you're
thinking your buddy gonna be like oh
he's gonna talk about weird people and
how they're so strange and Mauro and why
he hates them well that is exactly wrong
I'm gonna be talking about why you
should embrace it
kiss it hug it
yeah I don't know why I got bleeped all
I said was love it
so like I was saying in the beginning
I'm gonna be talking about weird people
growing up I was always considered weird
I was the weird kid hey guys can I be
your friend no way you're weird get away
fat okay
everybody call me weird and you know
what they were right I am weird and I'm
part of it because being weird means
that you're different it means that
you're unique unlike you normal people
who else was weird Michael Jordan
Michael Jackson Michael Johnson Michael
Buckley Michael Wazowski from monster's
Inc all right just kidding but seriously
they're all weird because they're
different normal people can't do what
they do which is being awesome so why is
being weird such a bad thing so what if
I'm talking to a webcam in my room by
myself and nobody else is around so what
if I imitate the sound of a unicorn
getting tickle so what if I talk to
inanimate objects hey what's up little
man you wanted to be like big man it's
all right he moved on your lab that's
never gonna stop don't see let him dream
wait yeah no no don't say it little
dream you're not even a lab no no I'm
alone you're not a lab silly hearing
iron yeah give it up already man wait
wasn't there one more on you yeah
where's douche lip dude I'm totally
hooking up with this outlet right now I
need friends anyway the point I'm trying
to make is that being weird is not a bad
thing because without weird people in
the world life is gonna be like vanilla
ice cream without sprinkles you know
it's gonna be like a big sweet white
blob that's all boring and melting all
over people's hands but everybody's
hands sticky so that would go to
people's hands it's gonna be sticky as
well before you know what everybody's
hands are gonna be sick and what happens
when the hands are sticky that's right
they're gonna be climbing all over the
walls and it's all because of you normal
people so unless you want to live in a
world with webs and spider-man's all
over the place I suggest you stop being
so normal stop picking on the weird kids
the weird kids can be weird embrace the
weirdness I hate spiders and remember
the next time somebody calls you weird
just say this I got one word for you
thank you so unless she's not what so
unless you want to live in her world
so unless you want to live in a world
where so unless you know so unless you
want to live in a world with