Oh Sean's racist too cuz he respects
Liam Neeson I have no money I need
something that's I'm jobless one guy a
lot of girls and they're all trying to
fight for his love they caught something
else like not porn and re-rolling
yeah all right let's do the claps
everybody okay well I don't know if I
should injured now I'm just gonna do the
clouds first yeah ready welcome back to
another episode of off the pill podcast
and we are joined today this man needs
no introduction but I'm gonna do it we
got a bunch of new stuff but listen I'm
getting off-topic already we are here
we're sean fujiyoshi everybody Wow there
you go so and we have a new thing the
sound board I know
welcome back Sean Sean Sean Sean Sean
Sean it's good to be back see me get it
right I know seeing seen is finally back
remember a long time ago when I made
that video um was as Sean returns yeah
have my roommate or something it was in
college like mm his name was Sean too
not his real name oh I just called him
that okay just playing Sean you just
playing she's me anyway Sean is visiting
for a before everything what anyone gets
confused he's visiting for a few days
maybe like four or die's yeah Sean's in
town and we had to have him on the
podcast cuz everybody's been asking oh
yeah so we have some of those questions
from Twitter at off the pill we're gonna
get through that later this is the part
where normally we're supposed to be
thinking our sponsors that we still
don't have so this could be you I don't
know I don't have any right there well
that's not a road is not a sponsor yeah
they sent us stuff
thank you very much Road so companies
this could be you I could wear your
stuff whoever's here could wear your
stuff good pitch that's it
yeah that's all anyway we it's like
ongoing joke but we really want it's
really comfortable yet no but Rhoda sent
this stuff that's not a real sponsor but
they sent us free stuff
sorry it's been a while you know it's
been a while so Shawn yeah dude it's
been uh he literally just got in so we
didn't really have that much time to
catch up I'm a little tired not gonna
lie
yeah I know you got got up pretty early
how's life been this super general but
that's blue like another one actually
yeah dude it's been crazy not what I
expected at all it's what were you
expecting to find a job for one Oh
instantly right I didn't think it's
gonna be this hard
right right right well that's why you
were using this podcast see another
thing in sponsorships shot needs a job
if you're in the Sacramento area and
you're looking for an engineer well I
don't know what if that's what you want
but yeah we're looking for an engineer
yeah trying to do engineering but do all
you engineers out there with engineering
degrees you might really do this but if
you're in school right now get an
internship because that thing means a
lot when you were in school did you
actually think about that did you
actually like they had the option to
intern I did but I had a lot of smarter
people with my class so they got the
internships I wasn't gonna get any you
actually tried though oh yeah I tried I
see okay so it's really important
because from what you were telling me
like what were you saying about the
issues with that you need experience
they arrived on experience but they
don't really they want to spend the
least amount of time to train you to get
you a two-speed which makes sense for a
business aspect you know cuz they don't
want to spend a whole bunch of time
trying to teach you from the ground up
of right how to do stuff they want you
to know kind of what the industry is
especially in your type of field right
cuz I mean so it's been like six months
yeah almost I think yeah I mean more
than I'm not sure it's about six months
yeah and you've been non-stop like
applying and reaching out to people and
it always comes down to experience yeah
and location - oh really because if I
was like in maybe like the one of the
main cities then I would have more
options to choose from more
opportunities more companies right
Sacramento is kind of like a small kind
of town it's a city but not really a
city it's more like a big town in my
opinion so well huh it's it's really
tough
do you think that um you know obviously
I thought I won't point something you
said that you met a fan or something
like that and their mom kind of like you
hooked you up with an interview I
thought that was like you got a job or a
see the thing that I run into a lot is
that a lot of them like me as a person
right and they really enjoy like my
personality is what they tell me but I
don't have the experience to be able to
you know hit it home with ya the
department's yeah because they're you
think it'd also be like wow this guy is
fresh out of college this fresh in his
mind he has interned for this company
why would they pick somebody who's not
exactly right so but the weird thing is
like if you can if you're open to doing
an internship yeah like a non-paid one
they're if they're not letting you do
that then like how are you ever going to
experience you know I mean well they're
for one there's a difference between
internships and volunteer tips are kind
of they're more kind of funded by like
the government uh-huh
so like there's a lot of legal stuff
that kind of go into it so you need to
be part of school still taught it get an
internship and most places aren't as
open to giving volunteer opportunities
right so you know there's that old dude
yeah well I mean maybe like like I said
that we should use this anyone in
Sacramento or in the Northern
Californian sac because it would be nice
in sac yeah Sacramento I'll commute to
San Francisco two-hour drive but you
want to volunteer you know Shawn needs
an engineering job well I guess would
you go back to like school since you
said internships are where you can go is
that is that a potential possibility for
you honestly yeah I've been considering
it a lot if well right now I'm in the
process of maybe getting a job but think
you're on a questionable just growing
yeah so I'm just hoping right but if it
doesn't fall it doesn't if it doesn't
work out then yeah I'm thinking about
going back to school okay well wouldn't
it be really are you taking the same
classes like knock out change
oh I see okay just pull up your old
report from some yeah but it's like I
was thinking about going a different
route maybe huh because I don't know I
took I took mechanical engineering
because it's the most broad engineering
degree that
you cover all bases of engineering to do
something more specific yeah I like I
like graphics okay it's kind of why I
was doing editing here yeah but I
enjoyed doing graphics and stuff so
thank you stuff you could use as say
that's like experience I've been trying
right you could I've been crying that
they do allow some to cross over from
like graphic design into CAD designing
is what they call it uh-huh
and it's just it's pretty similar except
you need to know some technical fields
about it you're like building like you
know little projects little mechanical
things or like architecture or that kind
of stuff so there is some crossover but
they would rather you learn within the
industry right right right
so it's a little tough so anyway your
advice to kids is yeah do the internship
get the internship because it makes a
big difference it makes a huge
difference okay well that's good to know
it makes a really big difference no
matter what engineering you're in get an
internship mm-hmm but you are open to
volunteering free yeah exactly all right
I don't see why people wouldn't want
that though you know like it doesn't
harm them does it that's what I love you
and that's what I think it might harm
because then he could be a potential
hindrance yeah because it's considered
volunteer work so you're not like oh I'm
like die hard for this company you know
it's like I'm giving them my spare time
I'm you know right so they want people
they probably want people who are like
invested into it know that oh they want
to be there there is a difference with
each company too though some are more
like family oriented were some are more
blue-collar you know and so like the
blue-collar ones just want experience
yeah where they're not gonna hook you up
yeah that one might be like oh he's just
a cool guy
unless you have connections within the
company on it okay that's another thing
if if you can make connections to that's
your another way in
Oh hundred percent connections are
everything that's how like a lot of
things work nowadays yes even then
especially in like the entertainment
industry that is how it works yeah from
what I hear at least like half the time
you know we need to open casting calls
for movies and stuff like that they
already know who they want they're just
doing it for the sake and they'll bring
in like some Asians and some color and
you know just to say like oh we casted
and this is just the best person but
they already knew who they wanted hmm
it's all about connections that's why
it's important to
nice introvert extroverted person like
me I think you too actually I don't know
if you're introverted I am I'm not good
at networking I'm so introverted right
yeah right um I think I can
I can't label myself as introvert
extrovert I think I'm a percentage
mm-hmm I think I'm like do both I think
I'm like 35% extroverted and the rest is
introvert it's not like yeah one or the
other
yeah kind of like a CD it depends on the
situation and who I'm surrounded with
hmm see we're doing we're giving a
business class right now and see what
you want to do is number one take the
internship number two be a little
extroverted learn how to network that is
the most important getting connections
and also make sure your tweets are very
clean go through your history clear out
everything that is a good that is
actually really true that'll ruin
people's lives holidays yeah or private
your Twitter right anything anything
that's going online you just have to be
more conscious like the whole receivers
are showing us yeah if he's seen this
and you know dude I've been watching you
you haven't had a job so what have you
been doing I mean I know you've been
applying a lot to different things
what are you doing your spare time dude
I just been applying and trying to
research no but aside from that I did
have like a little mini venture to Japan
oh yeah which was very out of the blue
and last minute yeah but we saw that
that was with Mari and am I saying that
was Mario yes yeah we're a hella jealous
when we saw that yeah it was cool boys
weren't that high but yeah finally were
like that no it was um
we were like Shawn to Japan why no I was
like why am I here in the group you're
with me like wangus and you're with uh
Wes and Mari I don't understand group if
you guys don't know who those people are
Marius formerly with James yeah right
and then Wes is part of the productions
and wangus is like a manager he's kind
of like a manager slash
he books people for stuff friends he
does a lot of this a lot it how was that
it was cool mangas it was so weird cuz
why he's hitting me up like a week and a
half before it was going down and I just
like do you want to do this and I was
like yeah I have no money I need
something a little bit yeah buy you some
more time yeah
but it was it was like a they basically
wanted my technical aspect of opinion of
what they're doing and that was the job
I wasn't like a meeting greed no it
wasn't a meeting role it was over video
oh so um I just yeah are you allowed to
discuss it I can say okay I'm pretty
sure I mean I didn't need to post
anything but you sign an NDA what is
that good then I think you'd be fine no
I think I'm fine
uh-huh but basically uh are you guys
familiar with SK too
just out of curiosity okay area ii south
korea it's it's a beauty brand like for
like skincare type of stuff i have heard
of that it's a very popular Asian brand
that's in Singapore no Japan maybe I
didn't hear about that okay go ahead
honestly I'm probably the worst person
to speak about this sorry SK 2 but if
you guys are watching you sorry but in
sponsors but yeah they were doing a
bunch of pops pop ups around around
everywhere and the whole the entire
thing was basically trying to have a
more interactive environment while
learning about the product so they did
this AR space artificial reality and
basically you take your phone and using
the video it like replaces a lot of like
the walls and stuff and like you see
like cool effects like coming out at the
walls or like you'll see bubbles popping
around everywhere so that's pretty cool
and then like as you go and like it's
kind of like a fun experience like it's
kind of like a playground with your
phone and and that's what so what did
you do they've basically just filmed me
mari and was just going through the
throughout the space and experience
everything every single room learning
about what the whole product was about
and then at the end they do like a
facial scan and it tells you like your
skin age
oh and then from that they'll recommend
you like what product you should use
yeah that's kind of yeah so they wanted
I guess they wanted people more in the
technical aspect I guess and to give our
thoughts about the space and what we
thought about it and give our feedback
so that's all that really was they just
filmed this going through the space and
then you we gave our two cents of what
we thought about that sounds like if I
were it's like a cool reason just a
excuse to go that's why I was like
that's awesome you tear and why would
they want me in there beautiful day
that's why thanks that's why they hit up
only you Wes and Mari hit anybody else
so you did that yeah you believe mean
that as cool so that was like a very
short time yeah but help because I'm
jobless okay we're gonna keep bringing
that up so that people really get across
it let's get Shawn a job please you know
I need some help but like in like you
weren't I mean obviously you you want a
job but it ideally in engineering yeah I
just what you have interest in yeah I
mean I think this kind of plays back to
like the whole introvert extrovert thing
mmm-hmm the whole YouTube life was like
a little I don't know the I wouldn't say
demanding it was just very controversial
for myself
mmm-hmm because you know we're like two
dudes from like a very small town in
Hilo Hawaii so out and you know me where
I'm more introverted so are you mm-hm
and the tension was kind of like a
stressful thing for me I can I can only
spend so much energy on it before I get
like stressed out about it yeah you know
yeah I have like capacity until I get
exhausted a lot I think a lot of
youtubers are like that and they have to
and you see it too
yeah through their videos everyone goes
through those same phases like that
video I made about the life of a
youtuber and it's always like this hype
and like you start blowing up and people
start surrounding you you move out to LA
and you get all this attention and then
you get exhausted you say I'll have to
take a break I'm too late I'm too tired
you come back once you find yourself
again and it's the same process and I
think that's what you're kind of talking
about is like it yeah it does get
exhausting mm-hm
yeah and you were in it in the beginning
then you went to college so you kind of
were out of it yeah and then you came
back and start building up again yeah
you went through it twice was my second
time going out yeah so for you then you
think this lifestyle fits you better
yeah and I think the biggest thing had
to do with my girlfriend as well right
because you know I don't know if I
wanted I guess I was more questionable
questionable about if I really want to
be surrounded by this whole you two-bit
attention while I'm trying to build like
a life right surrounding my girlfriend
and stuff because it's very serious now
obviously I would mm-hmm dropped
everything and moved to her right and
it's I don't know if it's a maturity
thing or maybe it's just like my own
personal quarrels of having all this
attention but I guess I don't like if I
have a family and stuff I don't want
them to know me as I don't want my kids
to know me as the YouTube guy I want to
do more in my life than just YouTube
kind of thing yeah you know I mean it's
always gonna be around people are gonna
bring it up yet over time I feel like
it'll chill yeah so and it just I think
to put more context in it like you guys
have been together for like a little
over two years now right and for a lot
of it was long distance yeah long
distance is tough man and and so I mean
there gets to a point where you're like
that makes you feel like oh do I really
want to commit to this exactly what am I
willing to let go and in a way it was
like a burden off your back because like
you said like you know you wanted to
build a life that isn't just viewed by
millions of people yeah
and so and is where you're I like my
privacy too yeah you know I like having
the split of a personal life and public
life so like you know I don't mind if
fans come up to me like ah I totally
enjoy just meeting fans in like being
appreciative that they've watched all of
our stuff and we're like longtime fans
like I still get approached to this day
especially in Sacramento there's a lot
of fans at sacrament right but I do like
having my personal life that's like my
my personal time my place to like you
know rejuvenate my brain and not be so
stressed out all the time I can just
enjoy my time with my girlfriend mm-hmm
that sounds so boring
yeah it is
don't you know what that sounds like
that's awesome yeah but it's it's more
for my son that does fit you though
that's like much more of like how I know
you
yeah and kind of like to yourself for
the most part very private yeah I guess
I I guess you wouldn't like that to do
that go out a lot and I guess it would
be kind of exhausting cuz I don't do it
I just try and that's why I stay home
all the time
mm-hmm that's why I'm not in LA so okay
okay okay
cuz I want to know I wanna look this is
nice we're getting all like sentimental
and everything make me smile and laugh I
wanna know what it's like a crazy fan
experience that you've had in your
career though cuz you're talking about
like you appreciate fans and you know
everybody that does appreciate their
fans but sometimes fans get a little too
crazy and they're just like oh I'm gonna
be best friends with this person and you
know that just just plays with that line
just a little too much
what is yours mine okay - why was that
VidCon right after internet icon um a
lot of people don't know about Internet
Mike really loud or is it just my
headphones I think he just got louder I
think I got closer I told myself down
but just a lot of a lot of a lot of
people don't know but that's kind of how
Ryan was more aware of me was this thing
called internet icon and it was right
after that is that VidCon I was in the
bathroom peeing and there's nine urinals
there right this guy comes up right next
to me starts peeing looks at me so
casual it just goes oh you're Paco right
and I'm like yeah and then he looks down
tan and then back up at me and then just
goes cool dude and then just leaves and
I was leaning you men there wash his
hands I don't know I was like what just
happened
I think you just got assaulted by his
eyes like what do i do do I pee on him
what happens I mean it's already rule
number one in a bathroom for guys yes
you don't go to the urinal next to
someone else yeah unless it's there's no
other option was there was there there
was nine well yeah I was in the only one
so that's already
he's breaking rule number well
radio I mean like whoa you know I'm
gonna cut my stream I'm gonna cut my
stream and be like um dude this is like
danger danger zone I would be really
freaked out yeah it's so weird
that's weird okay that just that as my
weird experience sex second one is he's
sparked a conversation Wow
without peeing himself that is like II
like the disapper everything looked at
me and then it's like cool dude it's
like just left and then he looked down
at your peepee dude yeah that's really
really a stretch numbers dude that's I
was just like this is an interesting
okay I don't have a story like yeah
mines is not that bad go ahead the only
one that I can really remember I was
with you okay and the bay
I think uh-huh and we're on one of those
tram things you know the public remember
we're in San Francisco you want the
large like moose heart things yeah yeah
run in the middle of the trolley
patrol the trolley yeah yeah we're on
one of those things and basically these
these two girls recognize this and
freaked out she screamed super loud that
it made the train person stop mm-hmm and
he came running over something like
thinking something was wrong and then
the girls basically explained that oh my
god they're like the YouTube guys Baba
yeah so he's like oh okay
weird I mean he kept going and then
we're like let's get on let's get off on
the next time this is kind of weird
because we're standing because it was a
fool like it was packed they're sitting
down right in front of us and we're
hanging on to the handles right above
them and just as we're about to get off
the girl in front of me just grabs me
and goes I love you so much and
something something something and but
she grabbed on to me and wouldn't let me
go and it was like holding up everyone
huh and I was like I don't know how you
got I just feels like you just feel good
yeah I felt so awkward and everyone
staring and this girl's freaking out
grabbing on to me and I'm just like I
gotta go yeah just for watching nice
meeting you and it was just like super
ah yes
part especially in the beginning I was
years ago right yeah I was like 2010
maybe maybe or something it was a long
time ago when we weren't equipped to
deal with that before because at the
same time it's like this person you know
it might be inappropriate to a certain
degree and but it's because they love
you yeah and they really like you know
you really appreciate that but it's it's
such a weird thing to have to deal with
like you have to be like kind of mean
they're not mean there's like boundaries
yeah there's some boundaries that you
have to I mean it's better now
yeah people are older our fans at least
but like when there's a young kid you
don't want to like break their hearts
you know oh my god he's such an ass how
he like pushed me away after I hugged
him for a minute yeah I got a similar
thing in Town Square where somebody was
hugging me and I got a little I wasn't
very happy it's just awkward you know
it's just like you wouldn't go up to
someone you've never met and just hugged
them yeah even if you saw them or if you
saw like a you know like a celebrity
like um Brad Pitt you know and then you
just ran up there and start hugging him
you would know not to do that but one
but because you're a youtuber and it's
not the same thing as I think people see
us is more approachable and more oh
they're relatable you know and the
community I know about their lives so
I'm allowed to talk to them like you
wouldn't even like you wouldn't even
think twice like oh I love them let me
hug them yes I know you I'm a fan I
subscribed it to like a celeb mainstream
celebrity you would never I think people
might try that but most most times
people would know like that's not the
really right thing to do
yeah and the weird thing too is like you
may know them but they don't know you so
it feels super awkward super strange and
the crazy thing is that it's weird for
us as guys now can you imagine like what
is it like to be like a girl emails
right it must be so like like increment
like exponentially just so much more
strange I don't think guys would do that
to a girl like they especially in this
day and age oh yes
I don't think I've never seen what has
been done has it it has it like you know
like certain things like some guys just
don't have social cues sure act not even
just guys people don't have soules
recused at times and they just like
cross those lines and just make it super
weird like oh I paid for this
Griet or I came to this like VidCon and
I get to like you know interact with how
I want to interact with these people
that actually brings up a really that's
a serious topic that I've been talking
to uh not recently but we all talk about
I guess a bunch of youtubers is how you
know if you have like a patreon or even
a YouTube channel where but someone
really supports you and there is like
somebody who's a little off I know David
was telling me and Keena they have this
one fan that felt like because she has a
because they have like a patreon or
whatever they donate they feel like they
own you a little bit and that's where
you get the freaky people the people who
are like come to your shows and they
expect something yeah and you know those
are the super fans and it's scary like
you don't know what they're gonna do if
they feel like they're not getting if
they can't have you then no one should
yeah and that's and like this is kind of
like a dark area to go into and I know
you know I'm going yeah which is like
the the christina grimmie thing yeah I
mean I don't want mean I was terrible
that ruined me for awhile like I used to
do we used to go out to a lot I don't
know if before you around we used to go
to a lot of events and stuff after that
I just kind of stopped I was just like
this is I don't feel safe anymore and
like I didn't it didn't feel real
because I thought okay that happens to
some celebrities very rarely but to a
youtuber or someone I met someone it's
just it felt so real and it scared me
honest I didn't want to do events or if
I was gonna do it and they had to be
super secure I remember that yeah I'm we
all I kind of like got pushed into
reality you know like holy moly there's
like actually some crazy people who
would actually do that yeah and to like
perfectly nice people you know like I
mean I don't know the backstory but I'd
only got to meet her once but from
everybody that I was like friends with
and knew like they loved her yeah like
always spoke so highly of her and it's
just it's insane that people feel oh
because I am supporting you you're MA
you're a piece of my property well I
don't know if that's the exact case and
we mean the guy you know shot himself
after that so we don't really know
exactly I mean I don't think we know
just from what I've heard yeah yeah it
was a fan nobody can have a crazy
scenario
um yeah I mean speaking of Christina she
was just like there's a lot of youtubers
that you meet and then used to feel like
okay they're very nice you don't know
enough about them but when you met
Christina for the first time I remember
first time I met her you just instantly
felt like she was genuine and that's
something you can't just like think you
kind of fake that yeah you know and
that's why I was really it was tough for
me man I was even that closer I couldn't
imagine for her family or like other
youtubers actually were like close with
her but for me even just meeting her a
couple of times I was just like Dan this
I was I couldn't believe it yeah but um
yeah that got dark yeah super dark sure
thing is hello it brings up a good a
good point though about like you know I
think fans need to kind of realize that
there is a crossing point that you don't
cross because we're still humans you
know like right you still kind of to
respect us as humans we're not just like
some like petting zoo or so there's an
argument for that too when I can
understand their side of it
not that it's their sides but people say
like you know when you're going into the
public domain like you have to it comes
with the territory like there's a reason
you're getting paid more to just do
events and stuff like that but even then
I still think with that knowing that and
I agree with that it comes with the
territory yeah it's still you got to be
respectful to people I think some people
just don't realize there's there's a
certain line like thing I hate the most
and I always tell you guys his when you
know honestly I don't mind if they come
up and ask for a picture and I'll take
it most times if not all the time I know
where this is going but um the only time
I didn't and I was like kind of grouchy
when I was at a buffet I was waiting
over an hour and I had just sat down I
was watching these people right looking
over at me I'm in line watching these
people eat and like they have like I'm
just starving and I'm in this line for
like an hour as soon as I sit down I'm
finally like happy I'm like oh yes let's
go
you know I'm about to get my food they
come and start talking to me they
approach me and it's like there's
another fan story I don't know I'm back
into it they start talking to me and
they asked for a picture oh no no they
don't ask for a picture they just start
and say oh cool and nice to meet you and
whatever they went back to their table I
go and get all my food I have like crap
I have like stings like my hands are
messy all over my face and
as they're leaving they walk on like hey
could we get a picture and I'm just like
um maybe like after I'm done you know
and already I was just like I don't
really want to do this right now because
for one I'm hungry too I look like a
mess and the oh we're actually going
right now I was like oh sorry and I felt
so bad I still remember today this is
like years ago I felt so guilty because
I saw their faces go from like oh we're
big fans said oh he's a jerk but that's
the thing too you have to always be on -
yeah yeah and like the moment people
think like oh something's wrong with
Ryan like he's he's not an [ __ ] or
he's tired or people don't assume you're
tired you don't know soon you're grouchy
they don't assume you could have a death
in the family that day and you go out
and you say I don't want take pictures
they're like okay he's an [ __ ] yeah
and they're not gonna give you call
because all they have is as reference is
what you are in your videos yeah yeah
yeah and there have this expectation
exact um so I can't I understand that
one of you but um I forgot what we were
talking about just like boundaries right
now just countries I guess cuz like I
don't know I don't know about you guys
but I think it's kind of rude if
someone's made eating and you go and
interrupt them it is it is I feel like I
wouldn't do that
yeah but I mean generally but I guess
yeah I do understand that it comes with
the territory but yeah come on let us
eat or he is hungry sacred place yeah if
they're peeing in a urinal that's fine
but eating yeah that's where you draw
the line yeah come on in do not take a
picture take a picture it'll last longer
but I did feel guilty for like years I
think I've been through that situation -
yeah I thought I felt guilty I don't
feel guilty but then it's like I'll
never feel hungry I know well the thing
is - I actually appreciate people coming
up and asking for pictures more than
just trying to snipe you from far oh
yeah actually while you're eating
because then you feel like man I got to
eat nice and like get stuff in my mouth
when you see it - and it's like making I
go like one of those kind of phases like
a side for people who just are listening
I just made it really you know one of
those when you take a frame from a video
and your eyes are like half open ones
you know yeah and they post that stuff
and I just like okay great yeah but
anyway I scared
someone doing that one time scared
someone doing what exactly they're
sniping from like afar yeah I knew
they're doing it it was super obvious
uh-huh my entire family were like I
think they're trying to take a picture
of you I was like I know yes I do that
what I ended up doing was I made a face
to them a super ugly face I just like
they freaked out and they dropped their
phone in their leg
I like uh I think this is something that
a roy or guava juice and then I think
also Timothy DeLaGhetto does they take
pictures of the people taking pictures
of them right I think I think that's
funny see that comes with a risk though
because what if they're not taking a
picture yeah and you're just that cocky
jerk who thinks everyone's take pictures
of them now you can tell everyone does
yeah yeah I know the people listening
won't be able to see this but people on
video do if you're trying to get a sneak
picture here's here's my advice don't do
the little turtle t-rex arms yeah like
nobody holds their phone this close to
them and it doesn't help you get a
better picture the best thing you can do
is kind just like you know hold it like
just be natural yeah everyone does that
the t-rex they make t-rex arms they
bring their phone super close like right
in their chest it's so obvious yeah if
you want picture for one just come up
and ask yeah it's like when you're in
that position
you're never in that position in the
first place so it's already like what is
that weirdo doing oh they're taking a
picture you be surprised how many people
do so many people just the t-rex arm
just come up to us yeah we don't fight
except one we're eating don't t-rex all
you want I don't want even mind that it
was just that one time
you know I was jealous of them being
able to enjoy them you're angry I was
angry I was angry but yeah that um yeah
I mean people gonna be like wow they
don't care but they don't love us they
don't care about their fans if they did
I mean I remember posting what that girl
that was hugging me for a long time I
tweeted it in that town square and I got
so many angry fans I didn't realize that
they felt that way like wow you don't
appreciate us oh I would love to people
coming up to hug me for minutes
yeah but the thing is they don't
understand how often it'll happen and
how it can like interrupt in your life
cuz they're just like I want the
attention I want this but I don't want
the negative parts of it you know I
don't want to have to like work super
hard and just to be able to like
get my stuff out there and express my
thoughts and everything I just want the
attention some people yeah I think most
of it like the most common thing now and
oh dude you can you can hear my passion
coming out I hear it I feel it yeah yeah
I got passion in my pants yeah um
they're teachers who asks kids now oh
what do you want to be you know like
before used to be like oh astronaut
firefighter doctor mm-hmm one of the
most common things that kids want to be
now is a youtuber I've heard that yeah
and it's just like it's it's so strange
it makes sense yeah they're watching
yeah because they want like the
attention they want the fame they want
all the all the good things about it but
they don't see like how hard it takes to
get there yeah that's true yeah and like
I think that's true for a lot of other
things to them yeah yeah yeah and they
that's why they there it's a it's a new
field mm-hmm the whole entertainment and
like social media like influence or
whatever and people just like wow I see
this person so much sure life must be so
good because you don't know everything
that's going on you just instantly are
just like they must be like making
YouTube money partying all the time
having so much fun doing all this stuff
I want that mm-hmm you know and they
they don't
again it's they don't understand or give
you guys the benefit of the doubt like
as human beings right how difficult it
can be I think it's a maturity thing to
a lot of these kids are like you know
they're kids they don't know the full
scope of being an adult
yeah I'm an adult yeah there's yeah
there are people who are like you know
even our age I want to do YouTube and
like you know they do think it is easier
but most people no say most people think
what we do is a lot easier than it
really is
and they I think the reason why I mean
you can see it in the comments and
someone like like Lily right she said oh
I'm taking a break or whatever instantly
people were like oh you know why are you
so another youtuber this depressed you
know I has meant to issues like they
were making jokes out of it yeah saying
like oh you know these guys are so
unappreciative they made so much money
and they're getting all this fame like
oh life must be rough you know but like
this brought me to the bite I thought
about this a lot I don't even know if
I've made a
brought it up but another perspective
and might sound bad but it's your
podcast yes my haven't done one of those
in a while
it's my podcast I can do what I want I
something I thought about a lot and I
think you really don't realize it until
you have it when I say that just because
you have those things happiness doesn't
come from those things and it's on so
common that cabinets doesn't come from
money doesn't come from fame and you
don't really really believe it until you
have it yeah because I didn't I used to
think okay yeah I just want a family and
whatever but in the back your head
you're like man if I had this much money
I wouldn't be sad yeah he's fine like if
I had this much fame like who cares if
you know something happens I'm famous
and rich you know like and you know you
you really don't understand that it
really means nothing um the best way I
can describe it is like someone like
Robin Williams someone who everyone
loved right everybody loved he had it
all he had money he had fame it's not
his career was getting worse everybody
he was a legend but he still you know
killed himself yeah and that just goes
to show you it has nothing to do with
that sure yes it does help to have money
right to do things I don't believe in
the saying that money doesn't buy any
happiness yeah but until you have it you
realize it doesn't mean as much as it
nearly you would think at least yeah
it's just coming from that perspective I
agree I mean I think that's like another
big reason why I kind of left the scene
right because it's for like you know
sanity mm-hmm if not like some people
can handle it
yeah people like me can't but it's also
you know I always say to it's always
like the grass is greener yeah I know
for a fact I wouldn't be happy doing a
nine-to-five clerk job it creatively at
least and so in that way I understand
I'm still appreciative of you know what
we have but at the same time sometimes I
do wish I'm like man if I just work 9:00
to 5:00 and just focused on that time
and not worry I wouldn't I could have my
nights and not worry about work
I could have weekend's you know which I
don't have because I have to make my own
schedule when you're youtuber you are
your own boss basically so it's a little
tough mentally I don't know if all
people are like this but I have issues
like taking breaks or taking day
or taking a vacation because I don't
even have fun doing it I'm thinking
about other things and that it's a
blessing and a curse cuz you make your
own schedule so you can take those
things but like like I said it's a
mental I think in your situation it's a
curse a lot of the time could be we as a
group have seen like you know when
you're just like like it's clear that
you're definitely thinking about work
and and when we're like doing other
things yeah unable to like just be in
the moment yeah yeah it is like it is I
mean even people know people know does
that about me but I am just always
trying to it's hard to just have fun
when you know that you could be working
if it was like a nine-to-five you know
okay five o'clock I can do whatever I
want until 9:00 the next day it's just a
mindset I know it's like a first-world
foot it is it does mess with people I
think a lot of people um any messes with
me a lot this is what I heard though
like when people say oh it's a first
world problem but it's also like you're
listening to a podcast like you live in
the first world most likely true sure
yeah that is true but I mean what that's
just I'm saying it in the meme sense
it's not even like it's something you I
if I really could mentally get over that
then it wouldn't be a big deal huh but
it's just it just happens I think a lot
of like even like personal businesses
anybody who owns a business really can
yeah really relate to that
it's all about balance yeah I mean
that's like one of the biggest issues in
life is like work-life balance you know
yeah it's one of the heart I feel like
that's like one of the most common like
problems in life especially like as you
get older and becoming an adult you know
like having that work-life balance like
really means a lot I mean that's what
you're even that's the whole point of
why you moved and stuff like that yeah
yeah and it's important for people think
about think about it cuz we're old now
you know yeah before we could just like
think about let's just make a video I
don't know let's go to Utah or let's do
whatever we want but now it's like no
but if we go there we're gonna be tired
when we come back this is a different
mindset I think and before we could do
like 24 hours a day working and yeah are
perfectly fine and we're cool we're cool
with like sleeping a few hours so that
we could play video games when we want
and yeah that's basically that that
changed I can't do that anymore
yeah I'm not living that college life
anymore I know we're definitely getting
older yeah
to segue even though we're getting older
I believe that we're all still part of
the nine year old army which is
basically PewDiePie's audience kind of
like we support is that a nine year
that's is that's like that's what the
whole joke is like he's had several
different regimes of audiences and right
now I think it's like the nine year old
army and you were talking about memes
earlier and we do the collapse isn't you
there's a huge just go subscribe to
PewDiePie kind of thing yeah but he is
doing a meme review with Elon Musk that
is crazy that is insane but at the same
time it makes so much sense right yeah
for Elon Musk cuz he had he knows that's
like one of the big it's like going on
an eighth like a late-night show yeah
but bigger uh-huh because his show is so
big and with the whole him battling T
series things is it's just like building
even more yeah it makes more sense to go
on that show than it would be to go on a
like a good morning show exactly yeah so
it kind of does make sense but it is
crazy how this this Janet this uh this
this wave I guess is Qi held mainstream
it's becoming the new mainstream media
it's finally branching on ya and that's
something also that I wanted to bring up
was the impact that social media has
because there are like traditional
mainstream mainstream media stars who
are very aware of the social media stars
and I feel like when the social media
stars meet them and they find out like
oh the traditional person knows about me
they're shocked right oh and it's like
but you you have almost like a bigger
reach than they do a lot of the time and
it's just like going to show um like I
think I think is something like Shane
Dawson's the minded Jake Paul yeah like
his viewership was beating a bunch of
Netflix original shows in terms of
viewership well for one I mean it's free
right yeah so not everyone has Netflix I
think that's a big part of it too but
like a lot of television is free the
difference is is that when Shane puts it
out you can notified for one and also
you don't have to you can watch it when
you want to watch it you don't have to
wait til it comes on at 9:00 p.m. or
8:00 p.m. you just pull out your phone
it's a new version of entertainment
mmm-hmm it's happening dude we've been
saying for a long time the internet was
gonna take over TV and it was always
kind of there and that was a joke that
killed the television but it really is
now mmm you know people like Elon Musk
are going on PewDiePie show you know you
know it's it's really changed a lot yeah
all right just subscribe be to t-series
bother gets so much nine-year-old love
the way that sounds we're mine
a we cut that part out right now we're
leaving that ya know what you alright
what else just how you did you watch the
Super Bowl you don't like football I did
you wash it though not all those you go
all the way through but I watched ya at
home
it was own kind of you would have more
fun watching paint dry that's not true
it was it was slow though yeah I watched
you the first half and I was like I kind
of have an idea where this is gonna go
I'm gonna check back in at 4th quarter
yeah I think it's part of it too it's
just like oh it's Tom Brady again yeah
what else is new I mean I like the Tom
Brady and uh Gronk Instagram videos more
than the actual game that's true that's
it's so funny see you know what I don't
understand I mean I watch football but
like I'm not super like serious like I'm
you know 49ers fan so we're irrelevant
but I always thought like I don't
understand why people hate Tom Brady so
much I mean I get the whole like
deflating ball things which from what I
hear at least they labeled him a cheater
but even if it even if that's the case
him as a person he seems like a really
cool dude doesn't he yeah yeah very
family man disease sons yeah people will
still make fun of that seems like like a
nice dude he seemed that the guy you
invite to a party and he'd be like hey
can I help you guys clean up yeah that's
the kind of guy like what should I bring
yeah mmm whereas some people some of the
football players they look like I want
to make it all about me
mm-hmm they come into the party they
start dancing and get a whole circle
around them extroverts I don't know how
but it's so it's so easy to hate on
somebody who's like that that's why and
successful yeah like everyone wants the
underdog to do better yeah and it's you
know but he was an underdog though yeah
well like team sports fandoms yeah yeah
they're hard they're hardcore so it's
true you know you're always gonna root
for your team I'm just saying there's so
many like other people out there that
play sports that probably deserve more
hate for being like kind of a jerk but
like when you're a humble person I mean
I think he's no I don't know well I
don't know him personally but he seems
like a nice dude like it just a clean
cool dude hey Tom Brady we don't know
you but you should come on this podcast
if we can figure out if you are not yeah
because he's definitely walk
oh yes ace social media influence you
know maybe his sons will find out about
it after he kisses his dad by the way
Ryan Higa wants you to be on his podcast
to kiss us yeah so we can have some of
your greatness mm-hmm that's right
Wow okay well I mean I knew you weren't
into football I just was wondering I
watch did you dude you guys do anything
like goat uh no I watched on my own
do you like the commercials though yeah
some of them I was a little disappointed
this year was yeah I didn't see too many
this year there was a one with the
Backstreet Boys that was kind of funny
Oh a chance yeah a chance to rap yeah
yeah yeah other than that I was just
like oh okay
it's oh man it used to be very like yeah
every single one was like awesome and
now it's just like oh that was cool I
guess different I wonder if it's like
the expectation because it's discrete
exactly Oh last year's was good now they
have to top it yeah that's what I was
thinking too house like maybe we're have
to high expectations yes it's hard to
beat and there's been a lot so you know
how many new original commercials can
you come up with yeah for sure yeah you
know what too though it's kind of like
what we described YouTube videos as like
if you're always topping you topping
your previous video a certain point
you're gonna plateau or people are gonna
get so accustomed to that so you do have
to throw some like fillers out there's
some like you know you don't have to
always be topping yourself but come back
with something some slow balls yeah like
yeah change and I would be pitching the
heaters gotta give them some change jobs
should we um I want to bring up the
questions that we asked people we
actually asked people did you see it the
tweet we sent out yeah bill Antonov the
pill yep on Twitter and we have an
Instagram as well and we had people send
in a bunch of their questions that they
had for you because yeah I was getting
tagged a lot I know you're the reason
why I mean they they have a lot of
questions so we're not gonna be able do
all this I think I answered some already
though you did but we can there's so
many dude there's a lot of bad ones too
so we could go into you guys want to
take the shishi break now and then go
into this yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
so we're gonna take a quick shishu break
we use that for those of you that don't
know this is where we could put in ad
break this could be you but instead
we're gonna go a she she what do you do
what are you doing I'm just showing them
this could be you
oh that I mean Road yeah like cuz well
we're not gonna if there's a real you
know if there's another sponsor were not
gonna be wearing Road yeah we're gonna
be wearing what they have or or I can
just read like a lot of people they read
like oh um yeah but let's show them we
can go above and beyond you're right you
know what like if for some reason
bananas like not even in just goodness
Republic no just the fruit itself with
like hey we want to support you guys
will give you guys 10,000 bananas and
we're like hell yeah and we substitute
these mics for bananas yeah and you guys
won't have a good sound but your bananas
would be in there and then we'll eat
them and we'll wear them and we'll slide
in them just like into your DMS alright
now you're thinking now you're thinking
I'm I'm there i we know she she break
yeah should we do it alright how do we
break into those again right back and
we're back
hey that was a fast break they don't
know that at least for them they thought
unless if we had an ad there where it's
supposed to be but we don't have that I
pooped you did yep yeah we're actually
you were just it sounds so immature we
were just talking about poopy
no but we were saying how so Shaun and I
used to wrestle and you know we had to
lose weight weight to cut weight all the
time pooping helps realistically it's
not not an immature thing is we had to
learn techniques to poop you dropped
weight when you poop yeah there's
certain ways that you and we found the
strats the strats to help us poop like
one is like rubbing your your your
stomach was it clockwise helps a lot to
help things get moo-ving we could be
just making this up by the way but it
for us it works yeah but the one that
nobody really can relate to that we used
to do it
we call it the bouncies and basically
you just kind of get up and you have to
like completely relax your stomach relax
everything and just start like slowly
like bending your knee like just
bouncing and laying your stomach or how
do you describe it just let it drop dude
yeah and it works it makes you have to
poop yeah you know I don't know if
people can relate to this I don't know
if you're at home just try it give it a
shot no audience yeah I know no girls
can do it to they don't have to admit it
but girls girls girls don't poop are you
sure yes heard that they might they
don't poop oh well the guys you guys
can't ride the girls eat you don't know
the sensation didn't have butthole you
know what we're talking about though no
bouncing up and down to height like it
makes sense like if you think of like a
ketchup bottle but let's shake your body
so it's you shake your body but you have
to be super relaxed like you kind of
like after you bend your knees and like
yeah just bounce up and down real like
lightly but like why are we all doing it
it's like we're trying to try it right
now describe it to people without having
to show it if four people who are just
listen nobody's here describing it
you're like doing it because you can't
do it if you're tense right yeah you
need to realize I bet you people
listening when you're describing two
motions they're doing it too if you
caught yourself doing yeah leave a
comment like driving their car to work
yeah they're stuck in traffic and they
got a poop and that's your fault and
your fault well it's actually hard to do
without when you're sitting it's way
easier to be standing I don't know man I
just had an experience getting off the
plane today yeah today you your
pants huh almost okay so what happened
was midway through the flight like you
know how when the ride gets bumpy you
like turn on the seatbelt light yep and
you can they're like you have to stay
seated right yeah I had to poop right
when that happened and because of the
turbulence was giving me the bouncies oh
my god intentional bouncies and I was
trying to clench - okay so that's when
you that's when you have to poop yeah it
works I'm just saying we don't have
that's the strategy we used to use dude
is like TMI but third time I pooped
since I got here that's awesome dude
good for you Ryan's jealous very active
bowels
that's my usual you know but ever since
I was on this keto diet its reduced to
about two two times a day that's not
pretty good it's good for not for me but
for I guess then yeah normal people I'm
pretty sure the podcasts in here the
dogs yeah
we didn't lock them up so so you ate
have you missed the dogs though did you
miss the dogs more than us
yeah that's the bait of all right you
know what you're just trying to lead in
for a joke you know no I wasn't oh that
was actually a comment or tweet I saw
that so I was like did you miss Morley
oh actually I read that yeah oh yeah so
you got all the questions already well
we can ask you well I read some I just
had a people want to know okay so we can
go through some of those questions in
fact we should do this go to our Twitter
or Instagram off the pill at off the
pill and if you have questions for the
next one
not that we know who that person is yet
who the guest is gonna be a bit to send
us stuff for now we have questions
asking about Shawn and the first one I
have is can we kind of answer that did
this first huh all right this is a this
is an easy one what's your favorite
video that you've been in it gonna do
that that I've ever been in a youngin
it's a simple one uh and the Nintendo
one remember end of Xbox all that a
Nintendo paper one yeah yeah got it okay
well that's a simple one that one's cool
well no no I have to take that back I
think my favorite was the how to be
ninja 2.0 oh really
Alan was fun yeah it was it was one of
those videos but I like yeah I was like
cool I don't I don't need to learn the
script yeah I actually liked our
sequence or an action sequence yeah it
was like fun those fun making it on the
spot yeah yeah I just remember like
scratching you okay this is another one
what was this is from Bianca I don't
know if we're gonna put these tweets up
but this is from Bianca just saw moi
I don't know what was a secret too long
best friendship with Ryan what do I
don't know what is the secret to bet it
just has a lot of likes so I'm gonna
read it okay a long best friendship with
Ryan what was this like a long
friendship yeah they want to know how to
become best friend cross that line a
fanship and become French I don't know
if that's why they're asking it's too
late I made it that question okay okay
well but we weren't like that's hard
fans know you're fans of each other
is pretty cool man did we did not say
that there's no way all right what how
did how did it go down then well for one
we have a interesting reading pass -
yeah
share it with the class well I mean just
to start I mean I think our our
relationship is kind of like we could be
not friends for a long time or like not
not friends but we could not hang out
for like years or talk or anything and
then once you see him when you're free -
we'll hang out you know like just like
nothing ever happened and I feel like
some friendships work that way
I don't know and some you just if you're
if you're not talking to them like
consistently they just forget about you
and you just never see them ever again I
think it's because like everyone kind of
has like a preference of what a
friendship should be like or if you know
it's kind of like the love language
thing like you receive love and like
affection in different ways than other
people I think for you and me it's we've
always had that friendship despite not
talking to each other and we're
perfectly fine with that
yeah and we still hold like a very deep
friendship mm-hmm despite everything we
don't need to talk to each other every
single week or like even every year yeah
but we didn't talk for a long time even
even when you when you were in college
and then you know it's like oh if you're
back home then we'll go hang out yeah it
was like nothing change and yeah yeah I
don't know what the secret to that is I
think it's just being both parties need
to know like it's nothing personal you
know if we don't reach out you don't
have to reach out to somebody and check
it check in on them like every single
like month just to maintain a friendship
yeah I think some people need to do that
but I don't think we need I mean we
don't need yeah because we understand
like okay you're doing everything I'm
doing mind if you happen to be the same
town we're gonna hang out yeah and you
know with like social media and stuff
like you can look from afar and still
like give someone love yeah and still
respect them and still be friends with
them without having to call them up
every single day I was just talking to
Paco about this I was like yeah dude
like I know I don't reach out to you all
the time but just know that I'm always
watching from afar and I carry dude yeah
I see his Instagram likes and you know
watch my storm like my boy Shawn yeah
see but like that's some people actually
get offended yeah that stuff I know so I
think if you learn if both parties are
cool I think that's I guess the secret
if both people are have a mutual
understanding like
you don't need to check up every single
week yeah it's actually if you're not
like hanging out you know it's like
relationships you got to have that
mutual understanding you need to know
how each other clicks and what like each
other likes and dislikes yeah everyone
is different I don't think there's a
real secret to behind it it just kind of
worked out with us yeah all right you
nerds the reason so Shane won Greg asked
um what's your favorite anime why are
you doing like a X is that well because
it's a favorite meme anime I don't care
okay I just want to know what your
favorite anime what's yours Shawn
favorite anime it's got a mean art oh
yeah I would say of all time even though
I don't know why no to get so much hate
oh sorry Naruto you say it wrong they
make fun of you too yeah dude but anyway
yeah I would say that was probably like
my favorite all over time yeah we're
just talking about this too about how
animes like I feel like kids should
watch them to grow up not to grow up wow
they're growing up like we did I think
it's not all animes especially the ones
like the ones that people hate on like
DBZ or Naruto or my hero like it's all
all the protagonists the people that you
fall in love with the one that you're
following have really good morals like
they're just good people
yeah I think also they have big flaws
that are very very yeah and it shows
like oh you can overcome this time
exactly and that's what we're saying
like for Naruto he's like this loser
he's a kid who gets bullied no one in
the town likes him that's what it starts
off and it really teaches you like man
you got to work hard like the reason why
you respect him is like man it's so
touching cuz he just keeps pushing he
pushes through you know and any has such
this dark past and I think it's just it
would be good for kids yeah he makes the
most of it and he ends up becoming like
a cool guy yeah I don't know spoilers
yeah
those been done alright yeah but hi I
like I like Naruto they reflect a lot of
like real-life situations while you
canyon i don't really watch anime you
watch online I know I really want peace
you guys'll I did watch a lot I like
read a lot of it and then you read manga
you
but it comes in like burst III only
do it when I was like oh man this sounds
so lame huh but I would uh the first
types of like manga and stuff or
Japanese cartoons or whatever that I
would read was a lot of uh like harems
sad which is basically it's like one guy
a lot of girls and they're all trying to
fight for his love they caught something
else like not porn
no there's clothes on and stuff that's
hentai
oh and I was there but the reason why
hmm
no but the reason why the reason why I
liked those is because I was like man I
never felt like that I want to feel like
this guy yeah that's cool hey you know
what at least you're being honest dude
it's how she don't think of it like what
are some titles is there any famous ones
yeah there's like Love Hina which is a
huge one Ichigo 100% oh isn't that a
strawberry but uh Ichigo is not from
isn't that the the dude with the orange
hair bleach in that bleach no Ichigo my
trip in I think it's different
oh I'm not too sure though I'm just
showing like how lame I am right now
that's not that lame would you so many
people relate to that yeah I don't know
I think whoa come on let's just look at
all the enemy out yeah there's a lot of
like I don't know like fantasies yeah
you know fanservice oh yeah and service
that's what I'm about up skirts no I'm
strong huh kind of you're into that real
I was into it now I'm kind of like I
want to see dudes up skirts
yeah it's he's not even making a joke
yeah yeah it's just funny or damn whoa
all right next question from John
kool-aid do you really listen to off the
pill podcast in your own time well me we
have to and this is funny that you
brought this up cuz Shawna we didn't
think Sean even heard one I've already
made some quotes in and I know Sean
actually watches them because he has
references in them that we did not
expect him to know yeah trying to grab
some sleeves it would
that's a good saying yeah I like that
way I know it sound and it makes sense
yeah yeah and everybody's like oh this
podcast really grabs grabs my sleeves
doesn't quite work but it works yeah
that means you don't like the podcast
but you are quoting the podcast showing
you listen to the podcast saying you
don't like the podcast go ahead grab
your collar get um that's events um yeah
up close in person oh I'm quoting we'll
get um do you have another one for Sean
no we don't need to go through all these
there's a lot yeah there's a bunch
I thought we only had one page but then
this is do one more and then yeah it's
more fun to just talk I want to see this
I want to see this one what's that um
give it to me so it's cuz I'm conceited
and I just want to know how do you feel
about Paco and rhpc not give okay so
joke somebody actually wrote that but
here so this is one doesn't one um
who's someone that you miss the most why
and then the second question is why do
you miss me the least cuz that's the
obvious answer you know no not
necessarily you don't think I'll miss
you the least you should tell the people
what you said to Dana I think you went
to Papua jokes a lot clearly you know
when we're not when we're off-camera he
jokes a lot so I'll come back to that I
just gotta say I just heard something
today that he said to Dana yesterday
that I was I was a little blown away
about like damn you can't you could say
it to one of us but you said that the
Dana dude oh man
Dana is someone who gets I think the
least amount of love who probably
deserves some of the most don't back
yourself I gotta say this because a lot
of people don't really know too much
about Dana today yeah I want to give her
a hurt much deserved what Robert have so
many years yeah props yeah yeah so
that's actually one thing that she does
she does a lot of props she does a lot
of set design costumes costumes she
finds places
works like hand-in-hand with Greg
they're in a relationship but also like
you know exposed yeah but they they she
does so much for the group and anytime
you're like wow look at the production
value of it if it's not editing it's
pretty much Dana yeah if it's not
editing it's Dana so I'm selling she's a
hands-on genius
oh yeah she saves me so much money yes I
don't have to buy things she makes them
can you make this and shake oh I don't
know but sure and she'll make it yeah
and she saves me so much money maybe I
shouldn't be telling you her story but
the first time that you're gonna lean on
yeah the first time she visited babies
she was already helping yep yep she was
already helping you could tell when she
came into the company that there was a
shift in all of like a production value
I think Shawn what did you say when she
came in
you're just like because you were doing
a lot of the problems before yeah a lot
of it was me and like Derek and Greg
just running around trying to make do
and I think like we used to buy a lot of
stuff yeah and like you know like I
remember
Aquaman was like a big boy yeah it looks
so I tried my best to like find all the
stuff that kind of relatively looked
like it but once Dana was brought in
dude look though I mean you guys did a
great it was part of the joke you know
to have it look kind of wack yeah but I
was tough though Dana was good Dana's
good all right set design like
everything just looks so like I like
pleasing to the eye yeah she helps a lot
she graduated an interior design yeah
considering how much time turnaround
time if there was a lot more time they'd
be even better yeah but she doesn't in
like a Boyar no no we're moving on we're
moving on we give her the processor it
was a funny I mean I was just kind of
shocked me too happened oh man basically
so the will has a girlfriend named
Monica Wow and I she's been in videos
she's been in videos and she was like a
gymnast and she liked models and stuff
and she's like she's a pretty person and
someone asked oh why is Monica in the
group and I was like Oh Monica can't be
in the group you gotta be ugly to be in
the group and I told it skipped my mind
that Dana was in hey Dana was in it and
she was right there next to me and she
turned around and went
what did you say and I was like I was
like Dana you're like a solid for people
like were like shocked but laughing but
like more shocked honey
yeah Dana you could say it to us and
like call us a 1 and we'd be like okay
it's a quick yeah but it's just nice
people it's so Dana's actually someone
we can like she has thick skin she can
take jokes yeah like she's awesome
person and so today she like I was
asking her for help and then she's she's
like why would I help you you called me
up for and I was like that's a
compliment you're 3 at best but it
wasn't she wasn't laughing the same way
and it was like oh wait she took that
kind of serious it was a little I walked
I walked in on that part and I was like
that's a little cringy dude it gets
worse but not because of me because of
someone else but we won't say it's it's
it's you understand like this is a very
friendly place where we can we rag on
each other a lot yeah I I get it the
most so I'm able whoa yeah yeah we do we
do give it to you a lot but yeah only
because you I mean you set yourself up
for that I'm okay with that
I know it's part your comedy I know my
role yeah it is fun yeah it's fun for
all of us but I think now everybody that
group kind of has that guy though yeah
yeah usually the loved one like in TV
shows and something I hope gets fragged
on usually that's the character that
people love mm-hmm but not at first
everyone's like oh it's so easy to hate
him and then after a while you're like
oh yeah guilty for hating on this person
yeah yeah but I'm like now I think I
like it more because I know how to fire
back you do oh yeah you do I've gotten a
lot better
but before I think you were like that
guy and then sometimes you'd be like man
I wish I was like the one who was like
not getting picked up no we talked about
this yeah I was like dude that's you
don't realize you're getting the hooked
up roll bro like that's the one that
people fall in love with you know that's
the funny one you know you're getting
the good joke
I am I am I'm still single by the way
but yeah I'm waiting for that okay well
um if you watch Paco's video I've
watched all of them me too oh you watch
all my videos well no the ones the
recent one why did you post more no I I
just posted one Rosano I didn't watch
the latest one but no to the
relationship ones yeah yeah
and we basically lived it but yeah
that's I kind of missed it that was like
right when I left yeah it was actually
right when you left yeah it's like six
months ago because yeah I just met her
and then I left
oh yeah her like the first uh-huh two
times like maybe and then yeah yeah and
then that video came out yeah
long story short cuz it kind of there's
no context really for people who don't
know I was recently in my first
relationship ever as a 27 year old and
then basically she wasn't the person
that I found out to be found out that
she had cheated on me don't say names
yeah I'm not of course I'm not gonna say
names oh you never know I don't want
dumbass no no no no but yes so then we I
broke it off with her and like it hurt
me a lot but it also taught me a lot and
I just made a video about it I was very
introspective um and like Sean Sean said
earlier he's not someone who like goes
into it but he shows support from afar
and like when I picked him up today from
the airport it wasn't something that I
expected I don't ever expect any of my
friends to watch any of my videos but uh
he was like Washington yeah I didn't
expect that is good too that's a
surprise to me why it okay so when
you're being serious and not being your
normal self we're never serious dude
then it's like okay this is concerning
so of course we're gonna be there good
you know but like if you're happy and
being you of course we're gonna pick on
you like it's just a dynamic but
basically like it it showed me a lot
like help me grow as a person because I
was someone who was like oh love is such
a beautiful thing like you know it's
this fantasy and you should do
everything for it but that's not true
most first relationships are kind of
yeah that's what you expect yeah yeah
and and you you kind of learn at
while like oh you know not you're not
meant for everybody and everybody isn't
meant for you you shouldn't be you
should know what you deserve
mmm type of thing and you can you kind
of develop self-respect at that point
ya know what it is and you have to what
I had a hard time realizing over over
time with different relationships Oh
tell them not not every single there's
no I mean I don't believe that there is
a absolute perfect person for you
because even if you find your it you
know your soulmate or whatever if you
whoever you think that is the perfect
person they'd like all the things you
like whatever it is someone that matches
perfectly with you you're still gonna
have to work on it together because
there's no perfect relationship yeah
yeah of course but you know it growing
up you always think oh I gonna I'm gonna
wait for that one yeah or you know
Garvey's installation man movies man I
told you movies like ruin relationships
for in the beginning yeah and then you
learn okay this let's be realistic yeah
a good quote I heard was everyone's
looking for the right one but nobody
wants to be the right one who said that
I don't know I just saw it that's like
something I don't know I don't know just
like that one dude who I was like makes
those videos Matthew Hussey yeah he
takes things and oh yes he has things
that are like so deep and meaningful but
I got like whoa you bow I bet you we
could make one right now yeah you know
in life you got to be a piece of paper
ooh you're open to so many different
things it's not about what the paper is
it's about what you write on the paper
and tell your story on that paper don't
be a paper that's just you know I gotta
be an essay or I gotta be a math problem
I gotta do whatever it just being up
just be a free paper and just flow just
be you at the same time paper wears
paper come from paper countries be one
with the earth the organic be you be
genuine see we're making one right now
behavior yeah also what happens people
will be paper chasing so that's what you
want to be to people would chase you
when they find out your true value yeah
that's enough anyways
Shawn you are in a relationship I'm not
saying you're a guru or anything but
like I guess because like we said
earlier long distances very difficult oh
what is what are some things that are
tit on that what are some things that uh
you feel like really helps I guess you
know that overcome difficulties like
that communication communication and
mutual understanding is the biggest yeah
so most important things it's simple but
it's difficult yeah because you know you
need to be able to have an understanding
between both parties and understand what
you want as part of the relationship and
there's a lot of trust that comes behind
it - mm-hmm because you know because
you're long distance you don't know what
they're doing on there and right they
don't know what you're doing so you have
to build a lot of trust and a lot of
communication and be open to it I think
especially for guys were kind of like
you know closed doors but that is true
actually that's another guys I think
majority men are typically more closed
off as like emotionally you know so I
think a big part especially for me I
don't know about other people but for my
from my experience it was being able to
be completely open 100% to your
significant other yeah and being able
like even if there's problems there's
always gonna be problems but being able
to come to a compromise and have an
understanding and build that trust
between both parties right because
without the trust and it's hope it's
hopeless
yeah you know cousin really like if
there's no trust then why are you with
this person exactly but that's how
that's how it should be with or without
the distance yeah you know so yeah
that's good advice
how about you advice wise yeah I mean I
would say in in addition to that just
like knowing that you don't need to
always be right it's a big deal to Oh
tell them I mean it doesn't if you
really think about it and sometimes it
matters because it is what's right and
wrong if you come to that mutual
understanding it doesn't a lot of times
I think fights happen and continue
happening for no reason until you really
realize why am i fighting and you
realize like oh it's just because I want
to be right and
my point but that doesn't matter if you
really care about the person you can get
over that yeah so I think for me that's
something I'd to learn and I think that
causes and solves a lot of problems and
I want to add on to that a lot of times
when there's problems they're in a
relationship people think it's oats me
versus the other person when that's not
necessarily the case
it's like both people as a team against
this problem and you have to work
together to figure out like oh how do we
solve this issue you know how do we
figure out how we both can win we're not
I'm right you're wrong you serve me yeah
that's everything that mentality is very
like toxic and unhealthy for a
relationship when you can figure out
like oh even just the wording of that
yeah yeah sorry go ahead
you know I mean wording is huge yeah
everybody will pick at small things like
I can't believe you said this certain
thing when it's like okay stop thinking
so much about that both parties think
about okay how how can I help us get
through this together
not even I we I mean you yeah yeah but
yeah you know you can yeah yeah but why
you nitpicking me John why are you doing
this well you said I when I said to be
about us okay we just went super
misogynistic cuz we made the girls sound
like that well I thought you were still
being guys do you consider that to sound
like girls yeah alright time for peace
eNOS of the week guys last week yes so
you guys shouldn't be making you can
make those voices you can make those
voices but it doesn't mean I'm being a
girl I'm just being a guy yeah it was
just a Sean Dee's coming out I'm sorry
yeah I know so that's um don't assume
that that was a female voice okay yeah
don't and that was PC this of the week
now we're going back to PC ness of the
week I want to talk about this cuz this
is kind of big in hallways I know what
you're gonna talk well obviously I told
you about it right yeah
I just knew so a a recent thing that
came up was a Liam Neeson was in being
interviewed and during his interview he
had talked about how a close friend of
his was raped and just this is like
years of years ago decades ago or
something like that the interview just
happened yeah yeah and he talks about
how he asked
his friend like oh do you know who this
was what race was this person and she
said black so he essentially and I'm
paraphrasing a bunch of stuff but
essentially he went out and looked for
somebody of black color to attack and
like he wanted to kill them for like
about a week and half I think it was
more so he was looking for someone to
cause an altercation with him so he
could really he could react and and and
he said in the interview right
specifically a black person yeah yeah
and that's where all the controversy
came from yeah because if you were to
stop that story there which most
headlines deal we'll get into that more
but go ahead but continuing the reason
why he was sharing this story and it's
basically after a week to week and a
half he realized like what am i doing
like this is this is dumb this is
foolish and he said he went on to say
that he's ashamed that he thought like
that that revenge is never the answer
and that we should learn from this right
but a lot of people wanted to skip that
part yeah skip that part
nitpick at certain things and just go
out to say like Liam Neeson his races
yeah because back in the day he wanted
one black guy did something to his
friend and allegedly to allegedly yeah
yeah and he was so angry that he wanted
to kill a random black guy yeah even
though that's not the full that's what
the headline would read yeah right and
then I could see because even when I
first heard that from you that story I
was just like good he's erased it like
that that sounds it's the easiest thing
to jump to yeah and then you hear the
rest of any like oh that's the context
yeah and it's like okay even if he
wasn't right he realized his wrong it's
a long time ago for one not that that
changes anything but most people leave
off the other end of that yeah and you
immediately jump to it cuz even I was
like that I was like if you just read
the the headline and you didn't read the
full thing or watch the video about it
it's very I mean it's hard to back that
up yeah he wanted to kill a black guy
it's true that's what he said
but it didn't have it the context behind
it and that's the part that I want that
we want to talk about at least oh no
what do you think about that
this is my first time hearing all of
this cuz I didn't actually watch the
interview but had some deep stuff first
of all props to him for even coming out
with that that's like a tough thing to
do at this point of time right now like
peace eNOS you know yeah yeah so you got
to get the men respect because he
realizes wrong see this and just even
you saying that to if that was cut out
from somebody they'd be like Oh Shawn's
racist too cuz he respects Liam Neeson
for even though he's a racist and that's
like that's just how it spreads and you
know why couldn't win friend groups to
they someone reads an article they might
not even read the with anything big hey
you hear well Liam Neeson he hates black
people yeah like that's kind of how
people talk in headlines people talking
head it's so like social media-driven
because we're taught like you know
that's what we need to grab people's
attentions right away that's why
thumbnails titles are like that and now
journalism is becoming like that because
journalism it you know is like hard to
maintain and get revenue you know so
it's like oh how do we drive people to
us yeah you have to jump on it now we
have to get people like oh what is this
thing maybe the more fully explained in
the article but very rarely do people
ever look deeper than the surface right
because there's so much stuff happen
that's why they could they call things
fake fake news yeah it's not necessarily
fake it's just they're not showing the
whole story or they're shorting trying
to push one side of it kinda and this is
kind of similar similar scenario to that
kid that kid that was wearing the mega
hat and I against that he was like looks
like he was standing on yeah in dude
yeah sorry are you an American holding
his drum in you know whatever
yeah but then when and I thought the
same thing I like Dan this kid I said
the same thing I feel bad now he was
just like everyone else I get tricked I
was like dad I this kid deserves a look
at his fate I want to punch him in his
face and then I watched the full video
and I like because I was told like this
oh this is not the full story and I saw
his interview after that um he's
standing there in a group of people
right there doing their own like school
chants or whatever like that and this
this Native American dude starts
pounding his drum peacefully like
nothing he's but he walks up to him and
the kid doesn't move he doesn't go you
know he doesn't move anywhere he stays
there and then we see him smiling right
and I saw the interview of this kid and
he seems like this shy like obviously
people are already gonna in Psych him
because he's a trump supporter yeah
or his parents or whatever but he did
not get in this guy's face like they
made the video look yeah and coming from
his perspective he said what could I
have done if I walked away I'm
disrespecting him I think is mr.
Phillips or something I don't remember
his name is if I if I don't smile that
looks like I'm trying to intimidate him
if and keep in mind this is in the
middle of he's a 16 year old kid yeah
this guy starts beating this drum in
your face you know that's kind of that's
way more aggressive than somebody just
walking up to you and smiling there's
there's so much like I didn't even know
all that I was like oh snap another
races kid yeah and I didn't I didn't
like him yeah I just judged him and I
was wrong yeah I don't think not that I
doesn't matter if he's a trump supporter
or not he did not do what people thought
he did yeah and like the headlines wrote
kid arrogant kid intimidates whatever
whatever and that happened like what a
week two weeks ago I don't remember it
wasn't that long it's very recent and
now we're on these like Liam Neeson
exact there's so much stunning uh I
believe like maybe within this week yeah
having this week yes like this past
weekend that the article might have went
out um but for so much information to be
constantly just thrown out there and
people still have lies people still have
to work you know have a social life
interact with friends how are you
supposed to be able to digest everything
fully and get like the facts from both
sides before making a decision
everyone is just so will so willingly to
just believe what they want because they
want to be like oh this is my side you
know I'm either a Democrat or a
Republican you know and this is what I'm
just gonna believe right and I'm just
gonna voice my opinion and support what
I think yeah I mean that's I mean that I
know a lot of my friends like that it's
nothing against them that's just how
we're how the media is has made us yeah
I think yeah I mean I think that's a big
part of it I mean how do you how do you
feel about the whole scenario I mean I
know you just heard about the Eocene
thing but you know what we're talking
about dude I have mixed feelings about
all of social media at this point like
marketing strategies and stuff it's very
uh I don't know what's the right word
for it it's very uh like brainwashing
cents or they make you focus on certain
aspects without giving the giving you
the full context and that was like the
whole like political thing to you know
like you know you can take snip like how
much can you fully understand the full
context of it if they're giving you like
a ten second video mmm versus seeing
everything that happen from beginning to
end and it's like the same thing with
like you know anything controversial
when it comes to like police videos or
you know political stuff peace eNOS like
everything has context behind it yeah
but people like you said people aren't
willing to nobody wants to have that
open conversation yeah and it's so
mind-boggling how people are just like
this is my view this is my view blah
blah blah blah blah blah and then when
someone else is like well this is my
view you're like no shut up you're wrong
you're wrong I don't want to hear you
you know yeah close you get just call it
close-minded you get called things to
instantly they people love to label yeah
just like oh you know just like I said
it's the holy omniscient thing it's like
we're not I mean we you know since we
are defending him because we're
defending him in in that not necessarily
him that we're defending that it was
told in a not inappropriately but it
wasn't told there's like misleading it
was misleading yes what it was and was
what we're not known we're not defending
his action we aren't no don't get us
wrong yes what he did before was and I
even and he agrees wrong is what I think
what we're more saying is that there
needs to be a better conversation a more
open conversation about this or before
we jumping on people and calling
labeling them racist which is a very
serious thing yeah like people are so
easy like they use that word like it's
nothing now it's it's it's actually
lessening the word it harms people who
are affected by racism yeah because it
means almost nothing now yeah it sounds
bad they're gonna take that clip and say
Ryan Higa says racism means nothing
right but you know I mean that's that's
the thing though it's I think it's we're
so close to labeling people and I'm not
close to where it's so easy to label
people with in this day and age and
people do it all the time and I think
before we do that we should really get
our facts straight
yeah yeah and including me because I
felt like I said I fell for the same
thing twice same here and I just wanna
they're there were actually people who
were talking on this article a little
bit more deeper and one of them was an
English footballer
or you know for soccer player
john barnes who more in detail talks
about it on a news interview and like
the way that he presented it was like so
much more insightful you know and it
really drew to like let's have this
conversation even even Terry Crews right
who was like let's let's you know cuz
black people were attacking him yeah
like Oh Terry Crews like you know you're
gonna get canceled you're not on our
side but all this stuff but Terry Crews
was saying like I'm not condoning his
actions he's describing a situation so
what do we do
he wasn't saying like let's do this you
know he wasn't trying to say like oh I I
have the plan for everything
he was asking his fellow people like
what do we do about this in let's have a
conversation yeah let's figure this out
what's the answer and so many people are
just like oh you don't have the answers
you're wrong you don't have the answers
that I want you're wrong that's just how
it is that's how it is nowadays it's
especially once you pick a side yeah I
mean I'm trying to find a relatable
scenario where once you feel like you're
on one side you hear things differently
oh wait say you're MGK fan or Eminem fan
right you're naturally gonna be biased
oh yeah and you don't you know that why
can't we just see it think see things
we're saying why can't we see things
from both sides and it makes sense
everybody has a bias and I think they're
people need to be people need to at
least acknowledge that they have a bias
so that I think that alone will help
them realize like am I being biased or
is this actually a hundred percent
believe in this yeah yeah I think that
might help and it's also it's easier
it's easier to just like be honest I did
not listen true I think that's a huge
thing a lot of people just like yes so
much easy especially the popular side
yeah yeah it would be so much easier to
be like you know what he was wrong
that's not giving the better let's jump
on the bandwagon boycott his movie yeah
even though like like I said we're not
defending his actions we are defending
how he was portrayed I think in yeah and
I think that's what people are trying to
say yeah
same with that like that Magga had kid
it doesn't mean we support Trump but I
mean if you do great if you don't
whatever you shouldn't have to you know
that's that's all aside that politically
that has nothing to do with it
this kid who I mean really they'd
screwed him yeah he's just getting death
threats and stuff like that and the
narrative was completely false from what
I seen the videos that were cut out and
on the news channel and stuff like that
it's dissimilar it's a similar situation
yeah and I think in the same essence of
like look if we're wrong if what we're
saying is incorrect have that
conversation you know yeah like we're
not saying oh like like you know that's
why I like the comments that we have
yeah I've had lately where people are
addressing things that we're talking
about like neo incest thing like how you
know the last the one with Davey we're
talking about how the last episode how
oh you know why at what point does that
stop being you know because of the whole
peace eNOS there yeah at what point
maybe in the future it'll be acceptable
and people gave their opinions and
saying why we're wrong and I we'd read
them and we appreciate that like there's
no right like just talk talk have a cup
like Sean said have communication that's
why I was gonna relate the relation
right you know yeah well they work
together yeah it doesn't have to be just
cuz someone has an opinion
you know how was yelling at them and
change it how does insulting them help
them that's my strategy I mean that I'm
thinking about if the Democrats really
wanted to change or really want to do
something about Trump why keep insulting
him it's clearly like they say oh he's a
child he acts like a child you know he's
the whole government shut down he's
acting like a child
just cuz he's not getting his way why
are you insulting the child why are you
like why would you do that that's not
gonna work why don't you try to befriend
the child say you know what that's a
smart decision but here's some
alternatives yeah I don't think he'd be
more open to with his ego more open to
hearing that and then just being yelled
at like why would he change that's how
everybody is to you know if you like
more positive you work with them yeah
they're more likely to listen to you
exactly yep and it just so happens he's
the one in power yeah so even more so
why don't you just you know it's clearly
not working yeah I just trying to fight
him so why not I mean I don't know
enough I'm not smart enough but I know
why it's just why I don't see why it
does someone didn't take that strategy
like say what if this whole time Kanye
was actually a Democrat and he's just in
like sucking up and it's just like I
can't do it Kanye but he's like hey
Donald you know like I'm all for you
like ass
port you your smart guy you're awesome
and you don't trip he loves him yes he
because Kanye loves loves him what if
Kanye was just like a Democrat this
whole time
secretive right and it's all part of the
plan and he's like you know what this
whole government shutdown thing like you
know what let them have the win like
just you know I mean it's not a big deal
like the wall like we could build the
wall we don't absolutely make it that
big like it let's just let's talk about
it he would listen to Kanye more than he
would listen to someone on the other
someone yelling very sure yeah yeah I
don't know enough actually I'm not that
sure but doesn't that sound more
appealing don't you think someone like
how far these from what we see doctrines
would be don't you think that's more
appealing at least to somebody who they
consider a kid I think that relates to
like all problems in our lives when
dealing with someone else you just got
to be open-minded and you know yeah just
like a relationship come to a compromise
Yeah right because come on
are we really right or or wrong mm-hm
and if you're trying to fight so hard
for your side like are you really
helping you them and everyone else has
surrounded or are you interested or are
you just fighting for one side because
you want to be right like we said yeah
you know and then it all comes back to
relationships and so ultimately you've
got to subscribe to PewDiePie yeah and
you said t-series I said the BT so I was
like oh you're about to get
nine-year-old hate Oh anyway
shoot how do we get on that I just want
that we're talking about peace enos
that's what that's right dude that's the
first time you said how did we get here
no thank you
no a second time right I was like I was
less lost today yeah the other time I
didn't realize until I watched the
podcast back I was like I say that a lot
but I really was lost every single time
and I didn't realize I was saying that
anyway how do we get here dude we've
been going for a bit yeah it's been it's
been about an hour and should I say
anything else you guys want to bring up
I mean I'm Sean's here for a little bit
we could do another one honestly but
I'll do the second one I know maybe I
don't this is fun this is yeah I like
this one a lot of people are like oh
don't agro Bob
politics and who cares yeah it's my
pocket I don't know I don't either but
I'm still most knowledgeable about it
but yeah but we acknowledge that yeah
and also I think it's like there's no
we're giving our outside perspective I
think most people don't know a lot about
politics hmm a lot of people know stuff
and pretend to know more than they do
but really they're just watching
Facebook videos they're regurgitating
information they've heard exactly but
they only watch one side yeah most
people only watch one side yeah you know
head coach you need to be open-minded I
think I think we're gonna buy so cuz
we're raised in Hawaii we're we're
experienced us yeah you're kind of
forced to be open-minded yeah
and you and well-poised super laugh -
isn't it that's what I've heard yeah
yeah I pretty sure it is I think what
the culture like because we had to grow
up with a lot of cultures and accept
other stuff yeah look I I'd say we're a
little more open-minded to a lot more
things annyeong well at least for us our
group at least very different I don't
know about everyone but at least I know
between us 3 like we're a lot more
open-minded than mmm yep jumping on
dangled and like it's like super quick I
would agree
I would agree so do you hear um Sean's
accent we're actually talking that about
that a little bit I don't even notice if
I mean it if you I know what I've been
speaking pidgin not really no no no no
no okay but but he doesn't hear it
here's a light it this is what we're
talking about in the car and they're
talking about pidgin I was like his is
pidgin when we hang out it's kind of
like it's like that little piece of
parsley it's not too heavy
yeah but as soon as all three of us oh
yeah are in Hawaii we just have a kalua
pig plate he's like how easy bad I know
yeah it's like a switch it just goes
yeah people I I mean that's like when
people tell you like hey oh you're from
Hawaii can you speak pidgin like it
doesn't really work unless every but
someone's speaking - yeah yeah I mean
yeah it's like hey you're a comedian can
you can you make me laugh tell me a joke
something comedians can do it yeah they
don't want to they know it's not the
right context ah man well this is fun
this is really fun yeah it's been nice I
mean it's nice to see you again dude
it's been like half a year oh yeah it's
nice to be back yeah I did miss you guys
I think
I didn't we asked a question oh yeah
yeah we have waited a little bit but I
mean yeah it's just say you miss Dana
the month she needs was a mean person I
can't say there was anybody I missed the
most earlier you know favorite the most
you guys are all my family so you know
having aw I was something else then we
should close this up again I'm happy
with that ending alright same thing is
before Shawn I mean you were here but
you didn't go podcast yeah we always
exit with the maybe we should ask that
like from now on like our guests do they
have anything that they want to plug
that's true yeah is there anything you
want to plug other than trying to
getting trying to get a volunteer ship
or job internship or job I don't know
anything job or career yeah anything
about it okay we thought about a lot of
stuff that I wanted to talk about so
yeah awesome I'm pretty good dope well
thanks guys for having me thank you for
being here and we may do another if we
have time and if you guys have any other
suggestions for guests to be on off the
pill podcast don't I want my radio
don't just let us know yeah send it to
them force them okay sorry go ahead let
me go into my radio voice do you have a
nice voice pretty good I like that voice
it's over good guys if you have any
suggestions for potential guests in the
future to be on off the pill podcast
don't forget to follow us at off the
pill on Twitter and Instagram and tweet
at us
Walt right well while tagging your
favorite influencers just like kind of
like annoy them so that they have a
comment so they're like what is this
what's toughest cuz we're in Vegas yeah
so many of them are in LA but like I
just really don't want to do this then
you'd have to bring all of this stuff
over and yeah alright well like Paco
said thank you guys for tuning in to the
off the peel podcast episode 3 we'll see
you next time time to breathe no David
said it's actually really bad for the
mics to do that moisture but I think if
we put like the things do anything yet
we're still working on this podcast
we're gonna get better
all right that's cool