he punched his uh his monitor and the
cameras on the monitor so just you see
him yeah oh man what's wrong with your
face today they said to even in person
one one month two people were at it and
it was like one person would donate a
thousand and then it was two thousand
from the other guy and then three does
it I was like what is going on
should we clap for the cameras clap yeah
yeah this is how we've been starting
every single part yes
and we just cut to every angle okay so
welcome back to another off the pill
podcast we have two very special guests
this time we have David and half ooh
that was a good sound effect we're gonna
put something in like a little clap or
something I just did put in the sounds
of our claps just barely anyone clapping
I mean you guys can talk about who you
guys are like you guys are from the
streamer world that's how I want to
describe it from my understanding
David is a professional I can always say
it wrong but I say her heart the stone
not hearthstone not hearthstone players
hard to play but and Paco said you're
the number one player in the in North
America yeah or is the world on my
ladder ranking Yeah right now it's crazy
and then ha fou from my understanding as
well is the og streamer streaming before
you know all the little kids hopped on
Whaley was it twitch was it always
twitch that you were on yeah twitch for
six and a half years now Wow how long
has twitch been have you been never the
song I started like eight years ago I
was looking at the top trends I'm 16 oh
wow for the people who still stream now
I'm sure they're long yeah yeah yeah for
people who are still streaming now I'm
like 16th oldest
and dig pride in that is that good we're
just oh yeah we've been doing it for so
long do you know anyone I don't think
probably not but do you know any other
streamers that are just completely
different you not just give their names
how do they do it though for so long
because you have to stream for hours I
think some people have a persona and I
think they stream less so a nice dream
and if I do like a 15 hour stream by
hour 10 I'm not talking yeah zombie mode
that's my leg just like people don't
people love it right they're still like
I mean they're probably there with you
just chilling some people you know if
they have like a persona that they have
to they have to fulfill and I mean
that's even more entertaining to watch
but that's not all twitch is right like
there's a lot of different things you
can do right right right right that's
well said do you guys think that um
ninja is authentic or is he I mean have
you met him yeah we getting into it I
mean I'm just that's the first person
that came to mind cuz he's like the
biggest person biggest one on Twitter
yeah I think I worked an event with him
a few years ago but yeah I think he's
more or less the same but obviously you
give it a little bit more and I watched
too much of his four-night stuff because
I don't play for tonight right um I
think I think he's more or less genuine
and or like very true to his his normal
self I don't think he I mean you can
also have to like filter yourself a lot
but like not a lot but like a little bit
right like you can't be being like super
vulgar if you feel really angry you
don't want to like portray that right
right so you kind of have to like filter
yourself a little bit and try to get
yourself in like a better mood and yeah
it's just don't think that would be fun
to like if someone I really liked though
got super mad when they lost it anymore
that one streamer what's his name well
yeah Tyler one rage is like a shroud who
like punched his camera no no those are
out that was something
Samet he punched his uh his monitor and
the camera was on the monitor so just
you see him he's another one like the
really old streamers oh yeah I think
that's been on the platform for a long
time and he's kind of always been
themselves that's how he is Canada
summit rage see that was like my biggest
fear even for doing stuff like this I
always felt like you know even vlogs I
have to be so like hey guys like right
energy that's how YouTube was and it
just always been my style and it's
exhausting like nothing just talking
like this you could do this for a long
time I don't feel like if I had to put
up that that kind of energy for I
couldn't stream for like three hours
even yeah I mean that definitely makes
sense you're acting yeah that's it is it
is or super over exaggerated yeah if you
like strained out if you do that yeah
yeah but I don't know most at least me
and maymay are a lot of streamers
they're just kind of like hang out and
play games I'm curious are you guys have
you ever did myers-briggs the
myers-briggs test we took it for each
other I'm Steven s are you funny are you
guys what what all right do you remember
uh I know I'm like super extroverted
yeah you can see that remember I'm the
thing for the entrepreneur I'm like
close to that or the Entertainer like
one of those two and then David was I
don't know I think we're like INF I
thinking that you are an i that's why
I'm curious because that's usually
basically introverts get tired from
having to be around people I guess but
the because you're not you are with
people though I am with people that I'm
not with yeah right like I feel like I'm
not trying to like entertain I'm just
kind of like being there right like it's
like watching TV you can't really get
drained by watching TV so there's hope
see it is possible to be introverted and
stream streamer I thought it was like
there's no way introverts would last
it's too exhausting for them yeah I mean
it's a form of interaction yeah you're
interacting with people to a certain
extent so mmm-hmm
but well the the reason why I guess it
what's kind of ingrained in me because I
learned really a lot when I was a lot
younger
I guess high school time doing doing
videos and blogs and stuff like that if
I wasn't that character like if I wasn't
on and like happy everywhere I go in
blogs people are like why are you such a
dick why are you so mad right now I know
this is this is my face all the worst is
when it's like are you sick but yeah if
you don't make a bun yeah oh man what's
wrong with your face today they said to
even in person people wouldn't say it to
you in person though no I haven't had
that in person
oh maybe sometimes at school if you have
less makeup on we're like are you okay
today you feeling all right yeah well I
mean that's just like that just I mean
that's gonna happen to girls everything
online I'm sure you have some it's
probably such a different experience for
girls I would assume it's gotten a lot
better especially as the gap between
genders in gaming has diminished so yeah
yeah still fine so what are you
currently are you still playing are you
guys playing the same game stone and the
new expansion just dropped the content
still feels good going again yeah right
cuz you for a while when it was it was
kind of getting like I mean even you
guys were having a hard time saying like
oh yeah I want to play something else
sometimes but like I guess if they
created new cards or what they did in
the expansion it kind of changes
everything but doesn't it always end up
being missing yeah like there's like one
like really good deck is that Colin or
certain things it always ends up being
the same thing right it takes time to
like figure that out and that's that's
when it's really fun when people are
being creative and like you know making
decks and things but you're the guy yeah
I look at the copy they copy you yeah
actually God is so crazy yeah that's
crazy and whenever I play those kind of
games or any kind of game I'm all on
that guy who's gonna go with the
weirdest route
because I want to be different but it
never works like the smartest ways just
to look it up and then copy what they do
but still be more secure you can't do
that you're having fun you're that guy
who actually knows what he's doing and
gets to have fun green the new thing is
yeah I'm the same way I liked writing
something like really weird like find a
mechanic in it like can I make this work
and then so satisfied but all the pieces
of puzzle together and it's like yes
yeah so did you start um I don't know if
you already said this but when did you
start streaming ah
I started streaming four years ago I
think about four years ago yeah yeah
long time it was out of college I was
just kind of bored I was like myzel
stream what are you going to college for
biology degree that's pretty bad oh yeah
okay this sounds like me kind of but you
finished I did finish but I finished
like a year late I was supposed to
graduate like I don't know a semester
earlier but has it helped you in
streaming no but I don't going to
college yeah I mean it taught me how to
interact with people a little brighter
and take care of myself
not that I do that great of a job of it
but uh healthy
I mean I'm alive you know considering I
mean a lot like you said a lot of the
time you guys I don't know if we said
this when the cameras are rolling or not
but a lot of times you guys sit very a
long time er sitters they need to try
and think of something that the somebody
was talking about like when you sit for
a long time there's something really
dangerous about that I don't know if you
guys read that or not I was my entire
life style is terrible you guys look
fine like we don't leave our place to go
to work yeah that's like I feel like if
I had one of those pedometers mmm so
it's called the domitor never stops ever
starts it would say like less than a
thousand
within like a month because from my bed
to the bathroom to the computer and it's
just a cycle like that's it that's your
morning routine pretty much everyday
right most part as much as we can yeah
some days just want abstain yeah some
days you just don't feel it and like you
just don't do it you don't want to
spread that to other people right yeah
and you just any what you have to tell
people that oh you guys I'm not gonna be
I'm I'm not gonna stream today I just
got lecture today by a so when we watch
the nice dream line it was like you said
you would stream today and you didn't
even stream and then oh no I mean I just
found out I'm gonna do this podcast so I
didn't stream and I well thank you and
we apologize to your to your very
faithful fan yeah
that poor guy was a guy yeah and how did
they reach out to you if you weren't
streaming like sponsored stuff so he's
like almost like an assistant and say
okay he was like you should told me so
was it just waiting around I was like
sorry
wow wow that's interesting so they do so
oh well I guess he you guys kind of work
together then and you know yeah but you
met through like you man and there's
always ask people who are like in every
stream to help them like those are the
people you want because they're there
anyway right right right yeah so that
really is your lifestyle then I thought
you guys were exaggerating the last time
we know about that
I think people always think that we
exaggerate but no we are we're no life
yeah you enjoy it like staying home
right I mean I love playing I don't know
how I've gotten away with this lifestyle
for this long cuz ever since I was 17
and I was like well I can't do this
forever but I somehow I used to be a
professional World of Warcraft player
mm-hmm
Ted I'm 27 oh my gosh but when I
seventeen it's just so weird thinking
about that girl
yeah I feel so young but I'm old now
yeah
I feel young because I've had the same
lifestyle ever since I was young and
nothing's changed
it works I mean yeah you know in the
same way I mean I felt very similar yeah
I thought you know at the time it was
like youtubers careers lasted maybe
three years once they like kind of and
then I've had many down years and then
many up years is just like oh that's
very fortunate but it's not gonna last
cuz there's always gonna be someone else
the weird thing is that there were so
many more people coming to watch YouTube
that and I think it's the same with
twitch that even if there are other
people getting bigger there's just so
much people to you know there's just
some part one person the actual platform
is growing right right so there's more
viewers for you so it's not like anyone
else is taking anything away from you
right exactly and I don't think at the
time people thought of it like if
someone else is big you're done but it
kind of was because it was like people
would shift over but now it's like
there's so many people to go around like
everybody has their own personal tastes
I'm sure and he can consume YouTube like
you can consume multiple people at SIA
how to say it that like one viewer can
watch a bunch of youtubers right it's
like yeah you know a five minute or a 10
minute segment or even if it's like an
hour of content week it's still another
just like channel channel hop right
right I would say in streaming it's a
little different yeah you can die in
streaming because when you die in
popularity it's like you're competing
like one viewer can open a few streams
but they're really gonna be active in
one maybe uh-huh and so you if you lose
a viewer then you're you actually lose
oh they start watching someone else and
then yeah that person kind of takes over
so that's the obligation yeah you kind
of need to be on like one consistently
that sounds exhausting in my opinion I
don't know how it is in YouTube because
I do know that like peoples it's like
your total view count right is what
matters that well it's a lot of it is
watch time now oh okay that helps you uh
you know get suggested pose and like it
helps you basically stay more relevant
um so that's why people have been doing
longer videos and you can also get
better ads like significantly better ads
so you like double your revenue triples
sometimes so yeah it's it's heavily
based on that everyone should keep
watching yeah but I mean like that's I
mean that's one of the reasons why
podcast it's taken off you know and I
think people use YouTube in a different
way
and I think just in general
entertainment even like twitch like I
feel like five even like five ten years
ago it was it was nothing like nobody
wanted to just listen to other people
but I feel like they use even for me
like I use YouTube and listen to podcast
just what I'm doing other things just to
have somebody like not somebody there
but like just to have something almost
like background noise kind of right
right like I'm not there watching yeah
you're not actively watching you're just
kind of like yeah look it's a similar
thing that's kind of like the whole
trend that's happening from streaming I
mean I feels like that's like the
popular thing right now yeah I mean I
usually always have a stream on when I'm
on my computer and I just have it in the
background yeah right and it's like I'm
never like just sitting there staring at
those because you're not like actively
watching but it's like I don't know it's
a very passive thing for me also yeah
see I'll have yeah you'll have someone
in the background you're playing games
and like oh that's interesting or
something exciting happens when yeah
that's that's crazy so that is you're
okay so that's your lifestyle you pretty
much stream everyday you wake up
bathroom food and I know you guys have
you you get food delivered so you really
have to leave your house yeah that's
amazing
what was even crazier to me is that you
guys leave the house so little and when
you do you BRR or take a car or whatever
right once I was um I don't know if I
should tell this story know you can tell
me to stop once I was taking the two of
them home and I was like oh so wait do I
turn here for a little bit but it's so
crazy to me but it makes sense cuz you
guys don't need to leave for your job or
yeah yeah I mean I don't know the way to
the airport and I go to the airport a
lot that's true I guess if you yeah
right you don't really need to know
you're probably doing all this like on
your phone like you need
attention it feels really weird oh man I
wanna like another show on Twitch called
analysis northernlion Super Show and
they were like kind of interrogating me
because people finally realized that I
am that you boiled water and I was like
no never done it and it's because I mean
when I was younger we had one of those
like water boiler thing yeah and I make
my instant noodles that way like right
how I would and but yeah I mean I order
all my food and then I also drink
Soylent which is like a meal replacement
drink uh-huh and so that gets me through
like really long streams hmm did you get
sponsored yeah we have zero sponsors so
Soylent has to go Soylent yeah well
we'll see I mean I drink it like anytime
I'm in the long hours it's actually
sponsored does it actually make you feel
like you're uh like full it's 400
calories so it'll make you feel like you
consumed 400 calories and more
importantly oh man my okay this is bad
to say but my body doesn't like feel
hunger anymore I just get headaches and
that's how I know I'm hungry
it's very strict bad because I just tune
out my hunger because I don't want to
stop streaming especially when I first
started because I was always afraid like
if I stop streaming I'm gonna lose my
momentum you know I have to just keep
working because I love this job and
that's some crazy aggression and now I
know I'm like over time I think for
everybody especially when you're on your
your highs you know you want to make
sure like I got to keep this going yeah
you ride it right right yeah I think
yeah as long as people um I mean I think
for in everything you just have to know
not I truly believe it's it's a balance
to everything and not finding
getting too high when you're high too
low in your low you know one extreme or
the other in everything
how about for you David uh I'm a little
bit more well-rounded but not as much
especially this past year I've just been
working a little bit but I mean that's
fine I mean we just like hanging out all
the time and yeah I don't do much I eat
and I sleep and I scream what would you
do if I've got every mess it up every
time
hearthstone mm-hmm doesn't become as
like let's say another game comes out
and I heard some becomes less relevant
yeah you still try and stick with it
which what would make you take the leap
I'd probably just play whatever I want
to play you would I think I played I
want to play I mean I do I do for the
most part like I'll put in hearthstone
or as long as I want to play it and then
I'll play something else you want to
play DotA but you don't want to stream
it it's cause it's like my relaxing time
right like it's it's something that I do
to like I don't know I get embarrassed
but like he's very good though yeah I'm
like pretty good but like it's it's more
for like myself right like there's
things that you do for yourself and like
and you don't really want people to see
makes sense yeah but I'll stream
everything else yeah I don't really care
from bad you care about your views uh
yes that's what I'm saying yeah you
wouldn't really do just like I feel like
your account matters because it's ours
it's like otherwise it's not that you
care about like the money or anything
like that but it's like to be able to
care about it a little bit yeah and I
always ask people I like but you should
just stream what you want to stream and
I'm like okay would you go to work if
you got paid half the amount they're
like no I'm like okay well yeah yeah I
mean and that's the thing too is like
people I mean you can say even for
myself you can say you know it's not
about the money but you still need money
- yeah I think I think people are
starting to I mean at least in the
YouTube world they kind of get that now
they know it's heavily involved it's
about it's a balance like you said yeah
you're balancing between probably what
your viewers want to see and you want to
play it have fun exactly I mean you you
play games with less viewership right
yeah yeah my numbers we're like one
third literally one third so I usually
like three four thousand viewers
okay so what were you playing like
thousand do you think it's cause of the
games your fire battle right I mean yeah
they're just like less popular but and
I'm less good interesting like we play a
hearthstone and people will watch
because of our good watch and learn
where's like why the hell would I watch
his good play
batteries she sucks I'm sure he just did
like IRL streaming like people would
still be very interested in that too
right because they don't get to see you
in that realm like they don't get the
season every day we did a little bit she
did IRL Street my best friend we went to
Japan and we are else named a week there
right
I know it's it's exhausting that's
exhausting because why moving if I go do
one thing like if I have like a doctor's
appointment that like stresses me out
like ooh bring out and going to the
doctor's appointment and coming back
Michael that was my day people uh-huh
I'm lazy you can be a lazy extrovert
that's I look very very lazy extra
weight and I mean I liked I liked
hanging out with Becca so that was great
but just like you have to keep doing
something interesting you have to like
you know go to the next place and you
can never just sit a lot of activities
right like yeah you don't think they
would be cool with you just not doing
much um maybe but that's not the point
of being in Japan or like
[Music]
yeah well I mean I feel like at this
point if they're watching you long
enough it can't just because you're
skilled like they must just like you for
you and there's a basis of my viewers
that will watch me play anything and
that's why it's like the other people
just want to see how good you are at the
game or right something like that sure
for me too like when I watch certain
streamers I'm watching them to play a
game and if they play something else I'm
not interested really if you suddenly
I'm trying to think of an example for
YouTube uh-huh if you started hmm like
if you tried a singing career do you
think people would be as interested I
think there would be initially because
there'd be like this is funny I know
what you mean same thing with this
podcast why are you doing this but it's
gonna happen I mean I get it I get it
but then you might find people who are I
mean like anything you know over time
it'll build ideally they might like you
their streamers do variety all the time
right I don't think okay I'm not I
always say this and I'm not fishing for
compliments but I don't think I'm like
the most personable person I think I'm
okay but I think people watch me because
of my gameplay and that's okay right
like everyone has their reef they like
their niche right and they have their
strengths and like day9 can stream
solitaire or minecraft yeah I think for
me yeah I mean like gameplay
yeah people watch me because I'm good at
the game and I watch me because I'm like
the most entertaining person in the
world and that's fine yeah that's fine
yeah interesting that is interesting
though that's like kind of mind-blowing
to me actually I thought it was and you
like a lot of people are just naturally
drawn to you and you can make anything
fun right so well not necessary I'm
hacked
I've tried streaming before like a long
day you guys remember when um blog TV
was a thing no
okay so that was like an you stream or
on that time it was a block TV like paid
basically all these youtubers back in
the day to just stream like you don't
play games you just talk right ten years
ago right yeah and it was just the most
awkward things it was like a minimum of
like three out to three hours like twice
a week and it was like the most
exhausting thing that I had to do it was
super awkward
because at the time - I didn't they I
don't think you could do the
picture-in-picture thing live like like
show what you're doing oh I'm sure you
could I just most people didn't do that
or know how to do that and I just felt
like okay I'm just not a streamer I
guess I'm not good at this yeah I mean I
think some people naturally the fact
that you've been doing it both of you
had been doing it for so long it's clear
that you guys I'm sure you guys realize
that you're gifted at it it's not
something that anyone can just do I felt
really weird and awkward the first time
I streamed I think that's normal for
anything even with YouTube I'm sure it
wasn't completely natural at first and
then it became natural right like it
became more and more but what I'm saying
is I think like if you really want I
feel like you have the skills to switch
to anything don't you think because you
know thanks after doing it for so long
you know what people want to see and you
know alike you know the ins and outs of
street listen oh yes there's there's
ways to do more there's always a way to
do more but you like we've talked about
the balance is like the balance between
what you want to do and like what you're
willing to do for more right yeah
whether that's money or viewers or
whatever it is
mm-hmm so when you guys are not you know
I mean just chilling hanging out and
stuff like not streaming what else do
you guys like to do I know you say you
stay at home but I'm sure you like I
mean do you watch any of shows watching
shows Netflix yeah that's like Oh
marvelous mrs. Mazal yeah we just
watched that is that it's a show on
Amazon Prime
it's like free free Amazon Prime users
but it's it's about like a Jewish
comedian
cuz the girls a movie or is it oh
actually one thing that just happened on
Twitch is now you have a bounty board
where you have like sponsor deals come
directly through twitch did that for you
- probably not maybe YouTube bringing us
deals yeah yeah yeah oh okay well now
there's um
I mean twitch did that before right deal
this one's through this one's through
twitch the client there's a like there's
a page you can go do and it will show
you your rate and it'll be based off of
your concurrence it's like a bounty lit
like a list it's little bounty board
that's funny and it'll be like play a
trailer for like I I did one for
homecoming which is like um a new series
on Amazon Prime and all I do is watch
the trailer on my stream for free
wow this huh have you guys seen Fairy
Tail the anime no but I I think I've
watched a few episodes I couldn't get
into it are you into it not I mean I
watched I got into it for a little bit
but you got kind of repetitive that's a
um but date that's system is very
similar to that in that show they do
like a you have a board and you pick
missions requests yeah yeah but that's
such an interesting concept
I don't think YouTube has done that no
it's pretty cool it's like a it's really
nice game deal I didn't know that you
did it right though you recorded it
it'll shame you activate the bounty and
it will change your title for you and
then someone else
well I'm sure on Twitch checks that you
actually did it and then you do as many
as you want there aren't that many right
now oh I have like five available like
two or one but I mean I just asked my
viewers I'm like have you heard of this
game is is warframe any good and they're
like oh I play it it's fun I'm gonna
play it when you do ads like that oh
they don't get upset some people are my
viewers are better
about it than his view but I don't do it
very often
it's so crazy I would think yours would
be my viewers are kind of fickle because
like most of my viewers are from like
I'm like usually the number one or
number two spot on hearthstone so it's
mostly just people who don't always
watch me they just kind of watch the
game of arrival they are always number
two or number one I used I used to have
like a bunch of rivals I like made a
list of people but I want to be like to
rise up like extreme at certain times I
would try to be very entertaining no I
don't really care as much because I'm
just kind of it's such a luxury just
again I really need to just the best I
lose like a third of my viewers if I'm
streaming while he was streaming because
it's like a incident right YouTube
that's I was saying before it actually
matters because like if you if you're on
and I'm on and you're bigger you're
literally taking my viewers right and so
I usually stream like the night shift
when no one's around and no one wants
that spot competition you're the number
one person at that spot number one I'm
like the number two person but it makes
sense though so do you find that because
you're doing that you have more fans in
like other countries yeah yeah no I I
looked at my demographics they have that
on Twitch and I'm still mostly American
Muse kind of crazy time so what time is
this cuz you sleep it really strange
right
I try to ideally I would start around 11
or 12 st yeah yeah 11 p.m. PST and then
I would end around like 7:00 or 8:00
a.m. PST
and I'm still mostly American but I mean
I stream all I streamed every time slot
and that you can think of because I'll
do like 15 hours streams then that's
crazy
there's no way that I mean I'm hitting
every time we've learned so much I
should have been taking notes this is
like a very educate this is like not
even for like
for me to learn Wow we have been blowing
yeah you take the shishi break no you
guys need to let me call it the shishi
break no but every time you think every
time they say do you need a bathroom
break them like do I have to wait do you
though we could take a quick one quick
break quick all right she she break
their back heading back and we're back
from the she she brings the she she
break is over Hoffa was just asking us a
a like a rope would you rather kinda
okay this question I really like I
always ask everyone and it's you have a
100 sided die so if you've ever played
while slash role okay and you roll a one
you die a painless death I wonder what
it would be if it was a painful death
yeah one evil a pain you you die a
painless death
you roll anything else you get a million
dollars do you roll a painless death
painless death wonder how much of that
changes people's ante it changes my know
what yeah I mean I think yeah yeah I
mean if you're not getting tortured I
think I would roll really yeah million
can you up it a little bit I mean it's
yeah if you want to do torture question
like if you would roll then it would be
at what number would you not roll and if
it's like if you wouldn't roll then out
what number or what percentage what do
you know I would do I would roll for 10
million percent 1 percent what do you do
painful then oh paint like how painful
are we talking talking about like a
stubbed toe or like it's gotta be
tortured I like sent a buyer painful
yeah yeah
burn the witch see that I wouldn't do i
wouldn't roll yeah
one thousand two still you still won do
it no million out do it one hundred like
this there's gotta be there's a number
out there come on hard but like even a
thousand yeah pretty hard but like what
do you do one in a hundred for infinite
money one in a hundred painful painful
death you know I wanna do it infinite I
would probably do it infinite money is
infinite I would probably do it well the
thing is it nothing to logistically let
people know the people know because then
your whole life becomes horrible when
you have the most money that is true
what if you just have the ability to
reach into your pocket and grab a
hundred-dollar bill and no one else
knows check a check check well no the
money you bought a card okay no one
knows no one knows no one knows and one
in a hundred for a very painful death
the infinite sign that's it no one knows
that even the bank I don't think I would
limit less credit card forever it's
doing I would do it I would do it one in
a hundred what if you what if you land
on it then your dad didn't know you're
not just dead you get tortured but if I
don't everyone around me their life is
it's over dude
I can buy anyone anything forever
forever would you could but you would
destroyed the economy and if that's not
kind of it factors that come each other
it is a lot of power see where were
those people when you ask those like
questions that we make we ruin the game
see taxes it's a person that just says
yes it's just like yeah okay
and then they're gonna be assassins
coming for me I could pay for bodyguards
does this last until I dam and the other
million dollar questions if you do roll
how many times do you roll some people
go crazy there like hunch of time till I
die for a million right you get the
pitiful one do you get a give the money
away if you've like you've successfully
rolled it's not like I can do this it's
not like I want to kill you for is the
die right now if we had that right now
that might convince me because chances
are is not gonna lie on a one I know you
don't have to roll the dice to know it
one percentage but things happen man
[Laughter]
if you had the money beforehand I would
like go to every like religious thing
and everything that is true actually
yeah I like that one that's a good one
yeah nobody ever heard that the
questioner they're like asking my twitch
at is do you think for us it's a little
bit more personal do you think you're
the smartest or smarter than the average
person in this room so for viewing this
room I thought about that same question
before a lot of times not just in the
room but just in general
mm-hmm and so the reason I thought this
was because of Kanye actually and even
though some people might this is the
easiest comparison and the most recent
even though most people think he's an
idiot and he might be maybe he is a
genius you know the fact that he can't
communicate it to enough people is that
still considered intelligent what I mean
is if you're like me Albert Einstein of
our generation like say you're not
however Highnesses you're someone else
but a genius on that level of that IQ
but nobody can relate to you are you
still intelligent are you still smart
because you
can't convey what what defines how you
do everyone smarten their own way right
right like you probably wouldn't be very
good a hearthstone right yes Martin you
a hearthstone Zach but when it comes to
YouTube content and what if them
actually really good everybody's smart
in certain ways I think it's a hard
thing to answer but if you're talking
like book smart are you talking like but
you know some people are smarter than
others yeah they're that you know the
other person is smarter see but there's
some people I think of and like I really
thought up because I have thought about
this before like it's just dumb but he
has a really smart face though right
just like maybe there's they have to be
really good at something else that I or
maybe they're just so smart that they
just can't communicate to me you know I
mean like maybe they're just geniuses
and they do communicate that's true they
could also be like really ditzy but they
could be a straight A student in
everything they've ever done I've met
this name right so you are they stupid
are they smart you never know like
there's also the people most people who
are those like super smart straight-a
people a lot of times they don't have
common sense
so is that dumb that's a good question
actually I mean the only real like way
we have determining smarts is like
school right it's like the grades in
school for most people I don't know how
does like how do I Q test work I don't
even know that's trainable for any test
yeah like you can study for the SATs and
you'll do better right right doesn't
necessarily mean you're naturally
smarter than someone yes I don't know
unless if that's what G if we were going
by numbers and it's easy that you say oh
I got a better score than you yeah maybe
if he's got score a higher IQ than your
brain is capable of achieving higher
than someone is lower that's what maybe
that's other thing is this such an
interesting topic because and I only
thought because I was running a video
bulk on you and it's not not the only
read it was before this yeah like
just writing videos in general just like
thinking like a lot of times I'll have a
script that I'm really happy with I'm
like no one's gonna get the reference
it's like no one's gonna get the it's
too it's too much like it's like you and
I said kind of like dumb it down I do
that's what I'm saying it's almost like
I say dumb it down but like that's how I
see it but it's actually smarter to
people if I do it that way and it's like
if I'm trying to communicate right for
me to put out a video that less people
understand minority understands it's
actually dumber of me even though I
consider to be smarter because it
doesn't reach or communicates it as many
people it makes because more people can
understand it right be Dumber if you
made a joke that only two people got
right everyone be like this is not funny
it's stupid yeah but then it's but in my
opinion I might be like oh this is smart
because right for me this is like
brilliance yeah but at what point you
know of your genius do you realize
you're actually dumb if you can't convey
that stuff to them but you're an
entertainer that there's a difference
when you're doing it to entertain and
there's a difference between I mean like
figuring stuff out
yeah I mean just talk like I'm dumb when
it comes to cooking Dave I mean I don't
cook so I can't really but doesn't
necessarily mean experience experience
yeah like if you just because you don't
know how to do something doesn't mean
you're incapable it doesn't mean you're
incapable but you're like dumber than
the other person who knows if you can't
do something well maybe they'll isn't
the best word so what is what is being
dumb then something I would say unable
to learn I think the learning is the
smart play so we're people who can learn
really fast early the smartest people in
the world it's it's about if you're able
to learn and to wit to what depth you
can learn right you can learn how to do
anything but like I could learn how to
cook right but I could I learn how to
cook like you know like could I become
that good and I think you can yeah I
would say dumb is kind of a relative
term
- like where you are in terms of
learning something so like you could say
someone is dumb who's like just hasn't
learned as much as you right that's kind
of like what we use a hard thing down in
like if we're talking about us in this
room yeah like which is the original
question yeah I really don't I mean like
I like it relevant no I think about the
Kanye one because that one's pretty
interesting - well that's the thing he
probably I mean he describes himself as
a genius yeah you know and whether he
might be maybe we're just all not smart
enough to understand what he's really
trying to say some people do understand
him you know you could say that about
where they say him Kardashian
all right or any of them any of the
Kardashians like are they dumb are they
stupid or they're brilliant because were
there yeah insanely well yeah and you
look at how they communicate with each
other and I think okay that's a dumb
person but they're not dumb yeah it's
all part of the plan I don't know like
this one I think a good example is like
Paco he's actually likes to he's
actually a lot smarter than he looks
he portrays portrays he likes to portray
I think it's a defense mechanism that
he's something that he's not as smart as
he really is a lot of people do it yeah
in the room yeah no but I mean like I
think I think it's it's it's so you
think maybe what I mean though what you
in Jenner in a general sense do you
think that is magnitude to Kanye West
and some sort like in what do you mean
he now that made me not a defense
mechanism but he wants to portray yeah
maybe maybe he's like is super like a
genius but yeah it could be that tracing
that many layers deep yeah but I I think
I think I don't think he I think he
actually is like he is a really deep
thinker it's pretty clear than what what
the things that he does say yeah but
sometimes she goes so deep into it that
the fact that he doesn't know how to
convey that to the average person you
know he might be a genius but I still
consider that dumb at that point in the
same way is I would not put out a video
that I person
think is really smart unless if I dumb
it down because if it doesn't apply to
people then what am i doing like I'm
just doing a dumb thing so he's going
too far into and he's not dumbing it
down I think that just dumber smart
that's the easiest way to describe it
interesting and I think sometimes
whether he knows you know he knows how
to dumb it down or he just thinks I'm
I'm appealing to people who are thinking
on my level I don't know why he would do
it but clearly he knows how people react
so he's doing it on purpose yeah you
know lissa t but you know that too
that's so crazy or you could just be
dumb I mean anyone like that I feel they
have to be smart in certain ways right
but it it just depends on how you would
define smartness I think we've already
said that yeah yeah I think being smart
and being knowledgeable are different
though true and I think people confuse
it to you so how did you describe smart
I think the process of learning process
of learning okay
capability of learning to be able to
pick stuff up and then and continue to
yeah understand things at a deeper level
yeah okay like the depth
I think the depth of which they can
understand things and learn things it
whereas knowledge is just memorization
in my opinion hmm but it's it also the
ability to learn these things and convey
it I actually think you know I think
because I actually think I understand a
lot of things at a deep level but I also
have a very hard time conveying what I'm
thinking a lot of times I think that's a
different skill set right right but
maybe you can be smarter one thing and
dumb and the other yeah yeah
comprehension kind of that's like what
you struggle with right like you we're
talking about this with a PhD we're just
like if you read something then they ask
you what is it say you go well what is
what like I just completely forgot it's
kind of similar yeah it's it's just that
well that's a little different I think
um I think I just I think in that way I
just learned
different ways from other people no yeah
I mean everyone learns differently too
right I remember like some people are
visual learners and some people are word
learners and they need an index cards
I'm definitely like visual or just do it
and then learn yeah experience I can't
when people explain something to me I'm
like it doesn't even matter whether
they're just like words that just tell
me but uh yeah need to see it even when
I'm like writing it's like so much
easier if I like put things in certain
places just visually so I can keep track
of what's what you should show you
should show your work I'd want to see
how you like come up in the video
oh no it's like school and it's so like
it would not make sense
cool it's entertaining notes and you
just be like oh this is gibberish pretty
much new just words no that's great I
people should comment if they want to
see that I want to one day uh take a
screenshot or something I've had some I
mean you you guys have seen some of like
I make my little note cards for like
when we do those conspiracy videos where
everything has to connect that I
literally have to draw out because it's
just too much going on in my head to
like figure out beginning middle end and
all that stuff yeah I guess we're all
visual learners then are we I don't know
how do we I mean I mean your left hand
is your right brained for sure but I do
I'm ambidextrous I do everything with my
right that's physical yeah but you know
your right brained cuz you're very artsy
and you're thinking that way maybe I
think most left-handed people are right
brained rights the right brain is like
the creative side left brain is
analytical I think I'm more left brained
I think I am - you're definitely a
little brain happened I think you're
sure especially for what you do like
analytical and Barry just like so oh my
god because I'm playing in a tournament
this weekend for hearthstone and it's in
constructed mode I usually play rina
mode they're two different modes AHA and
explain explained the
constructed is you have 30 cards that
you can build like you build a deck and
you choose all 30 cards so yeah it may
choose out of the 30 no you choose you
have access to all the cards you choose
what you want in your deck like if they
gave you booster packs you open it with
your packs maybe if infinite booster
packs and you can make a deck so you can
make the ultimate arenas different you
get offered like three choices and you
pick of the three until you have a 30
card deck right which is a draft right
yeah yeah so I'm an expert in draft mode
for hearthstone and so I'm trying to
learn constructed I've played for 4 days
now and so I have the best coach ever
but he's been playing with me and we're
just like talking through plays and
sometimes I got so impressed there's
like such a big brain sometimes
sometimes sometimes so oh my god like
wow to see inside that mind yeah it's
not just like oh he's just know there's
a there's a science to it
I'm assuming there has to be method to
his madness to learn anything that quick
that big you're entering a tournament
that's crazy yeah yeah it's a rank I
mean top 25 in it North America I can
make 9 to legend in like two days which
is a you go from rank 25 to rank 1 and
then I drink 1 if you win there you get
to legend and in legend like the lower
rank legend you are it's like a ranking
system it's certain position in the
service ranks are like levels and then
once you get to legend then it's like
the higher the number that's always
higher than the number the better this
is in the new mode that you just rented
yeah yeah I mean I've hit legend in the
past but it's not what I stream it's not
like my expertise and then I was 14
hundredths Legend and for some reason I
just kept winning
I just kept winning and David woke up
was like I'm ranked 400 and then the
next day the next day I started
streaming from like
ring 400 and when he woke up was like
I'm ranked 40 mean I will say everyone
that I've ever met that is so has some
kind of serious interest in card games
into some ascent mm-hmm they're always
they always have like a very intelligent
mind you know I think it just comes
naturally with it maybe it's pretty good
at all games or most games not enough
yes as I've seen her general you have to
be for most games you have to recognize
Pat it it'd be smart right patterns
because that's the only way you can
learn like if it was always random then
it's not really a game mm-hmm right you
have to always find the plan you read
the system it's actually you know yeah
yeah you have to be pretty smart to do
that I mean I went so I wouldn't say I'm
like a professional high stone player
because I don't compete but I play at a
very high level for arena I'm like one
of the just the top rated people period
and then but in and here a decade ago
and I was also a competitive bloodline
champions player which is another game
and I've definitely I'd love competing
and I'm okay I'm okay at most rounders
of games yes almost everything almost
everything as I said some games you're
not good at FPS so first-person shooters
so like pubsey or something right for
you first person yeah no its third
person and we've read it was third very
different I haven't played are you good
at uh fighting games no I don't play
okay okay I've only played so many
genres so I started playing video games
on his 14 and World of Warcraft was my
first video game and I went pro in it
talk about very fortunate addict and
then that's a good thing
I mean for a while he committed 14 it's
pretty late to like start because girls
didn't grow up playing games and I had a
sister she didn't play games so why
would I play games right girls looked at
us when we play games and it wasn't cool
back then yeah it was like a secret
almost yeah I go home and like play
Warcraft three years
I wouldn't ever tell a girl yeah but now
it's like yeah my stream more
embarrassing but you're saying that you
started at 14 which is actually that's
pretty late and you went pro on your
first game I mean I went like when I
started playing World of Warcraft I they
call it like keyboard turning like you
just instead of using your mouse to turn
use your keyboard to turn your
characters really slow in an efficient I
I like don't think I realized I leveled
up until I hit like level eight and I
just kept chained dying to like I didn't
know anything it's it's just trying to
do something completely new in role of
our path was of quite complex game if
you've never played anything before like
just moving around and like abilities
the whole like UI and I get user
interface in that game is like confusing
for someone brand new you know like I've
played pac-man right like I could level
up if - how do I quit bytom's like my
friend had to tell me press Enter /w
space you know yeah and I was really
thrown into this world and I remember um
when arenas first came out which is like
the competitive mode my friends told me
I would play with them as like teams
before and then right before the
expansion came out and like the mode
came out they kicked me off the team
before I even got to play because
they're like wow they told me I was like
a 15 year old girl and they're like we
don't think they'll synergize well with
us and I looked up the terms energized
okay yeah I understand and then you went
wrong yeah and then I vowed to beat them
oh you're like a villain I was so
spiteful they got ranked 2 in the first
week in my team I played with random
people I got was like ranked 300 and I
was so salty yeah like oh man
and I was like I'm gonna beat them I'm
gonna freakin beep and I beat them on
the way up there yeah so in a way you
gotta thank them for your I drove you I
would not have tried as hard yeah until
they were like you can't play with us
and I was like what do you mean i can't
play with you yeah this is exactly like
you're in an anime you would be the
villain that's like getting revenge and
then you have to talk I guess you could
also be that character too if it's a
darker enemy I guess vengeance like a
Kill Bill kind of thing they excluded me
they did because I believe you actually
I my first teammate that I hit Rank 1
with I didn't use my microphone I didn't
use voice chat until we had taught top
20 Wow because my voice used to be even
higher than it is now so I would talk
like this and then no one would take me
seriously and only after he was like
whoa that's funny cuz I feel like when I
was playing games and there was girls
with like really high voices all the
guys were just like do everything for
them yeah they would do people I thought
I was you know awesome because everyone
wanted to play with me but right
different than competing they'll give
you gold they'll give you free stuff and
they'll want to spend time with you but
they will not want to compete with you
that makes yeah I could see I could see
how that would work
yeah especially back then cool well I
mean I think this has been a we've been
flown for a while I didn't even notice
yeah but um I think we should wrap it up
yeah cool yeah thank you guys so much
thank you guys so much David and Hoffa
will cuts there I don't know what you
want to put up your twitch I guess we'll
put up that little yeah little thing
thing right there we do an outro we a
product explain since you have never
seen it
we're basically how we all charts
because we didn't think of it
we just breathe into the mic really
close and heavily so yeah but that being
said thanks for tuning in to off the
pill podcast
well podcast again maybe we'll see and
you guys are welcome to come back
anytime yeah that being said here we go
three two one wet over there alright
thanks guys
see you guys