logan palsy extremely talented rice gum
Hibiya and he wanted to box me yeah
alright well welcome back to another off
the pill podcast today we're here with a
very special an old friend old meaning
I'd known him for a long time not insult
ian hecox hello I never knew if I'm
saying that right Wow teeny pops right
Paco coming in with the hits I know he
got I got fire B oh my gosh
sorry What did he say I never knew if I
was saying your name right he [ __ ] okay
yeah I don't know why I thought
otherwise but what did you say he [ __ ]
okay you got it
it just doesn't it just I don't know I
don't know I mean actually don't even
I'd never know how to say Anthony's last
name either yeah it's alright you don't
mention talking okay no more dude I
don't think so yeah I mean where we grew
up a lot of people said his last name
wrong as well Padilla yeah okay but it's
padilha it's Padilla is it really yeah
it's like Spanish this way right yeah
like kiss idea I thought it work at Taco
Bell and I would hate when people say
Casa Dilla I just say that I've gotten
out but slide it you mean quesadilla
Polly you're one of those I'm a douche
bag Taco Bell the truly authentic
Mexican experience yes yes so well it's
great to have you man it's been a while
it has been last time I saw you we were
getting Korean barbecue and wasn't it
that burger spot no like where you live
oh it was okay what was that spot
super-good yeah then why I don't think
we should do yet I literally live above
burger place uh-huh place is so good
okay don't don't ever mention where then
okay well fine but I will say though
that they have a burger where they put a
slice of flaming yon in the burger Oh
like on top of the regular patty I could
give him more I know
just keep give him more hands what is a
street name rhyme way so we can find
this burger spot not your place you know
this burgers but I don't even know okay
Google Maps tells me where to go and
I'll just go alright you someone who
uses Google Maps or ways actually Oh
Google Maps for sure well yeah cuz I
mean like the UI on Waze is the grossest
thing I've ever seen you're a infection
yeah oh yeah come on man actually what
is UI I don't know user interface got it
so mark it's just it just looks really
ugly and there's a lot of like logos and
stuff and I've never I've never actually
used it ever I've seen other people use
it and so you're gonna call it ugly and
never use it you know I am one of those
but also they they make some pretty
crazy recommendations like they'll have
you do a left turn across like six lanes
of traffic and I mean yeah you can do
that but I get crazy anxiety over that
kind of stuff because I don't want to I
don't want to edge out and then block
other people because I don't want to
inconvenience other people so I I'm
always trying to be as like considerate
described especially for an LA driver I
know it's not a good pairing I always
say though that la drivers although they
you know have a reputation to be very
aggressive and whatnot they're one of
the you got to be a really good driver
in LA yet right yeah I think that that's
the strange thing about LA is they breed
really good drivers like not nice
drivers know they it's arrogant they're
arrogant drivers because they they see a
space that the car can fit into in
traffic and I'm just gonna wedge right
in there and yeah your car can fit there
but you could also cause somebody to
freak out and crash into you but it's
really funny whenever I go back to
Sacramento because the difference in
drivers of LA and Sacramento while still
in Cal
for Nia is night and day because people
in Sacramento are nice but also
completely clueless like whenever I go
up there I always find somebody that's
just not looking they just start merging
into my lane I'm like hey hey
so yeah la is not Ellie's not that bad
see in Hilo in Hawaii we don't even have
that many lanes so you don't have to
worry about that but people also don't
drive over I would say forty miles an
hour yeah it's terrible it's terrible
driving back home and actually Oahu is
pretty bad it's kind of like la have you
been there have you driven there it's
pretty low it's slow yeah but the lanes
are so narrow and like it's I mean
that's one of the reasons I actually
don't like ahoo as much and la is
literally a traffic just makes me upset
yeah I'm one of those people yeah one
who is it Oh wahoo was interesting
not my favorite not my favorite of the
islands we're out where else have you
I'm like humble bragging well I went
it's really funny the first time I went
to Hawaii we went to the Big Island
you're your town we didn't go to Hilo
though but went there with my parents
and Anthony it was like there it was
like our graduation gift I think
and they took Anthony along as well but
when you go on vacation with your
parents it's kind of I mean like it
doesn't matter where you go it's kind of
lame because you have to do whatever
they want to do right and also you know
we were 18 I was I was still 17 and you
know you can't drink at that time
there's so much you can do there yes
general yeah yeah well I saw some sea
turtles that was pretty dope okay yeah
so you know that we went to the volcano
that was that was like you know it's a
big bed right now it's a little more
interesting now a little more lit really
now it was cool Maui was like the sort
of cross between Kauai and Oahu I would
say mm-hmm where it's like it is
touristy but you still can get out yeah
and then there's like the if you want to
talk about narrow roads the the road to
Hana oh yeah dude well that that's the
Rope did you have a renter you're not
supposed to go on that road
we have a jeep oh yeah I don't think
you're supposed to go there in a rental
yeah it's crazy like it's dangerous dude
yeah well they have I know that I saw a
shirt that you could buy there and said
I survived the road to Hana because it's
essentially most the time it's a
one-lane road and the locals bombed that
road and there's bridges that are only
wide enough for like one car uh-huh and
and so you know you see somebody coming
the other way you better get the hell
out of their way and like drive into a
ditch they'll just run they'll just run
you off the road yeah nuts it builds
character
yeah and then um and then kawaii Oh is
my favorite island like especially
living in LA where you know you don't
see a lot of green mm-hmm and the green
that is there is just kind of like brown
green and then you go to kawaii and like
everything it's like somebody turned the
contrast up in your eyes like just I
couldn't comprehend the greenness of
everything and then a Wahoo's like all
right there's a lot of tourists here if
there's there's a lot of there's a lot
there's a lot of people in general yeah
well did you find that um I don't know I
always ask people this especially if
they're white did you experience any
racism there because believe it or not I
don't know if people know this but in
Hawaii white people I from what I seen
experience the most racism which I know
a lot of people argue that you can't be
racist to white person and I don't agree
with that argument but I don't know I
growing up I've just I've seen the most
racism directed towards white people and
especially tourists I understand why
I've heard I always heard about the
racism towards white people there which
honestly I understand mm-hmm I mean did
you experience how they don't belong
locals I did I never I don't think I
ever really experienced anything
firsthand I haven't really experienced
anyone ever be rude to me from another
country I had one guy when I was in when
I was in Paris I had this one guy that
[Music]
I asked him if he spoke English in
French because I don't that was
basically the only French word that I
knew and and he was like stem of D James
was that his food how about now maybe
yeah but I mean that's the rudest
anyone's ever been to me in any country
I think as long as you respect everybody
right then they'll show you equal amount
of respect unless they're just having a
really bad day you're just a nice guy
you know you don't in traffic you let
people go like maybe that's why I don't
know well in my experience I've I mean
Paco knows to like naturally I get it
makes sense you know I mean the islands
were illegally taken over right so
there's always that you know there's a
negativity there but um it's especially
towards tourists I feel like people
don't it doesn't matter how polite
naturally a lot of like local people
don't like tourists and is there cuz I
know I think I mean I've heard that like
in Hawaii like there's there's even
there's more racism against like
Filipinos there oh no I'd say with uh I
guess minorities in America mmm in
Hawaii there's equal racism to everyone
because it's such a melting pot yeah
like it's kind of like nobody really has
claimed like like up full claim cuz
you're yeah you're you you have you're
you're like Japanese yeah i think
there's everything yeah I think it's the
only state with no majority so everyone
is a minority there yeah and so everyone
and it's just like everyone is equally
racist to each other and it's just it's
except yeah but it's almost like less of
a problem like you but don't take racism
as seriously there yeah I think at least
growing up because it's like everybody's
different yeah
and like a lot of mix too so it's like
the races racist comments and stuff it's
just like it's mostly stereotypes there
are jokes most of the time yeah so
everyone knew a little oh yeah anything
yeah it's a little different but like I
said to me I still think the white
people got it the worst there well I
mean I get it because we're the most
we're probably the most recent invaders
of Hawaii right you know so I get it and
there's a lot of money coming in there
people you know
a bunch of people from mainland America
saying oh actually I loved I'd love to
live there I'm just gonna bring all my
money I'm gonna buy this big house and
I'm just gonna drive around in my
Mercedes I'm just gonna buy everything
that I was at rich people sound like to
you
well there was actually a couple of
months ago though but this I guess
Caucasian female said I moved to Hawaii
a year ago fell in love with the place
and had like this whole like video on
Twitter of how like oh you know I'm
exactly what you how you're describing
he's doing this and a lot of people took
it and said you didn't fall in love with
Hawaii like you fell in love with being
able to vacation the whole time and
experience like all this stuff while
actual whole way and the people are very
different from what you're showing yeah
100% yeah and that's and that's that
disconnect and you got it you got to
really respect the people that are
already living there if you're ever
going to move to another place you have
to show that respect and understanding
of the people that were there before you
because then that happens and you look
like an idiot we should sell just that
clip right there
you like the Tourism Board oh you're
saying everything right right now okay
well that makes sense that people were
nice to you so you and you went with
Anthony yeah this is okay what what year
was that because you graduated 2005 so
we went in 2005 okay
yes a bit yeah I'm an old man
no I they're like four years older than
us ruff three three or four years always
like we're all the same age they were on
YouTube from the very beginning yeah oh
five right I mean it first came out so
yeah and they were in uh you guys were
in high school yeah well no we we just
graduated so it was the summer between
high school and our super prestigious
Community College yeah that's funny you
went to the Big Island the year that I
started YouTube actually you're welcome
yeah yes you heavily must have
influenced you heavily influenced me and
actually I mean that's true story I mean
I used to watch your guys stuff all the
time I mean I told you when I when we
first
like we used to watch you and I mean you
guys were my favorite and like Derrick
comedy yeah a lot of people don't know
but that's childish game you know god I
can't even aim yeah that was the out you
guys were my favorites to watch back
then and I think about Tamiya brats and
beretta exactly they started working
with you guys
right yeah Joe Joe worked with us for
probably three or no probably four years
and then and then luke luke barats also
did some work for us as well right right
I got those guys are funny they're
amazing yeah they're super underrated
they're both really talented Joe Bereta
went off to do a alley folk
yeah the Valley folk it's separate
Channel with some of the other people
that he met through SourceFed uh-huh
yeah and all right so I guess going into
the first Twitter question since we're
talking about this which is going to
Twitter already I mean I kind of want to
talk about it because they just
presented itself in such a natural and
organic way go ahead masha xk asks when
i was in elementary school it was a
controversial topic who is better Smosh
or nigahiga so have you folks ever felt
competition between each other I mean
not competition in in like a angry sort
of way but back in the day well this is
a podcast you can be real if you were
like who is this no way
no because like like Ryan said he was a
fan of our stuff we were a fan of
nigahiga as well and like back back in
that time there was so little content
yeah everybody knew everybody and
whenever you met another person like we
met at VidCon for the know you do some
YouTube live right oh my god remember
that yeah YouTube live soldier boy Katy
Perry yeah I forgot you were there yeah
that's where I met everybody and Bo
Burnham yeah like I met everybody there
I even met keV there for the first time
I mean we talked obviously but I think I
met cab for the first time there too
yeah people don't know about you to live
dude I literally I think I just talked
about YouTube live in our in our second
podcast and I was talking about how I
met Bo Burnham on the elevator and I did
recognize him because he's so damn tall
huge and in his old videos he'd play
with a keyboard on his lap yeah and he
had this giant keyboard so I just
thought he was like an average size or
small-time person - he's a giraffe he's
gigantic
he's super tall yeah also a super
talented guy I like - yeah um but yeah
that was the that was the first time we
met and I again like like you were
saying everybody used to be very
supportive of each other we used to have
those YouTube meetups even like random
ones like not even orchestrated by a
company or anything we just like there'd
be a spot and I mean I could barely go
to any cuz I was in Hawaii yeah there
was a lot that um people just meet up
and hang out you know yeah that was he
had somebody did a big meetup in San
Francisco I forget what it was called
but do you member SMP films yes yes yeah
that was the first time that a lot of
people met each other and it was in San
Francisco and Anthony and I drove out
there and we just hung out at the pier
and they're just like fans of various
channels Philip DeFranco was there I'm
still was sexy food yeah that's like
that weird thing you like bring up you
like oh yeah his channel used to be
called sexy feel they would think like
refer to him as that in my head
I still think I don't think Philip
DeFranco I think sexy Phil yes yeah for
this day I mean I wouldn't say that
there is there was a sort of strong
competition but back in that day there
was there was a competition to get into
spots on the page and there would be yes
most viewed and most commented ever did
most favorited so so there were a couple
times when when we both uploaded it like
the same time it's like ya know
especially if it's a video that you
really like - yeah or if it was like a
hot topic and then one of whoever was
releasing that topic first is like
dammit not people gonna think I copied
them but like there's no way we could
have made that in time you know but yeah
there other than that I mean like people
were more we're closer before I think
cuz the community was so small I mean it
YouTube was all about collaboration
until about I'd say four years ago
mm-hmm I remember the first the first
time that I ever experienced like
YouTube drama directed at me was like a
channel that was that was talking crap
about Smosh the movie and it had just
came out so I was I was really proud of
like you know the fact that we were able
to make a movie I didn't think it was
like a masterpiece but I was like well
you know this is this is a sort of step
forward for you know YouTube creators
getting into other sort of venues and
and this one guy like made this very
like scathing review and I got so I got
so hurt by it because I'm like this is
another creator and he's tearing another
creator down right and and I was so used
to before that being everybody was
helping each other raising each other up
and so that was my first experience with
somebody
tearing another creator down and then it
turned out that it's actually really
lucrative to tear other people
especially now yeah yeah I mean it
drives interests I mean ya can't there's
no doubt about that I saw a tweet
recently by a keemstar I don't know his
real name
keemstar that's not illegally first name
kiemce yeah they don't know what star a
star last name drama he just said
somebody tweeted at him like oh stop why
do you keep mentioning Jake Paul so much
like it would be nice if you didn't have
to mention him every video and he
tweeted back he's like well I mean he's
made me like two million dollars this
year so like if you wanna give me three
then I'll be happy to not mention it so
like and that's just him reporting on
drama not even being a part of it
technically yeah so I mean it it works
and it does Drive interest because when
things go down I mean like even for me
I'm not gonna lie I'm interested to see
like okay what did someone do now yeah
yeah I remember the first time I heard
about about drama alert I was like I was
that some kind of it was like a charity
livestream some youtubers were putting
on and this guy was like yeah like
there's this guy keemstar and like I
don't feel good watching his stuff but I
can't stop
I was like oh interesting so I went
checked it out and then yeah it just
kept getting bigger and bigger and
bigger yeah and I feel like you know the
the I feel like the real breakout with
YouTube drama was leafy oh right there
was that moment when leafy got really
really huge
you know tearing into people
unfortunately a lot of times they were
children yeah which isn't very cool I
mean like I certainly didn't said some
pretty stupid things when I was a little
kid and I wouldn't want to be crash site
criticized for it you know
and then I mean because he was the first
one and it got really big YouTube you
know basically cracked down on him
and destroyed his channel mm-hmm yeah
and um that's where we are today folks
yeah I don't know how we got there but
we were talking about how we were
competitive and it ends up now we're
just watching drama youtubers I guess
well I guess from you because we got his
perspective so from your perspective did
you ever feel like oh this is
competition even though like like Ian
seems like a very like Oh like let's
build up everybody but you on the other
hand I was ready to take them yeah
because you were a wrestler you actually
beat him up or actually we did wrestle
we did wrestle yeah no I felt um like I
said it was it was when I met everybody
it was more of an honour more than it
was kind of weird too because I was like
not you guys had already had meetups and
stuff like that but I could never go
because I was in Hawaii and then I moved
to Vegas for college and then I was able
to go to let YouTube live and that's
when I mean we've already talked I think
before then same with like keV and like
happyslip all those people back then but
I never met anyone even David
that's where I met David - David Choi
hmm I met YouTube live and everybody was
just so cool I wasn't expecting that but
everybody was cool I will say that keV
did say later way later down like five
years and then he was like hey man I
just wanna let you know back then I'm
super competitive with you but I was
like oh you know what I kind of felt
that to turn it before we were friends
because it's like another Asian dude
he was like bigger than me too at the
time just and he was doing the blog
thing he kind of was like watching kinda
thick I guess Phil was doing that and
then what's that other Asian dude wine
wine Cohen who was uh he was doing that
too so kevin was like conspired off that
and then he thought that was the route
to go we're dropping some names and a
lot of new people who yeah Tony picture
Lancome isn't a directory it's one of
the first I would say one of the first
like kind of rent style videos um and
I've watched him as well the wine Conan
like I was more into like skits and
stuff like that you know Smosh was doing
so uh I went kind of more that path and
yeah I guess in Kev's head I didn't
really see myself as a competitor with
him but I I get it because we're kind of
like oh people would pair us up in the
comments cuz there were two Asian dudes
that's the only reason and younger
younger asian if I were a different
ethnicity I'm pretty sure it wouldn't
have had those similar comments yeah
there was there was a time when we kind
of YouTube's seemed to be the sort of
kingdom of like Asian creators and gay
creators yeah and we're like man if you
could just get a Gaugin creator you
would rule YouTube yep because yeah
there was a certain time when and I
think it was honestly just because they
weren't represented in any other form of
media and finally there was a space
where you would actually see an Asian
person on the screen obviously still
it's not that great but no it's very
different but like the crazy rich Asians
really broke through I know
Olivia who's in our cast she said like
she's getting a lot more auditions
there's a lot more interest in Asian
actors yeah for sure yeah I mean there
I'm yeah I mean I did I don't want to
get too uh I got a little frustrated
sometimes about that whole scene because
it sounds so bad drop in your podcast I
just I feel like people especially in
the Asian community don't aren't
acknowledging how much better it is and
how much better it's getting and they're
just like well we're still not like it
it's it
it's only a small group of people that
don't that still think well it's not
we're not even close it's just one movie
but they don't realize like how many
more how hot of a commodity it is to
have Asians right now and then I
personally think they're gonna milk it
and then it's gonna be the opposite
again for a little bit I think they're
gonna milk it right now because it's
gonna make money you're gonna see a drop
in that because people aren't gonna get
a little over it over stature it's gonna
be like a little trend thing and you
know but it's all I still think it's
better like it's still better I'm I mean
I think I think China is becoming the
largest movie going yeah audience so I
mean I doesn't care about
asian-americans they care about Chinese
China China Chinese but I mean I think
China's Italy into kpop you know I think
they're I think they're interested in in
other and other people as well but
that's that's gotta be good I feel like
China like they don't obviously what's
his crazy rich Asians didn't do that
well they're obviously didn't do it all
because what they want is Tom Cruise or
they want like the blockbuster Marvel
and I think what I heard is it put trade
Chinese Chinese yep in like a bad light
mmm well from there one of the things I
read it yes yeah yeah it makes sense but
did it actually play over there it did I
think it didn't do well mmm yeah cuz
it's hard to get I think only a certain
number of movies American made movies
actually are allowed in and from what
maybe I'm maybe this is totally bad
information but from what I heard you
have to you have to work with certain
Chinese companies they have to be like
involved in the project and you have to
also include certain Chinese actors in
your movie oh wow so that's why like if
you watch if you saw xxx return of
xander cage you know a masterpiece of a
movie I think it's I think that's like
another H Brothers film which is it's a
Chinese company production company I
think and you'll see there's a there's a
Chinese actor in that and you'll also
see him in I think he's also in valerian
which was funded by some Chinese
companies
but it's really funny because because
there's also other roles where they have
to portray China in a good light yeah so
like with Transformers right when they
had like the big battle in in China
there's a scene yeah China comes and
saves the day well that's I mean that's
smart that's what makes money yeah you
make more money later yeah I think in
valerian was it Blair I think it was
valerian like there's like a there's a
Chinese character that saves the day
yeah at the end guys if we see China
four more times in the next 13 seconds
we're on route to beating Donald Trump
in his whole presidency well when I say
we're not saying Jane oh that's pretty
good dude thank you we're close though
we're close yeah we're probably on some
kind of list we probably won't be
allowed in so much TSA is like they're
on a no-fly list now anyway you so
before when I hit you up to do this
podcast it was like what three weeks ago
yeah I said I'd love to have you
obviously and you said that I would love
to do it but just wait a few weeks and
you announce something just very
recently do you want to talk about that
or yeah you yeah I would love to okay
can I talk about it I'd love to you tell
me I don't know what your contract
situations are like yeah so Smosh know
I'm burping now I do my big speech see
that's what happens
nervous it's all coming out it is yeah
whenever I had to explain this to my
parents and my family friends I I kept
doing that was like the whole Smosh
situation yeah I think it's just like a
weird like it's a weird sort of like
emotional reaction cuz it's it's been
like crazy so okay so backing it up a
little bit we sold Smosh to a company
called alloy digital in like 2011 or so
later on that company merged with this
company called break and they became
defy media which a lot of people know
about now
great reputation sarcasm yeah and in
October like late October early November
they very quickly closed down the whole
company and laid everyone off with very
little warning right and that left Smosh
in a weird place because I don't own it
it's not like it's not like because they
went out of business I get Smosh back
right
so essentially fell in the hands of the
bank and I then worked with the
consultant for like four months to find
it a new home make sure that it got into
the right hands and if it didn't go into
the right hands then I wouldn't be a
part of Smosh I would leave and probably
mostly everyone else would leave and
then and then that company would be
known for killing Smosh right but
basically at the final hour when this
there was a really really bad foreign
company that almost got it and I it
would have been bad I would have left
rhett and Link hit us up rhett and Link
the og youtubers are still there in it
don't kill in the game
some people might know him is good
mythical morning they came in and they
save the day they bought Smosh so so now
Smosh is a part of their mythical
entertainment thing and it's really
honestly and I'm not saying this because
I have to it's the best outcome because
it they're not owned by anyone like they
own rhett and Link own mythical entirely
so they don't have they don't have any
like larger company to report to that
can shut them down or they don't have
any investors that could just pull
funding or whatever so now we basically
get to really look at everything that is
Smosh and just kind of you know take
apart the Machine look at what doesn't
work throw that out and put some new
pieces and that that we wanted
you know we think can make the machine
work a little better it's it's been a
really it's been a tough ass four months
every day like we would we would go into
meetings with investors or you know
other sort of people and you know we'd
hear like yes we can we can fund this
bah blah blah and then we get a call
like the next day and be like oh sorry
just not in the time and like oh well
now we're screwed
and like every day it was like it was
like you know highs and lows we're gonna
make it we're not gonna make it like it
we're not gonna make it and it was like
it was draining as hell and I was under
NDA and all those other stuff so I
couldn't tell I couldn't really keep
everyone in the Smosh family informed as
to every step that was going on so I
just had to be like hey like you know if
you're able to let's keep getting
together and making videos because
somebody had defied me access to the
channel so I was still uploading right
but I hadn't been actually managing a
channel and so long which is like it
sounds so silly from like the outside
but no I know that's weird
yeah we have three channels one before
if you're counting else Smosh but I
didn't I didn't run that during the
downtime but three channels and I am now
in charge of uploading and making sure
like the video files are correct getting
all the metadata on there like
thumbnails it was a pain in the ass
meanwhile trying to also make sure that
Smosh doesn't go into the hands of right
some help [ __ ] ass company
congratulations dude you did it thank
you
oh you're waiting for that I wasn't sure
when to bring it out that was good so I
mean that's I mean that's great
but what does that mean like coming from
a viewer perspective was that mean force
Marcia what is that gonna change like
well if I had my biggest issue with defy
was just the leadership it was really
really bad
they didn't really put much effort into
Smosh they just kind of like Smosh was
successful so they just kind of let it
do its own thing and then they I think
probably put a lot of money into their
things
that maybe didn't work out which is you
know typical company stuff I can't like
yeah define did some really bad things I
can't say that everything defi did was
evil and bad you know they they
obviously supported us for many many
years and we did gross mosh with them so
I can't I can't completely dump on them
but some of the people at the top were
bad uh-huh really bad and I'm not a fan
of them and I'm glad that were no longer
associated with them I now have a
leadership position in Smosh so I'm able
to have a say in what happens next
that's really exciting there's a lot of
things that defy didn't do that I felt
was a really big oversight about in
terms of a content like where they were
you allowed to just say hey I have this
great idea yeah I want to do this on
this day they were really they were
really afraid of of legal things right
so every single script got passed
through a lawyer got it and and they
they even towards the end got nervous
about like mentioning brands because
they're like whoa you know we never know
you never know if like we're gonna do a
brand deal with them or whatever it got
really ridiculous and they were also
really afraid of some of the new YouTube
guidelines so they're like okay you can
never show a gun you can never show like
somebody that like like died in a video
even if it's a comical like if somebody
gets hit in the head with like a
football and they fall on the ground
they look dead like I can't do that
that's crazy yeah it was see I I always
felt that to be honest I felt like when
that change happened with you guys and
I'm officer I didn't say anything you
know yeah but I've always wondered I
don't know why I'm asking you now I did
always wonder like what kind of control
did you guys have at that point we had
we had a considerable amount of creative
control
there was just yes though those things
especially towards the end did get more
constrained right and like I don't I
don't want to promise people like like
oh like our videos are gonna be twice as
good now because that's
not fair like I I think we were already
doing a good job with with the YouTube
content yeah I do think we can do better
and I think we will yeah
now that we have more control and we're
gonna we're probably gonna loosen up on
some things but I think there's so much
more out there than just YouTube mm-hmm
I do want to figure out a touring thing
because with what we are it's it's so
different nowadays from other YouTube
content like you and me are pretty much
like the only people doing sketch comedy
on YouTube now so some are sort of
offering with the live show is very
different from you know somebody that's
a vlogger right we have a cast of people
that can we can create a sort of a live
like a variety show almost like a live
show and some other stuff I don't want
promise anything because this is all
very very preliminary and it's all we're
gonna leave this and say there's a new
live show coming we're taking pounds if
sound bites yeah yeah there's a live
show variety yeah
but if you get you saying Anthony's
coming back as well so well you could
just you could just pull out different
clips of me saying like Anthony and then
coming Anthony's coming back there
well we got it right there so thank you
yeah well speaking of Anthony yeah just
because I mean obviously you guys made
the video together and it's very cordial
is there anything else like I mean how
are you guys do you guys still keep in
touch at all like um do you I mean I I
mean I don't know I have a little bit no
idea yeah I mean we keep in touch from
time to time
obviously he's really busy with his own
channel right and and this is something
we were kind of talking about one I
don't know like when is this podcast
coming out this is coming out on like
next Friday's your podcast okay so like
I think are put I think I'll be talking
about this in in in our podcast as well
at the same exact day basically what
we're saying is like you know all the
people that are that are pestering us
and pestering him for him do I come back
to Smosh it's it's really disrespectful
to both of us mm-hmm like especially to
him because like he's doing what he
wants to do he didn't want to be doing
his
his channel he wouldn't be doing it and
for people that go on his channel and
say come back to Smosh like you're only
good on Smosh like that's super
disrespectful yeah so yeah I had to have
known that was gonna happen right Oh
100% yeah so I mean cuz a lot of a lot
of his beef when he left was was about
to Phi so I see a lot of people think
like well now that defines of the
picture it's it's gonna like you can
come back but it's it's obviously a
little bit more than that it's you know
obviously we've become creatively kind
of two different people so I mean you
know yeah with with with a duo or any
kind of any kind of partnership
creatively it it's hard to sometimes
come to an agreement on on content and
you know the fact the fact that we
remained a partnership creatively for so
many years is kind of a wonder yeah yeah
but the door is absolutely open for him
to come back and be in videos like I
would be really excited with the
prospect of him be like showing up I
think it could be really cool but the
first video video that he's back there's
a gun and he gets shot and then dies
just so it all comes full circle yeah
we're gonna we're gonna Bruce Lee him
yeah just because they can now yeah and
it get it gets to monetizing you can and
then you gotta go back to your own ways
I mean I'm we're the same way even now
it's like we gotta think about I mean
we'd get to do a little bit more edgy
things but like I've experienced it too
in terms of just like you mean using
like I sometimes would get away with
using like two seconds of a song you
can't do that anymore
yeah even if it's a mention you know we
got we got flagged for we got a flag
from a video from like seven years ago
where Anthony and I are singing I'll
make love to you acapella in bad Russian
accents that is so that's not even being
picked up by YouTube that's literally
someone look flagging it down it's at
like the end card so I don't I don't
know how somebody found that because
not singing it on key we're singing bad
accents that's how good you were and
there's no music playing behind it
uh-huh and somehow some someone
physically you had to watch it and be
like that is I know who owns the rights
to this and they go I don't know I don't
know it's like covers supposed to be
okay
no you'd have to get some kind of
resolution of some sort or be with like
a MCN yeah covers aren't aren't you
can't do covers covers aren't covered
covers on Cobra broke the claiming
business is actually really a really big
business yeah there's a lot of money in
claiming so a lot of large companies
will hire businesses to just scour
YouTube and claim videos well now it's
it's automatic like a lot of it's
automatic a lot of it is but there's
still a lot of manual no there are I
mean i-i've in this past year I mention
it to another video I think I've gotten
like literally probably ten times more
and probably like half my videos got
claimed and it's still happening every
like couple every week some of them
justified some you can do I could
dispute but like it's such a long
process it's like almost not worth the
energy it's like okay fine okay
this video still gets views over time
and I get over time you're gonna get a
lot more but like I just don't have the
energy to like dispute every single
thing yeah and some are some are
justified I get it it's just like kind
of ridiculous yeah we had we had one
that was really annoying we have this
really this really fun series on our
second channel called try not to laugh
where somebody sits on a stool and then
people dress up in props and stuff in
the background then they come out and
they get thirty seconds to try to make
that person laugh right and we had this
guy his name on like instagrams juji mu
foo he's like this big buff guy and he
does like backflips and all these like
crazy acrobatics I had him on the show
and we use like two like short clips of
him to like show what he does and Juke
and media claim that really whole damn
video and it's like because
we had him on the video like he would be
cool with us using these clips but
[ __ ] jookin we can't curse on this I
don't know we never said our first
really sponsor on this one so there
isn't so yeah I don't think sponsors
really care with pod casts I don't think
they do either I just never done it yeah
but you could be the one okay I was like
so I was occasionally I cannot talk
occasionally I was self censoring myself
because I wasn't sure cuz most podcasts
are like who cares I mean just all say
it once together I mean if it comes out
naturally then it will you know oh this
I just I get really upset I just have a
lot of hatred for jookin oh just like I
just hate that whole business model they
literally just they just buy clips and
then license them and whenever somebody
uses their clip then they just claim it
and take the money it's it's a it's a
shitty business oh I don't know I just
curse together great I just really don't
like chicken
you really don't really coming out like
you can see all the dirt is coming to
help man we're about to set up a fight
with setting up a boxing plate yeah just
get into that about would you ever do
that hell no I've never been punched in
the face before would you like our
wrestling our wrestling match was
probably the most confrontational I've
ever been with anybody really yeah that
was a visit me
filmed agents of secret stuff by the way
yeah for Ian his board yeah and we
wrestled and he was in his suit and it
was a little revealing
I was gonna say you can kind of see my
dog through it yeah interested yeah I
was wearing a blue suit and I tried to
last in the ring what 30 seconds so I
just ran around the ring and tried to
avoid you actually think I saw that one
yeah yeah it was funny it was fun one
more time
I was just wondering yes I mean you know
everybody's that whole scene is blowing
up it helps everybody that does it yeah
I'm sure it does but then after the
match
nobody cares true it's you know what I
did now it's gone I'd be afraid of if I
got into a boxing match and they knocked
me out so hard I peed myself
I think people would understand that
yeah but that was a terrible sex way
into our oh yeah we do have to do a she
she break okay that means - it's a pee
break but we just call she she anyway um
quick she she break yeah we've been
going for a bit anyway yeah we'll be
right back
she she break she she get road to help
you up that's the most controversial or
confrontational he's ever been dude he
just hit them on yeah anyway and we're
back
yo that's how we get back into it anyway
um what are we saying
I don't know talking about Obama boxing
and by yeah I will say that I I did
remember that one part from the boxing
match oh it's really funny because like
you know I didn't really want to support
that that match so uh there was a group
of there's a group of maybe maybe like
twenty of us that all went over to one
person's house so we only had to pay for
one but I do have I do have some respect
for God I forget his name he went it he
went up against the rock Iraq one of the
rack Iraq is it one of the drama guys
yeah yeah he's one of the drama guys the
guy that comes out from behind the tree
that's not his whole mean what is it now
we're she's gonna be upset
yeah anyway just look on your phone I
mean that was that was he was clearly
gonna lose yeah cuz both the wrecker
racket goes like have you ever watched
our videos yeah they're awesome but
they're insane yeah those guys are
insane and if you've like seen any that
they're hilarious they're they're like
amateur wrestlers too so they're just
extremely physically capable guys and
they went up against him and it's like
ah man like yeah so I got to give props
to that guy that went up against the
rack ragged dude cuz uh-huh yeah man had
heart yeah yeah
I'm just the most important thing but I
help you win but yeah I respect no I
don't help you in I believe in heart you
know it's a big part of it oh for sure
um I'll hit you up to uh or who if you
had to who would I box yep
if I had to everyone's like oh there's
no way we could hit each other we're so
passive-aggressive against each other
but if you had to though I don't think
of them standing any worse quite
everywhere just like talking about each
other yeah I don't think we ever even
like raised our voices at each other
yeah like yeah I was gonna say like one
of it one of the people that was running
to Phi or Junkin junket yeah yeah I'll
box Juke and media yeah okay I shouldn't
say that because maybe there's some like
MMA bro that runs that yeah website I
don't know I don't know if I ever said
this publicly and I don't think he would
mind but when that all was happening as
it was getting planned out the second
the second I think no the first fight
actually rice come hit me up and he
wanted to box me I think you did mention
this I might have mentioned it I don't
know where though where would I have
mentioned it when I think oh maybe it
was one I don't think I at least yeah I
was like one of those like really our
test versions okay
I don't think like boxing or I mean you
would still annihilate him but he might
be a great boxer for his good reach he's
got he's wrong and I don't know how to
you right it was an MMA fight I think
I'd be pretty confident but not in
boxing I'm a browser
oh you're what I mean it's the same it's
the same advantage that Logan had you're
a natural-born athlete well no I
wouldn't say not I wouldn't say natural
okay but I mean you're and I'm very much
out of shape compared to like when I
used to do a lot of sports he says that
and he's like as you said he is flexing
a little bit but I mean like obviously
you're you're a highly
Pettit of person you were where you
liked state-ranked or something with
with wrestling or wrestling yeah he won
first place in States come on man it's a
small states Hawaii yeah it's not like
it was uh all right how strong was he
when he beat you up though and he was
smiling the whole time right yeah he
wasn't really trying that's the thing
it's necessary think cuz running around
in a slipper I was suit I was fighting
for my life well that would be an
interesting that would be an interesting
fight I don't say it I wouldn't say you
should do it though no I mean the thing
is I the only reason I would do it if it
were MMA because I'm a fan of the sport
yeah and I already have some experience
in it so I wouldn't have to put in like
you know granted his experience you know
that's not fair if he has none but if he
does have some experience in boxing yeah
and I've experienced in wrestling and
judo then it kind of balances a little
bit more you know yeah I mean it just
wouldn't be fair no it would
it wouldn't be fun to watch if it was
MMA because you would just take him down
and put him in some kind of hold unless
you're really good and nobody knew he's
better he's really good at like
surprisingly athletic at basketball we
played with him oh really he's good he's
actually really good at basketball and
honestly when I first looked at him I
didn't think he was gonna be athletic
he's pretty good okay well maybe I take
everything I said maybe he was like he's
a sleeper he's one of those people
who've been training and he thinks like
I think he doesn't know how to fight but
he can fight he's waiting that's what I
said I didn't fall for the trap rice
let's try Brian yeah nice try don't and
while you by your screen name yeah why
were you buying
why were you balling with rice gum
what's that all about he uh so he lived
out here so this is like right when he
was kind of getting big we uh he kind of
reached out and it was uh I would say I
even mentioned it in that song exposed
song that he when I went out we hung out
with him he was like you know I know he
has a bad rap and stuff like that and he
does the whole like forcing kids but
when I know he's like a very nice shy
kind of I guess a kid at the time he's
um he's probably always been a nice
person it's just I just have a persona
exactly yeah but you know we we filmed
with him and I dare you a long time ago
he was story
to get big and I kind of see like you
know okay he's kind of he's feeling it
you know I mean everybody goes through
it a little bit right when you start
getting that fame you kind of feel like
oh I'm getting more money than I ever
thought I would I'm getting more girls
or you know whatever it is and at the
same time he was like you know we had
this really deep talk after we played
basketball together I was driving him
home and he was just like stressing like
I don't know like maybe I should move to
LA or what do you think I should do like
he's very like he was very kind of um
I'm sure he doesn't actually I don't
know if he'll mind if I'm talking about
it but it was just very normal he's a
normal guy going through like a lot of
stress yeah and I think part of that you
know whether it's a persona or whether
it's him he it's kind of like a defense
mechanism I think I think it's because
he feels that's where he feels
comfortable that's what got him made and
he kind of just ran with it and you know
just liked it like a prank channel or
anything you have to top yourself you
have to go above and beyond consistently
or else people lose interest yep so yeah
I think happened I mean when you when
you build your whole when you build your
whole persona around always raising the
bar and pushing the envelope then you
like you said you have to keep pushing
the envelope yeah if that's what your
game is eventually you're you're going
to reach a breaking point yeah whether
it's your content or your mental
well-being
exactly see but that's why I think like
um like I get why he gets the hate he
gets it's the content that he puts out
right so but I don't think a lot of
people know who he really is
and that I think it's also just I mean
it's not their fault for not knowing
that but I think a lot of youtubers are
like that actually they know that it
works I'm sure there's some that are
very genuine that are very not saying
that he's not but I'm sure there there's
some that are very much just douchebag
[ __ ] but and they put on like a
family-friendly front yeah there's that
to it there's that you know that is like
strangely a thing yeah where if they're
putting on like a nice sort of thing
online then yeah I don't know no it's
true yeah I mean I
I we're not gonna say names but I'm sure
we you know people over the years and
stuff like that I mean most of the
people I've met have all been wonderful
yeah me too even if I even have never
met I don't think I've ever met
rice gum even if I met him in real life
I don't think we had have a bad
experience
no get along just fine probably super
pullet even when I met um Logan Paul for
the first time I wasn't and he wasn't
this is before like all the you know
controversy and stuff like that just one
of the nicest people and I only met him
once but I you know he can't get much
from one meeting but he just came up to
me at a party he said oh I was I'm such
a big fan of your your videos from back
in the day I was like oh I like your
vines I didn't know he was on YouTube at
the time but yeah it was like around
that era and it was just like a normal
conversation and then when all this
stuff started happening I was like oh he
messed up well he's gonna get some PR
for that made him bigger yeah and then
just the thing is it just made him
bigger and bigger so how can you really
it's positive reinforcement yeah you
know like in his head obviously it's
like well yes all this drama things
making people say some bad things about
me but I'm also blowing up so like how
can he yeah I mean it's all speculation
but I think you know when you're
creating content like that without any
sort of without any kind of purpose yeah
when you're just doing it because you
need to push the envelope yeah you'll
get a lot of views but you're not you're
not I don't think you're really building
a core sort of audience and that's
something that I feel like you know you
guys have done I feel like that's
something that Smosh is done like our
audience has always been like not very
engaged but I feel like you know we've
we've always had a sort of core and and
you see those sort of channels that that
have just followed a certain trend or
they get locked into one sort of like
format and they just ride that thing all
the way up and then once the algorithm
shifts you know and that trend is no
longer good for the algorithm the bottom
falls out from under those people
except that the algorithm hasn't changed
in a very long time it has there there
are things in the algorithm that a
change well I mean they're still doing
well oh yeah that's true
actually they're not what it was even
last year but they're still huge yeah I
mean there was there was like recent
there was recent stuff that that picked
him up a little bit again but you know
that they kind of because they don't
really stand for anything you know if I
have to they have to keep pushing the
envelope and I mean I'll still say it
like Logan Paul is extremely talented
yeah I do think he's really a really
talented guy so I just I'm just really
disappointed because the after the
forest then I was like I was like this
is his chance to completely reinvent
himself yeah and go down a new path and
it'll be really good and he didn't do it
and I mean he still obviously succeeded
yeah very well I know what you mean it
could have took that other turn and kind
of like reinvented himself yeah like cuz
it was such a big event that's like your
perfect opportunity to I mean look at
any celebrity goes through that stuff
you know there people want that change
and then you can always change it up
again later but like the whole like it's
very similar to that like at least how I
see it is like the whole Miley Cyrus
situation is like she was this very
clean whatever girl and then people are
like what the hell she turned into this
Miley drug Miley twerking Miley and
she's so out of character people were
just like super interested but at the
same time like hating on her like this
is not how I should be she want a new
audience there but now that she's kind
of reverted back to old Miley it's like
oh now I want to root for this girl cuz
she's like you know she's seeing her
wrongs and like she's trying to be a
better person and she's dating that
famous dude Hemsworth again you know so
it's like it's like a very I don't know
I think it strategic yeah it's a really
good really good career move I mean I
guess before her Christina Aguilera did
it
I mean we all remember the dirty area
era of Christina Aguilera come on you
guys remember it
I mean I'm trying to think of the people
watching remember probably not
oh god world no yeah but that was the
thing like Christina Aguilera started
out with like genie genie in a bottle
like she was like this kind of like a
little bit risque but like still sort of
wholesome I think I don't know I wasn't
like a big fan but then she came out
with dirty and she went like full-blown
like like I'm like this sexy and like
you know as a freshman in high school
and that came out that was very stoked I
mean it just Britney Spears same thing
right yeah yeah and then and then they
had kind of had that sort of with
Christina I feel had that sort of like
MIT like she matured and then she was
like acted because she's an amazing
singer so she was able just kind of like
mature into this sort of like I am now
like I am now a woman I'm mature woman
and people loved it but it's the same
trend everything look at Justin Bieber
same thing this innocent little kid
right plays like you look cute kid
that's like you want to support him all
the little girls love him closer like
this this man face like I'm I'm the man
I'm gonna take off my shirt and then
start you know get tattoos and stuff
like that and look buff look but he is
you got buffer yeah um and then now he's
back into like well I'm going back to
church and well not that he didn't go to
church but you know he's putting on that
uh but I don't know I think it's the
same trend I've seen with celebrities at
least oh it happens all the time and
that was Logan's chance to go through
that phase I think and then he could
always come back which I think would
happen but yeah and I think he's just
like uh it's an it's because people see
that as being human that it's relatable
like if someone is perfect and always
perfect it's like wow I love this person
but I can't relate to them I would like
to be this person but when you see
someone fail and then and then they
succeed that's a story that you can
align yourself with and be like if they
can do it if they can go through
something way tougher than I went
through then then that gives me hope
yeah yeah I honestly I
I thought Logan was gonna was gonna sort
of like go down the the route of like
raising awareness for suicide like a
little bit later a little bit he did one
one video yeah one and then it was and
then it was back to as far as I remember
got back to the haze though a dead rat
or something like I was like I really
like this soon man maybe could also be
the people that he's around to knows I
mean like I mean yeah you gotta find you
gotta find good people to surround
yourself with if you surround yourself
with with yes-men people that'll just
tell you they could also convince
convince you that it's oh yeah that's
not that bad ya know yeah yeah I mean
who I mean we're gonna be called
apologist now Logan Paul apologist Logan
apologists you guys having podcast as
well yeah I'm impulsive also yeah yeah
now is that something that either of you
would ever consider going on go on Logan
Paul's podcast yeah um I mean I don't
know it well enough but I saw clips on
his Instagram of like doing some kind of
crazy stuff here like some guy gets
kicked in the balls or did he do some
crazy stuff is it gonna I don't know if
I would want to do that but if it were
just to talk to him I'd have no issues
talking to anyone to me at least I don't
know about you I know people might
associate your brand so it's like a
little you know but to me I'm okay with
talking to anyone
yeah it seems like he's I don't know
I've only seen clips again yeah it seems
like he's kind of trying to do like a
Howard Stern thing mm-hmm like it's not
like I thought again he I thought with
the podcast he was gonna reinvent
himself and go like a little bit more
mature yeah and then it was like the
third guest on was a porn star I'm like
all right dude
but I reading the comments and stuff it
seems like people are really really
liking it like apparently it's good
I mean it's entertainment yeah yeah you
know this I mean like this is just us
hanging out and talking we're not
kicking people in the balls we don't got
like random strippers or whatever yeah
but I'm not opposed to having a stripper
to talk to or a pornstar sorry I would
talk to a porn star
I wouldn't make her do anything crazy
also a Kara is actually so funny the way
AUSA Kira who was a porn star
did she also do like go ahead deeply a
passive yeah I think I just want to be
clear I'm never I've never heard that
name I don't have any idea who you're
talking about up Christina Aguilera I
was stoked she went on
Qasim's okay that's going deep yeah I
know you can't do something like that on
YouTube no Qasim is so he's so good that
was so funny
yeah and as a last question as the
grandfather's kind of of YouTube in a
way you guys have been here for so long
we're dying you dying literally a dying
breed though sketch comedy how um what
is some of the strangest fan
interactions that you've had what does
this one always come up with every
person well it's because I'm asking that
what oh yeah I'll let Ian go because
wherever we already answered this yeah I
mean the weird one that we always say it
was a time when back when Anthony and I
lived at the same house the address got
leaked and people started showing up at
our house like on a almost daily basis
and somebody somebody decided like in
the middle of the night that they were
gonna go into the side of the house like
through a fence uh-huh and they took a
picture of Anthony through the window
that is so weird
yeah that's cool I actually have a
similar one to that I didn't tell it I
don't know I didn't tell this story but
similar same thing somebody I mean
people found out where I lived my other
place and I had cameras though and I
just so happened to have my TV on that
has a different cameras and I just see
these kids like just I might you know
not not doing any of my front like kind
of garage area my on my driveway so
you're not really like trespassing but
then I just keep watching them and then
you just see them talking and you see
this one kid go over and he runs up the
stairs looked in the window and he
starts filming inside
yeah and then basically it's just like
that's one of the main reasons why I
moved here because I was just like that
was happening a lot at the other house
once they find out where you live it's
um it's very uncomfortable I always kept
my windows closed and you know it makes
you feel weird man yeah I mean I
wouldn't suggest everybody goes and go
and do this but I mean I bought a gun
yeah like oh you're gonna get so much
hate yeah I know
well it's look I I definitely don't
recommend everybody go out in California
yeah
you can that oh I guess you have to just
get a which one call right like you need
some kind of license or something in
California with a shotgun no oh really
always literally I paid 300 bucks and I
had it in like two weeks or something
like that you do like a background check
or something but they do you don't need
a permit for a shotgun or a handgun you
have to take like a written test a
concealed weapon yeah and then no not a
not a concealed for a handgun yeah just
for at least back when I was thinking
about it oh you had to take a test like
a written test and then you had a permit
that expired like a couple years later
right welcome to gun talk yeah and it's
obviously I didn't I didn't have the
intention of going out there and
shooting fans but yeah well I mean it's
its intended purpose if someone comes
and breaks into your house like you have
some way to protect yourself if they
have a gun too you know yeah and like
and that was my reason for the shotgun
over something like a handgun was the
sound alone should be enough to scare
most people away unless you're like a
quasi murderer which is very rare you
know if you're just somebody looking to
break in and steal some equipment like
you're not gonna take that risk so if
you just hear that then you're you're
not gonna stick around yeah I don't plan
on shooting anybody
I certainly don't want to shoot anybody
I don't fantasize about shooting anybody
I think you know gun violence is
obviously a huge problem but yours I
mean you have a you're a special Kate I
mean like not to make you feel like you
know but I mean it's true like you
there's a very legitimate reason as
- why you have that gun yeah and it's
not for fans that are that are trying to
take pictures through my window it's
it's it's the fact that you know our
address is out there it only takes one
person to say well they're youtubers I
bet they have some pretty expensive
video and audio equipment or one crazy
person that's all it takes
yeah I mean I've never banked on the
crazy person aspect of it but it did
happen it did happen to Gavin and make
turn I know yeah and that that was scary
as hell cuz that's that's sort of the
thing that every sort of youtuber feared
and and you know thank god they're okay
you know like that one crazy that's what
I mean though there's so many people in
the world and because people know you
there's a higher probability of someone
crazy coming and doing something that
yet and I mean obviously the the girls
online have to worry about that a little
bit more yeah sure oh yeah there was
there's some there's some youtuber that
was telling a person so this is gonna be
a third person story but they said that
they had a there this guy reached out
out to out to her it was a fan and he's
like hey um I'm just making sure you
haven't been talking directly to me have
you and she she was like no and he's
like okay thank you because I have this
mental condition where I watch when I'm
watching something I think they're
talking directly to me what yeah so so
he had the wherewithal to realize that
because of this you know mental illness
that he could not be possibly thinking
straight yeah but it's those it's that
possible that's a fortunate scenario
that is very easily with a very people
who are self aware of that yeah you know
yeah and then and then it's those kinds
of people not that I'm trying to like
say a certain type of like mental
illness is responsible right this is
anything but the people that aren't
right in the head that you know the guy
that broke in there was obsessed with
Meg right like had thousands of notes on
his phone about like his love for her
and like how he was gonna kill Gavin or
whatever it was nuts yeah and you know
obviously it's not like something that
youtubers should be worried about every
moment of the day but yeah but just you
know being aware of something like that
yeah see the thing is the way that I
justify that that you know I know that
already people are gonna be like oh I
can't believe Ian has a go what and
there's gonna be people regardless
because we shot a video where we
literally just went to the desert and
shotguns yeah that's I think you do out
here I didn't think much of it and we
got so much ridiculous hate for that I'm
sure but the thing is about the whole
situation and your situation and why I
think it's fine is because if everybody
didn't have guns that there was no guns
yeah of course well you don't need a gun
even though it's alright
you know if but the fact that you don't
that's not put into place you know like
that's you need I mean I understand your
concern for that yeah I mean I my I have
no black or white thoughts I think
that's that's the issue with with you
know any sort of gun control debate is
it so black and white of like you're
either for guns or against guns and I'm
like I mean there's certain cases where
like maybe it's it's alright but like
there's also a lot of people that
definitely should not have guns and
maybe there are just too many guns
yeah well the original reason was for
tourney right like that's the reason why
that a Second Amendment
sure yeah but we all had single fire
muskets like two minutes not that we
need to not that we need to get into any
gun control talk because that's really
not an interest among the concert people
like yeah I know but um yeah that's
that's that's cool of you to admit it's
in that same and that's also kind of the
funny I always think about this with
like there is like a lot of people hood
you know from an outsider perspective
like everyone thinks California is like
this you know super liberal Democrat gun
control hellhole it's like well I know a
lot of people you could basically
classify as rednecks like uh-huh like
California is a very diverse sort of
state and I mean we're you know a lot of
us are descendants of pioneers people
that traveled across the frickin country
in a wagon and wrist you know life and
to come out here and you know there's
still a lot of that sort of like you
know rugged sort of lifestyle that that
exists I mean there's there's like like
a more like way Northern California they
tried to secede ya know they try to form
their own state north California
it's called know there were sorry there
was gonna be three right well no this is
early as it was called the state of
Jefferson oh I didn't know that yeah and
it's like a little bit of Oregon and
then and then like like northern
Northern California huh and yeah they
just they didn't like how things were
and they wanted their own state whatever
happened to the separating California to
three parts that I think the courts the
courts knocked it down
no so it showed up in our it showed up
in our voting yeah but it said like the
Supreme Court of California or something
has like voted out yeah so it wasn't on
the ballot it was such a stupid idea
anyway like I mean I didn't know enough
about it to comment but I just remember
I was like Oh more states to remember
yeah you know sucks for kids yeah
anything like 52 states you have to
learn about now and Guam and all this
stuff I mean as maniacs would have to
change their song yeah it is kind of
weird though that California is one
state but there's what 40 million people
that live in one state such a big sock
it's like two-thirds of the East Coast
or something like the size of it west
coast
no it's the same oh yeah two-thirds of
like I don't know it's huge yeah yeah I
don't know Alaska's 3 times the size of
Texas I do know that yeah Paco's coming
with those Africa's tax something times
the size of I don't know I'm just
looking at me and we're doesn't even
memes boy I just love whatever there's
like an asteroid they're always like
it's twice the size of Texas or like
three times the size of Great Britain
I mean it's a unit of measurement for us
you know I guess so we wouldn't
understand in cubic meters or somebody
with no I mean yeah if someone is like
it's 5,000 inches how does it and then
you convert it to feet it's not as
impressed let that be easier for us and
like meters because we're not on the
metric system that don't you haha wait
this topic got like very serious and
dark towards the N huh yeah that's how I
like to take things now that's good rope
you in with the light fluffy things and
then I'll just tear your heart out and
then we talk about gun control and now
that's every what everyone's gonna be
talking about unless we talk unless we
bring up something I don't know but I
think it's we don't really we always end
up bringing some political thing in here
but what my original intention is to
talk about things I'm interested in
obviously what the guest if there's a
guest what they're interested in - and I
guess I am interested in politics kid
always comes up at least once a podcast
yeah
but um you're talking about life and
life is politics
and I but the thing is I'm not the most
educated person on this stuff but I have
my own opinions what politics you off oh
that's good there's your next segment
Ian Hecox a shotgun how long were you
waiting waiting for a bone I'll sit on
my hand I saw you thinking for a little
bit actually I was just like oh [ __ ] was
being really quiet today yeah unless
have some kind of joke ease Wayne to say
anyway we went a little bit over what we
know they do but you know what it was
actually a lot of fun and very
entertaining so again thank you Ian for
being on yeah
before we end Ian what do you have to do
I was about to do this anyway
yeah go ahead I'm sorry Paco that's okay
he cuts me off so I'll cut him off yeah
you can come me off go ahead
well you know we're getting a new lease
of life at Smosh and our podcast the
Smosh cast is is a good old time we just
launched that it's available on all the
places we can get a podcast yep and at
some point I am going to visit you for
that as well I would love for you to
yeah I'm gonna visit too but I'm not
beyond the box so hard it's so hard to
get Ryan out it yeah la and then I have
to go through his mom and she's so nice
well I mean to schedule this yeah yeah
yeah but yeah I died I don't go out a
lot there was a stir so there's like a
whole tour of podcast that I said I was
gonna do eventually at some point and
I'm just gonna try and knock them all
out at once well if you come if you come
uh to do the podcast with us you
probably do redlynx yeah yeah and then I
was supposed to do actually I really did
reach out a while back but I was I just
I don't know what happened with that h3
I'm supposed to their podcast as well I
don't know why but will told me to be
worried about that one cuz they're there
uh I guess if you mess up saying
something I don't know have you done
theirs yeah oh yeah why does it wear it
wears them I don't think there's
anything to be worried about I mean the
audience is is pretty critical
yeah but podcast is fun Ethan's great
guy yeah yeah so I I mean I don't know
but we'll figure that out okay anyway
yes make sure you guys check out the new
Smosh new and improved and more free and
also the well I guess that's on your
you're putting the podcast on their
podcast is on a separate channel the
smosh smosh passes on a separate channel
okay and this marsh cast which at some
point i will be on as well yeah hell
yeah that being said we didn't tell them
how we end this but you know what we're
just gonna know but he's watched it he's
watched it we can see the ending is
basically how we ended we just get naked
you fail yeah you first you don't see
what I got trust me all we do is we
breathe into the mic oh good yeah it's
just it's not good for the mics I don't
know why we do it it's probably gonna
break at some point but it's just been
our thing i I've been ending my podcast
going that's pretty close to be honest
it's just an annoying noise there's a
lot no this is some more right there
that is true actually
that's a summer yes Murr yeah awesome
are you an ASM artist no he just said
the puns
I'm an ASM martyr I'll die for it
let's end this before people are gonna
click away like to puns ago so thank you
for watching off the peel podcasts thank
you again to Ian I guess we'll talk to
you nest next podcast then yeah baby
Oh Oh Twitter and Instagram I almost
forget all of us on Twitter I off the
pill on Twitter and all the other
podcasts on Instagram so that you can
get your questions in with that being
said see you guys next time I wonder how
that Mike's like this probably as a
consistent like sugar-free Red Bulls
like kind of so yeah that kind of smell
that yours probably has a kind of
interesting smell but this one is
probably like a mix of so many different
smells Jelly Belly popcorn
[Laughter]