how did you and our didn't me we just
kind of made our chaos is coming into
town again and he went to a club I'm not
sure what should we just glad to clap go
for it alright welcome back to another
episode of off the pill podcast why
would you do that we already have that
in the beginning yeah me I just like to
read sing it yeah I like it anyway
um getting straight to our sponsor again
we have a second round of SeatGeek
everybody Thank You Sookie SeatGeek
is a ticket app that makes buying super
simple they put all tickets in one place
so you can focus on what matters most a
live experience you can find all events
on seek such as MBA Ariana Grande Travis
Scott literally any show or game you can
think of is probably there the hook-up
that you get for using our code which is
he got hig a you get $20 off your first
seat geek order and you know the link
will be in the description but make sure
you guys actually do that because again
it makes us look good and they will want
to respond to us again
yeah and you know we need those sponsors
or else we're gonna have to cancel the
show anyway thank you again see geek dad
I think we're good well we got new cups
well what's that in your hand
whoa this looks like a new off the pill
podcast coffee mug get it No
can we get it now I don't know it just
got sent to me like it is sometimes
it'll be in a link to you and listen to
this
drinking noise anyway yeah I thank you
again to see key I don't know if I said
everything I needed to say but it helps
a lot sounded good
right yeah you can there was actually
people who did I did see that people did
actually use the code last time cuz they
sent me screenshots so thank you to
those people which tweeted that to me
yeah um it actually makes us look cooler
than we are to see geek
well we're super cool dude called town
do believe in yourself cool then we look
I don't know I don't feel very cool
right now why don't why don't you feel
cool right now dude you know I mean for
one we're sitting in this tiny little
room
I wonder people when they watch this do
you think they think this room is big
because we're not like in the same shot
that's one thing yeah for sure when you
watch it cuz I I when I want I mean we
know what the room looks looks bigger
does it look bigger I think so it's like
you know when you watch TV shows and
then you go watch it like I remember we
went to a BDC
when they saw it on TV and you went and
watching a live audience you're like
yeah dude this room is so small like how
do they do it like it's true you know
even NBA games yeah when you go to when
you go there I mean the people are
obviously gigantic but if you go to
actual if you go to an actual NBA game
using see if you go to an actual game
it's the court looks so small in
comparison to what it looks like on TV
and the stadium itself I mean the
stadium is big but the court looks so
small and the people are just gigantic
there's got to be some kind of like a
like name for that right like there's
something something effect is that like
the camera adds 15 pounds to you like
that's everything that really does that
that does happen though no higher
definite I don't know why but even like
even in person like I remember I went to
go watch a Spurs game and I saw for the
first time I saw um Manu Ginobili in
person doing all the clothes because
we're sitting behind the Spurs bench and
he looked so tall and skinny mm-hmm I
was like dude he looks so unhealthy
right now but like on TV they look
normal he looks skinny on TV but like in
person they all look so much taller and
skinnier yeah makes you wonder who else
what do we really look like in person
actually everybody says that we're a lot
shorter than they thought we would be
yeah I don't know that's sad
it's hard to tell with like YouTube also
because you don't really see usually
like you can't see our legs yeah I'm
gonna
sitting like this in the podcast like
we've met people that we didn't know
we're super tall last the case I was
actually kind of tall okay so all the
big though all the really big - he
doesn't look tall but he's actually
pretty tall rice come my school yeah
yeah like who were there right we're
just short they also we're normal like
normal height but we're all like 4 feet
5 speaking of which chaos is coming into
town again and he went to a club I'm not
sure what with all of us wait is it just
him or the sidemen aside mint - he's the
one who you know so I think they want to
do some kind of collab what but um we
should think of something - maybe we
should you know what he'd do is make it
like a suprise because he didn't tell me
what they're gonna do either so we
should surprise him and like just I
don't know what should we should just
all when he walked into the room would
just box him all of them oh yeah he
loves and we just like start mauling him
just mob him I think I still probably
knock us all out yeah he's so big we're
only 4 or 5 no but then the the twist is
we all lose on purpose and then out of
your room comes Logan ooh and then they
just had the fight right there no Jake
he's fighting Jake no I think he said he
doesn't know really Logan we're gonna
find out the true details and we're
gonna give you guys the exclusive
we're gonna find out what's the real
story here I wonder if no III think I
don't know I feel like evoke isn't Logan
way bigger than Jake I think he's like
considerably no I don't think that's
fair do you think that's fair Logan
versus Jake doesn't Jake seem way
smaller than both of them he's no wise
because you cuz the effect oh yeah yeah
anyway yeah look that up but I know that
Logan was a wrestler was Jake a wrestler
too I'm pretty sure they both are in -
yeah some kind of like combat sport you
know wrestling or whatever I always had
this idea when I would I wanted to do a
Ryan tries I want to wrestle one of them
I mean they're really good they're
really good wrestlers there way heavier
I know but it's not like a serious it's
just
like just for mr. wrestle you know it's
like it'd be like fun I would watch the
hell out of that video yeah
but Ryan I would probably spray beat up
Oh to be titled Ryan tries wrestling
game Paul look at the Paul's the Paul
brothers yeah but I think I would it
would be better to wrestle Jake because
he's smaller I think like more closer to
your weight do you know can you look up
his weight cuz that's a big spoke with
wrestling is like a weight is a big it's
like Dean yeah because if you wrestle so
on even the next weight class it's it's
a pretty big disadvantage right it is
yeah it's I mean the 10 pounds or
whatever weight difference is sometimes
even as little as like 5 remember you'd
be like there's like a 119 weight class
and a 125 130 Wow or 132 or something
like that but it's like that little
amount makes a big difference so for the
boxing match Jake wall weighed in at 82
kilograms which is a hundred and eighty
pounds how do you know that the internet
saw how much is uh how much was ksi and
Logan they would be more I think there
are over 200 I thought kilograms I mean
I wouldn't be surprised there he'll must
kill so case I weighed in Oh for his
earlier fight against Joe Weller was a
182 pounds oh oh they're about the same
oh I don't know where I'm still got like
a bunch of pound yeah I guess Jake isn't
that much smaller than Logan there's no
guess I oh well I guess I can't wrestle
anyone then nevermind rice gum I'll
still do it
no I used to he's too light look him up
let's look him up I think he's like 140
pounds how would you know though there's
not like I'd say he's probably more than
that he's tall but he's skinny dude
that's true but he's pretty muscular
like is he I think so like athletic I
never seen he's good at basketball I
know that what says he weighs about a
hundred and forty three pounds oh don't
you dad that's not shocking friend and
he says that's with the three supreme
chains that he's wearing what are you
where are you getting that this is just
the Internet
okay yeah all right well what kind of
topics we got today
I don't know but well I'm gonna find
somebody to wrestle we're talking about
a lot about a YouTube drama and stuff
that's going on it's a little bit yeah
but there's actually two different
things that we can talk about which is
the Shane Dawson incident which you guys
are already familiar kind of but not
quite and there's another one this Romeo
Lacoste I believe was that he is a
tattoo artist oh I did hear about yeah
he's a tattoo artist he's done tattoos
for like ariana grande Dolin twins ninja
a lot more people and it's come out
where there is allegations against him
that he has been messaging girls gender
age underage girls and also we know that
this is true though like I mean has he
come out and defended himself here he's
done an interview that's defended
himself but with so many people coming
out and saying things and it's not just
like screen shots there's like videos of
it showing that he said certain we'll
say allegedly yeah that's why I said
alleged he saw that he DM these girls
like really sexual stuff and at the time
those girls are like 15 or something
like that 14 15 I just it's still it's
so mind-boggling to me that people I
mean you still do that and have written
proof like don't people learn like even
like a head of files don't not saying
him specifically but how do people still
like wouldn't you know better might not
like that is how do you get caught right
like what this different one you don't
like if he didn't know right like he
didn't know what she was underage but he
said something acknowledging it like
something like hey do you want to wait
till you're 18
or are you more doing it now or
something like that so he acknowledges
that they're underage mmm but how do you
what goes through your head being like
hey this is a good idea I should write
something that's probably think it
doesn't go through the head like this is
a good idea
they're just that's easily thinking with
you know something else
it's penis I just have mental
[Laughter]
no I just want to push the bus you know
you can sleep you say I'll go recorded
that on the Somme board we'd never used
it but I guess there's a reason he is
thinking with that and you know it's I
mean it's a it's got to be like a mental
illness right yeah I mean I'm not trying
to make excuses I'm just saying it it's
there has to be something wrong to be
out or maybe just the person's like a
bad person hmm you know part of me
probably sort of like if you were
talking to a girl and even if there were
I mean obviously talking to underage
girls is like not okay but you don't
really think oh this person is gonna
like tell on me you know I mean or you
don't think of that I would think
because it's I mean I don't know right
but that's kind of what I think of like
when I if I'm sneaking from his point of
view now see for wil and I we've had
experiences not maybe not directly but
we're a friend of ours or something has
spoken to an underage person you know
and and unknowingly yeah you do you do
well me personally knowing I didn't
nothing happened nothing happened though
whoa
we got you exclusives all right okay
what epochal do so see this is out this
is also for like my and my stand-up
stuff but basically this what do you see
in your head at but it was it was on
tinder and to be on tinder you have to
be 18 and over and so this girl on there
had her ages 19 and then so we're just
talking and you know it's just talking
getting to know each other and then how
old were you at the time I oh this is
like maybe a couple of months ago you're
same 8 12 8:28 okay so we're just
talking and then we exchanged snapchat
and still talking on there and then she
goes oh by the way I turn 18 next week
and then I said yikes
and then she said don't worry the legal
age of consent in nevada is 16 and then
i said double yikes
dude what so this is the scary thing cuz
what if what if you already assumed
right what how old she was
yeah and you had already said things
that were sexual to her yeah and then
she said that you'd still be in trouble
yeah even if you didn't know luckily I
didn't say anything though yeah no I
know but I mean that that's that's the
that's happens to people oh yeah
definitely it happens all the time yeah
well that's that's that's scary like I
think in your instance it was uh I mean
you know it better so you wanna yeah I
mean it's not really my story to tell so
I mean I wasn't exactly in the situation
but essentially like I had a friend
growing up who yeah got in trouble and
got accused of doing stuff with younger
girls but he like pled not guilty like
he went through the whole process and
the system is kind of like set up to
like of course like favor of the victim
in that which I guess it should be but
it's also like you would hope that the
system is fair and stuff like that but
depending on which side has more
resources right more family has like
more money for lawyers and stuff like
that obviously that's a big difference
within the legal system and so yeah it
like completely affected his life in a
negative way and so I have at least on
my for my experiences and like my
opinions on that kind of stuff it's
affected by that yeah because he was a
friend of mine and I obviously believe
him that he said like he didn't do
anything right and so let's just say
like what happens if like they're in a
bar a place that's suppose your seems to
be 21 and over
right and there's bouncers who are
supposed to check IDs now let's say that
something happens after that you know I
don't know who should be at fault I
would say I mean I know I know who is at
fault or II the person it's gonna get I
don't I don't think it's right but I
think the person that falls should be
the bar bar should be you know how to
accountable for letting this person fool
them and then that kid or whoever it is
you know using a fake ID to get in there
should be in trouble as well you
shouldn't just be the person who's
talking to this person unknowingly yeah
it's different from what that guy did
when he knew that that girl was underage
I think like I mean I think this
scenario I might be completely off-base
there might be a reason why I don't know
if you guys can think of a reason why I
just think it's not
it's not fair like sometimes girls or
guys even look a lot older than they are
and then it's vice versa sometimes
people look a lot younger than what how
old they are yeah so I mean it's hard to
say just based off looks and you're not
gonna go up to every person you mean be
like hey before we talk how old are you
yeah and even then it was the motion
illegally you're supposed to yeah and
then if it's a fake ID then what yeah
what do you do you just go to jail I
think it's different to like if you know
if he's the person that has like if the
girl right is underage and the guy has
knowledge that she's underage yeah and
the guy continues that's you're in
trouble
agree you should be in trouble like if
you know like I don't know what this I
don't know anything about that situation
but if he was like oh I know you're
underage let's wait till you're old or
whatever and then they kept talking yeah
in that scenario supposedly in the DMS
yeah that she took video of or something
like that he said some like will you
wait well he acknowledged like do you
want to wait to you're 18 mm-hmm so he
knew yeah that's probably allegedly
around a lot allegedly
no but just because we don't get you
know yeah caught up in anything I
allegedly farted on this podcast did not
that's quiet anyway speaking of well the
thing is that this kind of correlates to
what we were talking about before to
where she ain't no shame show that to
Shane's incident last year about him you
know he had that whole pedophilia thing
cuz he made some jokes and whether it
was taken out of context or not that
happened again this week this past week
where Shane
I guess he's getting something
resurfaced about him saying something
about him doing something sexual to his
cats or we had the quote right yeah I
don't know if he want to read it cuz
it's pretty it's pretty graphic but uh
it was on an episode a now-deleted
episode of Shane and Friends on
September 11th 2015 he says one time I
laid my cat down on her back ellipses I
moved her little chicken legs spread
open or whatever and I came all over the
cat it was my first sexual experience
what was it the head nice trying to
bleep myself out there's no bleep all
right well and he says I was also like
but he didn't so he didn't say the
reason why there's controversies people
have pulled that clip up right and I
guess it didn't seem like he was joking
in that supposedly it seemed like a real
story like he was telling a real story
and that's what people have the base off
of it right but he for I guess in the in
his public statement that he issued he
was talking about how it was kind of
like based off an awful sketch that he
never did or anything so he did he say
that though in the I didn't see the
actual interview but did he say like oh
this is based off of a sketch I think it
was in the interview as a tweet oh I see
well then well I mean okay well they
need there's no context there he kind of
put that out there mmm
I could see why people would be upset I
mean but uh honestly I don't I don't I
know Shane that's the cut that's like
his comedy ya know but I don't know I
can see why people would take that
another way but you also said that like
gee he's been in trouble for a lot worse
things he said a lot worse than yes and
he's done videos that are significantly
he doesn't make videos like that anymore
yeah but his his stuff before was pretty
raunchy well that was like his last
sentence was um
I learned my lesson and I'm more
confident now my ability to about
entertaining not just being myself and
not being so shocking well that's his
apology yeah he made so he had to make
an apology for this and I granted this
is again back when he used to make those
kind of jokes I'm gonna assume yeah I
mean it's cons it is way different now
it is wait yeah yeah and I think that
shows like the growth in who he is and
like who you know and like how he is
transformed his entire brand how he has
grown is not just a content creator but
as a person how like you can come from a
place where a lot of people will deem it
as like oh this is like inappropriate
and raunchy and now but the thing is it
always comes back to haunt you because
anything you put online will be there
forever and it's happening every single
year something is targeting Shane
because the more successful he gets the
more of a target he becomes yeah and
that's what really what it comes down to
and we said it before like Shane's
killing it right now and he's made like
a very like slick transition into like
what his brand is now
and it's very sick he's very successful
and they're like Ryan said that's it now
he's an even bigger target so it's like
but we do have to say congratulations
right to Shane
cuz you got engaged oh yeah yeah for
what the cat forget I shoulda got
engaged Congrats to Shane um but yeah
that's kind of unfortunate that that's
happening right now when he announced
that engagement yeah so um do you guys
feel that there should be a time period
of like after five years certain tweets
are like you know you should let those
go to eliminations you're like
presenters kind of yeah like if you
commit certain crimes after a certain
amount of time you can't be charged for
them you're smart
what do you mean such okay well I mean
there's certain things certain crimes
that have that yeah murder is not one of
them yeah
I can't murder someone and then 20 years
later you're good yeah if they find out
you're still you know yeah I think at
least so tweets um I think I personally
think it never will be that way but it
should be because things change a lot
agreed Society changes and you change
yeah like so like in memory in the in
the how to be ninja video we used the FA
G word yeah and that wasn't targeted at
gay people yeah it had a different
meaning for me growing up you know in in
Hawaii specifically saying that word not
that I would even say it now saying that
word had a different meaning in that it
wasn't even necessarily it didn't mean
gay it was like a homophobic slur no no
no it just meant it was just like
something you said to your friends to
make fun of your friends but it wasn't
meant gay it became like a it was more
like Ave action like how you acted no
like an adjective
yeah and then people just associated the
two and it became well this I'm just
saying from Hawaii didn't differ your
point of view yeah the way we grew up
people used to sit and it wasn't like
you could say that before you know gay
people used to say that we talked about
yes they used to say that to you
thanks man well I mean everybody use I
mean it wasn't like it was like another
it wasn't a good word it was still an
insult yeah but it didn't mean gay
it was a gay and that word was
completely different very you took that
down right there's that video we have it
it was down yeah and then I think it
might be blocked something like that
yeah unlisted or something like that but
but that's part of you growing out okay
yeah I'd know better I've already said I
apologized for it like I didn't know
back then I was 16 and even then like it
was a different time yeah I wouldn't
make that video now I mean not like that
you know we even called it out in
another video so I think yeah I mean I
think things change over time something
like I said last time something we're
saying right now could become something
offensive in five to ten years from now
yeah Oh exactly we don't know yet it's
one of those things where obviously
there's like a limit of like how bad is
the tweet all right then it's gonna be
like then that kind of determines I
think like obviously if you say
something super racist on Twitter ten
years ago you should probably have to
explain it yeah like no matter what you
should be like even if it's something
like well I was racist back then you
know I'm saying like yeah now I'm not
like now I've learned I've changed you
think people do you think people that
that have had that change and did
realized a mistake should still be you
know attacked for what they did in the
past even if they acknowledge it mmm no
I don't think yeah I don't think so
there's actually I saw there's mini
documentary about how this former like
races and like we say racist a lot that
we did we do but this guy who used to be
like a white supremacist no word babies
but he realized that his actions turned
around and started and he was a tattoo
artist and he would change people's
tattoos who that used to have like oh
that's like white supremists meanings
and stuff and and changed yeah and and
make it into something entirely new
that's so for people who wanted
Redemption yeah yeah and so that's like
a good story now if people were like
whoa but you're races and little and
just like attacking what people could
yeah people say he became big enough
like he became the next PewDiePie yeah
like that's how popular I guess
- you people would protest him mmm it
would say stop supporting this guy just
because he's he's taking advantage of
what you know you used to do he he would
get attacked I'm 100% sure that that for
sure but then those people are just
stupid idiots are they though they're
mad that's what I'm asking that like
those types of people yeah oh my thank
you - but I'm just saying I mean grab my
sleeve it's it would happen if that guy
even if he means you know he's he
acknowledges he apologizes he's even
making up for it in what he does it
becomes as famous as a PewDiePie anyone
even a shame he is gonna get attacked
for sure he's sorry for what he did and
there's gonna be people trying to take
him down
yeah and it's only because of his
popularity but that doesn't mean that
those people are right yes they're gonna
do that but those people are morons
that's I agree with that yeah because
that is like a huge part of changing the
world for the better
yeah as cheesy as corny as that sounds
taking the people that think a certain
way that's like super bad right yeah
white supremacists and then 10 years
later they're not and they've changed
yeah you absolutely want to praise that
person for making that change yes you do
not want to attacked him for what they
used to believe you know I'm saying
because that's important it's like
changing vote but coming from not saying
that I agree but coming from a different
perspective right
that guy becomes that powerful and you
you know you don't think that person
should have that power because of their
past and the way that they used to think
because you don't trust how they think
wouldn't you want to say stop this stop
this guy you don't want him to have
influence yeah okay well then why can't
that guy become president that no really
it would allow him to become president
what his past being that I think the
thing for me what I would see is like
right oh this guy has had a bad past
right he's aware of it he's admitted to
it and that shows a lot more morals and
Bowser and a lot of the people who are
like look at how perfect I am it's just
like no you're not perfect you're just
really good at hiding your your real
past or true intentions or however
you've been you know because everybody
has that that sense of like evil and
then we're human we naturally have evil
tendencies we're very selfish creatures
and to be able to that evil though what
being selfish a little bit I mean
everybody is selfish
please evil but we have yeah that's why
everybody has like natural evil in them
but to be able to be like okay I this is
my past this is what happened but now I
want to move forward and use how I
overcame this situation to inspire other
people and show like there's a lot
better to life and how we should be
treating people in a positive and humane
matter that that type of person I would
be a lot more like oh I know more about
him I can't relate to this I can respect
that then someone who is like this is
what I want
I'm perfection and all this because I'm
like that's not attainable you're a
lying you're lying somewhere could be
when what you're saying is people maybe
just don't believe that they've made an
honest change that's what I mean yeah
that's I mean because and that's up
that's totally up to them I mean whether
or not they believe them or not is is up
to the own is it yeah this goes back to
PewDiePie and you see the comments to
where people still call them out like oh
how can you support a white supremacist
or someone who said the n-word or
whatever and whether you apologized for
it or not and I mean he did there's
always gonna be those people yeah right
but you're slowly starting to see people
be like okay well he acknowledged it
like reasonable people right and you
know when you really break down what he
did honey we're not gonna get into that
anyway but those people are always gonna
be there
yeah and if you but if you think about
it it's not a minority like if you think
about a different situation like say a
president or candidate right someone
running for president you find out that
this person used to be a white
supremacist or a racist or whatever they
did something really bad in the past and
all of us and they acknowledge it right
that person never will win yeah he would
never become president but I will say
there's a difference in finding out that
this person has that oh but what if he
acknowledges it from the start if you
presents in Malia or someone even have a
chance I could say so yeah you think so
I think so
alright then maybe there's a new
strategy for some presidential candidate
there just come on the podcast and we'll
teach you our techniques to winning the
presidency Paco seems to know a lot
i I agree with you I think that would be
super interesting I think this is a very
honest person exactly but in the eyes of
other people would they be like well why
would I take this guy when there's this
other guy who would like you said we
know he's not perfect but on paper he is
I don't have an answer I don't I'm just
like trying to give another perspective
I'm not even saying I agree with that
I'm just trying to see like from another
from their perspective I mean of course
their policies would matter and
everything but on him but say it was
exactly the same and you had a guy with
a past who acknowledges it versus a guy
who is perfect on paper but you know
their stuff you just would never find
out I'm a I would honestly be pretty
stuck between the two I might pick the
guy like with more flaws in the back
history just because it he shows growth
he shows a lot of growth you know and
for that type of growth in somebody I
don't see why they can't inspire other
people around them to be able to push
through there they're hard issues in
life yeah I mean I don't think there has
ever been like a candidate that that
came out and said I used to be this and
now I'm this and be like super
vulnerable in that sense I don't know if
that would have the would be was Obama
saying that he smoked weed before I
don't know if they found that out or he
just said oh yeah I smoked weed in
college like I don't know if that was
like - because weed was a hot topic and
like I'm not that's true right that's
what he said I I might be lying I don't
know I think that's like then and that's
super relatable people were like and
then people were okay with weed and he
said this is another thing had you said
that maybe ten years ago 15 let's say 15
years ago he would be like oh my god
he's a drug addict yeah no weed wasn't
seen the same way as it is today yeah
that's for sure right well I think it
comes down to the it's like the
whoever's believed the listening or
whoever's listening whether or not they
believe it or not it's like kind of you
can transition into like the MJ story
right or like whatever that was do you
guys watch the documentary I did not
I've read about it well I didn't watch
it yeah
because it comes out of like what you
believe like whose story yeah because
you know facts aside or whether or not
there are facts or are not facts it's
like this person says this this person
says this so yeah it's like it's up to
the person to believe like I know I
should watch it because I should be
up-to-date on those things I just really
don't want to yeah because and it's just
a personal thing yeah I just don't want
to root like I know it's like oh that's
sort your response but like
I don't know like I said I should watch
it but I just don't want to ruin my
vision of what I currently see yeah and
I think that is you can call that
whatever it is but I mean I also like
you said it's coming from someone's
story it's not yeah he's not the venoms
of either so that's just that's unfair
yeah I should probably watch it nothing
is I'm probably much Oh we see she
breaks she she break I need to refill
anyway so refill
she should break come back yes no don't
come back no no no we need the junior
out role cheeky break okay do you
remember what he did yeah here comes the
she she break but I can't sing so you do
it I can't sing and we're back now you
guys are late she's back from the sushi
break which means you know what what
like Blue's Clues
which means you know what time it is
guys SeatGeek time see geek time seek
time and we have our sponsor seek again
shout out to see key for hooking us up
with a sponsor again it is a ticket app
for all you people you if you for
whatever reason skipped the beginning
they put all the tickets in one place
you can get anything I mean pretty much
any kind of tickets that you want
whether it's NBA games I don't know why
this specifically point out Ariana
Grande Travis Scott I think the most to
popular I mean they might just be
popping well who's probably Taylor Swift
and you can get a lot of tickets to
different kinds of concerts and shows
and all kinds of stuff
geek Weiss yeah I don't know about that
one
but you go to see geek and use the code
Higa hig a and you get $20 off your
first seat geek order and yes you see go
again please use it if you're gonna go
to something you might as well look it
up and see
geek use our code so that we look cool
also you save money so that helps you do
save onion on your first order 20 bucks
yeah which is a lot you know there's
some tickets cost 20 bucks I don't know
what but it's kind of cheap so don't
forget
oh speaking of tickets I think I
mentioned this earlier but I saw when I
was driving on the highway here I saw
this this billboard and read in link
we're actually gonna be at Green Valley
Ranch yeah this is not a promo for them
but I just saw them I was like oh that's
pretty cool no it's a promo and now they
have to be on this podcast and they have
to pay us yeah no I just saw I don't
know what it is but like their tickets
were like I don't know like less than 20
bucks do we get if CG does that do we
get paid to go no I just saw them on the
bill I thought that was cool anyway yeah
we're back we're back you wouldn't ever
do live shows yeah what do you mean I
used to I know but now I mean I'm not a
hundred percent of polls I just don't
know what I would do
I don't know so how much opposed would
you be Hardy post-16 not just 16 okay I
mean I'm not that opposed to doing shows
I just I don't like the travel part I
don't mind doing shows I just don't have
anything to do mmm
like when we did ytf and toured and
stuff I was just the host like that's
not hard to do just get the crowd for
the real talent
what you do in Manila then I did like a
very poor version of a song that people
know that's it you danced as well yeah
but it's not like Rio dancing it's like
watching very very very amateur people
do very very amateur singing and dancing
but it's because it's us it's better
than nothing you know that's how people
see it oh at least they're trying but
it's awful like it's it's but it's bad
like I mean our performances were bad in
comparison to real dancers and real
singers it was better but very close to
nothing yes yeah but it is better than
nothing it's like at least which it's
better than us just coming out and doing
nothing yeah I think that's why I wanted
to do it
and it's like kind of like schizo we do
like Live skits away but yeah I'm not
I'm not a performer you are you doing I
mean like to do stuff like that yeah
because I need attention and that's all
what I'm fueled off of but I want
attention attention too but that's what
drives me and this tiny thing I have but
for you if you if you could do something
I guess what would you like to do if you
had the ability to show yeah yeah
honestly I've always wanted to do like a
I mean not just my stuff I would want to
coordinate some a show like 8:00 like if
I had dancers and I had singers and make
make us basically a long video mm-hmm
but live mmm this is a place behind a
kind of but like in using different
talents I wouldn't personally want to be
in it director kind of like a director
writer I guess and then kind of okay I
have this talent and I have this talent
and this time how can I make this all
work and then make it like epic at the
end and you know like follow a video
thing where you build up something plan
things in the beginning have them like
slowly water it and then pay off at the
end like I don't know I just think
that's fun that part of it not me
actually being in in do you like
musicals mmm it depends depends I don't
I never used to but it depends I like
the ones that have actual story and it's
not just for the sake of singing yeah so
like have you seen wicked no where's
that it's I like a spin-off of Wizard of
Oz oh but it's like from the witches
perspective and stuff it's actually
pretty good
is it a movie or a musical like where
did you see it in a theater in a theatre
but like a musical theater oh oh I see I
see
yeah yeah here no in Hawaii oh yeah
sounds great yeah it's pretty dope I
seen the Lion King one oh that one's
uber good so it's pretty it's cool
because I've already seen the movie and
it's you're getting to see it how they
are doing it alive
that's the only cool part to me yeah but
like I don't know I know I wasn't I was
a big fan of musicals how about you will
am i a big fan of musicals like what
have you seen
I saw the Nutcracker when I was super
young excited music oh yeah it's a toy
sounds like a wrestling
musical I'm never what is it about it's
a Christmas musical Nutcracker yes oh
yeah yeah that toy comes alive for
something I've never liked a battle has
a ballet in it it's very classical oh I
didn't know yeah it's like Christmas Toy
Story yeah are you making this up
no no Nutcracker Oh song - yeah I've
heard of Nutcracker by pretty sure it's
that little toy thing with the yeah
that's what it is story the story is
like this girl gets it and then it like
comes alive or something somebody copied
somebody he just had that Netflix I was
watching that
alright I liked it I know as I like to
go back and watch old movies that now
when I watch them I'm like damn I know
this isn't good but I love it because of
it just reminds me of a different time a
time where I used to lie in front of my
TV and eat nectarines technically I
think the nutcrackers a ballet no I
think about it oh yeah you got to be
technical people will get on you for
that when I did music was in real life
the video mm-hmm I got so many comments
that were like these aren't real
musicals like you guys are left out how
could you leave out this and Hamilton
these are just Disney movies I don't
know why they sound like that but get
him yeah but they were so salty I was
like I didn't know there was such a clan
behind musicals yeah yeah they meet they
I was I guess I insulted them I'm sorry
I don't know my musicals hey don't
apologize any other podcast I'm sorry
every time on musicals uh Twitter
questions we should get those we have we
have to get through some of those all of
them it's my favorite part is it your
favorite part I like we'll start off
with this awesome comments going hey do
the Twitter questions Paco shut up yeah
yeah they're hating on me for that and
I'm not sorry all right
more a job more than that it says to
talk about dead series such as Park
Horus willing Greg while
cars cooking but not really teatime and
I dare you will they make a return and
the gang like making these videos bed
alright they're not dead we just haven't
had everybody around recently they're
hibernating bro so normally when we do
those videos before it's because people
were always free right and now Derek's
in China China he's coming back he's
coming back in a week
pretty cheap roll weeks he's gone for a
month yeah he's dancing in a job walkie
show um that's not private information
is it no he's dancing in a show so he
had to be what he was gone for a week
and then Sean was gone for life no shot
well not that we couldn't do it without
him because we have like even like Park
horses only five people hmm oh four five
five people it's been so long it's dead
I know I can already forgot but we do
need to do a tee time because we have a
lot of stuff that stuff filed we do have
to do that I'm down to do a part course
for a while I couldn't because I had
ankle issues from basketball but I think
I'm good now injuries definitely played
a pretty big like par course you need to
be like physically ready ready
dude I'm winning the next one you always
say that now I'm confident this time
anyway the first time Paco was on par
course I think what episode was at the
bridge one though on the pond was the
bridge or played one yeah when he jumped
over a little river thing yeah yeah
whatever episode that was Paco before
that this is before he did any part
course he would just watch them and I
think on video it looks a lot easier so
he was just like he was so confident
yeah and he was like we should we should
have bet him because he I knew he could
there are certain things that you just
it's harder than it looks
I'm wearing shoes next time okay yeah
that's the problem you got out the first
one I was the first one I ran into a
water those that don't know Park horse
is our series where we do parkour but
it's our version like it's it's not
parkour yeah we do stunts but it's like
horse so like if someone does something
then the next person follows I like that
series it's just I for a long time I was
hurt and then you know not everybody was
around I read by people did a good way
to describe it is that it's not nothing
it's a little bit better than nothing
it's amateur people doing parkour
the other thing is when we made it we
were like 21 and now we're almost 31 so
what yeah not us
well I mean on average yeah 29 you know
well we did it I think the first thing
we did in Australia which is me Greg and
you Greg and Sean John yeah and we were
just you always had the idea but we'd
never did it we just bore we're in we're
at a show where I was doing something
like hosting and we were in the green
room for like six hours or something
like that we had time to kill so we just
started turning on the camera stuff we
already did
mm-hmm but yeah that show did really
well yeah we should probably do one did
I made a best of parkour video for you
to post its but that's just like the
same stuff people have seen yeah but
that's like a good a it's coming back
okay well we'll do a trailer then how
about that make it a trailer yeah
well Greg willing Greg is it is it dead
it's probably dead I don't know we're
gonna make it
maybe wild card is dead maybe no is it
coming back big into that zone I don't
know cooking but not really I could see
us making that probably more than any
other ones yeah actually when Shawn was
here visiting he we were like going to
do it but then he we only thought of it
on the last day this no it isn't gonna
take all day those takes so much longer
than people think because we don't know
what we're gonna do to that day yeah so
half the day is me and Shawn just like
hey what if we did like a burrito
but it's pizza like that's right yeah
most times it's not something that we
that's good like the one time we did
that one for Shawn like I got the
experience whatever you like it's ours 2
to 3 hours with us just sitting there
like what should we do yeah as a cos
this relate to short like you know it's
it's a lot yeah it's it's genuine I mean
it's not fake like we don't like we do
it for real yeah so it's not like us
like we're not pretending like we're not
coming up with it on the spot
TV time you already said yep tee time
again I dare you we do it just now
there's so many rules on YouTube
everything I all the I dare use most of
the I dare use that I put up got
demonetised or age-restricted because
it's like dangerous things or gross
things so it's like it's tough I mean
I'll still probably I'm still open to
doing them yeah it's just we make
nothing
off of them so unless SeatGeek wants to
as well it's pretty hard to do it and
commit to it something that you are
probably gonna lose money off yeah oh
yeah it's a big umbrella answer for this
is as a good time schedules lining up
because Derek coming back healthy
Rebecca having everyone available one
day you know that's pretty rare so it's
we need we'll bring it back and we need
to start some new stuff too yeah some
new shows cuz it get tired of doing the
same stuff yeah um next question from
Kelsey crushing neck what are your guys
thoughts on the cancel culture what is
canceled we already touched on it a
little bit but it's kind of like where
if somebody says something or it gets
brought up from their past every uh that
all Twitter will just be like oh this
person's can so that's exactly what we
talked about yeah exactly
so we already touched okay and this does
that come from like if you get a show
cancelled I have no idea that's like
Roseann trouble when you get your show
cancelled yeah I think I think in
general it's just like the new thing
yeah like if somebody does something and
damn you're cancelled I didn't know it
was called that okay me neither which I
was like makes sense yeah and then like
outraged calls your type of thing I like
Anthony we kind of get out of here give
our opinion you're cancelled give our
opinion on that area I think right yeah
we definitely did okay
Thank You Kelsey sky wings do you guys
have any goals or dreams you'd like to
accomplish some time in your lives which
are maybe outside of YouTube Oh an
example hobbies skills or places to miss
well go ahead you seem excited I mean I
have a lot of hobbies as you know you
have too many hobbies one that was like
actually a realization for me was um
it's like so weird and random another
thing you guys know this but it was I
was traveling I think it might have been
coming back from twitchcon and I was in
the airport and I saw someone who was a
dog handler like you know like they like
she's you know sniffing for security
person security person but they have a
dog and I was like yeah I think I could
do that yeah you have a dog and I really
like working with dogs on that like like
that level of training them and like
having giving them something they feel
fulfilled you know and like giving them
the work and stuff and but will it ever
happen I don't know probably probably
not cuz that's like a huge commitment
yeah I have to be super like educated
and a lot of I think a lot of people in
that field are usually probably like
ex-military or you know police police
work and stuff like that but I think as
like a random career hobby thing that
I'll be really interested in oddly
enough that is kind of it for me that's
really specific I remember seeing it and
go because they were working with a new
dog and that's why they were actually
actively training and so um I was
looking I was like man that looks really
cool and like fulfilling and fun and and
then it's just one of those realizations
that you see something and you're like
yeah I think you could do that kind of
thing how about you man you have a lot
of I have a lot of things you're I love
myself as weird you're one of those
people that you get really excited about
something and you put so much effort
into it and then something else comes up
and then you put so much effort into it
and then sometimes you bounce back to
those things and you put so much effort
into it and I'm kind of like at you
jumping around yeah I'm kind of like
that as well like you want to be a
rapper
at one point no I didn't want to be a
rapper oh what I just did it cuz it's
fun
oh okay well then you want to do
stand-up which you have been putting
time into yeah which is I think you
would be good at I think you actually
would you know performing you're a
performer more than a thanks more than
you know oh and then you want to be a
waiter so we were at dinner then my dad
I was with my dad and we're talking
about I don't know what your grad season
epochal goes to Cheesecake Factory a lot
lawyer sell a lot of loads buys like
three at once and he takes them home to
eat throughout the week yeah he knows a
lot so we were with my family and my dad
went to go there we didn't really know
like there's some of the menus
ridiculous like it's so big yeah and
then and then Bach was like explaining
everything like he knows everything
oh if you won't try this something more
savoury and like he's like giving the
whole thing and my dad is like oh you're
a better
you're a better waiter than you are all
youtuber and he meant it in like a
compliment like he didn't even think
like and we all just started dying and
Paco got so mad he walked away from the
table like anything I jokingly I was
like laughing but I walked outside dad
met didn't mean it that way
and I don't know you said it again but
then he said after that after like I was
like huh
come on uncle how you gonna call me out
like that and he's just like see that's
what you get for calling me dumb but
really at the first time you said it he
wasn't making that joke yeah but are you
like your ex you're really good wieder
that's what he meant to say basic you're
a better waiter than your youtuber I was
like damn that is the best disc
yeah he was referring to the last
podcast where you said or to podcast I
guess what I wanna do like you said is
like stand oh yeah
so that's like what I'm pursuing writing
going a lot I like open mics and stuff I
believe in you
trying to hit up shows and things you
know yeah I've been talking to a lot of
people who do like panels and stuff at
colleges cuz that's like that was
something that interested me too I was
like but the college circuit is so
different it is what you want to do
panels yeah are you comedy oh they're
comedy and panels and stuff because I'm
gonna get to be himself yeah Oh like
talking about your he's performing
essential I've got more live stuff yeah
just I think you're better at I kill at
those dude okay well now I don't want to
compliment see this is exactly what we
talked about that's why I don't to
compliment you anymore good
anyway funny when you get big a big
stand-up person and you go on Joe Rogan
mm-hmm tell him I said hi and the people
on is yeah yeah but only like really
like successful ones yeah or his friend
yeah and a lot of them are stand-up
people tell him we said what's up all
right
hey this podcast I was on like last week
says hi yeah oh yeah I love that vodka I
want to be on there I'm gonna get into
what am I getting to stand up just so I
can meet Joe Rogan and be on his podcast
I think you could do well you just don't
want to I don't think I could that's
good
you just don't believe in yourself that
way yeah this goes back to the beginning
of the podcast I don't believe I think
you could I think you're good at writing
jokes and you could figure out a way to
deliver them in like I don't know you
know what it is though have bad memory
that's also true
I would you spend on a lotta time but
you could make it like a thing where
you're just like sitting up there
reading jokes you know that's like could
be a thing all right yeah I mean jokes
Rogan something like specifically Adam
tell me you're good tell me a good joke
right now man I just did
good you farted Oh get out uh do you get
people like when people ask you what do
you guys do you know and you're like oh
I gotta do YouTube and stuff and I know
what kind of content do you do or
whatever and you're like oh what do you
guys say I say sketch okay
sketch in vlogs I say yeah I see like
something some like kind of comedy like
I say like I'll kind of random stuff
like fake trailers I say like a like a
handful of things like I just a general
audience comedy oh but I don't like fake
movie trailers like music videos like
sketches I say like do people ever say
Oh tell me a joke then or something like
that oh no really
okay why I don't know it just feels
weird when people say oh tell me a joke
like if I they're like oh what do you do
I like comedy stuff and they told me a
joke then really it's so awkward why
don't you just say no knock-knock joke
Rogen laughs tell them that go away it's
a good one it's pretty bad hmm okay what
were you saying you saying what would
you do outside of YouTube Oh outside of
YouTube well that's it has closed the
question even I forgot what's off top do
you have any goals or names
to accomplish some time in the law in
your lives which are maybe outside of
YouTube papi skills be a UFC fighter
really I mean if I if I was like 10
years younger and I I'd get into YouTube
or and I dropped out of college and I
was like damn I got nothing I would
start training you wouldn't be a fighter
I think they're talking about right now
about likewise I still would want to be
a fighter now because I know what else
we're gonna do
dog handling but I would like that a
career wise so yeah I know I'm what
wouldn't be I mean I would love to be a
NBA basketball player too short and I
fast enough can't shoot three I can't
jump yeah my wrist is bro I would
probably have to rebreathe my wrist my
wrist can actually grow my shooting form
yeah but since that's not realistic can
you get out of a wrist grab
oh no for the listeners will grab yeah
and then he hurt me sorry I would do I
mean I I I would love to learn how to
fight yeah well yeah I mean I like
combats well I do yeah I mean I grew up
doing judo my whole life and then
wrestling and I dabbled in jiu-jitsu and
it's just fun it's not even like a
matter of like wanting to beat someone
up it's just knowing like it's just a
very it so it pushes you so hard to the
point that you feel excellent after yeah
it's just a weird feeling after you get
done with a session and you're just like
at the brink of like man I would rather
die than keep going if you haven't felt
that it feels so good when you're done
yeah I don't know it's just a good
feeling put you in a better mood
well so yeah just spider Wow
yep that's what's up I'll fight ya out
of here do you agree all your sleeve I
think matter the last video is like if
you get 10 likes we'll fight we unlike
that'd be a good video ryan tries
fighting Paco yes why just me though why
not everybody I'm not fighting that's
war I'm not I mean I'm not a I'm not a
fighter either like we'll nose out a box
I don't know a box
you said you boxed before no oh I did a
wing John he did we I did Wing Chun and
yeah that's the same type of what is
McEachern that's the fast one right
that's like it man yeah
yes you did that how fast are you people
they went really fast like soul free
camera and look like they weren't moving
[Music]
yeah uh I don't know no when the whole
boxing thing happened I was like kind of
excited mm-hmm but I was like I really
would like to do MMA but Mike I don't
it's it's tough because I don't want to
hurt somebody
yeah and at the same time I don't want
to get hurt you know like really met you
get really messed up but if that was
like I said if I wasn't doing YouTube
that's something I always wish I had
trained in at least that's why I like
for me cuz I man I'm a terrible person
but I like hurting people but not in a
physical way Oh like that's why I like
this no like like in roasts battles
that's why I saw a rapid though cuz it's
fun just like but that's not really
hurting them cuz you're expecting to get
roasted yeah but it's fun it's it's if
you like being the person that is like
you got them you're like getting I like
getting got to like if someone hits me
with a good dish I'm just like damn I
respect that I respect you for that
mmm I'm a sadistic person interesting
yeah all right well thank you sky thanks
for that that's a good question I like
that one questions are this from Madison
meme or Mamie questions you get asked a
lot that you get annoyed by this go dude
the question I get annoyed most god this
is oh when I when people ask where's
Ryan
for what what do you mean like if I'm
just walking around and then they're
like oh Paco
hey where's Ryan or something I'll let
you know good I like that question you
text me I'll probably add in my room
that's what I say but and I you know I
may be in the kitchen no I say at his
house because I know 90 something
percent you know I'm right
makes me so annoying it's not annoying
because people asked where you were I
would say I don't know maybe no but
nobody asked you where I am sometimes
I passed them hey where's Blanco yeah
he'll be like it's not really late but
for me it's just like when you're trying
to do be able to do something on your
own with your own type of branding and
stuff and to always be constantly
reminded of like Oh where's Ryan your
boss or the guy more successful with a
new type of thing you know it's just
like for me I'm sure not I'm not more
success for you in twitch no or other
things you do or stand-up no you you
have such a platform that you're no like
like yeah I get that yeah I get that
could be annoying but now that you've
said that it annoys you you're gonna get
it way more yeah and I'm just gonna ban
everybody okay
well banned me I'm gonna ask the first
behind me I made a twitch just so I can
comment and stuff
I don't think I'm trying to think of
like questions annoy me do you have a
specific question that annoys you
where's Shawn know what about riding did
you get annoyed by that question a lot
no I don't get annoyed because I just
don't answer it we also don't look at
social media what do you mean you know
look all the time what question just
don't always respond yeah I look all the
time I don't know I honestly cannot
think of one like specifically that
annoys me mm-hmm all right this is from
Vanessa specifically to you well how did
you meet your girlfriend Monica oh you
talked about this oh I don't think so so
how so we had a group of step boys we
talked about that last podcast before to
to last one with us yeah and then Dom
Dietrich so when I was like 16 they
started going to a gymnastics place and
that's the one that Monica's parents
owned they owned a gymnastics place and
its really pretty common or she's really
fortunate for breakers to be able to go
to a gymnastic Center and work on stuff
because you can work on flips you can do
stuff in a setting that you won't get
super hurt right yeah yeah and so that
was like a big deal so we started like
going there and then Dom actually
started talking to Monica well I think I
was 16 I was really young how old is how
old is Monica they were at the time I
mean she's only a couple years older
yeah a few years older I was 16 or 17 so
we were kids
and then so that was how she kind of
like knew everyone was like she started
hanging out with the actual breakdancing
crew yeah which was what Dom was in and
she was in their crew she was in a
better way better dancer than I was and
yeah so that's basically how she kind of
came into like our group of friends and
that many many many many years later
they had like dated for just a little
while and then separated and then kind
of we started going there right and then
Dom went to LA and became superstar and
became famous and then we we were
luckily able to use her dance place
right for because we didn't have that
much money we needed a place to practice
and so we started going there and then I
don't remember it was like someone's
birthday we went out and we just kind of
made out started talking and then I was
like and I showed her some sweet dance
moves yeah and then she was like that's
exactly what happened but that's really
it was just kind of like she was in our
group of friends and she was like super
hot super model and I was like man she's
way out of my league still is shoot high
and then I was like hey and then yeah
the bases start talking her and and then
we became super good super good friends
and became close and then I remember
before like before we started dating
because I remember calling Dom because I
knew they had dated a lot like a long
long time ago but I called him I was
like hey cuz I didn't want to you know
date some friends yeah we were also
super close and I think you were
actually there I was in the apartment I
was living with Dom when you called him
yeah like I called Dom and said you know
I got something to tell you like I
started you know I'm getting pretty
close to Monica and I know you guys
dated a long time ago you know is it
cool if I start you know spectively
trying to pursue like being in a
relationship with her and then that's so
crazy that you were those in the observe
even knows that I remember when he got
off the phone they were talking you guys
were talking for a bit yeah remember
when he got off the phone he just
started laughing it's like dude guess
what you won't get who just called me
he's like we'll just call me and
he says that he asked me for permission
to date Monica or something like that
yeah he's like laughs he's like I think
oh did I didn't know I was like did you
guys date is it yeah we did like a long
time ago yeah something like that
and I was there and now we're all
connected well it meant a lot to me you
know because he was afraid he's a really
close friend and I wanted to be like
upfront and be like him you know I'm
talking to this girl and you guys used
to date so I don't want to be right yeah
and so yeah that's what I called it was
like is he's cool basically yep and
that's the story of William Monica and
that's a story how did you and Arden
meet
well that's the question yeah wait wait
oh I see a yellow Paco
how did Ryan and Artemis exact question
that was my question I tweeted that um
we initially met apparently Orion has a
different story but I thought we met
outcomes effect on well we're trying to
get on the next podcast when she comes
in she's comes back into town spoilers
oh but we met this is my story on the
set
I seen a video when we were like I was
made Wong foo casting agents of secret
stuff yeah 2010 and I was weighing their
videos I mean like okay who would be a
good tailor which is the name of the
girl in the in the short so we're going
to all these different people that want
food kind of like auditioned or whatever
but apparently according to art and I
was there at the auditions and like or
the casting and I do not recall that at
all I don't remember seeing people
reading I was never a casting person I
never you know I wouldn't know how to do
that so I'm pretty sure wasn't there but
she says I was but supposedly we met
there and she auditioned for this thing
and I looked through the tapes these
different tapes and I remember being
like oh she's good I want her and that's
how we met initially on that set and we
weren't dating obviously we're just
working and it was after I guess after
we finished filming we kind of stayed in
touch and we kind of started hanging out
more we weren't really dating um but
basically it didn't work out we were
like we like I think we've both liked
each other but it just didn't work out
at the time I think I was like not even
19 or 20 20 maybe and she's like 24 or
something like that and she's older than
her
we're 23
on line she was like older than me and I
can see from her perspective being the
girl and you're not even now remember
like we'd going I couldn't even drink
hey tell of a snake story dude oh yeah
and then the steak story does a snake
story well I want to bring that up when
she when she uh when she comes on so she
can defend herself my story is way
different than yeah that's what I mean
so I think it's well that was how we met
yeah how we started dating and then we
got back in touch later down the road
before a collab that we did every room
the romantic knows before that before we
we got back in touch through Facebook
before that whatever what was that video
romantic romantic something blows up at
the end I said directed by Michael Bay
that video um in Vegas or LA it was in
Vegas it was in Vegas we were filming
member in that shed and it was like Joel
figurines yeah I think is a romantic
movie one something like that but it was
that was it was right before that collab
yeah we got back in touch but that's
like four or five years later no yeah
and that's about it
nice good story I can't wait to hear
Arden's so I know I know
so Paco how did you meet your girl what
are you having yeah dude so she and I
met I don't have a girlfriend do I wear
Crocs you do have a are you trying to be
private about this you often I've never
I don't have a girlfriend oh you're just
what I just like I'm not player I just
crush a lot yeah I wear Crocs though so
if it protects my virginity because I'm
a wholesome person you know sure yeah
and they're camouflaged I have Crocs as
well yeah I bought everybody Crocs yeah
basically Paco still in the market
ladies
is he though or guys not anyway that's
it for today guys give me so I don't
have any sounds ready ok penis
thank you guys for the Twitter questions
this is my favorite segment yeah I know
we wanted to do another segment in the
future I just don't know how to do it I
want to do like a radio show you know
how they do like prank calls yeah but
like really like not just like your
refrigerator whatever like really
detailed ones like let's I really want
to do that
um there's there's there's been like not
I'm not that I want to get into pranks
but there's been this radio show I've
been listening to it here and they do
like these prank calls and they're super
basically a friend will recommend hate
prank call my friend hmm and they come
up with these scenarios and they get all
this information so they really make it
feel real I want to do something like
that I think we could do it live I think
it'd be funnier though if we did it to
other youtubers maybe cuz they know of
you people like you know yeah yeah
almost like a Punk'd but if we would
have to get permission from the friend
because that's how we would get the
information yeah it's hard to prank
youtubers cuz they already get pranked
like a lie you do is I know that even me
like I don't answer any calls unless I
know who it is so I don't know just
something that is just try think of
something else we could do yeah I don't
know let us know in the comments what
else we should do here I just got the
idea from that radio show also since we
are wrapping up and stuff we are trying
to use reddit as well we have a reddit
calm and then just started yeah nigahiga
so yeah there's been actually some
pretty funny posts in there very funny
people
yeah pleasantly surprised so yeah check
that out guys
beep our instagram twitter is at off the
pill pod no mom at off the pill you're
gonna fix that dude that's confusing and
Instagram is at off the pill podcast
right and we also have mugs now and the
subreddit is what's the suburb just
nigahiga boom got it so you can discuss
like other videos as well even though
those get posted a little less
frequently but we are gonna be a part
part of that community and like
interacting with you guys yeah probably
gonna do an AMA there as well whoa I
just don't know why it's just a Q&A
right yeah much but they call it that in
there but you can be in your underwear
right you can just sit there you don't
have to go to a place you just sit in
your PJs you do that with a Q&A to know
get them
all right well thank you thanks again
for listening to the appeal podcast I
guess we'll talk to you next one and
hopefully it's Ari
that'll be dope yeah we'll see when she
comes when she finishes filming so see
you guys next time outro song usually
ask a question while we're brief I'm not
I'm not going to I knew you were waiting
for something I was waiting for someone
else to step up penis