Brian literally just released a video
hopefully camera saying who he's dating
right I did just release a video thing
I'm dating it and then we like kissed
and then we just stayed there and then
the tongue came him swirling around
you guys like that new intro
Oh sicko intro oh good job David yeah
David did that we didn't nice we're not
the one singing that um okay well
welcome to that weather welcome back to
another exciting episode of off the pill
podcast the original podcast crew the og
crew it's only been like one month we
wanted to like five we've done the most
together though that's true yeah but
before we get started today I have a
very big announcement they already know
they already know what it is but guys we
finally did it things so a lot of you
guys out there and you know it was a
continuous joke we finally have our
first sponsor of the podcast so I'm
gonna read it real quick our sponsor is
called SeatGeek
and you guys could give back okay I'm
just gonna read the talking points
because that's what I'm supposed to do
apparently some students do this this is
my first time doing guys see geek it is
a ticket app that makes buying super
simple they put all the tickets in one
place so you can focus on what matters
most the live experience or the live
experience what makes more sense you can
find all events on SeatGeek like NBA
Ariana Grande Travis Scott literally any
show or game I guess you can probably
think of it's probably there I would
have to tell you oh you get $20 off your
first see geek order you get $20 off
your first seat geek order with the code
he got hig a see how special I am
special anyway there's gonna be a link
right at all in the description so click
it download the app use código for $20
off tickets that is a deal that is a
good deal and you know what guys if
you're out there and you're actually
gonna buy tickets save $20 make us look
good so they're like eh you know what
let's sponsor this podcast for they're
only doing this episode for real and
maybe one in the future but um it would
be nice to have a consistent sponsor
yeah
dude you killed it thank you doing her
very first sponsor now oh great l spent
at I did almost mess up on the part
where I said the live experience the
live experience I should probably read
and practice these things before I call
I before I go live on top podcast I
should have that practice anyway Thank
You C key our first sponsor nice very
nice but now that we've taken care of
that
pretty sick oh yeah there's so many new
things man we got the control how about
this since you know this is like our
first sponsor if you were to see a
concert or a sporting event
where would you go the first one I'd
that they have listed here the NBA Spurs
I actually have I mean I haven't used
SeatGeek yet but I mean I've if they're
consistent spawns on we might get some
hookups your name yeah I mean this does
that mean I get to consistently have a
$20 off your first purchase that's what
it says but I mean come on well just
type in he goes so that it looks good so
that we look good and it's like oh man
we got to give these guys more money oh
yeah what would you use or would you go
I would want to go to like a comedy show
call me show ya cool I see I see a lot
of people act so black pink I think I
believe what's that oh man I hope I'm
not messing it up but they have a show
in LA now like a concert it's it's a
k-pop group real popular and a lot of
that I think yeah there's a k-pop group
yeah female k-pop group and ever heard
they probably know this they like I see
a lot of people on Twitter trying to get
tickets and there's like two thousand
people in the queue before them online
and like people were buying tickets from
online vendors as white black pink whoo
yeah this is this new like an you know
they've been away for a while but they
can't be like I mean they're not like an
80s right no they're pretty big they're
bigger than BTS they're not bigger than
BTS but as a female group they're huge
yeah hey did you guys know get them I
don't know if there's this is gonna get
get us some hate but um did you guys
know that bTW
in Korean means something what does it
mean the Korean Americans I think I
don't know about Korean Koreans what is
this it stands they call BTS actually
stands for some not that not that group
okay when they can't they say after you
know it's just saying in in I don't know
about in Korea but for Korean Americans
BTS means burning Dunkleman syndrome or
something like that
Tong Tong Kamal is it Tong come on I'm
not Korean but I know it's like burning
toe come on sensation or something like
that and that basically means like after
you eat spicy food when you get fired No
so BTS actually means like fire poop
probably because they got fire
that's probably the name of one of their
songs fire shoes or something like that
that sounds like a BTS sorry BTS is high
they have so many hardcore fans that
like even just now I had to be like man
I should wear this very thing about them
is they have a lot of inspirational
songs that have like good meaning to
their lyrics but their fans how can you
understand it it's it's the lyrics and
like the meanings of stuff and you see
them you haven't translated but a lot
it's weird cuz a lot of times certain
parts of their fandom will be way too
aggressive and like not live what
they're praising you know so if they're
saying like yeah peace and unity and
then like their fans are like kind of
not doing this yeah that's like most
people though cult it's a gold well
alright don't put this on this is does
not reflect the views called I mean
that's theirs isn't that a sane cult
fandom yeah kind of thing so make sense
yeah but they are I mean like I mean
from the moment we had we had BTS
meaning behind the scenes on our second
Channel videos since I don't know how
long and I don't know where or when it
started happening but all these people
and I've just seen it grow over the
years these BTS army fans have been
there since I don't know do you remember
when it started happening I don't
remember exactly but I just kept
thinking yeah you just use all of a
sudden there was all these people say
like BTS army and then at first I
thought they met like this yeah I was
like yeah
yeah they're representing our behind the
scenes they really care about us
oh no they'd it's it's amazing how far
they've come
it's crazy and aren't are they like
considered them like most successful
kpop I would I would say so yeah ever I
would you know what I would at least in
the US for sure they hit didn't they hit
like one of their first number one like
the first Korean has kpop band to hit
like number one in the billboards or
something but they were also on I think
like Time magazine like the front the
front page mmm really I can't even I
can't picture a bunch of Asians on Time
magazine let alone one yeah I don't know
they don't really read do they all speak
Korean or do they like they've learned
English so they do interviews in English
and stuff like for the audience yeah
yeah yeah that's so crazy
well you know it's crazy that I thought
I thought kpop was kind of like dying
mm-hmm
I mean that's why I did we didn't really
like keep going with a whole BGA thing
but yeah I mean people keep asking I
thought I thought you would get tired of
it you know by the second one I still
working on another oh you heard what
that is not off the press is it uh what
is it called when you give out
information that makes exclusives yeah
that copyright can we do that well I
mean if you guys are doing a mother
working on another song yeah yeah you
guys could get a show and have a concert
and then people could get their tickets
at Sikhi there you go see it your show
at or see you could set it up because we
can't afford to put on my god those got
that kind of fanbase buying all that
stuff all that merch how about you will
how about you where would I go I would
probably pick a concert honestly I'm
usually not too picky when it comes to
concerts I mean as long as it's like a
music group that I like I'm down you
know or sports like go into a like a fun
sports event go most like support Jeremy
or who sees spurs like I'm down
siegy Jeremy just went over to the
Raptors yeah yep he's uh because you
don't know Jeremy Lynn yeah Jeremy Lynn
just
it wasn't trade he's bought out
basically he's on he went from the
Atlanta Hawks who are in the bottom
probably five teams in the whole league
to literally like the top maybe like the
top three team so he legit has a chance
to win a ring not likely because the
Golden State's always going to be the
favorite but God we got I don't know
don't get me going on basketball
basketball
nobody cares about basketball whose
leaves you grabbing in basketball we're
gonna do a side podcast of Ryan in
support I know I want to do like a
sports podcast so there's this um
there's this player on the raptors
actually Danny Green who has a podcast
called the green room I think he has a
podcast yeah gangrena so oh but I mean
I'm a fan because you know he's uh he
was a spur yeah one of my favorite Spurs
but he got traded within the whole Kawhi
Leonard trade again I think I don't know
if we should stand the topic of
basketball but basically has a he has a
podcast and I would definitely be dumb
and if he's down Danny Green actually
there's a chance now we have a
connection we I can tell Jeremy a get
Danny Green hey let's get oh you don't
be funny we gotta get Kawhi Leonard and
see how much we can get him to talk oh
that would be good honestly you would be
good for like a sports like podcast tell
if you like to talk about basketball and
maybe like fighting yeah like UFC or MMA
these are your hobbies and it's it is
your paw fighter you know no it's your
hobbies that yeah but you like those I
know it's like it's such a different
even when I tweet and I tweet about like
when I'm watching fights and stuff my
RIA every um my replies are so like
empty because nobody cares all like the
people who follow me and stuff do not
associate me with basketball or with MMA
or any of that but that's like my
interests we're about to have a second
channel podcast for sports first channel
is sponsored by see these get off the
topic of sports
yeah sports because I already know
you're so uninterested it'll be
on the side podcast well I mean it's
like hobbies so why don't we just go
into hobbies and stuff cuz this I guess
when it's us and it's not about the
guests and we're s have any guests like
you know the audience just want to get
to know us a little bit more and hear
about like what things we like to do so
Ryan you know a lot of people are
curious like oh when you're making when
you're not making videos which is almost
24/7 what do you like to do in your free
time cuz even I mean not making videos
24/7 because you're always like working
we talked about it on the podcast Thank
You Minotaur we're not I thought you
mean I'm not working on videos 24/7 I
was like that's pretty much all we do
nice I think I said when you're not okay
video yeah which is got it okay yeah
then what like what are your what are
your hobbies that you actually like to
do in your spare time did I actually do
I mean yeah I think it talked about this
like just video games video games yeah
basketball watching best one fighting
just pretty much there's not that much
honestly very boring people we don't go
out normally unless people are in town
actually yeah that's that's pretty much
the only time we ever go out we're very
boring people actually you go out a
light right ooh go out I exercise a
hobby kind of like stay fit you know
that's I mean that's a deficit me
anytime
yep you have quite a few too many you're
an outdoorsman for sure I have too many
I'm like a hobbyist for hobbies like
hobbies are my hobby
pretty much like there was one time
where I kind of got into this tabletop
game called Warhammer and was basically
like models and painting and it just
like it put together a lot of things
that I like to do so like models and
then I also like playing word games and
I also like painting so it was like very
easy for me to be like man I want to
like get into it and I had fun doing it
I kind of stopped for a little bit cuz
it's a lot of money in time and and
stuff but and then I got into board
games and if I collected tabletop board
games computer games any other games you
can add that list so pretty much we're
just a bunch of because popular yours
you play video games that's like -
alright
yeah much it's like almost like a
borderline addiction I think especially
for you yeah cuz you will sacrifice your
sleep like even come into work and be
like oh you didn't sleep for like you
only set up a couple hours cuz you're
playing video games that night til
however a.m. in the morning sleep a
little bit and you wake up and play
games before you come in and like you
just look exhausted yeah that's nice
because you know that you you know that
yeah there's now I got Deven like I mean
it it's true you have like an addiction
to gaming yeah I mean like okay so Ryan
has always said like oh you have an
addictive personality which is like I
get addicted to things very quickly yes
like things that easily interest me I
will just dive into very hard and I just
go through like little seasons of habit
so kind of like you like having hobbies
yeah but I go to the extent of not
eating or sleeping sometimes just
learning about these do you guys I mean
have you that's a good that's also not
necessarily a horrible quality some
people with addictive personalities
actually become you know some of the
best athletes some of the best like
because if you're spending that much
time on something you're bound to be
good at it you know if you're gonna
spend that much of your time
investing in like studying and figuring
out how you're gonna be better at
whatever it is like I mean that's how
you become good right like yeah you kind
of have to be an addict to a certain
degree yeah but I think I could spend my
time on a lot better things yeah you
could but I'm just saying like people
with addictive personalities if you
think about it like Michael Phelps he's
probably addicted to swimming you know
like he's probably can't focuses on oh
how can I become a faster swimmer or how
should I train and same thing with any
every basketball player I'm sure they
watch tape on themselves like people
with addictive personalities are
actually the people who succeed usually
yeah I can't think of many people who
are completely successful who aren't
that kind of personality
so because you're successful in making
videos would you say that you were
addicted to making videos or making
people laugh or what made you grab onto
YouTube very very late with with your
whole life I guess I mean I think I was
um it also changes a lot I think you
have to be a dick
did for me I was addicted to the fact of
trying to create things that I couldn't
do in the past they create new things
and try and create things that are
different and then it's very it's very
unsatisfying when I have to settle for
something that's not something new even
if it does well even if I create a video
that does really well it's sometimes
super unsatisfying for me because it's
just like man I already did a video like
this or I already did this joke but in a
different way it's not unique you know
so like what videos would those be a
video that did well that I didn't that
you weren't unsatisfied I mean there's a
lot and there's videos that I kind of
even go through all of them but just the
one that's sticking out right now one
that sticks out that did well yeah that
I am not necessarily proud of like was
it fortnight or in a fortnight we did
some new things and then which I was
like kind of happy about I would say
probably something along the lines of
like a evenly like when we did the how
to be ninja - mmm it's like it's kind of
a parody of a parody and it was just
like oh well you know what it was fun
because we did the fighting thing and
that was different
yeah but the rest of it was just like an
ecstatic my excuse to kind of uh do
something different by using something
that's not if that makes sense yeah yeah
yeah so it was my it was my wig I
literally all I want to do is do that
fight scene so I wrote the entire script
that'd be just good enough not great
the whole rest of is not it's not good
it's just like basic like jokes they're
not to me at least it's not the most
creative thing in the world but I was
very satisfied and I was happy with it
because of the end scene because it was
we didn't do anything like that we never
did an action sequence like that
so I mean that's my version I guess yeah
I would say probably it's it's probably
safe to assume that if there's any kind
of like cinematic qualities you're
usually pushing for like that's usually
you trying to push it into like a new
realm of like making it higher quality
and then if it's like a list or like
something where it's like more flog
heavy that's probably something you're
less likely to be satisfied with right
yeah no I mean it's just like I use I I
mean especially before I used to use
these videos to like sneak in things so
if I wanted to act more I would put in a
scene where it has to be more dependent
on acting versus just straight-up jokes
but then I but then obviously those
don't usually do as well cuz it's it's
not what people are used to it and what
they want right you just want the same
specific format for the most part I mean
whether they they I don't know people
were listening agree or not it reflects
in the numbers yeah it's always show and
the likes and dislike ratio so and then
despite what people say that's that's
just how it is alright proof is in the
pudding because I feel like we said that
last time no no see I remember reference
is hobbies so your hobby is gaming right
yeah and that's it pretty much like
that's your main hobby huh oh and video
making that's I just like my main
hobbies making people laugh so stand up
yeah just any form of comedy I just like
that not so much making videos making
videos is just a way to make people
laugh right right so let's talk about
this new hobby you both have been into
the fishing you've been trying to know
who's fishing is great no it's not you
missed out that's when Sean was here I
was talking about that game you keep
trying to get me to play a pape X yeah
I'm not even a fan of it you're never
supporter
like anything that becomes popular if he
was if if we weren't into apex or if
nobody was really into it you'd be like
this game so dope you guys gotta try it
but the moment it becomes popular he's
like not even about that dude I remember
when we were in for tonight was getting
big and I was telling me I was like hey
this game he was into pub G cuz I was
like the you know less popular one in
the original and I stopped playing for G
because I was playing for tonight this
is years ago more than oh you did
because I said they're coming out with a
game oh yeah but you didn't play it but
you were you refused you're like oh
you're one of those you play for tonight
and then
wasn't few months later he's just the
guy playing more for tonight than I ever
played and he's just like and he was the
one telling me oh wow you're playing for
tonight I'm a pub chief I play real
games yeah it was a better game
Mogi yeah well not in terms of numbers I
don't think it is you are like that
though yeah I would say so it's a quote
it's not a bad call it's just funny that
it's like it is if someone if someone
tells you dude you gonna watch this show
this show is is amazing like I love the
show you your first reaction is like all
right whatever and then you watching
you're like what's cool even if in the
back of your head you're like no no no
no no not true at all I don't think I
think it actually makes him believe that
it isn't good when it when it could be
because he sets himself up for
expectations
yeah there's but you know what there's a
lot of people like that and that is like
the hipster mentality and it makes me
curious like what looks like let's break
this down a little bit let's go inside
the mind of Paco
Wyatt what makes you you know you you're
aware and you acknowledge acknowledge
that that's how you think so why do you
know why or well for me a lot of it is
like there's a it's like you know how
you said like a general audience will
like a certain thing and it's not
necessarily the smartest or the funniest
or the most well thought out and so
that's where I'm coming from
well I'm like okay this may be good to a
larger audience
sure but does it do I like it or am I
gonna like it because other people are
like you like apex no I don't don't lie
no I after I played it a couple of times
I was like oh it's just in another B are
you like it no reason why I don't like
it is because it's it's very fast-paced
similar black ops and that's why I liked
pub G cuz it was slower is more
thought-out yeah you know there's no
there's other ways that you can see that
yeah okay I guess so I don't know that's
like for tonight for tonight's a kind of
a faster pace in pub but it's it's it's
it's it's faster than pub G but it's
slower than black ops in Apex yeah I
guess so so I have the ability to still
try and think my way out of situation
here yeah okay
yeah well well for that specific
I get that but I mean you like you said
you acknowledge that that's a quality of
you yeah yeah yeah and I'm still trying
to figure out the root of that I think
it's something a lot cuz we know I know
a lot of people like that it's not just
you know yeah I mean that's what a
hipster is right it's that that's like
the stereo just want ya the stereotype
stereotypical hipster right right
somebody who wants to be different from
the mainstream sure I don't know if
that's a good definition they don't want
to be caught liking what's hot or like
yeah I mean that's like I don't know
what the technical term I don't wanna
offend people I know I told Greg once
that he was a hipster not knowing it was
a bad thing and it's cuz he has a
mustache and you know he had like you
would wear like overalls and stuff like
I don't think he mean was just drinking
so I don't know it sure I didn't mean it
like you know make it was at the time it
wasn't a negative thing yeah I think I
was just oh it's like a hipster thing I
was living in LA and you know we were
drinking all these jar things I was like
oh yeah Greg's pretty hipster and I
think he got legit offended wasn't a
mason jar I don't know we were like I'm
one of those typical LA places with like
a jar where they put water I just want a
cup I don't want a jar loom you know I
mean yeah and that's pretty hipster it
is it is yeah Jason jar Oh anyway um I
was it makes me think like I kind of I
get that but like what makes somebody
like that is the fact that they're
insecure about the fact that they need
to be different or is it because they
feel like they need to be it's cooler to
not be hmm
similar cuz everybody wants alright this
is my thought process as to why I'm like
that and it's just because I was always
kind of different and I was seen as
different and that's almost my identity
and so because for my whole life I've
been different and I like different
things right there's no reason for me to
like normal stuff seep no but see I'm I
grew up very different too you know i'm
i think is my insecurities and my the
way i coped with it is the opposite that
i would try to fit in so it was much
less cool with that but this is because
I'm a stronger person than you thought
yeah different that is probably exactly
why all right arm wrestle
I don't want to beat him so here's a
question for you then if it was uncool
to be different back in the day and now
it's cool to be different are you gonna
be not different you got me Andy
catch-22 is it mean that much to you
would you like flip-flop no I think for
me is just that make sense you know
because it's like I get what you're
saying
yeah but I think for me I'm gonna do
what I find interesting in what I like
no but but we're saying is sometimes
what you find interesting is affected by
what everyone else finds interesting
yeah hmm and that's the web part I wanna
figure out it's not even like if there
was a vortex more like a a a world
universe where you're literally just by
yourself you have all these different
routes and choices you can make like oh
I want to be into this gate I wanna do
this hobby you would probably pick
something completely your route your
tree your route tree would be completely
different from what it is in this
reality I think you've heavily in
affected by what other people think yes
and no because if I like something like
yes pub she was very popular it was it
was it was I was still like it's true oh
I really like this game and I stuck with
it I played it a lot so if I do like it
what is popular I will stick with it but
when fortnight got popular and I told
you to hop on it yeah what did you tell
me I was like Oh gross yeah though is a
little kid who plays portney that's your
reaction like you're in like natural
yeah yeah because it was at the time
when I told it to him I was like dude
it's bigger it's bigger than pub G like
way bigger
why don't you just play this it's so
like there's a reason why people are
playing it hmm see I I think I'm very I
get that mentality but I am uh I guess I
was just a little some nerd trying to
fit in you know yeah cuz you liked it
and you were like all this game six oh
yeah and especially the for the fact
that people are playing it like you know
even more some but like okay I want to
be in you know and be way in with the
cool kids
it's yeah I don't I I can't do that
stuff so well regardless I think Ryan
would probably like apex because he
likes black ops anyway yeah for the
people who don't have context to why I
brought this up yeah will has every for
every shoot has been trying to pitch me
to play this game yeah and it's not
about me not trying to fit in because I
know what the games getting big yeah
huge this season thing is this I'm so
different I'm such a bad way like if it
gets big in about probably jump on the
opposite of Paco because you see like oh
there's a lot of people playing so you
see the value yeah and I should probably
learn about it yeah
like even just for YouTube but I think
I'm pretty good at seeing a game and
being like oh I think Ryan would like
this cuz I know what kind of plate likes
play style you like and I remember
seeing fortnight a long long long time
ago and the reason why I said to you
even before it came out they were
working on like their tower defense
version to the single-player and I was
like Ryan this game is for you like we
got like we gotta play this and you like
you actually probably like that mode
better huh yeah I mean I I personally do
I like games that you um not just games
I just like things where you if you're
working on something if you don't put
time and effort into it that you keep
keep that status or like you keep
growing within I am not as big of a fan
of something that you just play and then
you start over yeah yeah that make sense
um just because I feel like it's a it's
not worth the time yeah you know what
they're not a sponsor of this point no
absolutely not
so apex great let's move on from that
enough apex it's about the 30 minute
mark so and you said SeatGeek
oh yeah yeah you're right i well we have
to take the shishi break and then we'll
come back yeah I don't know that the
shishito being either but we have to
take the cheesy break it's our normal
break yeah we could literally just say
we're gonna take it and sit here and pee
here alright quick she break em breaks
[Music]
and we're back we're back yes and oh yes
a second time second one come on bring
it bring it
yes sir hold on what is this
that's the money real what you just got
paid that's like a fishing reel I don't
know if I'm supposed to read the same
thing twice
but we have been bringing up Sikhi Kola
I don't think we normally have to do
this but I'm just gonna bring it up
again
just a reminder in case for whatever
reason you jump ahead to the if you're
one of the people who just jump ahead of
the shishu break I will say that when
after our she she breaks I think our
podcast get better I think so too I
think it's because we're warmed up and
we're talking like normal anyway back to
seeking our sponsor again see geek
it is a ticket app again I'm gonna say
the same thing because I didn't write
anything else down that makes buying
super simple and basically I don't think
I have to say this again nobody you
wanna get events online huh
no if you want to get you can find all
events on SeatGeek like literally
anything but mba whatever whatever you
wanna get tickets for you can get on
SeatGeek
basically they have a hook up for you if
you're trying to get tickets for an
event you can get $20 off first your
first SeatGeek order with the cold Higa
each i g a there is a link right at the
top of the description click it download
the app use the code he'd go for $20 off
tickets he's your first one though AGA
yeah I should have probably wrote
something different second time around
so I'm not reading the same thing
alright anyway again thank you so much
the C key for being our first sponsor
and I hope they do it another one in the
future but as of now this is it anyway
very first good job on your second one
actually killed it that one wasn't good
I just wish like I had something
different to say that time anyway thank
you seeking segi k-- talking about not
doing as well the first time you know
first impressions are really important
and it looks like valentine's just
happened ooh
so how did you say guei that wasn't a
sound bite that was me going
ooh
how did I segue that no Howard that just
don't see the correlation it's okay
whatever you don't need you don't need
to okay yeah um yeah Valentine's Day
just happened last week yeah yep
it is yep 20th 21st so I mean will will
we know you have a girlfriend I do what
did you do
me and my girlfriend Monica - seen her
in some videos we didn't do anything on
Valentine's Day but the day before we
made a really good dinner I made a juicy
super juicy steak you might have seen it
am i into the story I don't use it often
yes her a married couple no I made like
this really expensive steak and she made
vegetables and potatoes and it was so
good and then Valentine's Day
nothing Friday after Valentine's Day
couples massage boom that's something
it's not something we are you we never
do that like we've never got a massage
it was it was kind of weird you know
like when you go and do you mean like
you know when you go to a massage you're
like take my clothes take off some of
your clothes usually leave your
underwear on or put on a little leave
sometimes they give you shorts those
shorts to wear I've never gotten oh but
we were new at it that's why we were
kind of like even when they give yeah
even when they give me give you those
shorts you know did they give you those
by the way no they they give you like
these box are just sitting there man I
still do not trust like that they don't
like they had washed that so I still
wear my underwear under the underwear oh
I just get naked
oh so you're dirty yeah but it's
comfortable dude
I'm sure I just would prefer to I don't
know if how well they're cleaning you
know they change their sheets every time
how do you know cuz I see you oh you see
every single person I saw I saw the
washer and dryer okay and he's just
going to a nice nice spot speaking of
massage this is just a quick little
thing I'm gonna say one time me and Ryan
we're on a vacation oh no we were on a
work trip in Indonesia I think and we
were getting a massage and the girl we
were in the same room the girls that
were misogynist or burping we've just
had I don't know what
lunch or something we thought we were
getting pranked legit here in Indonesia
and for a show I believe yeah I gotta I
gotta add on to this story by the way
but look anyway let me finish this we're
into Indonesia and we told um the guy
who was taking us out basically like oh
he's like what you guys one do I was
like Oh booked massages for you guys
it's two to a room so it's like a couple
of massages but it's obviously mean
we'll and then I forget who else was
with us everybody is to do a room yeah
mine anyway me and we are in here and
we're getting massage and these girls
come in is Indonesian women and they
just keep like the cute going like the
whole time for over an hour JIT like
over an hour maybe not that loud but it
was like you could hear like someone
trying to hold back their burp and they
just kept burping yeah and then like at
one point I think like 20 minutes in
like they left the room and once we
broke you know like when when you and
your friend are laughing and you have
that connection and we just didn't say
there's of woke we both laid up from the
little hole look at each other and you
started laughing they came back and we
had to shut up we put our faces back in
the hole and I could still hear a little
bit and my I was in like the shoulder
shake it was so fly I couldn't stop
laughing and he just kept burping I
don't know I mean it was a great massage
I thought it was a really funny story I
could have swore that like some could
swore that I don't know if you were
thinking this but I thought for sure
we're being filmed yeah somebody was
like playing a prank on us
totally cuz they set up that massage
yeah book it like we didn't walk in
there it was like set up for us so I was
like oh my we're getting pranked like
I'm waiting for the cameras to come out
or whatever it was surreal
like it was like but it was because they
were both doing it maybe if one of them
was just like you know for an hour of
burping like every like five second
seconds it was crazy
that's the story that's it friends in LA
yeah I know
oh and I drove home yeah hit me up but
because you're busy working with David
oh the first two days yeah yeah I was no
Liam
did you guys celebrate Valentine's Day
like oh it's dinner or anything I was
driving home on Valentine's Day so I
spent the day driving from LA to Vegas
and then being single and playing video
games
oh yeah it's good stories it's great
story what do you do i first ryan
literally just released a video
hopefully Okemo saying who he's dating
right I did just release a video thing
who I'm dating you so we can say this
now and this unless it doesn't come out
then it's this off the pill I know if
that video is not it better be done
better be out before this comes out on
Sunday yes I just I guess yesterday
technically it would be hope specific
dates anyway yeah I just I just said
that I just released that I am dating
Arden which most people had already
known do claps thanks yeah
we have we've been dating for a long
time yeah Oh while yeah I mean it's
things we never said we're gonna hide it
per se but um we just didn't we didn't
feel the necessary to announce it we
don't want to make it like one of those
channels where they just make their
things about the relationships yeah I
mean it becomes like messy I think it
becomes like it puts a strain a
different unnecessary pressure yeah on
the relationship makes sense and you
guys it means your own private life I
mean yeah to a certain extent but anyway
did yeah we didn't try to hide it but we
just didn't announce it yeah a lot of
people already knew yeah
what uh so what did you guys do for
Valentine's um Valentine's Day while I
was there first of all to work with
David on another song oh sure you've
been off a little off today yeah no
basically what we did was on Valentine's
Day we just had a dinner
to this place because I was still on
keto and it was a brazilian Brazilian
steak place that's like that other place
where people come around and they just
cut me off uh they literally come to
your table and they say hey you won BIST
this yeah you stick your fork out and
they cut off a piece of meat and they
have all these different kinds of cuts
of meat sauce guys those places are
super good it was really especially when
you're on keto did you you're sick dude
you're sick congratulations on the
announcement of yeah were you guys
surprised so shocked I didn't know no
every time everyone every time anyone
asked me dating I just go some of my
business won't you just tweet them you
just ask him like there's so many
pictures all with like fans and stuff
like that it's like so obvious we just
never really um we just didn't announce
it yeah it's like unnecessary but it's
just easier especially when we doing
this and like if she's gonna be on it to
like just it would be weird to not talk
about sure you know to avoid that but
yeah we didn't again not that special
didn't do anything special I mean going
to a nice steak house yes that's a good
one
and you don't make that steak house
better is if you kissed do you what is
wrong with you today is wrong with you
what is wrong with me every day no this
is like extra wrong and weird I'm pretty
just tired yeah I think we're all those
are I feel like we've been talking about
this a lot so when I'm tired I just
wonder if my friends are kissing
yeah pretty and that's my thing no I
think you did the way that you're making
it sound like he's like you're getting
some kind of enjoyment out of picturing
I not picturing you guys like knowing my
boys or you know I'm sure they kiss here
yeah but I want to hear from him you
know we just have to keep wondering I'm
not gonna be able to sleep until I know
I mean we just started dating yesterday
so
that fast when you kiss everybody in the
first date [ __ ]
Wow yeah I know we're all acting a
little weird today sorry guys people
listening we were just we literally
filmed all day today we had to do this
podcast though
how about we've been consistent so far
yeah yeah no no no I was gonna say like
why we just you know talk about a normal
shoot day what its usual describe it
what's kind of interesting I think I
mean maybe not tell us but I don't know
I don't know it's not that interesting
they see BTS I just watch BTS
I mean break it down very simple start
at 10 that's a that's like our most
common start time 10 o'clock come on
usually we're come on Ryan's someone
picks up like a lot of the equipment we
meet over here unload it we'll have like
a shot list that's created by Dana and
then we'll match the equipment to it and
start with whatever whatever
um shots and film until we're super
tired see I told you guys I was really
boring and then we do a podcast with
zero energy I know well you know what
this is our first time that we're doing
it that I actually feel pretty exhausted
yeah we went a little bit long I feel
bad about this podcast like we I don't
even remember what we talked about to be
honest I had its moments it had four
energy drinks today and that's God above
my limit oh I almost forgot
I was gonna bring up the other story
about when we were talking about
Indonesia and a funny story about that
and um I don't think I've ever said this
publicly but uh apparently at that show
I met rich chigga oh really he was at
our show I was there yeah he was he was
at the show and he was I have a picture
with him
he sent it to me and he's like crazy huh
that's not his name anymore by the way
oh yeah rich Bryan is it racist to see
chica well I mean he I didn't I didn't
make that up like okay well people know
I'm rich I'm Brian rich I think he just
goes by Brian now No
that's awfully similar no but yeah he
sent me a DM I don't think he cares that
I'm saying this anyway but he sent me a
DM I'll just like because I guess I was
following him this is after that big his
first big song when he was wearing the
polo with the pink polo hmm that that
video kind of went bad I was like oh
this guy's funny man like this guy's
super funny so I didn't think he was
serious about right I thought I was like
he was like doing like Lonely Island
kind of stuff anyway I was I was
following him he D and me as I call it
send me a picture of me and him and I
was like what this what is where's this
from and it was like apparently who's
that our Indonesia show no idea but
anyway um but you couldn't at the time
know like when you meet him hey you're
gonna make a song no I mean I did not
know obviously but I just had no idea
that cuz he wasn't he was backstage
where the picture it wasn't like a like
a meeting greeting no backstage so he
must have been somebody a part of that
you know behind the scenes it's a crew
people so yeah anyway that's what it's
only because we were talking about yeah
you know why because everybody likes it
that's what you it's off mate um okay
speaking of Valentine's Day and you
probably like the person you're with
segue we got a topic here that I
actually do like well you did like read
it Paco hit me with it
it literally says can you like Oh guys
we're so tired anyway this is a good
topic I wanted to talk about this
alright well the topic is uh is it
possible can you like someone's art even
if you don't like the artist like for
instance the whole r.kelly situation
which is going on right now there have
been many documentaries articles you
know exposing how he had harassed and
abused people sexually many of which
were underage mm-hmm and a lot of people
are calling for artists who have
collaborated with him to call him out on
that so is it possible that you can
define the person as he admitted to this
I'm not too sure yet or like been proven
it's hard to say because I also like
what if we find out I mean obviously I'm
not trying to defend him yeah and it
seems a consensus that it's true yeah
what if we find out later down the road
like holy crap we were wrong and then we
start adding I think they have physical
evidence of some okay so that hasn't
been proven then yeah but there's so
many different cases you can think of
like how do you know do you still like
watching The Cosby Show do you still
like maybe an actor even if they have
like different political views like yeah
or movies that were created by Weinstein
yes like a ton of great movie exactly I
when I read this it was something I had
thought about before I kind of see some
most people from what I read at least
and not that I've seen the document I
haven't seen a document me neither and I
don't know if they're completely true
I'm assuming that they are but I don't
want to I'm not gonna say that they are
or not because I don't know but from
what I've read from what people wrote
like you know I have friends on Facebook
Twitter and stuff like that they're all
like it's your I don't care if you like
the song I used to like it's tough you
can't support it the consensus is like
you can't like the you can't like the
art if the artist is like that but I
don't completely agree with it I think
I'm in the same boat as he actually yeah
but moat you beat I think people are
gonna be very upset about hearing Obama
saying that but I feel like I mean the
reason why I liked I get not supporting
them like not buying certain exactly I
get that but like it's something that is
pleasurable to you like in your ears or
in visually like you can't help but feel
a certain way about something yeah you
know you're not trying to you don't like
him because of our Kelly the person it's
it's just good good content its whatever
he's crazy but like even in the wine see
thing what are some movies that Harvey
said his name Harvey Weinstein you're
lying so what movies that he's created
so many big movies um and like really or
not just him but he's a part of so many
big movies in like I can't just all of a
sudden that I found out he's this
horrible person that you know I can't
say oh I hated I hate them when I'm not
gonna I understand not supporting it but
like you already have supported right
right um I guess it's different with
movies but like well I think I mean I
think it's pretty similar
like you said it comes down to obviously
there's a difference between continually
or continuing to support the artists in
terms of like buying the songs or going
to the concerts or whatever but in terms
of a song existing and you listening to
it and being like oh I still like the
song like it's I think that's probably I
think that's okay I think you know so I
have the solution to it you do yeah
so if you don't like the artists but you
do like the art what you can do pirate
exactly download it illegally you don't
support them strew and you still get to
experience the pleasure and this sea but
people already say you shouldn't be
enjoying their art Kelly's music well I
don't know about other like I don't know
if with me like movies and stuff like
that but I've read like I had to stop
list I completely stopped listening to
our Kelly I deleted all my songs with
our Kelly it's even artists I'm say I
took off you know people who
collaborated with him said I took off I
don't know what they took it off eBay
Spotify or iTunes like I took my songs
off who was it there's a few celebrities
that did that I singers I think there's
one main one I was a tailor so not too
sure mm-hmm
it might no not tailors I know what it
makes sense why would he be working with
Johnny she was a little kid when he was
popular that's why off the pill another
one that's kind of like this is help
what's his name Chris Pratt is getting
kind of like flak Wow because he was
I forgot what talk-show he was on he was
talking about how he's with a church or
like an organization and that church is
kind of in line with like anti-gay I see
and so though he was getting like flack
for that and like a lot of people and
that I kind of thought of that when I
heard that because then it's like do you
not like his movies anymore or like any
of the movies who's associated with or
you know I mean like that's kind of in
line I think a little bit where trust is
like they'd they you can still maybe
like it
this is why I think you can like it but
what the trance is like you can't watch
it anymore
cuz you can't control what you like but
you can control what you watch you think
that's what they're saying or that's
what you're saying no I mean I think
that's that's what they're saying I
think it's okay to still watch it to be
honest and I think I still I'm never
gonna buy another r.kelly song yeah that
I really buy songs anymore but if like a
certain song comes on and I don't even
the thing is I don't even know sometimes
oh our Kelly sings this like okay that
doesn't change how I feel about the song
yeah it may be like in in playing it out
loud then I'd be like be careful why I
played around but like I if I didn't
know like it doesn't change based on
what that person is for me at least I
don't support artists in the same way I
go by the song it's like are you kind of
coming at it from or agree with us in
the sense of like you can support an
artist without a green with them on
certain things you can like the art you
don't necessarily up there like the
artist right yeah I agree with that you
do 100 we need someone to be politically
correct here so I'm gonna say you guys
are horrible people okay and I'm gonna
flip to then pop oh you can't you're
horrible that's messed up huh yeah I
mean you guys don't like you can't play
his music anywhere he can I mean for one
obviously you can't buy it but you also
can't like it your habit you can't Space
Jam is one of the greatest movies of all
time you can't think about it and they
have I believe I can fly in there
that is true oh speaking of which I
don't know if you guys know this or not
I think I told you already but did you
know he says suck mod he does he says
yeah it's subliminal I'm pretty sure
it's a true thing it's like in the
enemy's like yelling like flying that
thing is run he goes woo segment no
listen to it again
you're trying to get me anyway yeah that
it's it's an even connect that too he he
did it don't assume you know you know
what no it's all adding up he's doing
putting subliminal messages thing about
that is a lot of artists put subliminal
messages and you are one
I have some subliminal things in my some
of my songs a lot of your songs yeah but
it's just for fun just for like me and
David mmm I just tell you guys about it
after the fact
people can go listen to it if they find
it great but I don't care basically what
happens is listen to song everybody goes
hey I said this right here and then it
says it and I go it's either like really
quietly or it's like played like like
behind something kind of like the
r.kelly thing it's not saying suck my
yeah that's saying that so this is the
other extreme of it right so can you
like someone's art even if you don't
like the artist is there a threshold to
where if there's so so bad of a person
will it stop you from listening and
supporting like huh like Hitler Hitler
made mo Baba
if Hitler made the most fire hits Hitler
made the best hit and then you found out
like who Hitler was right like say he
didn't know would you listen to his
music or would you be like okay that's
too far right if he made the most and it
was like iconic right and it was another
yeah okay well I mean honestly I'm not
comparing our hey she's not your fault
if you didn't know and you'd like the
song it's not your fault but I don't
think you should be buying it or
supporting the artists in the same it's
the same things like it still sticks to
it I don't think you should be I mean I
personally am NOT gonna go out of my way
to listen to an hour kill a song right
it doesn't help his case it doesn't mean
I don't like his previous songs cuz I
didn't know that about him when I heard
it and like liked the song it's like
nostalgia for us yeah I think for me you
know a lot of those songs like even like
in the Space Jam when I believe I can
fly is that the title yeah or something
like that hey that's what sing it no
seriously so sorry
yeah anyway I forgot to say PC news of
the week this is kind of peace eNOS
right yeah the week that was the outro
it's pretty good yeah anyway
moving on we're about to move on to
Twitter questions actually yes we got to
finish let's finish it up with some yeah
so we have a Twitter account you can
follow it off the pill at off the pill
head off the pill yeah and one of the
questions Graham to Instagram is off the
pill podcast so I believe yes on
Instagram yeah and one of the questions
for the Twitter was how do you become
motivated when you're in a rut and you
don't want to do anything and I think
that's a great question especially for
Ryan because pretty much all of last
year he was in a rut I think yeah I'm
dude what'd you get roasted dude I think
that's a very rude thing to say but that
is a good question yeah well I mean I
think I mean I did talk about it and
that was it this year or the last you
know this year the first one the first
video yeah what's different but goes
back to what we were talking about
earlier as well of like me deciding to
do things that I want to do like this
podcast like it's like something I would
have never posted and I already knew
like the views we're gonna drop and
obviously they did but you know it's
because it's long-form content and it's
not necessarily what people come here to
see sure but it's something that I've
always been wanting to do and I'm I I
have fun doing and I think for me it's
rediscovering why I did YouTube in the
first place and that was to have fun
creating new things and doing things
that are different that I'm not getting
tired of yeah and for me it's I think
when you're in a rut in anyway you got
to figure out why and I think if you
really look at yourself and be like okay
this is you're in a rut for what reason
I don't know if it's gonna if this is
the same scenario for this person but at
least for me come from my perspective
you have to I think you have to get to a
certain point where you feel like you
feel so stuck that you have to you have
no choice but to kind kind of look at
yourself and come up with why you're
there yeah
in general a general rule that I always
is always ask why for everything asking
why has helped me in every aspect of
life yeah whether like if someone's
being mean to you don't don't
be sad about it don't cry don't while
you guess you could cry but you give me
sad you can be sad it as well but I'm
just so if you ask yourself why when I
was getting bullied and I hated it I
hated life I had to ask why and that
helped me it was like okay what he's
doing it because you know he wants to
make people laugh why because you know
maybe he doesn't at the time wasn't
think this but later because that person
probably gets enjoyment
it makes him popular so by thinking that
way you find solutions like well okay if
that's what he wants and that's what I
want how can I do that how can I make
people laugh or how can i you know if
that's what if that's what he wants then
I should know it's not about me you know
I mean that well that's one that's one
example but asking why and everything
even in in in making YouTube videos
looking at like other people's videos
that are doing really well I had to
learn from it I don't wasn't always you
know successful in YouTube it's you just
watch videos and see like oh I just
posted a video that's a skit ought to be
ninja and it did so much better than
like the lip syncs and I'm like why does
why did this get so much more views you
know like I didn't know at the time but
if you always ask yourself why in every
scenario I think it helps everything in
life final Twitter question is how was
your guys's first kiss first chaos to be
honest I don't really remember mine damn
play a play in the house it's not
because I've kissed a lot of girls oh do
you remember yours like very big I
remember my first kiss ooh it was
outside of a movie theater and it was
very how old are you 15 or 16 15 but
what is that sophomore year for us
sophomore junior sophomore junior was a
freshman Oh another 14 or 15 okay
outside a movie theater and it was I'm
pretty sure her first kiss or not
experienced because I do remember
kissing and then trying to use tongue
and and the weird part was that it was
so I thought she was
more experienced because she was the one
dislike sticker talking here yes and it
was like a little like I didn't know
what didn't really know what to do to be
honest and like I just had there was
like this little whirling effect went on
like a little tumbling like her tongue
as I do a little circle thing and then
by just because I didn't know better I
started circling back that TMI or what
no no but I do remember that vividly
because we as hugging kinda like just
like I embrace I guess was it like it
was like a hug yeah yeah and I just
remember your eyes closed are open I
don't remember that but I'm gonna assume
closed cuz I don't I don't specifically
remember blend yeah I do remember the
tongue thing I was like that's not is
that how it is that sounds like a
stereotypical first case like outside of
a well I mean that wasn't like it wasn't
even up I thought was thought it was
just a peck right and then we like
kissed and then we just stayed there and
then the tongue came him swirling around
and then I didn't know but I mean like
and then I started swirling back that's
a good first story earth it's not wasn't
good but it was it's a good story
it hasn't happened since so fine
honestly if I had to think back I was
probably really young
I'd be like 9 or 10 day but it wasn't
like a tongue thing I think it was like
I spin the bottle with like curling up
neighborhood girls and we yeah we kissed
on like probably kiss like on the lips I
was like oh cool yeah right you thought
was so cool I mean I thought I was cool
but I didn't get no swirly swirls with
tongue so yeah but I was pretty young so
that's why it was not like that it's not
like a typical in a cool story like that
here's cool decided first one I was
excited are you
when know
that's a good one nice burn brand his
freshman year in high school and it was
at a same age gap band banquet and I
remember I asked bench I was in bad okay
job sorry good and I asked his girl if
she want to be my girlfriend and she
said no and then all of our mutual
friends started teasing me because like
hi you got rejected and then out of pity
she said I want to be your girlfriend
and I was like it's okay and she's like
no I do and I was like okay so then she
became my girlfriend that right there
and then we were dancing and then I
remember Gwen Stefani's hollaback girl
came on and then she yeah she tried to
kiss me in the beginning but I moved
away and she kissed me on the cheek and
I was like what am i doing why'd you
move away cuz I was nervous okay yeah so
near the end of the song like this is
bananas B and I was like I gotta kiss
her bananas every podcast leaned in and
I kissed her and it wasn't there was no
swirly swirl but I remember she like did
the fish thing oh yeah but then she I
don't know how to do that I had chapped
lips so it's like fighting rock jaggedy
yeah like lava rocks like she was making
out with Pele oh and then after that she
moved away and I said I'm sorry about my
lips
[Music]
that's another lame man we're not that
cool we're not that cool I'm sure other
B I mean like even wills stories like
yours is not bad your first kiss was
just normal like Peng was very like
boring
I had no swirlies no chapped lips it was
just like oh cool that's less
embarrassing well that's the end of our
Twitter questions
great questions yeah also there's a talk
of possibly getting a you know a
subreddit in terms of like nigahiga
stuff it was a thing
is but it's not in use okay we're trying
to see if that would be something that
the artist no interested in that's why
cuz I don't know yeah
Ryan is unsure he would want to know if
it's something worthwhile investing time
into sure so I guess in the comments if
you guys are interested in you know
being able to connect you know podcast
ideas you know anything like that
definitely in the YouTube comments and
still remember to go and bother your
favorite youtubers or
doesn't need to be youtubers I need like
anyone you really want to see on the
podcast go and send them messages and
bother them until they're forced to do
it with that being said that's another
episode of off the pail podcast
sponsored by already knew when it was I
don't know why I did that see geek
thanks again guys we didn't need to do
this I'm not gonna oh don't forget to
follow Twitter off yes and Instagram off
the pill podcast especially for well we
check both for the question it's not
just Twitter yeah check the Instagram as
well yeah yeah just we should pull
everything so we have these like little
things to cover the mics cuz David said
it's bad to breathe into them but I
don't want to put this on just to do
that let's just end it dude how about
you go like this it's just not the same
that's just ruin the mics okay thanks
for Road thanks anyway that being said
see you guys next time
swirlies you're good kisser
I saw your tongue it's a good kisser
jealous see you guys just jealous