hey how's it going everybody hey welcome
back to the 60th anniversary CICU
tear Mexicans engines 2013 so we really
are looking forward to what you have to
share with us this year so you guys take
a seat we'll get started all right so
let's go ahead and give a nice chair
full cheater do Rhynie get the person
better so my inventions caught if you
look at it all comes down to this every
chair I've ever thought of all those
years of waiting for my shot and it's
finally here and ready for this I can do
this dad I hope I make you proud if this
ever happened to you my pants are
nothing like a chair looked over thanks
ooh the pig pants your pencil never not
not be like a chair again oh the sake
pads uses modern science and technology
to give you the ability to have a chair
wherever you go he has one two three why
you have to do is open up the peg
pockets pull out the peg legs and screw
that pig spray up into the base of your
past it has never been easier with the
pig pen for a really long time
[Music]
you know what man boys girls women dogs
cats lamps me we even cut some of the
most famous people in the world using
the pig past such as Oprah Scarlett
Johansson Tom Hanks Abraham Lincoln Mona
Lisa Derrick Rose that one Asian died
from the Olympics the Leaning Tower of
Pisa every Dragon Ball Z character Simba
Miley Cyrus we even cut Soulja Boy using
the pay pass and nobody even knows where
he is anymore
I stand when you could be sick
like the great swing everybody's
breaking while the big pass still not
convinced here's some of our satisfied
customers well it's to be honest they
are most comfortable yeah it's great if
you don't mind looking like a stupid eat
before peg pants I still look like this
and now I look like this I actually love
the pig pants I think they're great
these are real people folks not P
doctors because we are paying them
weight white ideal is what you'll be
saying after you get the pig can hold on
a second that's aren't just good for
sitting there's many other different
uses for them as well Haigh nunchuck a
pig belt to hold up your pants yes I
asked you can see back use it as a back
strap you see but uses a putter whole
strategies as a grocery bag holder pack
your friends with the bike pay a stand
for a miniature gym thanks to working
and never again be embarrassed by smelly
gas buildup thanks the pic times
butthole but most importantly the pig
pens help you in every single scenario
especially the most common
[Music]
the plan at the man of the contract had
turned up
[Applause]