hey guys look so dark oh you know what
and not set up one of my lights and you
know what I'm not going to welcome to my
dark vlog that offensive probably
welcome to my dark and light vlog this
is getting ridiculous I guess let's just
jump into it
welcome to another view Ryan dear Ryan
can you attempt same Malik cyou and I hi
no funny story I never mentioned this
about Zayn Malik actually it's actually
not a funny story he when people say
that when it's not funny okay boring
story about Zayn Malik before he was
well known before you was even in the
group somebody sent me a screenshot
showing me that he was you don't
subscribe to my channel from his
personal call and during this time he
was a part of One Direction so I didn't
believe it but I went to go check it out
and it turned out to be true pretty sure
he does not watch these videos anymore
but you know what that's still a bad
story who just wanted to break sorry
guys fact is you're right yes I I don't
I'm sorry I don't know what song is this
a new song I've never heard of this you
and I saw so I'll probably have to look
it up it's just supposed to be
high-pitched yeah okay oh my goodness
that's high I can't do that I mean like
that's a high pitch yeah okay
my teas are a lot higher than that
probably won't sound as good but let me
just I can go that high I can do it I
can do this you
[Music]
all right one more time
is that it all right that's enough of
this dear Ryan my mom is in town right
now she's staying with me so I'm a
little embarrassed another funny story
this one again not that funny has a kid
I used to sing all the time and my mom
one day she just took me in and she was
like look Ryan you can't sing it's the
end of that story
funny right just gonna move on to the
next time do your Ryan what would you do
if someone stole your cell phone if
somebody stole my cell phone I use it
every single day they have some all my
schedules everything I need like I need
to live by that if somebody stole that
from me
I'll tell you what I do see this right
here yeah I'd sell this and go buy
another one can't sell it now it's
broken
dear Ryan can you do Pokemon impressions
I don't know why I keep getting asked to
do impressions something impressionist I
will attempt it again like all I get
emptied Dragonball I only know the first
generation of Pokemon sorry I don't know
all the new ones that the kids are into
obviously I'm not gonna do all 150 of
them or 151
I don't remember let's see there's night
plus Alaska and Hawaii 51 yeah there's
151 so that's way too many to do I'm
just gonna do the ones that I remember
that's a hard one to start with Oh Cho
square turtle doors dad
Harley Marley bow the five you saw baby
when my neck of a nurse or
the hell even says me next hey yeah
that's that is enough impressions for
one day I'm like exhausted I don't know
if you can hear but I'm like starting to
lose my voice already whoops that was a
Pokemon - dear Ryan me and some of my
friends love your videos you should
totally do your own rap about cheese
thanks if you do if you don't oh well oh
well dear Ryan can you do how I'm just
playing I'll do it cheese rap huh sounds
delicious
[Music]
let me get that Gouda give me give me
that whispered it out like we know not
the Fresh Prince but the king of Italy
been working on my crap but I'm no sign
of don't own either city dance just go
[Music]
dear Ryan can you do a ping pong trick
shot you actually think we're gonna do
another trick shot video yeah yeah
[Applause]
so I know you must be a little confused
now because of the title you know saying
that they were fails when clearly you
know her don't know why I'm talking like
this well you see ever since we did our
first trickshot video we've been getting
a lot of crazy requests to do a bunch of
other ones some are repeats clearly they
haven't seen that we already did those
and there's also some crazy ones like
these like throwing knives and and bow
and arrow trick shots dangerous ones
well the reason why I pick ping-pong
balls over all the other great options
is because you know I learned my lesson
from the other ones we broke a lot of
things and people did get hurt and
that's why I picked ping-pong balls
because they're safe and they're light
and you know they're nothing's gonna get
broken from a little light ping-pong
ball is what I told myself before we
started doing this
[Applause]
you all right my foot oh my god Oh Frank
look at the den Oh a surprise just
didn't break my heart is going to almost
died oh well so leave your questions in
the comments below and you could be
responsible for the next video
[Music]
that would in the basket anyone and all
your