i'm just gonna grow it out both the
beard and the hair i'm growing it out
really hates it see he's mad hey guys so
i'm gonna be talking about one of the
biggest trends that exist today
prank videos and i'm sure you guys
already know but right now prank videos
are like the most watched videos that
are online and i mean i get why
i personally always love pranks pranks
are always gonna be a big thing but
lately i feel like there's just so many
prank videos out there
we've seen all the best pranks it's
really hard to come up with a new
funnier prank because there's so many
funny pranks out there and because
there's such an over
saturation of these pranks prankers are
being forced to step their game up
they're all trying to top each other and
of course not all of them but i feel
like a lot of these prankers are just
going way too far to the point where
they're not even pranks anymore they're
just straight-up crimes some prankers
are like going on the streets and
they're like calling
out random guys to fight or like
grabbing random girls butts
i've even seen a video of some guys
throwing fake bombs at people because i
guess terrorism and
murder is so hilarious like that's not
even funny that's just like shocking the
only way that these so-called pranks are
not crimes or if they're staged or fake
but that's like a whole other story
we'll talk about that later anyway it is
getting ridiculous and not in the good
way pranks used to be good
innocent fun nobody got hurt or sexually
assaulted or
bombed thrown at them and i don't know
maybe i was just brought up differently
but you just don't prank people that you
don't know you prank your friends
whatever happened to the good
old-fashioned clean harmless prank
like when we were young we used to spray
like pam on the floor so that when
somebody would walk on it it'd be like
slippery or like the pat someone on the
back prank where you're really actually
putting a sign on them that says
something that would probably be
considered offensive today or like when
one of your friends leave their phone to
go to the bathroom so you and your
friends grab it and hide it and then
basically watch them freak out a little
bit and then give it back or like what
even happened to the most innocent
harmless prank of all the prank call
hello hey is your refrigerator running
well you better go catch it oh my god oh
my god do you know something
i'm sorry what what my son he's been
missing have you seen him have you heard
something
i don't understand please he's a little
white fridge with abc magnets tatted on
his lower right door
doesn't even have a freezer yet please
we're so desperate
no i i actually don't know anything
about any friends why would you call it
it was just
supposed to be a prank call my baby goes
missing and you think that's funny
i i i didn't know i'm i'm sorry i'm kind
of sick i'm so sorry i had no idea
i didn't know what i caught him
you see good old-fashioned harmless
pranks no one gets hurt anyway lego was
saying pranks used to be innocent but
because there's so many good pranks out
there that now you just have to do
something completely crazy to stand out
those innocent pranks you just saw
that's what pranks look like five to ten
years ago but those pranks would never
get viewed today because they're not
crazy enough not those pranks came out
today those pranks would look like this
hey dude we should spray pam on the
floor but this time we add glass shards
and a lemon so that when they slip and
fall they get cut by the glass shards
and the lemon just goes inside of their
cuts
how's it going sean working harder
hardly
fire working working hardly working
i'll be right back
dude look he left his phone you know we
should do we should hide it
but this time let's not give it back
yeah
and we'll take his wallet too yeah
and you know what we'll take his truck
all right let's go wait we're taking his
phone his wallet
and his truck and not giving it back is
this even funny
[Music]
dude we should take his mini fridge yeah
that's a prank what do you guys do hey
mom
sad part is i'm not even exaggerating
that much these primes probably already
exist somewhere sorry
not pranks these are crimes there's so
many pranks these days that are actually
crimes that people think it's okay
so many people these days think that
just by saying the infamous lion who's
just a prank that they can get away with
whatever they want and those people
are absolutely right
what it was just a prank oh okay then
what the hell just the prank broke third
one
[Music]
it was just the prank oh
hey it's just a prank
what it was just a prank bro
[Music]
oh dude too far that's a rocket launcher
i'm sorry man i
didn't realize it was you shot that way
too far i'm right here
it was a good one though right yeah a
good one but what do you think is going
to happen to that rocket though
hey we're taking mom
no
it was just a prank no i don't think it
was what do you mean you just blew up
two people in a fridge
that's not a prank oh that's a social
experiment
it's just an experiment i'm done come on
like before people get all defensive of
their favorite prankers i'm not talking
about all prankers i got a lot of close
friends that make prank videos and
they're still successful without having
to commit crimes in their pranks i'm
just talking about the ones that will do
whatever it takes to top their last
prank and i'm not gonna name names they
know who they are we all do they're
willing to either break the law or
stage their pranks in order to get views
and yes i said it earlier prankers fake
pranks all the time big surprise this is
not news i actually have no problem with
stage pranks if they're still
entertaining what i do have a problem
with is when they lie and say that it's
real when it's
obviously not real just own up to it
it's entertainment there's nothing wrong
with that and if you're gonna fake a
prank and pretend that it's real at
least put in the effort to make it look
real it blows my mind how many of these
videos i've seen that are so obviously
fake and people in the comments don't
seem to catch on i mean it's pretty
obvious when pranks are fake you just
have to use common sense here's some
really quick tips to tell
if a prank is fake or not for example if
somebody's committing a crime in a prank
by grabbing random girls butts on the
street and they put it on social media
for millions of people to see i'm sorry
to spoil it but there's a very great
chance that that prank is staged because
if not that person would be in jail
that's video evidence of sexual assault
that millions of people witnessed
another obvious sign of a fake prank
the camera is far away but you can hear
the pranker and the victim talking
clearly chances are they're both mic'ed
up or even the camera angles there's
certain shots and some pranks where
there's absolutely no way that the
cameraman could get that shot without
the victim noticing them so it's either
staged or they filmed that part after
the price so basically
it could be real but they shot it twice
and probably the biggest giveaway is
blurring faces well not blurring faces
but getting permission from the victims
to use them in the video especially for
big prankers all the popular prankers
know that you have to get permission
from the people that you prank in order
to use them in a video because if you
don't that video is going to get removed
or you're probably going to get sued
just think about it for a second a lot
of times these victims they get
extremely mad or upset by the pranker
which is
perfectly normal they should be upset
but the truth is the fact that we can
see their face on video means that they
gave
consent to be on this video if somebody
just pranked you or
scared you or hurt you in in some way to
make you that mad why would you consent
letting the world look at you like an
idiot unless of course you were paid off
or
more realistically staged there's a lot
more little ways to tell a prank is fake
but i
i'm just i'm getting off topic anyway
fake or not pranks are going way too far
and it's becoming a dangerous culture
let's stop escalating these pranks
before it's too late and somebody
actually gets killed let's just go back
to the good old-fashioned harmless
innocent pranks like pam spray
or prank calls about your refrigerator
running you know the classics cause even
though they're pranks
in the end everybody's still happy
everybody still wins and most
importantly
nobody ever gets hurt
kevin mama
[Music]
calm down it's just a prank bro oh
so thank you guys again so much for
watching if you want to see bloopers
behind the scenes click the one on the
right if you want to see the previous
video click the one on the left
just kidding if you click the one on the
right it takes the previous video if you
could go on the left you see the
bloopers and behind the scenes i pranked
you guys all