rhpc how Swindell ebony why did you
where's that supposed to be oh it's a to
let you know like where we are on like a
date and time but isn't it Saturday and
it's night Oh plus it's not even our
house well that's that's not important
what is important and the reason why I
called you guys over I think I finally
made a breakthrough in the new case Oh
God we're doing another one of these I
should have known better
what well we're sitting on the couch
you're standing what are you talking
about first thing you're gonna do is
pull a lever or press some secret button
and bail your super-secret lab they're
gonna have to listen to your conspiracy
theories for hours dude what are you
talking about I was just talking about a
breakthrough on this case wait is that
my Sookie oh yeah friend to tell you had
to borrow it for the pun you drill a
hole in my suitcase why would you do
that I just told you for the pun yeah
because of the hole is like the
breakthrough and their cases I don't get
it sha and also I needed it to gain
access to my secret labs so that we can
start the next crazy conspiracy theory
well what what is your secret laughs oh
that's in the other room then why did
you have to drill a hole in my taste
what was all that for huh to open it oh
oh there it is
now we can get into the secret lab when
you delete the any other room all right
as you guys can see here been working
pretty hard this new conspiracy proving
the earth is actually flat cool where
did that come from
but it doesn't matter are you serious
are you doing all this because of the
kind of arrogance equate who you know
Kyrie Irving who famous basketball
player that came out said that ye also
believe the earth is flat it's
ridiculous she all said it was
ridiculous to do I do a little bit of
research and father there's actually a
lot of people that believe it yeah and
they're ridiculous and I and one of them
no you gotta be kidding this is a real
thing okay people actually believe that
the earth is flat the called flat
earthers what they believe is that the
government has actually tricked people
into thinking that are this round from
the time you're a little kid okay how do
you explain actual satellite photos of
Earth Photoshop editing okay well what
about people who actually traveled the
entire close going in circles not around
the whole thing meaning I'm not gonna
lie this one is kind of hard to believe
exactly why would the government want to
lie about the shape of the earth she
that's exactly it they're hiding the
truth from us the truth so mind-blowing
that if people found out the whole world
who come to an end I am this close to
figuring it out
what are you doing on school right
that's um Spencer's love Spencer all
right let's go back to the very
beginning Kelly you see in the beginning
everybody thought that the earth is flat
but who were the first people to
actually suggest that the earth was
round ancient Greek philosophers and
these philosophers have discovered a ton
of things that we live by well why don't
we ever question them duration for
example ancient Greek philosophers are
the same people who have discovered
conservation you know the idea of
connecting stars to make pictures like
the Big Dipper or zodiac signs
I'm Emil I'm uninterested but if you
weren't thought about this as a kid and
you were just a look at these pictures
it looks nothing like what they claimed
it to be you mean this looks like a
child
connect the dots one more from our class
which by the way here she should
probably get an end fork so it's nothing
like a fish sorry Homer combo look I
agree consolations don't always look
like weather supposed to be but what is
that have to do with anything we're
talking about planets not scar that's
exactly it but if it's both see our
solar system is made up of one gigantic
star and a bunch of planets orbiting
around it kidding this each of these
planets are actually just points in one
big constellation see there's always
been rumors and questions by people
including Sciences that believe that if
at any point all the planets align the
world will come to an end that's the
constellation they're trying to hide
from us I call within just Sun why not
Mercury Venus Earth Mars Jupiter Saturn
Uranus Neptune that's to me is only that
sign a modern day human how is that
supposed to be human being it's a
straight line looks like a somebody test
or class right what does this have to do
with proving that the earth is flat at
all all right let me point out the
obvious was it two more vital things
that humans need to survive I don't know
your brain
yep and your heart exactly your brain
your heart are the two most important
things you need to live just like the
two most important things that you guys
need to live in our solar system is the
Earth and the Sun located exactly where
they should be
in a constellation if some powers
everything in our solar system just like
our brain doesn't yes we can't survive
without the earth which is literally an
anagram for hard if you just move the H
at the front okay but what about the
other how to hell the mercury
represented bait actually it represents
your mouth why the Sun is ahead as we
all know the Sun gives up an incredible
amount of heat and
your head is feeling extremely hot what
does that mean you're saying precisely I
mean you're sick you go and get a
thermometer I put it where in your mouth
geometers are made of mercury exactly
remember this constellation wasn't
created today it was created a fairly
long time ago back in the day it didn't
just stick a thermometer in your mouth
check your temperature
really where else would you see the
Khedive your anus it couldn't be more
obvious Uranus is literally slow
vengeance on Venus which means that it's
mercury is a mouth and Uranus is the
anus and we can figure out everything in
between by looking at a regular human
body what is good a little the mouth but
about the heart your throne for your
next test Venus and since Saturn is
right above Uranus that must be your
hips or your butt you'll explain why it
has that big pool of cooper on its body
right we go back up to Mars which again
is just another anagram for arms pretty
self-explanatory and Neptune is just
basically everything below your image so
it has to be your legs as for Cupid I'm
not quite sure I mean obviously some
agreements between cars hip area since
Jupiter's the biggest of them all
there's a little more to it it's not
just the normal stomach they're saying
that it's a huge stomach a huge stomach
meaning that the venture Sun has
something to do with the process of
eating really meanwhile so they make the
stomach that being and when you really
look at it it does just look like a
digestive tract time so what about Pluto
is Pluto used to be considered a planet
but now it isn't so what is that like
his toe or something and it somehow
disappeared wait a second
it did disappear who don't look and
actually attach to the body but it
represents the most human-like
characteristics that leads us to our
next step
are you talking about yeah I'm not too
sure you think Pluto in the park it was
in summer to read on Venus passing Earth
and Mars oh just an interpreter
preparing for takeoff from Saturn and
boom right on your anus flying past
Neptune off of the space before what
disappears
you really expect anyone to believe this
I believe this I mean there's literally
a picture right in front of you don't
you see it it's a line well like I said
earlier did you get an F in our class no
well then you don't have the eye of a
Greek philosopher so you can't see it
probably just like how you didn't see
that having an F in art literally spells
up for [ __ ] for I can't believe you're
resorting to fart jokes isn't have joke
what don't you understand
I understand a lot of things like best
and sign okay you want back some science
I'll prove it to you you already know
that a Florida's simply gas that comes
from Uranus Uranus has 27 moons a third
most in our solar system is do you think
that when you expose your buzzes someone
is called morning then you did it right
there why are you talking about your
anus when it has a third most moved on
to talk about Jupiter or Saturn at us
there's a reason why Uranus is right
number three for the most moons know
exactly the biggest and gas hissing in
our solar system the Sun you see the Sun
is literally a gigantic ball of burning
gas made up of mostly hydrogen helium
and a bunch of other random elements
such as carbon nitrogen and oxygen when
you add the atomic number of P to these
elements you end up with 24 3 sure the
number of moons that you represent and
what was your anus ranked on the list of
clans to the most moons that's right 3
bringing us to 2017 that number of moons
and Uranus heads so we know that your
age is connected to the Sun that's not
the only one usually right all the times
backwards there's only two planets that
are connected to the Sun Uranus as we
already know and one more Venus the why
Venus out of all the planets why not
Mars we all know the saying men are from
Mars and women are from Venus because
Mars or men have always been their way
to distract us from the truth which
lives of women or more specifically
Venus think about it why is the stars
called the Sun and not the daughter yeah
why don't we call the beginning of the
week Sunday well why is it called
another [ __ ] but not daughter of awake
which you can be saying that on this
channel
what's the family channel why not they
say it on TV all the time if they don't
stay on my authority Explorer
I'm a [ __ ]
we we are we are updated now you see
[ __ ] by definition actually means
female dogs we know I was thinking about
yes it is because the novel has to cut
this part out but males are just called
dogs so doesn't that make you wonder why
you wouldn't even call a female dog a
[ __ ]
no exactly it's very intrigued you've
heard of a female before right you know
the one that leads to pack in beta one
that's impossible
what about that's just like everything
else in our world betas gravitate toward
health investment dogs with humans
planet moon orbits the earth and the
earth orbits the Sun although alpha and
beta a and B before you go on please do
we at least take the sign down it's a
little event
what's the a [ __ ] line to not no no
it's not a [ __ ] remember because the a
is else when the B is beta so but B
gravitates for the a and making average
there's a group what ABS are obviously
referring to your stomach and an itch is
just discomfort so it's stomach
discomfort
hey remember there's a reason why
they're distinguishing between men and
women it's just a last step to proving
my theory thank God I can treat those
discomfort specifically for a woman and
only a woman can only mean one thing
pregnancy the creation of lemons however
because men can get right is the only
thing that sells it'll ferment
approximately mean is something we
already know and so far for our babies
I'm then because women don't worry again
for the villages sighs how does a part
prove that the earth is flat look it's
simple giving birth is the creation of
life to a human being but a fart is much
much bigger than that
lot of this we're right all along the
earth is flat that's not the only thing
to Sun all the other planets everything
in our entire solar system the entire
universe oh because it's all Fletcher's
hey can you stop doing that what I'm not
letting it end like this
not getting away with this morning away
with it I just proved it the earth is
flat its regiment special in screams
farting don't worry I had to look it up
to on going get it Sean and what are you
confused about it all adds up the Big
Bang
what is the fart made of gas just like
the Sun yeah but see that's the Sun and
we're talking about the earth and the
earth isn't made of gas it's a solid
which indicates all of your logic and
props you for doing all of this but that
does not prove that the earth is glass
it is true yes that means the earth is
in the fart
thank you it's a solid form I thought
about what about your fish it