hey guys yeah I'm gonna win a new room
it's a real long story I'm moving that
wasn't long at all no wasn't long stood
up it's not even a story yeah so I'm in
the middle of a move right now I haven't
posted a lot lately because I'm moving
for one and then I also probably gonna
be on my book tour if you guys came out
to the events it was nice seeing you
here hey hey yeah I just have to talk
really quietly closer to the camera like
this hey guys so today we're going to be
doing a yes m-more experice I hope you
guys get to take in building feelings oh
oh my god anyway welcome back to another
episode be a riot let's just get started
okay let's just get started pretty sad
dear right can you do ten handstand
push-ups in a row pretty sure I can do
that I mean I can barely do a handstand
and stay in one place but if I'm
balancing against a wall that's pretty
easy right well there's only one way to
find out how though I don't know what
way that is oh no they weren't helping
me right oh dear Ryan can you make five
threes in a row guys I have a nice
surprise for you guys someone just
called me David toys in the house I'm
filming a vlog right now you just made a
cameo this is what me and David do every
day he calls me naked in bed while I'm
filming fun story just so you guys know
I grew up playing basketball for me ages
5 to age 13 because in high school when
I turned 14 I went and did wrestling
instead of basketball even though I
loved basketball I was not good at it
and I was a little bit better at
wrestling part of it is because of this
wrist right here my shooting hand normal
wrist like my left wrist you're supposed
to shoot it straight like this on your
elbow up and down rich gold right but
this wrist doesn't Bend back because of
the metal rod I have in here or had in
here and
yeah long story short that's not sure
this is a long story I can't shoot the
ball straight because my wrist doesn't
Bend that way this is go stray season
the amazing you know the guys at the
park they actually refer to me as curry
as in like it's short for Korean they
think I'm Korean at the park not Korean
it's my Park the Ryan's Park call me
Ryan Park ready never done this in my
life
first one easy all right first one first
take that's why I meant easy
[Music]
the wind
I think the winds is Norway
Oh
[Music]
I'm nervous you finally got it feeling
it boys 3 2 1
one two three four five others intro
this is why they call me Steph Korean
[Music]
this is my bark
Ryan far dear Ryan can you do a boyband
song about sandwiches okay I see what
you're trying to do there and I'm not
gonna fall for it okay we all know boy
bands always sing about girls and you
want this to be about sandwiches girls
and sandwiches like the sexist
stereotypical saying that we all know
I'm not gonna fall for that next time
I'm not gonna fall for it might fall for
it this time right now
[Music]
turn on the attitude
walking all along by the subway had to
catch up endless to the proper word to
say your your funds looking nice and so
fly hey what kind of meat did you get in
there I'm so hungry
[Music]
with guilty she took it from me show me
something sweet and I would never I
thought
I knew that you were one
[Music]
there's old so I wrote all this in one
sitting and I didn't realize until after
I made the song that its kind of not PG
and by sandwich I mean a baby that's
like kind of sexy dear Ryan can you give
some cheap Pawnee gift ideas for my
annoying rich friend I made a video a
while ago kind of doing the same thing
and I'm assuming you just want to see
more of that but this reason is exactly
why I made this video
chopping for an incredibly rich friend
who has everything they want because
they are rich is one of the hardest
things you can do so you don't want to
just buy them something because it'll
mean nothing to them you got to do
something for them that money can't buy
because they're rich and apparently
annoying here's some cheap Pawnee gift
ideas for all of you out there we'll
have a rich annoying friend you got me
an aunt
not just any ad though this end is
special this is the only one to leave
the colony it went rogue
okay yummy a rogue ant why because it's
just like you arrogant see that's David
that's Trent and that is Michael down
here why won't you give me a book about
doctor these aren't doctors these are
nurses male nurses why would I even know
a nurse that's a man's well maybe that
one day you can learn some manners
[Music]
this is a miniature school or something
yep and you get to be the teacher why so
that you can have a little class it's a
chest filled with knocked-up my favorite
movie that I already own great oh but
you don't have this version yet see it
took the time to reverse all of them and
they're all backwards now so it's not
knocked up it's up knocked and they're
all yours between the chests
why why would you reverse it what what
does that even mean you're obnoxious
just a clothes line yep we're some cheap
watches on it actually they were all
free I have more free time to hang out
[Music]
what are you doing Shh wait
how is this the pressure on okay
you just tell me what this is patient
what is that okay I'm lost
oh my god hey I'll be the rich guy you
play me then what does this even mean
nothing I'm just trying to give you
morals why do you keep yelling oh it's
so loud how else am I supposed to give
you morose wait where's the music so
leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
[Music]
right