hey guys I'm sorry I just a little
thrown off today I don't know if you
guys know or not but I wasn't
it's so stupid I was nominated for this
creator of the decade award that's going
on right now I don't know if you guys
even know what that is
I don't even care at all it's the first
time I heard of the sharding Awards what
I don't even know what that is like I
mean like the label would like creator
of the decade is kind of a big deal you
know it's not just one year it's a whole
decay like five times as many years
normally I just little thrown off you
know like kind of question to myself
like whatever I've been doing all these
ten years then and like am I even
blogging right right now don't care for
the record guys I don't care like I
don't care
seriously I told I don't just didn't
rough you know just being like just been
other stuff
[Music]
at least always never gonna win one
was it even nominated talking about
nominated for what a shorty award
creator of the decade you know I always
thought that if you worked hard enough
you really put your heart no matter what
I mean this huh how did you oh you got
this when you want it five years ago uh
I did yeah and that's that's a shorty
yes it is so can we please get ready now
wait wait get ready for what the
streamys the real award show right the
streamys yeah that's that that's the one
that really matters what was i nominated
nope and that's why I don't even feel
like doing this vlog right now cuz that
cutaway was so damn long and boring it
sucked all the energy out of me really
don't know when to stop this is going on
way too long hey guys so if it isn't
obvious you know I was being sarcastic
just a little bit I really do not care
about winning some shorty award no fans
to show you a word I'm not sure I like
don't shade or anything I'm just that's
not one of the reasons why I do YouTube
and don't get me wrong I actually really
appreciate that a lot of you guys didn't
care that I didn't nominated for this
award it was actually a lot of you
whatever really angry about its knowing
how bad you guys wanted me to win this
award already is that's more valuable
than the award so I mean I'm not gonna
lie I'm still human like it's always
nice to give win Oh award or be
recognized for something you know it's
human nature but after a certain point
of you know winning these awards or
being nominated are going to the award
shows themselves you kind of get to a
point where you're kind of ah it's gonna
sound that don't that you don't
appreciate it anymore it's just that you
get to a point where you kind of realize
like all these awards and award shows
are pretty pointless and I'll rather bet
I just have to go and say that I wanted
to make this video a long time ago years
but I never did for two main reasons
reason number one I did not want to
appear bitter I was actually waiting for
the opportunity where I would win one of
these awards so I could make this video
and not seem like I'm being bidders
right now I'm probably coming across as
somebody who's just being a bitter sore
loser not the reason guys I don't care
that I didn't win no but seriously I was
gonna wait until I want an award to do
this video but in the form of a speech
this is gonna be pretty much my award
speech good thing I did
it wouldn't have been smart to do you'll
see why second reason I never made this
video up until now is because let's be
real there's a lot of powerful people
and politics that goes you know behind
the scenes when it comes to
entertainment these particle people they
they create and run these award shows
and the reason why I'm finally speaking
up right now is because I think I'm
finally in a place in my career where I
don't really care that much not that I
don't care about my career but I don't
care as much it's been a process over
like two three years where I I decided
I'm not gonna go through the BS just to
make my career but luckily I don't know
how a lot of you guys have still stuck
around which that's why I'm so
appreciative that you guys still watch
and then you guys still want me to win
these random awards I'm just finally
comfortable enough to a place where I
feel like I can speak my mind and not
worry about the consequences and I think
it kind of shows in the videos I've been
making recently like the recent rear
ioan video or like the how to get views
on YouTube they're very critical on
YouTube and that's not something I
normally would have spoke out on because
it's so controversial and I think a lot
of you guys who've been around with me
long you don't know that I'm not the
kind of person to go out and start
controversy or be a part of any drama
but I'm just calling it as I see it you
know I'm just speaking my mind whereas
Oprah would say speaking my truth I
don't know if that's correct I saw
someone caught it on Facebook I don't
watch those stupid Awards just these
things like that they get me into
trouble anyway back to the topic right
after these messages I think I said it a
few times already but I personally
believe that you know these awards these
award shows are kind of part of this
like for won these award shows that you
know we all watch I don't want to say
that they're fake it's super misleading
and I started finally going to these
when I was like 10 years ago back in
high school I was shocked at what these
shows really are like during the scene
this award shows were honest I think
people would not care about them nearly
as much they'd just be like this is just
for promotion again I'm facing a lot
it's off my own personal experiences it
might not be the same for other people
also heard a lot of things from friends
who told me their stories as well so I
think it's a pretty commonly known thing
in our industry but the public doesn't
ever get to see not even talking about
the award shows themselves the real
important things happen even before the
award show happens it's easier if I just
show you guys let me just show you some
of the things that happens behind the
scenes of these award shows and you can
decide you know
your hand makeup should be there on to
third in your wardrobe we'll be there
shortly after noon well I'm pretty much
ready all right oh they helped you
already know I just did it myself okay
yeah they'll be there 2:30 okay uh how
about your date does she have her own
people oh yeah I forgot to tell you G
actually can't make it tonight
wait what yeah her grandma got sick so
she's not gonna be able to make it why
didn't you say something earlier do you
at least have a backup no I just figured
I'd go by myself no you're not a loser
you know I'll figure it out I'm driving
meet me a block away from the venue all
right and Jackie sorry so yeah we have
picked up the person of interest we're
gonna be your on the way and oh sorry
Ryan this is no your name's Hennessy
yeah Hennessy she's gonna be your date
tonight what we we just met yeah so do
we we just hired her hired her is that
even legal Ryan she's not a prostitute
she's just here to hang out with you
rich people do this all the time to look
cooler we're here all right well thank
you no no no look
cars not big enough uh what time is it
let's circle the block again sir what
why look there's not enough people you
show up too early you look like a loser
you show up too late all the real
celebrities get the attention you gotta
find the sweet spot so we just drive
around in circles yep this looks doable
wait let them do it
all right here's the plan
you're just gonna stay here and look
good you're gonna go talk to some fans
and sign autographs and when I come up
to you just say just give me a minute
why would I have to just do it fine Ryan
we have to go but you just told me to
come over there inside I have oh just
give me a minute
Oh fine hey so how's the event go and
it's pretty good right where's the
Patrice Hennessy is gonna be waiting at
the end of the interviews which I lined
up for us so what do you want to start
with oh we know people we Matt Jacob
really all right new plan so what you're
gonna do is you're gonna go over there
you just say hi you're gonna have a
couple laughs and then we're gonna move
on that's it I don't even know the guy
he's 22 years old 12 inch sub has a
younger sister good luck
it's so good to see you again nice hey
how do you like be from Hawaii
how do it what collab yeah okay sure
check it your email or okay so maybe
these things didn't exactly happen that
way but I'm just trying to show you an
idea and to be honest it's not that far
wrong and I'm just speaking from my
point of view of things I've witnessed
other creators who's been around the
block long you know if they might not
say it publicly but they know what I'm
talking about they know the game oh they
know Z that's them meeting me up about
the game because sorry guys I put some
sorry and I know it might seem strange
from the outside
like why would people do these things
through this it works this is the BS I
was talking about that I don't like
doing but to be honest if I really
wanted to help my career and if you're
an entertainment you want to help your
career you should be doing these things
that's why so many creators and actors
who hate doing these things still do it
because they have to and it's not
anyone's fault they have to do it to
stay relevant again I have nothing
against these award shows I think it's
great entertainment but that's it where
I have an issue with this is that we as
a society value these awards so much
more than just entertainment some of
these awards we treat it like it's an
integral part of our society take the
Oscars for example remember the whole
hashtag oscarssowhite
controversy remember that we're a bunch
of people even other actors and
celebrities were saying like you know
the Oscars are racist because there's so
many white people winning and not enough
you know people other misses and being a
minority being Asian myself I always
thought you know I completely get why
people are upset but I always thought
like this happens every year nothing
gets changed you know there's what's the
solution and when I really thought about
it my point of view was always if you
really think the Oscars are racist then
why are you watching them why are you
supporting it there are all these
celebrities that are speaking out
against the Oscars seeing the asean
racist ills showing up to the oscars
hoping to win one you guys want to
change then make that change and stop
doing this silly piece of metal more
value than it really deserve we are the
reason the Oscars are valium we don't
need the officers or any award show to
tell us what's good and what isn't we
can decide that for ourselves by caring
so much about these awards we're just
giving them more power for example all
the people who are Leonardo DiCaprio
fans and we're so upset that he'd never
won in Austin does why without an Oscar
Leonardo DiCaprio is not a great actor
he's not one of the best just because he
has an Oscar now we're suddenly like
okay now he's one of the best doesn't
make any sense it's like letting a whole
group of other people decide all our
opinions for us is if we can't do that
ourselves I'm sorry getting mad I don't
know why we are taught the known Oscar
is this incredibly valuable prestigious
award and I know a lot of people are
gonna say oh yeah it is valuable
prestigious because just like having one
you make millions more as an actor well
again yes that's because we were taught
that it is worth this money in the grand
scheme of things that if you really
break it down is this little trophy
really that great if the Oscars were
invented today and you know all the same
actors all the same movies were all
nominated nobody would care who won the
celebrities probably wouldn't even show
up if you gave a little kid who has no
knowledge of the Oscars a choice between
a Oscar statue or a pigeon spinner
chances are you applied to this
without being taught how valuable an
award is it's meaningless even by
complaining about it so much you're
showing how much it matters how much you
care you're just giving more power to
the award that's your fault anything is
the people in charge of these awards
just become more powerful you might not
think it affects you but it does because
if you control something that
celebrities want you have control over a
lot of Kievan all that power goes all
the way back to the top right now
believe it or not the same thing is
happening with these internet award and
then because I was there to see it for
the very beginning it's just so clear
and brilliant actually how it happened I
didn't make something value you can't
make something valuable without people
paying attention how do you get people's
attention celebrities do you get
celebrities to be a part of it there he
goes tell them you want to give them
something to show them how great they
are once you get a few big celebs there
then all the other smaller ones join in
too because they want to be a part of
whatever these bigger celebrities are
doing once all of the celebrities care
about it so do all their fans and I'm
sure you can see where I'm going with
this it just keeps spreading let's be
real you know celebrities come together
and collectively say something about
anything it becomes a fad that's just
how our society works because nobody
thinks for themselves including myself
we like to be told what to think we just
accept what we're being taught oh I'm
sorry guys I haven't made a ran video
like this in a long time probably set up
a bunch of stuff I shouldn't be saying
publicly but you know whoops
overall what I'm really trying to say is
whether it's a shorty award a Streamy
award an Oscar even is not an award and
all just think for yourself don't just
believe everything you're being done
including everything I'm saying to you
right now as always that's why that's
the motto out of the vine again this is
just my opinion and probably a very
unpopular one I'm just trying to give a
different point of view it doesn't mean
it's right it says for you guys to
decide I go for this video wasn't just
to change your mind about award shows it
was at the very least just to get people
to think for themselves that's the real
thing I wanted to say before you just
believe what you're being taught think
twice about I was really getting into it
at that time see and I swear my silence
did but I'm not even texting this person
back and they keep
as I was saying you know my goal was to
get people to think for themselves and
but you know the thing is sometimes
celebrities are popular for a reason you
know like there's still some validity to
what to what's behind you know someone's
popularity so first sometimes maybe you
should just listen to just maybe
sometimes
[Music]