hey guys so if you follow what's going
on in the YouTube community and I'm not
just talking about my channel I'm
talking about like all of you - you've
probably seen some or at least heard of
some YouTube drum and by drama I mean
like you know youtubers fighting online
it's all public for everyone to see and
I'm pretty skeptics Oh at first I
thought you know these youtubers were
pairing up and agreeing to have drama so
that you know I would create some
publicity for them and also you will
never know but I think it's real I think
it's a hundred percent real I mean
they're not just like tweeting like
snide little passive-aggressive remarks
they're literally calling each other out
there making dedicated vlogs to like
talk crap about each other I've even
seen some youtubers make raps about each
other like it's some kind of rap battle
I think the whole Drake and meek mills
thing I'm just sitting there thinking I
feel a little left out I want to be a
part of the drama life I cannot be with
someone I know how to roast I've had
roast beef like okay uh PewDiePie uh
more like a Buddha pie boop doop I is
what I meant roaster que si uh what does
that stand for kilns per square inch
hole jenna Marbles
more like jenna more bowls of poop de
pie that's measured in ksi why don't you
apply some water movement on your bird
butt up with the wat put water first to
clean it okay as you can see I'm not a
good roaster I'm a great one but as much
as I want to be a part of the whole
drama scene like I don't want to fight
with anyone I don't like confrontations
I mean the closest thing to ever being a
part of the drama life was literally
when I made a draw my life back in the
day when I first started like 2005-2006
you tubers didn't really fight with each
other we all got along for the most part
we help each other out you know we
supported one another we all collab and
if there was drama you wouldn't
necessarily see people posting about it
so publicly online I guess people are
more open about that stuff these days
but it's obviously completely different
now and I'm missing out which is why I
came up with this idea
you probably already know because of the
title it is the roasts yourself
challenge it's easy to call someone out
on something or it's easy to make fun of
someone else we as humans naturally do
that we're always judging other people
he's so sure he'll look at all that
girl's dress fat that guys she needs to
take off her makeup and put on some
clothes the idea behind this challenge
is basically to look at yourself as if
you're another person and then do
exactly what the title says roast
yourself
and like I said I I don't know how to do
it exactly I think it's pretty open as
long as you're roasting yourself making
fun of yourself then I think you've done
it you could blog roast yourself you
know literally do what I'm doing right
now but talk bad about your stuff you'd
create a clone character of yourself and
have that character roasty or you could
even do one of those rap battles with
yourself like we mentioned earlier like
the whole Meek Mill and Drake thing
except it'd be you just roasting you I
mean it is a little bit more work but I
actually think that would be the most
fun way to do it anyway just do it
however you want the only rule in this
challenge is to make one of yourself is
to call yourself up because like I said
so many times before we're always so
quick to judge other people but a lot of
times we don't even realize but we have
just as many flaws as everyone else once
you realize and call yourself out in
these flaws it's a lot harder to make
fun of someone else's flaws so let's
stop the drama stop making fun of people
stop mocking and judging people and just
take a long look at ourselves just tear
ourselves a new one I'm Ryan Higa
and this is the roast yourself challenge
started the game young looking back in
oh six yeah I wear a hat too if my head
were dipped in piss but I guess I
shouldn't hate on a kid who's relevant
good thing you're not anymore you thinks
I'm right you elephant relevant like
television what are you been watching my
cell in prison oh you wanna prove me
wrong let's test your intelligence but
you can do the math yourself right your
age what you dropped out of college you
couldn't make your this race through
your race couldn't either win a tea seal
a button like the [ __ ] I please I saw
you crying mothers they saw a jelly
forgotten hotel they'd never been on
Ellen Duffy
watermelon spelling felon like his felon
is your only talent hunting talent that
in silent Allen will not tell them and
last but not least the best parts about
to happen the song is finally and then
man I'm sick of hearing your rapping
transmit fire but you can skate like a
spare tire you are a pig you should
retire give it a break drink cuz you're
literally unimpressive and your raps are
saying aggressive and your flow is like
a carpet getting worse with no
progressive there's only one thing that
could make this rap worse than it could
be by ending with and overused on this
see when you roast yourself no one gets
hurt it's a good challenge I'm just
trying to make the world a better place
so like I said earlier the next time you
feel the need to make fun of someone
take a look at yourself first if you're
gonna go and judge someone for something
then go ahead but just know that you're
not perfect either and you should be
judging yourself as well and just like
any challenge I'm gonna be doing some
call-outs to youtubers who I want to see
Rose themselves as well but it doesn't
mean that you guys can't do it either in
fact I look forward to seeing a bunch of
you guys do your own Rose in fact yeah
I'm calling all of you guys out as well
but anyways specifically I'm gonna be
calling out a bunch of my friends to do
this challenge that I think not only
would be good at it but these are all
people I think that aren't afraid to
make fun of themselves and I think where
this challenge you have to be pretty
confident cuz you have to be comfortable
calling out your flaws so with that
being said I'm calling out the following
people
Jenna Mar the tracks cutie-pie yes I
Timothy DeLaGhetto iisuperwomanii and
Jeremy Lin if I didn't call out a
youtuber that you guys want to see
roasts themselves as well then you call
them up I'll leave them some tweets or
comments or whatever that being said
thank you guys so much for watching
looking forward to seeing all you guys
roast yourselves oh yeah and if you guys
want to buy this you know epic smash hit
rap diss track on iTunes
you can't cuz I'm not gonna put it on
there