hey guys happy Valentine's Day past
already actually late Valentine's Day is
a day for couple day for love a day for
romance a day for pissing the rest of
the world off who happens to be single I
mean I'm all for supporting loving
couples and all that stuff but why is
there a specific date to celebrate that
if you really love someone shouldn't
every day be like Valentine's Day for
all you girls out there wouldn't you
rather get flowers and a random
unexpected day rather than a day that
you're supposed to get them and for you
guys out there why the hell is there an
expectation to get girls flowers on that
day anyway you can't even use flowers
you might as well get her something
useful like an iron or a kite or
something at least that's not gonna die
in a few days anyway I'm getting off
topic I made this video to tell you how
my Valentines Day win and you can
imagine it was obviously super cute and
romantic and just all-around beautiful
was like a movie
take a look
[Music]
this is so I know we just met like a few
days ago and this is gonna be a crazy
step would you quality
actually it's pretty cold out it's got
bacon tails
watch it laughs roses are red violets
you the grass is green tiles are white
so mr. blacks and that's great I like I
do you feel it beating do you hear what
it's same thing I wanna see this but
does mine is fleeting
[Music]
right ready to be you complete me I
don't care that you here with a mushroom
or that your breath stains are that your
feet look like hands it doesn't matter
to me because this what's on the inside
that counts a nine ten ten you cheated
you can change this whole time no no I'm
done I'm gonna feel it
[Music]
please don't bring this movie sucks okay
so maybe it wasn't exactly like that but
it was still pretty awesome actually had
a wonderful night
so you guys in the pillow fights or what
I need a girlfriend okay all that
matters to me is what's on the inside
that was wrong
[Music]
[Applause]