[Music]
hello I'm Rob boss and thank you for
joining us today today we're gonna be
doing a painting tutorial in the style
of Bob Ross no affiliation not related
but let's get started shall we so at the
bottom of your screen you're gonna be
seeing a bunch of the colors that we're
gonna be using but while you're looking
at that we're gonna get started is using
some of this white paint and we're just
gonna go ahead and just coat this entire
painting with a bunch of white just
continue to paint the entire canvas same
color it already is see the reason why
we do this is because when we're
actually painting it's gonna be a lot
easier to blend the colors I can't
actually tell where I've already painted
because it's the same color but what you
want to do is just just keep on going
keep on stroking up and down up and down
not left to right I don't think it'll
look skidmark right here know how that
happened but we'll just paint over the
house see there's no real mistakes in
painting you just go ahead and paint
over it there's no mistakes just I I
like to call them the happy little
accidents kind of like a lot of you kids
out there we've got a little bit on my
black thing right there whoops that was
a mistake as I say just on painting
should be a nice relaxing tutorial just
watch them nice smooth wisely oh love it
issues cut to that really colorful
screen with the bead thing well loosing
a little bit of Bristol's right here
know if that's a good sign or not you
want to just keep sweeping that bad boy
out
something wrong with a little hair and
you're painting but you want to start
with the blank canvas let's just get
that that a little straggler in there
keep that hair on it it's not a really
moving but just like anything else it
takes time takes a lot of time
I probably could be using another brush
or something to get that out maybe even
my hands I can't I can't reach any of
the tweezers or something is anyone ever
- either is or something no okay we'll
just keep at it once I get this last
hair off there you go
there you go thanks for watching
I'm Rob boss what I wanted to do first
to get started is to start off with this
bloody coping health got a little bit of
that blue color in there but we got
start off with this little bloody red
just want to get the tips of your brush
pull it down so it's a little bit
lighter okay so now that we have a nice
even layer on both sides of your brush
of this nice bloody red what you're
gonna do next is essentially paint a
bunch of X's because we want you know a
little bit of pink in our sky and
because we have red we painted the
canvas white in theory it should be pink
so just give it a try shall we it's
pretty pink see which one does create
these little X's this is gonna be in
your sky and you just really want to
make this X format go with a light touch
a lot of X's a lot of X Factor a lot of
X go and give it to you that's not good
don't put that in please don't put that
in and there we go all right so next
thing we want to do is continue our sky
with a little bit of blue OH as you can
see there's a some of this doodoo brown
is starting to go on my thumb I'm sure
we all can relate to that so the next
thing we want to do like I was saying is
continue building our sky we're gonna go
with a little bit this blue right here I
don't know where to mix this because I
used up all the space with the red but
that's okay hopefully gets a little bit
lighter it's not we're just gonna have
to go with this so we're gonna start at
the top and paint the rest of our sky
with more X's little X's like so
kind of painting the top handle of this
bezel but that's okay
if the X's aren't don't seem to be
blending too well you might want to try
some other letters so maybe let's try
some wise lowercase wise it's pretty
much just Mac's
as you can see you can't tell what one
color starts and where another one
begins I can't see it also colorblind if
you want to give the illusion of a happy
little cloud right here you're gonna
want to just kind of dab it in and
strokes a car okay that's that's not a
happy cloud it's a little angry but like
I said you know what I said let's just
go and try and make make make this work
a little bit just think really happy
thoughts and just spend it in now you
have nice little cloud as you can see
just blending in thanks for watching I'm
not boss let's put some water in there
how you gonna really love water so you
want to start from the bottom and always
go left to right
start from the outside-in might have
gotten a little bit of black on the
brush another big whoops you want to be
very generous with your paint you can
have that nice dark look on the outside
just like my soul
always remember to pull from the outside
in horizontal strokes only as you know
the ocean or Lego is horizontally
there's no ocean that goes vertically
and there is your ocean what we're gonna
do next is dark in all the corners even
the bottom right here some at the top
want to really give it that that one
little filter thing on Instagram
the vinaigrette thing so you want to
keep darkening each corner it's okay if
you're painting shakes a little like
this I'm not sure why it's moving
sometimes your paintings just come to
life and if this one is definitely it's
time to look good and it is coming to
life but we need another little baby
thing let's go and do that and once you
finish off your corners this is for the
really fun part washing your brushes so
you're gonna want to dip your brush into
this water and paint thinner and you
don't want to spill it like I just did
it so you can i really want to rinse it
out as you can see I put a little bit
too much paint
and we might need a little bit more
water whoops
and now that you have your relatively
clean brush what you're gonna do is
basically just blend everything in
starting from the lighter colors in
which is the pink area just blend it in
and I pretty much do that pink let's
move on the next thing we're gonna want
to do is just take a little bit more of
that blue this time we're gonna mix in a
little bit of white oh no just a tad bit
lighter this is the real fun part here
watch here you're just gonna take the
corner and just Dad and pull down just
creating that distant little trees in
the back no I may not look like trees
yet but we'll get there
then you want to grab a clean brush and
you kind of just one on dab it pull up
create that illusion of mist I don't
know what's next what we're gonna do is
add another layer of trees but a little
closer so you want to go a little bit
darker and we're gonna do the same thing
just a little closer and pull down
everybody likes trees that is your
second layer of trees and then we're
just gonna take our clean brush again
and just do the same thing create that
illusion of mist I might have put a
little bit pinkish pain again common
mistake you're gonna want to pull up
from the water you're gonna do a pull up
that works kind of yep next thing we're
gonna do is get our little knife thing
right here and we're gonna just take a
little bit more of that blue black add
some red in there as well like soon why
not add some white while we're at it put
some white in that bad boy it makes this
bad layup totally up to you
what you want to do this painting is
your world you have all the control but
really what you want to do is check Bob
Ross's tutoria to make sure you're doing
it right so we're gonna do is give
ourselves some trees so what you wanna
do is just kind of dad making little
trees still in the distance might look
like a bunch of sticks for now but they
are trees don't be shy
every tree needs a friend Chandler some
Monica
Austin Rachael right here Pheebs no
choice we don't need no Joey's and those
are some pretty not detailed trees it's
gonna do is we're gonna take a little
bit of white it's nice too little need a
little trick I like to call creating
that just get some white and you're just
gonna tap it in between the trees to
give it a little looser of a having no
no trunks in there tree trunks just a
bit here and there don't need a lot fact
you can barely see it a bit but I can
cuz I'm really close to it the next
thing you want to do is take your knife
just get a little bit of white re a
little bit on the edges here we are
gonna create a water line do these
little slices right here all the way
across just like rick ross i next we are
going to make another color get a little
bit of red in there a little bit of blue
a bit of green really just mix in
whatever the hell you want to do
whatever makes you happy so you can see
it's just another dark color being as
colorblind as i am they all look pretty
much the same this dude who is still on
my thumb ain't nothing wrong with that
use your head
this parts really scary but remember
there are no mistakes they're just happy
acts happy just start right here I'm
gonna start them in a straight line down
here's my kids are really crazy what you
want to do is take the edge of your
brush your fan brush just do a little
dab right about here I'm gonna dab on
this side and then back on this side
just a little bit wider and just
continue the pattern you're just gonna
because ease just gonna make as ease
back and forth back and forth
lots of Z's lots of trees I'm sure
there's some bees and here are my knees
there's one tree and I'm just gonna make
a couple more same technique make
disease make the seeds I'm sorry
and the next thing we're gonna do now is
it's a little bit of that same color we
made the tree out of with a little bit
of yellow you should make a nice bright
green color and what we're gonna do with
this green is go back in here and just
put some highlights just make sure all
your trees can equal a lot of love he's
just as happy as his neighbor
you know I ever want to have angry
neighbors trees are no different so
we're gonna take some of this white mix
it into that try not to get this blue
mix into that same green just take this
lighter green color and just pop in some
indication of a little bush down here
and it should be floating on a nice
little yellow yellowish green submarine
and that's its Island and since we have
our island now what we're gonna do is
create a little bit of dirt so finally
we're gonna use my do to brown thumb and
we're gonna mix it with the remaining
white that we have here
all right what we're gonna be doing next
is creating gigantic trees in the
foreground and this could pretty much
ruin your painting even mr. Ross says
that this is a bravery test so we're
just gonna just try it we're just gonna
go ahead and try it because we're not
afraid this is our world we can do
whatever we want in our world even mess
it up so let's go for you gonna take the
edge of your brush and just start
dabbing at there's some green on there
that was an act that was some happy
mistake hold on just cover over that dab
in a way until you in what you have make
some bushes down here why not everybody
loves a good bush use a little bit more
pink but I am kind of lazy to make it
again it's really up to you guys to
decide how many bush how big your bushes
it's always on as your own personal
decision you decide your bush just just
end or in the middle or you can just
keep your bush going all the way
basically just paint in the corner of
black um so what we're gonna do is just
draw a little trunk straight in there
let me just check one more time what he
did
[Music]
Shh I got scared and I stopped pressing
down because it was so wide but you know
that's why it doesn't look good
never paint with fear let's try this
again remember to make the sound is very
important and that's very thick that was
not intentional
no mistakes though shh shh
so not the best line in the world but
we'll see all right so I think I put a
little too much pain so I'm gonna try
and just just scrape a little bit off
scrape a little bit all make it a little
lighter oh I mean oh okay that's that's
a little less so then we're just gonna
take more of this green that we had
earlier and you're just gonna take the
corner and just kind of DAB I mean don't
be afraid just dab in some leaves
[Music]
now it's time to get that's right even
crazier what we're gonna do more trees
and even riskier than before cuz we're
going big okay you know what why not
let's make another tree let's go right
here let's go a little curvy but this
one not everybody's completely strained
if you know what I mean just like that
and we're just gonna just do a little
sarees we're not even making Z's anymore
so you doesn't even matter don't you
start getting a little bored of painting
you just start messing around kind of
give up a little bit but it's okay next
we are going to take some of that green
that we made earlier and just add a
little bit more yellow just make a
bright yellow color and just paint out
our individual bushes wherever you want
it to be you know there was a bush here
did you and that's supposed to be a bush
you know what let's make some rocks so
what we're gonna do is take some of the
brown little bit of the white what's
really gonna give it some color is some
black they add a bit of black very
lightly just drawing some indication
that there's some rocks right here and
then we're gonna go back to our
construction green dark chocolate brown
nice little path right here
nice big skid mark would have in a
lighter color i light your skid mark
give it some flavor just make a few more
bushes and just keep making your bushes
until you are satisfied and we're
basically just gonna make some sticks
with the dark brown from earlier these
little details are what really makes it
just some more sticky I guess huh
this pointers tired another way you can
add some sticks to your painting you
actually just take a clean knife and
you're just gonna carve through it and
just pretty much keep scratching up your
whole painting everything you work so
hard to do just scratch it another
technique you could use just get like a
cat and or dog and just let them run
loose and after adding all your
scratches pretty much the last thing to
do is to sign it one of the hardest
parts of cursive is the B so we're just
gonna make a squiggly line because no
one really reads this do they and there
you have it
something
look at this how are you die am I done
I'm sick of this man that was irritating
so mad hate this piece of slow ass want
to be all relaxed Jim be real dude being
real you know tough clean
[Laughter]