my name is Ryan Higa I've never believed
that these go stoves were real because
they all seemed so overly dramatic oh my
god I just got chills the a/c vent is
right there it is crazy how cold it is
right here and extremely easy to fake
hose that but then one night I had an
experience of my own that completely
changed my views on gosu ghosts are real
well they're not as they are what that
wasn't the experience I was referring to
because I don't have footage of it
however I can assure you that despite
all the jokes and obvious ghost show
parody everything you're about to see
and hear is 100% authentic even if we
end up capturing nothing at all this is
Brian tries ghost goes on him so right
now we are headed about 40 miles outside
of Las Vegas Nevada to the town of good
Springs to investigate the historic and
famously haunted building known as the
pioneers has been featured in multiple
movies and TV shows including Ghost
Adventures which were definitely not
coffee we're planning to stay throughout
the entire night to capture as much as
we can hopefully we actually get
something we have our normal filming
equipment normal audio recording devices
but in addition to that we picked up
some night vision cameras and some
actual ghost hunting equipment including
like those EVP recorders and clothes box
but two random stuff that we don't
actually know how to use but luckily for
us we are going to be meeting the owner
of the saloon who is
a lot more experience in this than we
are you a man
yeah meet you the legends here good to
see ya other legend a pair so um can you
just tell me like a history of this
place I sure bet so this is the town of
good Springs which back in the teens it
was one of the largest city in the
valley so good sprees got its big boom
of course because of the mining so I
mean I saw the episode that they did on
Ghost Adventures here and that was you
beyond the bar yeah right so I saw a
little bit of your story but just so
that we can have it tell us a little bit
of your experiences here my experience
it was about probably about nine years
ago I was getting ready to close up the
bar counted all the money made sure the
doors were locked but there's a full
apparition at the end of the bar that
drinks a beer maybe about that tall
beat-up cowboy hat just by looking at
you know he's you were looking directly
matically I didn't disappear or we had I
would say eye contact but that would be
impossible
you could tell by just looking at him
that he was there but not is there
anything correlated to the history
probably the best documented situation
at the bar there's three bullet holes
they could see daylight through all
three of them and that's from a card
game in 1915 where one of the players
was caught - you try to cash out ten
dollars and the dealer ended up shooting
him
Wilda justified homicide his punishment
was to bury him in the cemetery
interesting okay and obviously we're
gonna need some of your help with some
of the equipment that we're not used to
using I'm lending you guys the full
staff of the haunted lock down to her
and then they're gonna guide you guys
through it with all the spirit boxes all
that but you're out that's a good night
yeah all right all right
again well thank you again so I
appreciate know we appreciate it yeah
this is should be interesting
[Music]
all right so I'm here with Jill and
Daryl and you guys want to explain we
have a bunch of fun devices here but you
want to explain what you guys do exactly
yes actually we're members of the
Pioneer saloon Coast team yeah so
basically what we have here is a
collection of the devices that we use
for the lockdowns and Joe can explain a
little bit about them yes this right
here is one of my favorite devices it's
a spirit box with this device we can
actually communicate with the spirits
through the white noise this is just a
radio receiver what we do is we scan it
in Reverse so this just cat scanning
different radio frequencies and so
sometimes we'll pick up words or in a
very rare occasions you'll pick up whole
sentences which is pretty cool because
you're it's like you have before in the
pen just to explain we're not in the
saloon right now this is the SI nexus
alone so there's not any technically
anything here right that we've gotten a
lot of activity here I think it's really
the whole property well you were also
telling us that electronics for whatever
reason here messed up like we've already
had one of our batteries a couple of
them actually just fully charged when we
came here just dead that's a that's sort
of typical but here the body a lot of
people a lot of guests have said that
like oh my phone died and this doesn't
that happened were like Mike that's not
surprising this is one of the original
it's called a EMF detector what a lot of
people in the paranormal field use this
will you can measure when the lights go
up
okay that means someone a spirit is
close to this basically measuring energy
so what energy becomes comes interactive
it's the same with with the RAM pod
that's my energy interacting with it so
the so the closer something is exactly
this is the Ovilus five this actually
has noticed that was this this is
speaking now said raised and this will
actually it has a built in dictionary
and the spirits can actually pick the
words that they want to communicate with
us through this right so why did that
just happen now raised an end I'm not
real sure um is there ever a time where
you feel like it's just how do you know
it's really thank you can be it can it
can be random because it's affected also
by the environment but the goal for us
is like you know if you want to try to
get one of these to light off will say
are you here think you make the meter
light up and try to get a specific
reaction to a question now we do have a
lot of prominent spirits here one of
them I'd love to talk about on this side
actually because ultimately she was
murdered right over I'm like fried by
the second booth over Gerrard left her
name was Ruby Ruby was here in the store
the cafe it was a mercantile store back
then she was alone and someone came in
and they beat her they raped her and
then she was strangled and she was left
for dead right over children after all
right a man that seems like a good place
is in the story right as we began to cut
cameras and move on to the next part of
our investigation one of the devices
unexpectedly began to go off on its own
I mean it's fine if you work now nobody
touched that as you guys just saw but
you got that cold there you go they're
doing it again yeah
can you make it go to red my gosh what
does that mean red only just ask them
okay I take it you guys are ready to
tell Ruby story that let's let's do
after reviewing this footage carefully
with headphones our audio devices also
capture what we thought sounded like a
scary ghost more
only to later discovered that it's
actually a familiar noise that our
cameraman Gregg makes when he scares
we're in the booth right now where ruby
was murdered well there wasn't a booth
it was she was on the ground yeah
correct right where we're setting her
head was a little bit past year is where
she am okay so this is the first I guess
spot right so about ten thirty one night
we drive house to Cemetery which all saw
and it's pitch-black we parked on the
outside and there's a fence there so the
woman said should we take photos I said
of course I always take three this is
what was in the second photo is that
amazing now until someone can tell me
differently because I know this girl and
I'm very unsound
but right you can't tell me that is no
person that's that's her did we get what
is happening right now Ruby loves that
what her story's told I want to show her
photo they get very excited it's going
crazy yeah they're just I I adore these
spirits they're amazing and they're very
friendly that's good to hear yes after
these two strange occurrences in the
cafe next to the saloon it was time to
investigate the saloon itself by sitting
at the exact same table that the poker
player was murdered at back in nineteen
something a long time ago is there
anyone here with us right now
[Music]
that's like yeah this is tip give our
audio recorders closely can you guys say
hello to us how many spirits are here
with us
Ruby are you here with us three and you
make his meter line up in front of him
thank you
okay how many ladies are here with us
that was a girls voice
really after closer review we noticed
that the flight pattern of those orbs
looks similar to that of a bug but since
we're not experienced enough to
distinguish between actual orbs and bugs
we can't debunk this one so for now
we'll just call it the bug is all here
with us right now anything you want to
say Paul hello we continue to try and
communicate with Paul for nearly 30
minutes but had little to no response
but because Paul died playing poker we
decided to bring out playing cards in
hopes to trigger a response from him
when this happened hey Paul Paul do you
think we should call yeah but that was
the only coherent response we got for
the next twenty minutes so we decided to
move on to the next spot that has been
frequently reported for having
paranormal activity but right now we're
gonna have its I don't know it just
keeps going red which supposedly there's
a lot of activity we're gonna head to
the bathroom because weird I'm not
sure what happened there but they said
that a lot of women say that a lot
happens in the women's bathroom
specifically the women's side I think we
should check that out all right so we're
going to the women's bathroom
nothing this is like less activity than
out there
yeah your other man's
it's really yeah that's the keys playing
red I'll be good right here
look is there someone in here
[Music]
it smells so bad in here compared to the
other one I think men are just smelly
there's definitely some activity yeah
look this was never going on there's
someone in the bathroom with me Oh Oh
miss appear sick right here
it's a great oh it's right here we go
hard up glide up you got a little red oh
yeah
that's a cold ass that's a strong red
that's solid red who else is in here
what do we take that is about that yeah
let's do it
yeah when we do it on the ground I'm
trying what is this thing base please to
show you the consistency when you go
like this so earlier I was going off
when it's on that's why I freaked us out
hasn't really done since there's
something there continue to investigate
the men's bathroom with the REM pod we
also got a coherent response for the
very first time from the Ovilus v the
device that allows spirits to
communicate using a select number of
words almost like a modern-day Ouija
board this may not seem like a big deal
but throughout the entire night the
Ovilus v had little to no activity and
even when it did it gave us words that
seemed completely irrelevant but when it
gave us the words look area and much the
exact same time that we were looking at
an area very much Lee we couldn't
pretend that we weren't freaked out much
Lee freaked out
you this is your show are you still here
oh what's on the other side of this wall
the only thing that's actually out here
no it's yes at this exact moment outdoor
audio equipment could barely capture it
two of our cameramen heard a thump
coming from behind them on the other
side of the room what was that what you
hear I was like that like a door on this
end
never would be addressed
I'll remember I just went through this
door to get the card yeah the cards in
this door with Isis both of these doors
are open
no we call it we closed it no well what
else when I when I went in there to go
get the SD cards because the SD cards
were on that table over there
both of these doors were open cuz I
really yeah for sure 100% pause I'm like
99 just one that's what sounded like
wood or something yeah kind of like a
like so desert like a breeze that
usually goes guys I can close these
doors yeah when he tries was open try
and open it and just see if it will
close on its own it was like this yeah
for sure
because I went in I remember we closed
it remember to for the sound though you
guys were in yeah I remember it coming
out quick because I didn't want to be in
here so I went like and then like dodged
the door somebody closed this door over
here oh wow it's peaking right now oh
it's a cool I know dude whoa look look
look can you see this
so you this you see that it shows you
felt the same thing
and then this thing just shot up also
was you asked somebody close it did hurt
yeah yeah so that there what really was
open
can you move the door again or something
we felt something really cold and we're
assuming that was that was it me real
quiet the ladies were yeah
what's your name with that would you
hear two syllables wait Reuben what
thousand rupee yeah you like these guys
huh yeah Ruby did you close the door
for us please
I was a
last yeah
I think that was great again despite all
the silliness and jokes with these
voiceovers all the footage and audio
that you've just seen and heard is
exactly what we captured that night and
whether you're a believer or a skeptic
there are things in this world that
we'll never know for sure your spirits
really trying to communicate with us or
was it some kind of interference do we
capture actual orbs on camera or were
those just bugs flying around in the
dark did we really in fact witness a
spirit physically closing a full-size
wooden door or is great just a big fat
wooden liar we will never know all we
know for sure is nothing this is
right rice or ryan trying if we change
it because that's what you guys want me
to do but ryan tries for now
Oh something is going down yeah even
those things are going on yeah all the
salmon rolling I'm not it you gotta get
that is that you don't want us to lead
it was crazy
[Music]
no you don't want to
[Laughter]