I cannot believe this video has over a
hundred million views there's just a
bunch of girls shaking their booties
well that's exactly why it's girls
shaking their booties come on that's my
point that's what all these songs and
music videos are about these days that's
all guys want to see I mean not all guys
I personally would rather see a nice
sweet innocent girl for a change than a
girl who's the acting like a stripper
there's never going to be because
rappers don't want to rap about that
stuff what you want in a girl is like
the opposite of every rap song well then
I guess that leaves us with no choice
we'll just have to make our own rap song
[Music]
with a turnip yeah well a beet and dough
and bread that was made from the dough
yeah I still don't get it if I said
we're making a song what does any of
this have to do with big booties I mean
I don't I don't know I mean I just I
didn't have a good segue into the music
videos so all these rappers be like I
want a bad chick I want a big booty she
covered up nice with the JCPenney shoes
[Music]
do show you a bunch of kindness is not
respect you good clothes and smart sent
them my way don't need double D's I want
straight it's a good hobby store in
Michael Jackson take my jacket anytime
tell me all your secrets and I'll keep
them locked down deep
when you need a show to tissue I got
this future
three feet apart zip and I
till we combust full house
sweet
[Music]
sweet home
like that girl
[Music]
buzzer but we can't say
give sound
once we post
sweet wholesome
sweet
[Music]
if I cops
baby show me what you got
[Music]
first guess when we say
Oh
[Music]
oh my god what are you doing what do you
mean did you just try to kiss me yeah I
don't know what I was wrong about you
I'll host them at all
[Music]