there's an epidemic happening right now
spreading across the entire world and
soon the whole nation Twinkies are dying
they're disappearing from pantries
shelves offices and all of them put
together pelvises before we know it
Twinkies will be gone forever unless we
do something about it and if you never
had a Twinkie before I know what you're
thinking all this over a fatty snack
well it's not just a snack it's much
much more like a dessert or a type of
pastry or like a school bus filled with
a bunch of kids they need a tan Twinkies
are a way of life it's my childhood you
know they've always been around since I
was a toddler I mean all the way till
now I'm an adult I don't know what it is
about Twinkies they just keep you
extremely youthful you know when times
are tough some people eat ice cream some
people eat drugs but in my most
depressing moments Twinkies have always
been there for me you're such a good
listener 20 you are so sweet
especially on the inside when you take
that first bite into a Twinkie it's like
watching a unicorn jump over a luscious
rainbows at farts goal does it seem
tender kittens bark velvet cotton candy
it's just not the same some people claim
it's better this way
they said that Twinkies are unhealthy
and they cause obesity well I've never
seen a Twinkie sit on a man and kill him
not the way that a cow can yeah we still
eat burgers don't we these are facts and
it's not just terrible for us think of
all the Twinkies and what they're going
through don't have to do this Twinkie
listen to me you're the last week in the
world if you jump there will be no more
have some faith I thought you believed
in hostess do you know what it's like
waking up every morning hoping your box
doesn't get chosen and when it does
watching each of your family members
being slaughtered so do I believe in
hostess but if he does exist tell me why
why would he create us to live such a
cruel life drinking you can the plastic
is already off right no goodbyes no just
don't let this happen not just for us
before the Twinkies so please don't let
them die just spread the message and
save the to save the Twinkies and
hopefully we'll never have to see this
situation again ever
[Music]
Oh bless you