can't you see
that
guys and me f-feeling take my head
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be afraid to cry
beyond any guy
cry don't be afraid to cry cry let it
free fall from time yeah come wake up
see a sunrise let it free fall from your
eyes stop my day in a rita sonic god got
a soft cheek with the tear running step
bomb and the skies are clear I'm a man
and I have no fear take a step
you see can't you see
[Music]
those are bad
crying don't be afraid to cry
crying don't be afraid cry
[Music]
baby we can go out on a first date but
you come and pick me up half an hour
late girl I'm not gonna lie that you
almost made me cry but I'm a masculine
guy I'll be okay yeah your place Toy
Story 3 the greatest all-time kids movie
but I forgot any leaves woody and now
the tears are coming right back
[Music]
those super bad
crime don't be afraid
[Music]