hey guys so as you know what I didn't
know I didn't even get to no one told me
either didn't even get to finish is that
what you were trying to say
yeah dog what are you talking about you
have to run to finish your sentence
because okay listen as all of you know I
got to watch the film this big boomy
earlier today and guess what I love to
guess things anyway I was allowed to
bring home one of the actors and let me
tell you who am i God really why is it
Steve Carell no but miranda cosgrove no
no listen up stand bebop oh my god I
love him what no he's not even an actor
well then who'd just spit it out already
you know what let me just show you
already Dave Dave
[Music]
ille
so like what the hell what is that like
a Pokemon or something no he's fat
he can't even fit to door oh right uh
why don't you you know turn this
sideways there you go there you go you
got it all right so uh this is one of
the minions from the movie his name is
Dave and on what movie are you serious
cuz I just I just said that earlier what
you think a plain dog you think I'm
playing you think there's some kind of
game you wanna play Monopoly yeah can't
be be sure anyway uh why don't you
introduce yourself I'm sorry what what
what are you trying to say he said that
his name was Dave weren't you listening
yeah don't pay attention understand me
seriously can't understand a word let
him finish sorry what
wait he's seriously hard
[Music]
[Laughter]
what the hell is going on here
[Music]