hey guys I just got contacted by the big
boss at YouTube and he anyway he wants
each of us to make a PSA and help
educate the viewers to make the world a
better place what do you guys think
what's up the saw what
you know PS APIs ah no won't be ignant
dog everybody knows the P is silent so
it's just song no Pierce is not a word
it's an acronym what's that I'm gonna
say it's a type of dog no it means that
PSA stands for something right it stands
for pasa or do you mean PMS know what PS
a PMS and PSA is like the same thing PSA
stands for public service announcement
Thank You Hana Tino please tell them
what that means well in PSA the pee is
not silent no the air is Oh what so it
actually sound like deflating balloon
how is that anything like deflating
balloon you know
[Music]
you
all right show me what you guys got who
wants to go first I'll go so I did my
PSA on sex all right let's see it there
are five things you should know before
you have sex first sex is like cookies
protection is your dinner your appetite
is your life
doo doo is your baby and toilet paper is
your tools you can't have cookies before
dinner or it will ruin your appetite
because then you'll have to make a
doodoo and you won't have the toilet
paper to take care of it so in other
words if you don't want to have a baby
then just stop eating
that was different
anyway who wants to go next how about
you our diesel
what you ready to go Wow where we going
no let's see your PSA oh right uh yeah I
did mine some like everything everything
okay well that's great let's see it
when you do drugs you will die if you
have sex you will die if you don't
recycle then you will die you playing
with fire to die die die
are you serious what you know what
forget I asked you guys I'm just gonna
take my PSA because obviously you guys
don't take this seriously but wait I
never get to show my what you're gonna
yell at us some more I forgot my keys
[Music]
so this is what I came up with I know
you're a nice guy but feel free to be
honest each year tens and thousands and
thousands and thousands and even
hundreds of children and dogs being
murdered by themselves due to hunger and
starvation and the code and error a
terrorist boom
but with your help we can give these
children F dollars we can give them
blankets without holes we can change
their lives for life all you have to do
is dial a simple number at 1-800 stop
the the the help the children and dogs
not die dot-com
because together together together we
can stop the ending for not living for
children and dogs because all it takes
is just a little bit of this so if you
can help us at one eight hundred stop
the Ltd help the children and dogs not
die calm well then at you
bless you
[Music]
so what do you think what tuck was that
uh-oh I'll just talk about PSA I think I
just got mine ah that's okay because you
can use my shampoo again