alright guys so it is Valentine's Day
and we're all here but you know what it
doesn't need to be sad because we have a
girl here Martina what you're a girl
duh and we're all guys so the comments
say find the dumb one
no but you know why don't you pick one
of us to be your date for Batman now if
we don't all have to be sad right okay
you know how do we decide who used to go
with her
oh we could have a con this or we could
just lend her John I don't have a date
for Valentine's Day so I was wondering
and wait what are you doing what I said
pick one of us oh well why don't you say
that next time be more Pacific I did
well Who am I supposed to pick well I
have an idea why don't we leave the room
for like a little bit and we'll all come
up with something to present to you and
you can pick the one you like
hi John it's me again sorry about
earlier I got disconnected man so the
last time this is Papa John's we serve
pizza we are not a person
Oh John he can be so silly sometimes
[Music]
all right we're back anyone Michael
first I'll go no Regina this is for you
oh thanks art art is I wanna why don't
you go first oh yeah I wrote you a poem
the deepest love I've ever felt so far
by Art Basel for shizzle my nizzle
after his we just start shut up okay
I've got two caps in your butt both free
I don't need another girl that don't
need me so you better watch out or I'll
cut your face will you be my Valentines
Day that is beautiful
okay how does it go ahead
[Music]
I like your face
thank you that's it we had three hours
that's all you wrote no I never write I
was drawing cat see unlike these guys I
did something a little different I wrote
you a song so really shut up okay I
loved it really but I'm gonna go a
holiday because he was just true to his
heart I could feel his heart I could
feel it it was all warm and puffing and
I could feel his heart like I could feel
hey we get it I don't feel his heart it
was like it was warm and it was like
popping and I could feel like he had his
heart I can feel it
[Music]