my hair is ugly man hey guys so as a lot
of you already know I made my own energy
drink called ninja milk now that's the
stuff that's not our slogan get your
everyday kick ninja milk and like I
mentioned before I have two other
partners that I work with who basically
run the business side of ninja Mel I on
the other hand am in charge of the
creative side you know the marketing
since you know I am a well genius when
it comes to selling things happen to you
if this ever happened to you have you
ever happened to this usually it has not
happened to them and I still haven't
really sold any of those products but
that's what makes me a good salesman
because I never give up anyway about a
few months ago give or take a year I was
given the task for my business partners
to come up with a ninja meal commercial
and I just had so many good ideas as you
could probably imagine but like I've
said before my partners and I were just
not we have creative differences let's
just say that you just don't understand
the salesman's mind they don't
understand what people want they're like
oh we've actually built businesses and
made them into multi-million dollar
companies whatever big deal anyway I
have good ideas and this is basically
what happened all right so I have a
bunch of great ideas I think you guys
are gonna love ideas or they you know
these ideas done or cuz I was under the
impression that they're gonna be
finished by now oh yeah they're finished
in my head I was gonna I just have
something ideas I want you guys to pick
the best one and then I could was just
gonna knock it out and like a couple
days or something well let's just see
what you have sure all right
so for my first idea
we um ffs
okay sorry
so for my first idea I was thinking well
when you hear ninja milk first things
you think of ninjas milk
what if ordinary guy picks up a can and
all of a sudden when he drinks it boom
turns into a ninja starts fighting off
this huge army of other normal people
and I'm ninjas just beating everybody up
and at the end it cuts to a pasture of
that ninja on all fours and you see me
walk in and start milking that ninja
strained to the can right there text
pops up ninja milk how dairy how dare he
milking and ninja isn't very appetizing
kinda graphic what else do you have
you don't like okay so um this one might
need some explaining for 30 seconds of
this commercial
it just says yup period that's it yeah
it's because it's the answer to the
famous got milk but ours are just yep
okay I mean maybe you could have a
little more or you know like don't
either
okay so Red Bull right they say they
give you wings
what if our commercial we do like an
animated thing like theirs except for us
we say what ninja Moe gives you a sword
because we can't give you wings you know
what let me go back to the first idea
right with the milk and the ninja what
if we just change the slogan I know it
sounds disgusting but what if we changed
it to ninja milk utterly delicious like
utters is in utterly like the nip like
the nipple thing the concept new are
those are nipples of the car do they
have the data and the data or maybe move
on to the next one next one yeah that's
that's it that's all I see it
it's about that wrong so this is it this
is all you've come up with yeah why no I
say forget it I think we should just pay
someone to do this we what we can't
waste any more time well I have I have
one last idea you didn't hear that we
don't need any more job no I promise I'm
telling you this one is really good it's
just like it's just like the Nintendo
paper one or the cardboard video you
like it's it's a stop-motion so if we
gave you this chance you're gonna take
this seriously this time serious as a
cue
and you're sure no stupid puns it's
actually going to be something cool cool
as a cute I think I was a line earlier
we even have time to get that done we
can't afford two maybe three weeks three
weeks at most there's any way possible
guys guys it's a stop-motion okay it's a
bunch of pictures it's not a movie how
long do you think that's possibly gonna
take
[Music]
[Applause]
so what'd you guys think I mean at least
this one didn't end with a stupid pun oh
did you guys want one for the end oh no
no because I could easily make another
one in utter one oh shoot I press the
other button I mean how long do you
think it takes to take a couple of
pictures how long reg like week two
weeks so once again thank you guys so
much for watching if you wanna support
and order a ninja meal for yourself go
to Walmart comm slash ninja milk and if
it happens to be sold out in your area
then just go to ninja milcom we'll get
it to you eventually we're not as fast
as Walmart but you know we'll get it to
you oh I also shout out to Greg I mean
he worked look at me look at him look
he's like teleporting all over the place
he's all bald now that's how hard he
worked he's like he's like one punch man
you just look at him bald