hey guys so recently I've been noticing
a trend where a lot of people have been
saying that awkward moment this or that
awkward moment that and a lot of the
times it's not even awkward they're all
like that awkward moment when Justin
Bieber doesn't reply to my tweets that's
not awkward it's very normal he has a
lot of things to do he has a lot of
friends okay mom I am so sick and tired
of people contributing to that stupid
say okay you're just gonna go huh oh my
gosh this bed it's really hot I'm just
like being gay hey doll look real pretty
right now panting you a ticket you hey
you you're really good lucky hat that's
really mean
hey man I just Aynsley [ __ ] I gotta for
you
ah thanks bro
hey man really hope you watch your own
videos do desperate that's pretty lame
dude whoa
at least I'm not where mom's sure I mean
I was doing laundry in the city
okay so maybe I exaggerated just a
little bit but the thing is awkwardness
happens to everyone it's just a matter
of how you react to it don't feel
embarrassed own it laugh at it enjoy it
you'll never have another awkward
situation again bro you already made a
video about awkwardness uh yes
Tony you saw it oh yeah yeah right um
yeah I forgot house it was a it was a
really good video it was captivating and
good the time is it's like you don't
watch my big idea