hey guys so as most of you all know we
are currently living in the era of big
booties and I'm assuming this is gonna
be another very unpopular opinion of
mine but honestly I don't get it and
don't get me wrong it's not like I don't
like people with big booties I just
personally never got into the trend and
I don't see why people get so excited
over there I guess I've always just been
a fan of proportion I already know the
responses I'm gonna get from you guys
for making this video because I have
mostly guy friends and if I were to ever
tell them personally I don't really care
for extremely big boobs and booties you
know they would probably answer back
with an incredibly well thought-out
intelligent response such as oh okay
and again I'm not saying that I don't
like butts in general I just don't see
the fascination and why having such a
big butt makes you more attractive I
mean the trend is so crazy now that
people have made careers off of having a
big bar look at Kim Kardashian or even
Nicki Minaj her song anaconda is
literally all about having a big butt
but why are big bucks considered to be
so attractive but you really think about
it butts are just another part of your
body that's mostly made up of muscle
with a huge layer of fat on it and yet
we love it we worship it homer society
loves and worships a layer of fat that
has no other use than to cushion your
spine when you sit down and not to
mention that layer of fat is where your
poo comes out as well so when people say
things like damn girl you got the
baddest booty I've ever seen what you're
really saying is damn girl you got the
baddest poop article covered fat layer
cushion for your spine that I've ever
seen what oh sorry I mean damn guy you
got the baddest yeah that's the era we
live in because having a big butt is a
must these days especially for girls I
grew up in the boob era where everybody
worship boobs instead of booties and the
bigger your boobs were it didn't matter
be in a small booty was yeah big boobs
and just like this whole booty trying to
think I was never really into super big
boobs either okay
but anyway he doesn't boobs made more
sense in the booty trend because leaps
are a sign of fertility so
scientifically it makes sense why guys
would be attracted to them I don't know
why I'm shaking them like they're
talking but I'm pretty sure most guys if
not all guys don't like girls with big
boobs just because they're more likely
to reproduce they just like how they
look which i think is stupid because
again boobs are mostly just fat plus
guys have them as well hey check out
this rack doh yeah two minutes a guy gay
what is wrong with you you can't say
that what do you mean say what gay
you've been calling me that this whole
video yeah but as a joke this one
actually has a guy name which could
really be gay so it's not just a joke
it's homophobic so disappointed in you I
don't know how I feel about this
friendship anymore I love gay people
don't like the side of you anyway I
think you get the point when you really
think about this big booty trend it
doesn't make sense and in fact I think
it's wrong and unfair in the same way
that ten years ago people used to say
that Kirby people were unattractive
because you had to be skinny to be
beautiful and I'm all for Team be
comfortable with how you look but this
big booty trend is doing the same thing
to skinny people what skinny people did
to bigger people before make them feel
like crap for not being big enough for
small enough we trained ourselves really
messed up but it's happening right now
just the other way around like literally
a Nicki Minaj's anaconda song she says
the skinny [ __ ] the skinny [ __ ] in
the club I want to see all the big fat
ass [ __ ] and the mother Club you if
you skinny [ __ ] one that's literally
in her song if she got away with it
because she said the word skin could you
imagine how bad it would sound if you
switched out the word fat and skinny
exactly it's totally messed up and
that's another reason why I think this
big booty trend is ridiculous well at
least into our media decides to change
things up and picks another random body
part to worship in fact we should start
the next body trend why not I mean I
don't mean to brag but I do got a few
good ideas in mind oh my god dude check
this out damn tell me that is not the
nicest CDs you've ever seen I ain't
talking about Chris Brown talking about
collarbones bro she got them CDs or to
check these out damn
tell me that is not the definition of
SATs a slender Achilles tendon do not
study for those oh my god this girl got
some fat castro check this out the
basketball team
oh sorry freakin Google search right
there bro check out those calves oh damn
those are nice look at those calves
straight up Kyle's really small in there
everybody fill with milk miss bart's
make these bodies friends really catch
on we'd have to make it cool like
rappers do and put it in a rap song and
if you didn't like any of those body
trend ideas trust me
I saved the best for last damn cow so
fat that jiggle when she stepped in take
your shoes off Asian hall oh I can see
that sending got them CDs to cuddle or
something she don't even need a Luger
let me pinch your wiener
feeling pretty good about that last one
pinching your weenus man that could be
the next work if you do it fast enough
but all jokes aside what I'm trying to
say is that it's not about having a big
booty or big boobs or being curvy or
being skinny my friends are gonna come
and go and if you really think about it
it's stupid how much we obsess over and
as corny and cliche as it sounds when it
comes to attractiveness the one thing
that will always be beautiful is a
beautiful personality and if you can
find that that's like hitting the
jackpot that's like finding of an emo
what no a leprechaun
no Neiman works because Nemo may not be
considered to be the most beautiful fish
I mean he's small and he has a deformed
fin but it's all about personality and
that's the part that we should be
obsessing over not just big boobs or
booties there's a lot of fishing to see
with big boobs and booty find the fish
that's different
find the fish that's unique to you find
the fish that is so lovable and so
charismatic that Pixar has to make a
movie about him even though his mother
and siblings were murdered and he was
captured and abducted and imprisoned in
a tank leaving his father to have to go
cheese after I'm merely getting him
murdered as well just because he has
such a good personality find Nemo is in
the end isn't that what we're all really
looking for our very own deformed mother
and siblings murdered superstar movie
fish what oh sorry was that getting
weird very and also you're saying that
you want to find your Nemo
yeah and you do realize that Nemo is a
boy right yeah but the thing you guys
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers in behind the scenes for
this video click to run the left if you
want to see the previous video or read
rest up like princesses click the one on
the right I know that sounds kind of gay
but that's but it's not not that there's
anything wrong with being gay I love you
in the most heterosexual way what