first there was the board then there was
the skateboard then there was the
skateboard with steering and now for the
first time ever it's here the cardboard
the cardboard also known as the cyborg
air board rowing device is the future of
Transportation
why walk then you could be not walking
step after step after step aren't you
sick of it yet and you rather just be on
wheels all the time well with the
cardboard you'll never not not be on
wheels again so what would it cost
similar products will cost you an arm
and a leg but thanks to the cardboards
advanced design will cost you any body
parts at all just cash and did we
mention that the cardboard is completely
customizable of course we haven't we're
only at that part now the cardboard is
completely customized you'll never have
the same cardboard as someone else with
our crazy selection of colors such as
brown dark brown faded brown shiny brown
Tara Brown eye brown hot brown Cleveland
Brown and for the really daring you can
even get it in red yellow or blue all
mixed together to create a nice
prominent Brown but that's not all
you'll also be able to customize the
safety straps as well not to mention the
headlights and taillights too so how
does it work now I know what you're
thinking the cardboard literally defies
gravity so it doesn't really work well
the answer is simple definitely maybe it
might you see gravity is nothing more
than a science book and so is the word
oxygen also known as o2 to most
scientists meaning there's two O's tools
and tools are what makes things were
moving that the cardboard indeed were
noisy place the cardboard wouldn't defy
gravity is in space because there's no
oxygen so how can you get the cardboard
unfortunately it's not available we've
been having a really hard time funding
our Kickstarter campaign because of all
the homophobic comments or trolls they
keep saying the cardboard is faking gay
well before you type that in this video
let me ask you this does this look fake
to you exactly faking game more like a
real in gay so how can you help now that
you know all the facts and information
you now have a choice nay a decision nay
a responsibility main aim to help us
make this world a better place by
bringing the cardboard to reality
you have to do is go to our Kickstarter
campaign and donate as much as you can
whether it's just a little bit or a lot
as long as it's a lot we'll take it cuz
without you the cardboard is just silly
Nellie it's only just a dream so donate
now and bring the cardboard to life and
before you know it we could all be
looking like this
oh yeah it's transformer as well too
thank guys so much for watching you want
to see bloopers and behind-the-scenes
good throw on the leather you want see
the previous video click the one on the
right and thank you so much to the
people at floor board for sending us
these boards even though we threw it
away we didn't mean that you guys it's
actually a really good product