hey guys as you can see I'm back home in
boy and I was planning to pose a
different video today but being the
idiot that I am I forgot that video in
Vegas on a different computer so but
anyway every year come back home during
the holiday season I try to play at
least one nice thing for a random stream
whether it's paying for someone's meal
in a restaurant my buddy gets where a
homeless person or like punching a
crying baby on an airplane in the face
because I care about it nah just kidding
I don't have the homeless or pay for
meals so yesterday I thought it'd be fun
if I dressed up like Santa Claus and I
bought a bunch of toys and flowers and
burgers and just gave them all to random
people just to make their days been
except for the minor detail that I
didn't have a SATA suit so I just want
an enjoy one instead because I feel it
with all the negativity happening in the
world with you know the shootings and
you know just a bunch of people doing
crazy things because they thought the
world was in there I feel like people
are losing faith in humanity and one
random act of kindness could change the
mind of someone who was planning to kill
someone or planning to do something
really bad and also I just really wanted
to wear a ninja suit and walk around
town because I thought it'd be fun
chickens
but in all seriousness I didn't post
this video so you guys can be like oh my
God he's such a good person I'm really
not I punch babies on airplanes remember
I posted this video with the hopes that
it would inspire at least a few of you
to go and commit random acts of kindness
so again sorry this is not my usual type
of video I will post that other video as
soon as I get back to Vegas but until
then from all the people at the Ryan
Eagle production company we hope you
have a very happy holidays in a great
new year and just remember that if
you're traveling be safe and know that
God gave babies nostrils for a reason
who can screw brood