has this ever happened to you I don't
think the world revolves around me hate
being liked by everyone I wish I didn't
seem so intelligent well look no further
with the douchebag workout you'll never
seem humble like more smart ever again
all you have to do is watch this video
follow along before you know it you'll
go from humble - humble like moves like
a pro smart - oh hey gang welcome to the
douche bag workout if you're beginner
take your time we're gonna start off
with a simple warm-up so come on let's
get started
set up the tripod set up the lights take
out your camera lock it in tight turn on
the timer run on back unbutton your
shirt and punch your back out breathe in
exhale out clench your abs and make a
pow
import picture Photoshop add some
contrast make them Wow export upload
almost done don't forget your humble
caption pain is gain and here's a taste
diet's working happy spin out share to
Facebook Instagram tweet is Tumbo emails
BAM like it first make sure you tag all
your friends like a real douchebag
congratulations you just completed the
warmup double swag you're officially a
douche online but that's nothing boats a
true douchebag is a douche everywhere
especially in person beginners take your
tie you're not gonna become Kanye
overnight just follow this program once
a day every day and you'll be set here
we go
wake up in your movie jammies brush your
teeth touka bathroom selfies skinny
ripped jeans aviators indoors super deep
v-neck with chains galore now slick your
hair should've baked fries
stroke your brows and lick your nose
take your car roll down the windows turn
up the baseball stereo force yourself
into that Lane cut off one quarter and
the other tailgate let them off as you
slow down don't signal till you turn
right now take your time even though
you're late cuz you can always use your
gum as handicap space out back to work
check your comic style others account
each other charity should get all my my
rubbers keep looking busy by playing
Counter Strike but only for the fireteam
kill till night now hit the gym to a
girl before you go to the board and then
girls with your bros prove your
toughness taking shot at the Josh burger
fight for no reason get blocked and
dropped wake up with a headache on a
hospital bed and decisis to the guy who
put a fit inside your head now take a
pic of the money you got say hi you
start from the bottom that you're on top
you're officially a douche
congratulations my friend I was time to
sleep wake up and do it again it's just
like that you're officially a douchebag
hashtag cutie he wasn't that hard that's
what she says follow this workout once a
day every day and before you know it
it could be just like some of our
satisfied customers such as Kanye West
John Muir Ashton Kutcher the bebo
Spielberg every guy not wearing a shirt
in their profile picture Larry some
spongebob walk - a beluga and anyone who
enters yeah bye say uh Jim the list goes
on and on ouch and that was just one of
the workout was the easy price of 6969
you'll receive the complete douchebag
workout DVD which includes bonus douche
bag features such as how to take up two
stalls work on the saying borrow when
you really mean keep sing-alongs know
how to eat from both fries on your way
home tutorial and it even comes with a
whole mess of douche bag activities for
you to do with your friends such as
infamous leg tripping dude
ever-so-popular knee buckler the classic
nut shot and even this thing but that's
not all but if there's no 6969 she said
you can get the douche bag workout
finish it goes with a gold trim DVD case
for free
runway order now and you'll receive this
protein powder shame that you can carry
around everywhere so that people know
you work out a hold on you order now
we'll also throw in your very own way
city with percent Rio cubic
zirconia you order now you'll also
receive 51
children small that your mother listen
to your laundry why someone waiting for
order now before it's too late for some
longer valid because you waiting too
long it's a thing guys so much for
watching but away if you want to see
last week's video click the one on the
left but wait if you want to see
bloopers and behind-the-scenes new on
the right by the way if you want to sell
wait that's that's all there is
all right but wait