was the night before people were
decorating and designing a spooky
haunted house I just drive in the same
line using house at their house that's
three times the same right now no more
let the story begin with a mouse that
clicks on the house you see these these
are scary what we did not so much I mean
no offense you knew guys
Steve mm-hmm ray and I'm sorry I already
I already forgot well don't even worry
about it that was like 45 minutes ago my
name is Devon oh that's right yeah Sam
Sam I'm sorry it Sam th am what the hard
to understand
hey who's stepped on my cord on me
anyway like I was saying this really
isn't looking scary
speak for yourself my decorations are
scary things do you know all you did on
a was hang a pregnancy test
yeah and there are positive
I get scared just thinking about it why
the hell you blaming us for how do these
not even you're helping us huh then it's
true man I did tell him to because some
candy and clothes on his way but it's
not like him to be late were you here
the whoa I scare you all ya know you
actually really did scare anyway oh my
god how'd that you jive I mean great
you got diet yeah coke same thing nope
it really it really isn't the same thing
but it's okay I'll get the ice one guy
died it's not that bad there's some kind
of there's a note in here what's it say
we started off as a nice day we'll start
anew with and with what that's all it
says there's just like two blanks
oh maybe we fill in and win prize yeah
probably one of those contests where you
can win hey why do you ever rise oh I am
sorry this is my friend rocky I'm not
gonna rock you kind of weird by hey he's
cute where'd you find him I was kicking
in the whole way home from part and then
I realized that he is good at rock how
was that good luck no he could rock to
kick I'm surprised he's even friends
with you if you were kicking hands let
me get this straight you showed up 45
minutes late you brought diet coke in a
regular coke and instead of bringing a
friend to help you brought a freakin
rock hey he may be enough but he has
feelings yeah Brewed why are you guys
talking about
it's alright
is it it wasn't much ice left but
freaking storm when you guys grab the
Landers in there there's over here one
jewel
yeah right about see there you go
here pass it down is everybody okay
mm-hmm what's that sound
what if that kind
he's dead oh my god I'm gonna be sick Oh
call 9-1-1 did anybody see what happened
maybe he just tripped in the lights but
I said we get the hell out I know it's
ready outside you know how long it took
me to get my hair looking like it's on
fleek I can't get a thing no it's
probably cuz of the storm huh I mean
even if we do get a signal what are we
gonna say that somebody got murdered
when the lights went out and nobody
happened to see they're gonna blame one
of us look I don't mean to be that guy
but maybe maybe it was one of us you
know this is the first time I'm hearing
you speak Steve you have a nice voice um
thank you don't mention it or you can I
don't know guys this is serious we're
talking about murder here okay I don't
even know how that's possible how do you
die from an i-strip
we say that again Regina that again
Regina say what you just said I don't
even know how that's possible the other
part talking about murder here no that's
what I said how do you die from an ice
tray ice tray yeah yeah makes sense now
what note from earlier what started off
as a nice day
we'll start anew with an ice tray a your
wrapper I mean somebody planned this
wait there's a second note
it's blank oh I think it's the wrong Oh
well what does it say trying to read it
if you would stop interrupting me I'll
be done by now
there's too many make words I don't know
my card with darkness hide and the Sun
shan't go just with each inside look in
a and that's all for darkness hides
something that you can look inside of
thanking me anything
I mean if it's anything like the other
note we know that it has to rhyme right
yeah that doesn't narrow it down much
there's so many words that rhyme lingo I
would know I'm a rapper there's flow and
bow look whatever it is maybe if we
figure out before the killer strikes
again we can stop it what how no wait
Sam is right if we figured out this note
before the blackout we could have
stopped the ray from getting the ice
tray you're rapping again trying to mock
me dawg
guys we have to find this next clue how
if we don't even know what we're looking
for what we do kinda we just have to
look for something that you can look
inside of that's in the darkness and
rhymes with go oh what about like bold
bold I said it first yeah things like
that got it I'm on boy I'm ready to go
let's go this is crazy how much Steve
what a crazy idea I don't make it stupid
look if that's the only clue we're going
off of we'd have to search this entire
house which is why and I again I know
this is gonna sound like something
straight out of a horror movie but I
think we should split up into pairs
something straight out of a horror
movies right that sounds like a bad idea
I mean do you have a better idea - do
any of you what if instead we all play
the Wii the Wii like we is in the gaming
console yeah it has enough controller
for everybody yeah sounds way more fine
oh is that gonna help us find the next
clue on it eh ha ha I don't know am I
the only one taking this serious someone
is dead okay oh my god who I give up I
quit look guys I said I don't want to
split up Ryan's right we'll cover more
ground that way
thank you can we please just pair up now
fine I'll go with our difficulty great
I'll go with holotape and rocky too and
his rock which I guess just leaves Steve
you can pair up with Regina well I'll
check different rooms if you guys find
anything just shout out and welcome to
you come for good cool
let's see this project called and stop
did you stop that oh sorry
meanwhile small stole skull skull
hey what about skull nope don't want a
real word
dammit well well how about neither its
goes well checked all the bowls I guess
it has to be something else could it be
my god this time it's a real word rhymes
with go pull well I guess that's a
little better cuz it's like the chemical
panther but that's still not a real word
that is what about like simple only part
of a word the Pope all real word is
police not even the right name okay I
got you I got you
what about the pool box what the PO box
you know like some people don't get
their mail with their house do you have
to go to the PO Box to get their mail
you mean peel box
yeah the pull box that's what I just
said you ain't gonna spell it out I'm
not stupid
meanwhile look according to that last
for the next one is supposed to be in
someplace dark that we can reach inside
of and rhymes with goal I know something
that rhymes with ghost do you man but
you do what is it how about below if you
know what I mean cuz I'll blow you a
kiss any time you want dear man would
you stop your breath
will you cut it out and just help me
what sorry theorem you stop calling me
that it's just Steve it's not short for
Steven there's no way I enough something
elephant doesn't have an end I really
don't get hair thing I'm gonna bother
just can you look in there I'll check
out here let me know if you find
anything okay
anything for you stammers hmm mean whale
my favorite things
no no but I did find a bunch of stuff
that I thought I'd lost someone like
well like my D s and my cacti book this
is from when I got LASIK Manuel
hey Steve Steven Zoomers skinny Steve
Steven Steven Steven Abalos
what what do you think our ship name
should be or what our relationship name
do you like Reeve or do you like
Christina uh or how do you feel about
Steve Aegina steve steven steve' tickles
find anything out here hey how's it
going in there you find anything yeah I
found lots of things really
where'd you find that found clothes and
bags and random board games no I mean
did you find the next clue yeah how'd
you know that's one of the board games
yeah no I'm not gonna go through with
this stick okay I found those two how do
you keep guessing are you a psychic aus
I stick a my side chick god you're so
this is we are never gonna find anything
this is hopeless
it does feel hopeless but I know I
fought at least one thing yeah okay what
what did you find now huh love and I
hope this place
wait but how did this stuff get here and
why is this light on
the killer knew that he was gonna be
standing there oh my god
if that the next clue no this is what
Steve was reading when you got shot
at what to say it's just goodbye Steven
which means again the killers one step
ahead of us
wait a second it has a goodbye Steven
yeah his name of Steve there's only one
person here that caught him Steven what
Regina you didn't see him what I mean
you're the only one that calls him
Steven and if he weren't the only one in
the room with him talk about how you
shot Steve in the bed what how would you
say that I thought you guys were my
friends look we are your friends Regina
but all the facts care about the facts
just you know already what just because
I was partnered with Steven and I was
the only one in the room and even though
I love God and I accidentally shot two
people in the back who both happened to
be standing rid of a toilet as well
doesn't mean I wanna get it we are in
love even though he didn't love me back
we were in love I believe now I remember
the first time we met it feels like it
was just yesterday you guys just met
like a couple hours ago love has no time
right but the way that you guys are
attacking me even though someone I love
just got a shot I wouldn't expect any of
you to know what love means I'll have an
I guess we did point fingers pretty
quickly yeah and I suppose that anyone
could have met they conceived for Steven
phone and I mean we didn't actually see
her do it no it really does look like
she actually was in love with him
despite only being a couple of all right
what what are we doing what it's just
everything you just said you just seemed
so sad yeah moved on I was like one
minute ago I just met him tonight how
long he expect me to be sad about it
love it's all about time Ryan and even
loving that long I mean okay then I
guess we'll just move on okay what are
we
well we still haven't found the answer
to the other clue but if it's anything
like the other one it has to be around
here somewhere
well then again we're darkness hides in
the sunshine goal just reach inside look
in uh you know what that's what we're
trying to figure out Oh
what about hole yeah that I could
actually work I mean I suppose it's
usually dark inside of holes right and
you can wreath inside of it well you
mean like a hole in the ground how are
we supposed to find out on the third
floor
I got it I know where it is but where
it's in Steve's butt hole beneath what
think about it where darkness highs in
the Sun can't go that's when the Sun
doesn't shine that's a butt and the next
part is just reach inside look in a hole
a hole [ __ ] it's a [ __ ]
lion doing its own like a mean no no not
me I mean Regina it was your idea and I
mean you were the closest to him so yeah
no I don't care how much I loved him
right reaching into the booty like
groceries
that's gross Suri's oh that's why they
say that all right this does not leave
the bathroom ever no way
no of course none of us are gonna say
anything oh my god you're actually gonna
do it well what other choice do we have
I was just gonna recommend my other idea
but this is funnier what other idea I
was gonna say we should just check the
other home first
what do you mean another what what hold
the random hole behind you
it's warm how long ago did you see this
a while ago before you guys even got
here then why didn't you say something
earlier I don't know I just didn't think
it was important it was just a random
poet's smoke coming on and you thought
that a random holding the wall with
smoke coming out of it right after
someone got shot was it worth mentioning
you know what I don't need to take this
from you you're a mother thing someone
follow you we're at all wait there's
something in here it's the next clue
don't stand in thought from the prize
pour the blank and it will blink yeah we
got to figure out two now there's no way
we're gonna figure this out
we couldn't even figure out one I agree
I mean I say we all stick together and
make sure that we all know where
everyone is if someone goes missing
we'll assume that they're the killer we
just all have to stick together as a
whole make sense wait a second say it
again Brian really like the whole thing
because that was like a lot of words you
said stick together as a whole
yeah that's it holes where darkness
hides and the sunshine goal just reach
inside look in it where you guys going I
have to answer we already do that one oh
yeah all right like I said upstairs so
nobody leaves this room but why don't we
get hungers just eat the candy that
Conti brought for the kids but these are
just crackers cracker really what ego
glue with coke no it doesn't yes that's
what they are for it says solar cracker
on the box so you dip inside of the coke
just like are you a dip audio inside
lemonade
that is disgusting you just have to try
oh no I should I am why not hi
Hey where are you going I don't get the
call we just talked about this nobody
leaves remember but it's right there I
mean we'll fill me with him fine just be
quick because we're really getting
off-topic hi
all right so how are we gonna figure
this out well the clue did say something
about being in thought from surprise
meaning they've all been surprises so
far through that you know what the
ending is actually pretty interesting if
you pour something it was something like
why are you can part water yeah I mean
like any liquid really anything that you
can pour I guess huh I almost forget
about that
how does pouring something even kill
someone well you can party lava on
someone yes you could that is one option
to given
how would I even relate to being sorry
for my surprise I mean I'd be pretty
shocked to be pardon lava on me wouldn't
you be burnt still good
they don't stand in shock liquids what
liquids are conductive come to wet Tim
you would literally be shocked if you
poured it on the wrong thing oh that's a
stupid one then all we have to do is not
pour something and we live right now why
would we even pour anything Oh what I
think goodness no I mean we we thought
you were gonna die no I just pour the
coconut rise too fast and spill all over
the wire good thing I not standing
paddle cocaine rice that's it pour the
coke and it will rise well if we figured
it out before hadn t got thought that
has a messed up computer charger man you
gotta get a new one
yeah wait how are those even sparking if
the lights are off hey hey what's that
there's candy in there really wait don't
you little these are mental diet coke
and mentos that's why the coke grows so
fast well at least you figure out one on
Hey look there's a nice clue in the
electrocuted puddle I'll get at no fuss
to get the wire
this is an unlucky room it's the final
clue time has come for you to be what we
do this in another room cuz that's
bodies all burn it smells alright here
we go the time has come to smell it okay
are we good now we're literally a floor
apart it's not like thrashing hair Tibet
ready the time has come for you to be
wise make a choice if you wish to
survive you have all the information you
need I've told no lies for every
Halloween you gotta be kidding me what
there's five blank slate so this is it
it has to be one of us
I mean that's what it sounds like and
according to this we're supposed to have
all the information we need to figure
out who it is we don't have any
information other than the fact that we
know it's not me what we don't know that
and now that you said that I'm kind of
leaning towards you don't lean on me I'm
not major guys not what guys we can
point fingers all we want but the only
way we're gonna prove it is by solving
this that's impossible
or I have idea that 100% okay huh all we
have to do is wait until a kid or kill
everybody then we know the last guy
standing is kid up brilliant that does
work that defeats the whole purpose why
would we care what the killer is if
we're all dead I don't know this is
exactly why a part of me thinks that we
should wait a second what if it isn't
one of us what are you talking about
we're the only ones left no we're not
has anyone seen rocky lately last time I
had a rocky it was upstairs we're
upstairs by the cloak I played him down
to make the call but rocky would never
do such thing are you sure about that
because I knew something was not the
moment I met him yeah Ryan did say if
you leave the group we assume you're the
killer so why didn't you follow us down
here alright that true yeah cuz he's a
freaking Rock okay are you guys kidding
me I'm almost at the point where I'd
rather be killed by one of you than to
listen to your stupid idiotic useless
ideas that sounds like something a
killer would say yeah hi oh my God where
were you during the black Owen
stand by the ice tray the exact same
place is you how would you know where I
was if there was a blackout sounds
suspicious to me wait what what about
when Steve got shot in the same room as
me were you then not in that room so
first you were saying you were in the
same room as me when Ray died now all of
a sudden you're in a different room and
Steve died sound like something's not
adding up oh it's all coming together
now that makes no sense and last but not
least when Hannity was pouring the coke
in it was rising to spilling they're
gonna form a deadly part of the I was
gonna put my hand in but Dan's jumped
inside the way it for me instead of die
instead where are you that out of all of
you probably the furthest away from her
in fact I don't even think that that
needs to happen she only died trying to
save you that may be so but you didn't
die trying to save Pam trying to save me
now did you check me or is it just check
check all the clues finally makes sense
the ice tray the hole the coke rise what
do they all have in common you put ice
inside of the coke you put coke inside
of the hole and the hole will rise to
that you know the hook it will rock okay
know you're innocent because mouths
don't rise wait a second that's it what
I straight hole coke and rise that's
that's five words that's what that's
with the clue man what are you talking
about it says we have all the
information we need now we just have to
fill in the blanks the time has come for
you to be wise make a choice if you wish
to survive you have all the information
you need I've told no lies for every
Halloween ice tray whole coke rise now
we have to figure out what that means oh
my gosh I get it really I know cuz
mouths don't rise they don't for every
Halloween ice tray whole coke rise I
sprayed nice day
do mouths Rhys dies flies told no lies
for every Halloween what do we do every
time we so how was all of your Halloween
no target with tightness sports so much
candy
Sergi the how is your Halloween I have
the worst time ever not one came to my -
wait that's not fair I never get to tell
my how to eat story I'm sorry for every
Halloween I stay home cook nice holiday
can be Oh can't it Ryan your accent
Scott your face it's less handsome hon
attack yes Regina you had a gun this
whole time indeed I did
that's perfect not the killer comes you
can shoot him Jeanette he is the killer
oh my god a hurry shoot him ah feels so
good not to have to make that face
anymore
hunted why you try making your mouth
like a puppet but all day it hurts no I
mean why are you doing this I think you
know exactly why I'm doing this why
don't you finish that flashback you were
having earlier wait how did you know I
had a flashback finish it okay yeah oh
wait that's not fair I never tell my
Halloween story I'm sorry how is your
have a nice day won't poop nice nice now
do you see I mean not really nice to let
you tell your story
you let Regina and or doesn't have the
entire video to tell the story you only
gave me five seconds and there was after
the teach you're doing all of this
because of one video oh no not just one
video you have no idea
we're not starting with you hon t I
don't even know what I even do you what
why not what the hell are you talking no
but wait
look okay honey I'm I'm sorry okay like
I can give you better parts you can be
the star of the entire show you see I
thought about that but why would I want
to be a part of schizo when it's a dying
show I'll just start my own show I mean
I already pretty much wrote this entire
episode what do you mean
everything that happened tonight played
out exactly as I planned one might even
question the script because of how
perfect it all played out I mean it
might have worked out for you but
there's no way you could have planned
everything like what about when Ray died
you couldn't have planned to have a
blackout there wasn't any black guy was
there why do you think I stood where I
did when I entered the room you stood
right by the light switch and in the
same path that Ray had to walk through
in order to bring the ice trays which I
had already attached the note to it's
funny I gave you all every single chance
to guess that it was me all along what
do you mean I was the one who brought
the coke that had the very first clue
remember I was the one that was closest
to Ray when we found him dead I was even
the last one to mysteriously show up
from behind the counter yet none of you
suspected poor harmless Holliday because
I'm nothing more than a punchline to all
of you okay what about when Steve got
shot even if it did come from the hole
in the wall we were on the complete
other side of the house you were with me
but it was I yes you were right when I
went to the closet you you were bi you
see over the years I've been collecting
some of your favorite possessions
remember all those things that went
missing in that one episode we did
called schizo the missing things
wait no we've never uploaded an episode
like that exactly because just like
everything else that you were distracted
by in that closet it went missing that
still makes no sense this whole
explanation makes no sense you know what
else doesn't make sense I already caught
this gun once to shut you up but I'll do
it again if I have to okay okay just go
ahead as I was saying while you were
distracted by some of your favorite
possession I waited for Steve to get
into position where I had already made a
whole pointing exactly where he would be
standing okay I mean I don't mean to
offend but how did you know that Steve
was gonna read the note
Regina read the note because I wrote the
word read on that no remember Oh read
that's what that's sad what I saw then
no way before Steve different I thought
it said read as him it was already read
so why would I read it again you're an
evil genius I know alright fine what
about the coke and mentos thing hmm yeah
you could have easily killed yourself Oh
see he planned that too let me guess you
froze the Mentos in the ice tray knowing
that by the time we got back from all
the other events if he melted so that by
the time he poured the coke it instantly
spilled everywhere next to the wires
that he previously cut but no you didn't
spill the coke on yourself
you spilled it exactly next to use a
puddle would form and it would look as
if someone else tried to kill you said
you'd be the last person we suspect to
leave the next clue in the electric
puddle knowing that only Regina would be
dumb enough to reach into that puddle
causing them the jumbo didn't save her
Gina taking her life in the process
actually that's the one thing I got
lucky on what do you mean I kind of
forgot that I set that trap up good
thing I wasn't standing in that puddle
right but what if none of us wanted coke
because it was diet well you had to
drink something right
why else would I bring silver crackers
and it's true alright that's enough of
this explanation long story short I set
everything up and now you're all here
ready to die why are you doing this on a
tear are you serious I just answered
that in the beginning oh well then at
least tell us how you did it I'm gonna
enjoy killing you the most I think see I
knew he liked me the most
but now that I've unnecessarily
explained my entire plan it's time to
put this to an end please honey think
you already made your point you don't
have to do this yeah plus we're the main
cast the other guys could die but if we
die there's gonna be no more skits off
perhaps that's exactly what I wanted
say goodbye to skittles forever and say
hello to the one and only hotter taste
show what the better luck next time
buddy has finally come to an end
no more artists Allah is uncontrollable
temper
no more Regina and her complete
non-existent intelligence no more Ryan
and his wealth is boring realistic joke
setups and storytelling and of course no
more Han attained quite possibly the
most random and beloved character of all
maybe finally enjoy the r.i.p no may he
finally have the ri me waiting maybe
finally right me so he finally also say
or IP may he finally our IP that's all
you had to say but that make no sense
maybe finally you nice and pot seriously
we're ending this whole entire thing and
we cut away just for that joke no we
also cut away to show people that I
still had I wait so thelma's a girl