we are going to find a way to rickroll
people again no we're not who would
actually click on your video not expect
it especially on April fools strangers
people who don't know us I don't know a
lot of people who many have already fell
for it it's not gonna work love the idea
Ryan but I think he's right this time
you both are just gonna give up then no
we're not giving up we just don't think
ricarose work anymore since you know
heaven expects the truth is you Rick
Rolled people last year to remember
isn't the number one rule surprise to
not repeat the same rules since when are
there rules and like I already said it's
April Fool's it's not gonna work Oh what
do you guys really think I haven't
thought of that I have a lead on how to
find the next Rick rule full thought-out
plan but I'm still gonna need your guys
commitments what I'm just trying to help
I feel like I don't contribute to any of
these thinking you're right back on the
same page Sean let's get this started of
course he's gonna side with you again
you guys know that in Rick Astley's song
never gonna give you up he says the word
never quite frequently wouldn't it be
crazy if I told you that there's a song
that says the word never even more than
that even though the song is about never
saying never get this in Rick Astley
song he says the word 41 times exactly
including the title in Justin Bieber's
song he says the word 69 times including
the title from a guy who's saying never
to say never isn't it a little weird
that he's saying the word never
twenty-eight more times than Rick anyone
starting to see the obvious sign here
other than the two of them saying the
word never a lot no there's no
connection guys it's so obvious
seriously you two Sean I still don't get
it
justin is 20 years old why don't take a
guess how old rick astley is tell us
already you are no fun he's 48 how much
do you think the difference between the
two ages are I'm just gonna take a wild
guess and say 28 the exact difference of
the number of times they say never in
each of their songs seal in the
connection yet gotta admit that's a good
one making one connection or coincidence
I should say doesn't mean anything you
sure about that understand this
Never Say Never was not just Justin's
biggest song but his biggest movie
couldn't be his only movie if he keeps
getting arrested I'm on break he's a kid
who said it yourself he's 20 years old
he's all grown up never mind I was just
trying to contribute again gonna shut up
now let's just get back to the topic
you were saying down to the roots of
both of these guys never mind what
they're doing now what are they best
known for gonna have to say the internet
run the projector around 2008 is when
Rick rollin got being
that's about the same time Justin Bieber
got signed and well deserted YouTube as
well never gonna hold it against him
making way more money and more famous
than he could ever do online going
off-topic can you please just finish the
damn I'm or why don't you all I'm trying
to do is figure out the next Rick roll
and I'm just never gonna get to the end
I get it okay
it's April Fool's you're wasting
everyone's time ha ha good one Ryan now
if you guys don't mind I'm over this
stay then again Greg goodbye what are
you trying to get it never gonna that's
what you just said tell me you guys
caught that just now lie back down for
this one I think I just figured it out
and I think I'm still figuring it out as
we speak hurts my brain just thinking
about it especially because I'm not the
only one that figured it out it was the
both of you you just finished it Shawn I
know I was just trying to contribute
again what are you guys talking about
the next rickroll it's us it's always
been us the beginning of every line
we've been saying up until Shawn just
finished it I didn't notice until now
but that's it that's the ritual
we are no strangers to love you know the
rules
SOT I full commitments what I'm thinking
of you wouldn't get this from any
further guides I just wanted to tell you
how I'm feeling gotta make you
understand never gonna give you up never
gonna let you down never gonna run
around and desert you never gonna make
you cry never gonna say goodbye never
gonna help live and hurt you so let me
get this straight
you rickrolled people on our video about
Rick rollin that's so stupid you're just
gonna piss people off well I mean it
could have been worse at least I didn't
do the actual rick roll we're just
kidding everyone we're not actually
gonna rick roll you we just made this
video for fun in the spirit of april fer
hope you guys didn't get tricked too
many times today especially not with the
rick roll because personally i can't
think of anything worse than getting
rick rolled on april fools so thank you
guys so much for watching if you want to
see bloopers and behind the scenes click
the one on the left if you want to see
the previous video that we posted like
four days ago click the one on the right
I know that's got to be some kind of
record we posted two videos in one week
that's so not like us where were you
like pewdiepie now no we got way less
subscribers