sup guys haven't um seen you guys since
Halloween it's good to have everybody
but what are we here for I was about to
get there but apparently a lot of people
didn't get the ending to our last skit
so video what are you talking about no
the last schizo episode we did the 30
minute Halloween video I don't recall we
didn't do that wasn't even that long ago
how do you guys not remember what was
the name of it the last skit so it is is
what the last one what if that's the
last skit so then what is this then
where am I am lying Regina that wasn't
really the last I am you guys know how
to get to Ryan's how high I'm supposed
to be there Everett video yeah I think
that's like one Street over oh my gosh
thank you no Jenna sit down look that
obviously wasn't the last skit so that's
what I've been trying to say this whole
time people just thought it was because
of the title title of what the video
what video
the last skits oh my god it is I'm lost
again
all right now that everyone knows what
we're talking about we're all on the
same page right yo hi yep page 3 what oh
hey re on page 4 I think we're still on
page 2 okay no guys there's no actual
pages yes there are see Ryan says what
are you guys talking about there's no
actual pages Regina says yes there are
see Regina holds up scrip and reads
Ryan's that's not supposed to be in this
just put that down no I'm just kidding
you guys it actually says Regina puts
down script but I'm a rebel
I don't even have script I don't know
how to read anyway now that we're all in
the same I mean we all know what we're
talking about we all know that schizo is
not completely ending but I do think it
is time that we come up with some new
shows you know we got to keep this
channel fresh we got to come up with
shows that people actually want to see
skits like these are a thing in the past
I can do that it's easy I got some ideas
hi well that's good then let's hear your
ideas who wants to go first I'll go
sounds good let's hear it so I know this
channel has a lot of guys that watch but
I think we're missing out on all the
young girls cuz young girls need
somebody to look up to you know somebody
that's like young and smart and
beautiful and smart and intelligent and
all six of those things put together and
I'm gonna do just that with my new show
that has one of my best friends and it's
called beautiful young smart in
television oh yeah my shells caught
Regina's and shandies hi I'm Regina but
you can call me Regina and I'm Shawna
but you can call me Shani when we're
together you can just call us Ron Dury
which I know sounds like a racist joke
about an Asian saying the word laundry
but it's not we're not racing and we
hate laundry wicked Regina
Shaun Diez
so welcome [ __ ] thank you guys again
for tuning into our show you guys don't
already know we're the coolest teens in
our school home school and we're gonna
teach you guys how to be coolies like is
that right Shaunie's Yeah right okay
right yeah
most of our swaggiest friends live by
the motto of yo only live once but the
cooler and swagger kids live by a
completely new model that we made up
awesomely never not obeying Yolo is not
good
also known as noe which basically means
you should awesomely live your life
because you only live once because if
it's honest [ __ ] and today we're gonna
teach you guys how to sound like an
annoying team just like us the first
step in sounding like an annoying T to
fork in your word words are long if
something is crazy all you have to say
is oh my god that is so crave something
is amazing all you have to say is whoa
that is so amazed and if something is
crazy amazing all you have to do is put
the two together and say oh my god whoa
that is so creamy the next step in
sounding like an annoying teen is simple
all you have to do is add ears or ease
to any word it easily becomes annoying
boards now pace shanties are you hungers
right now so cults hungers how about
yeah oh my god I got the rumblies in my
tum er you should totally go to Chipotle
Chipotle Chipotle is like oh my god I
can't even and the last tip we have for
you to sound like in a knowing teen is
to make up your own trendy word just
like Gretchen did in the movie Mean
Girls even at the word fetch it was
completely new and completely original
most unswayed thing you can do as a teen
is to use somebody else's trend words
wag oh my god what the [ __ ]
make sure you make up your own original
word don't copy all you have to do is
think of a completely different word
that relates to the word that you really
want to say like if you see a guy who's
looking really cool you can say oh my
god that guy is so cold because cool and
colder like twinsies where yeah and if
he's hot he's hot and he's cold ya know
like God just at the Katy Perry song
Holt's cape more like cat purrs for sure
at parrots are like dog bark dogs are so
door yeah but barks are never barks or
like from tree likes trees have branches
branches are likes Ted likes dogs and
sticks do go together because when you
throw a stick like two bags
oh my god that's the perfect word he is
so fast so glad we made it up so thank
you guys again so much for watching let
us know if you have any other team
related questions and put them in the
comment box below I had to do is hashtag
regina's and Shaunie's and women
answered you next but until then I'm
Regina and I'm Shawn Diaz together we're
just
Regina's and Shani's
let's leave it up high so why'd you guys
think I should thought it as a good deal
I mean it's definitely something else
thinking that to something I knew it was
something yeah um anyway Dante or DISA
when you guys want to go next
yep I'm not trying to rush you but like
are you gonna tell us already doing it
doing it huh you haven't even said a
word well I gotta say it out loud I
thought if I just thought about it it
would just show up no oh it's a common
mistake well my show is basically what
everybody comes to the Internet to see
pranks I mean pranks do well but it's
not that original and I did just put out
a video about prankers going too far
exactly that's what makes my pranks
different the house see all those
prankers that are taking it too far I'm
gonna prank them but even farther
further further I'm not a reed got you
so bad man there's a prank
who's afraid hello mr. harless Rowan
yeah this is Charles Brown who's this
hello Charlie this is dr. our disa I
mean dr. dizzle our junior that the
third fourth the 34th yeah your parents
were recently in a car accident and you
were there emergency contact oh my god
what happened or the OKs they're both
still alive but in critical condition
we're gonna need you to come down here
immediately yeah of course I'll be right
there
oh come on mr. Brolin it's brown like
poo uh oh sorry oh come on where's my
parents can't see them yes uh you will
be able to see them shortly but I do
have to inform you that we don't my
dolls can you oh this real quick thank
you what is this sometimes we use the
dollars to explain to kids what really
happened so they're not shown I don't
need that helmet do it anyway oh um
sorry
uh look your father we had to amputate
both of his arms and well your mother
coincidentally we had to amputate both
of her legs how happy so we actually
thought the best course of action was to
take both one arm and one leg from both
your mother father and sew them on each
other so that they both have at least
one of each what the only problem is I
kinda mixed up the arm in the leg during
the surgery what what does that even
mean well it means that we accidentally
sold the same leg on your father and the
same arm on your mother so now well this
can't be happening it is it did mr.
Pooler there's actually one more thing I
need to inform you about could you have
possibly done stupid stuff none of this
is true bro what my name is art dizzle
I'm not even a real doctor doesn't even
happen you know what you just got breaks
on
parents aren't even in the hospital huh
okay where are they they're in the river
what I killed him
yo what up is your boy or dizzle make
sure you guys like my fanpage if you
guys want to see more pranks that was
disgusting yeah I know his name was the
color of poo I like it I I just need to
can we just please move on Hanah take
can you go oh yeah yeah my show is about
the gaming gaming videos and again
that's not something new but gaming
videos do do pretty well yeah dude you
know my name is different from everybody
else also everybody else filmed himself
playing game but I'm going to film
myself watching them play the game I
don't like this on attack there's
another good idea that's my favorite one
yet
are you serious flat you actually think
that's a good show why you always gotta
hate on our show ideas we're least we
got ideas where's yours hand it back off
I guess there's no better time than now
but this is my show idea what I don't
get it I still don't have scripts so I
don't know what to say for all these
years of skits love it's finally time to
reveal it feel what well the truth
that's about it just told them the truth
I mean I know you told me not to talk
back to these voices in my head but I
mean what am I gonna do I needed show
ideas and they had different ideas I
never would have thought of it's like
they have their own personalities like
that one that wanted to do a pranking
channel that just went way too far and
another one that came up with the gaming
reacting video which we probably can't
even do because we probably get sued for
that now the girl man I mean I'm not
gonna lie she probably had one of the
best ideas out of all of them but I got
a she so annoying I mean sometimes I
just want to yeah just I just I don't
know how much more I can take you know
what do you think I should do well first
of all just remember when you're feeling
these feelings just remember what I
always say just breathe
everything's gonna be okay secondly I
think you do have a flow idea I don't
think you need those other ideas all
these voices that you keep hearing
inside your head
I mean if themed queen - that fam really
you're just gonna cut me off I'm just
saying hi to them
hi dad oh hi Regina it's been a while hi
you were supposed to be dead Oh Regina
that was just a skit for halloween
remember that's why i haaaate still
alive - I mean I thought you'd kind of
figure that out since the kind of
fitting right next to you how to take
your life to life wait this doesn't make
any sense how are you guys in a second
fam if you're still alive and how do you
still life that must mean oh my gosh my
Stephen stammers was alive I love it
yeah you see about that um what the heck
where am I hello Steve and welcome to
heaven no I can't be dead oh that's
right I got shot actually you're not
dead yet but you are in a place between
life and death and you must choose your
own path what do you mean you have a
choice you can choose to come with me
right now and enter the gates of heaven
or you can return to your body fight
through the pain push harder than you've
ever pushed before and not only will you
be able to see but live amongst all of
your loved ones once again it is your
choice even it my mistake yeah no I'm
just gonna stay here oh I get it he's
waiting for me he's such a sweetheart
he's so fetch right all right are you
done with what uh interrupting me by
talking to people in my cutaway or my
skit talking to people in a fake world
oh wait hold on you think that you're in
the real world
uh yeah we obviously started in this
world and you were my show not no this
is obviously the real world I mean you
guys are just a bunch of voices in my
head you're not real isn't that right
dr. Sam well yes but are you talking
about them I thought you were on our
side no I'm on this side in the real
world so it's not the real world it is I
call us beta Baker's we ran with the
actual doctor right here he's not lying
it's not the miracle yes
I don't like this holiday so thank you
again so much for watching if you want
to see bloopers you kinda seems to come
on the left you want to see the previous
skits of video click them on the right
and remember if you do click them on the
right it's you're gonna need like 30
minutes because it's a long video but it
does explain a lot of things in this
video so you probably if you didn't see
it you probably watch that one come back
to this one and then you'll be like oh I
get it now