guys we go come downstairs get in here
so 3:30 in the morning think I may
finally be on to something guys you're
still doing this hasn't it been like
three days now actually it's been four
days and you just see the text at the
beginning of the anyway why does this
Melanie yes most like piss I mean I've
been literally working non-stop so it
probably is Oh
pulp pulp is good for you dude
wait why doesn't mind have any pulp in
it anyway guys I think I might finally
be on soda is this all about it
finding the next big thing on the
Internet you know I'm sick of always
being late on those stupid trends like
planking or those coning videos in fact
I think I only recently just saw that
nan cat video isn't 9 K I think it's
nyan nyan yeah yeah anyway I think I
just figured out how to find the next
big thing on the internet can't really
predict that it just has to happen oh
yeah remember Aaron Carter the teenage
heartthrob when we were kids I guess
it's just a coincidence that his brother
Nick Carter was in the infamous
Backstreet Boys the rival band NSYNC
which consisted of who Justin Timberlake
one of the biggest stars even till today
who was even bigger than him right now
someone with the exact same name Justin
me and just when we thought no one could
possibly compete with Justin Bieber boom
I've just been gamers all in one
direction you see now they're all
connected I mean I guess 'sir kinda
connected but it's kind of a strand I
thought you'd never ask
what oh I thought you were gonna you
know ask cops as relevant to the video
and I thought you never asked you
remember the evolution of dance one of
the first viral videos of all time and
he just so happened to dance to the song
baby got back time
the most popular things on the internet
such as dancing baby laughing baby
serious baby babies babies babies oh
that's why Justin Bieber many considered
a baby at the time that was always this
very person single baby featuring
ludacris which just so completely borrow
and what word is said more than any
other word in that song
baby baby baby which brings us to more
babies except a little bit older now in
charge of my fan totally became a
memorable name especially after Charlie
the Unicorn and who believed in unicorns
people on drugs but not just any people
on drugs babies on drugs which brings us
to David after the dentist what are you
need to go to the dentist's for bad
teeth deeply pachuco not just any
chipmunk the dramatic speaking of
dramatic of course you remember one of
the most dramatic videos of all time
leave Britney Alone by Chris Rock which
just so happened to be a crossdresser
just like Liam Kyle Sullivan and oh my
god shoes the borrowed music video that
was so fun to watch but making a little
bit irritating kinda like the superstar
sensation known as French speech that's
not the character with a super
high-pitched voice almost as high as
that sneeze from ceasing peasant at you
more like blessed shoes which brings us
to wait we already did that one so you
must be thinking ah here it goes again
the spectacular music video ok go
dancing on treadmills which everyone
uses when they're on a diet coke and
mentos and who would have done that such
a simple couple mix together we create a
closet I probably quit buying everyone
like chocolate ring once again a fire
busy video where the artist K Sunday
says the phrase Chocolate Rain a total
of 48 times
now this is where it gets tricky 48 no
try for da it's a simple math equation
really the forwards of D obviously
meaning DAP is in deaf hands are harder
better faster in the song totals 56 and
what's the difference between 56 and 48
that's right eight you see for D eight a
lot of charm thanks Nick no problem in
and well that's all I got so far
dang so close you do know this doesn't
make sense wait we'll see that again
what then you don't really make sense no
what you did before that you just sighs
so don't you get it psy Gangnam style
the most viewed video of all time right
now that's the next connection that
doesn't make any sense
well doesn't it because I think it's
simple it's easy as ABC ABC one two
three exactly 123 the National pokedex
number for the bug Pokemon Scyther
there's your proof proof of what tell me
just connected the very last and biggest
trend today okay even if I did believe
your crazy theory what about the Harlem
shake that only lasted a week and it
doesn't count anybody that did that
trend is probably an idiot so what's
that for sigh then I don't know well I
mean he's Asian Wow
King dick what wait no you guys are both
right the word Asian and dick what our
age is most commonly teased for being
Fox fresh off the boat and dick is just
another name for Richard
you see folk rich WAP really gonna make
you stuff
what do you do when you're on a boat row
correct
and what's short a way to say it Richard
Rick wait
well we really just made all of you or
sit through the whole video just to
recrawl them that's kind of messed up oh
it's not what would be messed up is if
we were to make the viewers sit through
this whole video just to see us by the
way I never bought oh that's just my
piss