alright guys as you know we just
released paranoid 74 and well the
reviews aren't that good Wow I know
right there saying it's exactly the same
as paranormal activity three two and one
that is just silly so what we need to do
is create the next sequel that is
completely different from all the other
ones any ideas
cut what do you got alright what if we
do everything we did in panel activity
for but at the very end when they least
expect it
hang on will activity six because
they're gonna be expecting five that's
what no that's exactly how we came up
with the first three sequels we need
something different I've got a
paraplegic activity we start off of a
shot of a guy in the dark we soon notice
that he's not moving like a normal guy
he's moving even though apparently jig
means yeah it's like a robot right no
it's when you're paralyzing you can't
walk oh but what if we put the robot in
the wheelchair doing that dog do
pare-pare that's normal activity a pair
yeah like the fruit pair yeah that's
scary
[Applause]
[Music]
you're not even trying anymore yeah at
least my robot idea had a person in it
yeah that's not even relatable you're
gonna choose a fruit at least pick a
scary fruit like a squash yeah or like a
cabbage yeah yeah fine
guess I'm not scary enough to be here
great don't do that okay you wasn't
preaching anything good anyway
any other ideas and you got what are you
writing
new guy pay attention
so you're telling me this isn't scary
see he gets it