has this ever happened to you I have no
burger well look no further thanks to
Carl Jr's new $6 portobello mushroom
burger you'll never not ever not have a
burger again what that's right just
saying the name Carl Jr's new portobello
mushroom burger Carlos dnews new
portobello mushroom burger collagen you
put a bit of mushroom burger is loads of
fun cars didn't approve brother mushroom
burger fail moving on you're probably
wondering what is Carlos Jr's new
portobello mushroom burger well to sum
it up in a few words which a huge juicy
delicious round jaw-dropping doorstop is
table citing people waiting face
pottering armpit wiping notebook writing
car cleaning sexy-looking sensor
covering portobello mushroom cover
burger that's all nice things but can
you eat it
can you eat it why yes you can
how do you eat your burger
Hey