energy get this shameless plug
doesn't mean even shame shameless plug
up I'm a little ashamed
hey guys speaking of which and just a
quick update before you get this do Ryan
started I just wanna say thank you to
call the people who actually ordered
ninja milk since the last video when we
announced it we saw a lot more than how
we were going to and again I appreciated
so much so thank you guys don't worry
guys I know I know not everything I'm
gonna be posting is gonna be just fun in
Jamel Noah I definitely know what it's
like to follow a celebrity or a youtuber
they know they create a product and all
of a sudden their whole entire life and
everything they post about is about that
product Conor McGregor used to have
funny tweets and plenty like Instagram
stories and stuff that made his whiskey
and everything was above that I actually
almost had fallen because it was
literally just about his whiskey and
that is kind of what I'm doing for the
moment but don't worry I'm not gonna be
doing that for it's just cuz we just
launched but with that being said yeah
shame shameful plug Mitch Malcolm we
should we still have a lot to sell just
to break even but seriously thank you to
everybody who did order back to the deer
ride he's actually gonna be a specialty
arrived because I'm gonna be giving away
secrets thanks to this first year Ryan
dear Ryan can you make a video showing
us how deer Ryan's are actually chosen
that one had no likes teach us the
algorithm I'm just to break it down even
simpler for you guys so you understand
the way I think D Ryan's are not
necessarily always because I like when I
feel like doing it you're Ryan video I'd
go to addy Ryan not only the most recent
but the past year Ryan videos you can
check the comments I think screenshots
of all the deer Ryan's that have you
know tons of up votes and tons of life
but a lot of time even those your riser
there a lot of are very much the same
like the same ones over and over not see
sometimes they're really good ones and
really interesting ones but I would say
a majority of the time they're things
that I think I've already done or done
something very similar to it or it's
just something I don't want to do or
it's just I don't think it's gonna be
entertaining I know because it has
something likes it means people want to
see me do it I just I'm selfish I just
do the ones that I want to do all of
today's D Ryan's are gonna be ones that
you guys want to see because it's the
ones with the most likes
starting with dear Ryan can you go
outside and scream teehee
one point six thousand people wanted to
see me do that I mean like this is a
good example like I don't I don't for
one I don't want to do that it's hot in
summer but the thing is I don't
just don't see how that's gonna be
entertaining 1600 people want to see me
do it so I'm gonna do it whether I want
or not I'm doing it all right so go
outside we are outside and I just have
to scream TT right
I see like this is this is stupid like
what is it mean I'll do it
it's not hard to do is just I don't
wanna you know disrupt my neighbors I
mean I could do it louder I just wanna
you know what let's go down the street
yeah this just go down the street so we
don't bother these people alright so we
actually went to the end of the street I
didn't realize that there was gonna be
construction workers and I don't want to
be screaming and then they think
something's wrong who do we go a little
bit further all right so we are a little
bit of a hike away from the houses I
think we're good you know what birds I
don't want to disrupt them I don't want
to issues with PETA so maybe we should
just like a couple more miles okay I
think this is good I mean we're a few
miles away from anything I don't hear
any birds so yeah it's pretty wide open
yes we're good can you keep it down
you're not the only one out here sorry
hey we could go a little bit further do
you Ryan why are you so talented I mean
I guess some people are just born with
gifts yeah
I don't know how to that happening are
they trying to do it you're right you
and your friends pretend to be each
other for a whole day hey guys nice I
just got this dear Ryan and asking if
you and your friends could be each other
for an entire day you guys down
oh yeah I'll be dead I guess I'll be
Greg no and then I'll be will oh but I
mean who's gonna be me then and Who am I
gonna oh I thought you said we were
supposed to pretend to be our friends
what my only friends are men are my dogs
so we kind of see you more as like an
owner type of figure than a friend that
makes sense
do you write when you prove that one
plus one is not equal to two
see this one is just dumb like one thing
another thing always makes two unless
one Apple with another Apple you just
got two apples one plus one equals two
Michael if you had one cup of water and
you had another cup of water and you
added that together you still got one
cup of water just a bigger one proving
that one plus one doesn't always have to
equal two it's just a bigger one show
that to your math teacher dear Ryan can
you do a face reveal I actually had to
just google it because I didn't know
what the hell a facial is and apparently
it's a trend on YouTube where youtubers
who've never shown their face before I
guess aren't showing their faces for the
first time on video I'm not sure how I
would be able to do that because you
know I I you've seen my face before but
then I realized there is something I
actually could reveal since I'm just
releasing all the secrets on to you Ryan
I might as well keep releasing more
secrets guys there's another person that
makes appearances on this channel and
you may recognize her from skin cells or
others random skits as the real dumb one
yes I'm talking about Regina and I know
this might come across as a little
shocking to a lot of you but both Regina
and myself
well we're actually the same person
that's right there is no lying ah see
now you don't have to worry about how
dear Ryan's are chosen because there is
no Ryan's just me your dear Regina tune
in next time for a special episode of
dear Regina it's Regina Regina dear
right you make a whole song using only
the word TV ever since I started this
show dear Ryan I think over the course
of a I don't know how many years that
has been the most common one I've ever
gotten and the most the one with the
most likes and upvotes has been this
making a song out of the out of my
teehee and I'm not sure why everyone
wants to see that I guess because that's
what I'm most associated with is the
word teehee I'm just warning I never did
this one because I know it's not gonna
be good but I guess I'll just do a bunch
of T's and see what I can come up with
all right let's see what we can make
[Music]
[Applause]
so leave your questions in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video
[Music]
[Applause]