when we get this and they're still
coming in investigate Trump do one on
Trump tell us the truth about Trump it
must really like it then you might
actually be the opposite maybe we should
just try again tomorrow
maybe we'll get better ones I just don't
get it okay what he's been president for
a URI excited Attorney anymore so not
like we're ever on time for the trends I
mean do you remember the Miley Cyrus
video or even the Beyonce one yeah but
those are celebrities we're talking
about the president here we're not gonna
be making another video about Trump
[Music]
oh hey guys no no don't you hey guys
that's like you're about to start one of
your videos I didn't agree to that all
you said was to look for some common
requests that's all yeah no those
weren't real what yeah I wrote them all
didn't you read the account names in the
comments these aren't real right I wrote
this can't believe you're still reading
these hey Sean hey Paco sucks 69 real
yeah okay not that one was not me the
profile picture is literally you doing
that oh how did that work out we just
spent two hours looking through these
Lilian only took me an hour to write why
Holly because most of it was copy and
paste so why did you make us do this
well if you would just have a seat and
let me explain instead of wasting
everyone's time now you're concerned
with wasting people's time so now that
everybody's settled in prepared
yourselves what I'm about to tell you is
something so shocking so mind-blowing so
incredibly secretive that even me saying
it out loud right now could get us all
then don't say it oh don't say that it's
gonna put us in danger danger no I was
just saying that if I say it all out
right now it could get us all to be
closer because then we'd have like a
really cool secret together you know and
then we could get friendship necklaces
like these those are ties what does any
of that have to do with trunk get to the
point already fine you wonder why me and
Sean have these and you don't yes that's
why you say nothing today I am gonna be
revealing the truth behind none other
than our president in Donald J
that's the graduation song oh so you're
probably wondering what truth is there
to learn about our president because
there's so many questions about it like
for one why would a billionaire want to
be president in the first place is it to
actually make America great again or is
it to benefit himself and his businesses
or maybe it's just to boost his own ego
everyone has their own opinions and for
some reason the majority of those
opinions seem to be pretty negative gee
I wonder why why well in order to find
out the truth that's the first thing we
need to do we need to ask ourselves why
do so many people hate the guy isn't it
pretty obvious the things he says the
things he does he mocked a disabled
person like who does that exactly no one
does that especially when you know
you're being watched by the entire world
and we all know Trump loves to be loved
so why would he do that because he just
doesn't get it get what people humans
it's almost like he doesn't realize and
the things he says and does are not
things that people normally say and do
the guy is different and not just a
little different he's very different the
way he acts the way he speaks even the
way he looks but we just here to roast
Trump because everyone already does that
oh not at all then just tell us because
I don't see what you're trying to get at
what I'm trying to say is that I truly
believe that our president Donald Trump
is
an alien but it makes everything make
sense you said it yourself he does
things that no humans would thing to do
like mocking that disabled person on
national television that's because he
said it said sit avidity or is it
because he just doesn't understand
humans and when humans consider right
and wrong and normal and weird just like
that one time he had that interview on
the view i've said that if Ivanka
weren't my daughter perhaps I'd be
dating her see and when everyone else
left he just didn't understand why that
was weird when it should be obvious to
any normal human that that's not
something you say about your own
daughter
especially on national television just
because he's weird doesn't mean he's an
alien what about his appearance there's
a reason why people are constantly
pointing out things about his looks like
why is his skin orange that's not a
normal human color people with spray
tans are the exact same color what about
his hair people make fun of his hair all
the time because it doesn't look like
normal human hair it looks like some
kind of wig he's old old people wear
wigs but it's not a wig and even if it
were out of all the wigs he could have
chose he picks that one that hair is not
a choice a normal human would make oh
people make fun of his hands being small
see he's not consistent with human
proportions either oh and he always
wears that big red friendship necklace
not too sure if that's one Shawn but the
hand thing that was good this is so
stupid
stupid what if Donald Trump's favorite
word's along with weak loser wrong smart
top bad huge yes for all aware of how
illiterate he is at his minuscule
vocabulary many school vocabulary it's
not like a school with like tiny books
oh for his tiny hands see I personally
think it's messed up that people like
you make fun of his basic English just
like making fun of an immigrant for
having an accent or speaking funny you
go try and learn a new alien language
and see if you can remember complex
difficult huge alien words you actually
think Donald Trump was an alien just
because he talks acts and looks a little
different I wish that's all I knew
Donald Trump was born in 1946 which is a
very important year for alien conspiracy
theories Speer C theorists you mean
crazies one year before all the activity
Roswell exactly Roswell one of the most
infamous alien incidents that's ever
been recorded in history but you know
what that's not the only one then right
right there two more in Washington that
same year Mount Rainier Mari island Wow
yeah that's right how do you know all
this but you don't know the word
miniscule well I went to a regular-sized
one you see alien sightings happen all
the time but these three cases were
singled out as some of the most
evidential cases of all time and they
all happened in 1947 a year after Donald
Trump was born first as we already know
Roswell New Mexico where a rancher found
actual physical evidence of a spacecraft
before eventually got covered up then
the Mount Rainier Washington incident
where our pilots saw actual UFOs while
he was flying in the sky only later to
find out that people on the ground
actually saw the same thing and finally
the Mauri Island incident where a sailor
couldn't they saw things but later
retracted their statement after a
mysterious man in a black suit
approached him and told him not to talk
about the incident eventually in this
specific incident actually inspired the
men in black movies to be made don't you
guys see a pattern here yes in 1947
people were very gullible nope that's
absolutely wrong Shawn there is a
pattern all the people who saw these
things they all saw them in 1947 the
same year well yeah well yes that's
that's true as well but there's there's
another pattern as well think about all
the people who made the sightings in
Roswell it was a rancher in Mount
Rainier it was a pilot and the Mariana
incident was a sailor it's earth air and
water like the Avatar what a rancher who
represents earth a pilot who represents
air and of course a sailor which
represents water but what about fire
isn't that a thing - well before Trump
started running for office what was his
most infamous phrase you're fired you're
fired
goodbye you're fired you're fired
Hillary you're fired he's a firebender
not just that Donald Trump is the avatar
are you kidding me is if this wasn't
stupid enough now you try to convince me
that Trump is based off of a cartoon not
at all see if the cartoon was based off
of him and what he represents oh yeah
what's that
world peace just like the show is based
off of earth air water fire they all
represent different nations all
different parts of the world long ago
all these parts live together in harmony
and then the Avatar disappeared and
conflicts began fights and battles
became normal Wars broke on and began to
become more and more dangerous from
World War one escalating all the way to
world war ii when the first atomic bomb
the deadliest weapon in existence was
used and then the war ended and there
hasn't been a world war or atomic bomb
use since and what year did all of this
end 1945 one year before Donald J Trump
was born hey why does he keep making
these funny years he's trying to imply
that Donald Trump wasn't born then
because he wasn't that's just the day
that he Donald Trump the alien avatar
came back and restored balance to the
world and although he has a lot to learn
before he can save anyone I believe that
Donald can save the world
this in your head you need to fix that
you need help both of you yes we all do
we and we have that help in Donald Trump
we are on the verge of another world war
and that's why Donald Trump finally
after all these years decided to run for
president to bring peace back to the
world people suspect and are currently
investigating Donald Trump for having
ties to Russia I believe he does and he
has since 1947 a year after his birth
right when the Cold War began thankfully
it was a war of ideas and not an actual
war all thanks to one year old Donald
Trump keeping the peace between the two
strongest nations in the world the time
the Soviet Union MB us that's his secret
tie with Russia so funny you your logic
can you hear yourself
yeah I'm not deaf you're saying Donald
Trump's goal in life is to connect the
world and provide a world peace I mean
he does own the Miss Universe pageant
and world peace is of pretty reoccurring
theme the same Donald Trump that is
obsessed with separating countries by
building gigantic wall
oh you mean great walls like the Great
Wall of China which if you haven't
noticed he's already trying to build
ties with China China China China China
China I get it regardless it's still a
wall and wall separating true but the
great wall is not just the wall it's
also a pathway and pathways connect
things
oh my God look I found it hard to
believe at first too that's why it took
me so long to make this video didn't why
now well obviously because the whole
news of the Olympics duh huh why it's
the Olympics they've recently announced
that in 2028 the Olympics are coming
back to the US so the Olympics are
literally made to bring peace and unity
between all the different nations of the
world it's the exact symbol of what
Trump wants and it's finally coming back
to the u.s. in 2028 again
so what oh my gosh do I actually have to
draw this out for you yes fine like I
said before the Olympics are gonna be
back in the US in 2028 the last time
they were in the US was in 1996 in
Atlanta if we lay out a continuous map
of the world and place out each of the
location in order starting from 1996 in
Atlanta to Sydney Australia in 2000
degrees in Oh Fort Riley no way London
in 2012 found to Brazil for the most
recent Olympics all the way back over to
Japan for the next Olympics in 2020 and
from there here's where it gets a little
tricky the 2024 Olympics haven't been
announced yet but we suspect it's gonna
be somewhere around Paris friends there
we head all the way back to the US for
the Olympics in 2028 and there you have
it if you take a step back and look at
it as a whole what do you see I don't
know intersecting lime triangles the
Illuminati Israel that's a different
video China
oh well what is it then what you see
here is exactly what you never see Trump
without a big red time the friendship
necklace once again groovy that just
like the Olympics just like the avatar
Donald Trump the alien is trying to tie
the entire world
[Music]
wedding storms hey actually I have one
last question yeah the only thing I
don't get is that if Trump is here for
all of these great things why does he
hide it from everyone that's the only
thing you don't get well see that's the
even greater truth about something no
one can find out because if they did
they realize he's an alien and they'd
freak out but he's a good alien he wants
to save and protect the world right now
but we are still human it's really
stupid stupid humans so even if Trump
were to tie and connect every single
nation and prevent every possible future
world war and world hunger poop gold
even if Trump were to actually achieve
actual world peace it wouldn't matter
what why well the greater truth is
Fuzzy's an alien an undocumented illegal
alien he's got to go home