hey guys so most of you guys know by now
but I'm never on time for trying clearly
as you could probably read the title but
this time I feel like we were way ahead
of the game like years ago if you guys
watch our identity series you guys know
what I'm talking about okay yeah it's
not quite the exact trend because you
know we didn't actually hammer it and
polish it but I'm Japanese so that's
like half the trend you know anyway for
those of you that don't know what I'm
talking about this trend is called the
Japanese air polish tinfoil ball or
something like that it's basically just
taking a bunch of foil and making a foil
ball and feeding it up until it becomes
shiny and spherical sphere sphere
Fiera cool but for the majority of you
you probably already have seen this
trend done like a thousand times I mean
just searching foil on YouTube you see
tons of these videos just like
everywhere a lot of them kind of click
Beatty I mean it can't all be the
largest world breaking ball in the world
I mean I'm not trying to throw straight
you guys seen the thumbnail have like a
perfectly shiny ball on the thumbnail
that looks like perfectly round and it's
mirror polish to the point that it is a
mirror then you watch the video in the
end product is nothing like that I mean
if I'm not mistaken that's what
clickbait is right you mean like what
you're doing right now what the ultimate
foil ball sounds pretty click baby to me
wait how did you know I was gonna name
it that it's right there and seriously
that thumbnail you're gonna make a foil
ball that's the size of a person that's
definitely click big what what's so hard
about it is you just make a ball out of
tinfoil right I do that every single
time I have leftover see anyone can make
an ordinary ball out of tinfoil to
create a perfect mirror polished
Japanese tin foil ball one must hold the
pasta tin foil ball okay honestly how
hard could that possibly be
yeah no I didn't even start it yet I
didn't really feel like doing it so I
kind of just been sitting here for a
week I'll probably get started in like
an hour or two so
[Music]
[Laughter]
open up a ball before you take a hammer
to until it's fall
wrap it up again and again and now you
got yourself a gold ball basically
that's always to when you idiot to get
this wrong don't know what else I can
say I didn't even need to make this song
mr. zall my
[Music]
to go away
the cost like a big break when they're
working
oh hey guys I'm finished with the song
now and now presenting the ultimate foil
ball I knew you were gonna make one as
big as the one in the thumbnail but come
on that was just sad oh this no this is
just for the swish to open the curtain
for the real foil ball what do you
really need that ball for that switch
and is that even a real lever yeah look
guys
[Music]
really it's the green ball no that
that's all foil when you compress tin
foil enough it kind of loses its
shininess and what happens is this green
tint well it's the green ball okay fine
I wrap the green ball in foil but this
this is real this is a lot of wheat I
know you could make one as big as the
thumbnail without baking it's not fake
then where is it huh where is this
ultimate tin foil ball right here I just
told you that is not ultimate that isn't
even close to the size of the one in the
thumbnail okay
what are you trying to say that I'm
trying to say that your title is
misleading and not only is your
thumbnail fake it's a straight-up eye so
you know what that makes you a cheesy
clickbait er see I know you're gonna
make one it makes the thumbnail without
making it it's not fake
well except for this one but the next
part coming up that's all real
[Music]
see pretty good thumbnail hi I told you
it wasn't fake but the title was still
misleading come on fine I'll admit it I
was wrong I know yes she made a real
ball even though it isn't as big as I
thought it would be and the contraption
was pretty cool so so what are you
trying to say this video wasn't
clickbait that's what I've been trying
to tell you from the start
see doesn't it feel nice to know that
see cuz when you compress tinfoil