I don't know about you guys but I have
the most awkward situations when I first
shake someone's hand maybe it's just me
maybe I'm just off now I couldn't be I'm
sure everyone has experienced an awkward
handshake before especially to all you
guys you know what I'm talking about
right every single group of friends has
different handshakes that they and I can
never remember which of my friends do
which type of henshin I've had a lot of
awkward handshakes in my life but
recently I just had one of the most
awkward handshakes I've ever experienced
before and it basically inspired me to
make this video there's really no way to
reenact how bad or awkward this was but
it kind of went like this so there I was
about to enter a house party with my
friend Derek but we'll call him Darrin
to protect his identity I'm not gonna
lie I was a little nervous because I
don't go to many parties where I don't
know anyone and these people were all
Derek's for dead Darren's friends we
entered the house and just like any
other party there was a lot of people
there instantly my heart started beating
faster and faster knowing what was
coming next that's when the guy throwing
the party came over to greet Devin and
myself I watched as he went over to
Dennis and gave him the classic
handshake to hug flawlessly and that's
when it happened
don't have been pointed to me and said
the worst that would lead to my
inevitable day and as he turned to me I
had to make a decision what handshake
should I give him I know for a fact that
he does the handshake to hug me because
I just saw him do it to Dexter but he
also lives in a relative in this house
which means he's probably some kind of
businessman that there's a lot of
business handshakes but this was a
business this was a house party with his
buddies so maybe he just wants to pound
it yeah that's what he wants
hey what's up mask yeah that's when I
realized I had to get out of here with
or without Darrin either that or what I
have to kill every single person that
wins the Darrin and that's when I
realized I was narrating all out okay so
maybe I exaggerated that just a tad
that's that that's not what happened but
the situation was pretty awkward and I
probably won't be hanging out with those
guys anymore I'm tired of always having
awkward handshakes with people there are
so many different handshakes in the
world and I believe the more handshakes
you know the more prepared you'll be
when it happens and after countless
hours of research and lab tests and
googling I created the ultimate
handshake that will help you in any
situation no matter how awkward but
Before we jump into that you have to
learn all the basics the single grip the
double grip the pounded the fist bump
the pound it - fist bump the pounded -
fist bump - explosion the cup the
chicken fight the cup - chicken fight
the cup - chicken fight - Emily rolls
the handshake - hug
the handshake - snap the high five the
high ten the high six the double hit the
too much strength handshake the drug
dealer
the handshake handshake the no hand
handshake the cross-arm the French
handshake the cheers the foot handshake
the Linsanity
the et that I just washed my hands and
she walk to remember handshake The Fresh
Prince of bel-air handshake the Hey
Arnold how to be gangster handshake the
pigeon the turtle hey the spider the
jellyfish hanji the what up dog
hey what up dog the hand hug the sports
handshake
the Batman handshake why are you mocking
my handshake style the beats by dre
handshake maybe I'm going deaf maybe I'm
out of my mom
hower foe heroes teaming up handshake
the jutsu handshake the fingerless hand
shake the finger leek handshake to wave
the finger lease handshake to wave to
wave handshake and this and last but not
least the ultimate handshake in order to
perform this handshake you're gonna need
a friend who knows it as well right now
you should be comfortable with every
hand she but in order to perform this
handshake not only are you gonna need
everything you learned so far but you're
gonna need to prep like this
[Music]
and once you're prepped and ready to go
you can finally perform the ultimate
handshake hey man thanks for coming to
my party bro on has ever gotten everyone
to participate in such a poorly spoof
song before Amen just what I do
[Music]
so I guess I'll see you guys later or
there you go in their log Shawn I don't
know what just talk to the camera like
it's me hi hey guys I'm Ryan Higa I'll
take that
[Applause]
yeah