dear right you do parkour here right you
do parkour here Ryan do parkour Ryan
Parker on parkour Kumar Clark so this is
probably no definitely the most common D
Ryan that I get all the time every
single time I posted your ID video and
I've actually done things kind of
similar to parkour but I've never
actually really done it because well I I
just I don't know how to do it
III can't do parkour ever since I was a
little kid I've always dreamt that I
would one day learn parkour but you know
no matter how many times I tried over
and over and over again I just just
could never seem to get it you know I
remember this one obstacle in particular
this dinosaur in the middle of the park
was you know the hardest thing I've ever
had to do and I could just never figure
it out I could never get over it I could
never learn parkour if I could not
defeat this dinosaur I always thought
one day I would I never did and just
made me realize that you know it doesn't
matter how much you want something it
doesn't matter how hard you try some
dreams some dreams just don't come true
you know what no forget everything I
said earlier if you have a dream you
chase after it as impossible as it may
seem even if it seems like it's a it'll
take a miracle to get it done miracles
aren't possible at one point it was
considered a miracle that electricity
was possible or America without we could
travel through space even the idea of
the Internet was a miracle and yet we
still accomplished all those because
there's nothing in this world that's
impossible till you believe it is so
never give up on your dreams because
there's no obstacle that you can
overcome make a miracle happen defeat
your dinosaur
so thank you guys so much for watching
if you want to see how long this video
took to make and all the tedious things
that we have to do in order to make it
click the one on the left and watch blue
bridging behind the scenes if you want
to see the previous video click the one
on the right and once again thank you so
much to everybody that watched it's not
just this video but the entire 2014 year
really looking forward to making some
weird stuff for you guys next year so I
guess we'll see you guys in 2015 have a
wonderful holidays and a Happy New Year