from the makers of the iPod even we know
percent yeah I never gave you where to
go we need to be somewhere good lot to
get there is no here ya go right in
three point three miles batteries who
needs some plugins cut up ye died a
pewter is some food
yeah happens in many different styles
such as mail go left
female may left taster yo dog you best
me cry ninja your dog your best makeup
emo and that's just a home on comedy
yeah that's alright it's your the driver
and even your favorite kpop some jump
some might and way John head you say
y'all you don't believe us everyone
check out our sets like cover turn left
at turn left at recalculating make first
legal u-turn at recalculating
what's a right in 500 feet 400 feet 800
feet what time I left at next right turn
so that isn't even Mexican one for 3.2
sandwiches Park in reverse while going
forward what's your destination is
approaching on the left in point five oh
thank you of ears what what the other
sensors all cursing hey mother fleet to
see me
I'm feed the road right now you pieces
be I'm gonna be you better eat go
alright now come on
EEP EEP EEP you chop your feet and off
your piece of sheep will you stop with
those peeps
okay recalculating mother be it's too
late too late