dear Ryan can you do a third installment
for things that ruin Thanksgiving my
story began like any other a wonderful
life playing in the Sun with a lovely
wife and a beautiful son it was the best
time of the year when the leaves fall by
the lot everything was perfect the cages
were lonely
despite the others everyone kept to
themselves because no one knew who was
going to be next
all we knew for sure was when the leaves
fall we all fall
what do we have here couple of chicken
Jonathas Chinese Turkish
and at that very moment had but one
choice to make
freedom or revenge
well Elway how did you fit in there what
do we have
so leave your question in the comments
below and you could be responsible for
the next video