things that ruin Thanksgiving look mom
dad before you meet Mary yes what is it
son I think she might be pregnant with
emotions right now because she's been
looking forward to meeting you guys for
a long time so please be nice and also
we're having a child ish fight right now
pretty much about nothing just that well
she's having my baby oh brother
pick her up right now you know your
other son oh because I was here helping
you guys set up I couldn't get her and
she can't try because well she's growing
a fetus right huh you know fetus isn't
feet fungus like is this terrible feet
fungus that a lesson Amin please just
can't take this anymore please just
bring her in oh yeah sure oh don't worry
she's just fat
all right who's ready for Thanksgiving
dinner babe giving thanks Santa Claus
and presents and so I'm from the UK so
we do have Nash see anything us things
are ruin Thanksgiving what's wrong right
what are you not hungry
oh excuse me sir you haven't have any
food on you
no sorry I mean I am I just I can't eat
until I make things right
[Music]
look man sorry about earlier today I you
asked me if I had food on me I said no
but I I really did have food on me and
I'm sorry I should have never lied to
you and well
you probably need this more than I do so
[Music]
things that ruin Thanksgiving hi who's
ready for some Thanksgiving football man
[Applause]
they're not supposed to be caring to
both their hands but sorry still from
the UK it's not real football things are
ruin Thanksgiving oh hey Ryan did you
get the yams yams oh yeah I thought you
said jam no but we could use some gems
for the biscuits your mother's baby come
on tell me it does not look like this
kinda right look that even has the
little details like it's like parts we
get caves in like this I was like push
hard you release you push hard again
like you know you see the sea though you
know no the corn all right I'll keep
working on things that ruin Thanksgiving
oh hey Ryan did it get the yams yams oh
yeah I thought you said have actually we
could use some ham so that our bad radio
things are ruined Thanksgiving okay uh
before we get started
mom dad yes what is it son come on tell
them we have some wonderful news
Oh Liz and I we're having a baby
what I thought you guys would be happy
for us that is your sister things that
ruin Thanksgiving oh hey Ryan did it get
the yams yams oh yeah I thought you said
can it you actually did it
you picked up the can of yams yams no
these are the new jams in a can by
Yamaha things are ruined Thanksgiving
[Music]
dad scared now don't worry son
if one of us gets chosen it's a good
thing it means you're special dad lost
your mom you got chosen him we haven't
seen her since because now our wings
really work and she flew away and if you
get chosen well you would just be flying
with her - I could really fly
what do we have here couple of chicken
enjoy nervous Chinese Turkey
no please turkey Franks oh no please son
it's okay take me instead
take me instead that's right you could
be with mommy
[Music]
things are good Thanksgiving
hi I'm Ryan Higa we make a lot of jokes
here at the Ryan Higa production company
but the one thing we don't joke about
killing turkeys that is killing turkeys
we don't joke about that so this
Thanksgiving do the right thing and
remember turkeys are humans too so from
all of us at rhpc and speaking on behalf
of all the turkeys all over the world
thank you
gobble gobble gobble s
[Music]
Oh oh no this is this is not a turkey
this is just a chicken it just looks
like one because it's really fat chicken
chicken come back here you know I didn't
mean it like that
well if you're gonna go can you at least
pick up more jams in the can we're about
to run out
well we will thank you guys so much for
watching if you want to see bloopers and
behind the scenes click the one on the
right if you want less waste video click
the one that laughs and if not then
we'll