things of ruin Thanksgiving hey guys the
food's getting cold dinner's ready
yeah things are good Thanksgiving thank
you for this food at our table we thank
you for everyone sitting around this
table and we'd like to thank you for
your welcome thinks I ruined
Thanksgiving you know isn't it funny
this one meal could feed a whole village
in China thinks a ruined Thanksgiving
thanks and ruin Thanksgiving it's almost
my dishes things of you and Thanksgiving
oh thanks a good Thanksgiving dad huh
I'm gay thinks I ruined Thanksgiving oh
hey Ryan did you get yams
yes oh yeah I love you said ironing
board thinks I ruined Thanksgiving dad
dad I'm straight oh thanks and ruin
Thanksgiving
thanks everyone Thanksgiving dad hi mom
Oh things are good Thanksgiving so bad
names the foster jobs so there won't be
any Thanksgiving food this year no food
how could it be no food it's
Thanksgiving we'll also you're adopted
what oh oh that can't be true oh it's
okay we're getting a divorce anyway
there's nothing makes sense what why
you're saying is what you know what
let's just go enjoy the day and watch
some good old-fashioned Thanksgiving
football
you guys look and watch football how am
I supposed to enjoy this
when all this is happening here watching
it silly your claim what thanks Andrew
and thanks good so adjusting for my
Thanksgiving video what so what you guys
we got my Thanksgiving video on
Thanksgiving sounds fun
oh no it's our house to like okay let's
just go enjoy the day and watch some
good ole Thanksgiving that's got cool
fashion things people calling right now
just really dumb idea what let's do it
spotty to what
ha