I've wrestled people who smell like [ __ ]
like literal like poop the last two
years like two years ago we did decent I
don't know maybe like 150 K for the year
and then last year we did like 250 K are
you having class please do that for
claps yeah yeah I guess that makes sense
that we usually yeah I mean it is a
weird thing even when we first put it on
we're like all hearing yourself is such
a weird you know like you take it but
you're not you do it haunting yourself
or like listening to your division it's
different when it's alive - yeah I guess
so and especially it's worse if there's
a little bit of a delay this is the
longest intro we've ever did I did not
intro welcome back to the Pihl podcast
today we are joined with our very close
friend mr. Jacob foo popular in the
moderator seat as well that's all you
get you need to earn your class for
those of you who don't know Jacob foo is
the brother of Josh foo Josh was with us
for a little bit yeah and we have Josh
Josh is move back to Atlanta where you
guys are from right yep sorry we make
these kind of jokes usually off-camera
and we have Ryan Higa in the modern host
seat sorry all right you can host it no
I want to do that I want to play with
one day we should switch I'm down all
right
sorry so Jake you sure this is about
Jacob you should see the seats right now
I don't want to
after the shishi break yeah this is
Jacob tell more about your relationship
well let's talk about just I guess we
can talk about just you can explain
actually what you do yeah talk about how
we met and stuff we'll get into that
later buildable Jacob yeah but it built
you telling your relationship builds
this Jake okay
s-sir and is there's my wife we moved
back to Vegas in February so we live
here now we're on a travel blog
full-time and for the past six years
we've been moving to a new city every
year to write about the city
um the surrounding area nomads nomads
it's kind of this one a nomad is right
somebody who doesn't have a like yeah
yeah this is long as they please for a
while you guys are gypsies yeah yep
basically and he's pretty humble but
their blog is like one of the biggest
right travel vlogs
yeah it's if not the biggest travel blog
not the biggest but it's it's the
biggest travel what's up there yes it is
Vegas yeah I'm just saying it's the
local adventurer local adventurer I
don't normally read blogs but like like
you were saying cuz I was asking we were
talking about this beforehand yeah I
thought your fan base was just like like
a really small dedicated not small but
very dedicated fan base but you were
saying that a lot of times it's it's
just people constantly coming in and
checking all random articles and yeah I
mean I think it's partly because of the
way we built the blog when Esther
started it it was primarily because she
couldn't find the information that she
wanted uh-huh so she's neither of us are
like we're not great writers we don't
really like writing like stories per se
but we like to find information and give
that information to people so that's
kind of how the site was built and so I
think it's more of a resource than it is
like people following our personal lives
right yeah what's so funny all right
Jacob we're cool right yeah all right
you know if I throw out some some small
burns here and there then what do you do
just just keep moving on keep moving
yeah yeah no I don't know I had last
time with the Kevin thing there's a lot
of people were like I don't like that
punk was going after Kevin like that
they're probably not gonna defend me as
much it'll probably make the don't think
you're you're a jerk or dick or whatever
it sounds funny I think it was pretty
apparent that you guys really yeah but
there's some people who are dumb I think
you just just get very
offended but not I just get surprised
that there are people that you get wrong
you're pretty sensitive I'm not I'm
hardest look at this body
dude ah I went to gym once this week
with that being said I guess we're
jumping back into I don't remember cuz
you know poor it laughing yeah they're
right I met Jacob and I met you I met
Jacob on internet icon
yeah sure that we did that was basically
like American Idol but for Hubert yeah
yeah I guess yeah at the time especially
and that's where I met Paco as well but
the following season we only did two
seasons and and and J and Jacob was a
finalist with his brother no he well I
wasn't a final what did you get I got
fourth but we both got eliminated
basically on the same episode right
before the finals kiss season 2 had
three finalists yeah yeah I don't
remember if I voted to get rid of you
guys or not yeah I don't remember I
don't know I think it was Kassim it
might it might be I don't think he liked
us I think he liked Lana and the right
elves were kind of a shoo-in right elves
were killing it yeah the rhinos were
shooting so it was between us and Lana
and I think he just like Lana better
PewDiePie didn't like me because he's a
racist and and he just hates me
now that's we're gonna screen cap that
put that in the intro hey we got you
know what you're I didn't want to be on
this podcast so we're gonna cause drama
for um say didn't want to be on it no he
did actually he responded to the tweets
what tweets wait up he just straight up
said no thanks well he was kind of like
what he said is he doesn't want to be on
podcast because we asked him to be on
the podcast
see now now you're revealing who runs
the Twitter I know I'm not revealing
it's not me but you're narrowing it down
it's pretty obvious that it's not me
writing the Twitter I get that I see it
after the fact when it gets narrowed
down to oh these are good questions for
so-and-so
yeah but basically the the whoever is
handling the Twitter was like oh yeah
would you like to be on the podcast and
eat on one of his videos
he saw it and basically like roasted it
was like wow you're pretty much saying
that your fans want me to be on the
podcast but not you
it is just like damn that's very true
and also he was like he doesn't want to
do a podcast because like media will
take things and like twist it in a way
and you know he just don't want to be
responsible he just gets done by yeah
yeah exactly so that's why he's like I
don't wanna do it he has to be very
careful with what he says which is very
understandable
people always yeah that's how I argue
that's how we were an internet icon we
and like Josh and I had this
conversation before you guys started
filming like they can take anything we
say and twist it yep we should just make
sure we're always super nice but then we
got cut out of everything because that's
how reality shows work but don't realize
like even the most realistic ones it's
there's no real reality show oh yeah
other than being like I mean like
YouTube like vlogging and then even then
you don't know for sure that it's being
like a hundred percent real you don't
know what they're cutting you don't know
if they're acting but most reality shows
it's like unless you're crazy or you
know that's usually how they get you
that that's how you get screen time yep
but I'm gonna cause drama
yeah I've witnessed that when we were
filming that show I wouldn't stat
firsthand I was like oh this is so
interesting because we had producers and
stuff and directors that have done this
before and I was just like so interested
in like their their discussions is like
how can we throw a wrench into like
things are going too well for people how
can we throw a wrench into I was like
wow that so this is how it works this is
interested they specifically talk crap
about anybody um I don't remember it was
probably the earlier episodes because
search the ending it was like the people
that were great for the show and that
we're good you know it wasn't like fan
voting because that would have been too
costly to have to have live fat boats
yeah figuring that stuff out so it was
based on like the judges and none of
that was fake like we actually came to a
consensus but then they would have a say
- they they would give their
recommendations like this guy is like so
not good on camera or this person is a
you know really good yeah
so what was your impression on of Paco I
was the one I was on like to him
initially you know because I didn't
really know him yeah I I'm editing this
so I can just cut it you could write
that boy you could I could just watch
put it back I mean I mean I liked them
they were you guys were on the show so
obviously I liked you guys actually no
you guys did really well yeah to a guest
I mean what not it would do really well
yeah so I mean you're currently still
doing this blog it's very successful I
saw yeah I found this so interesting
because I want to go check it out
because obviously I wanted to do some
research you know really read blogs but
I find it really interesting that you
posted you guys post your earnings we do
this past month
you made $21,000 well a little more than
that off just doing that blog have
sponsorships and they show their whole
breakdown they show your costs I think
and I thought that was like that's
fascinating for one like why did you
decide to to show that because it's very
private thing and then also how are not
the easiest thing to get around you know
I mean like it's very specific also are
you hiring yeah but usually people you
know it's funny it's like we make these
same jokes
yeah but then like when guests make it
it's like well it's all adding up it's
very hard future employer
I'd watch this go ahead we're looking
for like you know the Gregg quality like
yeah so we we were really it took us it
was a lot of debate over sharing our
income reports every month but I think
the idea was we wanted to show other
aspiring bloggers how we do what we do
right and so it was supposed to be a
resource yeah it's a really private
thing and we don't want to post it to be
like bragging about anything didn't come
across anything that sort is really to
show because I think there's a we get
the question a lot like
how are you guys doing this full-time or
what are you and I'm sure you get that
question as like a youtuber like anymore
yeah I guess it's more common back in
the day when I can make money all the
time for blogs it's still pretty a
mystery you know
yeah so it's uh we we posted it up just
really for that reason to show people it
can be done because I really believe
that people can do what they want and
chase their dreams in like a responsible
way that's a very nice thing to say
yeah but you know what though I mean I I
found cuz I read I read that one and I
was interesting cuz you or I don't know
a faster wrote it but you were talking
about like initially so when did you
guys I guess what I'm asking is when did
you start and then how did it okay
because initially you she said you would
you made like 50 bucks in a month we
made them wants nothing at the beginning
and primarily because we didn't know how
to make money right so Esther started
the blog actually when we moved to LA to
do YouTube so Esther was doing was at
2013 okay relatively recent yeah so she
started too then because we she had a
wedding photography business before that
and we left Atlanta she was looking for
something new to do and just started to
post about our travels because we just
like to travel and then she realized
that people were doing this full-time
and so started doing some research of
like okay how do I do this more
strategically and be smart about it and
so started to build that up and then
when we moved to Vegas the first time
that's when like there's they're good
like just a little snowball effect right
like there was there are more people
finding the blog it was getting a bigger
audience and she's amazing on the
backend creative side but needed help on
the business side so that's when I see
you YouTube and then decided to help oh
so when that was going that was like
what what year was money for remembering
yeah 2014 20 did you guys just we're
just leaving Vegas yeah yeah we when
Josh stayed right so what at what I mean
if it's not to person I guess it's not
personal you're posting about it yeah in
that first when you that first month
when you decided to stop doing YouTube
what was your income at that point
honestly I don't remember then
it was definitely not enough to be
sustainable right but that's why it's
interesting because to take that leap ya
know to go in a completely different
direction in something that's not making
anything really we saw I think it's just
that I saw the potential and we so this
is the same with YouTube we we didn't
make a crazy amount of money but we made
enough to make a living off of it right
for two years especially if you live in
Vegas yes Vegas is so much cheaper
Atlanta the same it's about the same
yeah yeah
California is way too expensive yeah but
we gave ourselves a year initially when
we moved to LA to say like if we can
make enough money to make a living then
we'll try again for another year and
then we came out to Vegas to do the same
thing and we weren't really seeing the
growth that we wanted to so that's what
I'm talking about like it's good to
chase your dreams but be realistic about
it because we basically give ourselves
the time frame of like okay we have
enough savings to pursue it for a year
beyond that you know it's not really
responsible for us to do it anymore
we talked about a very similar thing to
before in the past about like I think
what the question was like aspiring to
be a youtuber yeah oh yeah yeah oh it's
like the same thing we were saying like
we don't want to be the people it ended
up sounding like don't follow your
dreams but it was like the point of like
be smart about it
and no like you have to weigh out the
risk like if I had quit YouTube yeah
right and when I was in college and at
the time we weren't getting paid really
then you have to realize my mom made me
realize like hey all your friends will
be graduated I mean you have to come
back and be with a bunch of kids ya know
so it's like you weigh out the positives
and negatives so for you guys like did
you have a fallback plan um so I think
we've just always had the mentality that
worst case scenario we can go back and
get regular jobs right you know when it
comes down to it I don't have an issue
getting back to I used to work a
corporate job I can go back to a
corporate job if I need to so in the
blog when I when I end up quitting and
helping Esther where the blog we still
had you know we calculated we had enough
savings to do like a year and a half two
years of like living conservatively to
see if we can make it happen and then
that was about when it broke for us like
the tipping point of it
doing well so the last two years like
two years ago we did decent I don't know
maybe like 150 K for the year and then
last year we did like 250 K so we were
able to grow and scale the business and
then in terms of how it's just I think
it's like YouTube in terms of it it's a
numbers game
so for us we have a decent amount of
people visiting the site every month so
we're able to make money off ad revenue
but then we also do sponsorships and
then like a small percentage off
affiliate sales so that's like if you
were if we tell you hey we bought ninja
milk on Amazon and give you our link and
Paco goes to buy it it's still the same
price for Paco but we make a small
percentage of that right because you're
still bringing people to this thing and
and you're putting your stamp on it
yes entually and your stamp is valuable
now so I was wondering about that
because what if have you ever have you
ever endorsed anything or about a place
that you did not a hundred percent like
let's say you did oh completely loved it
especially at the beginning oh really
yeah because at the beginning when when
you it's like I bet you can remember
like brand deals early on definitely
where you're just excited for the first
brand deal I think the biggest regret we
had was Bud Light Lime really good yeah
we got that and we're like we hadn't
even tried it we tried it work this is
disgusting I put my Bud Light Lime
really I just you know I wouldn't drink
a lot of it yeah I mean like I don't
mind it I hated it like we but like for
me it's like I also signed a contract so
I was gonna be professional about yeah
I'm gonna do it I don't think we wrote
raving reviews about it but we also
didn't say we did it right you know
here's a new thing yeah exactly
what didn't you like I think I wouldn't
know if I was reading I was like oh yeah
I'm sure you know yeah I'm sure if you
go back I think it's still on our site
you could probably tell that we didn't
like it really but yeah I think it's
like lessons learned you know we learned
okay we shouldn't endorse products that
we don't like because it just ruins the
integrity exactly yeah I had to learn
that too
yeah the hard way but I mean it was even
more so
like back in the day on YouTube we're
laying in view even if it was a product
you liked what just did hated you yeah
any brand deals like all of this Ron
used to be so genuine and so like he
wasn't a cell and then the moment you do
something that you even even if it's a
product you like it's like you're a
sellout
it's different now though people are
more open to it yeah we didn't have any
ad reads today but thanks to ninja milk
for sponsoring this happens is are a lot
more open today you still kind of
refrain from doing a lot of brand deals
and you do have opportunity for the
podcast we do some we do it oh yeah
there that we're very selective with it
so I think this is very interesting
because you come from a place where like
you said your ad revenues really does
really well but brand deals I'm sure
that's like a huge end that it is a lot
with staring or tea ryan is more like
Adsense or whatever you get I mean I
should be doing more brand deals usually
I'm just it's different when like for
like the podcasts like this is it's a
lot easier cuz it's just you know you do
a read and if it's something that like
oh yeah I could use that or I used it
it's super easy yeah because we're just
talking about but if it's like oh make
up like a trailer like one of those like
fake trailers around this product or
something and it doesn't if it's not
funny or like cool or interesting and
that's not a easy thing to do without a
product if you throw a product in there
it just kind of ruins it yeah you know I
think there's a difference though the
type of content you're building is very
different it's not yeah vlog II or just
challenge videos that you could just
throw the product into right you're
doing like fully scripted stuff yeah so
a second channel view is obvious
yeah like play game or like do whatever
but yeah making a whole skit around the
product is not that easy so you get a
lot of crap for that - well this is a
dope-ass video like fortnight yeah what
that one wasn't like fortnight came to
me I had the idea and I went to
fortnight and let's talk about that I
guess because there are a lot of brands
that go to you but you know you you kind
of don't you rarely ever like I put a
second thought into it at first you had
to reach out for brands but now brands
are coming out to you
still mix but yeah yeah for sure and how
did you start that off because you know
like being like oh check out our blog is
very like legitimate and everything yeah
out to the car yes so I mean my
background is in sales and account
managing so I kind of knew how to do
that already but it was essentially of
putting together like a media kit or
putting together like a basic deck of
your numbers and then just reaching out
and saying this is what we want to do
and this is why you should work with us
so you're saying you make a deck for
every single sponsor know that you make
like a generalize yeah yeah yeah then
you pitch with your deck you send it to
the company or the place you want to go
to see if yeah it's some kind of sponsor
right mm-hmm and ask them a rate yeah
interesting
so for bloggers out there who want to
make their own blogs I mean you they
should really just check all your blog
because that's what you guys talk about
right and yeah I actually built a holy
course on teaching how to do the brand
stuff I'm gonna it's uh you would have
to do a blog you gotta write a lot no
I'm not gonna do it but there's a way
that you can apply it what would I put
the course together for is geared
towards bloggers but all the skills are
usable for anything that you do hmm that
you're trying to sell yourself or like
for branding your brand is that yeah
it's on how to how to how to pitch and
negotiate yes like this is applicable to
like any form of social media yeah
Instagram YouTube twitch whatever you
know I think there's like some things
you have to tweak but for the most part
it's all skills that you can use
anywhere see I think that's interesting
because that if people can learn to do
that or like do it on their own you
don't have to go to these other like
come like these people these networks
that are trying to sorry I know you just
I just joined an MCN yeah yeah a lot of
that is stuff that people can be doing
on their own yeah not necessary if they
don't have the time but I'm saying
that's all they do basically a lot of
what you're what you guys are doing on
your own exactly you could easily just
you know join somebody to help do that
for you or I mean eventually if you're
making up
you can hire someone to do it for you if
yeah I want to do it anymore I mean we
we use the same thing for us in YouTube
we were part of an MCN but we pitched
ourselves a lot mm-hmm - and I think
that's part of the allow that though
don't they take a percentage regardless
uh it depends on your contract right I
think it's changed now now like the
contract that I did I made sure that if
I found my own see people didn't know
that before though yeah yeah like a lot
of people got screwed and I mean it goes
with the whole like the whole phase
thing that's happening right now right
like isn't that their whole situation
about like the contract that he signed
it wasn't a good contract yeah what's
his name T foo Sifu
yeah his his contract I mean they just
released it today what it was and it's
not a good contract and they even
admitted it but like everyone back in
the day was just signing this is how you
get successful we'll help you out but
you give away so much and people just
it's not their fault you're not lawyers
you know a lot of people just get
excited and see opportunity and they see
their people they're fans of they how
big they got and you just jump into it
and I would say as a warning just I
always tell people because they asked
like oh sure way sign with this this is
what they're offering me just read the
contract yeah and I mean I got on
yourself too I think that's the thing
like most people think contracts are
very overwhelming they are they can be
they can be but I think it's a lot more
common sense than you think to like you
can just read some of the basic stuff
that like I don't understand all the
legal mumbo-jumbo but there's some
things that are like ownership of
content you know like some really basic
stuff that should be red flags if you
see it or just ask what ya mean yeah
exactly
there's a lot of times I ask about stuff
C but what they do is and then think you
guys think about this - you're not a 18
year old kid yes
you're not like in your teens or you're
not even in your 20s you know and and
imagine if you're that young someone's
coming at you with this you know do you
can be a part of someone so made million
million dollars this year he works under
our label or under our MCN this could be
you you know help you get those
partnerships we can they pull all these
flashy things out there and then you
just start signing people sure so it
makes sense and sometimes they do help
but a lot of times I know a lot of
people who like they are off they get
screwed yeah
yeah it's just a numbers game yeah I
don't know how we got in this topic
again well I mean work cuz we were
talking about brands and how he kind of
initially started right yeah he was
finding it for himself and then you
talked about how MC ends you know kind
of kind of took advantage of it in the
early stages of YouTube yeah I don't
know how that is now I don't know yeah I
think people are smarter but this is
such it was just a interesting thing
because that that whole phase thing was
happening yeah I don't know if you know
more about it you're the you're the up
to date guy well I mean there's not much
more to discuss I mean they are
releasing the contracts there's already
been a lot of videos about it is he
still suing then uh he as of this moment
he still is but he asked his lawyer to
kind of like retract a lot of the
statements for yeah and then even banks
is like yo like you live down the street
from me why don't we just talk like
we're gonna just talk in person I feel
like in social media now a lot of people
feel like if they're the first to out
someone yeah the whole internet just
jumps on their side yeah because of the
whole like canceled culture and stuff
yeah but I mean you could easily avoid
these things by talking about it in
person but if you want the numbers if
you want money you come out you just say
any any random thing and then everyone's
like what what what and you just get a
hell of views well you know what you
don't be even crazier like super crazy
is if this whole phase thing was planned
and it's just a phase what if they just
planned this together like hey we don't
have dropped we haven't had good drama
lately yeah like just all PR they're
gonna pretend to sue us we're gonna make
a ton of money I mean I'm not us I'm not
accusing them of doing this but they
could easily do that yeah look at
whenever there's something big about a
celebrity it's like Oh guess who's
albums coming out next week you're like
in like where they just announced you
know like that stuff happens all the
time
so I wouldn't hire people make sense
that does make sense
damn we win is that why you do so much
random stuff why just to be like
relevant all the time no maybe I should
stop doing random stuff yeah you got a
baby shoes now we didn't actually do the
random things back
I don't like the way you said it you
know it sounded very negative still
you're just like I'll keep them quiet
and then what it does something still be
disappointed let's not do that
I love when we have guests that actually
know us they always end up roasting you
so people can see like what the real
relations like it's starting to fill it
up yeah you're let's say this for the
the audience that doesn't understand and
know our relationship with a lot of
people like some people would think like
I'm I'm a douchebag Ryan's a douchebag
or like is lighting yeah it's never a
real argument like I know that we have
real arguments well yeah but it's not
like we hate each other the other day
somebody tweeted it Ryan
this clip of me and Ryan wrestling yeah
yeah and they're like when is this fight
gonna happen again
and Ryan responded
he's like whenever Paco wants it it I
was like yeah I said when yeah whenever
Paco wants to fighting him basically
yeah whoo yeah but I would not fight him
what didn't you want to jam yeah you
don't and I said yeah until you wash
them no I'm gonna come in as dirty as
possible yeah then I don't want this and
yeah or any of it strategy exactly every
advantage you're actually for wrestling
did you ever like not brush your teeth
the day of a meet or like nobody I've
wrestled people who smelt like [ __ ] like
literal like poop and you think they
literally well the thing is - it's you
never know because wrestling is such a
like a intense sport - like in that day
it's not like even like MMA we're like
the weigh-in yeah day before right and
then they're just like they rehydrate
they we eat like it in the weigh-in room
that morning you're you're like 20
pounds less than you should be no waters
in your system you know when you have no
water and your dehydrator you know what
your breath smells like yeah it that
like morning breath times a hundred so
everyone has that in the room plus you
don't care how you smell because you're
starving and you're thirsty so I mean it
there's no excuse for not shower you can
still shower when your own
you still shower I don't know but
somebody will really smell sounds like
people don't wipe by their yeah
there's there's been some people I feel
like I don't know maybe they're trying
to I mean you see that as a strategy
kind of cuz I mean he's already hard to
function and breathe yeah I imagine a
smell there yeah you know you're trying
to choke him there are smell although
that like because they smell I would get
upset and it would make me wrestle even
harder it's like because normally I'm
very caught like even when I wrestled it
was like I was very calm yeah a lot like
people who some people would use anger
and emotion I never really got like use
my emotion like I'm the only times ever
got mad I have it on video too actually
and Shaun can attest his - cause he was
there it was somebody like I had like a
wrapped finger cuz I was injured and
some guy tried to grab it and as I can
like the fight like AB regionals or
something like that and you could see
and he was grabbing I was like shaking
his hand off and I just got pissed and I
just destroyed him because like that I
don't like you like who does that like
you haven't he really going hurt me like
you're already at him advantage so I
don't know I think the smelly thing to
some I know it's not their fault but
sometimes when you smell something
that's that bad it's like come on dude
yeah but you could tell the difference
between body odor and poop yeah but this
is was gonna say I think you don't
realize when you're that desperate to
lose weight some people you take
diuretics laxatives like maybe he
actually did she himself at home yeah
and it was just like man I just got to
get out of here I gotta win or lose I do
feel like this setup is like two against
one
for what it's literally us always like
that but even on film days it's like
everyone against me yeah I mean you kind
of set yourself up for we don't have to
get into roast me this way we've done
this too many episodes it's gonna know
we need a break and then we'll roast you
again yeah talking about breaks it's
time for I already been mm-hmm really
yeah that's fast alright I guess then
xishi break I guess
[Music]
and we're back welcome back to the
second half of off the bail podcast um
yeah you guys should do a whole episode
just like that that's all um and so um
NPR NPR talks and it's something about
it that's really nice I think it's this
Claud this ASMR it's basically a Samar
though for like ER yes PR it is ASMR kit
is only talking considering as Noir -
yeah I think they talk like that English
chargers weird sound anything a trigger
do you think that triggers do you get
that thing cuz I try oh I don't get it
at all either
Wow no I don't get it
at lunch today though I wanted to I had
an idea to start an ASMR where I just
drink drinks I don't know if that exists
should be you literally we just so
happened to be talking by and you
literally had that I had that thought
yeah at lunch today things add up then
there's something about so you know I
was thinking about - I was resisting see
I recently saw Joe Rogan his podcast and
they were talking about you know
psychics and like he mean obviously real
there's there's a debate whether they're
real nuttin right some people really
believe in it so I'm really don't Joe
Rogan the stance is like they're all bs
pretty much but then they were talking
about and it made me wonder - you know
how when you like think about somebody
calling you or like not not somebody
calling somebody you think about
somebody and then they call you or
laughs yeah that that happens to you
guys right never happened to me you
never like thought about something
they'd text you all of a sudden know so
here's my thing ever - no that's
happened to me but I think what it is
though is that you just only notice
those yeah like you're always thinking
about like something or someone and it
just happened that that a lot yeah yeah
it's very coincidental
yeah and it's but there's a lot of
really like like it happens to me a lot
like very very frequent
and maybe it's just because and it's
like random people like people the only
time maybe the only time I notice it is
when I'm thinking of someone that I
shouldn't like you haven't talked to you
after today and then I don't mind my
mind is it oh I'm psychic my mind goes
to like the hut how did it they're
listening to me or like they're like
like yeah I guess this I get like
suspicious I'm a very I guess I guess
I'm paranoid everyone just has has bugs
in your house yeah I don't know I just
my first thought though I started
thinking conspiracy I bet you if we were
to take DNA test we probably have
Chinese in us I mean I think more sure
would yes as I'm okay Tommy will do
right yeah I think all these is just
like kind of a mix ya know yeah well I'm
gonna start claiming it when they take
over the world and then I'm just gonna
um I'm also a part you know you're just
sitting on the fence for now yeah for
now I mean I mean I just never took the
test but I'm sure if I did have you
taken the test yet
I've taken the MyHeritage one not the
not the what's the more popular one is
23 23andme my hair to join honestly was
pretty garbage like it was I mean it
gave me my results and was like you're
Asian
your that's how they break it down 98%
Chinese or Vietnamese like it wasn't I
would think you'd get more of a
breakdown than that but it was like this
really broad generalization so the guy
like they contacted us and sent it to
see if we wanted to check it out I said
I check it out first before I write
about it and that was one of those
sounds like I'm not writing about this
cuz he's like how how was your how are
your results I was like well I found out
I was Asian
surprising yeah yeah cuz I thought it'd
be cool if I got like a deeper breakdown
yeah stuff I didn't know 23andme does
like crazy stuff like how short your
legs are or like they do weird genetic
things to who you're related the people
you're related to
I think that's interests all we have
yeah cuz somebody we met was like yeah I
got a profile that said like you're
unlikely to be a sprinter because of
your like genetic makeup and what I
yeah I didn't this it's even more like
and as you keep developing it's like hey
you're probably not successful yeah
you're probably living hey
you're living with your mom in her
basement just like you're not really
gonna do anything in life having
interesting to know would you want to
know that's the question Oh see that
that is a good question though cuz then
are you the type of person to be like
I'm gonna prove this wrong right
you know it's personality based at that
point so Oh what let's take it even
further what if these types of tests
could be like this is the exact day
you're gonna die I want you guys to know
I would want to know - I don't really
yeah you wouldn't want to know I don't
know man I think as a planner like I'd
prefer to plan like maybe it's just good
to know yeah especially if it's a
guarantee yeah I'm not gonna die before
then obviously unless I do something
super stupid yeah what if it's like but
what if it's like the matrix to where
it's like they're telling you this to
actually make you live longer or they're
taking this and because they because you
read it that's why it's coming true
yourself of self fulfilling interesting
conspiracy I wouldn't I would want it
you would want to know yeah you would
want to know - I don't know I'm on the
fence about that one but why cuz like
you'd be scared to know when you die
well if I know when I'm gonna die and so
I start like oh I know I'm gonna die I
should start doing a lot of things
before that which sounds good but is
that really me doing those things
because that's what I want to do or am i
doing it because I know I have an
expiration date I think that's my
thinking too much about it yeah nobody
know I know what you're so what I'm
saying right yeah authentically
genuinely you're just thinking about
this loop and you're gonna be in your
own head until you die you crazy over
thought myself to death be crazy from it
all have this expiration date and we
looked it up and all of ours are on the
same day like what happens on that field
trip yeah we just think hey we can't be
around each other yes that day I mean
yeah but it would you know happen though
that's the thing so yeah I don't think I
would try to avoid it
okay okay so you guy said yes you would
know when you wanna know yeah would you
want to know also how you died yes yeah
absolutely sure I don't know why I
thought that would be there's movies
about this right isn't there yeah yeah I
would absolutely if I couldn't have the
choice to know when and how yeah why not
think so too
okay haven't you ever thought about that
idea I mean you you're more religious
right you're like yeah from a Christian
background and yeah but I always had the
thought because I didn't really know I
didn't really know I never had to go to
church when I was a kid like I always
used to think about these kind of things
like how it feels to die and like even
being like what if however you die you
just you know your brains too and I
don't know I know the science behind it
doesn't make sense but what if that last
feeling of whatever you feel is just it
just keep you keep feeling that's all
you're over Syria yeah or rest of
eternity and it's just like I don't know
it's a possibility
maybe that's considered like hell or
like this and then if it's a good
experience and that's your version of
heaven what I don't know I just have
right but what's like what's a good
experience in your dad a good expert
well some people say they feel euphoric
right people who claim who have died and
come you know right before you die you
feel like there's something release I'm
chemical right yeah I don't know that I
don't know what it is there's some
chemical that's released right before
you do it like I I don't want to talk
about it cuz I don't know enough yeah
but it's something like something you
work you feel heard that right as you're
dying or something like that and people
have said it because they've died and
come and or revived or whatever it was
hey you know what let's do it man social
experiment guys what you're gonna just
die yeah hmm you know I don't put social
experiment gone wrong well I mean dude
that's a YouTube Google thing dude yeah
there's another episode this can get on
Mon tires there goes the she she went
mad but how would you want to die yeah
you didn't answer
yeah oh and I didn't he but if I had to
die in a painful way yeah I would want
my body to be like stretched like one of
those old
why torture chambers you know I in the
medieval days that sound so why like why
I think oh man Dan I don't believe you
like I don't think it would be the most
interesting thing like who dies like
that anymore you know this is just I
don't believe you for one and this is
very dark
I don't mind it you know I know other
people do mind it's alright getting away
from torturing ourselves to death yeah
what else do we talk about that's a very
interesting segue yourself out of that
all right
Game of Thrones anybody see that haven't
seen it yet
I'm all out up except for the last
season I I'm the only one in here who's
seen it yeah but Papa doesn't watch
shows really ever any if it's popular
he's got like hipster no I see I'm just
trying to watch stuff now because I'm
like if I want to make you know if I
want to be a comedian and make content
stuff I can't you just admit that it's
good like shows are good I'm not saying
they're not you say not means is there a
show that you started watching before I
got popular and then it got popular and
you're like oh I'm not gonna watch Game
of Thrones he started watching and I
started watching it late yeah okay I was
on Game of Thrones lead but last night I
did watch Scarface
that's good not as good as I thought it
was gonna what's kind of old yeah it's
just like they did that was the first
time you've seen it yeah and I was just
like this is so real like story to it
you know it's just a lot of like cussing
and yeah what made you want to watch
that cuz because I was like oh I should
watch classics too so I have like
references that and things to look up so
I'm like studying and doing I was like I
was like so I Google that's like why his
Scarface so popular and then a lot of
reviews are saying Scarface was actually
a really poor movie but the reason why
did so well is it's a cult classic
amongst like like there's a lot like
that black and Latino communities
because it was the first of its kind
it was just so like different and vulgar
that a lot of people were like I like it
you know because it is different I was
like okay I can see that well I mean
that's like somebody I just saw a post
somebody posted like oh I'm this years
old and it's a picture of me doing like
the how to be ninja and how to be you
know and you go and walk back and watch
though you tell somebody hey I grew up
watching this and like if they go to
those videos I'm embarrassed like I
don't want people to today like to watch
that because if you compared to the
content that's out today you know I mean
like yeah
but that's in the same way that movies
back then you might have grew up on it
so you might like oh even if even if
they go back to watch those videos it
might think it's still like oh it was a
classic for yeah I'm you go back and
it's the same thing you go back and
watch movies because I watch movies I'm
like oh this was bad but I still enjoy
watching it because it's like I'm just
like reminiscing like Harold and Kumar
[Music]
it's an older movie no I'm talking like
going back to like the movies of like
home alone yeah right I saw and you
watch it again it's not bad it's just
like you compared to like the comedies
and stuff they have like the effects
everything that they have now it's just
like this is this would never hold up
today but it's a great movie still and
I'll still watch it yeah a lot of its
nostalgia like it's just that that's
what holds it together I mean like I
grew up watching like the x-men cartoon
yep
yep it's a horrible series if you go
back and watch any of those episodes
really that bad
the only cartoon I think that was
actually decent was the Batman oh wow
that's like 90s one oh that one for
really long remember though remember the
one where he had the red he turned red
and black he was like all like young and
oh yeah super skinny dude yeah
everybody was like may I that resurfaced
because you know Edward from Twilight is
playing the new Batman he's this verse
even pac-man and I was like oh isn't
that such an interesting choice that
they picked robber pens him yeah yeah
but I mean like you like it huh no it's
not that just from what I've heard yeah
and things is like his acting just got
you know way better and there's clearly
a reason why the casting directors are
looking at him I think I think he's one
of those guys who were probably decent
actor just unfortunately it was part of
a really bad franchise well or might not
have even been bad it's just like
because it was so popular with like a
younger demographic yeah it's late it's
early and because in our society now
it's it's like hey let's hate on this
cuz it's fun you know that's the thing
to do so everybody just jump Linux yeah
that thing about vampires I've seen him
you know why you're one of those it's
because it had so much lot like fans
anything with a lot of guys like Justin
Bieber his any anyone older than him is
like he's well yeah and like I was there
like I liked his songs like a lot of his
songs I thought were like this is super
catchy he's held talented I would make
Joe and I wouldn't make jokes about him
because I was the culture at the time
yeah but like it's just cuz he was
popular if he wasn't that popular if
like he had a he was like indie right
going back to like when people not that
saying that you just you do that but if
he was just independent a few people
knew about and back then there's this
good-looking kid he'd get sign I mean
he'd be like popular anyway mm-hmm if he
was like single I mean who's the current
person right now who's like the most
popular teen he's weaned on heart I mean
like ariana grande kind of a lot of
people like lover wait a bit lot of
people like to hate on their kids oh do
you think yeah Swift - well she kind of
she has a lot of PR issues okay that's
not a good example but like you know
like you know I'm talking about the last
Justin Bieber's of the world
One Direction it's like they can
actually be talented people but because
their audience is so crazy and in love
with them and young it's looked everyone
else's like that's so lame yeah what's
that new girl
Billy Billy I wish ya different though
but she's not mean she's not made she is
mainstream but she's mainstream now in a
different she in a different way
yeah that's true like if her fans start
becoming like I think right now she's in
that she's becoming that yeah but if her
fans start becoming like those hardcore
like oh my god
defend her at all costs kind of thing
you know in the way that BTS fans you
know like their yeah BTS is getting tons
of heat from people who aren't BTS fans
because of their fans yeah and it's just
like when you're at the top of that list
you know and you're the hottest thing
and all these young people who are
rooting for you and defending you like
more than they should be
it it naturally you're gonna have the
opposite effect when you have that much
love you need that much heat I wonder if
it happened with like way back in the
day before sexual I'm like I'm like the
Beatles
I'm sure there's Beatles here so there
was yeah and it's at the time and I'm
sure like you know now we're like you
can say something bad about the Beatles
yeah in 50 years or 50 in the 50 years
right we're just gonna be people were
like oh my god how dare you say that
about Justin Bieber he's a class he
brought our countries together he's the
reason why there's peace remember and in
the history books they talked about when
he peed in the bucket like you guys
remember the classic bucket gate yeah
alright when he was like driving drunk
yeah and it's really fast yeah same with
Jake Paul Logan Paul yeah all gonna be
part of the history books because of how
big they were and they're not gonna be
well they might be remembered in
different ways but their careers aren't
over you know like they still have the
hard question if they can still turn it
around for what their legacy is gonna be
do I feel like even just Logan already
has for how deep into a hole he was and
to where he is now it's night and day
like he was canceled according to most
people but he really wasn't you know
yeah he's still relevant despite what
people will say because they're
comparing to his the top of his game and
ksi said that he would be friends with
Logan
I'm Jake interested hmm and Jake didn't
even do anything that crazy I know we
didn't even talk about this after that
podcast you did you see that we I mean
you know that we work yeah I did a
podcast with him
he said that he would actually be
because we asked could you ever be
friends with Logan he was like I think I
could but I could never be friends with
Jake thinking that's such a strong
statement like so definitive yeah and I
and he said he's just a bad person
Wow I was just trying to figure out I
was like what like cuz that's how you
would talk about Logan so like what yeah
what josy like things can change so are
you saying just before that we're
talking about Jay Paul and how like
Justin Bieber before that yeah right and
then Billy Eilish
yeah Oh what I was saying about her
right because she's still kind of like
she's weird right yeah she's kind of
like Lord when Lord just came out yeah
I'm a weirdo like but like good music
and just just different like very unique
and it's a kind of cool yeah it's kind
of indie but mainstream indie that makes
sense oh yeah yeah I don't know how to
describe that kind of music
what's like it's it's like anti pop
right yeah so because it's anti pop a
lot of play and I and I just think that
it's because she's still new it's why
she's not getting that kind of hate well
and you know what it all it takes is one
scandal one thing she says wrong and
then she's gonna build a resume she's
young do that's what I mean
young people always say something we're
all like I've seen her interview where
she's like watching herself from a year
ago and like you could take that into
like all she's so relatable she's so
like you know a normal person but like
you could take that even that interview
in another way too
yeah so especially if you're on media
all over the place yeah it's running a
marathon
yeah and then even if you are perfect
it's like she's trying so hard to be
perfect like you know there's always
gonna the bigger you become still think
it's always a balance the more love you
get the more hate you're gonna get yeah
and everything and I think we can go
into that and talk about it especially
with YouTube because both of you guys
when when you were doing social media
uh-huh you had kind of like a clean-cut
you know family friendly type of brand
yep Ryan definitely family friendly a
lot of times when he swears on the
podcast people like oh my gosh he's
war or something and she but uh so what
what is the pressure like you know where
you have to keep it like this but you
know your personalities aren't
necessarily it wasn't hard I'll tell you
me really mean it wasn't hard for me
either yeah it doesn't make it it
doesn't make it funny like it wasn't the
jokes I was writing weren't based on
what being vulgar like so it's not hard
I mean sure sometimes you'd be like to
say even any an unnecessary f-word is it
it's like a fart joke it's super easy to
make something funnier if you're being
vulgar
it's like shocking I mean I still like
fart jokes though Thanks
abs are swearing I mean I agree I think
well we weren't doing like daily
vlogging or anything like that either we
were very we picked what we curated we
curated all our content so it was easy
to put together what we look like from
the outside appearance but I mean for us
it was just the thought of like well a
we came out like people knew we were
Christian and I think there's there's a
stigma with it that's good and bad and
we didn't I mean we're pretty I would
say we're very laxed about like how our
views are it's not like we don't curse
or any of that or drink you know like we
drink we curse whatever but it's just
the appearance of we just want to be
responsible with our platform because
people can take that one thing and just
twist it like we were talking about
earlier so we just kind of chose to say
okay well we want to come out make sure
we have a clean appearance also for
brands premieres a lot of business so
for me our first like when I first
started on YouTube it was actually more
like my content I said the F word I said
a bunch of stuff like I said [ __ ] I said
like a bunch of like thank you yeah and
one and also I just didn't think much of
it right and then I started getting like
emails and stuff from like parens and I
was still a kid too I mean technically
yeah and that's when I realized like oh
like there's actually kids most of my
fanbase is like not just thirteen to
seventeen because that's what you two
would show but you're like like
five-year-olds I would meet and like
eight-year-olds I would meet are
I'm eating him though they would just I
would just see him mocha and then they
would be like oh I'm a fan of like him
you heard me say [ __ ]
so warrants actually emailed you and
said could you add some that some of
that and then I saw it for myself in
person when people started coming up to
me yeah I was like yeah I need to chill
out on that not for brands at the time
cuz I wasn't making any money but it was
like oh I should probably not say every
good stuff but it wasn't like Mila it
wasn't that hard like it wasn't like
that wasn't my thing anyway that's not
what I wanted to portray I guess yeah I
so don't I mean even if I'm swearing on
this it's not like you know I don't
think it's not in a context where it's
like I'm trying to I'm trying to force
it I don't know I don't have an issue
people that swear to be honest yeah and
it's not like you're swearing every
other word yeah it's when it's
appropriate and the thing is to like
people who do talk like that
if that's just how they speak maybe
that's how they the way they grew up
like I don't have an issue like it's
just words I think we give words too
much meaning to me personally
but I also don't get offended easily so
yeah that's true but a lot of people in
the world do and that's why we kept
their channels that way yeah yeah pretty
much yes good question Paco you almost
done with good questions don't give me
another good question
all right why is your hair like that
what's wrong with my hair right now
no you just always have had like with
like bait the very stirs that what agent
haircut where it's like why are you
shaved on the side this is a second like
ever since the cab podcast you're just
trying to find ways to roast
no I'm man you picked on his hair too he
did heavens hair was he just came out of
Sunday school I'm so gonna send him this
thing I cut my own hair oh that's why
that makes sense that normal because I
honestly because we moved so much is
hard to find a haircut person that I
trusted he's like hair is a very
particular thing and I also my hair grow
so fast
I didn't want to pay for haircut every
week you're making $50 a month this time
yeah and now this 25 now I'm like I've
just gotten so used to it it's easier
for me to cut my hair than until I go
out and get a haircut mmm true I know
it's not a perfect I say if I know how
learning to cut my own hair I would
probably do that yeah it took me a long
time like it used to take make an hour
to cut my own hair so but your reasoning
is different you would only want to
learn how to cut your own hair so you
don't have to leave your house yes but
that's what like it's for convenience
like I just like and I just like
learning the new skill like to be able
to I don't like that no but you know so
I probably save so much money and people
don't you two would know because I'll
cut it really short and I'll wait until
it's super long that's true right
I am I am trying to teach kids you know
how to be smart with your money
yeah haircuts aren't cheap they aren't
cheap especially good ones yes so if you
if you just don't mind looking fugly for
like a good three weeks to a month you
could save a whole you could cut your
hair hair cut expenses in half just let
it grow out how often do you cut your
hair like once a month okay I know that
mine but I go like once I'm suin s have
a maybe yeah yeah you should we should
introduce wait is it that lady that I
think I might have gone to her once I'm
using the same person
yep yeah okay no I liked her I just okay
you just didn't want pity no I think I
tried it right before we left and then
at that point is when I started to learn
how to cut my own hair
no so yeah I cut it this way cause it's
the easiest way to cut it I can't I've
tried to like fade it more too hard and
the back of my head mmm so it's the
easiest way to come here
well for those that are just listening
he just has a very Asian stereo
you know so even Andrea our hairdresser
tried to give me that same hairstyle
where just shade on the sides and like
long on the top and kind of goes to the
side and I don't know why every
hairdresser just really liked that for a
short amount of time and then every
asian guy for whatever reason that not
just Asians get people to go but there's
a lot of what a lot of Asians have had
and I I just I don't know I didn't want
to just do the same thing I guess I
don't know she's uh she's uh she she's
German
yeah she was married to a black guy and
as like black kids really like in black
culture I asked her to do a fade
no no uh dreadlocks Oh dreadlocks yeah
you wanna hurt it hurts so much
oh you actually I gave up it was to pain
how far did you get into one string told
me he was gonna do it too and I wasn't
expecting to see it and then he just had
a regular she was like it's gonna be
three hours of this and I was like you
know I'm good you know do you respect
Jeremy more No
yeah dreadlocks right is that what it's
called or cornrows cornrows didn't he
dreads
yeah dreads yeah dreads are the ones
that look like little like what do you
collect Michael rose almost little
Charles like kind of like churros I was
gonna describe it but yeah that thicker
yeah and it's not the like one that's
like designed yeah yeah yeah really yeah
you had that for a little bit and he got
a lot of crap member can you watching :
yeah yeah it's from culture
appropriation that kind of isn't it
interesting how that was like the hot
topic and then all of a sudden it's like
kind of died like people still talk
about it but it's not like in every like
oh someone so appropriated this this
isn't like that was like a all these it
PC PC news of the week we haven't done
that in Y in a while PC is of the week
just real quick culture appropriations
not in right now
no you can still do it and get called
out for it but news articles and stuff
they don't really care about that as
much what is the current thing people
care about it I would say the most
recent one is not immigration it
supports the most abortion abortion
that's the current one yeah yeah
that's the most current one now you talk
give your opinion about anything having
to do with pro-life or parole abortion
or trying yeah yeah that is the it is
not a current just at the yeah at the
right time
this is if you want to have some
conversations with people post about it
and you will upset
laughs the world probably both sides I
think honestly the new cycle completely
changed with this presidency before it
was a bivy like more celebrities and
like that's what was interesting but
because of Trump right right
every new cycle is always something that
he causes well if he because he's in the
news yeah well yeah but like yeah his
stuff is so controversial that that's
always the hot topic in the news it's
something that he's involved in but
isn't it funny that when it's in it goes
and it literally is like people could
still be appropriate in cultures but
they weren't right about it because it's
not gonna get them views exact all that
matters like I know people are genuinely
offended by it but like people really
care about their views that's what it
really comes down to oh absolutely yeah
it's whatever remember when people who
are mad about ALS or like super into
supporting eilat like you'd like the ice
bucket I spent there was so much
controversy oh you're just doing this
for the views
I mean who who's still who's still
looking that stuff up who still cares
about ALS I mean other than the people
who really did care about it right talk
about it who stopped was talking about
it other than right now yeah if we
didn't bring it up I think people would
not care Oh No there might even be some
people who done don't even know what
that is I'm talking about all those
people that was like a couple years ago
more than that right feels like more
than three to five threes ours but all
those people remember we did it that's
why I mean ever a lot of people did and
there's so much backlash like you guys
don't actually care about ALS yeah I
don't like this has nothing to do you
guys have disrespectful and that was
like the hot topic yeah where are those
people now where they are I don't see
you guys posting about it like you cared
so much about ALS back then where are
you now
damn I knew I thought about this but
what if those people were deaf and their
sign languaging at you you trying to
make a really dark joke right oh they
you're gonna get cancer skit about ALS
while doing ASL American Sign Language
don't know why I thought about it it's
not even a funny joke it's just like and
had a mic on their hands doing a SMS you
guys are gonna get canceled man
get the show cancel anyway that was you
seen this of the week even though we
weren't being very peasy it's a good way
to end and this because but okay I'm
letting you do your thing good what I
say thanks for tuning in to the author
podcast that's not true I said follow us
at are you what are you doing right no
what you didn't do the following I was
gonna just do it I said you have this
fight every single podcast I'm always I
do sometimes but I were just gonna say
thanks for tuning into the off the pill
podcast make sure you follow us on
Twitter at off the pill and on Instagram
off the pill podcast that's right see
for once I really was gonna say this I
didn't forget this time anything you
want to plug yes
check out the blog if you guys are
traveling local and yet
local adventure calm Lockwood adventurer
adventurer spell it for us just in case
I can't spell adventure local adventure
rare like a person adventurer I don't
even want to breathe into the mic that's
all Matt I am just sigh at this alright
in three two one
I like Kevin's on last week I'm just so
just mad