hey guys so first of all I know I look a
little different today I mean don't be
alarmed don't freak out it's not
permanent just to get it out of the way
I will address it right now yes
okay I got a new shirt not a big deal
next video I'll probably just go back to
an old shirt so calm down I'm gonna be
making big changes to my image and not
address it okay so now that it's all
cleared up and out of the way back to
the real video so even if you're younger
and not able to vote or you're not from
the US you probably at least still heard
some of the drama behind the whole
presidential election Hillary Clinton
versus Donald trum I'm een it's gotten
pretty crazy and and very hateful over
here if you ask anyone most people
either tell you they hate Trump or they
hate Hillary some people hate both of
them well I like to be a little
different and here's something you
probably whenever hear I love both of
them I support Hillary and Donald and I
I just can't decide who I love more I
mean whatever happened to seeing the
glass half-full that's a can cuz we
Americans what you see this whole
election has made everyone so negative
and a big part of it is because the
candidates are so negative towards each
other making all their supporters
negative towards one another as well and
I watched every single one of the
debates when I was watching the final
debate about a week ago I just thought
to myself like these two candidates are
just such equally great and good people
I just wish they could get along I mean
imagine how great our country would be
if a Larry Clinton and Donald Trump got
along imagine how much nicer all of
their supporters would be to one another
imagine how we would look at these two
stop spewing hated each other and shared
love instead it would be beautiful could
you imagine what is this no go ahead
Donald no I'm a gentleman Hillary go
ahead
okay can I just say something crazy I
love crazy all my life has been those
hear reason or been mine
and then to believe I home to me I was
thinking the same thing cause like I've
been researching my whole life to find
my own place and maybe it's the party
talking or teacher found my lousy shame
and it's nothing why
[Music]
did you already
get your old man
you can show something crazy I can't I
grabbed you on the port can I say
something even crazier
yes yeah I don't know why I made that
either and I know it sounded really bad
I literally just downloaded this music
editing program without any idea how to
use it so I was just messing around I
use it again it'll be better I kinda
know what I'm doing now but sorry that
was just a test it was the best I could
do I'm sorry guys I'm not a music person
[ __ ] am I am I
no but anyway before this video ends
just because I know you're gonna be
talking about in the comments and it
kind of teased it earlier and of course
I wasn't gonna finish this video and not
actually address it yes I know something
looks very different today and I know it
looked very messy and no I'm not
changing the look permanently it's I was
just a little lazy today okay so I'm
sorry you have to look at this I
apologize next video I promise I will
make my bed not a big deal