and President Trump who had aspirations
to loosen restrictions by Easter has now
also we will be extending our guidelines
to April 30th oh my god 30 day
seriously don't know how much more of
this I can take
I am so over this pandemic
and this is sitting there chilling
staring up into the cylinder and
millions in the kitchen watch and see
little kisses fat disgusting with a fist
distant Pacific I'm mrs. Willet missing
the feeling of grill and dipping it but
never did I know I could finally clear
my shoes then again on Instagram my
friends are taking shots of booze why
not there's nothing nothing any one of
us can do can't learn a skill but prick
the mirror look up anything
choose coz up there just nothing here to
stew I could fix that clock that's an
hour off tick-tock different shirt whoa
different spot that that's just too hard
to do dude a blanket border house and
cars construction paper shadow are drawn
there to flip-flop trick shots ping-pong
two cups when you're not hip thirsting a
song Rick Ross there's still nothing to
do here there's people died and loved
ones while Oshkosh stock market crash
inside but hey
[Music]
and I'm getting kind of
didn't see or talk to anyone today just
binge-watch that tiger King show in my
pajamas
hashtag introvert hashtag homebodies
hashtag perfect dead but on serious note
everybody be safe stay home cook rice