hey guys services are posted by
censorship video I've been getting a lot
of comments from parents or people
pretending to be parents saying things
like my son started cursing and became
violent after watching your videos
delete all your videos immediately first
off don't believe your child's cursing
on me I don't even curse in my videos I
keep this PG ok yes sometimes there are
little bits of violence in my video but
really you're gonna blame your child's
behavior on what they watch and not by
your parenting I grew up watching shows
like Tom and Jerry where it's all about
a cat trying to murder a mouse and you
don't see me choosing any one around
with a knife I had the entire first
season of Dragon Balls here my part of
those still be little 9000 is to watch
and play pokemon religiously that's all
about getting a pet making it stronger
so that you can kill other people's pets
and I'm nothing like Michael Bay because
people aren't violent due to what they
watch their violence of who they are and
how they were raised violence is
everywhere in entertainment and it
always will be because people find it to
be entertaining could you imagine what
entertainment would look like with no
violence hey so what do you want to play
I got a call of duty modern peace Fair
Gears of love street hugger oh we can
play here we'll reach for the stars I
don't know it's really up to you you
guys heard of that new super fun game
what farmville we still don't want to
play that your hair looks pretty nice
your smile lights up the room you're
sweeping people off their feet call
yourself a broom standing right in front
of me you're looking pretty cool you're
a dog I know we just met but I think I
love you
Oh Sam I don't think I can make it you
just saying you're nervous to follow
it's just beyond this hill
oh you're right it's right there
everyone's that traveling tomorrow would
be difficult guess we showed them let's
not move Sam let's Brokeback Mountain do
not talk about Fight Club
do not talk about my club you want you
can talk about Fight Club but as long as
there's no fighting are you ready are
you ready let's go this wait
what do you want from me
okay no no no use your head you don't
have to do this Eddie if you go into the
light you'll burn to death no Jacob
you're wrong
I'll just Sparkle although I think
people should never use my eyes to solve
their problems I don't think you should
blame entertainment for it and people
think that kids are so impressionable
and should be hidden from violence so
why do we force them to go to school and
take history class where they learn all
about the wars that happen in the past
wars like the most violent thing in the
world I don't support violence and I
would never instigate it if I really
were that evil and I wanted to start
buying clothes would have to say is who
is better one direction or Justin Bieber
you would see tons of violent comments
in the comments section below I would
never do that especially not at the end
of a video ones still fresh in their
minds because that that would just be
sick