and the laws now are catching it exactly
this is why Bitcoin and crypto and
decentralization is the next wave it's
the most important evolution of the
internet and that was how we were able
to sell out of our bags and then grow it
to like 10,000 bags 30,000 and 50,000
100,000 and then grow up to a million
clap are we supposed to clap
simultaneously no it's just a thing we
do welcome back to another episode of
off the pill podcast we have a very
special edition as you can see
everything's very different this is our
first time being in LA where we're gonna
be we have another special guests miss
Michelle Phan and we have of course
david choi at the moderator seat and
Paco Leto right next to me see you're a
joke that's why everybody everybody's
laughing but yeah we have Michelle here
thank you for being here on our first
episode that's not quite ready yet I oh
thank you it's been um it's been a long
time for those of you that don't know
we've actually me you and David have
known each other since like I don't know
a long time ago ten years we're just old
youtubers like that's how people see us
now I know we're just old youtubers we
were at this is this is how dated we are
we were at the first VidCon
put it down there's five thousand was it
really just five thousand people no for
real haven't vaccin have you been back
since I went back a few years ago how
was it huh dude it's like a YouTube
heading zoo that's how I feel stupid
yeah well actually considering we were
considering of actually going back after
ten year because it's their 10-year
right 10 year reunion yeah we were
talking was already gonna go by himself
not with me or anything but David was
trying to convince me to go and I think
you as well I mean are you gonna go I'll
go you go you guys have tickets I mean
this comes out we win is VidCon it
should we just go it's been it's a
ten-year thing right and then we'll wait
another ten years I come back though
from New York on Friday so go on
Saturday
what does it start ten which is a
Tuesday I think oh maybe no Wednesday
Wednesday well okay okay so but we just
go in Friday then I can't come Friday
because I come back from New York on
Friday got it so we would have to go
Saturday okay I think about it are you
really gonna go though for real I'll go
if you go I don't want to go alone
let's go we'll be let's go together yeah
guys we're try and see if we can get you
in this carpool I got I got two spots in
my car well for people who don't know
Michelle is an OG youtuber it's not
don't take that as an insult people
refer to me as that as well I'm David
I'm obviously sniff dog is OG he is
there you go
and I guess you were I don't know if you
were the first but probably the biggest
makeup guru right and the for the first
and biggest makeup guru Phoebe I'm sorry
I keep touching the tea and we're not
used to having these mics so I got to
stop touching the table hitting it yeah
the biggest and one of the first makeup
gurus on YouTube pretty much right and
basically I don't know how do you how
did you even get started well it was in
2007 I got rejected from a job a beauty
counter I needed a job because I needed
to pay my bills and I applied and always
good but then because I lacked sales
experience they didn't hire me that's so
ironic well we can get into that because
you have your own company which is like
like hugely successful where's your cup
it's valued at almost a billion dollars
right it's crazy
oh yeah if see I left the company two
years ago though right but you still
built you still started that company
initially and that company is like
really up worth a billion dollars
they're doing great they sell three
million bags a month for $10 each it's a
subscription model so it's very scalable
and it's helped a lot of indie brands
punch and become vegan
we'll get acquired by the big trifecta
beauty brands like Procter gamble
L'Oreal how far into YouTube did you
start that actually it was when I
reached a million subscribers and I was
I don't want to brag though but just to
give people some context I was the first
woman to have a million subscribers and
that that milestone I knew okay this is
a good milestone to think about having
longevity because I knew it's the
Internet people have such a short
attention span that I'm not going to
last as long my popularity is not gonna
last as long so I need another stream of
revenue that's not based on my human
bandwidth because we made this
comparison about how being a youtuber is
like being an uber driver and your car
is your channel and you have to drive
your car if you want to make money and
with YouTube it's the same way where you
have to constantly upload and post and
even your doing this podcast you got to
keep it moving you're an uber driver I
know but it's funny cuz didn't you say
you wanted to come back into it don't
you miss it I do miss it I don't like
the politics though cuz within the
beauty of space well see you're not in
the beauty space so you don't really see
all the drama I know you don't want to
be dude there's so much drama in the
beauty space beautiful
go ahead alright so what do you mean the
politics let's get into the rarity get
into the drama version or okay call them
out nah man I only drink to you I don't
spill I have a sense of nobility where
I'm not that's just not my thing
sure it's like karma take care of it you
know and also there's always two sides
to the story
with everyone and you know most
youtubers even the ones who are kind of
like a little up a little they
don't have the worst intentions it's
true right they don't and I they're just
normal people in a way if people see
them as this grand grandiose Idol but
once the camera turns off they're just a
normal person and i i i do actually feel
bad for a lot of youtubers and beauty
creators who do get pulled into the
drama and it has become hollywood or
especially within the beauty space
because there's so much money in it and
where there's money there's
a lot of people who are going in and who
want to be part of this economy I feel
like you're tiptoeing around something
like is there no I mean in the beauty
space you're saying there's a lot of
politics like give me an example of what
that means
politics like a lot of these brands will
pay - for sponsorships and so if there's
a product that's not good
a beauty creator will still say it's
good even though everyone knows it's not
good I like just selling out yeah
selling out so that's one ask well
you're luckily you don't have to do that
right don't but I got lucky
see I got it early and at that time in
2008 so this was right when the economy
crashed and I was sixteen thousand
dollars in debt no one was hiring I
didn't know what to do then I saw
YouTube had Adsense and they just rolled
out the partners program mm-hmm
and I figured wait I can make money
making these YouTube videos that I was
doing for free anyways hell yeah I'm
gonna do this so you were actually doing
before the partner program way before
okay what under what time what date did
you like what year did you actually
start
I started in May 2007 oh wow that's like
same as me really yeah
what June I think or July did all seven
you're bored too huh yeah just for fun
that was in Hawaii there's nothing to do
David was actually before David's ogee
for oh geez what are your two thousand
six five right no no no not five 2006
Dan yeah bro you're late dinah so I have
I have a Joss I have a different account
that I was posting before David Troy
leak excuse I'm not gonna announce I
know okay well I mean sit like you said
you want to get back into it I was not
just telling you like I just randomly
and I haven't because you haven't really
been posting anything before in the past
life in two years yeah so I haven't like
clicked on anything on your channel and
randomly I just saw recently that your
your channel was suggested to me and it
was live yeah and I clicked on expecting
to see you and there was just like this
animation and just music playing and is
that that's what you're gonna be using
your channel for more or you're trying
to do something that's kind of like my
first it's like when you go to a party
and you just people who come in early
they can just enjoy the music
got it just setting the tone the
atmosphere it's really interesting that
you're using your channel in that way
yeah I mean you have those you know
those live streaming channels right yeah
the music ones I always had them years
ago playing in the background and people
actually loved watching my videos back
then because of my music that I
recommended mm-hmm and I have this
peer-to-peer marketplace I have this
peer-to-peer marketplace called thematic
where we help music creators and
creators link up and collaborate because
you know how hard it is to get music
rights and takedowns are mm-hmm
takedowns happen a lot and with article
13 and article 17 in the EU it's going
to become harder and harder and YouTube
now they're liable or anything copyright
it and so they don't want to be liable
for that so we have a lot of these
pre-cleared songs from actual music
artists for creators to use and so
that's a company that I founded because
I was sued years ago by a music label
and unfairly it was so unfair but it's
it's not even like there was no one's
fault there was a miscommunication along
the way like I have no hate or mmm-hmm
anything towards that music label what
happened with that lawsuit oh I just
settled it oh right I remember when that
was happening I was just like well
they're gonna I guess I could were kind
of big at the time too like that's what
you're a target yeah because I was
always like oh I thought we were safe
right cuz I thought were just
individuals who had like a big business
and well this is what happens that not
just me but even I'm not gonna say who
which youtuber this is cuz I don't know
if she wants me to say anything but
she's a big youtuber and she was in the
car just saying a lyric from a song just
saying it out loud like twinkle twinkle
little star and she got claimed to they
actually they actually hire people to
scour all the top youtubers so it's
sickening honestly there's one I one of
my biggest videos it's called proving
the Illuminati is real and the whole
video it got claimed I'm not gonna say
the lyric because they're gonna claim
this but in the end card of the video
what I rhyme with take me sup okay okay
something Lolo
something and I'm probably still gonna
get you know you know what song it is
but I said that in the endcard because I
was saying like wake up America right
wait
and then they claim the whole video and
there's nothing I can do about it and
that videos nothing to do with that it's
in the end card of the video I know what
you mean but that's that's how it is
that's it but that's why you created
sematic yeah but that wasn't even this I
wasn't using the song I just said the
lyric of it this is the sad part about I
mean the whole point of capitalism is
you're giving people have a chance to
build a business to build their capital
right they have a great product or they
have a great service that they can
provide competing against another and
it's better they can win it's it's that
opportunity that America gives to people
and I feel like when you have these big
lobbies whether it's like in the beauty
space or in the music space like the
ones who own everything they just make
it so unfair and harder for the smaller
people to win like they tell us like
yeah if you work really hard you have a
great idea you're gonna win that's
you're not unless you have 20
lawyers and this is why Disney is so
well protected even though most of the
movies that they create are stolen like
all of the fairy tales I mean that's
these are fables that weren't owned by
anyone yeah you know what I mean
I mean I hundred percent understand and
that really just reminds me of like
making this drink has been such it just
opened my eyes I thought like okay I'm
just sorry I keep picking them out I'm
not used to having things that thing on
the table so I'm making noise so I
apologize for the listeners and viewers
okay okay but just like getting
approvals for things takes so much
longer and you don't realize that you
have to go through all these different
I'm just being really careful what I'm
saying cuz I don't know I don't want get
in trouble
I'm saw a politics politics that's why
I'm seeing the whole point of the
Internet yeah was it's it was this way
for everyone in the world to connect to
share ideas you could choose what they
want to watch and what they want to get
into yeah and the laws now are catching
it exactly this is why Bitcoin and
crypto and decentralization is the next
wave mm-hmm it's the
important evolution of the Internet yeah
you're really I noticed that you're
really into crypto and and that you know
you're very forward-thinking in
technology like what what about Bitcoin
are you like why do you believe in it so
much
well not everybody understands what it
is first off right it kind of boy sure
um well that's a big statement it's
because there's some so many different
components of what bitcoin is but if I
were to give an elevator pitch what is
Bitcoin Bitcoin is the the true money
the truth truest money that we should
have had since the beginning of time and
just to give some just just to make this
easier to digest um why is gold why was
gold always considered the standard for
money even during like the ancient days
in Egypt Mesopotamia why was it always
gold because gold one its finite so the
fact that you can't find it everywhere
two out of all the precious metals it is
the most stable metal and three it's
hard like it takes a lot of energy to
mine gold like you can figure out you
can even have scanners and scan for gold
but to pay for the labor to pay for the
cost of like the digging and the lit and
all the people feeding them and just to
get a little bit that's why it's so
expensive because it takes a lot of
energy to mine gold and it's finite so
now bringing it to Bitcoin Bitcoin
operates in the same way bitcoin is like
digital gold but it's different it's not
gold because gold you can carry it
intangible but Bitcoin it's digital
um but the fact that it's a scarce
digital asset is what makes it so unique
how is it scarce
there's only twenty-one million coins in
existence that's it there's never gonna
be more coins it's not like our money
the banks can just print more money
right they want to and they do it
without our permission not make more
Bitcoin you can't it is impossible that
is it there's only twenty-one million
units and we've Bitcoin has the white
paper started in 2008 Satoshi created
this white paper and no one even knows
who suck no she is um it was an
anonymous person who came up with this
thesis what is Bitcoin
it's essentially a currency that's not
built on trust because if you look at
the back of your dollar it says In God
We Trust telling us trust in this dollar
it's money it's it's it's a real money
it's a it's a legal tender but can I go
into Fort Knox to count all the gold no
but with Bitcoin you can you can verify
everything everything's time-stamped
there's verification and so you have a
currency that's not built on trust
because people don't trust anyone
anymore you trust but verify and this is
what bitcoin brings to the table so um
since 2008 we've mined up to I believe
17 million Bitcoin units and six million
four million of them are lost meaning
four million Bitcoin people lost their
private keys which means we will never
see it again
it's impossible to retrieve it um and so
that even that drove the scarcity even
more it's even more scarce when you say
you mind I'm just because I really don't
know I'm not trying to like break it
down to me easy you mind a Bitcoin what
does that entail exactly it entails it's
essentially - mine - mine a Bitcoin you
need to have a computer you could have
had a normal computer back then it would
have been easier to mine but today you
need a lot of computers a lot of energy
because it's solving very hard math
questions and I think we've just reached
a halving point which means now it's
gonna be even harder to solve these math
questions it becomes exponentially
harder and they say the last few hundred
bitcoins will take several years and the
last one will probably probably be mined
by 21:40 21:40 will be the last Bitcoin
they say theoretically speaking if we
haven't come up with if we haven't
advanced into quantum computing yet well
it will take another hundred years by
solving these these math equations
though what that's kind of like what are
you getting from them just a number or
like what are you getting exactly what
is a Bitcoin like if you're solving
these if you're solving these I'm trying
to think of something like I'm picturing
a coin okay actual Bitcoin right or what
they think they're local the cool thing
about a bit Queen is you can buy them in
decimals meaning that you can buy them
in fractions you don't have to buy a
whole Bitcoin you can buy half of a
Bitcoin
one-tenth of a Bitcoin it'll called
Satoshi's by uh Satoshi and they say in
the future so one Bitcoin is a hundred
thousand satoshis it's like pennies it's
like having a hundred pennies equals one
dollar so a hundred thousand satoshis
equals one Bitcoin they say the one
Satoshi in the future would be worth ten
dollars so imagine what a full Bitcoin
will be worth I mean some have even
speculated this is the craziest number a
million for one one Bitcoin in the
future so you're saying there's 21
million and that's a cap right that's it
right it's finite who decided or is it
that's how she decided okay so it is a
construct of somebody the protocol yes
right
but he's said of intelligent agencies we
don't know who's to say that that person
right could just be like alright here's
more you can't it's just impossible
because the moment you don't follow the
protocol and then bitcoins worthless
right well I mean if it does happen then
bitcoins worthless but it's not gonna
happen because because you have people
who verify you have miners who are
verifying it who are making sure they're
mining it and everyone can verify it
like I said it's open-source those
Ledger's there's timestamps like you
can't it's actually impossible right but
like like how you said gold is a finite
thing right it's something you can hold
it's there it'll always be there
physically and like the the US dollar it
has value we all verify has value right
but it could instantly become worthless
right we've given it right week we gave
it value after around the Vietnam War
when actually it was actually the
Vietnam War when the dollar went off of
the gold standard so originally we were
on the gold standard and became less and
less and less and the Vietnam War
happened and that was when we became off
the gold standard that was when they
started to sign treaties with Saudi
Arabia to back up our dollar by
petroleum that's why you have the petro
dollar and again politics comes into
place in all of this um and the beauty
with Bitcoin is no one owns it like with
the dollar the Federal Reserve owns a
dollar but if you look at who is the
Federal Reserve it's not the people it's
private banks
right the bitcoins owned by no one
mm-hmm even the banks the banks could
buy half of all the Bitcoin and that's
actually what a lot of them aren't
looking into buying because they're
realizing wait we can't stop this we
should buy some because in the future it
might I mean there's theories but some
people say in the future some countries
might even buy a ton of Bitcoin and
their money is backed up by their
Bitcoin their Bitcoin reserve
interesting so you're buying a digital
land yeah like you're buying digital
real estate you know how real estate is
expensive because land is very finite
young that's essentially what they coin
is but the thing is with real estate and
like with gold you can physically like
that you can't just that won't no one
can take that away from you right I mean
unless they physically take it away from
you right with Bitcoin I just feel like
how do you know it could like if you
could you show me right now if your
bitcoins yeah I mean like I'm trying to
say how do you know it's not gonna
disappear based on like someone or
somebody else in the future well just
make sure you have your private keys
make sure you have your private keys and
an offline wallet in cold storage just
like you're not gonna have your your
gold on your table you're gonna have it
buried in the backyard you're gonna have
it and it is safe you know in a 10 hour
fireproof safe but you're not going to
take your gold and and like chip off a
little bit and go to Starbucks really
hey can I buy like no they're not gonna
do that
it's Bitcoin is not a lot of people
think well I'm not am I gonna buy things
with Bitcoin not necessarily there could
be future crypto currencies that are
backed up by Bitcoin but Bitcoin is the
reserve Bitcoin like gold protects your
purchasing power when the banks fail if
you have gold you're still good you can
still buy bread if you need to right
that's that this is how Bitcoin helps
people or something happens to the bank
something happens to earn money there's
a war you still have your private keys
and you can still protect your
purchasing power mm-hmm okay cuz I was
just trying to think like bear like
technology goes away right like it's
it's a apocalypse right Gold still has
value because you can use sure but you
know when when technology goes away the
last thing we're gonna care about is
we're gonna try and make fire we're
gonna try any exactly gold still has
value right because it's a metal because
it is finite you can melt it
examine it yes then we go to the true
gold standard but do you see us going
away from the digital I'm just saying
I'm just trying to I'm not saying I'm
just going to picture in my head because
I'm trying to figure out what Bitcoin
really is I never I always understood it
I just don't know why they've done tests
now I think like an appalled or
somewhere else where you can still send
Bitcoin is someone without fast internet
mm-hmm it's just gonna take a longer
time but you can still send it without
the internet Wow so how much Bitcoin do
you have is you know like here in
America or the Western world I don't
wanna say America but just in their
Western world the culture is everyone's
trying to flaunt through wealth like you
want to be on the front cover of Forbes
like yeah I'm rich well but then that
turns you into a target you know
interesting is I was reading an article
about in China a lot of the wealthy
people in China will pay money to these
magazines not just to tell it to put
them on the list because they want to
protect they want to be low-key about it
because they know they're gonna become a
target I mean I became a target that's
all yeah yeah that's what happened
that's why I've been just staying
low-key so the same with Bitcoin is
don't tell people you're a Bitcoin
billionaire you know you're gonna
attackers coming at you good thing we're
broke
we're so broke I'm no Bitcoin I have
seven okay sorry I was I didn't mean to
stay on that I just like I got it was
really trying to figure out what I never
knew I never understood it it's
fascinating it is it is a little
interesting only thing I know about
Bitcoin is that's why I like graphic
cards are getting expensive for
computers yeah it's harder to like pay
for the Facebook one I know it's not the
same thing but is that it's okay so the
Facebook Libre queen think of it like
Facebook is an arcade and you go in and
you exchange your dollar into the
quarters and that's what so you can only
use it within their ecosystem oh so
that's different then it's totally
different it's not the same it's not a
competitor I would I wouldn't even say
its competitor it could be one day
no because Bitcoin again it's finite
what about bitcoins competitors there's
other versions yeah but they're not
competitors they
offer different things util it like
their utility coins like aetherium they
offer different rings and some of them
will say like yeah we're faster than
Bitcoin we're better but it's like no
Bitcoin there's a reason why bitcoin is
at all right now
let's see how much it's at I know at one
point I think it was at 20 for a while
they say soon it's gonna go up to 30
thousand since are you recommending for
us so should we put in the title
why michelle phan says to buy bitcoin
now and then if they're sell their
things go up Bitcoin is at eleven
thousand eight hundred but it might go
down to nine thousand and migrate on a
three thousand if it does then you start
buying if it goes down to three thousand
because that's ridiculous really
but I tell people don't like stock
spaces it's not stocks well it's not but
it's not stocks like it's not even it's
gold isn't a stock Gold is a reserve
like she really think bitcoin is like
gold i think bitcoin is digital gold
digital gold real estate because it's
finite and it follows a protocol it's
all about following the protocol and for
over ten years it hasn't slipped it
hasn't even steered an inch away from
the protocol it's so when would you I
mean like you got in early hmm when
would you at what point do you yourself
decide I want to sell it okay so there's
different so you know I'm gonna have to
sell it you could buy a house with
Bitcoin I've seen a video and you know
the cool thing is you don't have to deal
with taxes or anything cuz it's at
illegal no one that's legal like no one
owns it's not government regulated I see
it's not and in a way we have the
internet we should have had a money that
went we should have had a currency that
went with the internet but we have in
everything's been tied to banks like
doing it so I was reading about how
there is 400 million dollars a Bitcoin
that was moved
guess how much the transaction fee was
four hundred million dollars just guess
Wow yeah with two dollars yeah exactly -
I'm a genius I know about Bitcoin but
you know in Zimbabwe they have a crazy
currency out there like I think they
have a note that's 100 trillion dollars
they have one note that's a hundred
trillion guess how much it's worth in
u.s.
I have no idea two dollars forty cents
but locally I think two days ago locally
in Zimbabwe Bitcoin was at seventy two
thousand dollars locally oh really yeah
that's crazy it dude like this is just
the beginning everyone so slept on it
I've been telling people for years
Bitcoin it's the future
well the hype sure died down because it
was at like 20-something when everybody
was buying Yeah right and I thought well
when it's down that's when you buy you
guys Warren Buffett did with stocks
yeah but Warren Buffett said um Bitcoin
is rat poison and now he's kind of
eating his words and he's talking to
crypto people oh really
yeah interesting okay well that went
down around I did not know I'm just like
alright well how do we do this though
like negative things around it though
like I mean whether it's true or not
well so was YouTube in the beginning
well you can make money on YouTube
that's so dumb yeah and the content -
they're talking about some parts you
can't argue there was a lot of dumb
stuff they're still dumb stuff but it
makes money there's people watch TV yeah
that's true - yeah well I'm talking like
current YouTube dumb stuff oh yeah
clickbait oh yeah everyone's there was
pick me before - though that's true but
I feel like now algorithm on YouTube has
become like a up god everyone's
trying to please and everyone's trying
to chase after and get and understand
and they're trying to optimize their
content to favor the algorithm there's
literal groups of youtubers I'm not
gonna say who but there's groups that
talk about this and this they tell each
other do you know about this anyone
there's a there's a discord channel it
will analyze the algorithm like on a
daily basis it's pretty pretty intense
to get oh can you send me that channel
yeah I just like to read it yep it's
interesting it is interesting but it I
it's hard to keep up with the changes I
would say that it never ends yeah never
ends they don't have to tell us either
you know so
Yeah right 30 minute mark okay I guess
we'll take a quick cheesy break a ninja
melt break ninja milk energy made with
organic milk and flavors she's such a
nice voice lightly carbonated energy
drink no artificial sweeteners or
preservatives and it tastes amazing let
me try let me try anyway try this all
right
lightly carbonated oh my all right quick
she she break and we'll be right back
[Music]
and we're back
hey david's rusty he hasn't been
moderating in a while actually I don't
think he's ever done this really yeah
we're still learning sorry Michelle
we're getting back into it a little bit
but getting away from Krypto actually is
that so talking about Krypto we were
just talking about your other company M
cosmetics right it's awesome that's a
second one did you why yes I did i
completely engineered the opening sound
to sound delicious and fresh we're just
talking about this off camera because
thanks because um I I didn't do that but
you asked me that and you said I should
tell more people that see Ryan says I
can't lie to people and I said marketing
isn't lying or just exaggerating okay
but I didn't invent that sound sound
that's just science things were actually
people who engineer sounds like that
like the Snapple bottle that yes okay
that is satisfying yeah but I am yeah I
made that I made it up what we were
talking about were just talking about I
distract em cosmetics I have and look
this isn't sponsored or anything David
wanted to bring this up because he
stopped by my office interesting story
few months ago
and he was asking like yeah so what's up
with this em cosmetics thing how how did
this come about mmm
so to give you some perspective most
people who start a beauty brand they
start it they boot strap it they you
know you have a startup so you
understand like you put your own money
into it and you grow it and then if you
get around like a million to five
million a year pretty good but when you
get up to around 10 to 20 million up to
like 50 million this is when bigger
brands like the Estee Lauder the L'Oreal
the Procter & Gamble they want to they
are interested in acquiring your brand
so they want to acquire it and then they
take your existing company in your brand
and then they just power through and
turn it into a billion-dollar company so
they buy you out and that's normally the
lifecycle for value meaning like you
don't have any part of it once it
becomes a billion-dollar company no it
doesn't become a billion-dollar company
they buy you at 50 million so they turn
it into a billion-dollar company okay so
with em we did the exact opposite my
brand was actually created with L'Oreal
and this was the first time in 2011
L'Oreal has ever created a brand from
the ground up normally they acquire
brand that's what they're really good at
they acquire the brands and they grow it
into a big business like NYX Urban Decay
it cosmetics and in my case with em
they're like hey Michele she's doing
this really cool thing on YouTube let's
take a gamble and let's create a beauty
brand with her and granted L'Oreal is a
great they're masters when it comes to
marketing creating beauty products
expanding on that but creating a brand
from the start you know from the ground
up it's hard it is hard because you need
to have you you can't take a corporate
structure and then bring it into the
startup world it's really hard to do
that because you have to oftentimes a
lot of the corporate structures there's
so many layers and bureaucracies and to
get one thing approved you have to go
through 15 different people on a startup
you just talk to three people and that's
it it's instant umm and so what's
interesting was when I was developing
the brand with L'Oreal and this was in
2011 I was also building it C at the
same time so in New York I'm building
MCAS medics with L'Oreal and I fly back
to LA San Francisco and
building obscene doing the two and it's
it was interesting seeing the dichotomy
between the two worlds because on the
Loreal side they here they had a lot of
budget and a lot of people a lot of
bodies in the company building the brand
with me but because we had too many
people involved things became very
convoluted my vision became convoluted
along with it um but then on the other
side of the spectrum we had it see where
we only had two point seven million
dollars seed funding and that was it and
we were able to use that money and
stretch it and go go completely
grassroots like our marketing was
through YouTube we would just talk
directly to these brands and that was
how we were able to sell out of our bags
and then grow it to like ten thousand
bags thirty thousand fifty thousand a
hundred thousand and then grew up up to
a million and then when we launched em
cosmetics in 2013 with L'Oreal it
flopped it's completely flopped people
were hating on the brand because they
said the packaging looked so cheap
the praat like it was too expensive it
didn't look like me and I was getting so
much hate even though I had no control
over anything
I really didn't because it really was
not like your branding then it wasn't no
boss
when people saw when people watch my
videos I'm known for a certain aesthetic
and they were so confused when they saw
em by L'Oreal because it wasn't it was
completely off of my aesthetic um it was
an authentic it was not authentic no so
I got a lot of hate and it really sucked
because I couldn't say anything
you know I'm under certain contract so
I'm like you know NDA's and all of that
long story short I was stuck and but
thankfully I had epsy that was draining
really well so in a way that was kind of
my savings my saving grace like that
saved my face like I wasn't seen as a
failure because even though the
cosmetics L'Oreal flopped if she was
here zip see like doing two million bags
doing really well and we only needed 2.7
million dollars and we never need it to
raise sense right um so really shows you
it's not about like legacy companies
like these big companies like you know
Google when Google started Google+ they
thought oh we can take down Facebook or
Facebook is like let's take down tik-tok
and launch last so like now dude like
innovation comes from small startups
it's always been like that that's where
you really truly see it because you
people who are very passionate and again
you don't have so many different layers
of people you have to go through to
approve one thing and if C is a great
testament of that so going back to 2015
we raise 100 million dollars for epsy
were able to use that money to buy em
from L'Oreal and to acquire it under
Ipsy which was great but again it wasn't
my brand it was oopsies so I couldn't
approve everything of course even though
I am a founder of Ipsy I have shares in
it there's still a lot of politics when
you do raise money for a company you
give up some some control um and it got
to a point where I just became so tired
I just wanted something that was mine I
was ready to also be independent and so
two years ago I left obscene and I
bought my brand back and so M now is
completely owned by me and that's
awesome and it's just been incredible
because we're small but it feels like a
family unit well when you say small it's
a guessing comparison to the other
things we've seen your office it's not
oh yeah
it's sick it's not small but I guess it
come in compared to what you I mean
compared to having 200 employees now
having like twelve it is really small
but we are forced to be reckoned with
because we everyone can wear multiple
hats like this I thrive in smaller
environments I can't do a corporate
companies I just can't it's just I think
it's it's so opposite of even who we are
yeah right like you probably get more
work done if you were to just work with
you and a few of your friends and if you
were thrown into like an office right
yeah you have a hundred people and
everyone just focus on one job rather
than collaborating it becomes super
hyper specialist and you
compartmentalize it's like oh so-and-so
does that to refer to them rather than
owning it together you're owning the
project together then because if it's
all you know individuals it always ends
up being like alright I'm just gonna do
my job pass it off if they're not doing
their job that I don't care I'm doing my
thing
exactly yeah that's that's tough well in
trying I got a question so you know
you're very successful entrepreneur
obviously and you've built large
companies
what are like the top three things are
or there's the top things that you you
think are required for people out there
who are trying to start something like
you did like what are some of these
things that you feel like can help build
a massive business like you have a
billion-dollar billion-dollar business
how do you make a billion-dollar
business
well okay evaluation let's rephrase that
what does it even mean to be worth a
billion dollars because you look at
netflix and they're worth a billion
dollars but they haven't profited yet
gee um you look at even Amazon I think
even Amazon is still in a deficit or
something they started to make more
money weirdly enough with Amazon Web
service so for the longest time
Amazon wasn't profiting really yeah they
weren't profiting freely years years
years and I don't know which year it was
at 2015 or fourteen I forgot which year
but Bezos because so many people were
using Amazon they needed the best
servers they needed private servers and
all that he decided okay let's let's do
redundancy servers where we build more
servers because if one server shuts down
Amazon can still run in like Colorado
because we have the servers there so
they did redundancy and it took a whole
year to build several several different
servers all across the nation for farms
server farms okay and when he went to
the board and he was talented oh no he
didn't go to the board yet he had the
engineers come to him and say okay we
finished everything and he was curious
he asked um how much is Amazon using of
all these servers no like oh just like
six or twelve percent like very little
and he had an aha moment he went to the
board he said hey let's create a
subscription amazon web servers because
we're only using a very small amount and
we have all this excess and we can make
money with just servers if you think
about it it's like genius because you're
not selling product you're not storing
anything you don't have to ship anything
it's just a subscription it's just data
yeah
and that helped them make tremendous
money and so now when you opt in to
Amazon web servers it's so impressive
because you can get like you can have
like machine learning involved in there
I mean it's crazy like it's not just a
normal it's not a basic setup like it's
very very robust and impressive so again
like going back to the valuation having
a billion dollars that's like height
that's like saying oh yeah my company is
worth a billion but
doesn't necessarily mean you're making a
billion dollars that's what the
investors who invested in your company
are projecting for you to be worth and
to make something sense know so a lot of
a lot of these companies who raise like
80 million dollars and they still don't
profit yet but then their investors will
be like yeah they're worth like a
billion dollars they can go out and say
that so it's kind of hype um thankfully
with Ipsy we were so anti hype we were
actually doing really well because we
were subscription people were paying $10
a month and three million bags are being
sold um but we weren't like we weren't
relying on that hype of being worth a
billion dollars so to go back to
everything I don't think I think if you
have the intention to build a billion
billion dollar company you don't have
the right intention in place you your
goal is mislead by numbers and what ends
up happening is if you don't meet these
numbers and these milestones oftentimes
you can lose sight of yourself and you
can burn out really fast and I always
tell people and potential business
owners and entrepreneurs don't set goals
set intentions first I think when I
started my youtube channel there was no
money in it because there is no Adsense
right but my intention was to teach I
wanted to share I want to teach when I
started epsy I wasn't I didn't have any
idea would become such a big thing but
my intention was I have this great
product idea and I want to help people
with it I think that's really important
so intention set intentions and the
second thing is look for a market gap
that's really important too because you
can have a really good product idea or
service but if it's too early on then
you miss out on that boat so you have to
be you have to know when to be ready to
launch it oftentimes so many people have
great ideas but it's too early or it's
too late so learn and observe the
different market gaps that you have and
market gaps so to bring it to bring this
into like I was like to like bring it
into my context because my viewers might
understand in 2007 there were no makeup
tutorials people if people wanted to
learn makeup videos they would either
have to go to a beauty counter and buy
products or pay for Beauty seminars or
read books and there is never something
where they can just sit at home and
watch for free and rewind
fast-forward skip and have someone
relatable speaking to them so that's a
market gap market gap is wait no one's
making these videos I'm gonna make them
so identify these market gaps in the
market I would that's one of the first
things you would say to like yeah set
the intention finding the market gap and
I guess my third one top tips
those are good tips and I think it is
important most people don't know when
they hear like oh the evaluation is a
billion dollars they don't know you're
not making a billion making like
snapchat for one there were another one
right that wasn't making dairy I don't
know what their what are they worth well
their IPO right note there they're a
public company right now but I think for
a long time they were making zero
dollars no money at all but they were
like the biggest thing in the world
because they had active users they had
millions of active users and so the idea
is like everyone wants to find the next
Facebook but for me it's like it's over
because all Facebook needs to do is just
copy it which is totally what I did yeah
yeah and there's no shame in that like
as in they don't see shame in that
because they have to look out for their
business and that's just how a cutthroat
it is China copies it too you know like
everyone's just copying each other and
that's why I always tell people don't
try and like create something that
Facebook can easily copy like look at
the future market gap if we are going
towards this decentralized market place
where money will even become
decentralized build towards that that's
gonna start happening in the next 10
years you want to build towards the
future if you want to build something
that you can sell fast and now then yeah
sure like build something that's
hyperbole and then try and find an exit
fast as you can but oftentimes when you
don't find an exit you're stuck you're
like a hamster in a wheel and you're
stuck and you're in this very old old
company that makes sense okay good
advice yeah that is good advice actually
I'm sure some people there's probably a
lot of people who are like I'm gonna get
Bitcoin I'm gonna start my own company
what do people need right now so I don't
know I think it's there you go
ninja my energy not paid for yeah I
didn't tell her to do this she just has
a voice that's worth a lot of money no
well two bitcoins I don't I don't that's
a lot
we just learned there's a finite amount
do we still have the I know we didn't
print them out the questions and stuff
do we have some stuff yeah it was super
sorry and thanks for coming it was super
last-minute dude literally David deems
me yesterday that's where we talk hey
you guys DM you we do see you a long
time ago on you had a different number
that time are you always changing your
number why is that dude I have some
crazy people man for real yeah let me
talk about that yeah let's talk about
these crazy did the crazies there there
is this one guy who came into my office
and my team they're like uh do you have
an appointment with someone here and
he's like where's Michelle and he was
like scratching himself right what was
like he's like he was just like I got
cracks machete I don't know yeah
no I don't know like and and my business
partner just sent me a picture cuz we
have security cameras are you wearing
he's like hey do you know this guy I'm
like no I don't know him right like oh
so I'm one of them
one of my co-workers I can't hook him
and like sent him really far away like
physically yeah like walked him escorted
him off the property
and I think like it was like a few days
later I was in had Instagram stories I
was going to one of my friends show he's
he he was DJing at this show and I was
gonna go and support so I when I arrived
with my other friend I hear this guy
he's like Michelle so your first
instinct when you hear your name is turn
around right so I turned around and I
remember him from the picture I'm like
oh I shouldn't same guy right and he's
like Michelle Michelle but thankfully my
friend was there was just blocking him
like totally blocking it like hey that's
not Michelle I don't know you're talking
about and they quickly like let me into
the venue and they blocked him and the
security guard was saying yeah this guy
showed up like he was here like six
hours early and when you went in he
started banging his head against the
wall I was like dude this is crazy cuz
I've been on hiatus for so long you know
like it would make sense
like you're active I was active and also
I mean not to like you know not not to
like shun anything or anything but it
was more promiscuous to like if I'm
showing more promiscuous photos of
myself okay that makes more sense but
you know like II go on my Instagram feed
it's just my cat and me and like anime
pictures and I'm so about even pictures
of you yeah dude this is crazy so I
can't even imagine other people who have
a following built on you know their
sexuality and all of that but yeah dude
there's like crazy people
I'm sure he's not crazy but you just
don't do that yeah I mean at that point
that's not even like a hardcore fan
that's like even fans I think having of
awareness to not show up and I don't
know I don't know if you added in the
whole scratching thing on purpose but
that sounds I could I don't know I could
be wrong I'm just judging right now no
idea this guy's like you just you just
don't do that like have some just have
some respect for people's spaces and I
and I feel like a lot of a lot of
viewers they they almost feel entitled
when they see online personalities like
oh I know them because they're my best
friend
and so they've I've heard horror stories
of youtubers where they would have
people like outside their block like
taking pictures of their house because
they saw maybe on their GPS like where
they were going right that's why I moved
and it still happens yeah I moved
because I was not in a gated community
and I have camera I still have footage
of people like kids coming to my house
and like taking pictures like through
the windows and stuff obviously I was
already paranoid by then so all the
things they could never see me but yeah
there's that happens all the time I mean
David had scarier story like your story
about your stalker dude yeah you and
kina and kina we had a his mascara
shared stalker why don't you share that
story you never talked about that sure
I'm pretty sure he's not watching but he
might be go ahead
but yeah so kina and I had this one
stalker on Twitter and he would put out
these like really mysterious like the
deaths the day of death shall come upon
keen like you tagged kina and I and you
just like come up with a lot of these
like creepy cryptic kind of
suja's and I just didn't really think
too much of it I was like oh this is
whatever I don't even know where this
guy is or who this guy is
so eventually kena and I we both went on
tours separate separate tours but at the
same time we were both on tour she plays
at this venue in Florida and I was gonna
play at the same venue two weeks later
so two weeks later hums by and I I roll
up you know with my gear and everything
and you know my crew and they were the
crew there they were they were like hey
David we heard that there's a stocker
guy and you know we have a picture of
him and we just wanted to let you know
that we are we know what's going on and
we'll keep an eye out for anything weird
or sketchy that may happen okay cool
awesome I'm in my green room getting
ready for the show guy a security guard
comes in he's like David he's like the
guy showed up I was like what no way and
they were like yeah he came in he had a
fake ID
he he he saw before before the tour
actually kinas shared me a web site like
and he had a mug shot he had like a
little mustache so he when he came to
the show he actually shaved off his
mustache and he showed up and the great
thing is he bought a t-shirt in a CD and
then they saw him and they caught him I
mean I'm glad they did after he bought
the t-shirt and I would have signed it
for him too so but he had a mug shot
yeah so yeah and then and then they were
like they escorted him out and that's it
yeah I was like did you guys not call
the police or anything yeah they're like
I mean he didn't have anything wrong so
we just identified him we escorted him
out and then that's all we could do just
not let him back in it was still kind of
scary because he could have waited a
block away with a gun and he could have
shot me with that that's why when the
whole Christine
machining grimmy that really affected me
a lot I stopped doing show not just for
that reason but some of the main reasons
I stopped doing I don't travel anymore I
don't do those kind of shows because I
don't know I just that that situation
really like haunted me you know because
it could it's if you think about it it's
really easy to do like the security is
there but it's like it's not hard to get
things past people right it's not like
we're going through actually I don't
know how like ariana grande tours are
like they have metal detectors and stuff
but for our shows it was never like that
crazy but it has to be now right yeah so
anyway that's just I thought it was
interesting because you brought up
something soccer related yeah no dude I
mean I think I think I do I feel like
some people they fantasize about having
a stalker you know what I mean like oh I
want a stalker
I think you think like people want to
stock quarterly Fifty Shades of Grey if
I haven't seen it either but like I've
read the wiki of it but I'm pretty sure
of that Christian Grey guy or whatever
his name is if he was a broke-ass guy
like yeah it would not be a romantic
story but the fact that he's a CEO and
super rich people fantasize that like
yeah he's a stalker it's so hard like no
that is not yeah I think you should not
romanticize whatever you what if your
stalker guy that show up to your office
he was like gorgeous like just the
best-looking dude looks clean his
business suit you just I need to see
Michelle I need to see a show and even
his voice is just like do you fake real
buzz would you have still send it okay
thank you would you still have sent him
away
because it looks matter in that case
because you're not gonna judge him in
the same way right even your co-workers
you're right looks do you matter
yeah if you don't have business with me
but even if he sure I've been a nice
Burberry I was trying to go my expensive
brand I don't know Burberry suit that's
an expensive one I feel like that would
just be plaid like he's also came up
okay but that's it happen and that was
your stalker and you saw him in another
event and he showed up it's a little
weird but it's like this gorgeous dude
expensive suit would you still have sent
him away that's my question or would you
have given him the benefit of the doubt
and had a little talk with him
would have seen just what is your
business here oh really yeah the most
gorgeous person even if the most
gorgeous persons like money man I got it
and speaking of time we're about to wrap
up but we want to get one Twitter
questioning with you at least and since
I've said three lines this whole podcast
I figure I should pitch it to you
go for it somebody asked so Michelle
what's next that's your question she
talked a lot about what what was in the
past sure yeah so you know we kind of
want to see cuz you know you're like you
said your channel is like you're
starting to use it now there's music
coming on so and you're like you said
you and made an analogy where it's kind
of like the beginning of a party people
come to it you know so the party is
starting up so you know how are you
kicking off this party in and out truck
coming in ten minutes I don't know I'm
just I don't know I don't have a master
plan I'm just really like you're doing
what you're doing currently right with
that but then you said you which I
thought was interesting because like you
said I'm an uber driver right and you
know I have to show up and drive but you
have created another uber but you want
to go back to driving a little bit you
missed driving a little bit wanna cruise
okay so you just just for your own
because that's what you love doing cuz
you started it because you love doing it
right you want to get back into making
videos or is it to make some other kind
of what else do you want what else are
you actually learning how to make music
like singing but like making beats
alright computer no I'm not I'm just
adding more to the the world to the
world yeah yeah I'm just trying to
acquire new skills I'm just I'm also
doing a lot of mentorship I'm mentoring
a lot of young entrepreneurs helping
them with their businesses need to hire
you to mentor me you've helped me a
little bit boy I spoken with like other
Asian content creators and they're
always talking about how they reached
out to you and you
like welcome them with open arms and
stuff that's something that I've had
like yeah well that's good random
craters see she's og man yeah I'm Snoop
Dogg yeah okay well I mean we didn't get
many Twitter questions in but I guess
that's about our time so again thanks
for being here do you want to plug
anything no for yourself yourself all
right well thank you milk also my friend
who I've been mentoring launched these
really cool phone covers called hype
slides yep you can find it on Instagram
type in hype slides it's a phone cover
and it's very practical because you can
just do this oh is that why and it looks
funny because earlier you were taking a
picture nice you can wear it Junko
laughs what are your a socials michelle
phan follow michelle at michelle phan on
fun I keep saying fan it's easier Phin
on Instagram all your other so shows
it's on there also drink ninja milk
support support I'm not chained by the
way I'm not paying one question quick
question you know the music stuff that
you're doing though
that's like skin I think that's
something that's interesting hello
somatic comm somatic thematic hello
somatic calm and you can have access to
all these great music for your content
without having to worry about takedowns
because article 13 and 17 is gonna
you all that's in the UK especially
right yeah yeah once the UK approves
that it's gonna trickle down to the u.s.
really cool well that's a whole nother
topic we'll have you back this year here
no we'd have to come to you because
you're far so I also uh follow us at at
off the pill on Twitter at off the pill
podcast on Instagram we still say it
every single podcast we will one day
have them be the same thing but until
then almost there that was uh that was
our first la podcast it was not bad
well kinks we got a workout we're kinky
but let's do the proper outro alright so
how we end these is you're basically
just breathe into the mic and three two
one
these ones don't have smell yet because
no one has done that yeah