hey guys so growing up I was a huge game
I know I know it's hard to believe being
that I was a very skinny small nerdy
Asian kid growing up but really I was a
big game I mean every single free second
that I had I was either on a gaming
console or a computer or a Gameboy of
some sort I would say about 50% of my
childhood was me playing video games 25%
was playing sports the other 25% was
making videos and the last remaining 5%
was me neglecting my math homework
don't get me wrong I definitely don't
play as many video games as I used to
because you know I'm not a kid anymore
I'm a mature adult so anyway if you play
or played as many video games as I did
you've definitely heard this before it's
one of the most irritating things you
could ever hear as a gamer why are you
wasting your time if you know if you
have something like that in your life
get rid of them not because what they
say they're what that voice is so
irritating usually coming from your
parents or girls I'm not trying to be
sexist I know a lot of girls play video
games too but let's be real it's more
guys it's it's a fact although there's a
lot of guys that will question your
video game playing too but I mean those
are just losers that don't play video
games because they have no lives right
guys there are three main reasons why I
think people say that video games are
always the time one they're not good at
them so they don't like playing that -
they like playing them but they have no
time so they don't want you to either or
the worst of all three they judge you
because you have an interest in
something that they have no interest in
which is so judgmental and makes
absolutely no sense to me that's like
saying hey mom why do you paint your
nails that's always a timer hey dad why
do you watch football and that's a waste
of time or hey or no that's a great show
I missed that show feel better now if
you get the point I actually believe
that video games are good for kids or
anyone we do games aren't a waste of
time they're good for you they teach a
life lesson and I think it's about time
that our society starts to appreciate
that for all the gamers the geeks the
Nerds the so-called losers I'm standing
up for you the next time somebody says
gaming is a waste of time like a friend
or a parent or a boyfriend or girlfriend
probably not the last two because you're
a nerd haha I'm gonna stand up for you
and let them know the truth and tell
them all the reasons why I'm so close to
the camera I'm out of focus all the
reasons why
gaming is actually good
first let me start off with the most
obvious one hand-eye coordination a lot
of video games required quick reflexes
especially first-person shooters like
Conor strong Gears of War halos modern
warfare attica I can't think of a better
way to teach hand-eye coordination I
mean how else would I be able to do
something like this candy too easy ah
problem solved if you don't run into any
difficult and it's just like life if
your life has no problems you're not
really living it that is deep I just
mean that oh that is a straight-up
annoying person's caption for their
selfie on Instagram anyway I'm off
talking both videogames and life you're
gonna run into problems a true gamer
never gives up problem solves until he
figures out how to win trial and error
looking for patterns keeping a 10 - he
gets better and better for example in
real life if you're taking a calculus
class at you're failing for you like a
video game try to problem solve never
give up and eventually you will succeed
if you know you're not ready and you
can't beat that level then lower the
difficulty take ceramics camping don't
be a camp for all you gamers out there
you already know in a camper but for
those of you that don't a Kaffir is
basically someone that will wait around
and hide and so their victims come to
them rather than actually playing the
actual game this is such an important
life lesson
yeah sure be a camper and enjoy the safe
route hide behind a bush or a couch your
whole life but if you want to have an
exciting life don't just be a camper who
just waits around to opportunity come
see it's not just lame to people it's
irritating you get out there and you get
go after what you want in life helping
is boring rice storm the front go go go
counter-strike references hackers
hackers aren't respected sure it give me
a hacker in life and cheat your way to
the top you and everyone else around you
knows that you have to get there and the
thing is technology is so good now that
if you're hacking you're gonna get
caught dare I say it
and so we'll make her dance bands but
good day
nobody likes a rage quitter you know
those guys they quit the game out of
frustration go go go settle quit if you
play games especially online you know
the feeling of wanting to rage quit
don't even lie and as irritating as a
rage quit or is it still teaches you a
life lesson sometimes you get so upset
and frustrated that you just have to
stop when you're in a place in life when
you're so unhappy with the way things
are going take a break take some time to
cool off and come back even stronger
money management whether it's coins
dollars minerals or whatever video game
seats you want to spend it whines for
example if you're gonna buy a knob you
have to member to save money for ammo
because that was pretty expensive not to
mention your secondary weapon like a
Diigo or something and we'd even get to
the part about the equipment like your
caliper and he'll made your frag grenade
your double flash bangs and/or smoke
grenade and stun damn I really am in
there if you get any of those references
you're awesome micromanage when you have
a bunch of Units you don't just auto
attack like some new you assign
different units to do different things
yet another life lesson each person has
their own specific purpose micromanage
each person to do what they're best at
that's efficiency by all and every
first-person shooter will teach you that
you're more likely to die if you get
shot in the head than the arm or the leg
okay maybe that one might seem obvious
but if you think about it it's probably
obvious because you learned that from a
video game or a movies Trula if you get
shot in the head GG bro multiplayer to
me this is one of the most valuable life
lessons you can learn from video games
most if not all video games these days
are multiple multiplayer teaches you
that if you have a bad team and you
don't work together you're probably
gonna lose you can't always do
everything by yourself the bottom line
is there's no I in the spelling of
teamwork just like there's no I in the
spelling of multiplayer with the bottom
line there it is and the sooner you
learn that the sooner we can all work
together like a multiplayer unit and
convince people that video games aren't
always the time new games are important
to teaching people how to really start
living life by not setting up camp but
going after the things they really want
without having to cheat their way to the
top even if they have to rage quit every
now and then they learn to problem-solve
and never give up until they get there
and once they do they'll already have
past any problems that come along their
way with the quickest reflexes the world
has ever seen because gaming is more
than just a game its life and like I
always said since I was a little kid
your life has no problems you're not
really playing the
wait if life has no problems the game is
not really playing the lute life what
when the life is a problem games our
problem is life is a game the problem is
if your game has problems to get back to
the store that you got it from life is
like a Xbox or chocolates
okay if your life has no problems you're
not really living in and that is the
bottom line
son of a I quit I quit hey guys thank
you so much for watching if you want to
see the previous video click the one in
the left if you want to see the last
blog pick the one on the right if you
want to see the origin of two working
before anyone else did it before Miley
Cyrus click the one on the bottom
working history is what it is it's the
first work just a quickie or the other
ones up to you I don't know