do you enjoy picking up random strangers
in your car are you struggling to find a
job or perhaps you just want to make
extra cash did you get to keep a
fraction of do you wear way too much
cologne well then tuber driving could be
the perfect job for you
being at uber driver could set you for
life our studies show that the average
tuber driver makes $20 an hour $20
that's five dollars more than Bernie
Sanders makes or something like that of
course for every dollar you make you
have to pay your share to tuber because
I mean we are the ones doing all the
work after all
and you'll have to pay for your own gas
that's your problem not ours and you do
have to use your own personal car and
we're not responsible for car
depreciation and not to mention taxes
that's on YouTube oh and also there are
some minor expenses that you have to
take care of as well at tuber we do
require all of our drivers to provide at
least two Fiji waters gum an iPhone
charger for every single ride but the
iPhone charger can be the one with the
shortest cord so it's actually a lot
cheaper than you think
here at uber we're all about quality and
safety for our customers is why we
perform extensive background checks on
all of our drivers all you have to do is
send in a picture of yourself and our
team scans the entire background for
anything bad and if they don't find
anything you pass the background check
welcome to tube or you're a driver
once you become a driver the next step
is to choose your style of drive there's
so many different styles to choose from
you just have to find the style that
fits you bet for example we have the
classic personal driver who's that one
guy who has way too many personal
questions I see you got a lot of bags
back there you're doing a lot of
traveling today where you headed to
California oh well for just some
business stuff nice is that like
entertainment stuff like culinary stuff
I am sell stocks really stocks make a
lot of money you live in a nice house
instead where you headed to what's your
social security number you want to make
some extra tips we had the sob story
driver yeah it's just been really tough
lately no I'm just tired all the time
just got off a 12-hour shift kind of pay
my rent this month you know and
hopefully be able to save up for some
food had twins last month we have the
creepy driver the one who doesn't
acknowledge you or say anything the
entire ride
as we mentioned earlier the way too much
cologne driver oh I'm sorry it does it
stink in here here the Bluetooth driver
the one who talks incredibly loud in
another language the entire riot
you know me sit on em well look at I
hate boys s : I yup the road rager just
cut me off like that
stay on your side of the lane be either
he's on drugs or a really sleepy driver
the I just watched a fast and furious
movie driver driver who thinks he
doesn't need navigation I've been on the
street before must have moved it
somewhere the driver who doesn't know
how to use navigation do you know how to
get back to the navigation is it the one
says camera and the driver who only
listens to navigation my house is coming
up right here
oh we just passed it nope GPS says we
got six more miles and so much more the
possibilities are endless
speaking of different styles uber offers
a bunch of different kind of tubers that
people can order so for all of our
drivers you can choose which kind of to
where you drive just like our
competitors we have all the original
options tuber XL to 4x and tour black
but we did modify them a little bit to
make us more original rather than
meaning extra large tuber XL now stands
for extra little and this is for all
your drivers out there who have a lot of
stuff in your car so you can only fit
extra little passengers not really sure
what X stands for for our competitors
but with tuber and you choose 2 bar X
you're only going to be picking up your
X's which is perfect for all your
drivers out there who already camp
outside of your ex's house because if
they call you you're already there the
black option actually seen the low -
edgy for us so we actually called it
tuber wannabe black and this option
comes with a little ghetto Asian girl
who makes basketball references hey yo
what's up missing your lone ace the only
tuba driver like a big rock ready to go
cut to the whole isolation alright let's
go and you don't have a car we have
other options for tuber as well tuber
motorcycle where you ride in the back of
a motorcycle tuber bike where you write
on the back page of a bike tuber skate
tuber scoop tuber this thing that was
popular for a day and of course one of
our more recently popular tuber you
where you just ride the back of a
youtuber wow this is a great club and
what a great strong system you have
thanks it's all because of my subs here
Kevin whoa
some convenient and simple wait where we
going right now to the top all right
let's go see with tuber you can make all
of your dreams come true whether it's
making more money or letting random
people into your personal space we're
just saving the world by providing a
cheaper way of transportation tuber is
job for you so what are you waiting for
sign up with tuber today and this
distant a gunman is holding down a
downtown parking structure roads are
blocked off and people are being asked
to evacuate but they are unable to get
to the car so we will be keeping you
live updated you know what that means
time for tuber to save the day - super
martyr - for more - were super
motorcycle
Oh
[Music]
get this hair chicken table you