Philip J van so good to see you
hold it do you see what's wrong with
this picture
two guys hugging putting nothing wrong
with that when you got a bromance
bromance the expression of affection
between two males were not necessarily
attracted to each other the word
bromance is a compound word combining
brother and romance which came from the
romance we all know built the pyramids
the act of bromancing or bromance
dication originated during the Roman
Empire on the battlefield when two
soldiers would celebrate a victory
nowadays bromance happens all around the
world dude is such a cruel cruel world
a dark petri dish died
sorry bro what was it yeah
no let me bro balls looks really good it
is have a cigarette saw you
Rose rose flew low for the food plus 9
minus 3 what hi yo what's up J long time
no see man looking good bro it's a new
haircut bro cat is man thanks for
noticing that is really this is this if
it's really nice this is Seoul beautiful
it's so soft it's like it's like eyebrow
hair that's really nice
so the weather's been nice
romance
I mean bowling Phil what do you like
basketball oh good it has been so sunny
yeah man California the home of the
cactuses yeah