hold it this is wrong in this picture
police you as well with this guy be
trying way too hard to be cool resulting
in the opposite he got more swarm the
way one presents him herself in an
uncool loser like fashion also known to
be the opposite of swag some similar or
related words are looser lame
undesirable to expose are gynecomastia
not cool wannabe whack the number six
the one guy who started so far who is
probably going to get this video because
I'm gonna show him right now
[Applause]
if you have two swag chances are you
have more swaggy situations you should
probably avoid ya laters baby a Late
Show let's go Kobe
let's go Kobe 102 94 is the final walk
so DJ Victor jr. head you shut up I'm
tryna watch Bob girl
Wow yeah guys would you shut up I tried
my hardest more more more more MORE
- ah - look at that sunset man - aw poor
shake it see it there's so much
pollution small I don't know if that's
blue she looks like hey you're all in
you're still in its doing now you're