hey guys so I know I never make videos
like this a lot of you been asking what
does ytf what does ytf stamp anyone
notice the ytf what's a stigma - what's
ytf and maybe a lot of you haven't even
heard of ytf before and if you look at
my past videos really closely you can
see a lot of secret 1tx hidden in each
video anyway YC f stands for yesterday
today breath and we're going to be
having our first concert in my own at
hawaii that's not in tune and i know
it's not the best place our first
concert but it really means a lot to me
because that's where I came from you
know that's where I first started
youtubing and it's always been my dream
to perform on a stage in Hawaii ever
since I was out and to finally be able
to make this happen it's like a dream
come true for me and I just wanted to
thank you guys so much for everything
that you've done for me everything that
you made possible in my life is because
of you guys I really appreciate
yeah those are never-before-seen clips I
made before YouTube even existed but
anyway here at a waffle come to our show
here anywhere else in the world
leave a comment where you want to see
why to get next wait I didn't even I
didn't even tell you guys who is my tía
you
you mean like this
yeah I know
what he hell global.com so again thank
you guys so much for making one of my
childhood dreams come true if you want
to know more about my tía go to Isaiah
Global doc maybe you don't and you're
sick of this video and sick of me
talking here's a little preview of my
next video yeah I write it that had
nothing to do with anything that's just
me in baby form so cute right what
happened though