shhh hey yo what up Derek what's up man
and you guys finish the rewriting idea
yet it's what we're working on right now
that's why we need your lights use all
of ours already well just to let you
guys know I bought these LEDs from
Taiwan they get kind of hot so just turn
them on when you need them or they'll
blow out door even got it yeah yeah dude
I'm sure it's fine what's the last
training it'd be anyways we don't know
yet yeah I'm trying to figure that out
right now I mean it has to be the
biggest trend of the year like last time
remember
how could I forget well as long as the
idea is not about planking I think we
should be up seriously what look if you
guys are just gonna troll me again I'm
Adi
nobody's trolling you dude I mean if
anything the only thing that's trolling
you right now is that outfit my outfit
hey you guys remember where the Warriors
have been 73 and 9 season though
historic season they made it all the way
to the finals and then blew a 3-1 lead
really you guys are gonna rub this in my
face again that was last season a but it
still happened this year yeah yeah it
did didn't it hey you know that could be
it we didn't use that yet what the
biggest trend that happened this year
the Warriors going a 3-1 lead it was it
was huge it was historic oh yeah yeah
that's right
everyone was talking about it kind of
became a meme than it kinda yeah you
guys can't be serious I wasn't even the
biggest China this year you guys are
just saying that because you know it
annoys well fine what else is there
thumb the Olympics it's already in it
Trump winning the election already got
that one man in can challenge please
that was a first thing we thought of I
know the PPAP guy that guy was the
biggest [ __ ] for sure the what who the
PPAP guy Penn pineapple apple Penn the
hell was up on the asian dude dancing he
was like the biggest trend is here I
have a pen I have a pineapple uh-huh
that's something you meet up at PPAP guy
was huge apparently not if everybody
doesn't know what it is you know I'm not
falling for this just remember that
these LEDs they get hot so just turn
them off or blow on them or something
stop worrying about it already dude we
got it yeah dude you worry too much
seriously you're such a worrier
yeah you are you're worried about your
LEDs from Taiwan yeah so all three of
them what are you trying to get it cuz
when those three LEDs from Taiwan get
too hot and blow on them because you're
worse over no one might consider you to
be a really you guys did all that for a
warrior Punk oh not just that yeah you
are a worrier but more specifically a
worrier that blows three two one lead
it's just like LEDs the spell it but you
know what yeah I'm taking these back
come on don't be like that it's just a
joke wait okay we're gonna do your PAP
thing for the ending just stay cause we
need your lights fine as long as there's
no more warrior jokes promise I promise
okay that was the last one good I'm
serious better be
Oh more warrior nope not one single one
for the rest of the entire base there's
another joke Andrey Ryan isn't there
might be this is a militarized police
force respondus is iPhone 7 battery
[Music]
yeah we didn't have the budget to get
the real Rock so
[Music]
white fans what about the black man shot
is offensive is offense wrong it's a
wall
it's a fence walk and walk and walk
[Music]
oh yeah almost had that one told you
guys there and burnout
do you do now I don't know you know what
I'm happy you didn't finish I know you
guys weren't gonna do the ppapi deal ass
anyways yes we were we kind of planned
on oh you weren't I know you guys were
gonna bring up something about the words
losing the 3 2 1 lead again I'm not
stupid Ryan I know your patterns and to
be honest so does your audience and I
hate to be the one to break it to you
but someone's gotta say it's getting
really old now I'll do that um that kind
of hurts
I mean like for the record I actually
was gonna do this whole pad thing and
use your idea but oh maybe you're right
it's all getting too old too predictable
well maybe I was being a little harsh
no you're right it's the same thing over
and over enough is enough it's all one
big pattern pattern
you're right all along it was the
biggest trend of the year what I'm not
falling if you spell up a path it's P P
a P P P a P is the pattern if this
pattern continued what would be the next
letters T a a P I don't know what are
you trying to get at it's a a a this is
the biggest trend of the year Derek was
right so was i see P P a P is actually a
song mocking the Warriors losing a 3-1
lead you see what both right really
could you guys see the pattern yet this
is the exact way that the Warriors start
off the finals three P's to 1a and in
the exact same order
win-win lost win followed by loss loss
loss Derek what are you doing I'm over
this but we need you we need your lights
not done yet yeah and what are you mad
about we were both right this time not
just me it's still a troll I don't know
how you did it but you somehow connected
PPAP dissing on the Warriors didn't make
it that way I'm just pointing out the
obvious you know what forget it I'm out
wait okay fine we'll do it your way
yeah sure we are I'm being serious we
need your lights to finish it so we'll
finish it your way and to prove it well
let you finish this entire video on your
own you can do the countdown and
everything we won't say or do anything
else until the video is over from this
point on really okay all right and now
for the biggest trend of 2016 in three
two one
what in three two one
what what am i doing something wrong I
got something on my face three two one
what what is the big deal on my saying
something wrong fine three two right
three two one wait what's the big deal
three two one three two one three two
one all still there in point