[Music]
today is no ordinary day little gang and
that is because today is my one-year
vlog of are see what a journey man what
a time to be alive
oh my god I'm excited ok enough talking
let's get this log stash I have been
vlogging you good I have been vlogging
for 365 days one year of vlogging every
single day bro what have I done what am
i doing
though yeah Brandon you don't worry it's
either I'm behind I'm behind the camera
no need to pants up by the way I can't
wait any longer bro it's out in
celebration just one second thank you in
celebration of Jesus yeah I know he
wants to just celebrate with us oh Jesus
oh god it's celebration of vlogging for
one year straight we were dropping this
exclusive maverick t-shirt for 48 hours
only can you shut the front door no you
you guys both were being little disaster
magnets this morning I still love you
though okay what anyways you got the
maverick logo the logo that literally
means and it represents my entire life
and what I stand for
giant em the 365 for every day we've
been slogging on the back of the
rocketship is y'all know this bro we are
headed to the top every day we work hard
we follow our passions we dream big be
in life through the legs of possibility
okay we are getting the universe
Thank You free that's support mapper I
appreciate them y'all know where to get
it look with balkon slash shop again 48
hours so go quick look who it is oh this
is this is the diamond play button for
hitting 10 million subscribers we're
doing this right now bro bro this is
crazy dude when I first started YouTube
it's good leave here for a second when I
first started youtube I never thought he
would come where I would hit 10 million
subscribers I thought it was possible
but I never realized we do it this quick
this quick the fastest YouTube channel
ever to do it I'll address that later
cuz Jake seemed to think he did it but
no
can't open it what did you do what did
you do
I lock it why did you do that even on my
big day my big day big day
I had multiple big days I wish I was
joking
sometimes the do skits in sketches and
stuff this is not a joke this kid I saw
you by the fridge last night I know you
were here literally oh the camera was
out I'm like give me the keys he goes
I'm not telling you where the keys are
off the vlog
[Music]
no no yeah we're doing off the vlog [ __ ]
where the keys look what is this vlog
trained in do it was supposed to be my
big day right you know what I need tools
to open this box we're going to the
store Evan and guess whose dress I'm
soft yet you bro wait what do you mean
why McClellan's my big day
[Music]
hold up what the back up reverse now
that chip plan bro look at this
Pomeranian there's a new chip palm on
the Block ship palm you best watch your
eyes going to savage taking over I just
want everyone watching to know like to
not be fooled by your size boat you're a
bully you're a bully only against all
people that's the majority of the world
[Music]
step low gate that the world's made for
y'all
nice oh wow he's hitting me deeper now I
feel bad what if no you have to take a
look we gotta go good - why would you
tell me that as I'm standing here in the
right lane because it look like you're
standing in right left straight centered
and boom you go straight axonal you bend
down you've been down longer than I have
I've been down the whole life how long
have you been down song it's a Drake
song I'll be nothing longer cut them try
said buy some shoulders of Steel broke
can you please park somewhere I don't
know do jumping jacks just please Park
[Music]
oh yeah no just go go go go market space
is taken
you've been cussing a lot in this vlog
it's my big day okay
I'm gonna need you to chill fudge thank
you no see yeah you do apparently give
many fudges because you stop cussing we
made it do you want to do the thing
driving at it with these digs hey will
ya Charlie oh you like it
I'm so sorry on one today bro we need to
find like some destructive [ __ ] what
about a crowbar crowbar would do
leverage right but uh what about a
plunger all a plunger yeah yeah cuz
Evans uh pushed
[Music]
bingo check it we got mallets bro look
at his mallet actually like that but I'm
gonna hold it cuz I'm gonna trust you
with it no go ahead and let go go thank
you yeah no we hit the jackpot crowbars
bro
I'm deck this looks good to say we do it
Oh devil Halloween's coming up but
definitely one of these some rope dude
like who knows what we could do with
some rope how is that gonna open the box
oh yeah where's the card guess you have
to five that too the only reason I'm
okay with him running away is cuz that
dent the universe looks so cool funny
bro you've never hit stuff you never hit
stuff all of a sudden you're hiding
stuff Hollywood's changed you haven't
used to in that coconut head looking
yours
people love coconut water pools on tools
on tools I'm feeling good O'Malley you
still don't wanna tell me where the key
is
you still know deserted we could end
this right now what if I mess up the
play button you would feel horrible if I
mess up my party but I'm gonna start
beating this thing this is no effect on
me oh no bro Evan see oh this table cost
me $80,000 first off don't think that's
accurate second off you should have been
being it on the table
[Applause]
[Music]
how's the play but not ruined at this
point though how do you meal is good
hey are you enjoying yourself is it
still what bro it's like so close
what's so far I'm have to turn on the
Jets bro like we took a little meal
break fine I'm gonna open this box if
it's the last thing I do now have you
done it first though surprise our good
bro hey you made food for yourself
yeah but thank you me as soon as I'm
done with this meal I I'm gonna destroy
this box
[Music]
it's almost open guys I don't understand
why you're helping me all you have to do
is give me the keys like you are an evil
dwarf you are an evil dwarf
[Music]
you noticed where is it [ __ ] where is
it maybe do all that I hate you so much
right now bro ah I knew I saw you like
playing in the refrigerator no I don't
know no bro I'm actually I'm smiling but
I kind of saw a man coming go to my
other friend's house man
mark mark oh hi mark oh hi mark
this is YouTube black button no clothes
not really put it up mark there gonna be
like a skin wrap a diamond play button
why because then it terminated
subscribers oh no time where is it sure
I got you mark this is like this is a
big deal bro this is a 48 hour exclusive
maverick merger exclusive 10th the
universe Marky damn damn all rocket hey
wait what school you go to
I'm not gonna lie bro I'm not just
saying this this is my favorite
exclusive drum I like this like like
it's a bit different than the stuff you
can put now it's just that good good bro
y'all know where to do I'm not even
gonna plug anyways I just came to drop
that off and tell you about my door
problems
honey no I'm scared of spiders and I
thought like facing my fear would be
cool and hold him mad commendable ah no
I'm good I'm good why not just got just
got plenty of good I need to deal with
today well that the universe then
universe bro I gotta go to the Georgia
South you know about diamond play
buttons diamond play buttons ha ha ha
it's gone yeah no but but I didn't give
you a piece of merch so there you go
Thanks what happened here diamond play
buddy and why does this look like you
was from the movie Fight Club
so you leave right after right but yeah
right after that cool I don't hate you
McCarley
I just like you I'll take that Logan I
gotta find this bro I'm gonna stop
looking that's a hint I'll take it
here's what we know it's not gonna be
anywhere higher than like brother keys
I have it I'm gonna destroy this place
the Lydia's gonna have to clean up
ever seen you open that drawer it is
hungry oh yes yo came with a YouTube
dude dear Logan Paul at a hundred
thousand we thought not bad that's a
healthy new channel at 1 million we
thought wow this creators pretty awesome
ten million at this point we're actually
scratching our heads how on earth did
you do that 10 million subscribers isn't
just a lot of people it's more than the
entire population in New York City my
gosh that's facts the fact is you're no
longer just a great channel you're a
movement you're a movement I love that
you've clearly touched a nerve in the
world and you found a legion of fans who
expect and receive great things from
your spot we hope you'll accept this
diamond crate award as a woefully
inadequate token of our appreciation and
our respect for what you've accomplished
and inspire us every day keep it coming
you're sincerely Susann CEO youtube no
no no no I'm doing this bro Paul
congratulations for surpassing 10
million subscribers
honestly this dude like holding this in
my hand right now and not tossing it is
like whoa how are you not supposed to
get fingerprints on this though okay
uh I actually no it's not yeah well this
sucks I'm leaving okay well in that case
I'm gonna do my thank-yous and a couple
things I want to say not trying to be
cocky but I've received a lot of awards
and trophies in my life but this is the
one definitely I'm most proud of the
diamond play button man be jealous
because um what ever since I was young
creating has been my number one passion
over academics sports I just wanted to
like make stuff in the fact that ten
million plus people now like 11.5 or
something have absorbed it and I'm
subscribed to my youtube channel bro
I actually holding it and not seeing any
YouTube videos is incredible but to be
honest guys this this is us this is 100%
us I owe it to you guys the low gang for
absorbing and watching my stuff I've
said this before but the most valuable
thing I think you can give someone now
and it's 2017 is your time right and the
fact that you guys spend your time
watching me my that is a kid to the
Logan we are and have been confirmed to
be the fastest the fastest Channel to
hit 10 million subscribers advert it
took us 333 days since the very first
video on the channel said before that
was a three hundred forty days I was
wrong because I was including music
videos that was just the amount of video
that 333 days yo and I know my brother's
been saying like that he was the fastest
biddin channel with that he was the
fastest growing channel he even even
said it in his new song take a look best
YouTube channel to hit 10 million wrong
Jake bro I love you and you're my
brother
but you're not dog like I love you so
much
but I got to take this one probably but
plus also you're two years younger than
me bro like you're killing it man when I
was 20 I was also killing it get the
scallion broke he had actually 200,000
subscribers by the time he posted his
first vlog but dude like who's counting
actually me with that say hello gang
that is the vlog I want to thank you
guys for this you mean the world to find
I started the blog without pants I don't
need pants now that is the blog my new
goal is to hit 50 million subscribers
into you we can do it gonna do it for
sure if you're not part of the low gay
make sure to subscribe I said we are
live and do not forget most importantly
copier new exclusive 48 hour maverick
murf d'ahhhh that's the universe what we
do every single day you see it in the
vlogs maybe we are changing the world
every day one day at a time
well Logan pole cop slash shop or
Lincoln viola gang I love y'all no see
you tomorrow take it easy tell me how
[Music]
No