[Music]
why did you stop as you guys know that
was my home last night yeah got the
blankets pillows and everything still
looking at the pizza on the ground
that's kind of gross but it's meat
lovers so it's chill but yeah guys this
pumpkin is rotting so we gotta just
exhaust all the possible content we can
make with these such as a stabbing Sachi
is making a giant pumpkin spice latte so
just smashing inside the pumpkin that's
not gonna going YouTube Oh life goal I
think so also today we got cameras
installed all around the house security
cameras everywhere follow me day one
camera gate to camp Boyer camera Rotch
camera Oh was that enough camera and
like 19 other cameras the point is we
got cameras skiing everywhere so if
you're a bad guy and you're watching my
vlogs first off don't be a bad guy
second off if you try to rob me I will
kill you not joking oh look at there's
so many cameras they're all alive look
at this one there's us oh you can hear
me subscribe enjoy the low game get your
macho look of all that comes lash up hey
he's always innovating the plugs always
bros hi how are you dude yeah I was
thinking the same thing every day I ask
myself how am I going to dent the
universe today I think I have an idea
but hi I just wanted to say hi and now
you're running away okay are you good
why what you talking where you going are
you afraid of Daddy huh help me I'm
trying to have a conversation I will Sun
you cut oh honey you got some balls
anyways here's the idea so I was
thinking today's my dad's birthday he's
turning 54 hey happy birthday dad your
old I'm singing if we lick lift the
forklift up through the air and sort of
like dangle some
thing beneath it we could drive down the
street and just be like like posting bro
I'm talking some King Queen sitting on a
throne text on a forklift you know I
mean so we gotta get rope we gotta get a
piece of furniture or yo [ __ ] sick
like what okay first off we need the
proper chair right this can't be just
some other like foo-foo chair kind of
like me hey I'm gonna put this on the
forklift yeah bro oh but but it's so
nice I know
it's still gonna be nice you'll be on a
forklift no I'm a different breed well
I'm actually freaking out yo you know
what the best part about this is the
Gucci make sure to tag me on the video
at Logan ball okay so you got the two
forklifts on the forklift we have to get
a piece of wood to set across it that
you can put the chair on but here's what
the physics come in here's with the
physical here's where the physics here's
where that you got this I believe in you
here's where the physics come in there's
gonna be a lot of weight right in the
center of the to force right here
there's nothing underneath it so the
piece of wood has got to be durable like
that can not can not break and people
could die and I don't want that oh that
would be good click babe I have no IDE
we can't have that we can't have a might
work bro like you will fall 20 feet and
die oh I want that
the first time in my life early I hate
you early everywhere everywhere watches
take me up Brendan hey we're going up I
got the dopest neighbors in the game
the world is mine I have a forklift in a
chair and a nice chair at that oh here
we go
oh he's pushing me up oh my gosh I'm so
high up literally if I fell I would
break my tailbone look I'm not scared of
heights that's not the issue the issue
is that I could just slip off at any
moment like the board on metal is a
slipper he'd probably look ridiculous
right now
aka my whole life I mean I could touch
it but I'm not gonna yeah if I just like
relax and just chill and focus on how
dope this couch is I'm good I'm showing
my she's actually sick all right bring
me down captain yeah nice work bro
that was fun you went all the way up I
couldn't oh really oh that was all the
way higher you know what sucks though
like we don't know what it looks like
bro we're know in a film it's mean you
Lydia's uploading footage somewhere yeah
top LA bro and it gets dark out so it
just doesn't do it justice so cuz I'm a
good vlogger I'm a good low gang man
Masterman I'm gonna cut the footage that
we're gonna shoot it tomorrow morning of
doing the same thing and we're gonna go
a little harder because we have did
[Music]
ya see set me free you give me death
there ain't no other choices when I lay
down and go to sleep I keep on hearing
voices little woof is in my head man
this you fight the lawyer by nobody that
designer baby pick your foot
Hey
[Music]
yeah if we come
Hey
here we come
we come yo you bought that a Harley yeah
you girl you you suck bro look at
yourself take a good look at yourself in
the mirror oh and just say it's everyday
bro cuz you shot I knew this would
happen
I knew you were gonna go and do some I'm
the favorite sodas oh I'm gonna over TV
spent all my money oh yeah you get it I
called it yesterday's vlog I'm sure Jake
is gonna go like way above and beyond be
like an overachiever I love my parents
I'm gonna buy my dad a gift for
clickbait well uh-huh forget you Jake
cuz I'm the better son I got it must
fall then what's it about
so let's go to dinner with our parents
and love them where's mom in the car my
mom's here jus oh my gosh it's so crazy
I'm a wrecked yeah I'm gonna go to
dinner with my parents celebrate my
dad's birthday
smack Jake in the face a little bit hug
my mom just real good stuff it's nice
when we can all get together and just
[Music]
make do this is dope I love the Eddie
bro oh snap oh yo see you here in Los
Angeles that's to move dog oh man I'm
glad I didn't get one still I'm not
changing my mind about that your valet
yes sir could you could you just put it
on top of the blue car right there
you're cool just put it on top of it all
right we got it now that we're all here
I think it's time to ask God Adam
Charlie or for his birthday
yeah bro that was my idea when I had
wisdom teeth taken out flashback video
is 10 million views of our eyes dad's
motorcycle nice and bro I got him a
[ __ ]
I got I got to Harlem you got me hard
yeah but I had to return it just now
because I thought about Jake I had to
just return it just now actually giving
it to me no your fradulent and oh oh and
he's not he's not fragile why I got a
y-you got a one-up me bro like why you
got to always get the cool gifts with
our parents bro chill mom is wearing the
my bracelet oh she won't know yes he is
this is my buddy
your mom was like Wilson Sigma Harley
you can find these two cohorts yeah
we're good solo gang that is the vlog
thank you guys for watching if you're
not a part of the low game make sure to
subscribe I make it late we do dumb
stuff with I'm letting my mom hold the
camera we do dumb stuff we put chairs on
forklifts so that that's hit the
subscribe button in the face for me and
copier maverick Murchie Logan Paul calm
slash shop or link in description we
just get a quick family hug I love all
[Music]
yeah if we come
what wait hold up what why you're just
hitting yourself right just smack me up
in the face