what's your favorite i don't know sexual
position
oh my god you can't ask this well what
if i had to say it'd be called the pile
driver
this mo it was crazy bro let me tell you
what happened so the dude is standing up
right and he puts his legs
my god oh your boy is back in the saddle
hey yo good morning little guy what's
poppin
all right listen guys i'm getting right
into it as you may have heard later this
month uh the ksi versus logan paul press
conference is going down here in los
angeles and on august 25th
the biggest youtube event in history is
taking place
logan paul versus ksi
paul logan paul any of the pools i don't
care jake paul
logan paul any of the pools what's up
with all these pools
there's a lot of tools listen speaking
of pools ksi you belong in the kiddie
pool because i'm going to make you my
best
if you saw my instagram at logan paul if
you want to follow me there
one of you lucky folk is going to be
flown out to los
angeles to come to said press conference
jake paul
just let me we can make fun of him more
just let me finish this any of the
points and then
we can do that because we just dropped
our maverick rule breaker line we are
all wearing the merch right now it's my
favorite drop yet bro because as you
guys know what it means to be a maverick
it's someone who goes right when they go
left is someone who's independent
speaking of right you gotta take it
right here i know i'm doing that and
listen guys while i'm not telling you
to go break rules i am trying to
encourage you to think outside the
cookie-cutter box
that society has placed most of us in i
was just a boy from ohio and using my
fixture
curiosity i broke out and now we've
started a revolution god bless it
in fact this merch is so hot i'm done
talking we're pulling over we're doing a
photo shoot
[Music]
hey why are you moving in slow motion
like you're moving slow motion in real
life
you told me that it was in slow mo it
will be in slow-mo
yeah yeah in post in the edit you can
move your normal normal speed
you said that we were doing it in some
in slow motion it will be in slow motion
the frame rate is higher you can move in
normal and then we will slow it down you
are you understanding because the way
you're moving your eyes makes you think
you don't understand
he doesn't look like he's understanding
right now what are you saying right now
can you please try and action
[Music]
yo you're still moving in slow mo you're
doing literally the same thing i'm doing
the same you're doing this
dude he's in my head yo mike what the
[ __ ] let me outside
i got him here no no i'll just go
i'm gonna go all right i'll wait
you gonna go honestly ditching the
montage
no not we dropped the blue cut off
sweatshirt the gray cutoff sweatshirt
the red joggers and then we got a little
fancy with these shorts look they're
like marvelous they got zippers on them
in case you don't like the color red you
can just go ahead and zip it on up
mike you can't even you can't zip right
i'll zip it for you in case you don't
love the color red you can just zip it
on out of there
that was weird man can you not do a
slow-mo replay of that
[Music]
yeah guys all you got to do is hit up
the maverick site logan paul dot com
shop or link in description and
you will be automatically entered to be
flown out to la for the press conference
hang with the scra
hang with some squad it's a fish it's a
good taste so you'll be able to hang out
just
tyler madison oh my god maverick are you
our neighbor
kind of since i basically live here yes
four houses down from here you guys are
our neighbors too
jesus mother and you too bro we got so
many neighbors
what is going on
oh the yeti is one powerful machine
turns out i can't stop it i'm falling
i'm falling
i'm falling okay all right georgie
georgie stop
georgie stop georgie stop george stop be
honest
man there's nothing you could do that
could get me out of this car not one
thing
not a thing you could do hey you said
your kids are at home this is one george
jenkins
all right george all right bye bye
all right man taking them guys
appreciate you
and another news besides the fact that
ksi is secretly megamind
as we know little brother uh jake paul
is on tour i think he's in boston right
now
out there with the whole squad yo man
i'm i'm pulling over bro dude i've seen
this face once before it's not good
bro
oh no oh no oh no i'm blackout before
sorry just hanging with my squad
as i was saying jake is currently in
boston so i hired one of my
goods to take care of him hi logan so
i'm officially
a block away exact spot where my friend
saw jake got the merchant hand which is
actually in the washing machine
and i had to pull it out weird like damp
moisture feels like it's gross and
sweaty
yo jake i have a special delivery
bro
gotcha little brother no coming back
from that one okay guys the title of the
video
oh god me and the squad have been
brought
[Laughter]
you suck bro it's cause you haven't been
vlogging dude
get yourself out of the squad what is it
yo i i don't know what's going on i just
keep saying it and now i'm getting like
a little worked up you know
you guys stepped on the screen all right
the joke's done now as i was saying yeah
guys the squad and i have decided i've
i've avoided this for so long
but i'm gonna do the typical like
youtuber 21 questions q a
i'm telling you that's the move they've
been asking about this how are you
so how are you dry all of a sudden bro
the merch doesn't get wet dude it's hot
as hell
oh it's sad oh [ __ ] i see what you did
i tweeted i asked you guys to tweet me
questions so yeah without further ado oh
god i'm i'm doing the youtuber thing 21
questions and answers
[Music]
uh what are we calling this deep
questions
maybe 21 juicy questions with logan paul
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen welcome can we just
skip the
antics and just get right into the
questions i already hate this
question number one why on god's green
earth did you become a vegan my brother
that was that was in part due to spencer
spencer's right there you guys said hi
there
bro i was at the point in my life where
i just wanted to like try stuff i was
very open and spencer's like yo
maybe try being vegan because he's vegan
and i just did i don't know i don't know
bro i've been vegan for four months i
don't know
now you're a full-blown veganism what
food do you miss
the most are all these questions about
being vegan bacon next question
i just missed bacon i had some this
morning
let me tell you it tasted pretty good
i wish i switched to veganism
[Music]
wait actually we have some questions
coming in from the logang here
what is the best and worst purchase that
you've ever made
the best purchase has got to be this
house i love this house it's like this
is the crib bro
and then uh kind of similar the worst
purchase i've ever made two
forty five thousand dollar each mercedes
couches that
why would you spend that much money on a
couple comfortable couch i've ever sat
up
actually i'm actually an idiot i just
want i don't i don't know i was
i just wanted to fly there's really no
proper way to sit down hey guys
bro next question what celebrity
would you rate as a perfect 10. hmm
bro i gotta go with the double c bro ah
chris christie governor of new jersey
no no no camila cabello oh yes she's
she's she's a cutie she's your girl no
not
not no she's not all right well
uh here's a tough one this may be the
toughest question of the entire
evening here which of your pets is your
most favorite
maverick the parrot on the wall there
because he founded everything bro his
name is maverick it's the brand it's the
rule breaker brand which by the way you
guys hit up the site liverpool.com
shop i'm gonna pick one of you to be
flown out here for the ksi versus local
press conference and five of you are
winning a 250
gift certificate dab who's ready for the
juice
yeah these have been pretty pg questions
here we go speaking of pets
we've been seeing a lot of chloe
bennett's dogs in your instagram uh
stories and i've some on hers care to
explain
um yeah those dogs must have been i will
they were running along the 101 south
and somehow
ended up here in my house so
i don't know they're here now
okay same topic are there any other
girls in your life girls
girls yeah
what's your favorite i don't know sexual
position
oh my god you can't ask this well what
if i had to say it'd be called the pile
driver
this mo it was crazy bro let me tell you
what happened so the dude is standing up
right
[Music]
do you have any advice on how to start a
youtube channel yeah uh
go to google open a google account and
then just
make your profile and then just post
videos
so just really do it so go and just do
it
[Music]
will you and jake paul ever release a
mini movie or documentary
about your training before slash after
the fight it's funny you
say that michael in fact i
am making a documentary uh not only
about the fight
but it's actually deep and we're going
we're going in it's the deeper story
um that happened at the beginning of the
year the behind the scenes the stuff
that
um people didn't know about stuff that
was going on internally with me and my
team and where i was
in my headspace and how such a
catastrophe happened and
the past six months and then trying to
become a better person you know become
more empathetic and more compassionate
and use the boxing match against ksi as
a way for
for me to keep my head up essentially
and and and literally i guess continue
fighting but yeah well we just got deep
bro next question dude
here's one that kind of ties into the
last uh question that you just answered
how do you deal with hate
yeah yeah a lot a lot of hatred this
past year and most of it is
is warranted but guys when it comes to
hate 99 of the time when someone is
exuding negative energy that usually
comes out
in the form of hate or mean comments
whatever it is it's a reflection
of how they feel about themselves where
they're at in their own life so like
don't don't take it personal
if you because like picture this you're
so angry and not content with your own
life
you have to protrude that onto other
people
that's that's what hate is to me and
also just like
do you bro believe in yourself be a
maverick like as much as i joke like
seriously be independent you don't need
the approval of other people to do what
you want to do in life
that was beautiful especially i don't
[Music]
wants to know will this question be in
the video
yes if you could say anything to jj
or his team right now like what do you
have to say you're my [ __ ]
that that quick that easy that's it
nothing else nah he's my [ __ ]
all right that's it for 21 questions
logan oh
thank god hi logang that is the vlog
if you guys are not a part of those make
sure to subscribe and join the strongest
family on youtube
it's a big month it's a big month coming
up and you do not want to miss it so hit
the subscribe button and guys
loganpaul.com or link in description
visit the site get yourself some merch
and you will be automatically entered to
be flown out here this month later this
month for the ksi versus logan paul
press conference and hang with us it is
going to be rowdy logang i love you guys
and i will see you tomorrow take it easy
you got me under your
influence i swear i'm never
gonna give you
you got a bad reputation
in my neighborhood