Logan Logan yeah hey so Logan wants to
know did you guys get your merch at you
wants to know what you know the women's
leggings have been restocked this is
very secure yeah it's not a real prison
guys you boys on set right now the last
day of shooting my movies are thinning
to coming 2018 on YouTube grid oh yeah
guys the shooting in prison today no
super savage look at there's money but
yeah yo calm /op buggies have been worse
- this is coming up we have the softest
in the game the game today guys it's so
crazy it's like a little bunk room it
sort of reminds me of the team tent
house Oh Barney guys I'm just kidding
the Wardrobe though does remind me of
Jake smart man also for whatever reason
you're watching this and you don't know
who I am hi I'm Logan last name Paul I'm
the founder of the Logan that's you if
you're not in the low gang if you're not
subscribed you suck don't worry though
you can still unsubscribe for me smack
the button in the face and let's make
the Internet great again
some privacy please what's up skating
huh you're still pooping
I guess we're shooting right now but it
just got so awkward and you look over my
right shoulder there's a bunch of dudes
and like gray things like me if you look
closely they have like a W on their
shirt at the anti Mavericks there hello
they're called the wave wave or the
whatever let's go we sell the motor on
here baby
fabrics dot-com forward slash merch
nothing I hate more than the web wings I
don't know what else to do other than
get naked I'm just kidding guys this
next scene I am naked actually my last
shot of the movie this is it it chose to
make me naked on my last shot on purpose
haha you don't producers haha also Mike
Webster you may be wondering why I'm
wearing this fire helmet yeah the
Christmas distractors fire
where we check Logan huh top you good
bro yeah well you've never seen someone
shower shoes and socks I know get
cultured Brendan now let me do my see
and be an actor speech speech okay hi
here's our fields here come inside
Michael so Michael's the director of
this movie thanks for bringing me back
for the city to grow it safely this
movie has been so much fun but there's
only one way I know how to end it bro
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
it's your first Christmas tree buddy Wow
I mean look it's it's tall it's gigantic
that's just the thing like I can I can I
know it's real this is a real steep
20-foot tree you know it's so crazy
about this field know who did it
is that you huh it was it I think it was
Frank this kid do you have anything you
want to tell me
or perhaps dude everyone's here have you
go is this you did you do this thing
over here
what follow me yo Evan you seen that
you're the best dude someone just comes
to grab yo side out again it's happened
before with that man when I was younger
oh you're so baby poop upside down only
one thing on my mind right now yo having
those joggers brother
back looking Paul calm /f you know how
it is we just restock nobody right so we
got a 20-foot Christmas tree
legitimately the biggest tree I've ever
seen in my life myself I'm just really
glad that you're just trying that
broncho
know we should definitely decorate this
tomorrow as the family guys I wrap my
movie the cynically just come on guys oh
snap guys I literally was so hungry I
forgot to vlog last is gone we all we
all had pasta it's almost finished well
at least we're matching that's anyways
guys I have good idea a great idea for
the vlog cuz we were on set the whole
day it's like midnight right now and I
can't believe we haven't done this 24
hour overnight challenge in the cool bus
which by the way looks so stupid that
it's cool who's doing it's beautiful I
cannot believe we did this
seriously one of my favorite parts about
vlogging is being able to do stuff like
this like I grew up in Ohio my dad's
here he can vouch I never thought I'd
have my own bus wrapped in a million
Christmas light it's crazy anyways the
whole crew is already on the bus ready
to have a sleepover slumber party we got
we got we got the Spanish salami Jew day
[Applause]
we got the man who burns me we got Mike
real maverick okay and then you got the
maverick guys this is gonna get weird
alright guys I said this in my Santa
Claus diss track I'm the new Santa Claus
that's a fact
ladies and gentlemen I prepared for you
the Holly is jolly as Christmas giveaway
good technical may and day you'll get
the biggest gift for comedy you stop
string ly like what are you Chris
crinkle oh this is a big deal for me
okay I have one person here who maybe in
my family I don't know if he's my actual
dad that's what I'm saying so let's be a
family and unwrap these guys go for a
Judi
[Music]
we can burst kill everybody great ideas
dad except for the one where you decided
to have a second child
[Music]
you're the worst part about this is
nervously paying me you owe me money you
mother
they are synchro
[Applause]
that was the hottest merch in the game
oh snap I have an idea
okay what are the Christmas without a
little pain oh hello gang it's like 2:00
a.m. we're all pretty tired I'm gonna
give calling his Christmas present here
but it's a bone definitely your size
thanks Mike it's just a Snuggie Mike we
had this conversation so we're gonna get
set up for nighttime and then just go to
sleep and hopefully no one farts the
middle of the night anybody does it's
gonna be you know hey you good looking
now you do yeah but hey looking how you
doing hey I knew this hammock would come
in handy
really hope it doesn't collapse cuz my
boy and my dad are under me and Kong
most importantly call yeah so this is
gonna be an interesting night but even a
more interesting morning I just want to
say make sure to get your merch looking
for my cops
and yeah that's pretty much it okay and
a can you hit the lights
Oh
[Music]
this car
endo
his breath
[Music]
wake up everybody it's your big day good
morning everybody good morning Judy
how'd you sleep
you look so Spanish in the morning hey
hey tin okay how's the squad sleeping
great it's weird ending the vlog in the
morning but that's what we do bro I made
a promise that every day I'm gonna
deliver you content distract you from
your busy stressful lives whatever it is
I got you if you're not a part of the
low game make sure to subscribe with the
strongest family on YouTube no big deal
we also have the hottest softest merch
on YouTube not just on YouTube in the
world stammers baby we all represent the
woman's leggings have been restocked but
don't wait down low beep all that cons
last shot or link in description with
that said low gay I love y'all I'll see
you tomorrow
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
The Hollies