[Applause]
[Music]
yes me you look like a fish tank
good morning look five is cozy
yo parsley because it is and partially
because I'm wearing the hottest
merchants again it's something keeps me
warm it's incredible of it maybe let's
go guys if you have not gotten your
merch it's okay you can still join the
movement Logan Paul that Kansai shop
also get on the Logan you can still join
that - good news it's your big date we
are actually thinking about doing a 24
hour overnight challenge in this tonight
I don't have a say I'm kind of just
making doing it in multiple areas
yeah it's melting 20 days straight now
I'm not gonna stop now all I do is push
myself to the next in highest level if I
gotta sleep in a goddamn igloo I'm gonna
do with that said um bro I thought this
would have melted by now at least a
little bit understand I'm getting calls
from my neighbors they're like yo why is
there snow in your front driveway they
hate it it's ugly it's slushy we
actually do have to get rid of this
somehow because it is gonna become a
problem yeah don't think that's gonna
work
absolutely not got a call hey that's my
fried anyways guys let's focus on the
positive designers are bringing some
stuff in today
[Music]
my boys done it again look at this piece
of wood it's black it's not race this is
blood yo check it up we got big giant
wooden poles we got brown poles we got
white we got a charge of lager missing
15% of his logs that's many blogs huh
15% of your vlogs that what I said yep I
meant to say boss growing up man
everyone's welcome love well cool unless
you're strangers and get the Scott stay
off my property
am i right George alley of duties we
still not any reaches the tops so
they're bringing in a bunch of stuff
today but I think my favorite be Oh guys
you know this room average so this is
like a crystal representation of the
burn and we got the spotlight there like
shine a light on it Crystal's good
energy this is just that's the spot and
I think it comes the air comes up golden
ass challenge we are messing around bro
tail off this $10,000 crystal sculpture
it was an accident you are just talking
about how this burglar represents like
the Maverick movements like a motion
movement mom kinetic energy my face is
right I actually like I hate when I
break stuff wait what no I love when I
break stuff important stuff but not
important stuff this I'm actually pissed
about I'm not gonna touch it ever again
I know okay
back to the vlog god bless it yeah Oh
get your ass over here why you Park in
the grass no literally fit one of you in
between this gap plenty of room I was
gonna say I'm not gonna take this l
that's not my brand all we do is get
double using wins so I'm gonna use this
to my advantage I smash t-pain once said
all I do is win win win no matter what I
money on my modded anyways I'm gonna
take what's happening today and use it
to my advantage way I look at it right
we still have snow so we're gonna dig in
here and get some fresh snow see if we
can make it smooth
package smoothie materials because I'm
not real-life bananas because I'm kind
of an adult and this fresh definitely
not disgusting snow from outside almond
beverage no I wasn't gonna do it but if
I get sick I'm marking this moment right
here cuz I know it's from this I mean
it's actually delicious
yeah it just could be filled with germs
and in pesticides pesticides oh hi
grandma it's me Logan Paul my boy did
you get your Marquette okay she's having
a majorette smoothie bro delicious I
mean if you dropped it technically you
just go right back from where I came
from but that's no that's disgusting you
idiots
why would you take anything from me ever
your grandson Drake's no smoothie okay
looking if we actually plan on spending
the night here this hole needs to be
bigger I don't know if you noticed this
but I am a little bigger than Evan I
hadn't noticed that huh what
ah much different in size branded and no
matter how we spoon right now the hole
is too small so here I am carving it out
to make it bigger what's up I think I
hit something hit something yeah I've
been like digging for a while there's a
lot of space in there right here like
hit something brother like it's been
there a while what do you mean like an
object I don't know bro it's like I just
know it's been there a while you can
tell it's like prehistoric
my god
[Music]
[Applause]
if you guys remember hey he's our
British friends from the UK yes UK how'd
you get in that hole I've been taking
for 10,000 models ever you have no idea
slumber party buddy my man we got tons
of space in the igloo we got wine we got
wine glasses we even got candles homie I
mean like if it turns into that okay its
2017 oh it's actually look there's a lot
of space we got a bunch of headroom we
got oh my Brandon this is nice Logan
Paul you've done it again y'all better
do me the honors shut the door shut the
door by Brendan oh it's official bro
why'd you put the wine in the wrong way
that worries me a little bit it's kind
of forming like a little nasty puddle
here I have you ever ordered a pizza in
an igloo it's and we were about to do
that can we please have one medium pizza
whoever's delivering it can you tell
them can you just tell them that we're
in the snow we're in an igloo in my
front yard do you think they're gonna
deliver it bro oh I'm not gonna lie I'm
a freeze baby if it wasn't for my
amazing awesome
maverick marching night I would be dead
right now literally dead and y'all know
where to get the merchandise was I
supposed to do just I'm in here I'm
the door okay oh yeah guys excuse us
while we how's it going in there would
you get the pizza over here cold pizza
that's innovative yeah I'm gonna I'm
gonna go to sleep in my bed all right
guys the pizza was delicious up we
should probably get to sleep just to
pass the time do you want to be big
spoon we're gonna try to get some sleep
yeah I'm the best big spoon ever ask any
of my side chicks
[Music]
oh don't
right I didn't know what he was doing I
know what they say bro when t-rex's are
on the loose you cannot stop them
yo yeah I think you can break into my
song you won't do it from jumping off my
balcony
a fun one today thanks for watching if
you're not a part of the Logan you saw
that's what I've been saying lately but
there's good news you can unstuck all
you got to do is subscribe I've joined
this didn't you ring no yeah when the
strong family on YouTube cap you
maverick merch the hottest softest
merchant gay model recently has been
who's doing it guys we're different
we're passionate we're unique we work
hard to achieve our goal that's what the
Maverick movement is about Logan Paul
comm / shopper link description low gang
I love y'all now see you tomorrow take
it easy
[Music]