oh I got you
your Gucci phase Jacob it's okay man
just stop right now and grab some
tissues cuz this store you might break
your heart I know it broke mine
we got a bit of a situation you know how
I'm forming a new team with talent do
you remember that one vlog we were
shooting when that polish showed up okay
first off don't touch me
in second option take a couple steps
back and get outside the gate okay good
step back for real are you coming in a
little hot no seriously so I need you to
cool off a little bit before something
bad happens
what's the problem who are you what are
you doing so we are youtubers from
Poland I came to your house I even wrote
to you but I you didn't read that on
Facebook this is gonna be chin
subscribers act that's true your brother
has mini cheekbone yeah look at me look
at me so I actually like oddly enough I
enjoyed that he had the balls and he was
funny you're pretty funny bro so I
wasn't too mad that he showed up at my
house although typically I am I ended up
staying in touch with a kid but then I
quickly realized like I'm being quite
honest with you the kids [ __ ] crazy
we have a knife listen man I'm not gonna
stab the dog I don't like we're going to
sign the contract like we need to cut
our pants yeah odd contract yeah let me
reach for something emails he sent me
subject medium Logan Paul is in the
department I have already refused to go
anywhere during the summer holidays so
friend you own me remember that my life
depends on you I am not participating in
admissions to high school the kid
dropped out of high school because I was
like hey maybe you'd be a good part of
this team and then he goes I'm leaving
the airport on Thursday and arriving in
LA at 2:40 p.m. on Thursday tomorrow
house ever hired you will get fired out
of a cannon I tell you I believe people
if there's a new deal one I'm taking
your phone away - you will not do [ __ ]
unless I can tell you you are doing this
is no more fiber communication with
anyone less its mom ever you are being
cut off your listen I'm just saying I'm
just saying if the kid shows up tomorrow
and I open my door to him be prepared
[Music]
it's that mother was funny and he needed
a place to stay cuz apparently drop that
I came all the way from Poland - oh
that's my friend I know him he knows me
as well - yeah yeah look at me I didn't
take any suitcase and anything and
anything I don't have only one dollar
and I told myself
give me one mouth I'm gonna be a [ __ ]
millionaire you really have a suitcase
no ridiculous like I told myself I'm
gonna make look and feel great again I'm
gonna be in his team I'm gonna be better
host of impulsive than yeah you I just
give us a sec me are you in hire just
stupid and it's kind of manipulative
what you do is you opening 80 push him
out you never say anything to me ever
again I mean you literally just shove
him straight out of here's why I'm not
cool with that me and Jake paw very
close and subscribers jake has a thing
an asset let's call him mini Jake Paul
his name's Titus the kid is the [ __ ]
bad
I needed mini-me but instead I got a
medium me
I can't believe and say this we stick
him in the [ __ ] back house with you
let's do it wow it's good let's get that
foot in the main house who said he is
off-limits until he proves that he is
not allowed to wear underwear
can we give him underwear okay but I'm
mob serious about that no for main house
there's twenty can trade secrets
all right this is your room this is
where you'll be staying
so in two months I gonna buy a house for
thirty two million dollars I found how
much 32 by 32 million dollar house in
two months I found one
welcome to American my guy
[Music]
so here's the deal um I'm leaving to go
to Miami and I'll be back on Sunday the
whole issue right now is that like as
like a joke for like a vlog you know
like this is all fine like you're just
like hanging out but like we don't know
you like who you are Logan doesn't know
who you are it's a liability for us to
have you here 15 years old like what's
your plan outside of like being at this
house like let's be honest you're not
gonna move in here you're not gonna live
here I could be a part of the team no
that's gonna happen I'm gonna be harsh
cuz it's real we can give him a place to
stay I'm gonna call Jeb hallo and Jeff
after this you were gonna get grounded
okay I was trying to keep it just me but
I'm gonna tell them and they're not
gonna be happy okay you're gonna tell on
me you tell on because because sorry but
it's my responsibility it's to protect
this house
I'm really putting my neck on the line
for a reason that I'm not even sure of
to be honest with you for you to stay
here like I got your uber from the
airport to the house right so like I
sort of feel like I've taken you under
my wing because I feel bad like quite
literally you have nowhere to go and you
also quite literally have nothing on
your back you have one dollar in your
frock --it one dollar
like that's that's crazy you can imagine
the hesitancy everyone in the house has
you know I achieved everything that I
observed because I I have for me I have
like many successes actually many sexes
yeah sexist successes successes yeah no
no I'm a vegetarian
oh that's tight I need to make something
much crazy like five hundred dollars
like I can buy everything with that one
dollar I could even die on an airport if
you wouldn't take me to your house so
that was like a challenge for me bruh I
feel like this um here voice
[Music]
I'm being yelled at by my entire team
hmm what I know yeah I know I'm sorry
yeah well you were but I can I can stop
apparently this is like a huge huge deal
[Music]
it's like having a ticking a bola bomb
you can't touch in your house it sets
off a ton of red flags for me no really
what if he's a international fugitive
its international incident level danger
this whole thing is bad news he's a
minor and he needs to go
someone needs to contact his parents to
make arrangements for him to be returned
today sorry kid I'm macro viewing this
now and it's not ideal yo I didn't tell
him to fly out here I was like please
don't and then he showed up and he's
like this is where my flights arriving
can you please get me over to your house
Mike Mike sent this picture in the group
chat missing boy last seen lax original
birthplace Poland Interpol has been
notified reward if found missing boy I
can't do it
I need someone much stronger than me to
handle it hey I need you guys to talk
somewhere privately
oh yeah you guys just talk you just work
hi yeah four-stroke we're gonna be over
here the day though the point is make
sure he's not heartbroken at the end of
this you still giving him an amazing
inspirational talk and it's just right
now we made a music pick them up yeah he
gets to write it down later and go to
school as University and be like here's
my social media project my little
brother at this point right it would
have worked out
I don't know what US law is as far as
minor traveling from Europe here but 15
years old I don't think it's legitimate
that nobody stopped them and asked that
question I don't want the parents to say
hey he kidnapped our son yes I don't
know he lured her son from Poland to
come there I mean they can say anything
anybody can say anything the truth is
the truth the kids got a set of balls on
him I gotta say like he he's gutsy well
he's got a dream and he's following that
dream here's the big question how much
time do we have before he is potentially
removed from the United States he's
gonna have to go back to Poland like a
couple hours we got like a day I don't
know nothing I mean we got to show them
the time of his life here in the United
States while we still can
okay kids so it's clear you got bars you
can rap and sing of course I think we I
made you an Instagram yeah and it's
called Gucci Gucci yeah okay bro I don't
know how long you're gonna be able to
stay here really so we got a milk all
the time we do have you're still wearing
the same clothes yes yes you still got
no underwear we should get you some
underwear fine clothes millionaires
gotta have clothes so we're gonna go to
the store I had another store they have
awesome clothes what weather right now
[Music]
we go bro that's right where you can
have anything in here you want it is the
hottest softest Merchants game after all
just drop this red hoodie hosting
Mississippi oh yes David you're not
helping
now you look fired though bro for real
that's a good start for real though we
got no maverick underwear so let's
actually go
[Music]
[Applause]
that fits like this like I can thank
this that's too expensive
everything is probably too expensive for
you well you know you say you have men
shake shaking why I kind of prefer to
take something for my sister's there go
you're such a humble kid I got you your
Gucci phase Jacob it's okay man under
system just cherished t-shirt I'm not
sure if I should spend so much money
usually so much money on that
are you saying that
the health and wellness of her family is
more important than material objects I
came here to arrange as you know make
some money and buy my parents house and
everything
we got a really good kid on our hands
hey come in American arrow
they're good kid good kid
go put on your go put on your shirt the
one shot did you probably like an
extreme form of a culture shock not only
are we like showing him the best of
America he's never experienced America
like bro at 15 years old I I don't even
know what I was doing I I can't imagine
what kid cries over someone wanting to
buy Gucci for him like he's oh you what
he said he's like that's so much money I
could give it to my mom and my family
[Music]
I'm getting these shoes though in
underwear
[Music]
look nine times better all right
so many things
damn bro I can be looking flies [ __ ]
yeah
and you got underwear yeah hey I have
have the worst news bro is bad huh yeah
I I know you said not to like I got you
the Gucci stuff I know you you're at
your Gucci face that what was $1000 do
you want some goodies he was working for
except Gucci people and in two months I
think less than that ones I don't want
to tell you man it's yours now I'm so
sorry so you have to deal with that I
will pay you back in two months
as long as you make me famous like you
keep saying you're gonna do I think yeah
I think that's fair I don't know how to
describe this feeling I've never felt
like the way I feel like I'm just a
normal kid from a normal school from in
Warsaw from a forest in Poland
[Music]
[Applause]
you'll apply it but still with the
labels if you want to give you back now
it's yours bro you look great
there's only one more thing we got to
make sure you can stay in the United
States like hopefully hopefully you can
stay in these here god bless what the
[ __ ] you doing what do you mean oh no
bro like this yeah
[Music]
yeah what are you up to just training
my muscles for beaches oh wait what did
you drink
hey Jacob it's got some news for you
yeah I think everybody here is going to
be traveling overseas so unfortunately
you can't be here by yourself so
unfortunately the place you're gonna
have to be is back home it's not over
not over just so it's just begun again
situation but we are talking only about
this two weeks yeah there's no way for
them to say with Definity what date that
you might be able to come back or
anything like that so it's communication
as far as coming back that's not as
important as you creating content in
their eyes go back home like you should
start making content you know start
building the like building the plan I
had a plan for everything that was our
plan I wanted to just stay there like
couple couple more days without this
camera wait for this vlog and then I
make this cloud everything you'll have
it once we release the video but you'll
have to shoot back home I understand
everything I just want to talk about
this future okay okay
[Music]
thank you so much oh of course
are you sad not son because I know that
I'm going back you're coming back here
yeah I'm not taking any of the scouts
not taking underwear not taking nothing
wherever you leave your Gucci cause here
yeah of course
because I need to why I think to just go
back to to have this man in my mind that
I kill what the [ __ ] I'm saying $3,000
on clothes for you I'm not it's like
when you have like a girl that you've
hooked up with and she like leaves
something at your house on purpose so
she knows she can come back why don't
you just leave like the headband or
something you don't have to leave all of
it here what am I going to do with
$3,000 of Gucci clothes that are size
medium I don't need even underwear I
have my Francey hey this is kind of sad
of course like I hadn't the best time of
my life what was your favorite part when
I touched your nipple I was editing with
Hayden and I was after my workouts our
shirtless and he goes hey Logan thank
you for everything he reaches over he
was I thought your nipple I don't I
didn't even met men to do that let's
talk about the future
my other thing for you yeah
I don't know I don't know we'll figure
out the because that's the most
important thing cuz like I don't want to
stay in my forest for next year's
well here we are random polish kid I
guess this is it good Gucci face Jacob
do me a favor kid listen to me come here
little dumpling nugget don't [ __ ] up
your life okay don't do drugs
don't drink ever stay in school oh of
course
[Laughter]
okay look bro you see over there that's
America that's what freedom looks like
one day all this could be yours if you
just don't [ __ ] up your life in Poland
of course
we have so much more video to record and
with and I kid I told one thing I will
make you famous
[Music]
they really did it by Jacob
she says
fortunately
[Music]
he was like a less controversial little
brother probably in this video
[Laughter]
[Music]