this is a big day yeah but there's only
one thing
that could make this bigger oh my god
yes it's true for my best friend mike's
birthday i got him
lana rhodes the number one adult film
star in the world who he's now in love
with is his girlfriend dan spends all
his time with and yes it's also true
that on my birthday he got me a shrimp
the six dollar shrimp however i logan
paul will
never ever stop getting my friends great
gifts cause that's what friends are for
today may 5th is the release of my best
friend mike's book the fifth vital you
guys probably don't know this because
mike's like the funny guy in the house
but he had a 10-year battle with drug
addiction
uh heroin he's seen a lot of his friends
die he's been on the cusp of death
probably 10 to 20 times
and he should be in jail for probably 20
years but he's not he's my roommate
who's also a felon
i think i don't know uh regardless this
is a big day so two weeks ago we started
the hunt to find the biggest billboard
that we could just
ah smack mike's face on this is for my
friend's book cover i want to find a
place where it's super prominent
everyone can see his big beautiful face
on a nice big old billboard oh
absolutely
all right amazing 25k for [ __ ] billboard
oh boy
it's a lot of money okay right but what
what is money is paper
comes and grows that's what you say it
comes and goes money is
paper you're talking yourself into doing
the 25 000 that way is that what i'm
doing yeah i think so yeah hey let's do
it my argument was only going to be that
we have
most of the cash upstairs oh my god
you're right the money from the mercedes
couch fifteen thousand dollars is it
seventeen
no because we spent two can a weed
we just gotta come up with ten thousand
dollars we can get a sponsor yo that is
a good idea
all right all right we'll get a sponsor
so that brings me here guys today's
video is brought to you by
no one no sponsors still which is
actually good because i prefer to do my
own thing and maverick clothing is the
new wave again it used to be maverick by
logan paul
um removing myself from the equation
still be gonna be like a face of the
brand obviously
but it's no longer about me we want to
make this big and not just an influencer
brand and you guys don't see it much on
this channel but i have a very uh
inspirational like almost contagious
motivational side that instead of just
preaching about greatness and how
awesome everyone can be which i will do
but i also stuck it on clothing because
you wear clothes every day you get
reminded of it you get motivated you
want to go out and do some
change your life for the better i'm in
i'm on your team let's go may 22nd
mapperclothing.com let's get back to the
video
oh i have an idea what what if we tell
anna about it
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
don't touch me daddy grope me
that's a great idea lana's gonna chip in
because she makes so much money
we need to talk to amara immediately i
need ten thousand dollars from you
ten thousand yeah for what i'm afraid to
tell you
because it's a surprise i think you'll
ruin it i'm positive you will
actually here's what i'm not telling you
the gift costs 25k
i'm putting in 15k and i'm asking you
because he's your boyfriend and you love
him and what not to
pay the remainder okay fine perfect that
was easy
to go back before he gets it gotta be
[ __ ] good oh it's the best it is the
best
don't even tell him like logan asked for
ten thousand dollars like like
amara truck the only way this is gonna
work if it's a surprise i'll see you
around
yeah yeah she's gonna [ __ ] it up
[Music]
so for my og low gangsters i used to
live in that building right there
actually that exact room and
unfortunately i also got kicked out but
i figured it'd be monumental if i put my
best friend's billboard on one of the
most iconic buildings in social media
history like this is literally the first
building that he visited me at first
building i smoked weeded dude i even
lost my virginity there
now all we have to do is get mike in my
car drive back here and surprise me
she's waking up getting ready for the
day yeah i was up late
just working on the launch and [ __ ] i
didn't get much sleep that's unfortunate
because i kind of need you right now i
don't say no more fam
hi you put 10 years of your life into a
book that was released today this
morning
how are you feeling i'm feeling pretty
good a little stressed
to be honest with you and just like
obviously there's a lot of a lot of pain
and
uh struggle put into it but uh honestly
like i'm happy that
it's finally out and um i wish i had a
better answer i'm i'm nervous i'm scared
i'm
i'm stressed i'm excited i'm nervous and
excited because bro you know me right
you know when i do things i can't i
can't do small things and i like doing
nice things for my friends
this is a big day yeah but there's only
one thing
that could make this big oh my god
oh my god bro what is that
what is that oh my god bro why it's on
the side of 1600
oh my god that's so epic
bro look at your big face what's up i
gotta get out
i gotta
[Music]
i remember my first billboard and it was
the coolest feeling in the world
so i got you the biggest most prominent
billboard that i could find
and when i say i it was me and amara she
chipped in
are you serious babe what the [ __ ] dude
thank you so much
yo this is beautiful this is my first
time seeing it
holy [ __ ] bro i don't want to kiss you
no you don't know i kind of want to kiss
hey did you see that coming at all no
yeah i had no idea at all
the support that i feel like from this
group of people is beyond anything that
i've ever felt my entire life like each
and every one of you guys are so [ __ ]
supportive and i literally love
each and every one of you my story and
my journey up until today has been
painful but you guys make it easier and
you guys make me feel like i want to be
here and i'm happy to be here
[Music]
perfect
when i got clean and i walked out of
rehab i walked out of rehab with a 400
credit score
up to my eyes in [ __ ] debt because
all i had was a computer that i would
pawn unpawn
pawn on pawn at that point it was so bad
when you walk out and all of your
friends that you went to high school
with they're married and they work for
dell and they have a 401k and they have
stock
options and your mom's driving you to n
a meetings
and you're 26 or you're 30 or you're 34
and you've never once had
any idea about what to do in this on
this spinning rock
here's what i will say to people
watching this that have no clue that
have no clue what they want to do
how they want to do it because i was
there i was just there it was a store i
was just there i started
trying things i knew i knew i had
something and i didn't know what it was
i didn't know i wanted to be a youtuber
i didn't have the luxury of
knowing what it was but i knew i had
something and let me tell you this
if you've made it through addiction or
mental illness
you have something because a lot of
people don't
if you are still kicking today
[Music]
battling those demons you have something
because a lot of people didn't wake up
today because they couldn't make it
they couldn't cut it and you [ __ ] did
so you have something
but you might not know what it is