I have no doubt in my mind you're gonna
kick the [ __ ] on this kid Thank You ro
my one piece of advice I've told you
this a hundred times I was saying on
camera for the first time woody I wanna
shoot way to start 2020 we are back we
are on fire feels good to be back guys
we're about to hit a hundred million
subscribers and hit that subscribe
button that's that is a lie the last
vlog was me surviving military death
camp and before that I did something
nice for my friend Mike's birthday and I
got him a date with his favorite doll
film star Lana Rhodes however for every
good deed there is an equal and opposite
bad deed so I read a lot of the comments
on the Lana video and a lot of them were
really nice it was like Logan seems way
more mature and likeable than he was
before
Logan's gonna make a comeback in 2020 a
lot of that and I really do appreciate
the sentiment guys however I do want to
make it clear that I'm still a 24 year
old boy with a lot of testosterone and a
burning burning desire to [ __ ] [ __ ] up
that said yesterday I went ahead and
bought myself a lawnmower
[Music]
my days back in the vlog life you
flipped a [ __ ] lawn mower and put
fruit in it consider this breakfast in
bed might consider this another body
shots are both lethal and devastating in
to the artist I think I kind of deserve
one just so you know I can still throw a
ksi before this so I'm actually gonna
throw a wild right edge I tried to trick
you I had no idea my friend was the
biggest [ __ ] in the world this man
brought my train box who the [ __ ] is hit
him maybe box is not my sport he's never
taken a body shot he doesn't know what
it feels like I don't so I think you hit
me once I'll hit you once I won't go
crazy hard but just so you know what it
feels like I'm alright but that was good
you want one more yeah got you the most
attention in 2090 boxing you'd think
that right which activity made you trend
at number one globally on Twitter
fake suck in the dick Donna Thank You
Valerie 2020 maybe take the fake off oh
you think is you're really suck a dick
I'm not saying you should but I'm also
not saying you should that billion
impressions that you copped off that
[ __ ] BJJ we are two hours late they
already did the surprise I saw it on
Instagram and it looked fun in this
party late not drinking with a decrepit
boxing coach and
[Applause]
happy birthday I'm so sorry ladies
keep it short and sweet you know when I
first met Jake I was - I remember the
first time I saw imma be honest my
initial reaction was who the [ __ ] is
that and not point fingers but I I do
blame you for mom and dad's divorce you
been up your training and I'm inspired
back in Encino just to see your
discipline cuz I've never seen you this
dedicated and focused on anything I
think it's really good for you I think
this kind of isolation is gonna do a lot
for your free personally and obviously
for your career in your business you
keep putting in the work you're at the
finish line and then you've got this and
I'm gonna be here and it's cool to get a
glimpse of just the actual pure
dedication and to your craft and the
discipline that I've been able to
witness so it's cool bro I want you to
know even as the little brother you
inspired me greatly I love you bro you
know I came here for your birthday 23
that's all that's super good keep doing
the age thing
I got also got to see practice and train
and you look so [ __ ] sharp your
punches are like [ __ ] arrows bro like
arrows with cannonballs at the end
verify your lethal fighter I have no
doubt in my mind you're gonna kick the
[ __ ] out of this kid Thank You row my
one piece of advice I've told you a
hundred times when I say my camera for
the first time do not overconfidence
exactly that's where I [ __ ] up I think
percent I think I wasn't realistic about
the outcome of the fight with ksi I
think that's where I went wrong and I
lost on the day you happen to have a
much stronger mental than I have so I
don't even think I need to save I just
wanna let you know and document it and
also I'm betting fifty thousand dollars
on you so no pressure
well anyway I love you love you bro Sam
coming to support of course of course
it's gonna get that ko now I'm coming to
avenge you
January 30th in Miami it's gonna be on
to zone I might use beer I hate for this
promo
but I'm doing cuz I love on thanks man
also all this runs in our family size
water with Troy