on the way right now okay okay here's
some update one I'm in Sweden ASAP rocky
got arrested here really though I wanted
to open this vlog and just say a few
things we shot this vlog so long ago
it's kind of [ __ ] I'm not gonna lie it's
kind of also the thumbnail if you look
at it we have the question mark on the
animal as if you didn't know what - no
it's very clear as a pig we got a new
pig but anyways if you guys have not yet
gotten your tickets to the Challenger
games July 27th the fastest entertainers
in the planet will be racing at Long
Beach City College link for that is in
the description it's gonna be skin sick
so hit that subscribe button
yeah yeah again sorry for the I mean I'm
just gonna say the quality of this vlog
but it's kind of cute in some spurts
okay we'll see Burrell is back here and
she's lonely this what we're exhibiting
right now exhibiting we are examining
her exhibiting ah they're examining
pearl exhibiting could be signs of
chronic the pressure this is not good
obvious as you guys know I love animals
but uh we've got another Pig for pearls
about another pigs coming right now is
this the same pig lady from last time oh
really the hot one
top things been going in any trouble
with the husband or anything like that
happens when this pig meets throw
Bingbing gonna fight an immediate
showdown there will be blood one has to
sum pearl is a wild beast all media she
can do a specialty you guys my favorite
with a girl that I bought her with we
broke it's okay I got custody oh he's a
good pig
[Music]
Oh red Lamborghini listen hey I know it
seems wild and it is but it's nothing
you can't handle piggy small we want to
die we're almost there
sound like how the neighbors can hear
[Applause]
[Music]
about 30 minutes and they're finally
getting used to each other pearls not
attacking his heart anymore and I'm just
trying to make sure that piggy small is
is nice as stressed as he was well I
have so many animals this is ridiculous
so we got who big three dogs a turtle
and a parrot as rude bra you guys yes
that's your ancestors I'll never forget
you come what what the [ __ ] is happening
I don't understand
pearl is the girl in this situation how
is it possible she was okay I'm going on
top that's it's only taking like five
days but it warms my heart to know my
animals are finally I literally could
stand back here all day and watch my
animals interact this is amazing what an
odd cast of animals bro you're gonna
piss her off
please don't
come back alive pearl kind of runs the
house right now guys I'm so sorry this
vlog is literally all over the place
we've been shooting it for the past like
we normally it's not like that but as
you guys know ginger is fairly new to
the family and she's a little bit of a
troublemaker you guys haven't followed
her on Instagram make sure to do that
her Instagram ginger the giant and if
you guys saw my Instagram story
sometimes she'll hop on the couch which
by the way each of those couches is like
$45,000 stupid bad decision I know Tom
Shean purchase but when I tell her no
just go limp like pure dead weight
couple days ago she tried to steal the
blanket from the house and as you can
see she's constantly getting wet
literally just laying down in the pond
outside although she still throws up in
car rides because she's carsick she's
just a big girl
maverick can you shut the [ __ ] up please
she's just a big baby so we need to
clean her I'm maverick please I want to
clean her up a little bit
literally I'm gonna try to give my bear
a bath right now
[Music]
good girl let me do this without scaring
her cause she's super timid about
everything
[Music]
the consistency of her fur is crazy look
at this ginger you a thick [ __ ] no no
no no you a witness all your clothes
yeah man I really only did the problem
of the red drop we just dropped these
new hoodies logo fall back on slash I'm
actually doing so well look at his face
bro just a big small hey I'm proud of
you how much you think that cost right
there he's like you stripped me of my
flow now every time a ginger mob webs of
hair come off her body I've thrown these
up like you know when you're making out
with a girl like so much of her hair
gets in your mouth you just end up
throwing up a hairball the next day you
don't say no I had no idea what you
think I get more experience in your life
Andre Oh anyway that's a blog like I
said I've been on fire with content did
the jeopardy with shock collars we lost
a Russian guys that do the face and now
that I'm talking out loud it's all just
violence and I'm a horrible [ __ ] role
model oh my god so sorry not really
though
well yeah hit the subscribe button this
one was a bit random I know that K you
know new maverick red inspire hoodie
logo ball icon / ah poor link in
description justify your shoes ha I love
you guys and I'll see you next time take
it
[Music]