then went Logan I've been thinking I'm
kind of tired of having all this money I
know Evan I know exactly what you mean I
feel the same way I feel like I've lost
touch of who I am you know can you go a
little faster with that thank you
yeah it's like LA has changed us you
know it really has dude it's seriously
eyes and I actually have an idea that I
wanted to run by you I think we should
get real jobs hell no I'm not going back
to school I'm talking real job this is
America
you got me tweaking on oh you got shirts
for us oh do you have any maverick merch
or okay okay I think you guys gave us
the wrong shirts it's okay it's fine do
you want to use the jetpack or use the
jetpack but was this built by Elon Musk
you use the jetpack
I got a jetpack okay there we go
that's vacuumed really well the sofa
please wait that's not a jetpack no it
is oh it's not well that's what is that
is that vacuum oh okay
got it
seems pretty legit I can do this footage
another Wang what no we know you think I
do I feel like the only way Christians
could end up like this it's through lots
and lots of sex everything
two best friends clean house today you'd
have okay back exactly exactly
yes maybe thank you why is this plan
shutting up besides a little I did not
mean to do that
oh hi I'm cleaning bro oh yeah I didn't
joke to me I'm representing America I'm
going in I'm done with this YouTube
[ __ ] yes bro imagine the life we
could live wearing that outfit you guys
okay look at yourself lucky I like how I
look
that's just sad are you concerned at all
with anything are there some signs that
your oh the guy that smoke I I think he
need to learn how to because you know
it's just going with him around and he's
done doing nothing just you have to to
do well the vacuum bro we look [ __ ]
good day so you're concerned that
they're not gonna finish on time I think
so they're not efficient thing I like
the way your muscles looking that shirt
oh thanks man I appreciate you dad look
I'm not gonna lie I really have to be
but I'm afraid to go in the house cuz I
don't want a dirtier work media power I
have an idea I feel like we're doing a
good job what do you think about that
that's not good oh my god guys
Lauren wake up please no one wake up
we were to finish you supposed to injure
your friend you need to go immediately
because you know what your fire both of
you you're firing us yes
I'm honestly okay with that fire that's
fine thank you thank you I appreciate
you guys and what you do seriously this
is not easy you off me no okay
a little stretched out oh that's fine
sorry about guys fire that's fine but
it's fine we'll see you guys thank you
oh no these guys know they don't know
how to do it work well that went pretty
much exactly as I expected not good okay
a woman's boutique store hi nice to meet
you
basically we just wanted to like ground
ourselves again cuz like we're like we
do the internet videos that are really
just like stupid and suck a lot we
wanted to just get a real job so we were
wondering maybe we could like help you
out today well it's a process it's not
easy
no he's just smiley yeah I smile a lot
yeah well first you start with you know
as you could have cut all
color-coordinated
oh that's chess are automatically an
issue because I am colorblind
no I I actually am nervous for you guys
oh you're nervous for us your business
okay okay hi there
customer Oh perfect
and anything any help it's a twin type
of shoot take over no no oh yeah
I don't know anything she's talking
about
you got this champ you go you got this
champ you're working for me for the day
there's the issue i I don't I don't know
what it's like to be a girl or wear girl
clothes maybe you could help me help you
tell me how have you ever considered
getting maverick by Logan Paul no so
maybe something to consider this this
looks exotic this could be good also I
have this thank you thanks okay that's
not gonna match any of these so for you
okay yeah I got you yeah you got that
loading another paying customer
how are you I'm Logan hey man nice to
meet you new boy here nice one um yeah
well you looking for a man looking to
pick something up for my girlfriend I
feel like I can't get in let me know
what it looks like okay you know you see
you wanna try it on I mean I can't see
how it looks on me like she's like your
height okay would you would you mind you
want me to try on one of the dresses
well I mean because then I can kind of
picture and see if it's not too short or
long whatever it is you like short of
things for like sometimes
[Music]
what do you think of it that's great I
think that's I think that's the one
right there
No what do you think of me personally of
you personally or in the dress we're in
the dress
um you know you actually make it look
pretty good thanks man so there's a go
if you want this for your girlfriend I
mean okay cool
[Music]
hey store lady well you just you set it
a little looser but yeah we are not cut
out yeah totally understand so yeah we
we are quitting thanks for trying
thank you for letting us lose your
business you're dead we appreciate you
bye
[Music]
you know I'm starting to think bro
once suck at things in general man let's
go get another job
another one another one another one
another one another one another one he's
coming back another one I feel about
farms of it I don't like the fall
reports it's the horses I don't like
understand my boy to the ranch today
back to our roots god bless america
stepped in horse [ __ ] I'm all right
howdy boys
get up here meatball come on let's go
get your horse I don't want call for me
now
they were bodies yo guys I don't think
you're a magical I'm talking you know yo
I'm Michael I'm I'm absolutely jealous
of this horse
yeah like it looks like you got a new
best friend gonna be jealous it's got it
[ __ ] do I want
oh no Pongo
hello he's got hair exactly like me
that's cool huh just be you and horse
today bareback bareback like no saddle
you you and horse nice bring your horse
on over here
oh she's gonna kick you in the face
understand my horse's ass so here's the
reason why I haven't scared of horses he
was shooting a music video at our
friend's house who has a mini horse and
the mini horse snapped that it almost
bit him and you got to understand like
he's the same size as the mini horse
right so it was pretty scary for him and
he ever since then he's been traumatized
by this animal so we're really
conquering some fears out here today's a
big day for him you know if he does this
successfully who knows he might actually
like many horses in the future
you got it yeah you're real cowboy it's
alright suck it up you got it that's why
you got the pads on hey yeah yeah that's
good it's perfect bro see
oh god these overalls are tight
grab some mane you're not gonna have
anything to hold on to up here Oh what
happened it's just you and horse Oh
mother god bless it I'm doing it yeah oh
my balls hurt I'm not oh my god good
pedal oh [ __ ]
a good horse whoo but naughty balls I
believe from the sounds of it balls it
looks like he's kind of having a tough
time do a lot of home
[Music]
yeah yeah perfect this is where the barn
was gonna go so I need you guys to
continue move some dirt we're off that
hill a little bit even more than just a
hair just a hair okay okay and you've
operate heavy machinery before yeah yeah
is that oh we driving that driving that
that's yeah we've done that's almost
like a car I need to make mentions on
this my grandpa shed okay don't don't
hit that all right
no not really [ __ ] I know I'm having
trouble seeing it's really hard to see
with Evan right in front of me but we
got this like you feel this
we got it we got it
oh yeah you got this oh boy I got it I
got it are you sure I'm pausing are you
sure positive
[Music]
yo what happened was so I was steering
it but then all of a sudden I was inside
the shed yeah you guys are fired we
should want to just like sprint out of
here this is so much better than yeah
man
it'll just suck good God dang right
thank God we're YouTube stars which
reminds me guys if you enjoyed this
season of best friends make sure to
subscribe to this channel and also let
us know leave a like on this video I
think we're gonna do a season two but
it's up to you guys comment down below
what you want to see what you think we
should do hopefully you guys watched it
with your best friends and if you did if
you liked if you want to see more
against subscribe comment we are gonna
see you guys very very very soon until
then we're gonna go do rich people
things I will see you next season
take it easy fam
[Music]
[Applause]