[Music]
evidence phone is ringing
that's a good sign we got a big day plan
for my boy okay gang skirts with me and
Spencer here I've got a little plan that
I might get heaven took and make it make
out a little bit of tongue action today
so let's go say hi for you it oh my gosh
I do know it doesn't look pretty good I
have a surprise for you
eyes a big one so guys welcome to yet
another episode off
[Music]
do you leave my number no I did not kind
of I kind of did but it's in a good way
in a good way to help you how is it any
possibly a question so guys if you did
not know this Evans a lover my man I
know you love to love you love love and
making love all sort of love things you
are a lover loving man and I know you've
been searching I know you signed up for
Christian mingle so I in bro the dating
apps nowadays you can't you can't trust
them bro 90% of people who use them on
their first day end up with something in
their butthole
you know if they dispense yeah I don't
use tender or Christian make I don't use
any dating lips I can tell because you
called it tender speaking of tender and
no mom boy's heart is tender I'm a
little old school so I decided to get
you a date the old-fashioned way the
[ __ ] out
Oh beautiful surprise big things come in
small packages that's you on that bill
boy how do you even get that photo oh
I'm an internet star I know how to use
Photoshop dummy single call me
wow you really put my number up there
and everything you're famous now is your
big day it's your big day you've got our
own billboard real one hey guys my big
day yeah good news though you look
across the street there that guy's
spinning a sign with my face on it I
have not gotten any calls yet but I'm
sure they'll come in no one you're not
getting calls he's spinning it in
traffic no one can beat it
hey check Martha can you stop spinning
the sign just hold it vertically there
we go
that's much better where would the arrow
even be pointing to oh hey there you
know why they're hooked right just saw
you on that billboard yeah that's what
it was hey it's that guy that I want to
meet you
yes that's my fault we could just do
this right now
do you have any nice hot friends
okay cool call you okay five seconds he
gets a number I don't you got to start
picking up your phone Evan double date
[Music]
answer that phone I hear a real answer
it
go don't hello hey I saw the Billboard
and I'm thought it would be a cool way
to meet somebody moved here so you free
later yeah yes amazing can i text you my
number and you took me back i sounds
good
perfect see you later all right sounds
good sounds great
[Music]
are you ready for this bro
you look cute you looking at somebody I
appreciate you that's my boy
oh hi Ali what's up you look so good
thank you thank you we're just waiting
on heavens day actually hi
it's Cassandra the one you called on the
phone you look even better in person
yeah you're very pretty thank you
[Music]
she too
oh you heard that Wow so where you from
I love ya filming
oh yeah this is for a web series called
best friends that's my best friend and
we just started so Anthony do you get
the boom out of the shot we're still
learning yeah we haven't really shot
like this before yeah let's make a show
so yeah you can't just keep the balloon
higher hey there can I have the cashew
ricotta I am vegan after all do you guys
cook dog I like you funny dog joke no I
actually have enjoyed it for a little
bit and over there they took some of the
best dog I've ever had
used to get it like every day
Pomeranians mostly I think I gotta use
the bathroom
Logan you wanna help me with the Aeon oh
yeah I do want to do
[Music]
[Applause]
I know hey George
uh long story short Evan and I went on a
double date things went south my girl
eats Pomeranians Evans day eats dogs so
sure you could come and get us out of
this mess we great man
way she's with you right now yeah yeah
no she's outside now she says she's
alone okay okay address by the way we
could tell it's you that's not even
covering your face you think I told my
mom she made it too big I said mom Oh
Oh gross Oh are you guys okay yeah you
look really stunned oh boy yeah that's
pretty great yeah yeah sucks at you with
dogs oh I don't need dogs it was a joke
you knew that right no I know I know I
thought you were serious no your humor
is so dry yeah
you're hard to read resting [ __ ] oh
no I don't think you have is face my mom
has that I don't think you have it well
anyways I feel like we got off on the
wrong foot uh I'm gonna go catch a movie
I love it here I'm going to be the third
wheel hey George sorry about that by the
way this could be karma some crazy bro
she a badass
[Music]
Wow so much fun being the third wheel
alright I'll let you guys go ahead and
do your thing guys that is the episode
with best friends I think we did our boy
good bro like he's got a date right he's
good to go I hope you guys enjoyed the
episode funny how that that panned out
if you guys are not subscribed make sure
to do so smash the button for me and I
will see you next week also ladies I'm
still single so call me bye guys
[Music]
[Applause]