what's good love gang okay this is a
weird rule this is not clickbait this
actually happens a lot of youtubers do
fake videos and I've done you know my
fair share of like faker staged videos
this is not one of those I try my best
to avoid that this is real this happened
today it's Sunday it's kind of gloomy in
LA we partied last night so I'm just
like taking a nap earlier like a little
hungover and all of a sudden I hear some
screaming outside my house and this
isn't like out of the ordinary there's
always like someone like outside saying
some crazy but this seemed like a little
aggressive
almost someone's screaming outside my
house my roommate Andre pulls in and he
shows me a video that he took of some
really blond guy screaming he decides to
push it England [ __ ] you know what you
waiting let's fight let's fight if I
will drag you don't go in Russia but you
can fight I will drugs and not just any
guy Evon skin Drago from Rocky four yeah
that's right the Russian I couldn't
believe it go although I'm feeling a
little down a little under the weather
this could be a good piece of content so
how to do something right so please
enjoy the most spontaneous random thing
that's ever happened in my life but
before you do that hit that subscribe
button and copy red maverick hoodie the
inspirer hoodie it just dropped today
logo ball knock on /aa twirling in
description don't let anyone tell you
that you're weird different unique
that's you rock that she's proud of you
logo ball that comes last shot for
linking description turn those
notifications I friggin love you enjoy
the break I hate when people show - I
thank somebody that like prepared to
look like a boxer yes but as you no idea
I think you should box them in the ring
he's joking like his hot girlfriend by
the way is across the street filming so
I can't know he's joy that's what if
that's the prize I'll tell you what I'll
box you but if I beat you I get your
girlfriend I was literally in the midst
of a neighbor's Uzis on it's already on
her Instagram like the view on the
streets pretty good you know what if
he's a professional boxer whatever I
can't read this [ __ ] I don't even know
like what do you know no idea rush it
dress like Yvonne Drago he's in the
street should Logan box him in the ring
yes or no I'm sorry you were breaking up
it sounded like you said yes I think I
see what you see
I'm not expecting this driving back here
to do it like this it's the only way to
do it real quick last time or these
shorts was the draw not this time
I was supposed to go to Russia like I
was supposed to be Russia right now
slapping Russians risk document you know
just case if you die you know he can't
sue us like like you once said like he
died he died if he dies he dies you know
you get it you get it so winner what
we're playing for is that woman right
yeah yeah you'd sign it yeah yeah
perfect
all right you ready to fight yeah
[Applause]
why are you doing this because you want
to go to Russia door being in
competition for Slav you know but he
never quite before really a Russian guy
you know knock him out definitely
[Applause]
foreign fighters doing you have been
here before bro didn't go the way you
want last time a today is different iron
you have been training since 26 minutes
ago for this fight he's bigger than you
yeah he's better-looking than you yeah
he's stronger than you I'm saying is you
are gonna go out there you are gonna go
out there and then what happens and I
said there's only enough headgear for
you there's no headgear for him and he
said how come I must wear a headgear if
you not wear headgear you must not know
who I am
he's really in character or maybe he's
actually goodbye he was like literally
laughing dude there was no no fear what
he was like bro you have no idea you
don't take it like V start showing any
signs of you
good no don't do it
damn gentlemen welcome to gloomy Los
Angeles California for a three-round
bout that will decide the champion in
the right corner coming into the fight
with an unknown record of not applicable
wins and not applicable losses the Red
Cross who showed up on our front game
boxing shorts Yvonne in the blue corner
coming into the fight with zero wins 0
losses and one job oh hi ok Logan
my fighters meet me in the middle of the
ring please for the stakes and the
reading of the rules this is a non
sation fight in the state of California
all forms have been signed and Google
has been notified the 3-round bound for
the winners decided by knockout or our
judges pillow Logan Paul pillow gingers
a giant blue I want a good clean fight
the winner of this fight will not only
get the glory but the girl courts with
her consent it's 2019 touch gloves go to
corners
five six seven eight in the quarters
boxers
one
one two three four dear quarters
fighters one was a great round by Logan
Paul clearly he was the winner of round
one
I got Logan Paul 10 points 8 points
thanks for all I appreciate the update
[Music]
four five six
reporters ten nine point nine
Oh Logan clearly you know you trained
really hard for this fight you traveled
a long distance really impressed by your
power showing up at the house what were
you thinking when you went in this fight
when I go in just fine I think I'm gonna
be in but I see Logan Paul is a
extremely seemly powerful and for sure
if he if he real because high heel kick
tomorrow and I think everyone here in
Los Angeles and everyone here at the
Maverick house thoroughly impressed by a
fight your skills II might drive on your
and your confidence in yourself why
don't you let people know back home
where they might follow you because we
are thoroughly impressed yeah I guess
you can follow me Viktor crazy on inside
you know on YouTube Viktor TV on YouTube
I do most craziest pranks
let's get the champion in here who's
who's with his manager who just won
three hundred and fifty thousand dollars
yes we did we got the money back that we
lost during the chaos I fight he was
gonna be rich amazing looks good to be
on our way back on Google preferred
let's talk to the tripod chance so you
were not expecting this fight today you
were home you were napping this man
showed up at your house correct what
quite literally showed up at my house is
there any reason to believe he's not
Yvan Drago at this point I'm not sure
hey I loved you in Rocky four yeah I
gotta give him props the man has a big
set of Russian balls on him
not a lot of people are willing to get
in the ring and I'ma be honest I feel
sort of sort of bad he probably just
came to Encino on a Sunday expecting to
get some sort of content and I [ __ ]
his life up so I apologize for that if
there's any sort of headache
we have ibuprofen and leave we really
could could heal you in any way possible
but overall I feel confident with this
win my first win I remain undefeated ksi
I'm coming for you I'm coming for you
ksi and we are more than excited for
that fight ladies and gentlemen let me
just say something else yo let me just
say some other any youtuber who thinks
they want to step up after I because I
that it's gonna be lethal I wanna be
ruthless it's a very fragile embark on
slash shop and that is it from the
champion guys we are more than excited
for this ksi fight as he mentioned the
red drop has just came to fruition
Logan small Comstock and let me tell you
our challenger will be getting a red
hoodie for his girlfriend today thank
you so much for watching ladies and
gentlemen discuss the trade-off of the
girlfriend how exactly will this take
place
[Laughter]
head back to napping hope you guys
enjoyed that spontaneous event that just
happening if you did hit that subscribe
button
low gang I freaking love you I live for
[ __ ] like that not gonna lie shout out
to him for real I'm proud of him I don't
even know him loved him in Rocky Ford
though hey listen I freaking love you
guys and I will see you next time take
it easy mister
[Music]
I'm a new robot
Sunday oh yeah we got McDonald's I was
eating McDonald's here with a beard for
here in a chess city know we was here
stammering a fear like a deer when the
car comin near in the middle of a row
bit of beer