how much money as if you don't know for
the past like two weeks my dad has been
putting the wood on my gate with sharp
points at the end of this so the bad
guys don't break in and so he comes up
to me today he's like yo how much you
pay me I'm like what you want to do it
like that
hi mister how much do you think you
deserve I say you were gonna pay thirty
four thousand yep that's correct I
delivered you a better product okay
that's up for debate
my son yeah you just did a weird thing
dad it is a good point you are his
father here's your saw so we conferred
and we've come to a place where were
comfortable basically I'm gonna pay you
zero dollars with the understanding that
I will still continue to be your son
[Laughter]
forty thousand put him to sleep
put him to sleep
hey yo good morning okay what's poppin
yeah I like your pants by the same Mike
your pants are so cool - wow wow yeah
y'all know we just had a new merch drop
for the ladies got the boyfriend
sweatpants we got the staple hoodies in
both black and pink they're selling like
a god chart because quite simply it's
the hardest merchants the game he
stabbed maverick movement the people who
are going to dent the universe actual
factual now in yesterday's vlog guys you
know we went to the pet store try to
find it anyways guys we go to the pet
store and today maybe get a dog for my
roommate now you I like being in the bed
Randy would you mind switching with have
it right now
but he's in the middle and I can't ID
just said he's like me in there only
being there either his face
look now my boys happy yeah how you guys
feel back here I hate you having as long
as my boys comfortable so what's the
plan well we're gonna see what kind of
dogs all right a pet store for adoption
or kitten ooh we don't have a cat yet we
don't have a cat well we just have like
a like an outside cat yeah I don't like
you
do you feel like you can handle the
responsibility of a dog cuz my dad
thinks you can't we're gonna give it a
shot as you guys know beginning of the
year I took a break from social media
like a month blackout I called it and
that cat right there looks looks like I
did during that time period under a
blanket not showing his face and
creepiest I'm really into dogs though
you know I think Evan is too
[Music]
I'm sure we can pick one of the other
they need homes to those absolutely they
need home but they're not gonna stay in
ours I mean I like dogs don't get me
wrong I say you don't like all your kids
everyone wants a pet he doesn't
necessarily need a snake but I'm still
gonna try to convince him to buy it
because I think snakes are cool you know
we got we got maverick the parrot right
we got calling to savage you know why
don't I get just get a snake and just
complete the collection if I'm buying a
snake the snakes got a bite right that's
what makes it fun bro you never know
what you're gonna get in one day my
snake slithering the other day my snakes
biting I'm 10 how big would I get it's
cool right
this time the good slither Oh having the
snake loves you yeah it totally looks
like it he's like that cat but a snake I
don't know anything right I'm just a
vlogger well I think you should get this
name damn it okay guys Evan didn't get a
snake someone's more responsible than me
but the good news is guys okay I brought
up that period that month first months
of January that I wasn't posting on
social media anywhere like it was a
complete blackout and during that time
on January 17th some of you may know it
was my brother Jake Paul's 21st birthday
that's a big deal and I didn't post
about it on social media and I didn't
even hang out with him in real life it
was worse guys I didn't even get him a
gift sure now that I'm back in the game
cooking up that heat think today we're
gonna go to Jay's house I got this gift
right here thanks for that marker Lydia
I'm gonna wrap it in paper towels
because we don't have actual wrapping
paper happy 21st - Jake love looks logs
I mean tomato tomahto I know for a fact
the kid is gonna love this no one knows
him better than me this is what being a
good
it's little brother Jake you like my new
brothers new brother got that part that
you just saw cut it I listen bro I got
something I gotta do dude ya know when I
wasn't doing social media for the month
right what did I miss
of yours my birthday
yeah I missed it got me a birthday
present it better be good I got you I
got your Lamborghini last year for your
birthday
[Music]
good there my house where's there my
life anyways no it was the new video guy
no you're gonna blame me for that
yo paper towel this is like Greg Paul
used to do it logs bro I wish you could
have been there how much my first
birthday bro would have been fun how do
some things take care of you know run
away to evening no where is everybody
[Applause]
what's in the BA hi I think it's time
bro I don't know man does anyone else
wanna open it for me oh my god a new
member March available now only I'm
looking for Mike I'm /i actually yo wait
hold up this is kind of legit what do
you mean this like like it's like ya
know you'll appreciate this one okay
okay am I gonna cry I'm so excited
really I can't even express it because
I'm so excited I mean it's cool but like
shoulda framed it should we go
mother lode I got you take just back
that one me naked
damn it man just I feel like Jake did
appreciate my gift but that's okay I'm
not tweaking it but yeah man I'm not
tweak but yeah man I'm not tweaking it
yo can you shut the stop please what are
you even doing I'm trying so people stop
running over your lawn oh you know what
carry on sir that's actually a great
idea thank you my son anyway hello gang
that is the vlog if you're not a part of
the family make sure to subscribe to
push the button second in the face kiss
down map enjoy the Strongs family on
youtube a family of mavericks a family
of people who do things differently a
family of people who are going to f-----
actually Denver can you get up okay just
let me fog guys Logan Paul calm /op low
gay I love you and I'll see you tomorrow
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I got one
I got one
[Music]
sometimes you gotta write a new love
song to that out