what are you doing just swimming with my
koi in my pond that I have now oh yeah
that's right you guys didn't see
yesterday's blog you're losing out that
means you're not in the lo game you're
not in the lo game what are you doing
bro subscribe we have a pond now we have
fish things are changing for the better
it was a bleak day now it's a sunny day
it was a bland day
now it's Sun fun day but put the fun in
funeral the funnel yeah
it doesn't make any sense we have so
much fun we die oh my so as most you
guys know the wildfires in California
right now are terrible my manager Jeff
had to evacuate his house he's literally
staying with us right now but here's
what we're experiencing our pool it's
all just ash bro hopefully my house
doesn't burn down some material object
you get it but like I'll be upset plus
we got a bunch of new stuff like this
chair it's so good at begging one it's
so susceptible to wildfire it's just a
giant wooden rocking chair oh this is
actually anyways we got this giant
wooden chair so I also decided to bring
my giant friend over really yeah I mean
it looks oh you're stealing it you call
these up and sewed them all together
they still wouldn't fit you guys did
this boy wake it up okay oh the bow bows
the tall guy looking I wouldn't beat you
up if I could reach you I would beat you
I believe you I believe you would you
would have fun think that anyway doctor
holy [ __ ]
[Music]
next the phone he's tall also I just
want to congratulate you on the
pregnancy Oh yup guys I'm pregnant
[Music]
yup guys I'm pregnant
you guys got a new pet this is our
Chinese albino softshell turtle his name
is pancake lady Oh what do you think of
pancake no Lydia how could you think
he's ugly this is pancake the turtle
[Music]
he's still in there he's doing his tank
that's a pancake that's pancake a
pancake pancake difference here's a real
pancake not a baby
easy there mr. tall man Lydia come on
Lydia look at her
what about this penis-looking turtle
grosses you out cute look while we're
here there you go got you pancake no pet
turtle of mine goes on maverick
Logan Poldark laughs /op Lincoln the
merch store yeah I'm not some real
Mensch today I respect it I really go
he's a maverick he's different bro it's
cool today
[Music]
and we're gonna take the cool bus to a
sports facility to throw a ball or
something manly written everywhere I'm a
savage in fact I'm a nun tint my
electric window so everyone can see just
how manly we are the bus what are the
rules what no teeters no Peters oh no
chatters no goddamn definitely no tutors
[Music]
I'm literally stunned right now this is
pretty solid people have done this
people have done this tonight huh
I have people done this and I yeah when
it was getting hard these are all signs
are called feel like I feel like cold
temperatures for me or just like I'm
cool
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I feel good I feel ironically warmed up
all I need is a bull perfect alright
guys this is Casey Patterson he competed
in the Rio Olympics you were there too
right I was there too every way I've
seen this video got removed from the
Internet 60 million views rest in peace
okay I brought my boys you're doing the
tape little man
Casey I want to have you serve and then
we're all gonna try done qualifier oh I
feel like like I'd know my boys an
athlete but I feel like he's just not
gonna have luck with this it's just like
looking at the size difference I got
good luck at it
[Applause]
baby about it nope no you're up Freddy
[Music]
I know this man but protects everything
thanks Evan that's my boy oh you suck at
being seven feet
whoa i'ma kill you problem you know what
I'm doing all right now we're gonna try
to catch a ball here's the caveat can
someone tell me how fast this ball goes
at 70 miles an hour we're gonna work up
to a hundred yeah let's just start at
okay buddy hit me right in the nose 100
miles an hour's pretty fast my pride is
too big I gotta catch a ball
[Music]
middle [ __ ] get him in the know for
what's the look for huh
what sniffle and it fell I would never
let you down
[Music]
oh go you deflected it yeah new
deflection like I don't think I can do
sports I don't think so either hey I
don't think so either
okay pretty fun day pretty manly day but
you know guys being a man doesn't always
mean playing sports or catching balls
sometimes you got to take the time to
rest and recover and just chill out boys
up here with these puppy things on our
lives do exactly they help you recover
faster so you wanna she's a little
camera-shy I definitely I definitely
feel that how you guys do you guys feel
like you're recovering faster look it
behind me there's this dome it's called
the soma dome it's for meditation
brennick you get closer and it looks
dope it's like Andy you're perfect god
you're not part of the logo make sure
you subscribe you don't even have to be
a man you don't have to do manage it it
could be a woman doesn't matter
subscribe to me smack the button in the
face and you haven't gotten your math at
Merced you look at it bro Savage we got
the best stuff in the game the hottest
stuff in the game this stuff is double
game everyone want to be a maverick I
understand I get it I wear the clothing
every day look the performance shorts
today they perform it's the best hands
down looking for like on slash shop or
Lincoln if you joined the movement baby
that shadow getting I love you on I'll
see you tomorrow