I Will Smith we're challenging you thank
you
it's a power moves type of morning
thanks miss I'm beautiful bro good
morning everyone
I hope you're feeling the same way as
Mike even if sometimes it's not true did
you just grab me you vegan pieces
[Music]
subscribe if you're not subscribed
already joined the low gang gang gang so
today's the big day mix in the morning
way to we're jumping off a bridge today
I had to wake up my roommates earlier
we're going bungee jump okay so most of
them were already raking awake Oh rake
they were already before we get to the
bungee-jumping this group of guys
actually me might meet my friends here
we did a little boy street boy muscle
place called Big Sur super dope
beautiful here's some highlights from
that
[Music]
here was a team maverick being complete
degenerate in nature and now they seem
to be attempting to host something to
social media it's a horse with a man
look at this thing this is the kind of
thing you don't help paper directions
can you make that noise again
okay now never make henna go there are
so many words can you stop making noise
you sound like a turtle having sex where
is Spencer all I see is urine he said
we're crossing three rivers good thing I
wore these white pants those white shoes
ain't in that white hoodie cause last
shot maybe I couldn't take the hottest
words in the game uh-huh yeah I signed
my waiver terrifying cuz you know you
don't read them you have to resist that
amazing I don't need this I don't need
that zipper just missing him by the way
this was his idea to go bungee jumping
our instructor is behind this you're
telling me just to do who drives a
Corvette where's my life that seems a
bit weird but okay I'm in too deep dude
crossing once again after five miles of
hiking two and a half hours we finally
reached the bridge to nowhere literally
that's what it's called probably nowhere
oh my god in my mind it's a great idea
chances of the cord like snapping and
falling on a rock pretty good okay
what's the purpose of this bridge I
noticed it runs into the side of a
mountain
why else would have made this bridge I
feel more comfortable jumping out of a
plane to be on something about jumping
out of a plane is lightly more
comfortable these are brand new thanks
for watching Oh sixteen idea
Will Smith we should get like Will Smith
go and challenge him to do like a bunny
hop out of a helicopter over Osram
Canyon holy Will Smith I don't like
after over the Grand Canyon yeah I don't
I don't mean to be the guy huh
yes they already did that what'd you say
yes dear he already did yes theory
already did what everything that you
just described really yeah
alright alright alright hit rock bottom
pieces I've been there this whole year
I believe I can fly I believe I can
touch the sky yo Mike - bro I'm really
nervous
[Music]
worst-case scenario you go for a little
swim right bringing the leg here we go
oh that's not that was really sick they
brought one more time
[Applause]
[Music]
I Will Smith we're challenging you
[Applause]
yeah some real man I'm surprised huh
dopey but I always sit though I can't
wait to do that with Will Smith out of a
helicopter over the Grand Canyon he
still doesn't get it Oh apparently going
back is it's crazy why ahsoka counts of
course you so what not which would know
oh yeah maverick what
Bhaiji oh there's a y'all think I look
dumb right now nah what is happening for
the first time in my life I'm not the
dumbest looking one at a thing talk
about nothing nothing you're fine talk
you're beautiful damn bro you got a
Kardashian t-rex ass this is the dumbest
thing I've ever seen in my life
yo t-rex arms the dresses are not
extinct welcome to Logan Paul vlogs this
is where we do dumb [ __ ] also subscribe
to impulsive video not yet and that's
how the t-rex went extinct wow what a
day what a fun day what fun time I know
that's it for the vlog today if you're
not subscribed make sure to hit that
subscribe button during the lo game and
I secure it also impulsive by the way
featuring my two roommates is absolutely
poppin off so subscribe to that channel
as well do you know we dated the same
girl are you still together no oh this
is wait that okay this isn't awkward
then yeah it's cool did you come on
thinking that was still a thing I have
no idea
holy Shh gonna put the link for that in
the description obviously mavin merged
how to stop smirking the game you know
where to get it Logan Paul that kind of
slash shop link for that is also in the
description I am getting so good at
talking fast thank you for watching I'll
see you guys next I'm thinking yes
[Music]
ah