notice the seasoned dishes knows we're
not recording you ignore that giant
camera no it's not recording yo good
morning lo gang what no so I got this
like dirt road deep gravel voice low
gang I think I'm getting sick Logan what
are you wearing a bro I've been waiting
for this vlog for some time now check
out that new the metallic chrome
maverick it looks so fresh and when we
take it off we got this sure you saw
yesterday yeah maverick much baby we are
innovating the game we are lighten up
lighten up the world
anyways yo the Mavericks man we see life
through the lens of possibility and
today we are doing a new merge drop also
just drop these brand new low game phone
cases never seen before so that's
exciting but that's not the reason I'm
like fully excited by the way good
morning good catch I think we got my man
Franco music can we get a little preview
Frank we got a little some winds going
north just full of talented branding
quick question am i bleeding from here
bro a little bit yeah I cut myself
shaving
[Music]
okay anyways here's why I'm special
today's world oh wow what is my gang are
you ever in a position where like you
know someone really messed up and you
just are so excited to like call them
out for it yeah Haley did it all the
time do exactly brows speaking of cutest
barkis ever done edible I don't think
yeah edible anyways that's what this
vlog is bro we are gonna call someone
out actually multiple people who stuff
so hard unlike
legal level and a moral level judging by
the title of this video you probably
already know what it is but we do have
one thing to do first as you guys know a
while ago I bought a school bus I'm not
actually on the phone I just wanted to
plug the phone case anyways I bought a
school bus and I named it the cool bus
cuz it's the coolest school bus on the
road and then I dropped it off at West
Coast custom they are currently decking
it out they wanted me to come in today
to check on the progress that's what
we're doing broke hey Brendon Brendon
what get ready okay where's you got me
bro I printed out some samples oh my oh
my goodness so the entire bus is gonna
be wrapped in this like blue green like
iridescent color that's the color right
yeah great yellow colorblind yet cool
obviously the Maverick logo right here
smack that y'all saw it last time and I
promise you the next time you see it
it's gonna be even crazier the bamboo
vibes oh we don't want to show too much
yeah you're right you're right okay how
many speakers did you say you're gonna
be in the area plus okay I don't want to
give it away it's gotta be a surprise
how's it coming together cool but no I
music
[Music]
everyone just called job okay good stuff
anyways I think your shower leg sings or
something squared
yeah you just fill your water you just
said my shower sings that wasn't you
prank oh you don't have to check it out
sort of just since we're gonna check now
Frank it's okay I'm gonna fix it it's
weird yeah he's an interesting one for
sure
yo you know what I know why ever not
brought this up yet look who came to
town bro it's my dad I love you maverick
pendant savage t-shirt maverick cat you
look good in my new van gogh's actually
mine so haha I still hear my shower
singing bro
all right I'm gonna throw my hand my
CFPB I'm gonna go oh I knew with you why
this is a dumb joke you made ruining my
time oh whoa not exactly that's my
friend Lydia calm down Fred we like we
like your hair Frank is not good number
six
tell Frank he's cute right when he wakes
up bro did you do that I wasn't with you
when you woke up though I don't even I
don't even like your night in that queue
bro back to the real vlog it's like time
to expose some people I need some help
with that my man ever brah are you down
to expose some people whether the Rolex
was sitting in the laundry my hair is
soft but you don't see me in your
laundry I'm gonna forgive you we're
gonna go expose some people dab on them
haters yeah so guys we are in Venice
Beach what I'm about to say doesn't make
sense like I could not make this over
the past two months literally two months
I have been collecting tweets that you
guys have been tweeting at me at Logan
fault yeah basically I never thought I
would be making this vlog or even have
to like say what I'm about to say Oh
maverick merch has gotten so popular
people are literally stealing our
designs putting them in their stores and
making a profit off of me if I find
y'all he loved it and that's exactly
what we're here to do today I've been
saying this it's a movement it's a
revolution this logo is like seeing life
through the lens of possibility people
who are working hard to chase their
dreams and apparently it's gotten so big
literally commercial retail stores are
using me it pisses me off like look at
it here's what we've been looking all
over for at Logan Paul merch but all I
found was this shady merch that's that's
a great way to describe it also if you
notice my brother's mergers in there too
why has the commercial world decided to
just steal our oh yeah cuz we're lit hey
Logan Paul found these at my mother's if
you look closely there's the maverick
logos there's the lo gang there's the
savvy looking ball more from the same
store here in Clearwater
hashtag fake maverick merch I don't even
know where clear water is but look it's
the savage logo how did the merch get in
a store all the way in Florida
adjectives in public I don't I don't
know I could wish I can answer the
question oh my gosh why are they our
sale maverick merch there's the golden
maverick in the you good bro survey bro
like well I like take the survey
yourself dog okay my guys losing my cool
I'm fake maverick merchants with Scott
win-win concert no I was in Ocean City
Maryland oh you're from Maryland it's
your big day and I was thinking it was
real Merce and I bought a hoodie and and
I walked out they told me who was Nick
off what is Nick off San Francisco
Delaware another Wisconsin New York
State Fair Old Orchard Beach Maine
Seaside Heights New Jersey I could go on
and on bro
go on and on bro and and worst part bro
they're doing it here in Venice Beach in
my home state of California
I'm from Ohio but I currently live in
California yo shut the front door here's
where this is an issue that come here
like okay they're recreating the logo
obviously we know it's the dopest the
mankind what our quality I spent months
trying to find the company that could
produce the quality that this is
see that's what I'm saying he gets
confused cuz he thinks it's a pill to
know it's murder I was fired
oh so today we're gonna find these
people Philip no okay not gonna kill him
we're just gonna call Nam bro like this
is my merch what do you do obviously
though I have to come up with the
disguise so I brought just the thing you
guys up in the sky seat bridge no reason
oh who you are it's not the disguise yet
guys perfect this guy it's not in
disguise your guy mustache yeah I got
you too
okay trust me no one's gonna know that I
am Jake Paul's brother okay I Logan pop
I gotta say I've never worn a better
disguise in this like obviously you have
no idea who I am you have no idea who
this is like who is that dwarf mama
Edward long [ __ ] I don't think so also I
had Lydia print out these notice to
cease and desist maverick notice to
cease and desist dear infringer
basically blah blah blah blah blah legal
legal I'm gonna sue you you have to take
down my merch nobody makes money off of
me except me and my boys in the fellow
Lowe gang let's do this so we're just
walking down the boardwalk here trying
to find our first culprit look I get it
guys you want to make money it's just
like don't disrespect the brand bro we
all you're changing the world hey we
should pop in one of these shelves on
your shirt do you uh do you see this
logo anywhere in here we can make it no
no it's all good you're in the clear
that guy was a good guy I could tell in
his eyes
have you seen this logo anywhere you're
a good lady okay I can see in your eyes
what you think all right are you famous
something no not at all
yeah this is totally working bro this is
totally working I feel like I'm getting
warmer this is a bit of a treasure hunt
one come on oh yo whose owner of the
star bingo brother behind me are you the
owner of the store why are you selling
this logo like you own it I know this
guy on YouTube he does this dope brand
it's called maverick
and I see one of them up there and I'm
like yo that's not the real maverick
brand come here I'm gonna show you
what's that bro it's a design no it's
not a design it's the brand bro are you
good bro I'm good I'm gonna need you to
stop selling my merch at your shop like
you own it like this is illegal so I'm
just gonna go ahead and throw this up
here notice to see some vicious nose
we're not recording you ignore that
giant camera no it's not recording good
session I'm not wearing a moustache no
it's not
gimmicks oh she's cute this is gonna be
hard the stock ah damn it she's cute
interesting I'll use a shop owner no I
have bad news you're conducting illegal
activities I mean all right go ahead
so we are we are gonna have to place a
few cease-and-desist here it's just that
what sure I'll save it for later the
issue is you guys are selling my logo
you know likes yours and I don't know
how to say that it's not it's mine so
can I talk to the shop owners here
there's a shop owner can I talk to you
outside for a sec hi Logan nice to meet
you walk by your stop I'm just trying to
like you know be a good person and I see
you guys are selling my merch like it's
yours you know and like I get it it
sounded like a god Church but you just
can't do it taking it off like
like if you're taking off like I'm
chilling oh do it
thank you brother appreciate it okay so
this is going alright there's not that
many shops stealing maverick merch in
Cali kind of sucks that our disguises
fell off but I always come prepared oh
yeah boys got some sideburns it does not
get more of much realistic illness damn
them I look good you can't even know
where hi how are you so I came to
infiltrate the dealer and find the
supply who's your supplier hi I came to
supply who's your supplier he's not here
all right I'm gonna go find it and
infiltrate infiltrate the dealer fun to
supply yep I'm gonna be honest bro I
don't know I don't know why you're
taking a picture
are you the supply you're not the supply
are you the supplier you're not the
supplier I'm from Ohio
he's gonna grow are you the supply
you're not the supply I'm from Ohio
I've come to infiltrate the dealer and
find the supply where is the supply
where's the supply the supply of the
Maverick March oh don't play dumb I know
your tricks don't take this offensively
but this shop smells suspicious you
don't even have to go to Logan Paul back
on slash shop I'm gonna put that right
here bro you owe me a hundred percent
commission that's all I'm asking yo see
this is what I'm saying
look at the blank hoodie up there dude
the new drop we slap the chrome Maverick
on it
this is Hoss dude every second of time
that passes I get more suspicious I use
the supply for the maverick I'm from
Ohio and my merch is selling like a god
shirt I dread to think of my phone and
my beard is just chilling on the Logan
case it's been me Logan all along guys
yo I think we did our due diligence
today like I mean like states I need to
attack bro Wisconsin New Jersey Delaware
Maryland Maryland disappointed right now
get just now right so I had to come here
I had to lay down oh no nobody all
honesty guys I'm not mad I just don't
believe it let's be honest I need a vlog
content from I do this every day
but yeah also don't don't don't try to
make money off of me don't do that okay
I think it's time to go home do you want
to hold hands and skip off into the
distance
and okay little gang that is the vlog
I'm excited about this drop rolling we
raise the level again never merged baby
to the top and it and I'm approaching my
one year of laga versary on September
12th I will have been vlogging every day
for a year every day bro it just gets
better and better we're gonna have an
exclusive piece of content for that as
well so get ready for that you can get
this stuff as you know Logan Paul that
comp slash shop or link in description I
said I will see you tomorrow you know I
just like let's get deep for a sec I'm
feeling good right now and I'm just
thankful I'm blessed man I'm glad to
have you guys in my life and I know I
say this a lot but I actually mean when
I say yeah okay y'all I love you and I
will see you tomorrow take it easy ma'am
you're not part of the law game make
sure to the back
[Music]
oh sorry sorry I'm not a bad person I'm
just a vlogger
which might be a version of a bad person
I don't know