dear Shane Dawson I tweeted this before
the series was out when the teaser was
released I said don't underestimate hard
work trains teaser just turned into or
did first off I love what I'm seeing I
love it Shane you are an amazing content
creator you are changing the game you
are paving the landscape of what could
be the future of YouTube and Shane knows
this I I'm friends with Shane I'm
cordial with him we DM today it was
romantic and but when I'm watching this
series there's just a few things I
thought I was trying to stay out of it
by I want I need to address them because
Shane the people are watching this
you're young and impregnable audience
you're young and impenetrable audience
you're young and impressionable audience
will not know any better so I'm here to
cut that [ __ ] once again makes a whistle
noise when I drink that's the first
stuff like I said I think information is
being told in a way that is extremely
misleading and that's what I'm here to
clarify also I get that not everyone
likes my brother and me included like
the Paul family is just currently
surrounded by controversy a fault of our
own plot but he made a comment in
episode one that just tickled me the
wrong way cuz I could like I know he's a
good dude
and that's why this content works cuz
everything he's doing is so genuine and
authentic and you will watch this dude
for 45 minutes straight who's doing that
on YouTube no one and you gotta like him
too
he's a likable guy for the record by the
way Shane also said in Episode two Logan
I feel like it's more likable
thanks man I'm going off on a tangent
ways in episode 1 right at the beginning
as he's setting the stage he said this I
thought it was just cringing you know
yeah that's all I can might be Logan I
didn't know they were different I don't
know why you said that cuz you know
that's not true I think it was cuz it's
very easy to also hop on the train of
like I don't like the polls he's one of
the biggest youtubers in the world like
he knows who you guys are not only that
about two years ago I hung out with
Shane for like an hour and half I did
his
Podcast you're gonna start did it start
odd oh I was on his podcast Shane and
friends featuring Logan Paul I think we
sat in the same room and talked for like
an hour so either a you're not telling
the truth be you forgot Who I am
amnesia classic classic YouTube brand or
C like I said it's it immediately gets
people on board to be like oh you're
right I didn't even know there's two
maybe I anyways he said this and I
started to not doubt but immediately I
was like well how much of this will be
truthful but again I'm going on a
tangent the original point I'm trying to
say is Shane you you are scaring your
young and interminable honey you are
scaring your young and Independence Day
audiences like this whole a second
episode is just suspense music and then
the b-roll the b-roll where did you buy
this b-roll
did you get this stock footage that is
not getting I would love to see your
search history human eats human out of
hands
why are you doing cannibalism who's the
sociopath man series is making me ask so
many questions no but this is this leads
into the point of what I want to say to
that is actually educational the meat of
this video that you guys can stick in
the back of your mind from when you're
watching the rest of the series the
buzzword that Shane is focusing on in
the reason why he's sitting down at this
therapist house who also offered in the
drink is sociopath so she's a sociopath
so she sociopath sociopath again before
I say anything guys i DM shane about
this I gave him my opinions because I
it's quite simply it is not black and
white
99% of the time someone is not a
sociopath or not a sociopath my opinion
is there's a sociopathic spectrum at
which point some people lie higher on it
than others and by the way some of the
biggest businessmen in the world could
be considered sociopathic mark jobs no
Steve Zuckerberg Mark Zuckerberg and
Steve Jobs a lot of people especially
youtubers and Shane touched on this you
can't just say like you're a sociopath
the word I would like to use is
sociopathic tendencies so a lot of us me
included
we'll do some dumb [ __ ] be some stuff
that lacks empathy strictly for views
right it gets us views which gets us
subscribers a motivating factor is to
reach the next next next level sociopath
is boil down someone who is just more
savage than everyone else I know it
sounds stupid but I'm making it easier
for you to understand cuz the way a
sociopath was described in part 2 of the
series quite honestly could be applied
to most people someone even tweeted at
Shane I need a voice of concern Ashley
and Dawson this isn't a call-out but how
much thought was put into the idea that
after a video like your latest that any
awkward kid including ones with
disabilities could be labeled a
sociopath due to your audience's
youthful and experience and another
person said if you think about it like
deep down doesn't everybody fit the
scription they gave four sociopaths I
feel like most people I know are that
way and don't even try very hard to hide
it yeah like it's so hard to say and the
big sticking point I'm having with it
Shane I feel like is trying to make out
a sociopath to be synonymous with
Psychopaths the words sound very similar
but mean very different things and again
for the young and interpret all audience
they will confuse the two and think
psychopathy means sociopath
not the case in fact in Shane's video
itself Hillel say the word and then show
the word psychopathy I want to talk to a
psychologist if he is a sociopath hey
everybody today I want to talk to you
about the word psychopathy and I want to
make that clear because even in Shane's
video itself there's a couple times
where he will say the word sociopath but
show something psychopathic or even show
the word psychopathy I heard Steve Jobs
I don't care about that I heard Steve
Jobs was a sociopath yet the thing says
with Steve Jobs of psychopaths what say
yes you're confusing people and the
reason I'm so intrigued and feel
compelled to say something about this is
because at the beginning of the year I'm
gonna open up here for a sec you guys
can imagine tons of people even people
in my circle close friends like yo your
sociopaths straight up and I didn't know
what the word met cuz I like is it a
psychopath is that what it is so I
looked it up and I had to ask myself I'm
like Oh sociopaths and for sure some
things I fit the description of that's
why I'm saying I prefer if we're gonna
label Jake a sociopath or not doing it
on a spectrum and where he lies on it
because again it's not just black and
white to quote the great Aristotle
there's levels to this so is Shane a
sociopath I don't know he's like clearly
I don't want to say forcing but these
reactions seem a little socio-economic
you know this bro I love you this is a
classic case of dramatics
on YouTube yo Logan I left your car keys
on the counter I don't know bro he's a
genuine authentic guy but I get I feel
like some of this is slightly theatrical
cuz I just don't think this reaction
elicits itself in every sentence like
you see that easily jarred in real life
like by simple things well last time say
I've met him what did when you shook his
hand was he like but 10% of me 10% of
that Shane was existent just like bro
you mean me in real life like I'm pretty
calm like whatever but I have that part
of me it's like but does that make me a
sociopath according to this therapist
check it then they also are impulsive if
I was impulsive I would use that clever
pun because my last name is Paul
impulsive and create a podcast coming
sooo to a screen near you I'm also not
wearing pants does that make me a
sociopath I have a [ __ ] pig this
video it's not black and white
sociopathic to be quite honest with you
it's nothing to be like scared of like
if your friend might be a sociopath or
has sociopathic tendencies he's not
gonna stab you in the middle of the
night when you're not looking I don't
think cuz what if he's a sociopath an
aside then you plenty simple you look
I'm excited for the rest of this series
I literally have no idea what it's about
or where it's going as much as I love
Jake we don't talk like normal brothers
do I think as much as we should our
family's a bit that if you couldn't tell
but I think that wraps up today's vlog
if you're not a part of the look yeah
yeah yeah yeah make sure to subscribe
Shane I love you bro like I said you're
doing an amazing job you are a pioneer
man and it's incredible to see that it's
been a while since that new wave hit
YouTube you're a maverick bro you
remember I'm gonna send you some goddamn
merch is definitely definitely doing it
different
respect bro guys if you're not shane
dawson and are not receiving a free care
package of merch from me hey cop
yourself some of the hottest softest
sociopathic merch in the game link in
description low guy I love y'all and I
will see you next time take it easy fam
so
[Music]
is that woman in sociopath