if you guys remember yesterday's vlog
Jake came over to my house and he made
slime and he threw it on my car thank
you and then during the whole storm
Jake kicked over this cooler that has
had rotting food in it for literally two
weeks and it smelled like my grandma's
toejam and I threw up we made it
rainbows cuz I don't know about all
those rainbows okay that's cool we had
an idea then we're gonna just put it
back in the cooler including the slime
and all the disgusting food I didn't see
funny reaction smell it smell it
oh my god that is gnarly hey thanks a
lot Jake you deserve this prank the
little rug rat is sly mom it's all over
my driveway nice words real omelet so
now we're gonna go dump it at the team
10-ounce you understanding if you put it
in the house of what's going to come
back if that smells that bad what can be
worse dude 24/7 security and and a
vicious guard dog who is somewhere
around here there is hi if you see a guy
that looks like nice name's Jay he's a
big blond Chooch he's not as tall as me
he's not was good-looking got a YouTube
channel less subscribers than me a like
and subscribe I the way join the low
games strongest family on the Internet I
command you to stop him stick your
tongue out if you understand good dog we
gotta get the cooler inside the bus
stuff like put on his hands Matt suit
Boop this is the only way bro this dish
is just straight toxic this is the kind
of thing where if you adjust it bro your
babies will have like eight limbs
downloading component nine into the boss
this thing opens or spills in the
slightest way that is a wrap
I'm literally everyone in the bus all of
us will have octo babies and I don't
want that gentlemen all aboard the boss
please be reminded component nine is a
coup follow all
the morning also just real quick try to
breathe through your butthole to avoid
inhaling through your nose that can not
spill grow there are human lives at
stake
secure the package all seals just blows
them up drive a little more steady
please sir guns arriving steady bite
I don't want to lick of air coming
through that container
the compound with component nine if you
notice is leaving the bus in the street
Jake is smart every time we prank him he
comes out he like throws eggs in my car
but not today
no his driveway is really long so after
we throw this we got a Huck it like the
mild my boy is right your taco Spencer
all jokes aside I've secured all my
belongings in the amazing maverick
joggers zipper pocket and I just want to
say plain and simple maverick by Logan
Paul has changed my life let's do this
pick up the bass little bit
diving they'd dive my friend
go to the video I saved you why you
gotta hide
whoa Wow that was crazy
you have some setbacks mainly a giant
dog dealer riding my butt cheeks but
other than that smooth operation guys
yeah you almost lost your ass bro I hope
that was my right butt cheek bro which I
need oh I see me honey it's like yeah
after seeing the way Jake's dogs attack
I just I feel like Kong needs a little
more training oh I'm so hot I'm sweating
my wiener off right now oh you guys are
hot I'm dressed in freaking foil I'm a
baked potato Wow mission successful and
guys I have some other good news yeah
yeah we hired a guy to powerwash the
driveway so no more slime omelets yeah I
will stay for the ones in the grass
that's a whole nother issue but we're
working on it
well well before we set up the blog guys
look who we have here so far why wait
bringing eggplants in my house just not
so ugly like that what do you think this
is some sort of show show it show them
the boomerang you just took look what is
this look perfect waving around the
eggplant like it's nobody's business bro
who are you
my lady and by the way that wasn't even
a boomerang that was her doing okay okay
I think she's gonna try to cook a vegan
dinner I think okay yeah I was right
maybe you guys are not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe smash the
button kiss another mouth huntingtin
face dab on it oh she's still on that
thing
all right and also guys don't forget we
just dropped these new dare to fly
shirts we got the Maverick Spencer's
wearing the blue joggers it's the
hottest merch in the game icon that
worldwide hoodie flow yard you don't
know where to get it Logan ball that cop
slash shop or linea description every
day we out here challenging ourselves
we're out here doing a different that's
the movement mic toss me that I play
ball she's freaking out low gang I love
y'all I'll see you tomorrow
[Music]