Nico a gentle Cinquecento cinquecento
means 500 this is the Fiat 500 it's like
a little coupe car all the way from
Italy first okay oh good morning little
guy who is father
I smell the pollution
oh I'm inhaling the pollution I'm vegan
perfect vegan pollution we're fine
hi I feel like now it's a good time to
say even out a particle okay to make
sure you subscribe with the most with
Channel family friends on YouTube bro
[Music]
yesterday we almost lost Kong he's just
so tiny it's so explores to be such a
fun good-natured dog huh I think the
electric-fence guys coming today so he
doesn't run away for good that's right
Kong the whole low gang loves yeah we
need you buddy and then he just any ways
yeah lots of good stuff going on today
as usual the merchants selling everybody
wants to be a maverick
my boy Evan actually you're getting a
new car today huh did you get a
cinquecento BMW oh I haven't seen the
BMW we got a Mercedes we got a bus we
got a Jeep we had a cinquecento we got a
spanish girl got a really dumb dog we
got a really dumb owner of the dog we
got a dwarf
we got a tying guy and uh Frank
[Music]
I'm back at that new shiny car you make
me proud boy mr. boy
I like that wood thing yo I didn't tell
you guys but we got a giant statue to
put in front of our gym in the back
everything about this house is lit bro
[Music]
vlogger bro it's not what I do not now
not ever
wait a minute why didn't you tell me you
were a blogger now you know you've been
hiding that for me this whole time
all right boys up in the Cinquecento Wow
why would this not work what's wrong you
you look great
yeah hop in oh absolutely
oh no don't move everyone calm down
come on me we have the Yeti but we're
choosing you did you shoot my friend
hello yes Italia okay thank you
no worries baby we take it right away
very quick Sportiva man whatever man
[Music]
all right
we are going on the freeway here we go
we're gonna freeway here we come baby
[Music]
by this
[Applause]
[Music]
okay yo that was like that was like a
zombie apocalypse oh I probably you have
no idea numbers what pull over what what
your dog died what I thought she was
getting surgery well are you serious or
hell what did they say happened
are you we haven't is this for real he's
nothing with you this is sad bro oh man
have it I don't like to see you cry I
love you bro we love you and we all love
you Evan love you bro yo I'm gonna take
someone this is a life lesson how quick
how quick things can change everything
was so good literally hilarious two
minutes ago 60 seconds later my friend
is in shambles
[Music]
that's what are you would want us to do
in the name of
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you got a new car that's cool you have a
new BMW so I'm just like what's just
happening right now I have like meat so
what happened our vitals were fine all
throughout the surgery everything is
fine the anesthesia was perfect and then
after surgery they went to give her
x-rays like see how the surgery went
then they came back then also and she
was pale so then they just said she went
into cardiac arrest and died cause of
death they don't know death was never
discussed in this they don't say oh she
has this much chance of whoa whoa you
called me even right now like you could
be messing with me yeah like that's what
it feels like it just doesn't make any
sense oh she's having a surgery on her
leg yeah
don't bro
this is cool though we got we got quite
the squad of vehicles here oh yeah bro
cool buzz the yeti chief with andis tent
on top evans brand new BMW and echoed -
Quinta Buchi quano
and Frank so yeah it all looks good and
stuff it's just the vibes I know I look
really serious and sad I I don't like
seeing Evan sad that's what that's what
makes me like uneasy about this
situation
he's my best friend and it always sucks
when you see people that you know or
love and pain whether emotional or
physical so this is like like you guys
know I keep the button - vlogs fun and
exciting but sometimes they do get real
I might go with you as Tim used to share
my life with you so you guys can live it
with me and that's what we've done we've
built this family like I feel like a
legitimately hopefully you feel the same
way it's like like I owe things to you
and just like give me your time watch my
vlogs and there's a trade-off my life
has become very real to you guys
Congress that's why we call ourselves
the Logan
[Music]
okay low gang that is the vlog I want to
say a couple things before we sign off
first off I'm sorry for your loss
genuinely this guy spent a lot of time
with Aria he cared for her so stay
strong I'm with you the whole low gangs
with you we got your back too this makes
me thankful for what I have
the little rascal over there I love you
bro I didn't even know that his his
sister's gone on the sad yeah it's gonna
feel weird it's gonna feel weird for the
next few days probably more for him than
me why you so quiet bro you're making is
there anything you want to say have you
learned anything if you have you taken
away anything you're just kind of like
absorbing it just feels weird but make
sure you don't take anything for granted
that's what I was saying like I dropped
this dog off like death was literally
the last thing the last thing guys she's
just a jumpy little fun dog okay so yeah
guys like you saw today life can change
in an instant so so live in the moment
live passionately and do what you want
to do man cuz it's way too short
unfortunately it is just a fact of life
and another fact of life is literally
right now you can get your March on
Logan Paul calm sighs be a maverick vote
no no no whoo you got to get to the mood
light hard it's gotta be fun again
that's what we do low gang that you're
in the low gang and if you're not
subscribe we do the stories that must be
the best family on you to ever we will
be back tomorrow
my boo is gonna attack the world with
fervor and veracity
for the entrance you can get a vintage
on the
I know give me a minute man I might need
a bit more peace of mind alright on a
rickshaw Oh
a pigsty in my mind and I live for