it was like you're my roommate been a
lot of for a lotta for too much for
tonight literally a bogan Paul was
taking on Twitch follow me there but
thanks anyway it's been about four night
it's been about twitching yeah but today
it's about vlogging you're skiing right
oh yeah
fasten I know all the things I want to
do there's only one thing I will do
today kiss dudes on the mouth ah that
was not what I was planning but I'm okay
with it I'm three two three we got a lot
of concerts today we're just gonna dive
right into it
uh-oh good morning good morning and uh
guys been a part of the logging how you
doing my name is Logan Paul it's my dong
every day my goal is to entertain you
distract you from your busy life here to
make you laugh smile father your
children whatever it is okay so yeah
subscribe you're not a part of the
family because as you just saw
sometimes we happen like we are about to
do now this is Damon he is a mural
artist he paints mural here's an example
of a mural Damon actually painted that
one very talented guy he painted me a
mural oh god but I do have bad news that
comes with this mural that I actually
haven't told you yet but we'll figure it
out I think yeah let's get this puppy
inside pocket make sure you okay I see
these guns bro check it out bro you got
a concealed carry permit oh god yo see
yo just I'm gonna let go for one sec
guys this is part of the fort night
problem you guys know I started I
started playing fort nighttime twitching
now at Logan Polk was taken if you want
to subscribe there why'd you call it
that because logo was so my roommate
Evan is building me a computer to stream
on and whatnot you finish it yet and
there's just there's a lot of stuff in
the room and we want to put the painting
on this wall right next to my penis
turtle pancake a pancake looking more
like a penis than a tree building a
computer or a bathroom I don't know oh
[ __ ] it
watch out for the computer
and the penis turtle oh no they got
anything happens I'm not someone out six
grand here we go it is an oil painting
after all just making up words over
there computer live to fight another day
hey when this is going to be done by the
way I might be wondering like what
exactly is it well these are some of
your favorite social media stars right
here we got Lele pons we got Wampus
Reed's
got amanda cerny we got battalions under
that scheme we got Chloe bridges we got
a boy LP we got king batch arielle
vandenberg nick bateman damn looking sex
nick swardson with a badly and the
monkey and they're all hanging out and
Logan with a movie coming out this is a
painting for my movie airplane mode you
guys have probably heard a lot about it
if you haven't here's a preview
it was almost about to come out
obviously yeah we had we had to push it
it's amazing post it's really yeah it's
phenomenal it just I don't know what
this movie is coming out this is the
gaming room now yeah we're gonna have to
move it yeah yeah it looks much better
up there
yeah looks dope up there I'm just
straddling that airplane good stuff bro
yeah so okay that looks dope something
else that's dope though we have a
professional BMX rider transitions
everywhere everywhere bilities bro
you know who signed the waiver waiver
yeah they say no one to be flipping over
cool what say you know just be careful
cuz we never break anything so just like
[Applause]
I'll sign away via on the waiver signing
you ate those wafers yeah okay the roof
is you know I'll bet you got a hug
pull away late could be wait that's my
manager he signed the waiver I hear you
alright look when I put the bounce house
ball pit in my room the original intent
will buy Celia the original intent was
not for me to break my $20,000
chandelier thus rendering it useless
so we can't really jump on it and I'm
gonna be honest guys the original intent
of these balls was not to do but rather
we have a guest bedroom and there's like
this weird spot like here let me show
you yeah we have this guest bedroom but
there's this little spike crawlspace
down here this guy creepy super creepy
so the idea was to get balls and make a
ball pit down there so it's like kind of
fun and not so scary but then it was
like you know how do we transfer them
for my room to here it's a lot of balls
how are we gonna do it good thing I'm a
genius using mainly my brain we've
assembled a tunnel system
what
[Music]
Oh God we're back at the electronics
store you guys know I'm doing the
Twitter now it's me you know the Hat
Logan Paul was taken because Logan Paul
was taken I just call it that because
Logan Paul was think I just listen I
speak but we forgot to get a webcam to
record them you have you see the webcams
let me know we're looking for webcam no
you had your Hawking it way too hard
someone stop those [ __ ] oh Jesus
mother nice hug bro better start the
wave oh no I don't know hey sure no no
he'll need it I'll back the low game
dude you're the best friend all right
oh he needs help as everybody's in oh
wow these are definitely webcam oh so
good at finding me stuff that was like
my roommate
[Music]
tomorrow one Logan bullocks
did Evan truly escape the balls to the
face to Devon attack Mike with a hockey
stick than the English intruder BMX bike
right a sign the waiver did manager Jeff
limit the liability in mitigating
potential insurance claim did look and
poke find true love
make sure to subscribe and tune in
tomorrow to see it our sugar cook
version for the days long also get you
much unloggable becomes a shot
[Music]
make sure to subscribe and tune in
tomorrow to see her sugar conclusion to
today's vlog
[Laughter]