I mean what's the worst that could
happen yeah what are you doing here what
I'm not even kidding low gang look I
worked out this morning I came back here
to my backyard he sat down on this
beautiful wood bench I'm looking at this
koi pond we just had built look at my
dog who can majestic over there like I
don't know or maybe it's the koi pond
everything is so peaceful and beautiful
even friends it's nice today to just
relax and you deserve to do that too so
that's what I'm here to provide you with
baby what's up my name is Logan ball
this is my house welcome to my yard we
call ourselves the low gang and if
you're not a part of the Logan make sure
to subscribe we are this channel you
tell me are you a so peacefully pause to
subscribe button in the face y'all this
feels good I haven't broken a play in a
while oh god damn it I got hit by so
many pieces just out here we're still
trying to come up with names for our koi
here's the video of them
[Laughter]
that's what I'm saying it's just peace
it stressed me out a little bit you know
what I'm thinking about now yeah there's
just plate shrapnel everywhere when
inside and he slipped out his red mirch
why Oh gang I'm planning on dropping the
Christmas diss track tomorrow ah it's
the hardest disdain for pro the victim
of this video I know you know who you
are okay I'm coming for you you're gonna
watch this video you're literally gonna
start crying you gotta stop doing that
it's gross
here's manager job we're sending it to
you I just said it looks like this
what's in the ID you'll see in
tomorrow's vlog I'll talk in the kitchen
no not to eat onions last night 1:30
a.m. since Linda I don't know what I'm
doing up I was eating a bowl of not even
a ball is just a box of cereal
there was the honey bunches of oats here
look it is not a free brand ale I'm
sitting here eating my box and I see a
little bog on the floor and bro it's
like no one likes bugs right exactly
what he's doing
oh yeah see get the bug away or you
could just kill it in its just took the
box and a crunch the bug is on the
outside of the box
yo yo yo let's play a game the game is
called supposed to be dead as a bug Wow
ah yeah yeah so that was weird tortoise
at I killed the bug he's no longer with
us but even sadder there's also someone
else who's no longer
[Music]
going bro what sports with this Porsche
yesterday more sports my boy loves your
sports ok respect I'm gonna miss you bro
give me hug
[Music]
my Evan will miss you bro back in the
kitchen yams everywhere bagels
yo don't get technical with me man
Andy's cooking food no one really knows
what it is but look at that stuff I'm
gonna add a real special ingredient this
time to what that's a sin in my country
and II feel like kind of responsible
they're not responsible but they make
food that we don't make think about it
we have a new transfer mommy penis meat
thank you from here other people we're
gonna eat this and now we just messed up
my whole cutting process the battle
between Mike and Andy begins now
traditional Italian this is comfort food
college student on a budget look what I
got in the mail a vibrator it looks like
what no guys this is a massage thing
look
you are my boy this is like 30 minutes
of massage but you've got to know when
and where and how do you doesn't make me
worry about a 20-17 I'm experimenting
bro Oh Lomo with my cat what else can we
make jiggle on our body you can do so
many things with rope but just one thing
I wanna do I've been wanting to do this
no no no nope what all right when I
first moved into this house I walked in
and I looked up there's two beams up
there in fact let me show you beam 1 and
beam 2 now imagine if your buddy talks
you still got it
and one was able to swing it between the
beams oh that's confetti from this
[Music]
[Applause]
yo Mike why'd you let go bro beef is
getting too real it was an accident
[Music]
doesn't stop here if we put a chair so
we're deciding what chair to use right
now Brendan thinks it's a good idea to
use this chair just unsure cuz it's made
out of wood what is strong please mom oh
it is what's the logic here cuz I'm
sitting here right and if I pull up on
the wood like I feel like I'm already on
we've got these chairs yesterday like
they're brand new so if they break I
will be salty let's get this [ __ ] up in
the air
let's give it a go oh just a maverick
move damn it Andy open up that door I'm
swinging outside from Ohio got a house
big enough to make a swing it early
knows how to tie your shoes yeah and I
think I got one
[Music]
[Applause]
we're all busy we all got stresses out
as long as you can find a day or a thing
or some time to just relax and hang I
think it keeps you mentally sane it does
for me anyways but that's what I'm here
to do for you if you're not a part of
the low game make sure that you have on
the subscribe button and then double tap
on the scout for anything after you're
done doing that go to logn pul comm
slash a shop and copy yourself the
hottest merchants against an average
merchants that maverick movement we
different we okay with it one day at a
time and a few rose petals we changing
the world
hey plus it's the softest merch in the
game it's the hottest merch in the game
everyone wants it and christmas is
coming up so get your maverick merch
link in description
yeah and I think I gotta yeah
[Music]