well
well well mr pewdiepie
how the tables have turned now in the
face of adversity you
my friend have called for the help of
the low
gang gang gang skirt
you see mr pewdiepie if that is your
real name
in the past you know we've had our
differences
but this morning as i ate my bowl of
captain crunch
my dear friend mike came up to me and
showed me the following video
guys the battle with t series is getting
intense
and casualties are high should we call
logan and jake paul for help
is winning worth sacrificing everything
yes okay
all right come on logan what's it gonna
be
that's right i'm that desperate i'll
take any help i can get
oh so now
you call for the help of the logang
butter lass
i'll play your game mr pie after all you
are my colleague my peer
my compadre we make money the same way
we've even made mistakes
the same way we're not so different
after all now
are we mr pie so hello gang
it is time for us to answer the call
at the time of this recording t-series
is less than 400 000 subscribers away
from passing pewdiepie
as the all-time most subscribed youtuber
of all time in history ever
period that falls under the category of
things you hate to see
now i'm only gonna say this one time but
uh technically you can
rewind the video and watch it twice if
you choose to do so but here's how
this is gonna go down logang i have put
a trackable link in the description of
this video that when clicked
will automatically subscribe you to
pewdiepie's channel but
here's where this gets interesting for
each click aka subscriber that we drive
to pewdiepie's channel
trackable only via the link in
description
i logan paul will be donating one
swedish crown
to a charity of my choice as homage to
pewdiepie's country of origin
for those of you who do not know what a
swedish crown is it's like a swedish
fish except less sweet you can't eat it
and it's used to purchase goods in
sweden 10
swedish crowns is equal to about one us
dollar
right so if a million people click the
link and subscribe to pewdiepie
that means i will donate a hundred
thousand dollars to charity now
my team suggested i put a cap on the
donation
in case i don't know 100 million people
click the link and i
in that case would have to lose
everything i own and
that's not good so it's true we've put a
cap on this donation but i will say
it's very very high so the charity i'm
choosing is very dear to me
as part of my continued effort to raise
awareness for the issues of suicide and
mental health the money driven from
these clicks will be donated to the
kevin and margaret heinz foundation
as they aim to continue to normalize the
conversation around suicide prevention
wellness and mental health some of you
may remember kevin hines
is actually the guy featured in my my
video suicide be here tomorrow that i
made at the beginning of this year
we have become dear friends we talk
nearly every day
to this day to this day to this day
and i look forward to helping him carry
the torch towards the solution for this
issue
you can read more about his foundation
in the description below now
[Music]
i do have one condition mr pi in order
for the aforementioned to occur
mr pi you must wear this piece of
maverick merch in one of your upcoming
videos currently being delivered to you
via courtier here's a real-time video of
my assistant hand delivering you the
hottest softest merch in the game
quid pro quo mr pie the ball is in your
court hello gang
do our youtube family proud and
subscribe to our swedish leader man
pewdiepie
by clicking the link in the description
i salute you soldier
carry on in godspeed