dude this vlog is gonna be how to be a
youtuber guys it's not hard no it's not
you all you have to do is create tell
you my q1 grocery shopping today as you
could see here I'm just looking through
here and everything speaking okay it's
official man guys it means I don't mean
anything that comes from animals right
no animal bribe right good five products
is what I meant to say like no milk
right no dairy no meat no steak my water
behind this smart bacon veggie bacon
chips what the is that how does this
this no this it looks like dog food bro
with the French oh it's not real me I
bet my dog wouldn't even eat this car
hello nothing nothing on the contrary
Kong what do you think of this perfectly
non vegan cheese fries let's see how
smart this bacon really it I think you
still have tick I think you still have
to cook it bro this could be a rough
life right so why am i doing it I've
been hearing from some colleague going
vegan makes you feel better enhances the
quality of your muscle fiber and
increases your merch sales Logan Paul
calm slash shop no really though guys we
just drop some new stuff for the ladies
we dropped up with a boyfriend
sweatpants in both black and pink we
drop the staple hoodies for the woman
again in both black and pink and as the
Maverick revolution grows I want to see
you ladies repping him and don't be
afraid to be different man people who
are bullying you people who are saying
you're weird or uncool it's wrong bro
you're cool you're a freakin maverick
plain and simple guys they're wrong
right embrace your difference that's
what makes you unique that's what makes
you special
in other words ready 1 2 3
[Music]
be a maverick for real though Logan Paul
Keim /op how to stop this merger in the
game now do you hear that
it's your dogie what is he barking Apple
I always say nothing but who really
knows who knows what if he's warding off
things that we can't even see the point
is guy's car has been barking hella
incessantly incessantly and my neighbors
are pissed we gotta stop this nugget
what are you working it buddy
what are you barking at wait where are
you going yo he just dipped there's
gotta be a way we can distract calm
would you want a sibling young dougie
going on in his brain today's national
nothing wait you can adopt dogs what did
you say to me it's like national it's
like with the weekend of like yeah
congratulations subscribers who else is
one of those you two please no give me
the tiny gold plaque just let me have
the diamond please yes bro I was about
to be like yo we're brothers and we
should go get a brother for Cong at the
adoption center it's just not the same
bro this is unfair treatment you can't
treat vegans like this you can't do that
that's Buddhist your food is alright
let's go get a dog why are you guys
still doing dog adoption week
no oh it's not today ma'am ma'am wait
ma'am yours before they come back I do a
vlog and I need a hashtag content
negotiation okay
they said they closed for the day yeah
but I don't a bro adoption weekend yeah
but they're done for today bro now do
you worry bro can I go mom are you there
are you there no stay there no move
we're still getting unpacked hey could
you do me a favor and shut up we're
going to get a pad don't get beads I'm
not worried about you right now
I'm worried about me so bring me pizza
everything meet like Ohio oh yeah I was
thinking since there's no longer dogs
available we get a different pet okay
but hear me out
and we give it to Lydia so it's her
responsibility you got a snake we should
give the giant snake four idiots with a
guy apparently he's getting a Python
that bites but I'm looking at these
birds here right to kind of remind me of
maverick but I'm not gonna lie
no bird compared Keats why would you
even try to compare it why don't we just
get this dog it was pretty cool oh you
like him but with more fur and slightly
more of a brain it's very very slightly
what do you what do you think Kong
nothing absolutely zero front door I'm
telling you right now my assistant would
love that
yo Abbi hold it he's kind of badass yeah
yeah I'll take him
are you kidding nope so we're looking at
tanks for a snake
it's not a snake how hard is it to take
care of a snake it's not too difficult
betting changes feeding you could do
that easy yeah this just in from the
legal team snakes will have to be caught
and will not be purchased and must be
caught out of scenes 42 through 46 in an
effort to make continued content that is
suitable for all you said where you
going to say please disappoint it I feel
like Lydia would have really liked a
snake do you like snakes no okay it's
such a boring day guys trust me when
you're in school and you get out right
it's Friday it's late you guys are fist
bumping and doing crazy things I realize
Friday
ah but my vlogs really devolved to
showing the sculptures that Lydia's been
making out of clay all day but
unfortunately my vlogs are a little more
lift and damn you don't become the
number one channel on YouTube for no
reason I'm pretty sure PewDiePie don't
so we're gonna do something fun in the
form of poetry poetry contests
I could spend a whole day just eating
spaghetti playing with calm and driving
the Eddie I love being a part of the low
gang it makes me so happy I think I can
scream this poem was written by Logan's
legal team Mike why are you even here I
thought hard to read
veins are blue I know I'm only for two
but it's more than Logan's YouTube
revenue
[Music]
this is actually good transition to my
thanks thanks everybody
roses are red violets are blue I was
never good at poetry by my March I
apologize
once upon a time okay today was kind of
wack I'm not gonna lie this blog was
just weird man and I hate to say it I
hate to do it but lo gang that is the
law and like the worst part they
normally write there's a theme right
just to click break the thumbnail I got
nothing man I just not got nothing gross
look like when you did that what do we
do thumbnail bro for the Clickbank alone
there's nothing nothing happened like a
poetry poetry not swag rose I got an
idea
dude this blog is gonna be how to be a
youtuber guys it's not hard no it's not
you all you have to do is create
exhilarating content all you have to do
is get out in smash plates good-looking
friends you got I have good-looking
friends and you gotta have a good
thumbnail so for this vlog it's gonna be
my thumbnail literally like my actual
thumbnail so now you know how to be a
youtuber if you're not a part of the low
gang make sure to subscribe to get the
strongest family on YouTube that's a
fair and do yourself a favor by doing it
different that's what we do is step
maverick squab the lifestyle of not
being afraid to be the crazy ones
because that's what it's all about
okay I love you and I will see you
tomorrow where I can promise the vlog
will be much better
[Music]
yeah
I think I got one
[Music]
times you got a new love song