the number one question we're getting is
how do i watch the fight how do i buy
the fight this is a quick video
explaining exactly how to do that
nothing more so here we go okay guys
first things first couple things you
need to know one this is the biggest
internet event in history but and it
costs ten bucks to watch literally two
cups of coffee trust me this is a moment
not one to make Wow
as far as watching the stream you cannot
watch it unless you purchase and watch
it we're gonna have hundreds of
employees removing any pirate extremism
down okay I think enough for the hype
jig when did you buy the flights watch
yeah yeah any highlight clips or
anything is not gonna be available you
gotta you out of my tech knowledge
that's it so there's actually two places
you can buy and watch the flight one is
on YouTube and if the stream on YouTube
is not available in your country the
other one is a website called UK both of
those links are in the description so uh
Sal yeah so let's go through the YouTube
by first do it so if you go to the
YouTube channel youtube.com slash ksi
versus Logan you'll see the ksi versus
Logan vol official livestream row I'm
fighting dead G why isn't that and
they're just had it keep it nice and
short and sweet okay whatever so click
on that you'll see the preview begin to
play and then you'll see an option to
buy right now we're in the United
Kingdom so it's seven dollars and fifty
seven whatever then you click on buy the
fight pretty self-explanatory good thing
I have my handy dandy credit cards we're
gonna blur that cuz yellow so you type
in your credit card information which
you can also pay with it with PayPal so
if you have a PayPal account oh that's
cool I actually didn't know that after
you've entered your credit card
information blah blah blah go ahead and
hit by a boom you've got the fight
however it is important to note that you
can only buy if you buy on YouTube on a
laptop desktop or Android but you can
watch the fight anywhere on iOS
iPhone mobile tablet whatever okay so
that for some reason isn't working or
like I said if the YouTube fight stream
is not available in your country you can
go to ksi versus Logan dot TV again link
is in the description really easy you go
here the previews playing in the
background you go ahead and click buy
fight pass it'll have you do a little
screen test make sure you can watch
everything smooth so click yes I test it
and I can see the video and wham-o time
to do the same thing again with my
handy-dandy credit card again blurred
out this so guys on this website you do
have to make a password which can
honestly be whatever accept the terms
and conditions process payment you got
it you have the fight you go to the same
website to watch it right there right
then and on this website you can
actually purchase on mobile so you can
you can buy this from whatever whatever
device you're using now that you have
the fight the stream starts at 5:30 p.m.
British I hit my knee hit his knee he's
fine he's fine
I can't fight it's fine he's no longer
fighting Deji but 5:30 p.m. British
summer time the stream starts which is
12:30 p.m. est and 9:30 a.m. PST my
fight is going to be roughly 8:30 p.m.
at BST 3:30 p.m. est 12:30 p.m. PST yes
so if you're in the United States it's a
little early so definitely just be by
your computer be ready to watch it
around like lunchtime because your boy
is going on after Jake at about 9:00
p.m. BST 4:00 p.m. est and 1 p.m. PST
Wow and again all the links for
everything we just described is in the
description guys if you are not a part
of the low gang make sure to subscribe
be a maverick join the Smith during this
Jarvis Vigo
during the strongest family on YouTube
and subscribe copy stuff surprised
looking for that concise shot or again
link in description you guys I love you
I will see you the weigh-ins are
tomorrow and on Fight Night get ready to
beat some ass take it easy
[Music]