hey guys
long time no see yeah you guys saw
yesterday's vlog i
literally just ended it like i'm
shooting an entire vlog tonight
because your boy is going to dubai
holding the biggest meet and greet ever
at the dubai mall november 11th at 5 p.m
i want to meet you
and shout out my babies you guys
remember lydia she was modeling the bags
that we just dropped as well still here
yes oh man they're so freaking fire
you're so
freaking fire what are you what can you
do when your merch is so dull that's
your running out of stocks
cause everyone wants it you get more so
we made more backpacks
shop or link in description guys
something i didn't say in yesterday's
vlog
i actually have not um showered today so
i'm gonna do that
and uh figure out just exactly what
we're doing for this vlog
oh guys it's the morning we couldn't
come up with any ideas so now we're here
and we leave for dubai in two hours and
i'm just kidding obviously i got ideas
like what the [ __ ] is wrong with you but
i wanted to show you guys before i leave
there's a lot of things going down
our house is teeming with life first off
let's start with the plants bro like
honey plants plants plants plants you
like succubus
me too so i bought a thousand of them
look at the succubus
it's uh succubi nope succulents
i think it's
dragon thing yo brennan bro i got no
brain you didn't know logan that's what
i'm here for bro
i appreciate it anyways by the time we
get back our house is going to be
absolutely
decked out oh and the mirrors are coming
in today nice mirror guys
it's just a lot of stuff going on but
i'm gonna throw it back to you past
logan take it away bro
i have an idea it involves this knife
now listen i know what you're thinking
logan what are you wearing bro it looks
good i know
yeah the big mavic hoodie sexy i know
it's not out yet so don't get your hopes
up yet it's coming soon but this knife
so i was thinking
do you like brendan do you really need
your toes does one need their toes
actually what do you use it for your big
toe holds 40 of your body weight
i don't think it does i don't think you
i don't think you need it yeah i'm like
let's do it
just feel like i always have 911
it's good thing we have chandeliers they
said that you won't do it by the way
they said
he's doing a play game called can logan
move his foot out of the way before he
cuts off his big toe
yeah i'm fighting for content i'll do
anything to entertain subscribe if
you're not the logang
one two three oh hey my [ __ ] down
no no no you can't do it because i don't
know when bro i don't know when you're
gonna drop it it's also not falling from
that high yes
play the game with him play the game
with him stab him oh
snap oh yo evan evan wait oh wait evan
quick stab that
okay great chantel could you make that
911 call we lost him
yeah we lost him okay so that that
wasn't a good idea of the knife thing we
need content bro
oh what we got what you got
brandon come on i got the good that bad
i love food bro lydia thank you we love
you
yo this is actually good so i'm gonna go
give evan some food but that
but that uh leads into something that
happened last night that it was a bit
weird
go gay for a vlog just one vlog you
don't think i'll go get for one vlog
i'll go get with everyone but that's the
only guy brown
don't tell me i won't do it i'm sorry
that's what they said i can't control it
you missed it bro you won't believe it
just oh
[Applause]
you are pretty hot like in a straight
way welcome to logan paul vlogs
after dark you know that's what i was
gonna say that's what i was gonna say
it's getting weird i've never done two
vlogs in one day so like at what point
is it too many vlogs
okay clearly i'm already crazy right
maybe it is because of vlogging and i'm
just literally just like filming
everything who the [ __ ] is calling me
it's manager jeff hey man
your client aka me i just i kissed a
dude
just now you killed somebody uh nope no
i said kissed a dude
i said you liked it
no no i didn't i can't say i did did you
like
i did not like it
you coming to dubai yeah of course i
wouldn't miss
managers jeff's biggest me greeting the
world it's actually my meet and greet
you'll be there
anyways bro good good good chalk i'll
see you later
did you see that do you see evan kissed
me
it's not you kiss evan i think that's
what i said too yeah i like his evan
he he kissed me jumped up and kissed me
in the mouth look at him did he even do
it
i don't know if you can jump that guy no
he can't bro he's really athletic what
is he doing right now
i don't have this in my bathroom so i
think i thought it was pretty cool
a good modeling evan hey buddy how about
you breakfast
it's a piece of french toast you
remember when we
did that thing yesterday why'd you have
to pick that up i don't know bro just
like it's the same vlog
it's kind of weird huh you wanna do it
again never mind all right
huh all right we'll see you later you
think these beams are strong enough to
support my body weight yo if it breaks
does the house break no let's try
hey good news guys it works
i don't care what lydia says bro how's
trampoline what's the move
ugh what was she saying she said it was
like ruin the vibe of the house
but really bro it's my [ __ ] brain
brennan
yeah throw me the camera why do you
always make me do this cause you can do
it please
catch it with two hands ready yeah
evan it's my boy oh wow hot you got it
don't land on my feet away you got it
you got it
good job oh
god brendan hey oh
we almost lost brenda look at us bro
we're roommates just
bouncing on a trampoline for the second
vlog of the day yo you think yo you
think i can jump
high enough and then grab onto the beam
oh my god
this is pretty cool bro okay
okay guys um i think
oh but
okay guys i feel like i have a bit of
explaining to do
um if you saw yesterday's vlog you saw
yesterday's vlog you're subscribed
i was i was just goofy i was goofy the
whole day i was doing i was running
around on the highway
it was because the night before we had
went out dancing at the club
and then i made the mistake of talking
to the paparazzi who were waiting
outside
of the club like freaking rabid hungry
tigers anyways as you can imagine i was
just not in the right state of mind i
should have never
opened my mouth and they started asking
me about stuff obviously guys you know
me i had to plug the merch
tell us about the merch room
but then he asked me oh this is where it
gets gnarly and like i said i kind of
already addressed this but i want to
like
touch on it more he asked me about jake
brother jake sorry who's that oh
let the roast begin bro so yo this is
good
that i have her here jake made a video
when he roasted her ice [ __ ]
destroyed each other and so she came
over i was like yo
could you want to be in this video and
now she's here and now i'm going to get
hella views
and hella subscribers thank you chantel
i know you're using me a lot
quick
bro i'll sidebar this again hey
so yeah there's some there's some
feelings some emotions going in here and
i know youtube loves drama so i figured
right now
while i'm on a flight to dubai we could
address this situation okay let's start
with the thing where i said i wasn't
close with jake
to be honest i lied i don't know why i
said that obviously i'm close with jake
i believe the thought process was this
ask me a risque question right about
jake getting like sued or something and
they've done this before like they
followed me to my dentist office and
they just catch me outside
and i like being on camera i vlog i vlog
every single day so i like
i feed into it i suck bro what do you do
when you get paparazzi
i usually um just don't say anything
they asked actually asked me about you
yesterday no yeah what did you say did
you tell him i was jotch and where to
get the merch
i i literally didn't say anything but i
plugged my new song that's what i'm
saying so
from now on bro i'm just plugging
anyways the thought process was this i
wanted to avoid the question
so i lied i was like what apparently
someone's sue suing jake over
no and then i don't know why i just
didn't shut my mouth
and i was like yeah dude i'm not close
with jake the issue is that i'm not
closer with jake that i don't know this
what the [ __ ] when i say that i love
this kid i may be the only one in the
world
right possibly but i do he's my brother
so i felt bad about that so jake i'm
sorry bro and then this whole day
i've just been feeling weird have you
seen my tweets about north korea
yeah everyone thinks i'm hacked
because i'm not hacked like yo when
you're bored and the
subs are good and the merch is selling
like a god church
and world war three is right around the
corner you just gotta call out one of
the most dangerous countries in the
world so i did that tweet number one at
north korea
you're soft but i didn't even i didn't
even spell out your dude i wanted the
classic
er cause i'm hard as [ __ ] kim jong
didn't get the message
so i said sorry tweeted a picture of um
charmin the toilet paper brand and said
call you charmin
because they ultra soft damn show them
kim jong nuke us
no
are you gonna do it are you to reverse i
thought about it but then i was like
hopefully you have a 401k oh don't worry
about stock investments and
matriculation headphones i mean since
jake said he was my dad
and he also said my dad hold up hold up
stop
pause with the daddy talk i'm [ __ ]
dead bro i'm daddy
everyone knows it i wear pink merch
yes dad yes yes bro
i'm not saying that right say it
and the mercedes that you drive around
in your dad bought it for you you don't
make any money
i just want to say since jake says that
he's our dad
and then he in turn said that my dad
buys me all my stuff
so jake i kind of want a lambo so um if
you're watching this
oh yo jake if you could give me a lambo
too bro yes dad
do you want one i would love one okay
we're all getting jake's buying us all
lambo
i love you this is why i love jake wait
wait wait you haven't said anything bro
what do you like what do you think about
jake paul let me just say this okay i
kissed logan paul
fact hi i witnessed that i wouldn't kiss
jake paul
okay back to you past future is the
future future logan thanks pass logan i
appreciate
you yo the pink looks good in the
daytime hot damns up
real quick check out these mirrors bro
we got them here
so this whole wall is gonna be covered
in mirrors by the time i get back the
gym will be coming together but right
now i gotta say goodbye to my boy
oh my god that was just sad
evan i'm gonna miss you bro dubai needs
me hosting the world's biggest meet and
greet november 11th 5pm at the dubai ice
rink at the dubai mall
anyways yeah man i love you just don't
die is the house under my name if you
did die yeah you got it
thank you what did you say is now
anyways little gang that is the vlog if
you're not a part of the logang are you
good bro make sure to subscribe join the
strongest family on the internet so
smack the button in the face for me the
pink hoodie is dropping soon i think i'm
the i think on the day of the meet and
greet and we got some other stuff so
just be ready it's the hottest merch in
the game guys loganpaul.com
shop or link in description no one's
doing it like this look at the bottoms
they are doing it like us mavericks baby
we're changing the world every single
day we're different we're passionate
we're unique and we chase our goals
until they are
it succeed exceeded exceed until they
are achieved and dubai i will see you
soon guys excuse me i have a flight to
catch logang i love y'all and i will see
you tomorrow take it easy
i'm at my
uh i think it's good yeah