hey guys welcome back
anyway as you guys know we just released
our flat earth to the edge and back
mockumentary so our surprise guys it is
actually the number one most critically
acclaimed movie in the world it's really
making hello waves on the internet and
we wanted to make this video as sort of
a tell-all
along with eight minutes of the funniest
bloopers you'll ever see in your life
because there's a lot of stuff that went
down behind the scenes that you guys did
not see and that like stories we
probably shouldn't say on the internet
but we're going to anyways about how we
infiltrated the flat earth
pretty weird place community devious way
i gotta say the flat earth community
is not happy so this video is for
fans low gangsters filmmakers pretty
much anyone who wants to know
how we made this documentary how we
infiltrated the flat earth community
to the core and honestly [ __ ] trolled
the entire internet so yeah we're gonna
answer some of your questions it's gonna
be kind of long there's a lot going on
there's a lot going on i turn 24
on monday april fool's day my birthday's
coming up we are doing a retro
yellow and black new maverick hoodie
drop [ __ ] fire dude not gonna lie so
be ready for that i think we we should
just go right into it so enjoy
the the outtakes and bloopers from flat
earth to the edge
in back
three two one
oh that was a lame clap i'm not messing
with you
i'm not missing
don't do that don't do that
[Music]
i don't think the earth is flat i
[ __ ] know it is [ __ ] know it is
my name is logan paul my name is logan
paul
my name is logan paul
dude my bad dogs have tongues that are
fully inside their mouths
in most cases
i haven't seen it yet i did not expect
that bro
he was gone stardust
me let me stop you right there for a
second sorry nasa for example right they
they you broke so funny when you just go
just like [ __ ] the whole thing yeah hi
my one friend pete good old flat-footed
pete
he lost his balance it was his flat feet
smash human-sized penguin one of the
leading
theories to support there were signs
everywhere like do not pass
do not go like do not pass go
um you know do not pass go
you're now in jail uh
i've done experiments and scientific
research i'll prove it to you guys right
now
i've done experiments in scientific
research and i can prove it to you guys
right now it seems rushed to me i've
done experiments in scientific research
so still saying it the exact same way
well i've done
experiments and scientific reasons and i
can prove it to you guys
right now and i can prove it to you guys
right now and i can prove to you guys
right now
i lost my best friend that day and my
youth
[Laughter]
i can't look at censor like dead
seriously you're gonna get an oscar
my image my reputation i fell in love
with the flat earth girl
sorry that was so much spit
it was so white and am i right my eye i
don't even want to say this right now
bro
but you have so much spit in your hair
on your chin right now bro it's
disgusting dude i can't even look at you
it's my girl's smile
[Applause]
it's flattered
the last thing that mike said he
remembers of his friend was
that's it yeah
[Laughter]
how are we gonna kiss down here the
earth is flat
the earth is flat people around the
globe know the earth is flat
i'm not a flat earther dude
i don't know i feel so stupid my head
was in the sand earlier and high
the clues are right in front of me i
can't believe this whole time i've been
like a [ __ ] peasant with my head in
the sand
[Music]
this is this guy yeah
suck my [ __ ] day you're [ __ ]
kidding me bro
oh [ __ ] god
[Music]
so much sense now mike everything
it's all it's all a lie i can't believe
i've been living in the [ __ ]
dick can you layer on that murdering it
before now it's so
like you can't even tell oh dingo i have
my body gravity gravity how come
scientists can't explain it right the
moon emits its own light i guess casey's
really rubbing off on me
what could possibly be happening in that
area pam is there anything else we could
do at this point besides go to the same
parking lot we've been to a million
times i'm sick of this [ __ ] pam i'm
literally with you pam it's greenbox
storage and chicken focaccia
every friday like let's do something
different we gotta switch things up but
we're getting a divorce i hate you
[ __ ] you pam you stupid [ __ ] i wanna go
back to that [ __ ] parking lot again
yeah man that [ __ ] was crazy okay the
tell-all how do we do this how do we
trick the entire internet and the flat
earthers and what was the process behind
it where do we even start
i would definitely say that logan paul
movie and that's another thing that he
outright lied about was the fact that he
was going to be doing a documentary that
was a movie with acting
full-on acting the entire thing was
scripted he's right it was scripted
five pages actually page one page two
page three page four page five there was
a lot of thought that went into this and
when you guys asked this question
muhammad said how did you get the idea
to make this masterpiece one day i was
watching i got sucked into like the
youtube like conspiracy rabbit hole as
like we all do
and i was fascinated this group of
people called the flat earthers that
actually think the earth is flat and i
and i heard about this a while ago and i
actually like referenced it in one of my
vlogs yo if you think the earth is flat
[ __ ] you seriously do you think the
earth is flat yo let me give you a
little science lesson spencer all right
the earth is round and then i heard
about this uh flat earth international
conference where like all these people
these crazy people gather in one spot
and i knew
it was an opportunity for golden content
so the first thing i did
was buy tickets and it sent mike an
email i was just about to move here i
got an email that said congratulations
you're going to the flat earth
international conference oh i didn't
even tell you i had no idea and then you
called me and you're like hey you ready
for your first acting gig guy
and i had no idea what was going on and
it was literally like the first project
that we worked on
a lot of people wanted to know how like
you were good bro for your first acting
gig ever where does that come from i
don't even know dude i think right after
we talked i started working on that
story
oh my god that's right came up with the
the story about his dad being a
contractor
for antarctica i think that was your
idea yeah and then you would sit like
people would come over and you would
tell them about your track your dad
and pete rest in peace i really truly
believed
uh what the storyline was and i think
mike his best friend really helped play
it along
that's because mike lost a a friend
all right pete didn't die pete doesn't
he's not even a real person
he never existed i don't even know where
like the the like inspiration came for
him the flashy
you you that was on the spot yeah
because like i was trying to think of
like how someone could fall over the
side because by the way i have really
flat feet yeah they're like big paddles
with bunions and there's flats that
scene was so hard to film
i mean they saw it in the bloopers that
was broke a thousand times
and i practiced it so many times in
front of so many people and then once we
all sat in here like we are right now is
in this exact room yeah guy just
couldn't
hold it together i was worried that at
the end of the dock
when mike flipped and said he was
spoiler alert that he was not a flat
earther that people wouldn't believe
that that people would think that was
the joke so we overacted it
with the little underlying hint that
like
you're [ __ ] around with everyone i
think well i think once people heard
pete go over the side
that they like the majority of people
right there were like yo there's no
there's
absolutely no [ __ ] way this is true
logan paul was
punking everyone at flat earthers
expense this was a great big punk on the
entire internet
because everyone was falling for this
that oh my goodness he's he's becoming a
flat earther
this is my favorite part about this
documentary like
part of the reason i made it it sounds
bad it was kind of like a
like a [ __ ] you in a way everyone in
today's society is so quick to hop on
the train whichever way it's going
especially if the terrain involves
hating logan paul that's like a
fun thing to do nowadays so this was my
way of tricking
every single person who wanted to hate
me we did dupe the internet i got duped
too
seriously i did by the real logan paul
he's over there
gotcha dumbass i even got comments a lot
of these actually i feel like you
finessed youtube and i have
much more respect for you now like you
guys saw at the end of the dock so many
people logan paul's an idiot he's a flat
earther
actually even like it was so hard to
stay in
flat earth character for so long like i
was just getting railed by everyone
for being a flat earther this part's
interesting the flat earth society
tweeted at me this went like viral on
reddit disdained me
and refused to acknowledge me as part of
the
society but the flat earth society what
the real flat earth is called we found
this out
controlled opposition the flatter
society aren't even the real flat
earthers but now i'm sucked into this
like weird spot where do i try to
explain to like the real world
that the flatter society is separate
from the real flat earthers and
even be involved with these people
anymore like i don't know it was just it
was so confusing it was like you got
uninvited to a party that you didn't
want to be at yes exactly
yeah they were just like yes i don't
want to be part of the [ __ ] group i
want to talk about
the backlash we're getting it's minor
the backlash i thought i was going to
get
was the media coming out and saying
logan paul is perpetuating
ignorance by even spreading this fable
that the earth is indeed shaped like a
pancake floating through space
thank god that did not happen the
backlash that we are getting you tricked
the flat earthers you know you lied to
their face
why did you do that how do you feel
about that like the doc was awesome but
you haiky lied used and took advantage
of those people and they genuinely
trusted you love the doc though
thanks dude my logic was this if they
were if they're willing to lie to
themselves
and lie to the world try and perpetuate
this movement of idiocracy
i was willing to lie to them about
something that i really
really don't believe in like here here's
me coming clean i
really really dislike this movement not
the two my own horn
you guys may know i got a full academic
ride to college for engineering i got a
five on my ap physics test science
biology
facts i guess you could say is kind of
my thing in math too like i was a
i was a geek in high school but i
promised myself that i was going to go
to the conference with an open mind as
much as
and you two remember when i told you
that you were going to become a flat
earther
you were like no i was worried none of
these people were
like mean in any way like they never at
any point were like rude tossed they
were all really nice people and to be
honest with you like coming out of it
i've made a couple of comments to you
that like i actually did there were
times where i actually started to feel
kind of bad about the situation there's
just like a part of me that like just
didn't feel
great about it but at the same time like
they are like perpetuating a lie
to like not only other people but also
like kids
i i can't i can't fully wrap my head
around it and i was willing
to stand behind my actions for the
satire that we created
to hopefully spread the truth about how
like honestly really [ __ ] stupid this
movement is and to be honest i don't
even want to call it a movement
i don't think it's a movement i think
it's a group of like-minded people who
simply refuse education and refuse to
believe
the truth the flat earth gathering is a
thing
because a lot of the stuff they say like
does make sense
because what they do is they cherry pick
they work backwards not
trying to prove that the earth is flat
instead trying to disprove that the
earth is round
and they cherry pick the facts that they
want you to see
to get to point b while skipping point a
they are so tied into this belief
that the earth is flat no one in this
massive group is willing to actually
go prove it right like they're like oh
we can't go to antarctica because
there's this rogue
nasa force that will stop us at the
border so we can't go there to
prove that there's this ice shell but if
you've devoted your like this robbie
davidson has devoted his entire life to
it
like go like go there someone do
something someone with a camera
be the patriot with a with a hidden
camera and and show us that you've been
stopped by this rogue
force of of government you know that
that won't let you pass
here's why it gets tricky like these
flat earth believers
it's bigger than just them believing in
the flat earth they don't believe in
anything they
they question everything but this is the
first movie all scripted
all acted from start to finish the
entire thing was a comedy that's what
i'm saying
that's proof robbie was we wrote him in
he's our protagonist
the way it works is there's a few of
them can speak well
and articulate and do have like a really
high
functioning level of intelligence and
they're the ones that are the speakers
for example this guy rick hummer he was
the master of
ceremonies he introduced all the guests
and sort of ran the show the dude like
many of the flat earthers is just out of
touch we were um
in the parking lot talking with uh
robbie and rick and the dude
throws out yeah and he's such a such a
bag because yeah he went from the cubs
to the reds like that
so i'm gonna reiterate the dude said a
no-no
when i heard it i was like oh
and i'm like you don't see the cameras
in your face you can't really the dude's
not gonna get canceled the flat earthers
don't care they're not they're i don't
know what i'm saying
percentage this wasn't like a a
hit piece per se i just wanted to show
how ridiculous
all of this was quite honestly just
crafting a story around them they did
the work for us
and that's why it worked so well why do
you think flat earthers
are flat earthers and is there going
back say they changed their mind from a
flat earther back to around earth
i'm sure like they're just like a
movement of people that
do what they do to kind of like feel
like they belong to something like a
club
that was that was the conclusion i
reached yeah like just like anything
like that
anti-vaxxers like there's just a whole
different a whole bunch of different
movements of people that i feel like
they
are able to like come together it's
almost like not in the same you know
vein obviously but like a comic book
club
dungeons and dragons like people coming
together obviously this is much
different than those but for some
common purpose and like they've been
probably cast out by
by reality social anxieties they have
or like social like the ineptness they
have and they come together and they
feel like they belong to something
together
more so if they were to leave
like if robbie davidson all of a sudden
if the earth was
proven for the millionth time tomorrow
to like
be round robbie davidson is no longer
the ceo of this non-existent movement
like what does he do what do all the
speakers do what do they all do
at this point they're locked in like
sure stick with your guns roll with it
you're making money selling
200 tickets by the way to a flat earth
conference like go for it i read this
quote today actually i have this book
upstairs i'm reading this book it's
called how to win friends and
influence people this was crazy i came
across this today on the plane some
authorities
declare that people may actually go
insane in order to find
in the dreamland of insanity the feeling
of importance that has been denied them
in the harsh world of reality how
[ __ ]
pertinent is that they think this thing
people call them crazy
and the only safe spot is around the
other crazy people
the only thing however that they didn't
fall through with was coming to
the mixer yeah and and danny his
assistant apologized profusely said
logan had some other plans i did not
have other plans
no we had to get the
[ __ ] out of that place the conference
was attached to the hotel so even when
we went up to our rooms we were
surrounded
we had to like live come flat and live
with the people there was always times
where like they started to
seem like they might be catching on to
us like the second day
one of the lead speakers that was the
biggest thing his name is mark sargent
he was in the
behind the curve uh netflix documentary
which by the way
if you haven't seen that it's incredible
it pretty much sums up everything we're
saying he was on to us he found out that
i was there and he went on a podcast and
he's like
logan paul is a troll he's messing with
us i can't be around he didn't call me
he was one of the main speakers and he
left he backed out yeah that led us into
the third day
when that happened like the last day and
that's when people started to look at us
like
we didn't belong there and as soon as
that started to happen like i felt like
yo we're in
enemy territory we have to get out of
here like it was it was getting bad like
people were starting to like say things
to us yeah
i was getting like [ __ ] talked and
everything so so so we dipped we didn't
stay for the dinner we actually
moved hotels we went to uh downtown
denver to a
hotel there should we tell that story
yeah of course yeah
so uh the whole documentary was made in
like three or four days it was so quick
filmed in three or four days but there
was so much thought that went into it
and i was so stressed i mean we all were
i'm so stressed out right now i'm
overwhelmed and i'm scared i'm scared
for my life
remember the uh the clerks bro they were
flat earthers yeah at the new hotel
you couldn't you couldn't escape them at
that point we were asking everyone in
the city what
what shape do you think the earth is i
think it's what and she was like i think
it's flat
and then we went to that bar we went to
the restaurant and he kept watching
videos of like flatter adamantly focused
on this video and he was sweating like i
looked over at him he was just
completely like drenched in sweat and i
was like yo man like are you all right
he was like i think i'm gonna go back to
the room and he stood up and he started
walking down the hall
you know when you stand up and you blood
rushes to your head yeah and
there's like little clouds circle clouds
around your eyes but normally it goes
away the
circle of color kept getting smaller and
smaller and smaller
and i'm walking down this long hallway
eventually i can't see i cannot [ __ ]
see i'm still conscious
but i'm blind and at this point like
this has never happened to me so i lean
against this wall and i had
enough strength in my body to to muster
one
final word and i'm leaning against this
wall and i go
i ran over he was like leaning against
the wall he was like
i don't know man i don't feel good flat
earth like just started like saying
things and he was just so
[ __ ] up i think like just all of it
like the elevation like lack of sleep
like all the stress of like making the
film like everything we made it around
the corner from the bar
and literally as soon as we got around
the corner he just face dived into the
ground like flat on the [ __ ] ground
for the first time in my life it like
was
out and so i picked them up i passed
that big ass off pulled them into the
elevator
and we were on the way back down like
the door opened some guy tried to wheel
a cart and he's like i'll just get the
next one
i like dragged him all the way down here
like dragged all the way down your room
this [ __ ] took a toll on me is what
we're saying like yeah i have never
passed out
in my life the flat earthers made me go
unconscious and headbutt it was just
like so much it's like any time like
you're like
trying trying your brain like that and
like expanding it and like i wouldn't
say expanding
i don't hate the people i hate the
movement it's almost even
dumb to talk about like nasa astronauts
will not give this conversation the time
of day
neil degrasse tyson he hates it there's
no point talking about it
well there's also that uh theory called
occam's razor which is uh the simplest
explanation tends to be
the right one the flat earthers will use
that in their defense and they'll be
like if they brought proof
of any of the stuff that they claim to
know like i feel like there's been
enough proof to show that the [ __ ]
earth is round do you still talk to the
australian girl that was in the movie
she seems really nice k spoon she's a
good friend of ours and how did you find
the girl who was also willing to pretend
to ruin her reputation for the joke
she trusted me i told her and like you
know sometimes when people trust me you
get [ __ ]
in this scenario it worked out pretty
well she was good too
she's never acted before the majority of
times it was you believed it too much
you're like i need you to actually tone
it down because no one's gonna believe
it at the end yeah you know what's funny
hearing robbie describe our storyline
yeah after the fact but really it was
part of the storyline
he was literally coming out as a flat
earther in his character
because he loved this australian girl
right that's another question we got
were you nervous to speak in front of
the flat earth society they aren't the
flat earth society that's
that's the difference like it's i just
so dumb explaining i was a little
nervous and not because of public
speaking aspect i actually love public
speaking i love being on stage i was
nervous because
that was the culmination of the entire
five-page script
that was the big moment and i had one
chance to not [ __ ] it up and not to
mention not only do i not think the
earth is flat
i'm adamantly against this movement so
500 eyes
on me people who like live and die by
this belief i couldn't [ __ ] up
and i i knew i had to nail it so yeah i
was nervous
penguin you guys are oh my god the
human-sized penguin
we implanted the human-sized penguin in
a lot of spots in this movie somebody
asked like what the relevance was
there's no absolutely none whatever yeah
i don't know what i don't remember what
it was that got you so hung up on
because i was just hyped bro i think
that was when i really started to
realize like how good this project was i
noticed all the throughout the through
lines
yeah between that applebee's so many
different like callbacks to applebee's
oh this was actually funny you'll notice
on this script some things are in blue
that's because this project was alive it
morphed and adapted
so much based on what happened at the
conference we shot most of the stuff
all of the stuff surrounding it after
the conference because we had to know
what went down for example the first
time
the very first time the human-sized
penguin was mentioned was in my
interview with robbie just randomly set
it off the top of my head
in the ancient like jurassic times there
were penguins the size of humans
absolutely i was like yo i like that
let's [ __ ] implant this and
everything so it's in the scene in the
woods there's a human
size penguin head in the background of
the classroom scene in the music video
the easiest way to put it about this
project was it just felt like what
happens when
a group of people all start cooking on
the same
wavelength all of us were just so dialed
in to always be thinking about like what
the next like
big thing could be we had prep the whole
team there was like seven of us
we said yo do not break character ever
do not show these people that we are not
flattered don't talk too loud
don't say anything like we don't [ __ ] we
were we were so serious about
not [ __ ] up here like yo if you drop
the ball and you're the one that [ __ ]
this up do you have any idea how mad
dude we're gonna [ __ ] be at you y'all
almost got caught
uh the one day i think it was a
publication called the daily beast oh
yeah that girl
this girl came and she interviewed me
and she's with her little camera phone
and she
was asking me if i thought the earth was
flat and i wasn't sure
whether or not to come out on the media
yet as believing it
and so like you like halfway there i
have waited
like crazy you're like the earth is flat
because our feet are flat
and like let's see the curve just look
at it and she was just like this dude is
such a [ __ ] [ __ ] you know
she's just the ending of that was tragic
i was like yo the earth is flat
obviously and she's like do you have any
numbers for that and mike goes
are there any numbers in there or two
two two
it's more just one in one when you
combine them yeah i broke
because that's what i hear yeah when the
flat earthers talk that's what i
hear them saying for their explanation
that was like the first
piece of press that came out because
like i think a lot of people asked us
about like the marketing for it as well
the idea was
to use the haters in the media give them
a little piece of
something to snack on yeah some logan
paul hate the snack promote our film for
us
and then make them eat their words when
it came out and they did it
by the grace we also did a little bit on
our end you know we talked about on the
podcast pretty much every podcast we
asked every guest yeah for the most part
is basically just seed the story
and like let people run with it they
went live we had [ __ ] ksi
tweeting about it bro like driving with
a link
bro with a link to his six million
twitter fans and i was like yo this is
one i knew you know like
yeah he said something like uh did i
really hit you that hard side no
no you i mean i've said this before you
hit like a little [ __ ]
how hard was it not to laugh on some of
the scenes all the years i've ever
watched saturday night live
and watch them struggle through scenes
and like you see their like lips start
to quiver and they're like starting to
fall off like
i don't know how you did a lot of it
because a lot of your stuff was
with the flat earthers and me too but i
think you had more because you had the
interviews with them it's like when you
asked robbie about the
the human-sized penguin like i don't
know how you didn't break down this [ __ ]
here
i could break and it would be okay like
if you started cracking up when you were
asking robbie that [ __ ] he would have
known well no what happened was when i
every time i would
want to laugh physically i was in pain i
was in pain it was so hard i
tried to empathize with these people but
i just couldn't
how long did it take to shoot the scene
where we were outside the restaurant
so long in case you really rub it off
every time every time you said that
everybody that watches this movie has
like a different
line that makes them fall out dude it
makes them start cracking the pete line
or whether it's like when you when you
would say to the dude about masturbation
and we like oh no but like yo literally
the one
thing i could not stop breaking on was
you saying
casey is really reeling off on me every
time you said it that was another random
improv
yo let's just have you start speaking
australia yeah that was that was not
in the script you've only spent two days
with her and you now have an australian
accent
are you gonna do more documentaries in
the future absolutely we have ideas
they can't be like this one cat's out i
mean sasha sasha obviously continues to
trouble people sasha baron cohen uniform
or whatever but like more than anything
like the thing that this hit me on was
just like it doesn't even feel like
we're talking about documentaries we're
talking about filmmaking you know what
i'm saying like we we sat
down we concepted we came up with the
storyline we wrote we had a script
we acted in it we took things to the
next level
for me the success was achieved i said i
was gonna get
this i was gonna be happy this got 5
million views which is going to
yeah i also think it's this is going to
be a slow burn this project like in a
year
i bet we'll check back it'll be at like
10 20 million because it is a solid-ass
piece of content and
it was exciting and fun to make so yeah
definitely want to do more i don't want
to say the ideas yeah no
definitely not but look in conclusion
here's what you need to know uh
p p p was real
and he was i'm still [ __ ] trolling
i'm still in character they're uh we
don't we we don't think the earth is
flat that's the most important one and
that's the only true one out of the
three he just said
well actually you know what again i said
it in the dock like out like
there's probably no earth if you think
about it might as well not be
might as well not be but honestly like
with the amount of [ __ ] that i still get
in my comments and dms i do not think
that the earth is flagged say that with
100 he had promised me i was going to be
able to break character
sooner he was like yo we go to the con
we go to the conference you get out and
then literally you could go on the
podcast to talk about how it was all
food
we get back he's like all right we gotta
film like two more months worth of
content i need you to hold character and
like people are attacking me i'm getting
[ __ ] up by the media whoever like
people are coming on the podcast i got a
whole character
but literally the whole from the
beginning of impulsive mike was yeah
yeah just if you notice during the
during the impulsive scene
the wall of pictures is one picture on
it like this that's it this has been
yeah it's going for so long but i'm so
happy to come back out right now and say
i'm not flattered one last thing i don't
want you guys to bully the flat earthers
and i mean that like
you don't have to agree with their
movement i guess make fun of it if you
feel like because it is
like quite honestly [ __ ] stupid but
don't bully the people and
once again to the flat earth people to
the flat earth community to robbie get
some proof for me dude like go
show me something show us something go
to the go to antarctica next
don't have the 2019 conference take your
whole group of people
and go to antarctica and find this ice
shelf
that you tell everyone exists or find a
way to show us that the moon is its own
life give us
something to chew on because as of right
now you've got
absolutely nothing except for a group of
people that
everyone is is doesn't believe like i i
don't know
it's the blind leading the blind he's
not gonna
he's not gonna go back you know how much
money he made off that conference you
know how much our tickets were i think
they were like two to five hundred
dollars and there's seven of us bro and
the conference had like a thousand
people there he's making a lot of money
it's a cult
so what i'm saying is again back to the
bullying thing don't believe them let
them go
play in fantasyland continue living your
life studying
staying at school or not and getting
educated well yeah that's it all right
we got some fun content again yellow
drop this monday
sunday my birthday's coming up april
fool's day your boy's turning 24.
this age thing ain't stopping huh it's
not going to bro soon you're going to be
me
and i'm going to be you me plus more and
we got a fun hawaii vlog coming out i am
going to respond to the
uh the the jake paul joe weller thing i
just and something tells me we're
probably going to be talking about flat
earth
robbie's going on date dateline nbc to
talk about this robbie davidson's going
to go on national television with some
sort of offensive again
i want to give a message to robbie hey
hey you you listening guy
robbie i [ __ ] got you bro i don't
know
and uh yeah we'll see you guys in the
next vlog
[Music]
[Applause]
you