yep it's exactly what it looks like ex
controversial youtuber Pogan law putting
a grown man to sleep if you saw my last
apprehension video there's a good chance
you did it with your eyes me and my
brother Jake saved the day and wrote a
bad guy like a horse oh well thanks to
this random guy named patty mayo we were
able to become bounty hunters again and
catch more criminals for pay but before
we dive into the video quick hit that
subscribe button and get your tickets to
the Challenger games taking place on
July 27th in Long Beach California
I'm betting $100,000 that I'm the
fastest youtuber link in description ok
enjoy the video he's huge in bulk
I want to go one-on-one against Big Boy
how long do you want with them until I
say do hey you're gonna get them you
like white like send me in bro
I want to go in it like this oh just
knock him out roughly square off like
this will let Logan go hands-on first
yeah we'll say guys oh you have a gun
killing you have a gun I'll load it up I
don't know about your gun bro I am a
Hollywood actor the career I need my
face bro so where the strike on the haul
system I need a gun you sure you can
just Google why you shouldn't give Jake
polygons yeah don't do that
so all we want to do is get this jarred
guy and get the [ __ ] top if we can keep
people out of cuffs that takes time away
from what we're doing force
de-escalation verbally is our key key
thing if they start getting ramped up
we'll go hands-on fall Pat's lead will
stay safe we're gonna go out of here
we're gonna be okay today okay guys
let's do it ostriches do it
[Music]
don't know jared is
you know Jared he's a big he's a big
bald guy tattoos we got word that he
works here
are you loading trucks right now yeah so
I've done this job right here so I mean
you know everybody it's your job here I
will tell you somebody to soon looks
like we got a couple lives on their
hands they're all denying that Jared
works here we know for a fact that Jared
works here listen man we ran up on you
bro you know exactly what I'm looking
for you know exactly when I come back
here he tells me that he knows who you
are
you're gonna go to jail for harboring a
fugitive you understand that Oh daddy
goes hard he goes away hard huh I don't
like any of this I don't like any of
this the whole lot is lying about Jared
there's a lot of people in there
[Music]
I'll sign in right now pretty exclusive
to me I hope you're having a great day I
mean this just happens they're a little
aggressive
oh here we go
[Music]
I have a warrant for Jared's arrest that
he tripped
I'm not gonna wear safety glasses
right behind a seat
[Music]
man please stop please just please just
awesome hey I got a son Jude I got eyes
on a forklift
for whip this up all
get us up there Paul
[ __ ] I see Jared he's darling thanks
these dollar things - no not like this
straight ahead who don't Patti you to go
off first
hey man you got a ballistic shield I'm
gonna be honest I'm going in
don't sending the dog now let's go check
what's good chair let's go patty let's
go patty
what are you got you got hammers
Oh
hi boys your right now
door boys good work boys good job
[Music]
I did a good job well thanks man I taste
the
[Music]
site on him oh yeah and you taste of all
those on it oh yeah good aim oh holy I
had a chance you could have gotten taste
but that was a risk I was just willing
to take and credible but you made it so
I could taste you kick the board away
then try 20 minutes go tackle if you
just presented his body you jump you you
taste them to the end like wanna grow
this is for Z for finality okay which
one of these suckers put my chopper up
on the left
thank you 18 you're next okay
what link could you speak French
Frosch Cebu Pamela it was good fam why'd
you do those things yeah those bad
things you should've done that will
forgive you will forgive you you got us
you guys now say sorry you say sorry his
manners
you tried to tackle me man I was d1 what
are you crazy
look that was dumb out of your mind oh
here's a tooth back I can actually tell
him and you have a real solid base hey
stop hey what's up guys hey if you're
not subscribed hit that subscribe button
I freaking love you give the video a
thumbs up he want us to do more with
Patti Mayo and the team okay I'll see
you next and bye
double the salary that's a fact we saw
in the movement