[Music]
whoa whoa I'm glad I did this man don't
judge a book by it's cover this is so
good
oh snap
no the water is very cold as y'all know
we're in the beautiful country of Italy
currently in Florence we came here to
pick up my brother's Lamborghini too
soon okay if you guys did not see that
that is definitely a thing that was a
disaster happen yesterday I was possibly
gonna get one too but the whole
experience kind of went south but
whatever bro were in Italy this place is
freaking gorgeous
speaking of good-looking yo andis
next-door neighbor is the mostess she's
a cutest lady I've ever seen bilateral
baby mama mia she's like this tiny old
lady like a short little haircut no
disrespect do you think she's gonna have
any idea what I'm doing with this camera
[Laughter]
if you have a daughter I would like to
take her to LA and put her in a mansion
Jill I wanna feel yeah Louis Volant
lucky me tomorrow yeah I have a patent
his name is Colin he's like you but it
does I miss you cause by the way buddy I
love you oh you watch speaking of dogs
my roommates Evan dwarf mom but he just
said to her mom he got a dog dude so
when I go back for King Kong is gonna
have a sister oh my god it's gonna be
let new house new car new school bus new
dogs look at everyone just corrugating
out here enjoying Italy Mamma Mia daddy
also bro yo I've been in the family for
many many go seriously this place is
historic as you guys saw in the morning
montage this place is amazing olive
trees grape vineyard friends pool judge
mama mean and I guess it's a good time
to say if you're not a part of the logo
make sure to subscribe hit the button my
brother's here but I think the fastest
growing channel I need to hit the button
now wait I'll wait here
did you hit it yet night we have rode
into town we are about to get paid hello
are you recording
Brenna's Brisbane okay oh hi how are you
Brendan camera Hyundai says the pastries
here are like legendary can you verify
legend daddy oh they're like a Nona's
cooking like my grandma the daughter's
cocaine no cooking oh there's fish here
how much for the fish can I eat those
sue she's good too you got cross on sign
crossing on some pastries that look like
boobs they can't be not good yeah cheers
brother Jake oh my god REO the cocaine
right lease you're so perfect - Mamma
Mia but what's better than food more
food we are at an Italian grocery store
right now I'm gonna stock up on the
essentials fruit water a condom telling
ya the produce here is second to none oh
they own me you know what's crazy look
if they sell olives here right these are
all super fresh but we have olive trees
at our Villa later Logan I think we
should go pick some olives put them in
our miles maybe butts and pick grapes -
its aggressive here bro he did Brendan
cha-cha llamo he's gone he did no my
worst nightmare has come true this is
the war cereal just rows of corn flakes
and it doesn't any some poolside cardio
meal my heart is about to stop oh sorry
dude I'm a blogger I know they don't
have many bloggers I was a Lamborghini
Oh daddy came to deliver summer calling
Bobby hey papi thanks Brendan yo we've
been here for five minutes maybe come in
it's my brother in its natural element
Chuck what are you doing bro
yeah I know how you feel
thanks Jake just cuz we don't have
Lambos doing me we're not brothers oh
speaking of I got you this Jake still
really upset about it he was gonna get
his Lambo now he's like making the the
factory owners like apologize I don't
know what I gotta say this wouldn't be
Italy if there's just random sheets just
hanging here drying stuff you see movies
look at who they have drying machines or
washing machines anyways like I said
earlier andis got olives dude Andi this
is truly remarkable
can I pause you for once I get your
American bro you don't have a Italian
accent so I can't I can't do this yeah
he's a hundred percent of American stuff
but I know but this is actually dope I'm
not a huge ala fan but like look at you
can't eat these right on the spot right
you gotta like soak them in liquid mr.
vinegar so they need to brine them so if
you day Andy let's go look at the grape
[Music]
beautiful bad BT in the middle of these
vineyards enjoy pick some grapes you
know oh you thought I was gonna say
smash that too I've never seen a grape
like this pure purple speaking of
Smashing though Andy has picked some
grapes for us and tomorrow we're gonna
make gonna make wine or maybe worse
master Gregg's with their feet smash it
and you're American bro go praying
mantis
yo how did you see this Brendan I don't
know it moves differently than a leaf
pick him up you can pick up a praying
mantis
he's not gonna pray on my mantis oh not
even kidding the last time I picked up a
praying mantis I was like seven kind of
since I act like a 10 year old but yeah
dude look at him just ready to prey on
everyone's mantis I bet he's praying he
just wants a free maverick mercy he can
get on Logan
I don't blame you Rose the hardest merge
in the game copy why you can't did I
just use a praying mantis to plug skated
literally just hitting me right now why
they're called a praying mantis because
he puts his hands like a [ __ ] I will
make you my babies with your husband I
might have a yard sale with your load
change what are you saying Andy have you
ever eaten a fig that is alive big like
Fig Newton fit no never like a testicle
looking thing yeah eat enough to treated
it's alive Oh alive it's real living oh
but have you ever eaten alive I'm
guessing it's a book pear on the tree
he's awesome bro c'mere pear oh oh whoa
yeah yeah
yes Brendan juggle the life beards yeah
yeah fun fact about I'm dying he's got
really old ham like your grandma Oh oh
nice Andy bro you're crazy bro it's like
a secret room for a first story ham and
possibly killing people this is cool
look it's just a time
Wow he's great just cause like you know
ham comes from boars is that is just the
hand we're gonna be just sitting right
there oh great Wow you could say we're
having live life or the experiences it's
it's fresh ham Andy said this would cost
two thousand dollars in the United
States House bill there's a lot of money
for pizza like me happy relic apology
for all my vegan slash and vegetarian
low gangsters I know it looks bad it's
not that bad I'm just like pretending
for comedic purposes this is actually
that kind of cool so yeah let's cut this
thing open I'm to like I enjoy good
piece of meat I'm actually I'm actually
pumped for this this is my big baby bro
oh I'm glad I did this man don't judge a
book by it's cover this is so good
[Music]
oh shoot oh cheese and a glass of wine
this is the most Italians ever done and
it feels amazing plus you got this view
so good right now I'm not even kidding
guys this is some of the best meat I've
ever tasted and with the cheese and the
wine it's a good day to be the logo also
I just want to apologize if I'm making
you jealous in any way I know it like
food makes me jealous like if I have a
girlfriend and she cheats on me whatever
like I'm not gonna be like that jealous
but don't take my food I'll be pissed
absolutely wrap the cheese in the middle
bro little prosciutto cheese Italian
sandwich oh my god chase it with the
vino that's a wrap that's a wrap okay
we're going to Florence downtown
Florence I'm a happy camper let's do
this
[Music]
oh you're my twin you look at me bro wow
this is awkward now I'll see you later
there is apparently a dome here it's
called the Duomo
apparently though it is a how do they
say it dear my buddy babel fish just
reminds me of the mini horse we're gonna
get for evan in the new house by the way
evan bro this is a message to you I miss
you roommate and I love you that's all
just like when the plumber comes over
and you know I kinda see his butt crack
when he bends down I see that this thing
wow this is nice
I've open about with me my garage has
Mojo's grazie mama mia Papa VAR d mo
come on to the file to me and we go I
just got suddenly more Italian this is
incredible pendant let me tell you
something about being multicolored
iversity
diversification Donald Trump I don't
think that Donald Trump Brendan you get
that photo pesum above know it's Logan
Paul calm / stop just get there be a
maverick you know how it's Logan Paul
calm / shop know exactly Logan Paul calm
/ did not get killed but you bet your
ass to go buy submerge bro what what
that's my brother that's my brother you
maverick you're not a maverick the most
real answer I've ever had that he's a
conformist what does that mean that's
the opposite of a maverick no no no way
don't conform don't conform no no no I'm
wearing it straight up on my chest he's
like nah dude I'm unsubscribing don't yo
hold up hold up go tell me I'm a
maverick man no funny story about being
a maverick
no way were you were you guys just the
ones cheering with my brother yeah yeah
let's cheer louder now
[Applause]
just like who I am it's hard to like go
places and not cause nothing I think
that's I think that's what makes me such
a charge I think I'll get position okay
guys ready yeah that's great
Oh excellent I feel like Hayden was
taking selfies most definitely taking
selfies yes your friend Brendan what
what what no you're not come get away
from me you're not good what is his name
what is his name
what is it did she say it called me a
rake I'm not he could be a rake oh yeah
yeah he's good he could definitely be a
rake he could that would be right and
okay low gang that is the vlog I gotta
say Italy has like tired me out bro like
I'm pretty exhausted I don't remember
end inspire so tired I don't know why
cuz I normally like don't get tired high
your kids Loki what's your boy as you
know is a certified savage so I'm gonna
do savage things tonight I shouldn't say
that sounds like I'm gonna smash which
what happened but I might like partying
but one quick thing the show I shot you
guys know what you love it Logan Paul
versus yet another episode has come out
it comes out every week on my Facebook
page Logan Paul I will put the link for
in the description the episode for this
week is Logan Paul versus demolition
derby yes like the cars like you get in
the car you just like run into other
cars but you get to go absolutely and
say nearly broke every bone in my body
butts so here is a little preview of
that
I think you got the balls to do it
no absolutely not better go find some
I'd be a vet
[Music]
so yeah I want you guys to go watch that
link in description it's on my Facebook
page like I said just Logan Paul while
I'm plugging if you are not a part of
the Logan make sure to subscribe hit the
button for me did you do it yeah hit the
button for me bro
join the strongest family on YouTube
copy of Maverick merch every day we are
out here being mad not being afraid to
be different breakout of or whatever
bubble you live in travel explore
immersing yourself in life that's what
being a maverick is about Logan Paul
that cop slash shop link in description
ok I will see you guys tomorrow I love
you I think it is
[Music]