stop are you going to Coachella look
like this guy I feel like I'm gonna look
identical to him that's what have some
sort of like scientist effects about you
guys know I'm sick like way too off to
trying everything to just Austin but yo
I okay but it'd be funny content oh
where does this fluid go how does it not
go in my brain my brain will drink this
I look like subscribe because we do the
most activity no real talk go guys
it's the Maverick movement it's the
hottest softest merchants ok we're a
little weird we're a little different
that's a major special how often do I
have to do that three times a day I love
you buddy you're such a good dog yeah
there's a big chunk you so hard
sometimes hi thanks for you fun help
I'll see you later all right now time to
do adult things you guys saw yesterday's
vlog we haven't returned the trailer
from Yosemite it looks very clean yours
must have done great work Lydia's on her
shift today brow cleaning nasal passages
clean and trailers she wants to go to
Coachella
it's I thought she was I've never seen
her this attentive guy just wants to
leave to go to cello oh my god let's
check the box let's see if she crushed
this one do you think no chain her over
no chance roaming the smelly box Gaza
plush smells - I will say it is a lot
cleaner whatever she did here again I am
impressed
but sadly it still smells like urine I
cannot be troubled by these things right
now guys ah we make fun of Lydia so
we're going to Coachella - I don't have
my chela outfit fight ready I think
today I'm gonna figure that where this
how all these girls talk prepare
yourself this weekend you will never see
more pictures of girls with flower
crowns on their head then now the
trailers dragging here it I'm gonna
check give it the old eyeball I think I
know the issue maybe we should have shut
the back whoa whoa I don't know it sound
like a little lame agreement my windows
trying to talk to me hello I come in
peace and with an RV full of peace
honey you can have her
[Applause]
problem just gonna go to store get my
cello outfit yeah I don't think you're
gonna clear that room plus is just a
pitch to park that works we're only
taking up one two three four good you
think so I think so
well that's a skirt do you think he
should wear this to Coachella yeah my
basic it's pretty hot let's get it this
has already been Coachella rated what
the [ __ ] happened here you just see it
now girls running in and out of the I
was getting off Michelle oh shoot I'm
gonna get this I wanna get this one
stop this is why I'm tearing your head
up my pink oh I look better stop I'm a
savage long Coachella oh that's your
challenge yeah my boy looking like are
you going to Coachella stop are you
going to Coachella are you crazy I can't
tell if I want to dance in them or play
checkers on or start off a NASCAR race
good fine Jeff good call about you I'm
Chell it out you going to a Coachella
okay
a my daughter going me that's why oh you
already are so yeah sure look like you
Connie I feel like you got potential
maybe you can come to Coachella with me
okay okay okay guys now that we're cello
ready I think it's that time bro I'm
gonna be the best-looking person there
for sure I actually hate Coachella so
much bro I'm being forced to go by the
way except freaking my god Bobbie
Spencer for now guys I have more
important things to do you guys know
we're streaming every day live 6 p.m. on
Twitch my user name is Logan Paul was
taken why is that because Logan Paul was
taken so yeah I'm gonna have to kick you
guys I don't know one say well I sent
some Huck's okay yeah we'll see you
later their speech
okay
I want this too bad I want this too bad
so I'm gonna do it for my team all right
guys all jokes aside before I sign off
the vlog there's one more thing I gotta
do oh I hate this so much bro oh one two
three I'm part of the long game with
this guy do it the shark is merely that
you do splashes subscribe button for me
be like talking while I'm doing it is
really nice making other nostril yep
also don't forget to cup your beverage
but the hottest merch is again looking
for like a spy's job or legged
description okay I love you guys helps
you tomorrow we're going to Coachella
take you
[Music]
yeah I got one
ah