[Music]
[Applause]
i'm talking about that
cash money yo this is ten thousand
dollars cash as you all know i flew from
l.a to ohio to celebrate christmas here
and to be honest guys okay
you know you just saw my 2017 best year
my life video
this year has been crazy like my whole
life has been insane but especially this
year and i
haven't really done anything like
incredibly super nice for my parents
what am i a [ __ ] shot
no hey yo good morning little guy so
yeah this is the year that that changes
oh hi
hello young doggy i brought kong he's
the best dog in the world
so tomorrow is christmas day we
celebrate it at my dad's house because
my parents uh decided to ruin my
childhood and get divorced so today
we're celebrating christmas here at my
mom's i can say this because the vlog
will not be live by the time you get
skipped i got my dad
an 80 000 truck this is the year that
logan paul is gonna do nice things for
other people it's time to spread the
wealth literally spread the wealth so i
had my assistant lydia get ten thousand
dollars and twenty dollar bills for my
mom my sweet beautiful mother and i'm
gonna make it rain on her i figured my
mom's such a nice girl from ohio she's
never had ten thousand dollars thrown at
her in fact a wise woman once said
i don't dance now i make money moves and
today we're making money moves
so if you're not a part of the logang
make sure to subscribe oh my god my
voice guys you know i lost my voice
sound like
rapper this is crazy really though
actually hit the subscribe button for me
do yourself a favor today do something
different it's good to switch it up it's
good to be unique that's the maverick
movement and i can't trust that santa's
gonna get it to you so make sure you get
it logan paul.com for link in the chat
the hottest softest merch in the game
now
i did not forget about this kid either
hi my name is yeah don't worry little
brother
i got you guessing a lot of gifts if
it's not a lambo i don't give a [ __ ]
i think you're going to like these
brothers okay it's actually dope okay
it's not lambo actually though i don't
care oh look
please don't run away yo can you shut
the [ __ ] up
i'm vlogging yo quiet wait are you
waiting for the bigger touch i'm the
bigger
what you think you're a touch i am the
definition of a josh bro look me up you
are pretty big chucks look at you being
able to look at the characters
you're wearing fourth of july guys it is
the fourth of july
what every day it's your dates every day
is a free day because oh my god
damn american what do you get a rolex
did you get mama rolex i already have
one bro wait what i did in fact
you got her rolex i got her ten thousand
dollars cash i'm literally going to make
it random
she's right there mom
no i asked him to not do that he's oh
god
there he is he's little please don't run
away bro i asked nicely
so this is a lot going down here guys i
will say it's cool being home it's cool
seeing little gangsters in the town i
grew up in we had a little incident
last night actually
whoa crazy life we live little brother
hi
my name is jeff but it's okay nothing i
can't handle because yo
it's jake you need to shut the [ __ ] up
when i'm vlogging dawg i'm about to hit
15 million
all right i'm about to hit four billion
views cuz oh with respect to that though
you know how many views that is
four billion you just said i was gonna
say no there's nothing we can't handle
though
look at the tree though oh it's
my big day you ready it's not a lambo i
don't want it i got you something better
than a lambo you gotta love it you're
gonna love it
i'm ready i'm ready but first i'm gonna
give calm this gift you got oh
but it is christmas so you have to wear
it mom is this one mine
is this one jake's yes there we go
thanks mom appreciate it look at all
this stuff
wow my favorite part is the chapstick a
lottery ticket i also got a card for my
grandma oh
jake there's money inside look no way
just a token to let you know that we
love you
two fifty dollar checks
i don't need the money right so she she
should keep the money so all my family
members watching this thank you thank
you grandma but keep your money like
go go go buy like socks i don't know hit
the strip club
yeah yeah so many better things to do
than give it to me did you win
i won what'd you win i won 20
you're a winner logan and a wiener trust
me bro you keep saying if it's not a
lambo you don't care
this i promise is better than a lambo
because it's it's like it's out it's
i promise promise it's not a lambo
it's not a landmass oh dude tickle
tick nurse bro
it's that map reverse problem that's
crazy
cool is this one yours too no no no i
know my boy
he can go out he gonna dent the universe
i see you definitely not a lambo
it's but it's better than a lambo logan
paul dot com
shop like why would you get a lambo when
you could just get merged to jake
love logan here you go yo
wait what no way you got the chrome
well that's crazy people are feeding for
this bro
you're stuck in life bro you didn't give
me any guess what yes
what oh it's better than a lambo this is
from logan yeah it's for me there you go
that's mine
yeah whoa
you know growing up jake love trucks
he's he's a car fanatic he loves all the
vehicles and
uh what it's just i'm wondering what
you're doing oh there it goes wow
you should put kong in the bathroom it's
your big day
cuteness overload well look how much fun
he's having yeah
okay i think that's enough of that
you see when i was a kid if someone gave
me a truck personally i would play with
it not destroy it okay
time for more gifts here jake i got this
gift for you i really don't want to open
it
oh my gosh yeah yeah cause that's the
only type of videos you [ __ ] make you
[ __ ] idiot
i'll make another laser video don't
think if we was gonna do it
let's do it
all right you're gonna love this one i
love the wrapping what
yeah yeah heck yeah you can thank evan
for that one
no not my roommate though the asian kid
what asian kid gotta give her that yeah
for sure no good call evan much
appreciated i can put my cosmo in there
oh i love you mom
thank you i just tried to kiss me in the
mouth i didn't know you did yeah you did
stay away from those so it's for
my girls here jake wow what could it be
it's a lemon honestly this is the
business i'm not yes
that's what i'm saying bro this one's no
joke it's not a good gift
that's a good gift it doesn't make any i
don't know edible i don't know
no it's not like i don't know guys they
squish
they're like plushies how does it squish
like that i don't
it's weird it's so squishy squishy so
squishy i'm gonna die
so you guys this gift is for logan okay
i asked lydia to help me
i know way too clean yeah don't drop it
though
it's breakable i already did flashback
that literally just happened
i said why you tell me after that i said
be careful with it and then he dropped
it
i mean he even did you know not drop out
of school just college
you be very careful what did you i got
your cologne too
this doesn't make any sense the story
behind it this is the clone it's worth
a million dollars right here actually
you got me a million dollar cologne well
i only could afford this much
smell it let's see what else you can
smell it without spraying it oh whoa
this is
all the girls all the girls this is no
joke it's not a joke
he's out wow actually thank you mom here
mom i got you another trust me jake
she's gonna like this one i liked them
all
yo you're gonna have so much sex games
oh no this is weird whoa
yeah i'm gonna go ahead and dab out of
here yo this is this is so awkward
because like now this next gift is gonna
be more awkward for me than i planned on
it being
um here you go me madre hurt logan i got
you logan do you know how weird this
is right now like seriously did you mean
this for a girl
a girlfriend no i i meant you do you
love it
i love it i don't know why i got that
i don't either i thought it'd be funny
but no i'm just kind of [ __ ] weird i
don't know what you had in mind
when you did this i know because you
didn't have any other girls to buy for
actually yeah
do give me this yo i'm bringing this
back to l.a
another logan pagan yo the maverick
shorts wait what
wait is that a youth maverick shirt wait
what yo i was thinking ahead
you can give this to your kids bro when
you have kids so i got you the youth
merch
oh what yo you got the big hoodie that
sold out like hot cakes
what are you doing oh no i mean it's the
hottest merch in the game it's still
gonna be hot even in the cold
another great thing about christmas is
all the pimples look i got this one
right here and i peeled it because i'm a
dummy thanks for giving me the best
genetics mom
you're welcome it's sarcasm we got acne
for days
what is this ma this is for you from
your uncle jeffrey
oh i have an uncle jeff oh yeah i'm just
kidding bro it's a joke because i make
comedy bro he made this
for me to give to you ready
oh my gosh this is actually amazing this
fits the vibe of the maverick house is
that wooden chair
i really like this gif uncle jeff thanks
man okay so this has all been cute but i
think it's time for your big gift what
is it
i got a big guess stand up you know this
life we've been living
me and my brother jake has been crazy
it's all thanks to you and i've never
really done
anything like big for you or dad and
this year i want that to change because
i want to share the wealth and i owe it
all to you so thank you mama now with
that said i'm going to blindfold you
with your new dress there you go mama
all right all right here come here okay
now stand right here
are you nervous yes she has no idea
i'm sorry i'm just now seeing the way
you look is it it's really funny
okay i'm upstairs i'm grabbing the money
oh this is a lot of money okay here we
go how you feeling ma
i feel weird is water gonna go on my
head no it's not a prank
bye mom take the blindfold off
[Music]
hey y'all there you go there you go yeah
i'm the sun
yeah what the
yeah this is it ma whoa look kong money
oh my gosh do i have to pick all this up
so this is it's
raining money hallelujah it's raining
money
so this is uh this is ten thousand
dollars cash i've never had ten thousand
dollars cash on
my floor and i'm sure no one's ever made
it rain on you either no that's that
maverick stuff baby who's doing it
so yeah here that's all yours thanks
honey wow
i guess we can go on a trip thank you i
got you
no you you
[Music]
thank you oh okay i i guess jake's doing
it he
just gave mom a rolex look at it oh
snap we could be rolex twins you're my
mom
you're my son damn bro
yo with the cash you look sottier than
ever right now this is truly incredible
our mind is a stripper but i'm repping
the merchandise
yeah ooh yeah she wrote that merch ooh
don't go like i'm
shot hey oh look family friends careful
there's jungle come on in
come on guys come on in guys there's ten
thousand dollars in the floor guys
stay back don't touch it's my mom's
christmas gifts
i mean i brought cookies yeah oh don't
stop it
yo so look this is all fun and games
it's been a good christmas but uh
there's still one thing i gotta do
i've come to cash this lottery ticket
how much is it i won twenty dollars you
guys have twenty dollars cash i'm all
about the cash today on some cardi b
oh thank you bro yeah don't worry
everybody
have no fear i got it yeah where was it
no i won that like one lottery
ten thousand and twenty dollars cash for
my mama look at that there you go mama
ten thousand twenty dollars cash oh
hello that was the vlog
if you find yourself confused sad lonely
and just downright unhappy it's probably
because you're not in the low game so
subscribe and all that can change us
subscribe join the strongest family on
youtube cop yourself some maverick merch
the hottest softest mission to get and
go out and be different guys the
maverick revolution is real tomorrow's
vlog is a huge one so be ready for that
turn your post notifications on ring the
little bell and with that said little
gang i love y'all now see you tomorrow
hey who's that santa looking at take
your gifts and give them back
maverick merch is where it's at got the
hoodie got the hat who's that santa
looking at you should drink more milk
down fat you should get my new backpack
throw away that dirty sack
yeah literally two of these burned
oh no oh [ __ ]
my bad oh my god