[Music]
how do we not get kicked out of our spot
yet we are literally camping in a
parking lot in Yosemite National Park on
the roof of a giant school bus towing
ATVs and dirt bike with the kayak on top
got it have you seen this view okay I'm
not even kidding you guys know it's my
birthday so we decided to come here to
Yosemite because I didn't want to do the
basic like la thing go to a club or
something
yeah I'm old I'm 23 now but this view is
so amazing that's a good finger wake up
to like four hours of sleep but this is
actually amazing this is totally
breathtaking you know that waterfall
reminds me of Wendy right you guys know
today is my birthday so if there's one
thing well I want two things for my
birthday one subscribe during the low
gang the strongest family on YouTube and
hit the little bell next to the
subscribe button for me look we're lit
alright and if I'm not mistaken I think
we got some little gangsters right here
have a subdued are you guys no low gay
guys in number two my birthday guys we
just dropped these new worldwide
maverick hoodies actually I miss is more
for you today is the last day to get
t-shirts yesterday they were on sale for
five dollars if you didn't get it then
you missed it I'm sorry we also just
dropped a new performance shorts in
celebration of the one-year anniversary
of the Maverick bread yo this is crazy
yes welcome Paul that cops last shot or
link in description let's check on the
downstairs how's everyone doing this
morning my birthday
what's up hi it was my birthday so we
just want to come to Yosemite and we got
here like 4:00 a.m. and this was empty
so we just kind of you right so a couple
of issues with that everyone who wanted
to camp wherever they felt like it did
there's that there's the fact that you
took up how many spots we're looking at
five spots
we'll just cuz it's a bus so like I
didn't know where else to do it you so
do you think that because it's a bus
that this is probably not the best place
to put it be considering now y'all are
blocked in I had the hunch
you know we getting ticketed bro I don't
know if Park Rangers they got weapons
bro I thought they just like control the
park but I just don't like it but times
right now it was so funny we thought
this would happen much earlier but we
got sleep bro it's a good yes hobby yes
guys we did not get a ticket holy crap
dude for the first time like 15 years is
my end up being a good birthday no
leaving LA was the move and even better
we ran into some little gangsters when
guys when I say we're family like I mean
it like this is a prime example of that
and the one mom her name was Trisha she
had an extra spot in a camber ground by
the way guys all the camping spots are
booked right now it's Easter so it's
really hard to make a reservation but
alas a low gang came through and we got
a parking spot time to ha yeah are you
Trisha oh my gosh you're a miracle thank
you the park rangers they they said they
didn't give me a ticket is my birthday
per se we gotta get that all our spot
here so make yourselves at home
you rock I'm gonna go look at this Lake
oh my god bro this might be the Huq of
all hop seriously dude University Logan
here's you here's your birthday give
beautiful Park and a camping spot oh my
observe how crystal clear that water is
- I bet you it's warm do we have some we
have so much stuff to do right now oh my
god the gas is leaking what happened I
think I heard you correctly you said
that this gas leaked all the way onto
all our food okay it's okay dude it's my
worst fear coming through the April
Fool's gods have cursed me for yet
another birthday how bad is it
okay so no one either ate like matches
around the food and also keep the merch
away because it's too freakin fire baby
oh shut up
baby come on we got the onion got the
peppers yeah you know this border fence
and I are gonna go for a little jog take
a little bath in the lake I'm just so
happy right now guys like this is such a
good birthday for me I thrive in this
environment I love nature and I gotta
say the Ohio boy is definitely very
happy right
are we about to get this joke right now
and you bet your ass we're going young
that trying to keep up I know
rhino comes quick no you have to go slow
first buddy I know I know all right
ladies and gentlemen let's talk
[Music]
- see
it's ooh
I'm gonna need that log sorry we just
get that with a beautiful job and by the
way guys I don't know how many times I'm
gonna say this this place is absolutely
stunning however we don't know the
temperature of the water we're hoping
it's warm and we got to take showers
somehow so yeah I would say like okay
yeah I'll take those odds we think you
look pretty warm
I tell you yes sounds like it's a little
cold from the voice right clearly
clearly right now
Yosemite not deliver anyways the good
news is I think chef Andre has from
English food prepared for us let's go
check it out and your God this deserves
like a two-second montage bro and go
[Music]
even the vegan burger is amazing just
like this is a meal of camping bro
Yosemite who's doing it it's cool cuz I
can't even taste the gasoline of them so
however you did that good job
anyways this birthday is amazing quick
clot to the next scene yo so a forest
ranger came by earlier he was giving us
the lowdown and he pointed at these and
he goes you can ride those we didn't
think we were gonna be able to in a
state park you look so good
[Music]
oh wow
yes Hawking is going fast slow down
there Speed Racer get it jack what I
mean
[Applause]
this one's dead
try to keep me
I'm afraid
fall asleep you doing this extreme Huck
we just had this is like you are basic
level maximum right now here now here's
the kids think listen life lessons you
work hard and you follow your passions
and gold you don't have to work a day in
your life okay so I don't know what this
work thing is alright Wow we are quite
the campers right now damn son I feel
like the world's my oyster right now
what can we do next love you guys true
they're waiting on Andy and Spencer to
get here so we can go hiking I'm so
exhausted I myself trying to take a nap
the last we've been spotted man you guys
got that Hawkeye how do we sneak entrap
to God idea this is your idea
help me hook
[Applause]
[Music]
they came from the hills handy
[Applause]
[Music]
it's very important okay I have 23 now
writes my birthday um you know but I do
got to be response to a little bit so
you know it is the national park I saw I
know where Linda Jesus mother of God
okay go but if we could keep the noise
down to a minimum right so I don't get
arrested or not
[Applause]
okay guys that is the vlog if you're not
a part of the Logan you can see right
here we are
not only do I want you to subscribe but
hitting a little Bell next to the
subscribe button be notified so you
don't miss the labor and also guys you
want to tell me where to get the hottest
news reel as you can see every day we're
out here change the world every day
we're out here doing a different locale
of your honor I will see you tomorrow
take it easy bad by the way thanks for
the best birthday ever guys I love you
[Music]
what's happening