very tall tall vehicle actually about
the roll over roll over
they'll be crazy hey guys I'm upside
down I'm not proud of what I'm about to
do I'm only here for camaraderie reason
Hummer honor II like friendship hate
myself I'm addicted to tic toc now
become a green screen for tick-tock I've
gotten my nose pierced for tick-tock and
unfortunately I'm doing tick-tock dances
kind of what chick that's the home of
courage and I'm happy to be there I
think I'm gonna lean into it
yeah okay I'm a tick-tock star now
YouTube's been there done that I know
anyways tick-tock I'm done to everything
devoid of all emotion so people call me
a sociopath like anything you know
friends you get over we're gonna lose a
friendship over yeah I'd be ridiculous
by the way where's Mike
[Music]
very tall tall vehicle actually about
the rollover
they'll be crazy I was TV right like 45
degrees and then life was like mass now
more than ever I realize my life is
really upside taste I should do boys I'm
not the only one addicted to tick tock
looks like this got all the poles wait
you said the alcohol looks round on my
mom's side of the family bro let's do
something that actually matters you
think I could punch through that
watermelon mojo guys not sure I'm a
boxer anymore I may just be a youtuber
again sorry podcast we have a doctor on
and I don't mean to scare you but he
said this is doomsday are you prepared
for doomsday this in our eyes is
doomsday I hear doomsday I think duct
tape so we bought a lot of duct tape so
I don't know how effective it is so
we're gonna try to build a bridge across
my pool you know I was an industrial
engineer in college before I dropped out
it has nothing to do with building dr.
bridges absolutely nothing
[Music]
aesthetically it looks great
functionally I don't know telework dude
yeah duct-tape bridge yeah awesome idea
gov oh come on it's on Paul and heavy I
need to disperse my surface area so I'm
gonna go down like on my back I think
the problem was I'm too heavy for see
how burly does good boy I've never seen
[Applause]
[Music]
if it were outside see I have no reason
to believe it won't work inside I'm
gonna just like shimmy my way across I
know how strong my bridges so no I'm not
nervous oh man it turns out I am nervous
[Music]
[Applause]
get on your knees
oh so original [ __ ] you people
his oval fake he's cutting it while walk
across