[Music]
coming to the stage the Challenger Logan
Paul coming to the stage again the
reigning defending you to top of the
world
k us
welcome to London [ __ ]
Oh sick that Walmart [ __ ] won't work
here boy
has an England already suffered enough
we lost the Croatian in the semi-final
we had truck come over last week now we
got you this week you got a new
girlfriend now Chloe Bennet will saw
babes
[Applause]
wait wait wait so why don't you
introduce me to one huh apparently you
only have any 5% of your testicle let me
give her the extra 15 let me show you a
real man shut the [ __ ] up [ __ ]
this is my town now [ __ ] it's so funny
shut the [ __ ] up it's funny to hear you
talk about your baby carrot dick keep
going I enjoy it how are you gonna
Torian we have auditions for Baywatch
get the par and still not end up in the
final movie
my soul ended up in the final movie
where were you oh yeah deleted scenes
you know what listen let's let's give it
let's get a chart going for the pool you
see you see everyone everyone has
everyone has my back and no one has
yours besides your Ludacris mom and your
disgusting delusional diet your
disgusting man
you said you beat me in the fight you
said you beat me in the fight with one
hand right
you wouldn't do [ __ ] you're an old man
but I'm sure I'm sure you wouldn't mind
last one round for the little girls you
like kissing
[Applause]
you sick deadbeat bald-headed prick
are you gonna make not one but two
dumbass children the [ __ ] is what will
your sperm if you want to ask you about
the video shut the [ __ ] up
ask your mom go ask your mom you ready
for some questions I said let's do some
questions don't throw anything calm down
all right
hey I'ma be honest [ __ ] you loca
[ __ ] you loco [ __ ] you loca [ __ ] you
loca
[ __ ] you local all right how you feeling
bro it's not lip covering hey hey I
would hear and answer your questions or
I feel like kiss I address everything
origin in the mouth shut see you August
20 bin
[Applause]
Babu [ __ ]
[ __ ] up poles [ __ ] up ooh
[Applause]
August 25th
mark my words that [ __ ] is going
down I don't play in this [ __ ] I don't
play watch what's your line virtually
cheap [ __ ] like I always say I
won't I told the truth
[Applause]
[Music]