[Music]
yup yup yeah I got good morning low gang
what's up I got the fur on I got the
Maverick on go as usual it's going to be
a good day actually I have something
really special planned
you guys know my roommate heaven he's so
he's a dwarf or a little person he just
moved on to LA like I brought him out
here and I was like why not get him a
girl so we're gonna wake him up because
I think he's still sleeping with the
classic maverick merged with the
classiest merch in the game
Logan ball complex job good morning Evan
my boy I do boom I'm doing pretty good
good good it's your big day bro
why I got I got something big for you
really nice it was not nothing babe
Russin it's your big day
walk forward buddy I want to do that was
oh my god you know what this situation
needs one drink cool great huh yeah same
thing okay
replay action
now I don't have an assistant cuz I look
whit I have to do the adult II myself
let me buy something this sucks like
this full-heartedly full fresh full
savage full it's like I'm pretty excited
for this you know I'm excited to do like
got Evan needs a girl straight up I do
you got
Chloe you got Laila I don't have
anything I took the liberty into my own
hands
and worked my ass off the fun perfect
girl from evidence I know you Hey
I'm vlogging just look at this badge
this game try to ignore it oh she is a
door but she's like the door fro like
she's hot dude yeah she's like she's a
[ __ ] the hottest I literally look like
world top 10 hottest Wars and she was in
the list I didn't know that's the thing
let anybody tell me that right but it is
dope for sure she's gonna come over I
figured you guys go on a date put a
microphone on you put a microphone on
her you totally invasive and intrusive
of your privacy and get a good vlog I'm
such a douchebag I think I think that's
on the vlog every time I'm sure I know
you feel weird it'll be a good time but
no they're not stopping
yeah very difficult
oh here we go here we go why do we have
to do that cutaway rest in peace Jake
Disney contrary well he still got this
is the contract
how can we get them to here watch it at
the ceiling I guess so
if it hits the ceiling hard enough I'm
sure later yeah here what are they even
making rooms I shot Murchison ah I
haven't how was the last time you've
been on a real date
me personally I went on a date last week
some kind of the master I know what
you're thinking yes I did smash so
here's here's what you got to know about
dates bro there's a simple rule and if
you follow it both ends Oh what now ten
out of ten ladies and gentleman let me
tell you about the three see I wrote him
on this hand first with the marker and I
realized I messed up because it's
extreme fade-resistant and confirmed
this stink coming off so that I had
Brendan redoing with the pen on this end
okay scene number one as a compliment
bro compliment the girls how does she
look she smells like so you like her
face or something wow I really like you
sure thanks low gangster life oh wow
ding oh sorry I've got an ear infection
I'm so sorry got row seat number to
cuddle so first you compliment her and
then you cuddle her I really like your
shirt Thanks low game for life oh oh oh
oh wow now I really like your shirt oh
now you've done the first two Z's they
got 1c to go kiss you kiss her that's
not just the king that's my bed
that's you stuff ready you make me look
dumb on my blog you got a kiss there bro
otherwise she knows you're trying to
marry her bro so practice on me okay
cool cool what stays after this for the
actual thing that said I think she's
almost here so my boy get ready yeah
Evan you got this girl you got a dog
how are you I'm added lovin that's me
too this is Oscar
she's young after you that's your last
name
take this anyways I said not me anymore
really
oh my god I so I know this pretty nice
restaurant down the street would you
like to go faster no it's show time
wait bro come on calm Oh
I came out to the states I like six
seven years ago
how'd you meet Logan he actually set me
up some ideas of like a you want to hang
out I was like okay hi I'm having so
much fun also also there's no microphone
here
could you hear all that no yeah I had
this ear infection my left ear ah that's
a door thing it isn't doing things and
then Logan yeah here decided to hit me
leer this one although I hit you I
grabbed you in an attempt to kiss you
like that sounds matter hey how are ya
how about oh there you go yeah I'm gonna
hang back you guys go do they met for
sure right Oh fer sure ha ha ha I would
you guys later
[Music]
yes not many people know about this
place
it's nice best shot called Jake Jack
okay so I took the fur off to stay
undercover I just saw the lovebirds walk
into Shake Shack interesting choice Evan
urban I like it i'ma try to stay
discreet can be tough because my long
blonde shot hair are you good bro are
you gonna tag me at least if you post it
at Logan fall on Instagram then there
right I think it's super important that
Evan doesn't forget the three C's
remember guys number one is compliments
oh I hope he's just dishing out
compliments I really like you shirt
excellent nothing was really good on you
thank you
I got to say I've never done this before
but this is the most incredible thing
I've ever seen in my life
yeah I'm like the annoying obnoxious
vlogger version of Cupid let's make it
people fall in love let me give you a
cup of water
[Music]
thank you they are very nice okay they
found a seat I know I'm probably not
hiding from them Brendan and I are
posted up behind a bush right now also
let me just point out it looks like
Brendan has a bomb on his back it's not
a box just microphones I promise okay I
think it's time for number two the
second seat go for the cut 11 yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what's up it didn't work yeah you start
eating Fatburger yeah he's pretty good
what do you do for a living I'm an
artist my paint and I oh yeah I like to
paint paintings and them so I didn't
make a living out of that oh oh yeah
she's Pablo Picasso girl yeah what kind
of painted video I play and I just like
pop culture like dog so much music maybe
you can paint a picture of me one day
Amy I'm dad you want me to paint a
picture of Evan like the Titanic I want
you to draw me
[Music]
I want have you been a dwarf I think I
woke up today and I realized that was a
source same thing happened to me last
week exactly in the legs are don't even
realize you're an orphan here one day
you're like I'm a dork
my name is food and like I need to get
the plate
I like plastic I'm glad we can relate on
a level and I was good so I thought this
would be super awkward oh it's not there
here you know man so are you uh not
gonna eat your food I'm not really
hungry honestly yeah I'm not really
either just going to go somewhere else
and damn high
[Music]
[Laughter]
so every took her to the cute little
star here were sneaking up on them I'm
not quite sure how obvious it is that
were right behind them this is big yo
this is like the final moment of the day
yes a bunch of just like pretty nicely
to know got a painted horse behind us
got a fountain off another boys why
they're just listing things that they
see ya guys
yeah so it's a pretty nice place to
unique not many people know about it we
hope out of like romantic a little
[Music]
what do you mean what I'm doing giving
you a kiss like I thought we had a nice
day today like we went out to eat yeah
we went out to eat we connected
talk about a Dorset is Amanda door
problems like I thought it was perfect I
like what I ate
I told Logan this wait [ __ ] so you
thought we just hanging out his friend
yeah this was my job like all right
we're grabbing up my thigh
not as a date like so long and I'm a
husband and like I was just gonna go
hang out we're leaving
well I'm really sorry I was a confusion
yeah we can go now oh no no no it is she
stopped so she's still there so that I
didn't know she did not tell me that
if she did I probably did I didn't get
that information I know I'm sorry
yeah we get a ride back yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
hey cop hi thanks for coming doctor yeah
no problem
I mean good things happen before you go
I got some for you some some maverick
woman's March because your maverick hey
there you go sorry be right down no I'm
sorry no I got I got good news what
number to toss out though oh oh oh
I hold you to a day I will do things
like that still okay locate that is the
vlog I feel bad really bad that I let my
boy down my days right there I know I'm
sorry
I didn't do my research but here's what
I do know the low kang is the strongest
family on youtube and the fastest growth
so if you're not subscribed subscribe
hit the button get your low gang and
maverick Maher - link is in the
description or live all i got slashed
shot I will redeem myself for Evan I
promise y'all got surprise for you today
I thought I'd surprise to break my arm
Jesus Christ okay looking that is the
vlog don't forget to work hard push
yourself be a maverick be unique be
different I love y'all I'll see you
tomorrow
[Music]