I'd like to dedicate this first move to
an invention that changed the face of
modern warfare and sexuality it's called
the Gatling gun Adam ah
Adam ah hey guys so of vlogging from a
GoPro I've never done this before I
wasn't planning on vlogging this I'm
currently in the Gucci store right now
I'm laughs because were you shopping for
clothes for my music video coming up on
the 24th it's called on my hand it's
called no handlebars and I was gonna
keep the outfit a surprise so we're at
the Gucci store right now we're not a
lot of filming there now I'm gonna do it
anyways Christmas apps but this jacket
that we like yeah all right let me just
show you anyways no honey no oh my god
you guys know this about I am NOT a
shopper I don't love spending my money
on clothes this'll be this will be the
most expensive piece of clothing I've
ever bought oh yeah this is my stylist
showing you this was your idea
oh my god is only five in the world it's
my big day I think I'm gonna keep the
mustache until the video by the way I
wonder if the audios weird isn't
blogging and I go for over so many
questions but my mind is racing what
okay so the Gucci people caught me good
news they didn't kick me out like even
these jeans what you're thinking about
are like $1500 and the worst part about
this is Gucci is not paying me for this
like Gucci you owe me money yo God is
doing it
servers get your maverick merchants
you'll be a maverick throwing the low
gang copy of all that got sliced 95%
because it's dope it's the hottest
softest merch in the game but 5%
currently because if you could help me
pay for my Gucci the way I just want to
point out personal opinions I'm in this
outfit mustache works look at this bro
mm-hmm oh my gosh this music video is
gonna be absolutely saying guys but okay
let's talk about what's happening today
so actually today's a big day
not because I have a wolf and an eagle
on my fingers but because it's the
premiere of my friend King baches movie
where's the money which since you boy is
the nectar I'm starring in it and we may
take the cool bus there with a bunch of
people in it and then watch the movie
it's gonna be dope maybe make out touch
buzz classic
so the three beans your shoes denim have
a denim
alright so 11:6 2890 just take this all
jokes aside guys this video is going to
be make more money just a real good life
plan at this point I think you're gonna
need to rob a bank
seriously bro Yolo gang you down bro
haha
twelve thousand dollars worth of clothes
right there
yo since when did heaven get boring
let's talk about this Brendon which is
like what like honestly bro like this is
weird dude I think it's because he kids
became a father yo I don't previous ly
to that throw this cabinet was undamaged
now I have to pay for this one as well
you're not doing so yourself kids and in
cabinets and cabinets and then I went a
little extra with this this bag here oh
my god oh it's a bird ring this is
badass some Mavericks bro let's go right
yeah I mean look it's a fact that I
might ok another dope but we're gonna
worry about it later I have a premiere
to go to and get ready for yeah I
noticed that after the vlog channel
started doing well my publicist like
pretty they forced me to get pretty for
like trivial events like a premiere that
it's not like trivial it's kind of a big
deal but I don't want to be Hollywood oh
just a guy David
I appreciate you though making me look
good removing my acne blemishes and
stuff David is there any way that you
can put enough makeup on that that
mustache goes away oh yeah no in fact we
have a better idea for you Brennen
actually are you making it darker
why don't burn it yes dumb dope huh okay
it changes the look now I'm extra double
I feel good
[Music]
here's the thing though I'm not quite
cool with my ankles showing I'm not used
to this Hollywood thing broke you ready
for the flood that's not my brand but I
feel like I look good it's a premiere
you got to go do this stuff also yo
check this out if you take a look down
here yes the cool book looking cool also
yo check this out right here baby the
Maverick on the what is this called
lapel pal lapel
look pal should be called the Paul am i
right okay and the Maverick on the back
yo cuz that's what we do every single
day and yo again since I spent way too
much money on Gucci get your mercy
looking for that come my boy Johan is
coming yeah one fact about your harness
you rub his head you get cooler no not
as cool as the cool bus look back close
just imagine bro come on come on we got
a premiere to go - jour/day that's my
flight hop on in ladies
it's cool it's the coolest bus
Wow I don't even know those girls go
get'em Geordi first time driving the bus
I trust him bro he's got the dopest
outfit in the game oh hey boss come
through for bucks coming through we're
gonna be late to the premiere bro I
don't know if we're gonna be late
it's gonna be more like fashionably on
purpose late I was under the impression
all right keep it straight you stifle
profession and showing your complexion
I'm stocking your decency Oh
[Music]
cheering apologize things I didn't know
until you compromise if you can't keep
your cool
they like this is bigger than I expected
there's so much going on all I want to
do is find my boy king Brad congratulate
him after all it's his movie freak until
we got Terry Crews in the movie we got
our Method Man cat grandma this is a big
deal I will find him and I will give
them just the warmest of hugs and just
kickin it have been priced them but
right now we just done with us all hi Oh
cat the cat Graham good luck for the
vlog you have to you have to bring
energy ma okay that's enough of that
ji-sook a worn out from the 70 you see a
cat will feel it really it's your big
day like I say it a lot as a joke today
it's your big day Charlotte it's our big
day you won the poster just as well as I
know you'll always be like I've seen you
in a week
I know
[Music]
everybody would be shooting in the
middle of my all-nighter and I like it's
thank me later best from here I've been
to for like theatrical a good wine no
I'm not lying so just a few more
no it's Method Man I've seen the trailer
for Saturday whole my boys the savage
always madman can I give you a bike or
just a warm hug of embrace like that
congratulations this is very exciting
it's just all this fun excitement wow
that's a lot of deaths today not a must
a must
[Music]
Oh
dedicate this first move to an invention
that changed the face of modern warfare
and sexuality it's called the Gatling
gun it works best if she's bowlegged
[Applause]
it's not my big day but it's it's it
it's my small day Wow
yo Johannes what you think yo I loved it
I stole a every what you think like I'm
not just saying this low gay this movie
is hilarious and yes I play a sidekick
yes like I'm the best character in the
movie but next Tuesday on iTunes it
comes out highly highly highly suggest
you watch this movie
yo DDR the lasting good were you filming
in there you got some laughs not so fun
fact
Brendan look look at my pinky no
the Gucci rings goes I lost the Gucci
ring I lost I spent five hundred dollars
on a Gucci ring they couldn't put them
both on cuz I thought it was cool in
maverick style it's gone sad day I like
that ring except it wasn't actually
that's one of the rings I bought like
for real-life stuff not the music video
so we just don't go fabulo game I'm
still gonna entertain y'all let's go
back down the cool bus okay locate that
is the law if you're not a part of the
low game make sure to subscribe to the
strongest family on YouTube also get
your maverick our slogan ball back on /
shopper link in description but no way
too much Gucci today $12,000 worth be a
maverick we are changing the world every
single day join the revolution or get
dumped got a little aggressive just get
out the way please if you don't join us
look gang I love you I'll see you
tomorrow
[Music]