okay I spent $14,000 on the contents of
this box so I could make history it is
another good day here in Logan Park
today we are flying to Nashville you're
actually chasing the great American
solar eclipse which is happening
tomorrow but yo
I looked out I didn't
back up back up like calm down I'm gonna
put him down okay cause I got it okay so
one morning good morning
we're out of any agenda guys on the why
don't we boy they are still shooting
their music video today actually
supposed to be drinking that yeah yeah I
wish we should go to that mellow games
heavy today I'm sorry I have to go pee
interrupt I say it all the time Rolo
gang goes hard on understanding that
people usually what did you have oh my
god this is amazing I have it this is
this is actually awesome that's really
cool pretty cool in that here I'm really
late we're just going to it everyone's
doing good just showing up all hours
late you guys I'm actually only
co-directing this as you know the real
director of the stadium bro hi are you
holding down the fort bravo who talk to
that because I haven't been here yeah I
wanted to be here but this load oh no I
got an eclipse to watch Eli's dead no
come ok this go call action please oh
I'm an action and action hire action
accurate nobody's doing anything bro
this is just like we got an eclipse to
catch bro like you know how this I think
we can I have a move to just arrest you
are a man join our see you tomorrow I
don't know why I said tomorrow we're
going to be in Tennessee tomorrow yes
thanks to watch baby higher ball they're
already ready to go
and with the roll is my CEO oh okay okay
so this is what a couple people chase
and solar eclipse looks like what's up
dude
I thought never mind we got our stuff
this is for I don't actually don't know
that's for to know the volume we've done
the music on the radio the music off the
radio so I'm going to copyright strike
here I'll just do it obviously guys
there's a lot of stuff that goes into
actually shooting the eclipse I'm no
scientist in fact I'm just a ChaCha
vlogger from Ojai what we did a little
bit of research and we know we need
whatever the that is and also a big
big lint this lens we're using right now
like Brendan show how far zooms that's
not enough to capture the Sun we're
actually going to the camera store right
now before the airport we are gonna get
just a big cougar see like long dead
just like what in just a lens
risa barely underestimate how big this
oh I'll just wait dude I do pro-q like
you could you can carry it I thought I
told you about that no fortune thousand
dollars this is no one's gonna document
this eclipse better than I'm excited
probably we could make history this
could be mean drugs this contingent I
just know this is work by the way guys
asking this guy to like stay here and
wait for us was the hardest thing to
like communicate hi yeah it really
talked along is a weird dog like a bit
like what dog likes this I don't even
know what I'm doing
he loves it I don't know this Kong is
registered actually as a service dog I
don't know we got that because I don't
really have like many problems besides
the fact that my ego is too big I'm
colorblind I have flat feet my vision
horrible I suck at geography and I'm
just an overall sure it's good because
we can take it one place it's efficient
lots of services dog cause named Kong
the set yo just remember Taylor put Kong
just average guys it's not calling the
savages tonk dumb SAP ill you just
this is tough bro thing is frickin heavy
doing vascular bro freakin don't try
something I don't think you guys know
for some reason whenever at the airport
I think it's knobby I get stopped every
time with the TSA and they have to check
my car what do you think they stop you
every time of it Hobbit is like I'm with
dwarf something I've been city things
made out of ants stop goes and doesn't
want me to tell you guys this but
dwarves are actually all made in a lab
oh yes okay I actually take back
everything I said Evans right there in
the clear my man Brandon what did you do
tried to bring school supplies why are
you bringing a protractor though I got
to draw a circle on this Oh for our
scientific solar eclipse video they were
making that yeah it actually makes sense
but I personally have choked and died on
a pro track they really sucked dude I
had to bring myself back to life and
just blah blah blah that's a vlog for
another day feeling at the airport on
the floor eating a burrito man Evan over
here has a dry bagel not telling it's
good it's good real high society stuff
huh no we got a delay how many other
people are going to the Eclipse are you
going to be Eclipse Emma can history
guess it just gives me more time to eat
my burrito on a regretting buying unit
Rolex bro like I should have spent the
money on a private jet
so we don't have to deal with this I
don't know how you'd buy a private jet
that's $20,000 he's right he's right you
know what I regret buying a house
because I could use that money to buy a
private jet
yeah we won't have a place to live more
kick last time we gonna bump
I'm sorry yo he's there you're talking
to the other side I'm sorry he's sort of
thinking about a good service to talk
you're an animal con just what be
servicing me not fighting me yeah
Tennessee here we come a first hold this
oh oh hey I'm sorry
the $14,000 $14,000 and of it is he's
doing alright oh thank trendy - you guys
ready - good videographer solid I mean
you gotta go we need we do not have it
come on nice he gave us go for $2,000
please be there by the end of the flight
you gonna watch the hood yeah
cool the contact come here calm down hi
puppy how you doing down there in a
savage I like that about you I named him
Congress Avenue stand up there we go oh
yeah oh yeah yeah put them under the kid
that can't touch the crown that's simply
that makes expense sense yeah I know it
makes sense don't like talk he doesn't
want to betray his dwarfism guys it's
just a dedicated kid right here that
don't see dedication thought it was
funny I bet Evan thinks you look so cool
you know hey yeah a giant dolphin yeah
cuz you know how to wear a hat for too
long and try to get a headache and acne
rosewater hemorrhage and naturally all
no they're not good at sitting down for
our dump like a like a chicken meadow
our destination which actually I should
explain a little bit how I do that I
wanted to say I think I made a mistake
I forget that like I have followers I'm
not even kidding
yeah a million of them I got I got I got
ten million on YouTube bro I got like 16
on Facebook I got like 13 on 9s job
working in this room now
oh yes 14 it doesn't matter the point is
stuff I think I tweeted like that that
I'm coming here and I don't want to like
cocky but I think like the low gang is
like over there yeah you didn't say it
in the last ball there you come to
national anything either I made a
mistake
let's just go showed up to the location
[Music]
it's $40,000 because they give me this
play yes that's my boy right there
dude the Logan goes hard but the father
sick huh
[Applause]
[Music]
you love the looking hello gang but
you're my Ober job is the savage but
what you're saying about over bro
over everywhere over everywhere okay
also made sure we prepared for the solar
eclipse no they got us the glass no
crazy this is the one thing that we
didn't bring like yeah yeah cuz Lydia
Lydia is in order that in common time I
ordered that make sense I don't know
what her deal is guys I really like okay
I freaking love you man
and and woman and anything in between I
love doing okay okay so as most of my
vlogs where I travel to go see cool and
unique thing we are kind of like in the
middle of nowhere
the place called Lebanon Tennessee so
it's about thirty minutes outside
Nashville and I can explain why I'm here
it's actually actually someone from the
low gang reached out to me about six
months ago okay we're here this guy's
name is Colby he reached out to me like
I said about six months ago guys hotels
have been both Airbnb s have been booked
for like years and I'm not even kidding
I heard everything in Nashville in like
areas where the eclipse is going over
hings have been booked for like
literally like two years because this is
happening once in our lifetime I don't
even I think the last eclipse happened
in America I'm like 1918 my parents
haven't seen their parents haven't seen
a week came
[Music]
don't forget what it's like being like a
small like urban like neighborhood
anyways this kid's name is Colby and
he's letting us into his how bad idea
Colby never been to someone's house at
2:00 a.m. and Nash also broke grind
dude's a cry
is that gonna be a problem
no let's not do that Roley though I
teach them Kobe no way it is late you
reached out to me right and then okay
you go you toast okay pretty much what
happened I got this crazy idea one night
on the floor something that's about to
happen gonna be once in a lifetime for
possibly for us for everyone okay now
look look do what better way to do it is
hitting on bully Logan oh and making
this happen straight up sure I tweeted
at Logan I would like bro got this thing
coming up I got an event I think that
this really could be something special
you know because like I guys I love
space like I look like I heard about
this eclipse and I heard everything was
booked us like no and then he reached
out to me I was like yes yeah dude it
worked out so sweet like literally I got
a random text and I was like there's no
way there's no way that's happening it
just happened so fast and dude like it
was wild it really was one of all the
things ever happen that was a real
maverick move on your part was oh that's
all the power I like that feels good to
be like in a homer game LA it's like you
guys notice we just have been living in
apartments and stuff and just like kind
of bought a house but we haven't moved
in yet so this is nice also your accent
is amazing
ahead girl right up from your ex in your
act that's amazing Brandi no I'm not
even kidding I'm lose my being in like a
house like a home is like we're broke
what I'll send a list about it's
actually dark outside dude in the city
there's always lights and stuff
that's crazy things the doors name
tapping her name's Stephanie my dog's
name is taffy boy yeah it's actually
called so we've invaded Kobe top spot to
upload some footage cons up there is
chilling video something's making me so
happy right now cold what you got
although it's not real sells upward not
true man's got a piece below it thank
you bro seriously guys there's nothing I
love more than Pizza except maybe my
brother Jake Paul I'm just kidding ruff
Facebook what are you doing
oh I just just thought we don't really
do like paper plates like given really
the last time I seen a paper I don't
even remember seeing like to have any
like ceramic plates or something yeah
let me let me go check real quick I'll
burn a sidebar my Colby's dumper I
really want to see the Eclipse but if my
man doesn't have ceramic plate say we
got a ditch really can't do I can't do
this place but I commit me to you
different place but I'm doing it I
bikinis can you demonstrate why we just
got we're salty about paper plate -
Colby watches right you see this cow
it's still in one piece per yeah math
but it's okay dude I'm I'm not going to
complain that's my porridge I'm lucky I
even have plates
there are kids there are kids in Africa
the kids all the world a little bit the
peace of God bro you know what I'm
watching right now this one's weird no
this is this is dope this man is
definitely a maverick title of this
video is saying Logan Paul a hundred
thousand times so I see this right and
I'm like [ __ ] I had a video 17 hours
long this no there's no no way no way
sister for 17 hours it says my name your
way into generating into not even Joey
bishop a jibbers - bro that's eight
hours in brothers that's like only $1
$15 in the theater sounds like yo what
is in my life bro this is crazy you
gotta see you hit a hundred thousand
look he's about to hit it
simple silver ball be an average
different that's my boy out in the
survey Logan Paul calm you know what a
legend holy what is his YouTube channel
but I'm giving you a shout out dog this
makes so much sense his channel is
called mr. B's guys that that dude he's
a please appreciate that mush plug i
like that like the maverick plug my man
is a savage room this is a video of kids
singing the fallen jake paul on stage Oh
what are you doing I don't know this in
here anyways kids pretty good listen
listen this is pretty is pretty fun is
not I do not know honey right you've got
me like 10 years old and shut up got a
me with you he'll would look anyway like
a champion it is he's a maverick real
last thing last thing I want to bring up
guys no big boy is a head honcho you
guys Logan I spent 14 thousand dollars
on the contents of this box so I could
make history holla seen it but you'll
ever check this out oh yo you do it like
this is what we're doing Colby but do
the thing is human just you give it up
and we'll cabro your eclipses straight
up gonna go on this yeah listen before
yeah there you go ahead done job man
take a photo of me and Colby oh my god
he's talking to Hong Kong no this is no
joke guys fourteen thousand dollars
anyways guys getting it very clear that
we legitimately are probably going to
make history with tomorrow's rule on
history like this is something when I'm
80 years old because it's eclipse I
guess that is never happening again in
our lifetime use your Logan eighty year
old Logan Bros this one's for you man
this is this is over do it for anyways
guys if you're not a part of the Loghain
obviously you can see it were just
latest food so just subscribe and it's a
maverick merch the link for that is in
the description you'll go out be unique
be passionate be different so k2 break
outside of whatever bubble you're living
in if you're living in a bubble maybe
I'm assuming
maybe I'm being an [ __ ] I don't know
it's late low gang I love you all and I
will see you tomorrow Coby thanks again
bro take these campus
[Music]
are you too much