I flew all the way from LA to Toronto
Canada surprise my roommate Evan here
the dwarf world games it's a good day as
usual I'm smiling I'm feeling good good
morning Lydia Lydia Liz thanks for the
enthusiasm good morning to you
my manse is looking like a star with
that new youth merch in the Maverick
house how you been huh it's not real
loving thanks for reminding me bro the
Maverick Yeti backpackers just drop oh
my god - fire - fire - fire - be honest
guys they might even be sold out by this
time it dropped it yesterday and we do
only have a limited supply these things
are expensive they're hard to make but
that's what it's about bro it's the
maverick movement either get on the
trailer also just dropped our
back-to-school line so like pencil
pouches
hey go Lydia for your pencils yeah [ __ ]
papa guys look at Paul's like I'm slash
shop or link in description also can I
just kind of just say one more thing the
logging is the fastest-growing and
strongest family on YouTube so strong do
I got some little gangsters across the
way what up G what up hi hi are you the
dad are you my mom I can't tell from
this angle but you know what they don't
have merch ah let me help them how about
that new what's bad yeah it's good stuff
man I I just passed my brother Jake Paul
and subscribers I want to give a quick
shout-out to my mom for birthing me I
appreciate you and respect you for that
mom cuz I don't think I could have done
it myself okay
oh we're Milo gang yeah yeah oh dang
that was really loud and it's okay I'm
running maybe that's why they want to
kick me out of here yeah don't forget
guys I'm currently homeless it's true
the man is trying to suppress the map
you can't do it I'm just I'm just a kid
do I need to look into buying a house I
need to look into it I don't even know
what else man I'm not an adult but I do
know one thing and that is it's time for
your boy to get swole I'm at the gym
with my boy Sebastian hi how are you
how's it going
gonna work on my beach pot so the girls
can go Logan I like you for you and now
you're following
[Music]
good morning ma'am yeah yeah I guess
you're right there that makes sense
that's funny you mention that actually
I'm actually about to go drop your Yeti
off to get fixed you guys remember the
car accident that I had yeah some lady
hit me I'm hoping her insurance will
cover it
okay see you later what you guys know me
I got a little something planned this is
not gonna be some like regular old
g-wagen I'm gonna get you fixed soon
okay this is the last time you'll look
like a busty ass side chick hang in
there baby we're almost there just wanna
take that little g-wagen to put some you
smart shot ah yep I think we're almost
there guys I'm clearly losing my mind
yes call me a Papa okay squad we are
here Platinum Motorsports wait
I'm sitting here and I look to my left I
see another youth g-wagen but across the
way yo easy down boy down look dude is
that another unity right now
oh we got ourselves the problem job are
you good but y'all check us out this
must be like the G Wagen Factory you got
one here you got one here always come
prepared with a youth March for the
youth G Wagen say go bro okay cool hey
guys it's me Logan Paul back on the
voice-over so this is me chillin with
guy talking about the stuff we're gonna
have done by car right now we're talking
about all the cool things that were
gonna have done to the yeti eyes my
plans for this thing are incredible the
only thing that's gonna be the same as
the paint I cannot wait to show you guys
but the time had to come how do you pull
me my keys it was a little sad it was a
little awkward but anyways back to the
vlogs kind of sad man seeing my yeti go
but I know it's for the better okay
we're sitting in the back of this uber
here talking about how basic jack is so
just like a ride right off the bat first
glance let's start with the green teas
from Starbucks like that's numero uno
basic Oh
number two look at these sunglasses like
that's that's oh come on you had me yeah
cuz I'm a guy and I love red man and
then I think just the thing that takes
the cake for me is the hoop earrings
that if you guys noticed she's been
wearing for the past week the bigger the
hoop the bigger the hoe oh my god
chokers hoop Starbucks ray-bans basic yo
we are in West Hollywood right whoa
we're in West Hollywood
chillax
we are in West Hollywood right now on my
brother's side of town if you guys
remember in yesterday's vlog Jake did
not let me move in with him
y'all know you can't stay here first off
screw you jack second off I figured
since he's also getting kicked out when
he has to move I'm gonna get my boy like
a little parting gift here's the thing
this is also gonna be like a
housewarming gift
that was weird got to be thoughtful it's
got to say I love you bro it's got to
say I just passed you and subscribers
etc like look the smokey bacon ketchup
says that I think just kidding guys I'm
not good at being doing this Jack help a
picture yeah I was gonna cut Jack's
yeah out cause it's like really annoying
but like that just again shows how basic
you got the goods we were posted up
outside like homeless people since I
don't have a car we got this picture
frame I think I have a pretty good idea
of what I want to put in it I also got a
ham a succulent cuz I actually don't
have a reason so without further ado
let's get a wrap it I didn't bring
scissors so this is this is not gonna
look that good I got this put the
succulent in put some youth merch in
there we just wrap it up wrap it up see
how much I care about you Jake you're
the best brother I've ever had
[Applause]
you guys are crazy Jake Paul is the
crazy okay okay I love it I love it you
guys are crazy my brother Paul I came
over broke because I know you're getting
kicked out and I'm getting kicked out
I'm not getting kicked out what I'm not
getting kicked out job we're making the
decision of you must be nice got you a
gift this is from me in the neighbors
Jake oh boy
Logan from the neighbors I also got some
more stuff it dropped out with popping
it it's issues merge - just drop it
looking Paul that cop / shot officer
gotta do something else something you
guys
oh it's a mini it's a cacti no it's a
succulent they're called do you like it
no I noticed something about Libya over
there Millia do you eat food or drink
let me eat food like I'm the most
birthday boy it's a Saturday guys you
saw I'm just sitting inside trying to
get work done across the way these every
weekend man like do you even grind oh
yeah I got this stuff but to shut it
down party's over hooligans
[Applause]
okay cool
I think that's handle 12 seconds later
what what's going on nothing bro you you
good yeah I'm good bro
yeah we're just talking to Evan about
the stock market um anyways no I'm not
gonna lie I miss him bro like I miss the
guy I can't be the only one bro like do
you miss him
yeah maverick what do you think brother
what yeah you do you do he does if he's
nodding okay guys I I imagine the low
gang you guys also miss Evans may
actually why don't we just go ask them
boy with a low-key winner
that we machen is knowing you are you
useful video we gotta you
[Applause]
Sebastian bro quick sidebar quick
sidebar I was doing my schedule is clear
tomorrow like attitude technically I
could go to Canada I could visit Evan in
Canada are you down dude I can't go I'll
never pass no bro you don't have your
passport to go I got the blog if I if I
if I went to Canada tonight to go visit
Evan would you guys do you guys support
that I think I need to go book my flight
seeing that kids break a plate name you
realize I don't think I've broken one
today anyway the Canada oh I'm doing it
is that too soon I know sorry
you don't need to bring it up right it's
all right cuz I'm gonna be at the next
door for all convinced dwarf dwarf we
don't say you like add the W it's not
Dorf
it's dwarf yeah guys evan is in Toronto
for the dwarf world games as you know
super athletic dwarf so that means
there's gonna be a lot of other dwarves
there too like this is this is gonna be
fine
holy Sh oh my gosh you know what I just
realized I met Evan at the for the first
time at the dwarf world game I swear to
god bro and guys you remember I was big
on a vine and we made this vine which
you might have seen yo that was like the
first vine that I was like damn anyways
this is gonna be fun grow things I'm
packing we got that youth merch boxers
socks hoodies pants and fake Kong just
kidding we don't need you think on one
thing I still need is the videographer
because apparently Sebastian is an
illegal alien that's definitely not your
okay also yo Evan just texted me I think
he is at nine
ninety-nine thousand followers on
Instagram meaning I'm going to surprise
him like as he hits a million on
Instagram dogs or aligning brothers oh
okay
looks good heat level hi yeah yeah I'm
dating me Lydia give me the good we got
a ticket that was large I do have one
guys it is 9:00 p.m. at night I'm headed
to the airport right now I kind of
forgot exactly how far Toronto was from
Los Angeles it's another country I'm
crossing a border so if you guys look at
this map here Los Angeles is a very very
very very very very very very far from
Toronto yeah that's a good six to seven
hour flight through the night okay also
I am meeting a videographer there by the
name of Kevin shubra last minute so
we're just gonna be at the gate but
Kevin is actually the one who shoots and
edits all the product stuff for our
maverick merch needless to say homies a
Chevy come on you saved my ass bro no
like I said I get asked and it broke
wait hold up by the way where are you
from I don't even think I know I'm from
Alaska
no is it accurate that you're polish I'm
learning but do you know what we're
getting into like we are gonna be with
the world's coolest Dwarfs ever I had no
idea that we gonna do it were there or
meeting them no I'm gonna have to put
subtitles in music oh my god he didn't I
didn't tell him we were going to the
dwarf world game that should be fun but
my boy Evan here we come heaven bro I
never want to hear you say I'm a bad
roommate again literally like I'm taking
a red-eye to Canada I don't even know
how I'm upload this footage but I'm
established oh I'm gonna do it no I feel
like I'm on an alien playing okay these
seats this is El Pollo Loco I kind of
like it though I kind of like it okay
before I piss everyone on this plane off
Toronto I will see you see ya I have
made it to Canada guys it's 5:00 in the
morning
Oh which means it's like to LA time
which means it's like to attend a
fricking Club and also how long till I
get kicked out a candidate for being too
loud we have an hour drive to our hotel
the same hotel that Evan is staying at
which point I will jump on him and wake
his little ass off here I come okay that
was quick ish
this guy how are we gonna do this my
friend Evan is competing okay do you
know what room he's in hey guys Logan
here obviously I'm gonna keep having
room number private but yeah I'm gonna
back of the wall this is it you guys the
moment of truth I flew all the way from
Toronto Canada [ __ ] I flew all the way
from LA to Toronto Canada surprised my
roommate Evan here the world games it's
a four-year university no since the day
we met no I know that
holy [ __ ] August 6 growing 2013 we met
at the dwarf World Games four years ago
oh one more thing
no other pump no Danny oh all this
bromance is too real this is too real my
Kevin bro just for old times sake bro
can you make your your fake haven't
faced can you yeah it's good to see you
bro hombre Danny watch me compete in
these sports yo yeah the door for days
oh we already saw some doors do the
coolest room we are I know right dude
you boys are happy people you guys could
learn his lesson move Dwarfs okay guys
that's the vlog I'm actually gonna start
tomorrow's vlog in like an hour if
you're not a part of the loading make
sure you subscribe we are the fastest
growing channel on YouTube also get your
mavar Mirchi for Dyson in the lake for
that is in the description bar local
ball nikon / shop don't you move my man
seriously it's a revolution in our
family's growing growing growing I love
y'all and I will see you tomorrow take
it is that
wait a second Kevin did Oh it's for guys
it's Kevin's birthday yeah let me just I
got it
also just met a little gangster what did
you what did you say if you have a door