[Music]
my name is Logan Paul and I have a
serious problem
I'm not talking about my inflated ego or
my micropenis or my little brother my
problem is I can't stop buying dogs
that's it dude things are happening
right now we I think I'm in a puppy face
by the way you guys my mom's in town
there she is you're so sweet mom by the
way I love you driving the yeah you look
in your element right now no way I got
eaten by a coyote and something about
that situation made me want to do two
things one to get get more dogs and just
make sure they grow up to live a full
healthy life without having to worry
about being eaten by a [ __ ] apex
predator what's it makes a predator apex
she's got a massive thing though ever
since I was in high school there was
this one dog that I always loved it
looked like a skin lying over dog it's
called the Tibetan Mastiff like look at
this thing it's an apex predator got a
bigger dick than all of us maybe not my
mom but yeah otherwise I agree with but
anyways there's this breeder who
apparently has like champion Tibetan
Mastiff a champion of my dogs are
champions browse subscribe button we may
or may not be getting another member of
the family today I don't know turn the
low gang because we are growing every
single day mom I have a question for you
were driving so slow why because look at
this wrong I'll take over from here
this is the path we go down to get
murdered no boy he's a bettin Mastiff
Jiraiya
I think we're in the wrong place Oh that
was a horse this dog is a big dog it
could be both what are the chances that
one animal eats a dog of mine well these
dogs are dogs you know I'm saying
like boiled balanced and when you put it
like that oh my yo he's actually pretty
dope if there's one dog I could hunt and
kill coyotes yeah well they don't even
come the Coyotes don't come close this
is his wife he only likes her all the
other girls he's like he's the exact
opposite of me it's cool great great but
uh look at that we got room for that all
night long
keeping away the Coyotes sounding the
alarm it sure contect silence was deadly
she carry a firearm this is the dog that
says let you leave and just let me guard
oh my god upside-down what incredible
truth
about that look right there can I get a
sec to speak with my colleague you can
speak with the colleague yep she's
sitting over there that would good
meeting it's a big dog I'm a big dog a
pig you have a small puppy penis head
turtle a parrot a penis and a penis
house and you give her back if it
doesn't work out you had a chance to
give Jake back and you didn't and that
didn't work out that's the face that's
leg about two just do it okay hey you
think it's a bad idea Spencer doesn't
seem on board I'm not gonna do it oh my
god hi girls okay she is so cuddly
[Music]
Oh God
my heart is so pretty
rubber face is priceless I can't get
over this animal
[Music]
oh my god yeah everywhere oh my god it
was so silent it was no warning I was so
close to catching it I was rolling on
the paper towels they're just wet hey
guys I'm starting to think we made the
right decision
[Music]
the good news is actually doesn't shed
that much no problem no problem
oh my god what have I done
[Music]
I did not know a dog could drool this
man this is insane I'm not even kidding
oh my god you go swimming girl oh she's
looking at me all sad
I don't know dude is there something in
that vehicle that I'm not human I know
Logan another animal it's probably a
duck probably a goose could be a
rhinoceros a teddy bear is it a puppy
that it's just oh I told you mate in the
cracks yeah oh that's great it's good
because the dog this big probably
shouldn't be crazy aggressive yeah you
say that would throw up on your ass I
promise I'll take care of you okay
what's the return policy they say we
already looks like he's drooling already
he's five months old can you imagine the
size of the ships can you imagine the
size of the friendship that's what I
said the ship like cannon Jake hey
should we uh should we introduce to
debroglie I really hope they get along
cuz they're gonna be brother and sister
or potentially make whoo imagine they
breathe the Husky Mastiff off offspring
what a dog oh it's been good knowing you
buddy
I always did like you
okay guys hey it's all good so bro Lee
is three months
this dog is five months and you can tell
there's an extreme size difference okay
I'm rolling calm down calm down
I just don't want hurt like snapping you
don't saying because you know she snaps
and it's over I'm glad they're gonna get
to grow up together because otherwise
I'm not sure this would work
no play time here we go I think he's
done as some of you know I'm inserting
the the World Championship Russian slap
boxing competition my mom is not a fan
but we've been practicing right because
I'm used to punching and boxing and
obviously slapping is different like
these guys are wild they beat the SH
each other so we've been trying to
master how hard I hit figure out which
way is the most effective to my hand
it's the morning after we got the
Tibetan Mastiff and I try to bring her
back in the backyard and she just she's
been having some problems she's just
really scared you see her she's
terrified MA she I played a logic song
she ran away
she looks so majestic and terrified poor
girl I put a crate next to my bed and
everything was fine last night and even
this morning she was all that cuddly and
stuff but I bet she's having like
separation anxiety from her family if I
had to guess it's okay it's okay oh my
god I promise I'm not gonna let anything
happen to your okay girl it's okay oh my
god this is definitely a thing I don't
even know what to do right now I'll come
back there with you okay hey we can do
this together
hi hi girl you want to hide I with you
that's no problem we can do that oh my
god this is ridiculous right now
I looking I'm gonna try to chill here
for a little bit and calm her down and
then and we're gonna revisit this in a
little bit close well I think she has an
extra toe see this oh yeah brothers
tooth there's two toes here her normal
paw here and then there's two talons or
two like little thumb toasters bro what
the [ __ ] we got a mutant dog got 12 toes
bro this is the craziest thing what he's
so sad you got too many toes can't find
a pair of shoes that fixed it's gonna be
okay oh my god I can't believe she's a
puppy holy she's just like a little
floppy dude though dog she gets scared
of noises and she heard a noise
yesterday she ran through the music
studio and got like caught in a corridor
some [ __ ] was connected to a piano and
dragged the piano through the yard this
is the type of problems you haven't you
get big dollars it's perfect you
recognize this pianos is your
responsibility I can't wait to see what
else goes wrong with this dog tell them
we got a dinosaur coming in uh come on
man - see here I'm gonna try thing she
ways especially 70 80 pounds 32 pounds
so she's not even halfway done growing
up with a name for her her name is
ginger the giant because she's a ginger
dog and she's a giant that looks just
like Broly like she's just a giant dildo
dog she's just super floppy
let's ginger ginger the giant what's
your fur so we wanted to make sure just
like with Broly that everything was okay
figure out why she's got extra toes or
something extra toes that is genetic
right so the only bad thing about it is
they don't hit the ground so don't wear
the claw down they can actually grow
like a ram's horn and go right back into
beautiful I'm not doing my dog will not
participate I can't I just like collect
boot from my ass another choice that I
will get you poop keep your fingers away
from my dogs you remember when I hit my
head and the doctor was like and I
jumped across the bed knows like what
though he put his glove it was a classic
like Oh even worse so like I was
literally just like blocked I was like
this is Doc's turnaround finger popping
[ __ ] and I'm the victim
[Music]
healthy dog and a new member of the
family low gang meet ginger the giant 70
pound red Tibetan Mastiff was going to
double in size hence ginger the giant
hit her up on the gram also hit that
subscribe button the low Gang Gang Gang
yeah guys I freaking love you I'm done
buying dogs by the way I'm done I
promise I might get another pig though
don't forget guys we're going to Russia
in like eight days or so to enter the
World Championship Russian slap contest
big things are happening low game I
freaking love you guys and I'll see you
next time take it easy
look there's lettuce in there how'd you
smell it
[Applause]
[Music]