I just found out that maverick died my
parrot the iconic maverick the para died
got pinkeye from my disgusting dogs my
canines and have to do an entire media
day in New York and I'm two days out
from throwing the biggest event of the
century the Challenger games and I pull
my [ __ ] hamstring I pulled my
hamstring guarding Snoop Dogg of all
people Snoop Dogg in a charity
basketball game I shouldn't have even
been playing I look like a
double-jointed silverback albino gorilla
in high school my football coach he'd
come up to me say Logan you're the most
unathletic athletic kid I've ever seen
in my life and while he was indeed right
let's be honest like q coach Campos and
what the new dog I mean what's really
good who knew this man's was so long and
lengthy his arms are so long he's in
nine places at once it's like guarding a
giant octopus but I digress the point is
listen you guys all know the Challenger
game so this weekend July 27 Saturday
Long Beach California by the way if you
haven't gotten your tickets yet please
do so it's gonna be wild the link is in
the description and if you can't make it
it's gonna be live streamed with a
donation link the charity we're gonna be
donating to is actually the Special
Olympics we just confirm Big Ups good
job team so please plan on donating some
money or asking your parents to donate
some money do a good deed so you don't
go to hell but yeah 100 100 athletes
gonna be racing including I have a list
here summer I can match destroying Logan
Paul's brother model Roz laurdiy awesome
mcbroom Brent Rivera Bradley Martin face
censor face rub [ __ ] Jeff with tech
Dylan Efron 20 my grind Garcia Vitaly
Rice gum alex wasabi and us just load
more and here I am working hard like I
when I was in Sweden this past two weeks
I'm training I'm working my ass off
[Music]
so then I get back from Sweden I'm a
good shape I'm feeling great and somehow
magically none other than Jake Paul is
at my house to put a curse on me what
are you doing here here's my proposition
it's good guy here's my proposition to
you since I snap my ankle I don't think
you should be able to train any further
and run sprints to make it a fair fair
race bro is funny to me cuz you actually
think you're my only competition bro
you're like your bottom of the totem
pole who I'm worried about I'm worried
about King badge I'm worried about
destroying table Jews though I'm weird
about Austin broom you weren't even on
the radar guy there's no what I'm saying
you have underestimated me so many times
in our life it's true and not only do I
prove you wrong every single time do i
you in the ass that's true no it's not
true okay then I got that cutter every
single time excuse that what you send
yourself stag yeah I was good the end of
being youtuber I'm 50 no no no I'm also
undefeated I'll have you know only - OH
- I'm the only winning youtuber I'm 15%
more man than you yes I a sperm count is
high it doesn't matter I have 15% more
of a ballsack than you do no means I
have 19% more of a man how confident are
you put your money where your mouth is
I'm the least worried about you dude
okay you really think that they're
faster than both of us who knows but
I've heard 100k down and I'm not willing
to take down hey boom literally the next
day I [ __ ] myself playing basketball I
told myself I was gonna go easy and I
didn't can you imagine having to go to
the sidelines and tell your coach who
happens to be 2 Chainz
that's you're the one guy that pulled a
hamstring at a charity basketball game
excuse me coach 2 Chainz I pulled my
hamstring you got a big booty sore call
it big boy no please mr. Chainz I mean
look back at it
horrifying right so now what I knew it
happened I knew what happened as soon as
I did it
then randomly Tiana Taylor's friend
Heron civils getting in a fistfight with
my German videographer David this was
odd this was way odd and then I think
like three days later Heron Sybil she
posted on her Instagram story ten signs
of maturity and oddly and ironically
enough number nine was you sometimes
prefer to be silent than to engage in a
nonsense fight slightly hypocritical but
that's none of my business David I'm so
sorry I couldn't help you I was
immobilized you're a good kid anyways
the basketball game ends I hate myself
for playing and the next morning you
guessed it I go straight to sports rehab
hey Pat okay cuz it does oh my god oh my
god I called it yeah you did I called it
I was like yo you're you are going to
get injured playing basketball right now
it's new dog the reason you pulled your
hamstring ya know it was a combination
of Snoop Dogg and Floyd Mayweather damn
bro Oh Oh what you gonna do run after me
it just keeps getting better and better
for the past week I've been going to
sports rehab every single day trying to
get this hamstring right to my
competitors this is your chance now's
your time go to the track now this is
where you can get that leg up cuz I
haven't been training I'm literally
gonna be going into the Challenger Games
having rolled out of bed but yeah after
a bunch of therapy cryogenic weird cups
on fire lots of ultrasound shock therapy
inflatable legs all knives are scraping
me and a collection of weird guttural
noises
I do feel a little bit better now the
golden question the big boy the thick
bit will I Pogan lo be competing in the
Challenger games this Saturday gets your
tickets no yes I think so yeah I will
even if I have to crawl across that
finish line I'm gonna do it so you
better not miss it okay I'm willing to
blow out my [ __ ] leg for you guys I
don't give a [ __ ] when I was in New York
I doubled down on Fox Business I changed
it from fastest youtuber on the planet
to just I went with fastest man on the
planet
I'm betting $100,000 and I'm the fastest
man on the planet I'm the fastest man on
the planet I mean what am i [ __ ]
stupid or just high and that was knowing
I couldn't even run but guess what guys
I'm still not scared of you Jake or
Bradley Martin or King - I will forever
be the fastest youtuber on this goddamn
planet hunter k bro
hundred thousand dollars I will see you
slowpokes
this Saturday like in sub scribe the
challenger games presented by halogen
the celebrity charity track and field
event of the year ticket lincoln bio
stream live on youtube i braum