I don't have a thumbnail Brona or
clickbait we should definitely do
something with this bed you guys I am
tired
let me try this again here we go that
took energy here's why I am tired guys
hey guys to me lug and it is a 7:39
right now I literally spent the whole
night shooting valley girl may have seen
it on my Instagram can you just calm
down for one second please I'm just
vlogging sitting on a second you may
have seen it on my Instagram story at
Logan Paul if you want to follow me
there but the point is you boys tired
okay so I'm gonna sleep for like two
hours and then back to the president we
go and now we're here and like I'm
literally seeing double this is but we
do have work to do I need to get to work
what do you do what are you doing and
what are you wearing what have you done
Logan sugar Jake Paul strip and I'm
urgently going my god no first off this
shirt obviously much better than this
one I don't appreciate them being paired
together there is actually this oddly
enough who does remind me I think new
merch is dropping today yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah by the time you're watching
this volume merch will have dropped oh I
think I'm getting samples later so you
guys can see what we're actually dealing
with but don't bro the link in the
description for that good morning I look
as beautiful as ever
Oh anyways can you give my dad some real
merch my boy needs help
classic maverick hoodie in the
subscription or the buy or something
Jesus mother and God yo this is why you
can't YouTube you know this yeah so you
don't know this I gotta be over here oh
yeah that's much better
alright I gotta go bye gram or nning you
sexy son of a [ __ ] can you unlock the
car you're like oh okay low gang so
here's what is happening on two hours of
sleep reassess forgive me if I'm not a
hundred percent there just yeah I am
making a surprise appearance at a big
YouTube event as far as I know there's
gonna be a a lot of people and B
I'm gonna say something onstage what do
you have to say to be honest I don't
know what do they want from you I've
been doing well on youtubes our family
the low gang has been blowing up and
we're like we're popping right now you
want to know why you're popping I don't
know but I could tell him I'd just be
like yo it's because we got the best
support system in the game and the low
gang is the strongest family on YouTube
boom so delicious oh damn bro you can
tell we're here they got water in this
place is that gonna tell you got water
Leila see the water you can't play in it
so I already did ha ha ha
God my jokes suck I need to get untied
yeah we're taking over Logan's camera
right now and he's literally about to
speak at the YouTube convention right
yeah we can't care we can't do Cameron
so unfortunately you guys don't get to
see this until later but um I mean you
guys know we didn't kill it I mean he's
wearing his maverick shirt like you know
be the best killer
[Applause]
[Music]
you did so good on your speech I gotta
ask you a question yeah tell me why did
you trust me say anything I could say
anything follow me on instagram at Logan
towel bro merch leaking items you broke
up a new merchant you did they run for
president I don't think it's a joke like
I think I'm going for president way
there's 2020 Olympics father I had 2032
president running Logan Paul is doing it
that was a dope thing talking in front
of people is always good push yourself
out of your comfort zone my daddy's
right here plugging a lot of merch this
bomb you have to we got to do oh I think
you're right you want to try the new
merch party I can make this happen
it's not what else do you know gang save
your money and literally plan on
spending it all on words I don't care
about my personal gain from this this is
dope you would be the coolest person
around wearing this Oh God oh oh you see
that bro oh man that is lit with the
July coming in a month you know we got
that American maverick bro
does it get any better than this the
answer my BS do you live in the USA do
you support the USA boom USA a maverick
Louisville next up this one could take
the cake bro
summertime tank top maverick America
long-sleeve action E's
never drop lurch like this like a long
sleeve like sweater maverick America
okay I'm done I'm done
I'm gonna wear this stuff throughout the
next month but yeah the fourth of July
March is in and it's women to the pocket
do not I have two decisions if you guys
remember yesterday's voice I'm gonna put
them on my mouth and kiss Ayla do I even
need to let you guys know that I'm on
set is first order of business hair
[Applause]
[Music]
girls move your crazy
oh do you you got water everywhere
you made a problem for everybody Chloe
it's on my pants and everybody I'd like
to say everything was it with the best
you heard like the rest Bennet admit
that was aggressive of her to throw
water on me I did have it come in
yesterday she went to go drink a bottle
and I squeezed it in her face anyway so
this girl is blue my eyes are blue are
we shooting valley girl or avatar
why are you blue are you acting an
avatar valley girl I forgot the shade
before I came to set by and I've gone
through puberty four times - my hair
grows like really fast where'd you go
you think I'm scared of you you think it
scared of anybody hold you up any are
you gonna turn me on I'm gonna major in
the feeling I'm gonna make you fall in
love with me and break your heart takes
two to tango Bennet she plays a
character named quake on on agents of
shield head you guys watch that show why
don't you use your super yesterday he's
like can I see you play I ate up a
cracker and I spit into Logan pan and
then he ate it it's - no cuz she didn't
think I was sad she's like she was like
trying to be cool and like she spit a
crack for my hands and then I went up
there and I just paid it that was the
first step of making anyone fall hey
what's that over there
but no Bennett said it I see my phone in
numb buns I see it Chloe I need it he's
do you do when the camera's not rolling
what is something the internet doesn't
know about you
there's a bit like they know a lot about
me what is something what I don't know
do you ever shave your nipples I don't
have that hairy of a Netflix you've
never saved this isn't the natural light
my hair phone got it got it got it so if
you guys didn't notice I've been like
kind of avoiding vlogging on set of this
movie I wanted to like you know warm up
and get to know the cat and not piss
people I told you this and I pissed
people off like vlogging and stuff as
you can imagine you're a traditional
actor a traditional director and then
this internet kid comes up with a vlog
camera he's like hey how's life do like
a lot it's been weird it really is do
but these girls kind of out weird me
dude I think I like it I think I love
you
Logan's gonna pour this sriracha in is
not for five seconds yeah 1 2 3 4 500
jury 1 2 3 4 5 you're good you're good
Oh down the hatch down the hatch
that was your idea guys she dared me
anything I would do it again I feel like
we're gonna bond in some weird way look
what you're doing
wait let me get the same one though I
don't know about us here I missed it I
don't know about this okay change it in
my wardrobe look at this they turn the
waterfall on bar there's people now in
the pool four more people so in this
scene I am actually jumping from off
right here and they have to cover the
camera with plastic obviously because
I'm a fat piece of otters gonna go
everywhere but also because of my beats
of my cannibals
oh the heat level is high up here it's
like the whole world is my oyster I can
see my house from here okay no more
foo-foo let's do this
[Applause]
not so fun fact about me I don't love
shitty and water without one let me tell
you guys something there's nothing like
hot cup of tea after a cannonball here
we go however this tea is not for me my
tea that is your - nope nope this is me
being a good cast mate are you in the
low gang are you the logic Chloe if you
want to be in it you just have to
subscribe and get your maverick merch
they're gonna get mad at you guys
Chloe of look she's not in the low gang
I don't like I can forgive you I just
don't know if they can should we go over
to the sex wing yoga swing school this
is the sex swing no clue we're all not
gonna actually this is why you're an
actor you're not a vlogger I got this
you guys there's ropes can you just let
me vlog for a second I don't know what
it's like this is a sex swing bed
there's ropes right here guys and the
bed swings whoa I mean I don't know how
to say this booze dumb smooth
like sick people vote went Logan's gonna
smash no hold on I don't have a
thumbnail bro or clickbait we should
definitely do something with this bed be
my clickbait Jesse yo give me a whole
wait isn't that a thumbnail right there
dude no no that's a nail are you gonna
ask me some questions okay Logan what's
the most rewarding part about being a
youtuber I want I want serious answer
shut up there not being cheesy or
whatever you guys are gonna think it's
cheesy yeah what it's legitimately to
people and I talked to it it's like just
like army of people we were like we
literally call ourselves a family
because it's insane how much I connect
with them and they connect them why do
you think people connect with you so
much cuz it's crazy I'm a maverick what
is the biggest sacrifice you've had to
make I think it's this like you even say
just putting the camera down like living
living a life I asked for a video camera
and like just inherently okay low gang
that is the BLA I know it's a bit of a
weird one today these night shoots man
like I'm gonna be here so like 7:00 a.m.
like it's literally 1 a.m. right now
they screw up my sleeping pattern my
vlog like the movie stop that's what it
takes bro and obviously I'm out here
doing the best I can for you guys but do
not forget numerous just drop man this
stuff is fire the link is in the
description get it now man be a maverick
rep this stuff today tomorrow a week
from now on the fourth of July whatever
you want well and subscribe if you're
not subscribed because like I said we
are popping right now on YouTube oh the
logging is fire I love you guys and I
will see you tomorrow I gotta go kill
this movie take it easy
I didn't I didn't know just now