I don't know I did not study last night
okay so here's the deal guys we are
three minutes away from the skydiving
center as you guys know I failed my test
last time I'm away how many was that
miss how many the questions are actually
so difficult which I guess makes sense
since you are risking your life and you
know jumping out of a plane damn son I
failed last time and I don't want it to
happen again because after we take the
test today we're gonna head over to
Coachella hey what is the biggest danger
to a jumper when flying a canopy pattern
oh I don't know back that you're jumping
on be provided with supplemental oxygen
I don't know Spencer be right back while
I go look Joppa - just drove like two
hours I'm gonna fail again you don't
even know what it's like so listen guys
if you're not a part of the low gang you
good make sure to subscribe hit that
subscribe button in the did you say that
yeah I don't know I just said it dude
because we're extremely late example
we're about to go jump out of a plane oh
my god if I pass the test and get my
license today my goal I want to jump out
of the plane naked because one of the
things when you get a license is you
don't you no longer have to wear a
jumpsuit arish longing they call it
perish longing a common term coined by
the swiss i dad about to take my
skydiving test again i so doing right
now I'm studying I got the manual right
here and I'm learning things
for a of what I'm a beast I've been
streaming bro and I'm going to go try
thanks for the advice dad now be right
back while I go learn Japanese twice oh
oh your point feels good I feel
knowledgeable I feel like imma take this
test i'ma go perish longing and then pop
to Coachella feeling good in my mavar
words baby I got the world how to Smurfs
on the game by the way y'all look at me
right quick a little pan up that yo
what's doing it baby love all that cops
last shop or link in the description you
guys know we just dropped a dare to fly
shirts we just got the hockey shirts
which are very appropriate for today and
do it again that's me
[Music]
it's just with the swiss thing yes yeah
me bro I could jump out of planes perish
longing dude haven't waited for this
moment since it came out my mom's vagine
that's a long time it's about 23 years
man so the Rolex is going on sure it's
coming it's the butt ass naked sander oh
you good if anybody has any sensitivity
to light please don't make direct eye
contact with my pale body I'm trying to
get tanner Coachella rose trying to get
a little Lobster II then turn into a
fresh little butter Chris you know what
I mean definitely know he's gonna be the
one filming uh trying to look like this
area need some pants here bro ever jump
has a license I'm [ __ ] baby fee
America
my
let you
in this town
in this town dude parish logging bucket
list check how was it bro dude I was in
the air and then I was falling and then
I was on the ground and now I'm here
that's very compelling yeah it was
pretty crazy oh the view is there okay
it definitely slowed me down was a lot
more drag than I would have liked I
would describe it as an utter flutter I
like that
alright guys no more games Spencer and I
got to go to Coachella to Palm Springs
if it is it Mike the dirt bike I've been
hooking in nude in the sky see this
thing this what all the kids wear out
super televised oh my god the amount of
basic here is gonna be so long and I'm
already getting high not because this is
a hoodie is cuz it's not it's merged in
the gay in the worldwide hood it was
this that's a stamp of approval
your boys an official a licensed
skydiver got it you got it
Wow Coachella is going great so far I'm
not gonna lie I didn't anticipate the
party being this crazy dang man that's
really great you know what speaking a
little too soon right once I get on my
cello outfit I think I'll be good to go
oh my god I look good
damn I feel basic but it's so good and
we got my boy max yeah all right guys
we're wasting no time the knighting
ceremony the 90 ceremony closes door oh
let's go
this is a very special moment some have
referred to these golden bands
the splendiferous of Marty McGraw this
here is an artist band oh how do you get
friends not easy if I do say so myself
let's start off with Logan under knees
please I'm gonna stand up but I do hear
endow the truth and all that is true
uh-huh thanks Mike let's go to a party
well it is one more thing we need to do
before we go
oh god I put nostril
hell yeah Uncle Joe already
our guys couch I was really looking up
this year so much fun so much dancing
alright guys that is the vlog I just
can't stop cuz how much I love Coachella
are you going to challenge no [ __ ] I'm
here
if you guys don't puzzle okay make sure
to subscribe run the Strongs Muslim
family on YouTube there we make parties
anywhere even if they suck ass huh look
happy may have emerged a heart it's
merch from the game a local ball I got
shot y'all know how it is all jokes
aside it is gonna get rowdy this weekend
with that fellow gang I love you I would
see you
died in this town
[Music]