it's really cuz it doesn't it doesn't
look it doesn't look like it what's oh
my god I don't understand he frickin
played with the tiger
yo this is so wrong okay the low gang
believes in you and the only way to
learn is by doing it okay so I'm gonna
go over my vlog a little gate and we'll
check on you in a little bit okay do you
think amazing house oh yo this place is
gonna be the YouTube playground like
when people come to watch YouTube in
general obviously you know they're
coming to looking for logs channel
anyways but like this is gonna be even
better for it reminds me um subscribe to
me if you haven't subscribed you could
be doing I know I'm talking to your
butthole but I believe in you and I'm
not gonna waste any more time in my vlog
for you okay and this is hard yeah
anyway subscribe you good bro make sure
to hit the button for me you may have
heard of the local gang or his family on
the Internet and we'd love to have you
bro no no honey you're not supposed to
be up there we brought your cage from
Hollywood Brooks no I slaved getting
that in the Yeti
come here sassy yeah this is Mavericks
new home he likes to yell we gave him a
view and everything deliver that spoiled
bird life and I spoiled you I also want
to show you guys the view from my
balcony during the day oh this is
freakin nuts Rosie the pool with a hot
tub I see the house my house got another
house so anyways get it together Logan
we got stuff to do we have to make it
actually more beautiful we have to get
designers to make it look good because I
am colorblind and also a grade-a idiot
so we're about to head to Hollywood to
do that
but let's check on Kong
I know you can do this it's called the
savage one of his eyes is kind of just
like the closing shot he looks so stupid
that might be a deeper problem two
things you need help in Jesus you got
this we'll learn eventually how to do
the stairs Oh oh you scared me oh oh oh
the brother and sister dogs are meeting
for the first time
whoa in that before I mean in them how
new house yeah that's what I said I'm
not putting her down because I don't
want you to pawn her literally remember
in yesterday's blood I didn't say I was
gonna punch her you did the act you know
I did you heavily implied it I didn't
say that I'm just saying if Aria poops
your piece in my know you live here too
now Brendan new roommate Brendan no
Brendan business true don't pee on my
own Evans you can pee in Evans room you
know on Evans stuff on Evan just Brandon
and I don't just stay away from us kay I
love my dog I saw it this morning it's
like swollen huh we need Lydia so much
stuff to do today I had him make my man
Brendan dry how's it feel driving the
Yeti yo by the way I'm used to it unless
you're I think you're the only person
that I've let drive this vehicle I'm
honored I don't know if I just Evan he's
his feet are not quite
so yeah you can't see over the steering
exactly and so Brendan Fred don't don't
crash down oh yeah right now we are
headed to the design store to uh design
and Lydia's gonna meet us there so we
can save young dougie Tori cog it's
gonna be fine and then I'm sending
emails and text and all that good stuff
cuz we're shooting our music video for
my song though handlebars tomorrow just
a budget I'm driving let's do this yeah
yeah okay before we go in this place
Brendan and I came here the other day yo
it's frickin magical like we said if we
take a girl on a date like why would you
go to the zoo or like a movie you come
to this place a fact it's a fact it's
the Zen the vibes like look around this
is like the date that you're gonna go or
if the girl or boy is into succulents
where looks succulent succulent
succulent Romanus Achilles no I was just
telling them how magical this place is
and we're just getting started tell my
name Joe thanks to Jacob his son Jacob
and I'm yellow my daughter they love you
like you're just like shouted I sound
like a little bit a little plug there
I'm an avid big succulence bro big balls
so yeah these guys look dude this is
like freaking that comes out of a dr.
Seuss book and what is that hey Lydia I
got something for you doggy yeah it's
just the one
did you just say Fetty WAP yeah my dog
looks like Oh cuz the eye finger okay
dog rapper yeah yeah his son sent a
video your son's actually in the lo game
yeah so yo you know what that means
free everything huh you can make a
custom maverick out of wood yeah no
problem
yeah this place is magical oh my god bro
I just want to make you these and bless
myself every King but I'm a prince right
now I don't know if I'm ready for this
is a nice table instead of our kitchen
table yo okay I told you this like I
don't know where I'm in freaking Rd over
Oh mom this chair has been sitting here
so long that it's bloomed into a flower
tree plant chair do you water this is
like ha I just happen to told you magic
will talk to me about that golden horse
Vicki oh really oh yeah I'll take five
when in doubt just take five dude I
think good $10,000 each great odds
that's awesome it says love I love that
and our house is full of love it's three
dudes in the house bro you good so much
love love good they found a giant zebra
and they cut off his balls nice I don't
know why but I walked by this and I am
in love with this statue sculpture thing
you have these like lightly colored koi
with the darker tree in the background
guys just carved out of wood we gotta be
gentle in here but like how does it
happen
pose motto characters tone it is not my
stuff okay look I'm learning I'm a
daunting what I definitely want to put
this in my yard we're probably gonna put
a koi pond in there as well so much
stuff but I'm learning with this place
especially you'll give that chair I'm
getting distracted with this place
especially I want to I want to take my
time like everything here like each
thing has a meaning it was like
hand-carved by someone don't want to buy
a little bit of this a little bit of
that and eventually it's all gonna come
together cuz good things come to those
who wait so that's gonna be a fun
project
well and it actually brings me back to
my to-do list ah stop spending money
make more money not doing well so far
since all that stuff's gonna be pretty
expensive but I know what you thinking
lovely where are you it smells weird
it's and it's so empty the balcony still
a mess yeah yeah we're kind of we're
working on it not really though all
right we came back here because we have
some extra stuff to get including yo
they didn't move the love says my
great-great granddad always said why do
it today when you could just do it
tomorrow just kidding don't ever say
that the official Logan put one of our
to YouTube play button damn son where'd
you find this man I can't let this go we
came from humble beginnings and now I'm
there we go new ring they putting in
that sweat equity what that's the stuff
we really need talking about them
speakers a lot of speakers bro we're
going into music we gotta blast em Bank
by the way buying a truck I think was
the most useful thing I could do you
might be young and dumb but you did good
Logan you did good yo what oh snap bro
we know kong's the funny dog but I don't
think I've seen some like this I
don't know what's wrong with this guy in
his eye I'm gonna show you first all
right oh my god what's wrong with it
Oh No
he said your dog looks dead just one
more time so you can enjoy oh no this is
actually bad it looks so good his conch
he's still alive yeah it's really cuz it
doesn't it doesn't look it doesn't look
like it what's oh my god what what's
wrong with him
Lydia and all sir we gotta get it out
that's it I'll see you later I think do
officers make your dogs afraid of stairs
[Music]
savage we going down tomorrow I hope we
have nine models hot models coming to
set tomorrow we've rented a studio that
looks like a city dropping more racks
and making music Bros the low gang is
out here which reminds me guys if you
have not reminds me got your maverick
merch are you are you being a maverick
today bro no you good okay y'all know
really get it the hottest merch in the
game Logan Paul comps I do this a lot
you do I do it's kind of lookup Olcott
slash shot or link in description okay
I'm going to unpack stuff and wait for
Evan to get home and wait for my dog to
hopefully be alive to get home as well
[Music]
that's good you send me a picture so you
look dead and he did look so dead I use
my thumbnail you popped him he was like
oh he's I haven't left a heart/lung
don't mean either I was just I was
literally just sitting there laughing
for like five minutes really funny I
feel horrible but it's hilarious don't
worry Kong you're home and safe how you
feeling buddy you okay Kong
I know yo this morning I was like kind
of making fun of him for the whole
stairs thing I feel horrible
now that I know something's wrong I feel
like such a bad owner buddy I'm so sorry
don't worry buddy we're gonna heal your
officer and you're gonna be Kong dis
savage once again I'll be free and enjoy
your youthful life we'll see you later
cause it's always tough you know seeing
your children hurt wait laughing it okay
no Olivia knows things if she says she's
gonna be fun it's gonna be another
little aah hey maverick hi
how did you get out you're not supposed
to be there okay hop up ma'am I gotta
send up the vlog okay locate that bar
I'm glad my pets are okay both of them
hopefully Kong's gonna get better make
sure to subscribe and see if he stays
alive or not
smash that just give me a sec smash that
like but some scribe subscribe button
for me but like I said earlier be a
mapper do something different today and
don't be afraid to do it baby
wrap that scrub Murch i'm logan paul
that cop / chopper link in description
low K I love you I was you tomorrow take
it easy
I just can't
[Music]