[Music]
ah we're on our way back to London for
the London press conference guys
remember last year's London press
conference and this year we got notified
at Twitter like be safe there's an
organised group in London and wants to
stab you would lower acid on Logan I
said that's fine you can stab Mike just
please keep the acid off me I have a
fight coming up on November 9 what did I
do to deserve my special you out like
this just don't distress yourself or in
my wine don't be stressed out for me
you're the one that's gonna get stabbed
so this should be crazy now if this is
the last video on this channel due to
some sort of accident involving acid no
I know make sure to subscribe to this
channel Staples Center November 9 ticket
link in the description and it for my
Mavericks out there the ones doing the
different we just drop these maverick
champion boxing club sweatshirts lit
it's soft Logan ball that calm slash
shop now before we go to London there is
one thing that I wanted to do involving
this I love my beard
all right now we're ready to go to
London you wankers
[Music]
wanna get free care no arms and no legs
no holds barred no professor using
alright bro I feel like a straight-leg
boxer out of that 1920s looking put them
up and I know the mustache was a bit
iffy at first but in this context I
think it's perfect but there's one more
thing I think I need how much is this
chain worth oh it's not gonna like fall
off right feel so powerful like four
pounds dogs this is by far out of all
the outfits I've ever worn for every
press conference this is my favorite
[Music]
it's so brilliant I got actually do bro
okay Mike you're gonna be alright
[Music]
I mean yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah coming
to the stage to maverick looking for
hey body language was decisive there was
one man sitting down defenseless under a
relentless barrage attack dude I love
that word barrage it's great great even
Shannon did pretty well listen
he was a model drops the amount of props
they pulled out dude we came in there
with nothing except for some dog treats
which by the way golden bro this poor
dog I swear to god this dog was like
like I hate to be right now but let's
get this dog off stage bro it was
terrified well yeah that was that was
great dude I had so much fun up there
now that was what I didn't do last year
like I just I just wanted to go in there
and have fun and like mock around a
little bit watch his body language and
then the biggest thing bro when when I
wasn't talking on the mic and like other
people were talking I'd turn to him I'd
be like bro you're like you're different
than last year like why do you look so
sad he goes ah no sir
I'm like wow just um focus on you I'm
like not even looking at me right now
guy like let's get some eye contact
let's get a fight it was great November
night Staples Center there's zone get
your tickets hey they're back in the USA
I know what you're thinking okay and I
can't take you seriously with the
mustache I look like a soccer dad named
Gerald I know I will grow the beard back
it just takes time for my facial hair to
sprout but I want to break this down I
want to break this press conference down
this was one of the most fun experiences
I've ever had in my life think it was
the outfit but I want to do a
step-by-step breakdown y'all know how
this works I want to let you know what I
was thinking during this press
conference because if you saw it it was
absolutely wild I was going crazy
similar to the Fox Business interview I
did where I proclaimed that I was the
fastest man on the planet and had
pinkeye many people thought I was on
drugs like cocaine or adderall I can
assure you this was just me [ __ ]
around and once again being a troll
what's new all right let's do this but
first this is gonna be a long video it's
also gonna be a great video lots of
information hit that subscribe button
and get your tics November 9 Staples
Center if you're not gonna be able to
make it to zone it's an app download it
you're gonna be able to watch the flight
ask ice
it's box office will show the fight in
the UK okay let's do it okay so I come
to this stage you know everyone in the
crowd is booing me and I'm just smiling
this is great I'm absorbing everyone's
energy good or bad I'm taking it hand up
I love that pose that's a power pose for
me so I'm thoroughly enjoying all of
this and I'm like I'm dancing a little
bit I'm doing spins and everything I
give to Jordi a pound but I want to
really show that I'm comfortable and
that your booze and middle fingers won't
faze me so I stand on this chair I
raised my hand in the air and I start
losing my I'm having so much fun and
then I'm like okay time to get serious
this is the most focused I've been in my
life right here complete ownership
domination I'm okay that y'all don't
like me but I'm still gonna be myself
pound my chest your man is let's do this
now if you remember the press conference
from last year in London quite a
different demeanor last year I was
sullen I was down try I almost looked
like I was gonna cry I wasn't of course
no bro I don't cry I was just sweating
from my eyes no I don't cry bro so I get
ready bro getting ready for war and
speaking of war I made a world war 2
joke that's a shame all the support that
we gave you in world war 2 and this is
how you return the thing I mean I mean
talk about turning a crowd on you right
away I can tell you honestly like I
didn't care they were trying to throw
things like you'll see projectiles and
by the way I didn't get hit by any of
them I saw JJ get hit with a nickel I
saw Eddie her and get hit with a piece
of paper some went through like some
glass holder at me I'm a boxer now but
like a bob and weave good luck but yeah
I was ready to make some jokes today and
then JJ came in so man comes walking up
the stairs and I see this little puffy
little dog if I was JJ I would have done
this however I can't do that cuz if I
brought a little dog onstage with the
amount of noise there was PETA would rip
my head off but I figured he would so
again immediate neutralization brought a
dog treat gave it to him but he hits it
out of my hand so the dog the dog is
terrified the dog can't even eat the
tree and I just noticed his dog shaking
so I I just wanted him
kind of cut the joke okay I get it is
funny but also the animals terrified
point is the man is predictable
he's a predictable boxer he's a
predictable showman everything this year
that he wants or thinks he wants to do
I'm ten steps ahead I can assure you I'm
playing chess man's playing checkers
you know why also I didn't like this
because I saw in a podcast JJ said this
I am human as well yeah if right who's
your dog it's like losing a baby yeah it
hurt so I'm not gonna just be like hey
you don't died low yeah this just stupid
it's inhumane inhumane I mean bro how
can you say that and then do this at the
first press conference I feel like this
year compared to last year I was
insulated in that there's not much to
make fun of me for last year I mean you
name it but this year Hong died
maverick died and then if you really
want to bring up Japan again but it's
kinda old news like and so I knew he was
gonna go with this joke even though in
the most hypocritical way he's trying to
pretend like he's got a heart at least
I'm out here beforehand in my interviews
and I'm podcast and stuff I'm saying
like no I'm gonna this man up and I'm
gonna try to install in him in defend it
also one last thing rest in peace Kong I
love you bud I can still hear his uh
precious little bark sometimes jj-just
brought a dog that resembles your dog
majority said that I'm like yeah no bro
I think that's the joke he might as well
have been like Logan you're wearing a
turtleneck was that intentional but yah
shoe guy I'm gonna light your feet on
fire guy it's a light his feet on fire
and look like food orders let your
daughter's talk
yo this man forgot how to speak this
year you're on stage role on my Yasu guy
I'm a yah see you what is that like a
toss with the why why is your mom on the
cheek my guys mean [ __ ] I'm like the vet
I also heard recently today actually
that JJ swears on his mother's life that
he's gonna knock me out I swear on my
mom's life he's gonna not dog that I say
wow he must not value his mother's life
and I know that sounds bad but then I
remembered last Christmas when it
sounded like in an audio tape released
by his brother that he like hit his mom
[Music]
and that's why he got kicked out of the
house and banned and ostracized from his
family so the statement doesn't really
have that much weight if you're already
missing the respect you should have for
your mom okay so so he brings up Kong's
death he brings up to Japan he brings up
my parent I had something in my back
pocket that I didn't want to pull out
let's call it the red button so I stand
up and again I'm kind of just getting
warmed up and I say something about I
guess I should just dive in here
abortion tasers on his abortion because
his brother desi came out when they were
beefing and even said it on my podcast
that Jay Jay's on his fifth abortion now
the circumstance I'm about to describe
is one of the most interesting
phenomenons I've ever seen online
I was very harsh in what appeared to be
my condemnation of Jay Jay's choice to
have five abortions and I said something
kind of just distastefully and way
insensitive about I think I said like
y'all I'm gonna kill you bro like I'm
gonna end you like you did to the babies
like it wasn't great in fact they left a
bad taste in my mouth even after I said
it however my rebuttal for that would be
that in the context of a fight where you
have two guys who were literally trying
to kill each other in a ring and getting
each other's heads this fell under the
category of fight talk which
historically we've seen can get pretty
toxic and stop and that definitely falls
in that category now this started going
semi viral on Twitter there was a
hashtag Logan Pallas over party this
might be an attempt to cancel me again
and I oddly enough understood it because
I said it in a chauvinistic hasty way
because I was triggered and I hit I hit
the red button and said the thing that
just didn't just didn't come out of my
mouth well now here's where it got
interesting there were a few
pro-choicers came out and assumed that I
was pro-life and they started trying to
cancel me and they're right when I
thought that I
could be fun like hashtag logan paul is
over party again the pro-lifers like
people with blue check and a decent
amount of followers we're standing up
for me and they're like hey i know this
is weird but like logan Paul's right on
this one and they use the hashtag Logan
Paul is over party but it wasn't the
cancel me it was to agree with me and
defend me and then Here I am like just
sort of confused if you guys remember
that a while back I had a tweet where I
drew tiny little dicks on the 25 Alabama
senators who voted to ban abortion and
it went viral it got like 150,000 favors
which then tip people off and I've come
out publicly and said it before I'm
actually pro-choice the point that I was
trying to make and it didn't come out
this way but I'm actually asking for
input here so please comment below come
I'm gonna ask a question that I would
love to know the answer to as a
pro-choice guy I'm wondering at what
point does JJ's blatant irresponsibility
sexually crossed a line because he's
using abortion as a means of
contraception that's the question and if
I'm living in a culture where I'm not
allowed to ask a question God strike me
now anyways I wanted to clarify that in
case he touches on it in his video or
anyone tries to take my words out of
context because it happens a lot and I
definitely figured I should clarify
after that happened I had to kind of
like press a reset button cuz I knew it
wasn't off to a great start but here we
go coming into this fight what is your
biggest strength Gordon against Logan my
biggest strength is my actual strength
just so you guys know that's what you
say when your your brain cells are all
of them have wet yo peace my biggest
strength is my strength I can tell you
with utmost confidence not a single one
of his punches affected me in any way
last year I was tired actually you know
what
nah yeah I'm done saying that I wasn't
tired I was excited I things I 'ti got
to me the crowd sucked my energy I was
chilly but the point is the mascot knows
my bit much I have the power you don't
have power you couldn't knock me out
would knock me down you had a guard on
you idiot says I don't have power
have you seen this oh oh I mean what's
good bro you say these things and then
makes me think that's you're a [ __ ]
you're sparring too much and I think
you're getting hit in the head too much
I think you should take a nap dude good
to go take a nap
so the Geordi asked me what is your
biggest strength coming into this fight
I know how to box now surprise turns out
I'm pretty good when you give me more
than three months and this face I mean
what's left under the bandana in the
hair is there anything inside the
cranium it's so clear to me just just
like the LA press conference he's
already defeated I mean it's done again
look at body language I'm standing up
this whole time I'm ready I'm ready to
go to war and he's just soft over in his
seat shoulders hunched in his home
country next to his to his coaches
promise me you'll bring it on fight
night like we owe the fans a sick fight
so let's make it a sick fight duty sure
you ain't for how long whatever for how
long the dog bro I mean this is what I
say this row you're [ __ ] see bro I
wanna [ __ ] you up I want to see that's
true hold on if you google Shannon
Briggs his name comes up I don't see any
of that kid on here I don't see his name
even scrolling bro like I'm I'm
scrolling way down I see what's his name
vital really I see chaos I traitor I see
chairs i trainer i'll see his name here
yeah bro you will watch this watch this
someone threw a a sunglass case at me
this was the biggest most violent thing
I've seen you'll see across the frame
that smoke bro this is my favorite part
of the press conference I don't know why
what are the main stages okay that
you've made since the last fight
question Jordy I'll use my mic now
there's one change I'm gonna win
question next question
next question no I mean think about it
boil it down it's as simple as that and
then also the flawless by the way if I
do say so myself mic switch from Geordie
to me BA and then just standing there
looking at two thousand people who are
booing me and I'm telling them straight
out like yo there's one difference I'm
gonna win this time and I'm gonna make
you a mean and you gonna be my [ __ ] bro
I'm gonna throw you in water did you
bake the cake bake the cake yes I really
wanted to know did he baked again I told
yo bake that cake bro do it have fun
enjoy yourself these last it's last
month or so and then trust I'm gonna put
you in water dude thanks bro but you at
the face I told him I'm gonna slap him
in the face with a fish so what she said
I'm gonna put you in the [ __ ] even
vitals reaction bro he can't comprehend
what I just said he's like yo a fish by
the way what is a fish yo is that that
that's the thing I eat my food off of
we're like no vital that's called a dish
like after I throw a coin in a fountain
we're like no vital that's a wish I
can't comprehend what I'm saying and I
get it on when I'm trolling on this
level I don't know how I would respond
to that cuz if he trolled back just
press conference would be even more of a
joke than it already is literally wow I
gotta save my pirouette
I was having so much fun in my outfit
JJ's talking and you see a projectile
just across the frame and I'm so now I'm
ready la I'm turning into like a karate
master over here I'm ready for anything
I keep don't think I'm dodging and
weaving again ooh and dancing I'm doing
the single ladies dance bro hey you want
[Applause]
this okay this part Jesus Mother of God
big Gib Gib
is his name they're trying to bring up
this kid because they want him to fight
Jake and I think actually Jake wants to
fight him too so hopefully they have
they have it they strike a deal with the
zone and matt reum boxing so this kid
gets yanked up on stage his boys they
literally Eddie hurt hey Eddie heard
grabs give pulls him up on stage oops
that big girl I love I'm trying to say
this from such an unbiased perspective
no matter any of the stuff Jake's done
in the past this man is so entertaining
he goes off immediately he calls him a
toucan sam looking at an Okie Oh big
know at one point look he he grabs his
nose who's got your nose this is
hilarious and give screaming no there's
yeah bro yo he's right in front of you
he's been on the stage the whole time
this kid reminds me of a sloth from the
Goonies like they keep him chained up
and then when he's ready to just like be
an idiot they let him go and he just
starts screaming I can assure you I'm
trying to remain unbiased here Jake I
almost can't even form the words to
describe what he's gonna do to give he's
gonna destroy him the kid punched
himself in the face twice I feel like to
understand the weight of what I'm saying
I need to repeat myself so I'll say it
again he punched himself in the face you
know what though I like his enthusiasm
you go get a big hippo it's gonna be
your big day like yo any time he points
out anything about my outfit I'm just
like yeah bro I look lit and then I just
raised my hand and just absorb all that
energy Justin Bieber's gonna watch you
rip his head off rip his head off and I
won't see my god oh good hey Justin's
coming so if you haven't seen Justin
Bieber commented on one of my posts
every piss head off so I'm here to tell
you that I will do that I even said it
they asked I'll skip ahead here but they
asked us our predictions for the fight
and what is your prediction
I'll go first first round decapitation
I'm going for the knockout like
knockouts were ever cool in like 2018
but it's 2019 I'm here to do my best to
separate your head from your body and
Bieber my guy Congrats on the wedding
bro I cannot wait to see you November
night do you have anything to say about
your fans of the UK so this was
important to me check us out
address everyone stand on the chair
love you and I accept yeah I love
everyone and once I beat this man I
welcome you with open arms really though
if you're a ksi fan I get it that's cool
but after this fight I hope we can make
amends and all be friends cuz y'all are
strong JJ's got a strong fan base and I
like it hopefully for the rest of my
fight career you guys can follow me and
appreciate the work that I'm putting
into this sport because you guys are
great to be honest and I meant it what I
said that like I love you I understand
at that moment in time there's two
thousand of ksi fans just booing me
flipping me off like throwing things at
me but I got I got nothing but love
boundless boundless love for y'all yeah
I feel much different that's a great
question here's the difference I have a
mustache now just me mug in the camera
this was perfect they had a screen right
to the neck to the side of the stage and
I could see it and I could see when the
camera was on I just got I got I look
good and just me mug the camera I love
all this like I was just having so much
fun with it so then they bring us
together for the faceoff at the end
every time we've done a face-off I've
been I've been like talking to him and
this time I figured I am going to look
as stoic and hard as I possibly can this
whole time that I was stared at him I
did not breathe I've never been this
locked in or focused in my life I swear
to God I cut all the games and I'm
looking at him and he understands that
I'm very serious about this he's trying
to play it off and be cool his neck vein
starts popping out and I'm looking at
this man and I can see his soul I swear
to God I could see through his skull I'm
looking at his brain I can hear his
thoughts like I'm so focused right now
and I heard him think this he said Logan
I'm just in it for the bag then the
classic hand up I'm ready to rock and
then JJ and his uh final attempt to do
anything he lifts his arms up I lift my
arms up first off look at how I mean
bigger than him my arms are longer
I'm mad at myself that I didn't grab his
hips and whisper in his ear I'll never
let go like we could have had a full-on
nice Titanic moment so I go to get
offstage give JJ a final goodbye do a
spin
DAP up that psych dab out of him and
then he's obviously pissed at this point
like you see his neck veins popping out
everything so he comes back on for final
sign-off but I mean bro you're the only
one on stage I think the press
conference is over dude like get off
this man is a [ __ ] clown anyways
November 9th at the Staples Center get
your tickets link in description this is
gonna be the greatest night of my life I
cannot wait for this if you're not gonna
be able to make it to the Staples Center
it's gonna be an app called the zone or
if you're in the UK Sky Sports box
office stay tuned on my socials to find
out how you get this stuff follow me on
instagram at Logan Paul
or don't I don't know let me know if I
you think I should keep the mustache or
not I kind of like it maybe survive and
most importantly hit that subscribe
button I love you guys as always thank
you for supporting me this is yet
another lesson in my life that I get to
do because of the platform that you guys
have provided me with so I want to thank
you for that and I'll see you next time
[Music]
[Applause]