a lot of people think this part is a
joke I mean who are not in the YouTube
community all jokes aside will be the
biggest event in the history of the
internet press conference
June 16th biggest internet events in
history ksi Logan Paul Jay Paul's edgy
I'm feeling good it is about to go down
team Paul in the building come on baby
you go in go in you go roast some toast
these boys
[Music]
I feel good I think we're ready to get
down have some fun today you look sharp
yeah man we take gonna be a lot of fish
[Music]
okay guys so the morning went well
obviously the squad is hype everyone's
energy is super high this is essentially
the beginning of what will make history
anyways I'm sure you guys saw the climax
of the press conference yeah yeah yeah
yeah little [ __ ] boy lost his cool
tried to attack me but we will get into
that first things first if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to
subscribe join the strongest family on
YouTube you guys will see we are
actually a family the energy coming from
the Logan at the press conference was
tangible you could feel that your guys
support was amazing speaking of that a
next press conference at the fight I
want to see you guys there both are in
London actually oh my god a lot of
information tickets go on sale for the
fight this Friday 10 a.m. PST the link
for that is in the description it's KS
ivy Logan comm trust me guys you want to
get your tickets before the arena is
sold out I think it's gonna sell out and
probably under a day so you've gotta act
fast again get your tickets for the
fight link in description and also
there's a lot of information on cheap
all shirts team Paul is strong are on
sale logo Paul Cobb slash out rolling in
description and we just shot this
brand-new purple away maverick hoodie
along with a five new t-shirts all lit
obviously you guys know it's not as soft
as merchants looking and needless to say
the Mavericks the Paul boys we showed up
at this press conference yeah we stand
all we do is done all we do is we start
oh we do it's done all we do is done
yeah we start all we do is done all we
do it's done yeah it's done
oh we do it's done all we do it ooh as
if this could not get any more exciting
so little brother Jake went first and
Jesus Christ this man ripped ended edgy
edgy UK's biggest mistake I think
everyone's favorite part Jake and Assad
edgy shoes they show up looking like
literally just dressed like bums
same with ksi overall both of their
brands are just like Walmart brand for
example this is how they prepared in the
morning Shumpert's loose loose loose and
then this is how the team Paul prepared
in the morning look in general they just
suck but the Walmart chant was born
I like that one
I like that one there
oh okay anyways time for the big dog
anyways I walk right up on stage and I'm
not playing games I get right in JJ's
face I'm like [ __ ] and then I go hype
up the crowd a little bit
[Music]
full of Vegas
you know how you play gotta do it right
away after static age of waters a little
bit I look JJ right in his eyes I wanna
see where his head's at
because every confrontation we've had up
to this point he did not look me in the
eye
and this time he's actually looking at
me so I'm like okay little little [ __ ]
boy grew some balls today that's good
and the huge where it gets weird so the
morning of the fight JJ posted a picture
on his Instagram stick out like try to
dig out it just deep bro it's only big
why would you post that picture in great
heights you got a little dick you why
are you giving me ammunition right
before the conference so I obviously I
capitalized on it looks like you grew a
little dick today oh yeah and I'm vegan
and I'm vegan so I recognized a baby
carrot when I see one oh look man you
want to show your dick fine but at least
come pack and heat like me idiot no
that's not a tumor that's my dick so
again this is just what I mean like over
all these dudes is just they're just a
Walmart brand everything they do is it
doesn't make sense it's weird it sucks
meanwhile Jake and I looking like
frickin studs our brand is Gucci and
there's just just straight Gooch and for
those of you who don't know the Gooch is
the area between the Weiner and the
rectum okay so I think JJ and Deji
obviously being related are equally as
dumb like mentally they just function
slower than Jake and I do mr. Michael
high is hard to do but they managed to
pull it off the only thing they kept
saying all the time was
creative creative
good job guys so good so my favorite
moment is when Jake and I did not
rehearse this they started saying it and
just the brother the brother instinct
connected to Jake and I were like yeah
bro if there is honestly one good thing
that came out of this it is Jake and I
connected like brothers like we haven't
in a while we where we haven't been able
to do something like this and forever so
yeah it's definitely gonna be fun to
beat up these these Punk's together on
August 25th
so then JJ starts talking I I didn't
mind it the more the more he talked the
Dumber he looked I Paul wait to punch
you right in your stupid smug face when
you feel when you like bro you're not a
supervillain you're not a dragon ball z
character do us all a favor and shut the
conference took a weird turn for some
reason everyone brought props they
brought props we brought props I better
turn into like a fifth grade
show-and-tell he brought his little like
Toy Story stuffed animals that he sleeps
with a night and then he also brought
the YouTube for dummies book that he
bought and I got a mat with his face on
it and started stomping on it and then
we threw away some of our ksi toilet
paper with his face printed on it that
by the way everyone in our house still
uses to this day and then you guys know
I got it I got I got to do it I got to
make a bed and a joke how many of those
do you have besides the one I found in
the back
it's just cause like I'm wondering like
discern like why does she always wear it
like what's good what's underneath the
band and what is so sacred it's so
special about that black bandanna that
he always has it on and then it happened
bro for everyone who thinks this was
like a joke or it's like fake beef it's
not I'm gonna beat the [ __ ] out of the
kid I really don't like him but this is
where it got real this was the magical
moment of the press conference and it
actually was hand in hand with that that
disgusting smelly bandanna so JJ's in
the middle of mocking my apology video
obviously for everything that happened
in January and I'm not gonna lie it was
pretty creative I had to respect it it
was funny but right away I got in his
face and I let the man talk for a little
bit because like I said like I was I was
like damn this is like homies getting me
good right here what can I expect it's
the one joke everyone makes it's the one
thing everyone talks about and
rightfully so but anyways he starts
talking he says a couple lines and
eventually I'm just like I I take my
hand I tear the wig off and lo and
behold in front of me right in front of
me is the magical bandana
all this is happening in a split second
I'm like host I want that this is my
moment I could do the world a favor and
discover what's underneath that bad Dan
I don't even think a sigh knows what's
underneath it it could be my puppy that
I lost in the seventh grade it could be
the bridge to terabithia the Fountain of
Youth who knows I am so close to this
thing I have one shot that's hope I go
to grab his bandana
I got a grip on this mother and I go to
tear it off I kid you not in that moment
it all made sense to me why he never
takes it off the answer is quite simply
because he can't that thing is glued to
his head I'm not just saying this I
gripped it like all hands and I go to
pull up and it does not budge not an
inch
next thing you know I'm full I'm fully
extended then that thing is stuck on his
head so many thoughts are going through
my brain right it looks like I just like
pushes his head really all I was trying
to do was get this bandana off then I'm
like I secondly I feel bad for jay-z
because some sort of super blue accident
must have gone wrong that he actually
can't take the bandana off and I'm just
assuming it's super glue it could be
stapled to his head it could be taped I
could have been pinned in his hair the
point is he was stuck so I push him and
that I had to start laughing about all
and then madness broke out
a little [ __ ] board threw a temper
tantrum he got so mad he got so mad who
does that Matt over bandana if you watch
the video play-by-play I'm standing here
like what what is this kid trying like
what does he think he's about to do
let's be honest AJ you ain't gonna do
soup you're weak you're unathletic the
way you charge me in general is just
embarrassing just like in the boxing
match it's gonna be the same thing he's
gonna like try to do his thing and like
be all athletic I'm just gonna play with
him toy with him but just mop so I'm
standing there and he does manage he
hits my glasses off of my head to watch
slowly bounces in the air and you boy
catches them I'm just a straight-up
ninja bro okay I'm too quick for this
and then his whole squad comes on chaos
breaks aah
his trainer tries to slap my brother in
the face and Vidale by the way quick
message bro he's their trainer maybe if
you weren't focused on training a bunch
of dweebs and you spent your time boxing
professionally like you should be that
slap would've landed so I think you
should hit the gym and get rid of that
beer belly and for now yeah I guess just
stick to protecting your [ __ ]
so everything wraps up and then JJ later
in the week releases the video from his
perspective and he sounds like such such
a little little boy like straight-up
just sounded so soft he was whining
about it
[Music]
that's what I mean I doing anything boys
she touching me just like seeing this
like after the fight you're probably
gonna be saying the same thing after I
knock you out I didn't do anything what
she knocked me out like just shut up bro
you're dealing with the dog now so step
up and be a man about it
anyways that was fun that's one of two
press conferences that's going down
tickets are gonna be on sale like I said
10 a.m. Friday that arena is gonna sell
out quick guys I'm telling you so get
your tickets while you can the link for
that is in the description and also
obviously new maverick merch this trap
checked out Logan Paul calm slash shop
or again link in description it's the
hottest softest merch in the game as
well as the team polisher it's just a
lot of information a lot of fun a lot of
excitement around this fight a lot of
hype I've been training my ass off homie
does not know what he's signed up for
low gang if you're not subscribed make
sure to do so and with that said that is
the vlog so I love you guys and I will
see you soon take it easy pimp
yeah we stand oh we do it started oh we
do it start yeah we start all we do is
done all we do is done
[Applause]
[Music]
we do we do sir