Oh
[Music]
Janny how long do we have until Mike
gets here okay I'm gonna say this we
have 15 minutes to put a nine-foot
alligator in Mike's room first things
first
please do the love of God that cannot be
here Wow today is a big day guys and not
because my mustache is finally long
enough that I can chew on it look no
three today at the Maverick House are
getting a new roommate you guys know him
you've seen him it's hey Big Mike hey
big and his last name is money
got it by the way do you even like him I
never really asked you know you don't
okay well we should have talked about Oh
but anyways guys um as you see coming in
the house right now is a nine oh my god
oh oh oh my god literally a 9-foot
alligator what are you doing with it
well Mike's moving in today figured why
not put it in his bed Oh
oh my god it looks fake I didn't know
that it's such a yellow head kick your
ass bro
my ass I do need my ass don't but my ass
it was memory foam bro he's comfortable
this is a memory foam bed okay I feel
like he's mad at me dude I feel like
it's definitely not in the logo which by
the way if you're not a little game no
that's your vote
you imagine you've moved your whole life
like everything you ever have from
Connecticut which you've been your whole
life late your big day you come to come
and move in with your friends and you
walk into your new room in your new
house and you see this what are the
chances that this Gator bites Mike in
the face very high okay
no honey no normal phenyl it distich no
no you tell them you don't know how it
got there
Danny how long till he gets here okay no
one act like you know why a gator is in
his room I think it is time to wait for
our good friend good friend
yeah yeah how do you feel bro cuz it was
like a big move for you
and I'm really just excited to be a
podcast gonna be sick I'm not gonna lie
impulsive gonna be the biggest podcast
in pods do you have to cast before who
knows millions multi millions I have a
studio I have a studio session well all
moved in no dude that was you guys later
hi
for a while
Ross laughing real yo what what is that
take you back to it that dude what is it
oh wow let's bake oh that's really it
whoa that I still don't see anything
[Music]
check it out bro dude who are these guys
hey man hey man I'm having a little bit
of an issue my room oh we got there's a
that's the room you wanted yeah I was
hoping like a like column would be in
there to surprise me there's an
alligator in there bro
and very strange men
very strange men alligator part bro cool
like hahaha jokes three random bearded
men not okay no bro is it like I know I
get it but like so Mike like you don't
even understand the past I have with
weird bearded man I could become one of
those you already are bro how am I
supposed to sleep now bro like I'm never
gonna be able get that thought out of my
mind
I'll show to you right now okay are you
me hey not a joke alligator a real one
anyway listen he's gonna he's your
father Ben he's your father baby no oh
[Music]
I got one thing to say bro what make
sure to subscribe welcome hey Big Mike
to love yo our new roommate in the
Maverick House go if you have not yet
copped the hottest summer in the game by
the way we just dropped a bunch of new
stuff it's in description for all make
sure to subscribe button in the
alligator goes there so hold my breath