[Applause]
where's no juice
[Music]
hey what's up that's me load money good
night I used to be a regular kid from
Ohio you know I love sports I paid
attention in school it was always a bit
awkward but then when I was about 10
years old I picked up a video camera and
became Logan Paul butt heads yep I've
always been a bit of a troublemaker fast
forward this was me in 2016 which ended
up being the best year of my life
[Music]
then this was me in 2017 which was an
even better year of my life so what the
[ __ ] happened in 2018 that made the
world quiver when they heard the words
Logan Paul and Paul Logan Paul and Paul
Logan Paul obviously you know the answer
but let's rewind for a second
after becoming one of the top vine stars
in the world the prestonby's vine by the
way I hopped from platform to platform
shooting viral sketch comedy bits some
of which you may have seen after about a
year I have gained about 25 million fans
between Facebook Instagram and Twitter
and then I heard about this thing called
daily vlogging
[Music]
what people of the internet my name is
Logan Paul and welcome to my vlog
channel that's right I'm vlogging now
you get to see more of me I began my
youtube journey with a bulldoze
mentality I was gonna work my ass off to
overtake this platform with fresh
explosive quick pace and outlandish
content I wanted to conquer and destroy
sometimes quite literally everything in
my path the bigger the faster the louder
the better I wanted to make noise so I
did
we became the fastest channel to hit ten
million subscribers in the history of
YouTube and I told myself that I was
gonna blow any competition I had out of
the water which at one point became my
own brother
and that got ugly
[Applause]
and slowly but surely in my endless
pursue of more views and more
subscribers it was becoming clear that
the vlog mentality was getting out of
hand
but I did not see that here's what I saw
Oh Mamma Mia take a look around
Oh Joey look so good at night boy just
dropped 40k on a presidential role
within the bags eleven thousand six
hundred dollars worth of Gucci clothes
Oh is this solid gold solid gold twenty
thousand dollars it is yours that's my
board the machine was beginning to take
on a mind of its own as my hunger for
success was growing exponentially so was
my ego the line for what was acceptable
it became more and more foggy and the
disrespect began to skyrocket
and it's not that I felt the rules
didn't apply to me I knew they did I
just didn't care about the consequences
if I broke them I didn't even consider
them no god I wanted to entertain my
audience every single day without of
this world content and behavior that
they could only find on local vlogs
consequences were rarely even an
afterthought
and not to mention I was the 22 year old
blond-haired blue-eyed kid from Ohio
with 45 million followers on the
Internet every single day my actions
were validated by five to seven million
viewers and as long as I wasn't doing
any harm no one was trying to stop me
now my peers not my family not even
members of my own team
[Music]
[Applause]
and then in December of 2017 I went to
Japan it was the perfect storm of
circumstance ignorance ego and downright
stupidity the backlash against the
social media star who posted video of an
apparent suicide victim is intensifying
the video viewed over 6 million times in
just 24 hours in YouTube star Logan Paul
is facing the fallout after posting a
video that showed the body of an
apparent suicide victim in the backlash
was massive people and creators of all
sizes denouncing Logan Paul and this
video actor Aaron Paul sang Logan Paul
go to hell so many people sharing
stories of people they lost due to
suicide and some specifically hanging I
obviously as a person as a human being I
was frustrated and pissed off and
offended by his actions a hero for a lot
of kids is to logan fans and when i see
that i care so much
I'm so disgusted how could somebody now
realize how [ __ ] up this is this
crosses the line and I am NOT surprised
that he would do something like this it
doesn't make any sense to me whatsoever
as a human being how about a little bit
of empathy like a normal human being
instead of being a [ __ ] go to a morgue
if you're that [ __ ] more big he
thought that that was a key thing to do
in less than 24 hours I became the most
hated person on the planet I had made an
inexcusable mistake completely destroyed
my image lost every professional
relationship that I had became the
Internet's favorite meme and most
importantly had my eyes opened wide to
the consequences of my actions
I felt every ounce of disappointment and
hate directed at me and while it was a
hundred percent my fault it was critical
that I felt all of it now here's where I
made a significant mistake I went into
panic mode
[Music]
being disliked was my biggest fear in
the entire world so and is scrambled to
try and reverse the past I asked myself
how do I fix this when instead the
question I should have been asking was
how do I fix me
I took a month break from the internet
and attempted to bounce back with an
anti suicide PSA in a donation but I was
still moving too fast I didn't fully
understand the significance of my
actions the depth of the pain they
caused and was literally becoming my own
worst nightmare
pretty much I know for a fact everything
I do from this point on will get
criticism it will get backlash so
internet please don't use me bro crucify
me vilify me as I fell more and more out
of touch with reality I couldn't trust
myself I wouldn't send my team the
videos for a review I didn't listen to
my friends and I refused to adapt my
content it was the highest degree of
self-sabotage
[Music]
but finally after nearly running the
rest of my life into the ground
I received a blessing in disguise
you said before this fight you have
something planned is there anything you
want to say to someone out OSE Matt's
got this bout right now and the YouTuber
wants it you can come get it take Paul
no can porn and there's a port I don't
care I saw this as an opportunity to
turn my disoriented emotions into fuel
after everything that had happened since
January this was my chance to truly
truly take a step back from the internet
and focus on something else with the
unrelenting passion that I knew I had I
knew that I had more to offer in this
world and I did not want to let my
failure define me
little did I know I had been preaching
this message the whole time and if you
lose if you fail fine in fact please let
me fail let me let me lose if you can
take a hit in the face and get back up
and learn from it that is a win consider
that a win because you are now better
and stronger than you were in the past
it's just like working out you work out
you work out you work out you deplete
your muscles you take your protein shake
and then your muscles heal and you're
stronger than you were before it's the
same exact thing
during the six months of four hours of
daily training I rekindled my
relationship with my brother I fell in
love with a girl who absolutely changed
my life and I restructured my business
and focused on my mental health and
emotional growth
[Music]
thank God for the people around me in
the support of you guys because I don't
know how else I would have gotten
through this year or out of my own way
and although the fight was a draw
whack is [ __ ] it turned out to be the
biggest event in internet history and
I'm looking forward to the rematch next
year
[Applause]
[Music]
as I've matured this year I've gotten to
exercise my creativity in different ways
with the number one podcast in the world
called impulsive a documentary about the
Flat Earth which is coming in January
and I'm hitting 2019 hard by releasing a
show called best friends that I shot
with Evan an animated storytime series
about crazy [ __ ] that's gone down in my
life as well as reviving the vlogs I'm
growing into Who I am and what I want to
make versus trying to fit into the mold
of YouTube personality or be someone who
I'm simply not the things you've been
went through this year have you shared
yet on this podcast or on your vlog -
three biggest lessons you learned from
this year what's that what's the one you
share the one is slow down it is the
first thing that comes to my mind and I
can not point to that as the reason for
what happened the singular reason for
what happened but that is a that is huge
what would be less number two the
biggest lesson of the year lesson number
two
[Music]
listening happen what way listen to the
people around you listen to what they're
saying listen to your audience listen to
your friends listen you're family you're
not right about everything or Logan will
be a third one biggest lesson that you
think will transform not only your
business your brand your Empire but also
your life in 2019 and beyond I think
empathy I think I think being aware of
people beyond just yourself
granted I'm still young and I still have
a lot to learn and by no means am I
saying I've learned everything and I'll
never make another mistake because I'm
far from perfect and I'm nowhere near
the man I want to be but the best thing
I can do is keep striving to listen
learn grow feel and adapt
now one year later although I can't say
2018 was the best year of my life I can
absolutely say this has been the most
cathartic and important year of my life
this year and how I move forward will
forever to find the type of man that I
am in the mission I'm on I'm blessed to
be able to continue doing what I love
and I want to thank all of you for your
support and if you're like me and you're
ever feeling low like the weight of the
world has been stacked on your shoulders
even if it is a fault of your own just
remember it could always get worse but
it will always get better
[Music]
who knows 2018 might end up being the
best year of my life but I got a lot
more to go
[Music]
you