logan paul he's had a background in
wrestling but not in boxing so I think
psi is gonna win so have your attention
now that's good guys oh my gosh I feel
like ah literally my head feels like
it's gonna explode my nose hurts I'm Way
actually I walked into boxing training
today my coach looks at me he's like bro
go home what's he doing he's like that's
great but you're also like five months
out for the fight I'm like I'm back I'm
gonna go sleep so that's what I did and
got this daily blog he is no joke when
you're sick and I'm been sick before I
actually much worse than this oh no this
ain't dawg if you guys are not a part of
the low gang make sure to subscribe my
name is Logan Paul I am here to distract
you from your daily life we all have
busy lives right we all have things that
stress us out but now when you got the
big blonde chach on your screen it was
good so yeah even just out of breath um
say even now that was like I'm out of
breath dude and I can't be sick man my
birthday is on Sunday guys I'm turning
2300 I'm gonna be a freakin adult yeah
well you got this thanks man
so you guys see the title in this video
you're probably thinking Logan that's
ridiculous why would you title it like
that well because that's exactly what's
happening today I am gonna react to que
si reacting to kids reacting to Logan
Paul versus ksi right well okay you got
it so I wake up this morning my head
hurts I'm like whoo yo how am I gonna
vlog today it's gonna be crazy and then
yo my new enemy ksi has provided me with
some content yo JJ thank you bro use
guys less anytime I can dog on the
real-life scooby-doo of YouTube I will
take that opportunity also guys big news
you guys know this we are having a $10
original t-shirt sale this week only
through Monday kinda like a little
birthday celebration for not only me but
also the brand it'll be the one year
anniversary of mavar by logan paul yeah
yeah this is one of them guys we're not
doing this sale again and and and we are
dropping a new hoodie and a bunch of
cool stuff on Saturday who's doing it
baby nobody that's the fat guys looking
for that calm slash shop or link in
description also as far as my birthday
guys I've been reading your comments
Logan you guys know I love when you
comment you know I like when you thumbs
up see that and a lot of
you want me to go camping so we're
working on a camping trip I can only
imagine the epic adventures that are
going to take place
now before we react to a kid reacting to
kids reacting to a reaction I don't know
you're building something in my gym bro
I said okay is there too many things in
here that I'll literally get to swell at
what point will they not let me beat
JJ's facing bro anyways guys yeah
another swole machine so eventually I'm
gonna look like that by August 25th who
is gonna be nasty thank you guys I'm
gonna go react to my kid reacting to
kids right now yo it's been a minute
since I've been a reactor heels go bruh
I got the two cameras how you doing over
there anyway I don't know I feel like
people care a lot of them actually what
do I know bro I'm just a youtubing
vlogger with the hottest merch in the
cave I'll go buy them alive with my fist
whoa slow down there Speed Racer first
off that is illegal and you will be
charged for our sins now if you ain't
gonna do cuz I'm gonna snap you want to
have like a toothpick I'm gonna punch
you in the face so hard you're gonna be
chewing your teeth like Chiclets I am
going to knock you out
and then take your mother to a nice
seafood dinner on me
JJ you don't want that man I am quite
the charmer
first of all screw Logan Paul and second
of all at ksi is it first off let's
start with this cake guys uh you're ksi
is not a good fighter right he is a
youtuber who learned kind of how to box
and I'm not even kidding eyes when I saw
him at the Mayweather gym training on
the couch what I saw in him as a human I
was like Doug this is not you're not a
you not a fighter and second off why
screw me bro where's your bitch-ass
spinner Butchie be fish pity I like
Logan Paul that's my girl yeah she is
serious bro cuz I'm I kind of view him
as like a motivational speaker ah yo
thank you thank you guys but listen guys
that's nice to think I'm a motivational
speaker but it's not about me right it's
about you and you can accomplish
whatever you want I want to see Kass I
beat the [ __ ] out of Logan Paul
hopefully Logan apologies getting his
ass what okay listen ladies and
gentlemen first of all I promise you
that first kid he's angry that they took
his fidgets better before they started
shooting their second off and you guys
should not watch you should don't buy
tickets cuz that is simply not gonna
happen actually you know what do buy
your tickets but we could use your mind
you know that I'm reacting to kids
reacting to kids or I don't know it's
gonna get used people say any publicity
is good publicity but no that's not
really the case people will hate you yo
this kid needs to be president president
president president president no these
feuds and the build-up around them are
all for clickbait views height and money
and although they will box it's all
basically a setup
yeah if you see two big youtubers
fighting it's going to attract attention
no matter what and that's not there's
nothing I can do
you know he's right he's right I will
say to me
the boxing is cool it's great whatever
we can get in a ring a box like people
can watch and have fun and be
entertained I don't fall Logan pool by
any means i Jay Paul I love them I think
that case I shouldn't be saying I hate
people mom yummy no hate no but he just
tells me who he is
oh yeah you hate sure my kids have never
done anything to you it no it's not true
I'm gonna beat this I'm going to and he
knows and he can tell the future Logan
Paul he's had a background in wrestling
but not in boxing so I think KS eyes go
to war no no what here's what these kids
think mom clearly they represented the
entire nation of America well of course
they do and since case I have won one
boxing match that means for sure he's
gonna win you know what I'm humbled I
honestly am dude like I feel confident
going into this match but I guess
technically the odds were not in my
favor so thank you thank you guys I got
a train my ass off I'm going to and I
promise you guys I am going to deliver
you the most entertaining fight you've
ever seen in your life literally betting
everything made in my entire life on me
bro even the winnings of the fight no
holy Sh man I want to slap him so hard
so hard that people are gonna look at
this and go James you should go pro yeah
for sure the kid's gonna go pro for
being a professional slapper yes JJ good
job oh this is gonna be good this is
gonna be good
oh okay low gank that is a vlog if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe also yo don't just
subscribe hit the little notification
about next time so you'll be notified
when I post because otherwise you
missing out on this litmus also you may
have noticed I've been changing my
shirts the entire vlog guys that's cuz I
as you know $10 t-shirts now through
Monday we are absolutely
not doing this again so get it while you
can tweet if you're a maverick if you're
in the low gang
y'all know better get it logo ball that
cop slash shop link in store or link in
description join in Africa movement bad
B low gang I love y'all have to see you
tomorrow take the voice disappears now
[Music]
president president president president