hey yo what's up lo gang so a bit of a
different video today not a vlog this is
something I have been wanting to do for
so long now however there is one thing I
wanted to address first you may have
seen me in the headlines recently
apparently I am dating some girl named
Chloe now I am NOT going to confirm or
deny this just yet maybe one day but I
digress I want to focus in the video
today so guys if you're not a part of
the low game make sure to subscribe join
be strongest family on YouTube that is a
fact
okay now it is time I am so excited in
case anyone is concerned that I'm not
getting your hate filled messages don't
worry I am oh god they are they're
amazing so thanks guys for letting me
know what you think of me and today I'm
gonna read a few of the most impressive
oh god I wanted to do this for so long
here we go tweet number one
remember the time we all had no idea who
Logan Paul was the good old days yeah oh
I wish dude I used to be a normal kid
now I'm just off my imagine being as
dumb as Logan Paul I got a full ride to
college for seven GPA in high school no
but you're right because as smart as I
am
that can also be you can dummy sometimes
okay here's one it's about my fight
against ksi August 25th get your tickets
link in description okay so I do England
proud and beat the lipstick out of Logan
Paul since England failed us that's
right England lost in in the World Cup
this is so sad on the upside though at
least we get to see ksi do the country
proud and skiing obliterate Logan Paul I
socket in August you think he means just
my eye socket like one eye socket is it
this one you think or do you maybe he's
talking about this one or maybe both
maybe he's a little back-and-forth
action but okay okay yeah oh no oh no oh
God an Asian filmmakers somewhere is
writing their equivalent of get out
based off Chloe Bennet dating Logan Paul
right now Chloe's half asian oh it's
pretty food probably a good movie I
would watch it I would go see that that
boy was perfect for you what didn't you
like about him me for all the boys out
there losing girls cuz they like
watching me [ __ ] boys oh no I knew
Logan pause trim reminded me of
something oh god no it's the diet it's
that dinosaur from Jurassic world the
one with the bowl on his head
[Music]
no matter what I'm going through I can
always sleep soundly at night knowing
I've never watched one of Logan or Jake
pause YouTube videos but you're still
tweeting about us got your [ __ ] gonna
pause next straight up look like a shaft
I couldn't have miss a two that broke my
neck looks like a penis it is huh
that's what their damnit that's
definitely what they're talking about yo
while we're on penis talk Rob Sheridan
says oh he's verified he says eat a
thousand dicks you useless sack of
racist trash Wow okay I will tell you
what Rob Sheridan if you can supply me
with those thousand days I will eat
every single one of them on one
condition every single one of those
dicks must be wearing the same cue
salt-and-pepper scarf that you have in
your profile picture every single dick
and I will eat them if you supply me
with them also quick little side note
for our scarf wearing friend Rob
Sheridan if you hadn't used the term
racist and trash in five other hate
tweets against five other different
people maybe your insults will get a
little more effective you know a little
more meaningful because they're just
lacking creativity so low gang let's go
show Rob a little love I think he needs
it kind of a little negative Nelly Rob I
see you there so do me a favor everyone
go tell Rob you love him tweet Adams say
what's up wish him well and uh yeah
hopefully he's doing great okay all
right I'm feeling good
let's go a little harder
whole youtubers boxing each others
getting out of hand someone just set
Logan Paul on fire and spit in his mouth
then let the rest just get on with their
content do you think there's a chance
that by telling someone to spit in my
mouth he meant to say it would put out
the fire that is me that me on fire
that's what I was thinking thanks man
appreciate your help Logan Paul is right
where trash for logs baseball field I'm
not sure I understand that one
Logan pause [ __ ] Dom is he okay did
his mom drop him on his head as a kid or
something hey mom did you drop me on my
head as a kid or something Logan Paul is
making a video about something dead
again but this time it's about his
career Wow this okay this is actually
good just found out that Chloe Bennet is
hanging out with Logan Paul again is it
weird that I trust her judgment Urso
strongly that I'm willing to give him a
second chance based solely on that
Thanks
I really love Chloe Bennet so I'm just
gonna give Logan Paul another chance to
be a decent human being
starting over wow thanks man
that's actually really nice I appreciate
that thank you okay guys as you can
imagine there are definitely plenty more
that are just as amazing I'm so sorry if
I did not get to read your your hateful
messages but that is it for now all
jokes aside Twitter and I guess just the
Internet in general can be a pretty
volatile place so for each one of the
tweets I read I'm donating five hundred
dollars to stomp out bullying org
they're an amazing organization that
does amazing work and at the end of the
day we all we all need to be better
better say that word we're man murder
boredom
Letta beauty and imma throw the revenue
that this video makes to them so go
ahead and leave a like on it so it hits
that YouTube algorithm and we get them
views
definitely think the hate should stop if
you ever feel yourself going to leave it
hey comment or say something mean or
unnecessary to someone do me a favor
oh no it's not worth it because it is
easy to sit at your computer or have
your phone and hide behind one of these
hide behind your keyboard and type your
mean comments but at the end of the day
we got one life on this floating rock in
the middle of an infinite universe
so let's spread love baby let's spread
positivity get your March lump all calm
/op it's like it subscribe ok I love you
now see you tomorrow take it easy
[Applause]
[Music]
that's a weird-ass noise bro I'm taking
that one of the grave
[Music]