it's a big day your big sporting event
going up I'm talking Mayweather versus
Thunder Tory's kind of maker I got I'm
excited for this fight tonight we're
gonna go watch it on TV Oh God the
elevator is broken today we are on the
12th floor if you don't take the stairs
you go through this door over here check
us out that door right here watch it
makes no arms on Mayweather son defeat
yo Mayweather time to feel stop
Mayweather is under feet no I haven't
stopped you know who I am
I'm Conor McGregor coming in 29 years
young Ave you shuttle sting mouth you
shut your [ __ ] mouth looking like a
160 ass skin beat I'm gonna bounce your
head off the canvas
you little a skinny punk ass you old
Apple head shut up boosting mouth you go
running home to the family baby we made
it we gotta fight
if you're not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe because we're a
couple of good things going on this
morning one if you guys are familiar
with the band v Harmons a girl a part of
that group her name is Camilla Kibeho
it's extremely talented artist is she
part of with harmony anymore
no Kamioka Baio is not part of youth
harmony anymore thank you for that
clarification anyways you posted on her
Instagram story look at that what do we
see hold up oh is that is that the
Maverick mark max and Harvey repping the
Maverick bird I'm Camille story yo
that's the max in Harvey bro y'all the
Mavericks y'all are in the loge a guy
like that just to Kamiya I know you're
in the low gang I know your hammock
if you have a cop Mirchi I do it man the
most fire merch in the game looking ball
that got flash off a link in description
[Music]
I'm dead the universe read the shirt
that's what we do here in the loge a
bullet Mavericks baby be different be
passionate working hard to achieve our
goals added a bro I don't have to be in
the gym but I want to get better
whoa I'm the war and I'm a grind and I'm
a hunt and I'ma be great and y'all are
gonna do it with me cuz I believe
[Music]
pause the montage started but I haven't
even worked out you sorry for blue
balling you guys donut montage but yo
the low gain came across the street this
is just like old times when their stand
across the way those of you who don't
know that is actually the reason I got
kicked out of this building because I
lived right there and the low gang would
like 40 people every day would just
stand on top of that parking garage and
like this whole side of the building
complained about me I love you I love
you so much alright now for the montage
[Music]
hey hey hey no trespassing door alarm I
believe in you
now I don't okay that for another vlog I
like my hands I I need them I use them
to subscribe to my own channel there's
another thing I've noticed these March
cannons are frickin dangerous bro
you leave them out which I don't think
you're supposed to do this is the psi
chamber and I think the co2 like leaks
into it basically it has a mind of its
own and like you could just pull the
trigger I'm gonna bounce your head it's
bad bro it's bad bro this is your fault
again all jokes aside we do have a
little problem here
yeah yeah hi can you buy my roommate
Evan here a new pair of headphones oh
hey good news guys the elevators are
working again yeah
they're not breaking me I feel like
that's part of the reason they didn't
work you've got your dog at the door
there bro yeah hey with those elevator
doors just attack here right you later
watch out for the elevator doors you
know what I mean
we need a house bad houses bad haha no
I'm not even kidding bro it's times like
these where I like I have to take a step
back and be like what if I created the
corral
oh let's get trampled every time
no I'm it gets dangerous yo the Logan
goes hard bro call them gangsters
straight step on call is bad like it's
get it really bad just stop with me next
Hey okay well gang this from the bottom
bottom very depths of my heart I
freaking love you guys like I actually
legitimately love you guys I know a lot
of youtubers say they love their
audiences like whether it's sure not I
don't know sometimes it doesn't come
across as genuine but like for real man
I care about all of you and I want to
try to meet all of you the thing I have
an issue with is like especially now
like you guys know we're blowing up on
YouTube and I vlog so like about 80 90
percent of my life is on the Internet
I've come to really value two things one
of my privacy and my space know when I
was growing up in Ohio good ol Ohio no
one prepared me for this like this vlog
like oh that's kind of cool so I ask if
you see me in person just try to be
respectful of my space I know it's hard
cuz ya'll the savages your maverick but
like when you're dealing with this
maverick just move on the walk back it
was it's important for us to like keep
moving so we don't get like just stopped
and bogged down but I would try to take
pictures with everyone you know come up
quick selfie like that's fine I'm into
it and then obviously when I'm expecting
it more like on tour or a meet and
greets or whatever then we're cool and
brother right now little rice come
update for okay for those of you who do
not know I don't know why I've been like
sneak dissing rice in my vlogs actually
know I do know why I spent Brad bro I
just I like roasts people's I even I do
to my brother I do it to a PewDiePie I
do it to her high school he's just funny
bro to this good comedy job who is he
noticed and he basically rice and I are
boys and he didn't like you but I didn't
like my jokes and he basically gave me
one strike left I did it three times he
said if I do it one more time he's gonna
have to roast me I left I left it up to
you guys the low gang to decide I'm
gonna take that strike the criteria was
that video I had to get a million likes
in a million comments you guys know how
strong you are and you did it then rice
gum uploaded just now a video called
Logan Paul look-alike in public where
he'd like address what's going on so
let's take a look
this video looks really funny ah before
I start there's god Bless America bro
okay just people partying across the way
as you guys know trying to vlog God you
can wrap up your party and go home never
listen let's see what we got here I
think it's pretty crazy that me and the
biggest youtuber is about to go to war I
guess I wait PewDiePie no he's no longer
the biggest load is the biggest YouTube
right now and me and him have been kind
of beef but I just kind of weird because
me and lo it used to be friends and like
look at this friendships true it's true
[Music]
I do kill traffic I also make kill
tracks and I also do bro it's true guys
it's true rice makes kill tracks this is
why this is like this is a big deal I
can't believe we're the only ones
talking about it bro
it might be too much ok so then he peed
he has both mature he has his friend
come over and the friend boots on just
like a swing and the Maverick hat and a
maverick sweatshirt and they go out in
public and for summary this guy has like
a beard and like black hair for some
reason everyone thinks that it's me how
is this working oh you know this is
hilarious alright that worked ok I don't
wanna make this like a reaction video
but I just have to address this cuz this
could literally like shatter YouTube my
cameras bouncing again you little high
the bell rings every time little game
for life but yeah it's up to Logan if
heroes me haven't hit this
once again I really hope you choose my
name out of his mouth I'm gonna punch
your head after you to snake this stuff
we can make a district honey we're gonna
be rich
that's what they'll be saying okay
here's the gist huh I'm just gonna keep
this camera angle right here how like
this dramatic effect if I sneak this
right this is not gonna be on purpose if
I sneak this rice I feel like that's a
bomb drops on YouTube this is gonna be
an interesting mix cold air okay low
gain
let's go watch this fight we're headed
right next door to George's house but
right here I have one out of the 50
official Canon taste you're gonna stuff
this like a turkey let's see what
happens you are you in the low game oh
no way
[Music]
[Applause]
am i bad amigo no Conor McGregor forgot
I'm aware that at this point in my vlog
it probably looks like I'm rooting for
McGregor I just want to make it what you
are no no no no I know I'm not well I'm
not next I am indifferent to who wins I
just want to see a good fight here's
what I think is gonna happen
Mayweather is gonna win for sure no
here's why here's why here's why he
gregor is it there's both world-class
athletes both worked incredibly hard but
McGregor obviously is not a boxer right
he's stepping into the boxing ring with
the best boxer of all time yet level is
just too high for me to go with McGregor
how if McGregor pulls this off I think
he will go down in history as one of the
best fighters of all time agree or
disagree
Rocky's way better Rocky Balboa yeah
that is a movie I mean the Russian guy
was better than rock even Drago
telemovie guys guy that was Rocky's
friend Apollo
yeah Jake's dog died no hello gene
Christ we're talking about movies there
was ever the fight wait Jake's dogs
you guys are so hard to blow with god
bless america
two things I love demi lovato in America
sing it baby
[Applause]
this is like the height of the decade
bro the low gays watch it with high
going into the boxing ring with the best
boxer ever this is yo I love having
Gregor's not a boxer but was afraid to
step outside of his comfort zone and go
in the boxing ring against the best
boxer ever for those of you who do not
know I wrestled on high school I went to
state twice in Ohio I placed fifth in
state my senior year and I wanted to be
an MMA fighter before I went to college
for engineering like this hits home for
me bro like like dude I'm freaking love
what yogi just stop the fight like super
early
that's what stop bro I'm pissed I don't
get pissed I'm a happy guy you're in the
logo you've seen me this ain't cool
brother I'm pissed right now you're
McGregor bro
well they cheated you dog let's start
with number one I was right - Mayweather
one number two yo both of you athletes
are leji Conor McGregor Floyd Mayweather
I have the utmost respect for both of
you Mayweather congratulations 15 Oh bro
you're going down in the books you're
making history proudly Gregor yo
stepping out of your comfort zone doing
boxing when you're an MMA fighter that's
unheard of bro like history was made
tonight I also have a confession
guys I'm not Conor McGregor huh I'm just
Logan with that said bro both of you
athletes are straight-up Mavericks look
at the logo bro its gleaming bro and
that's what you are congratulations guys
I hope to make a piece of content with
either you floyd mayweather or Conor
McGregor one day with that said no gang
if you're not a part of it subscribe I
love y'all I will see you tomorrow
[Music]
yes I am good bro you good bro calm make
sure you go there