okay if you ever see me running you see
there free cake pizza or zombies are
real but do you think that's always like
pizza Doug Christie even begins like
[Applause]
[Music]
pull up on you stand in with your girls
looking good I just gotta have you
started comma same then you ask me a lot
my shampoo thinking what's that about
but it kind of made me laugh so what did
you come through you know what we can do
[Music]
in the shower but the water ain't runnin
and you still got your clothes on you
know products in the counter and I put
it all together I just can't get you out
of mind
[Music]
and I know but I'm trying to blow dry
brush [ __ ] you just wanna touches just
can't get you out my I just kicked you
out of mine I just can't
[Music]
I just can't next day local feeling
funny but to do is money so it's okay
walking down stairs are your person boy
finger what's that about you came around
the corner with a can of hairspray let
me hit the replay looking so good and
I'm feeling even better I'm smelling
like a rainstorm
you said I got patty but she ain't
talking Gotti house just can't get you
out of my mind
and I never trying to blow-dry it brush
it you just wanted touches just can't
get you out - I just dig it - Adam I I
just can't get you out of my eye
a string
oh my god you're weird stay away from me
we're gonna get pizza
I'm Logan pizza okay
I stranger