oh gosh I see it logo it's a big day you
all know I like to spend my money on
stuff that helps build the brand right
helps me make better content solely you
kills it very very important every day
this brand just gets more and more
powerful and now we got a table to just
close the multi-million dollar deals oh
no this is amazing I'm not even kidding
just saving between the wings of the
Maverick right now tell me you don't
want to vent tell me you don't want the
merch right now guys so you've done a
good job I never do this ever but I'm
gonna let you plug solely go ahead and
plug yeah he's like my Keith no [ __ ] you
shop shop back I'm here
good morning Logan what's poppin if
you're not a part of the family yet
smash the subscribe button for me we're
the strongest sexiest smartest family on
YouTube that's a fact I can verify that
with research they a subscribe and also
if you haven't yet guys and I said who's
doing a different bro which one who's
gonna change the world today it's that
maverick movement people who were doing
it different y'all nobody get the
hottest person in the game logo ball
that concise shop goddamn my wing so big
ticket fit through the door careful now
boy loses some big wings it's just too
risky I'm going in
Wow you're helping a lot
you should have pop soon dispenser I was
soft with it Watterson I have invented a
new zoom that's called the butters the
butter just nice and slow nice and slow
what happens if you butter zoom on
butter holy the butter zoom my resume
was nice Rob you you like that
yeah like it's just bad news is butter
this happens sometimes at the display
all that vegan stuff is really going boy
Ross is here Lydia she's wearing the new
blue leggings Oh Vance you know no
matter what you see my room like Lydia
before I go to my room somehow butter
exploded all over the fridge yeah we
have no idea how it got there
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm like it Brendan's actually legit
gone no time telling no but Spencer is
cool too he's cool it's I wrote this is
write poetry
cuz Brennan right coach yeah but Spencer
he's uh he meditate you meditate this
room up with something we're second this
Oh what did we put a bounce house in the
room think about it would you like a
bounce house in here maverick hmm what'd
you say oh yeah I know you you couldn't
actually bounce any because you're just
like a bird and stuff no you couldn't
light it now you really actually
physically couldn't no yeah absolutely
not you couldn't oh yeah
no now I'm gonna bounce houses and I'm a
hug guys how do you think it feels great
we're gonna make no progress
I hate
[Music]
cogs doesn't at the groomer where is he
cause somebody's got to send it the
chair finally work he's about this big
did you die the more I look at the dog
yeah it's not Kong I know for a fact
this is the ultimate test to see if he
knows I'm his owner and he loves all
he's shaking dang you look so good no
they still what oh yeah there's still
some blood stuff yeah I don't think he's
still got blood stuff leave the buck
feeling my dog to you we're getting
sidetracked we have to get a bounce
house
oh my god I can't believe McDonald's
gave us their bathtub shaking up they
had a little playpen in the back and
they sold us this extra one just to see
a big old bouncer acting me Mike let's
not lose our heads here a little worried
about this light fixture but we're just
gonna have to work around it I respect
the stand though feeling I got it I read
the instructions here he's pretty easy
you just press the on button then I
guess just wait oh oh how much does that
chandelier cost right there
$20,000 just just
yeah well bro
it goes right on this oh my god everyday
from now on this is how I wake up ready
[Music]
so easily hit your head on this I know
yeah oh wow it kind of made it like a
huck of actually oh yes I know you want
to have the boxing match in London oh
good now we're doing it right in the
comfort of my own home in my box out in
my bedroom
there's only one thing that could make
this better I finally have a practical
application for my balls
[Music]
like one of the worst I've ever done we
gotta drain the hole and I may be the
only person that's like this what are
you silly I'm stuck
[Music]
I can't even see there's so much glass
of my eyeballs
I hear the class up good
what's new this is about to be the
coolest thing in the world
hello gang due to unforeseen
circumstances involving glass being
inside of the ball pit and also these
sharp shards of glass I'm sorry we
weren't able to send it thank you guys
for watching if you're not a part of the
logo make sure to subscribe normally we
box around and our bounce house is in
our room master subscribe button for me
also cop your mad rush the hobby shop
this merch from the game that's the
factual ha about being yourself look up
all that cop slash shop or link in
description low gang I love you
[Music]
Oh