oh here it comes pygmy pig little
nuggets bro poop nugget I know hey guys
welcome back if you get Evan see the
last episode we've just got a pig here
she is I'm holding watch all my you
stepped on a chariot already no
Raisinets or pig poop not sure we got to
just get the pig introduced to the dogs
I think one by one I'm making a run for
it I'm making a run for it
welcome to your new home look at her go
you already tell this pig is absolutely
a maverick absolutely I'm gonna be
honest I have many many good ideas and
I'm not yet sure this is one of them
it doesn't the adventures involved
that's what it's about she's literally
balancing on her nose scratching her
neck guys if you are not subscribed yet
do me a favor subscribe not only because
the family is the strongest on YouTube
but as you can see now we have a pig in
the family she loves me so much
look she knows that like you know I'm
daddy and whatnot and I'm excited to
sleep with her for the first time
tonight
I think she's gonna sleep that's a risk
I'm willing to take I'm just not sure
about this the bath no I think we should
they're just like I've never made a pig
before yeah and she's so she's scared as
Mavericks go oh no no no this is cool
this is cool man I need you two o'clock
two o'clock I don't know you gotta go
buddy we got to give the pig a bath be
free okay yes she just smells you know
she's been rolling around like pee and
stuff we discovered she loves to tuck
her head she just sticks your head just
right in there what's happening oh she's
a big in the water big in the water
[Music]
but when the pig is squealing like that
like the lady told us she was going to
do it and it's tough because you feel
like you're hurting her really there's
no danger you just gotta push through
and clean the pig that's what she said
you need earplugs when you bathe them
okay she was dirty danger of the
incredibly shallow warm comforting bath
is done okay
we've definitely bathed enough pigs for
today now it's the most exciting part of
the day bro is a bed time we get to
cuddle
probably you're priceless okay I'm in
bed right now
not going exactly how I planned I don't
think that's gonna work because that's
like my pillow and stuff you know what
I'm saying bro cuz there's just like a
lot of bad like you could sleep like
anywhere but my pillow it's it's her
first day here so I get it she wants to
be next to Daddy alright guys so I'm
gonna go to bed this is gonna be an
interesting night I already know it okay
here we go I will see you guys in the
morning
yeah hey good morning what are you
looking at right now oh no big ass in my
face so little high heels be like dull
knives Wow yeah like this hurts our
little V I'm not gonna lie one of my
many wishes in this whole experience is
that I don't be labeled there's like a
weird pig person with Chloe it's kind of
crazy it's just that's the live dude
guys
she's even the camera pearl stava dude I
think we got to take her out maybe we
just introduce him right now no oh no oh
no that's not good
Kong calm down listen Kong we got a new
member of the family okay
her name is pearl Bingbing on instagram
if you guys want to follow her yeah yeah
just sit calm down oh no pearls scared
oh I don't like this one bit I don't
like this one bit
oh she's running she could have handled
it it's a Deepwoods nervous poof I
understand done the same thing myself
Pig Oh calling a pearl meeting for the
first time okay oh my gosh it's freedom
you guys you vote in the woods I don't
like that I'm following you Oh No
they've gone away in the woods I've lost
them I've completely lost visual
they've made a pact to escape this house
why else would they go in a most
difficult spot to grab them she's
digging more holes not making your
mother happy yeah yeah pearl okay oh God
Bingbing meet the poodle oh this is good
this is going this is going amazing oh
here it comes
pygmy Pig no making out that's amazing
and disgusting ooh
Cloe the initiation is complete oh my
god what have I done
what have we done three dogs is not
enough let's get ourselves a pig Wow
look guys I'm gonna be honest with you
it's it's very clear to me that I have
the happiest family in the world all
revolving around Pearl Bingbing
it's okay baby daddies hate to hear the
daughters cry you know why she's upset
I'm upset too actually we're about to
take a picture for Instagram of course
add little ball if you want to follow me
there and Chloe made me put on the
tightest pants in the world Chloe I
don't I really am NOT just sure it looks
really cute on you
now the screws are pinged oh my [ __ ]
about to pop out his pants that's why I
like him
[Music]
alright guys we're gonna end it out with
a pearl montage if you were not a part
of the Lowe game make sure to subscribe
pump that we got a new member of the
family oh that's amazing that's why
she's so whiny
[Music]
like stopping
oh she is the cutest little thing guys
her Instagram is at Pearl Bingbing
there's a good chance she might be the
most famous Pig ever so yeah like I said
guys if you're not subscribed make sure
to subscribe if you have not yet Capri
Maverick merch make sure to do so a
Logan Paul dot-com / shop or link in
description emblazoned across my chest
maverick we independent we go right when
they go left
we don't worry about the haters we don't
worry about the naysayers we buy pigs if
we feel like it look I love the Internet
be a freaking maverick Logan I love you
guys and I will see you next time
[Music]