we found this in the trash can and none
of us are pregnant so we thought you
probably took a pregnancy test in my
house it's positive low gang there's
something I have not been getting a lot
of lately and that is sleep between the
past two days collectively I've slept
two hours yeah I wish I was kidding
actually no I don't I sleep when I'm
dead now I'm leaving under you guys it's
like five huh what yo guys we went out
last night yesterday was an amazing day
in the music video Black Friday you guys
are buying the Maverick merge God Church
status I can't believe I'm using
actually using the word God Church to
describe how much you guys are love the
merge what it's God Church there's the
guys it's amazing to see how many people
are joining the Maverick movement and I
have good news for you you thought I
like Black Friday's over the sales over
why is it still 20% off through Cyber
Monday I'm still picking two people out
to fly to LA go get your merch the
hottest Merson game the comfiest Merson
game look of all that complex shop now
or I leave Hyundai there's one thing I
have to this is amazing oh my gosh yo
these are fresh like they're literally
warm yeah I'm gonna take these eggs back
to Los Angeles that's gonna be cool yes
it's true also I forgot to say hey yo
good morning if you're not a part of the
lo gave me sir subscribe guys we're so
poor luck don't let that my voice is in
fact gone now I got my eggs
I'm miss Kong I miss Evan and I'm
stopping for to go back to Los Angeles
I'm I'm actually Jake
he looks so tired look at that
I'm not tired I don't feel tired I'll
sleep when I'm dead what do I know you
yo that's ridiculous bro this girl
thinking I'm tired I don't get tired
[Music]
okay maybe I'm a little tired but it
don't matter
coz I'm a savage and I'm a push through
I got stuff to do guys I got tasks that
need to get done
y'all got busy lives right but baby it's
all about hard work baby who wants it
the most yeah Bucephalus
oh yeah I'll help you for sure let's
take his back take it back oh no this is
this is awkward she's in my seat and I
was just so nice to them and said I was
gonna do a good deed and now I have to
be like yoga hey I think I think I'm in
that seat yeah I think I think I'm in
that scene I'm sorry I'm just I'm just a
vlogger I don't listen to going on oh
it's yeah it is my TV show it's logan
paul vlogs yeah you're gonna be famous
you guys can follow him on instagram at
logan paul yo so I'm sitting here and
I'm realizing that these seating
arrangements they made them purposely
awkward like the coulomb are sitting
next to you I'm leaving lady Jess hello
gang I'm back home I actually
legitimately love this place and I'm
with my babies - oh my god my children
the red Challenger that I've stopped
because I ran into the bus but it's okay
because it matches the backpack the cool
bus itself is so cool Yeti I
and let us not forget about the
cinquecento oh snap okay you're also
probably wondering why I'm alone Lamar
left as you guys know Brendan went home
for Thanksgiving but to spend time with
his family
ghost if you ask me anyways I'm videoing
myself for the rest of the day it's
gonna be interesting I have to go to the
set of the thinning and oh my god is my
dog and Kong you normally had a hand the
camera - Brendan here but now just hot
baby
how are you just out here it was so
magical Andy's family is incredible did
you have a good one
did you give thanks did you give giving
yo hi buddy
well I missed you cause you're just so
weird vlogging by myself I can zoom in
or maybe I can't see if I can like say
hi anyways I need Brendan no we got Evan
Evans here yeah we gotta have an
intervention with Evan soon guys oh my
god great God but indoors mom before hey
what yes you might film it for me bro
Brennan guys so here's what we're gonna
be doing today it's gonna get crazy
because we're Mavericks and the red drop
drop top look appalled that calm slash
it yo I just feel like you're filming my
dad like if I do this the whole time
yeah it kills my neck what about him you
think you could fell for me buddy okay
what about the parent never died why I
asked you to take care of my oh is good
we shot a music video a diss track
coming soon no the merch is good selling
like a got shirts everybody want to be a
member guys I'm teaching comm tricks
Karl sit good boy
Jake hey so cute Wow anyways guys
probably wondering who's holding the
camera right girl Lily
over there look at her she's over there
thanks anyways cuz this my friend back
look is go hot all u66 okay
you're not like a camera guy right who
cares
I found a cameraman good angle this is a
good angle really see look look he's his
Mac he's tall here maybe try again yeah
so low gang here's what we're gonna do
we're gonna do a prank today double the
action actually do have a prank idea
here's the situation huh no no feels
like actually prank Lydia like a solid
prey I had this idea hey what the [ __ ]
you doing cus bro I'm vlogging da easy
mom
yeah oh well you got popcorn you saving
that for later care of it here's your
popcorn dude oh it's actually smells
delicious huh oh god how funny would it
be pretty loud huh you'd be pretty loud
how funny would it be if we went to the
store and got a pregnancy test and made
it positive and then confronted Lydia I
was like what is this like she's gonna
obviously deny it and then we're like no
this is definitely yours and they like
make her think she's positive none of us
is pregnant no we find a pregnant person
you try Craigslist no I love pregnant
woman are you pregnant single and
wanting to be loved hate study do you
have regular monthly periods in our 80
do y'all not what I need I need a woman
who's not wriggle belly would a baby
aside nothing like a good old bye mate
this also makes me think bro Oh gang
like I want a son why because I want
dude can you imagine a little Logan
running around let's see no you could
wrestle him a little Logan just Jake
yeah I would tell anyone
well I won't be the best dad ever
anyways pretty late what I haven't found
the primary mantises are super rare I'm
super super rare and he's a super rare
I have a feeling that that praying
mantis is pregnant dude does it not look
pregnant
yeah it's pregnant yo we could get this
brain man just look how fat asses bro
look at sighs I'm gonna look up pictures
of pregnant praying mantis yo like that
asses wait what
we're talking about finding a pregnant
lady guys this is not set up and we find
a a praying mantis who are is a rare
insect in itself who is also pregnant B
to us miss what are you saying
no we need you to be honest we need your
help okay yo we gotta
she loves the merch bro who can blame
her bro is the hottest off his merch in
the kit a 20% discount so cyber monday
baby you're good isn't about to come out
oh yeah
yo we have youth sizes oh she's like
about to give birth dude you see that
dude her thorax is the thorax is beating
it's a door at its Oryx bro it's like
that one movie door with this ax no I am
The Lorax there you go miss it's your
temporary home yeah I don't have
anything weird Lydia you're being weird
we know there's a little idiot without
doing anything nothing yo I knew today
was gonna be a weird day bro I'm about
to buy a pregnancy test I don't even
know where to go Evan how we're the
pregnancy test it's not for me it's for
a friend who's an insect Oh a baby
let's baby hey hey there's a baby oh
really nice then we need some ice oh so
good to see you bro it's so chilly in
there there we go the one-step pregnancy
test by one get second 50% off okay
who's the first I'll do it wait yeah
control test to see if it's accurate now
I'm crossing my fingers I'm not break I
think that's how that works
hey back yeah and not like cameraman are
like here often but I want you in here
with me for this okay so oh you just pee
on this little like flabby thing here
and a plus means you're pregnant and a
minus means you're not pregnant okay
that makes sense
oh okay Oh see it's a - I'm not right
okay so the pregnancy test work but now
we have to convince a praying mantis to
pee on it
here we go it's a mantis hi baby looking
good okay so we have a pregnancy test
here I'm just gonna stick it in and
maybe we just wait a little bit
the key is to get it under the thaw wrap
it's perfect well she's on top of it
we're gonna cover this back up and I
guess now we wait all right guys right
max top four was explained the situation
you guys know I'm exhausted like I'm not
dying I'm just like I'll sleep when I'm
dead but I was resting my eyes for a
little bit cuz the praying mantis is
taking a while to pee but man took a nap
in Andy's tent and hey dude I've been
here for like 45 minutes get your
attention okay so max says he has a gift
for me yeah yeah so Logan oh yes last
week he said you liked my jumpsuit oh
yeah I was just gonna give you that same
jumpsuit oh you got me the cadaver
jumpsuit
my boy I lose I'm ready okay
yo this is damn I feel fancy badly oh my
god pants too bro ah be stylin this is
like this is like music video stuff like
I could use this for my next one you see
P good so excited yo how's it be mantas
moves yo Mac first up bro Thank You G as
the maverick movement grow stronger
sodas are closing oh my god oh my god
you have a praying mantis of pregnancy
test no king way yo I can't believe what
I'm looking at right now it is a plus
sign and according to this it means
pregnant okay so I think now we let the
pregnant praying mantis go and then we
use this to blame the pregnancy on Lydia
Weinke work bro she's got a family to
raise thank you for your services mrs.
mantis why just you got to go here you
go sweetheart
I hope all of your babies grow up to be
low gangsters and I hope they all by
maverick March twenty percent off
discount through cyber monday lo compose
icon slash out be free
goodbye miss mantis it's time to blame
my assistant for being pregnant in my
house bro yo I found a pregnancy test it
is positive who's kind of led crazy this
doesn't belong to you does it come on no
no no a man is peed on that oh this is
gonna be awkward dude what are you doing
don't worry about it I just like this is
a bit awkward for me yeah we you look so
innocent yeah and like we've seen your
true colors now my true colors we found
this in the trash can and none of us are
pregnant so we thought you probably took
a pregnancy test in my house it's
positive are you pregnant
no did you get pregnant my house
seriously
that's pretty positive to me okay but
it's not mine
yeah see no there's no marker on there
anything
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
exposed expose lady a caddy pregnant
with praying man buying you a praying
mantis pregnant praying mantis I'm sorry
she doesn't know you're pregnant we're
praying mantis bring over payment yo can
you believe it I know guys I'm pregnant
that's all I needed oh okay okay that is
the end of a very weird vlog Brendon
comes back tomorrow evening so that's
good and you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe guys we're
late with the strongest family on
YouTube we got pregnant assistant it's
all good stuff so smart the subscribe
button in the face for me it's weird not
having a cameraman bro like I'm using a
couch right now is I could dance around
and stuff also if you have yet guys you
still have time cyber monday maverick
apparel is 20% off you know that but I
just want to stress that we are not
gonna do this again for a while
customers while you can guys it's the
softest hottest merch through the game
no one's doing it like us oh snap one
quick thing before I leave ya can grab
some the baby
I'm sitting in front of Harry Potter
this is crazy
oh that's crazy
[Music]