[Applause]
who's ready for the 32 I got one I got
one who's got their merge baby
[Applause]
looking for my counselor shop I who
subscribe to Jake ball Jake I love you
bro okay yo you guys know the being of
lager being an actor combining the two
sort of difficult I gotta spice up these
vlogs
I just asked all the extras if it has
emerged they know it's the hottest Hey
so yesterday as you guys know we brought
a real live mom by a pregnant assistant
Lydia to teach her how to give birth so
good stuff good stuff funny you know
this yep guys I'm pregnant
denial is the first stage of pregnancy
it's such a big surprise I don't know yo
he just I'm like auntie Pro I'm on set I
know first off manager you're my boy guy
Jeff just got here he has to leave he's
got to go build the Maverick enterprise
and so Andy everyday is like yo let me
bring this to set let me do that let me
let me help make your vlogs amazing
spice it up
that's thing and he's the perfect guy so
today he says he has a surprise I don't
know what it is but
[Music]
go get the surprise one other thing he
told me I could get fired from the movie
for this but here's how I look at it
right I'm the lead of the film if they
fire me I don't know what they're gonna
do oh you can't replace me I'm one of a
kind you can't replace me even away here
until Andy brings his suffice let's just
cut the surprise oh my god
Andy why don't just bring the table I
bring the camera ready we've got three
what have you got hops broken go back
it's going closer he's coming on the
phone make it happen juice okay she does
it just okay it's just the camel lady
dude camera lady bro you don't know
[Laughter]
camels store water in their humps which
is the waters of beverage they could
store beer they can store the beer
factory but I don't think that the
location would be very happy yeah you're
right you're right we're gonna go right
camels over there
[Music]
watch either the camel in the road once
again I'm sure my beliefs is really
whose idea was it to put this key
blogger them don't forget guys I wasn't
walking when I did the first thing I
could see my friends from here have fun
Lydia this camel reminds me of your baby
guys I'm not gonna lie okay guy girl we
sit like this for so long
the front is drop my penis is just aging
right now then again my penis normally
hates me I put it to work
really the who's doing it I don't see
Leonardo DiCaprio bringing camels to say
I don't see Brad Pitt doing it I don't
see Michael Phelps doing it Michael
Phelps is a swimmer yeah and not once
did he bring a camel to the Olympics
Brendan use your pride I love you you
are so cool take this map merge and
prosper young camels urinating which
reminds me I gotta go get it back to set
right Jenna see I want to talk to me
right now
hi time to go active no Kel no camel
here bro
no no need to kick me off the movie huh
what camels are you talking about bro I
don't even know what you're talking
about my I would I'm not a camel guy all
right it's time to get serious guys
Blake reading coming back you know
what's funny about this movie I haven't
brought up it so the first thinning had
this shirtless scene and I wanted to be
like crazy ripped for it here's a
picture of me guys I lost like 20 pounds
like I could barely walk like that's how
weak I was but I look so good a little
different this year
I didn't didn't work out haven't worked
out in two months until it for four
months so being shirtless it's like like
I mean I'll do what I get I've just been
busy blocking play anyways I think with
some oil and I shaved my chest I think
I'll be good like just to make sure
let's get into good old workout montage
[Music]
[Applause]
wardrobe extra sure your honor you're
getting yo man you fell wants to get you
some water
hey we gotta iron no heard right I can
hear you fine this is a world don't oh
how would you do that we could warm it
with this hair straightener oh that's
hot too Oh Oh hold up wait horse just
turn into a gross Brennan I don't care
Brenda knows argh
enough of this foolishness guys I gotta
go beat people up and sir my dominance
Oh that montage work feeling y'all
it is oil my mom cooked with this oil
yeah all right
oh hi Kong hi dad was just out winning
an Oscar all right well he's just like
every girl in my life anyway guys it was
a 12-hour day on set also I forgot to
mention what are you doing bro literally
just wanted the camera time and bounce
your respect cast I forgot to say I
haven't eaten all day cuz I wanted to
look skinny and rip of the scene but I
realized not even doesn't make you look
grim working perfect bro us is so
amazing I'm gonna eat this and also I
got to lit things for you location and
they're both boxes guys for doing a
little unboxing to conclude the vlog but
yo not just any unboxing my unboxings
are lit now I know this was a big deal
this was said to be man
by my friend Mac I actually two friends
named Mac this one is at Mac on
Instagram ahh another custom one of one
maverick jacket this is my first time
seeing this oh my gosh epics down the
sleeve the United States of America flag
the top emojis wait what oh you know we
are here doing it different that's what
we do we matters oh I'm not just a bad
merge baby let's go I feel so out here
bro more than I already a oh snap uber
away like beer love in the mouth oh no
this one daddy
so this is from a girl named Claire
Claire Highlands I haven't looked at it
yet
I bet it's amazing stuff before you know
yeah she made this painting guy she's
really good
what am I looking at I don't know bro
but I see a maverick I see a blue tiger
and I see maverick spelled out on Tyler
Highlands homie you've done it again
thank you for being in the low gang I
appreciate it by the way guys maybe not
part of the gang you suck
but this good news you can unstuck are
you subscribe right now so it's very
clear the Maverick movement is growing
every single day more people join more
people get to rep their merch in the
streets and look absolutely Savage
well good nights the hottest merch in
the game look at all that cop / shop I
think it just cash ok sounds good
anyways love yang I love you and I'll
see you tomorrow cause I'm tired
[Music]