[Music]
we about to acquire this skin bread
Ari's the one filming right been
replaced better I don't know what it is
but I am feeling reckless smells like
regret today's decision who influenced
you to do this bro it's that one guy
that issue was I over the holiday break
my temple these fake henna tattoos I
kind of love it and I'm I don't want to
do a sleeve that'd be a full scent so I
want yeah so you know you have to pick
something that like means something to
you I got some in mind we're just gonna
do I trust you guys you're the best it's
my personality cuz I grew up loving this
Jake tattoos are like badass but I'm a
joke sky I like jokes and comedy and fun
I like fun oh how they started this is
Matt's idea okay to do a polka miles ago
you gonna poke my he's like ah he's
gonna squirt Alexie's I'm doing
something I'm doing Sporto models on my
favorite caterer because he turned into
a Bulbasaur no no it's a Wartortle and
then blast away squirtle riding a super
saiyan dude you've done squirtle to be
quite honest with you like do I need to
shave my pubes you gonna have to shave
your pubes I just met you okay no
problem before you lay down bro I just
want to say one thing wrong just
remember that it's forever
are you back turkey on me obviously I
know that
if you were to hop inside my brain right
now this is the emotion you would see by
the way can you guys tell that the only
thing I've been doing for the past week
of my life is traveling in party but I
look like [ __ ] so that I feel like oh
really shaving me by this now if you
guys would like you'll send this in a
bag imagine I got the text from my
friends like hey that's getting a turtle
for I go first off a few shots come out
it's not a turtle I do like turtles but
also it's a squirtle it's a Pokemon I
grew up loving Pokemon it's next to my
digging that's why you don't respect me
laughter you think that's what hurts
honestly for me I burn and the first the
first initial is the worst I get the
number after like the first like minute
30 seconds this is the worst
Alvar gonna be at the first part that
hurt like a [ __ ] bro kids don't
get tattoos I got real
it does right yeah this box is you know
I'm gonna be pain
[Music]
ah ah red acquired kids logo ball that
shot we know the drove no or just mean
we're just expressing ourselves putting
a cool squirtle on my leg is how I
express myself I need to do it I want to
be like a proper like once it heals
we'll see you later
hey there he had another night of
complete degeneracy here we are about 40
hours later and the squirtle tattoo is
looking absolutely just oh God oh look
there's really a pool of blood here yeah
you gotta take it off I wanted to film
it because I wasn't going to this is its
permits I gotta move hold on a second
let's revisit this one it actually is
like looking ok we are back it is on
january 28th it's been a while since
i've logged I feel rusty a little bit
how does this even water you say that I
don't know I'm just is also new to me ah
I'm just nervous I haven't vlogged in a
minute monsters our guys have been
absent been doing a lot of things but
obviously what we're here to do today is
show the final tattoo and I hate to say
it it got infected and it's kind of like
half assed I'm not gonna lie to you you
see how the lines faded here cuz they
sit scabbed up I know I told you I hate
to say that that I told you but I told
you this is the picture of the tattoo
like it was just night not in good shape
so I actually have to go back to Miami
and get a retouch what yeah yeah so
there's still hope trust me I don't I
never want to go back to my horrible
just having artists you yeah you know
yeah that was stupid it was a bad idea
now really guys we got a lot of big
things happening I'm dropping the
trailer for best friends which is
actually coming out next week this week
and the animated series of story time
about my life I think I want to call it
chach tales a lot of big things are the
wheels of the Logan Paul concept are
gonna be turning hey what are you doing
over there
like this and like this a lot what like
this video like vaughese like best
friends like a show coming out next week
yeah just like being using and not Mike
no okay no problem so yeah we're gonna
get this retouch it's not bad it just
could be better if you were not
subscribed with that go ahead but and
don't forget the cop you're mad for
merch the hottest softest merch in the
game the Maverick movement it's a little
like your right now it's kind of like
wavy kind of like dancing around like
this but this year is gonna be a rocket
ship Moby Paul back on slash shop or
link in description low gang I love you
guys and I will see you in about two
days with the trailer up best friends
take it easy
[Music]
it's a squirtle right next to my dick