so dick what's that logo like alight
guys today is a good day
follow me Spencer after months of
preparation and due diligence guys I
give you the brand new impulsive
so guys you know I've been talking about
this I've been hinting at it today is
the very first episode the link for the
podcast which is also like as you can
see a show the set cost $90,000 5
submerge so we can pay that although so
yeah make sure to subscribe to that it's
gonna be Monday Wednesday and Friday you
guys will see like what it's about today
but basically it's gonna be like
educational entertainment edutainment
let's calm but really i want to show you
guys the amount of work that went into
this if you remember before there's
absolutely nothing here hey
[Music]
let's go
once again I'm back around Russia back
inside
Haley's reconcile I'm so black and proud
first fo our guests today we also have a
guest coming as we're gonna try to do
most episodes is a a licensed sex
therapist yeah gonna get juicy real you
know see also you know some other good
news Thanksgiving is this week at I'm
full of funds family friends blender
also Black Friday is this week this is
this is a very big week for maverick
this Wednesday the 21st we're doing a
20% off sale through Cyber Monday Logan
Paul Cobb / shop or link in description
literally everything and the favorite
two-tone hoodies are back I'm wearing
one right now you're Spencer's actually
wearing D favor hoodie bang bang bang
first scene and help me help you music
video got my favorite hoodie also I'm
wearing actually two two-tone hoodies
that's why I'm looking a little thick
right now would that be for tone plus
why are you speaking in the mic hey man
what's up welcome to positive we got the
red to tone this one was seen in the
other Santa dis track so yeah they're
all back and if you go to the side you
buy something again now through Cyber
Monday we are gonna take two people to
fly out you and a friend to come hang
with us on the set of impulsive arrived
a little bit go get lunch do some dog
[ __ ] and basically be awesome together
so yeah for all my Mavericks out there
the ones who are doing it different the
ones who are gonna change the world
Logan Paul calm /op or link description
is our guest here sex therapist hey man
I'm gonna be honest this is like one of
the best worst ideas I'm good at
controversy you think she knows a lot of
us expert enjoy saying does she watch
did you invent sex I'll ask her no
scientist
Hey hi hi I'm Logan a lot of big big a
lot of big did you invent sex no I did
not I talked about sexual issues with
people I help people with intimacy
issues this sounds like in my life
guessing me great there's our first
episode of the podcast the first one yes
we figure we'd open up with that with
Kate with a juicy topic you know yeah
we're gonna scare the doctor but she's
already pissed off my cat oh no it's not
the broke the beard is bringing out my
acne okay I'm gonna saw me think oh wait
oh oh by the way yo
Podcast before we do we've done a couple
Drive runs so we like kind of know what
we're doing my boy Spencer gets his hair
braided members but only were two of
them talking yeah are you all mine
everyone has questions and a lot of
people are afraid to ask them so here we
are five four three two one
yo what is that my name is Logan Paul
controversial YouTube star boxer X vegan
and now I guess podcaster welcome to a
pulse of the most thought-provoking
mentally stimulating podcast on the
planet also thank you to everyone who
rated as 5 stars on the iTunes Store
making us the number one podcast in the
world number one in the world really
just great anyways like I said we are
impulsive guys I'm here with my
roommates we got Spencer Taylor hey I
like plants and we got at hey Big Mike 6
foot 3 I like long walks if you clap at
the end of flights I don't like you whoa
my special guest today is a licensed
psychologist that specializes in sexual
health and wellness she is a certified
sex ologist and sex coach I don't know
what that means we are going to dive in
wow that was a lot a lot of talk about
sex for not ever having done a podcast
like we kind of know you guys if you saw
my first vlog I was [ __ ] right what is
up people of the internet my name is
Logan Pauling welcome to my vlog channel
that's right I'm vlogging now you get to
see more of me ha ha ha
sick right it's probably eyes the link
for the the podcast we just did is in
the description also subscribe to the
new channel and subscribe I think it's
on like iTunes and Spotify wherever you
listen to podcasts it will be available
you subscribe to this channel dude if
you're not subscribed to anything I
don't do subscribe to everything
yes also guys for all my Mavericks out
there you know that and there's a
site-wide 20% sale through cyber monday
if you go on the site and grab something
we are gonna fly out you and a friend to
people to come out hanging out watching
you pause the podcast see how it's done
here with the Memphis house you can be
caught assuming again we still have him
well begun our guest for the podcast on
Wednesday is I'm just gonna say Jo Jo
see WA who is
brother get your giant bows down we'd
love to see hello gang I freaking love
you guys and I will see
[Music]
[Applause]