yo guys I'm getting better I stopped
myself that is something an immature
person would do he's learning oh hey
don't mind me I'm just watering my roses
cuz it's Valentine's Day
hey yo good morning okay would yes guys
it's Valentine's Day I got the ping map
of merchants I'm looking good right plus
we got a merge drop today this one's for
the ladies today's a day about know we
got brand new boyfriend sweatpants for
the girls in they come in two different
colors plus the best part is you don't
even need to have a boyfriend because
remember it's all about and our brand
new staple hoodie they come in two
different colors pink and black and
ladies I can promise you no one does it
like us it's the hottest softest merch
in the game and that's a fact y'all know
where to get it looking ball that calm
slash shop or League is killing all guys
I also got this bear for my Valentine
who's inside by the way saying Lincoln
description is literally just becoming a
noise more like it's coming out anyways
I also know guys girls love chocolate
and I got this Dona from the store today
found it too lazy to go get actual
chocolate so I'm just scraping it off
the top of the donut but I think she'll
be cool with it because remember guys
today's all about how are we always mad
I don't know anyway smile happy
Valentine's Day hey I got you a gift
I did multiple gifts surprise
happy Valentine's Day yeah so we got
this just big teddy bear for love I know
you like chocolate so I scraped it off
atomic donut oh and lastly I got you
these flowers mock us today that water
Bona whose boner floor cleaners Oh also
guys if you're not a part of the low
game makes sure to subscribe because
remember this channel is all about and
with the Strongs family on YouTube also
mah here you go that's the last gift
congratulations you're an inter thought
Slayer okay I have enough I'm gonna go
do something else
what are you doing I see you through the
door what are you doing
girlfriends quick damn this is gonna be
flying off the shelf you know I'm gonna
need like one box of this thing why are
you guys such a big knives I got a big
nerd Savage oh I wish I was a lady right
now actually a flashback to yesterday
hey I'm not just saying this all do you
get the funnier you get I swear to god
you have gotten funnier bro this is this
is big oh that's funny
what are you doing with Jake's YouTube
channel funny bad you know funny oh okay
talking a lot by the merch it's fire
right look I'm blossom I shot but I
think okay this is good so guys the
reason my dad is in Los Angeles not only
because I love him but he's here
building a fence for us before you could
see through the gate and obviously we
don't want people looking at us whenever
running around naked and whatnot so
who's been filling in the gap with spice
literally this thing is looking like a
castle sharp pointy spikes for
everyone trying to break into my house
we got to keep the security tight oh god
it gets worse I think it might be
woman's but it's just a medium I came
from why the way I am why the way you
are no no this is why I am the way I am
why I love you love you just the way you
are so I'm just sitting here watching
these mini marshmallows microwave looks
like they're getting bigger anyways guys
my ears are hurting and I was wondering
why I just remembered yesterday when I
was dangling from the helicopter oh my
god yes that makes me happy bro look oh
you changed it is hot almost as hot as
this murder well yeah when I was
dangling from the helicopter I've seen
in this clip or maybe this clip we had
to glue Jake's putting glue on the ends
of the air pods here this might actually
be scarier than the helicopter what if
the glue guns in my eardrum I can't hear
oh man oh man oh don't glue ear buds in
your ears kid unless you got a hang from
a helicopter for a dope-ass music video
Wow
Oh number two
just do it I'm good now the good news is
that I can still hear out of both my
ears but I do have bad news guys do not
forget right today's Valentine's Day
today is all about but the bad news is
guys I still don't have a gift for my
date tonight
[Laughter]
girls love arts but what do they love
more than arts crafts so we came to an
arts and crafts store that crafts I mean
every Valentine's Day starts with fresh
flowers they're made of polyester
because you really pulled her over with
your love stretch bit of a stretch
Oh girls of Hoops no but I do have an
Instagram channel at Logan Paula's gonna
follow me there how would this
multi-coloured ball it looks fun it
looks nice I feel like I'm the old me
would have punted that ball I'm not even
kidding
yo guys I'm getting better I stopped
myself and I was like punting the ball
is not the right thing to do that is
something an immature person would do
he's learning telling me if you put this
in and you spit it'll fly that just
doesn't make any sense
I'll take five custom t-shirts it will
show originality creativity splendor fun
you splendor in the same blender a
quality that outshines the usual yo like
slender man you guys know slender man
right the scary guy slender man the
exact opposite he's like slender man but
with the face and a blonde head of hair
we love Slender Man candles candles like
a detectives like there's candles here
these are the really nice ones too oh my
gosh if there's one thing girls love
more than candles there's nothing girls
love more than candles so I am NOT gonna
buy her one bad idea I might as well be
a girl I know what you guys like what
girls love BRR
houses to put their makeup in see look
this one reminds me of the team ten
house wait what no Disney Channel five
million you want to take a picture yeah
Valentine's Oh here I'll be your
Valentine's take this roller yep there
you go
all yours ma'am happy Valentine's Day
that thing is fine if I'm not the best
Valentine's day ever
oh damn looking at them in a pile I
realize I suck no wait we could still
customize the shirt to show splendor oh
it's now official maverick merch you
could get like 20 299 on the streets for
this yeah make it official oh my yo it's
official before side of the vlog guys I
know what you're thinking uggs who are
you going on a date with I can't tell
you who it is they don't know yet I'm
sure they'll take my gifts maybe well
let's not forget it's all about with
that set low gang that is the vlog not a
part of the family you suck but you can
unstuck by subscribing smash the button
in the face and join this strong family
on YouTube also edited a thousand times
today cuz it's factual you look so good
in this ladies we got you covered the
brand new boyfriend sweats this staple
hoodie Logan Paul calm slash shop nobody
does it like a squad of Mavericks the
people who do it different the people
who aren't afraid to be themselves a lot
of people who do a different squad of
people who themselves no matter what
hello gang I love you and I was here
tomorrow or do
[Music]
I think I got one
three times you girl you love some