but now that I'm next to it I think I
really can I get today you're not
feeling all days will wake up and we
don't feel it going to work rest assured
that when this camera turns on so did
you when that vlog goes out the fans
love it they want to see you smile see
you happy and that's who you are happy
show me that American smile I really
don't feel like walking today hello
thank you scorn seems really good to me
guys this ain't good I can't even do a
coke and mentos right it's all I'm gonna
do is give the bottle a little [ __ ] lame
excuse for vlogger every blogger you do
coke mentos at me why do I did you make
your smoothie yes movies are a great way
to just lighten the mood no I guess I
could do that
hey hello youtube this was a bit I was
supposed to drop the front end and it
was supposed to spray out I can't even
make a mess right fruit was supposed to
go in the blender and the blender wasn't
the fruit up in the air and now we have
a stupid joke on our love I hate this
vlog it's actually great okay so this go
work now so like I was saying earlier
all I'm gonna do is give this a little
shade and then I'm gonna throw it at the
ground and it should explode it just
blew the kappa i can't even vlog right
sitting in an igloo of inadequacy I'm
swimming through to see him self-doubt I
feel like I'm going to reverse on the
hey guys map record can come in May 22nd
the clothings waterproof guys we just
want to try the next bit can you give me
the corn I've always wanted
are you [ __ ] kidding me
nothing is working today really thanks
man thanks David I know since everything
I'm doing is failing I'm taking the easy
way out how do you get views on a vlog
tits dr. Barrett board-certified plastic
surgeon
he's the boom guy I've never liked
seeing these not in a girl's body
there's a great stress relief I actually
used to yes I just wanted to be hard as
a rock
when I grabbed her boobs I want to cut
my hand on so can we cut one of these
open oh I could do a doc oh my god oh my
god oh so it is really sticky sticky Wow
always filled the outside of busan nam
inside of them oh my god you got
something we want is a pong I'm a skin
tag most ridiculous taking me I want to
see she got amazing a small pillow that
exists on the
[Music]
like another testicle no give it to me I
could use some that's about 15 so now
that I'm next to it I think my god you
great Mike you're doing great Wow there
it is give me a Paul I can't thank you
enough for what you've done for me in
the past six months the sweet girlfriend
the billboard and now two more inside to
your amazing friends [ __ ] dude now
that things are going right again I
think we try the Dyke Oh
[Music]
the Seelye go jump in