[Music]
you broke it
why should it's too late now so here was
the joke we met to make I wanted to do
it again and that all happened yeah yeah
I did that what do you think huh get it
get it oh no it's got a dope yo
spongebob
hey yo spot you're in there bro oh [ __ ]
damn it also you might be wondering
Logan why are you filming today yeah
yeah my cameraman Brendan is gone but
it's okay cuz I got my boy Evan to film
you went shooting this real quick guys
we've been doing for the past three days
today is the last day 20% off on the
matter website guys at cyber monday its
discount day if you have not yet even if
you have actually go to the Mac room set
low ball that comes last shot copy
yourself the hottest merger in the gang
yo right here baby let's go we're gonna
be picking ten people to win a 250
dollar shopping spree 30% off all
backpacks $20 t-shirt free shipping on
pull up this one's actually big up to
the face ready free shipping on
purchases over $100 guys if you didn't
listen to the stuff I just said it's
huge copyright why you can load up all
that cops last shop or link in
description heaven heaven anyway yeah
guys we're not doing that sale again for
a very long time so you know well you
can but right now we have to cut a fresh
pineapple for the sake of yongi I feel
like we should definitely pick up that
glass before Lydia gets here car back
off also kind of sucks that that thing
that we broke was a piece of rental
furniture my bad oh oh
oh I eat the skin feast my child
actually you know what no bro there's
such a better way to get
here we go a lot of things I'm just
gonna send it get it up it's working oh
yeah how is it oh you're doing that
makes me realize this might be the most
useless thing I've ever invented yeah
guys do by the way if you're subscribed
you saw you oh wait hold up pause if
you're not subscribed what subscribe for
me do it for me do it for the Loghain do
it for yourself doing the strongest
family on the internet oh hi Kong how
are you buddy anyways yesterday's vlog
guys Liddy's my assistant we tried to
trick her into thinking she got pregnant
in my house we found a pregnant praying
mantis out here actually and had a pee
on a pregnancy test can't believe I'm
saying this it doesn't make any sense
but it read positive and then we gave it
to Lydia and this happened that's right
yeah guys I'm pregnant
yeah whatever Lydia anyways I came out
here to see a mama mantis is here oh
snap okay wait before I do it yo the
vehicles look beautiful mama mantis guys
we left her there yesterday we found her
under here mm-hmm she's made our home
her home I don't know if you guys know
praying mantises are like pretty rare
insects so the fact we found it two days
in a row is pretty cool which it looks
like legitimately we have a new roommate
also how cool to be if we're able to
like see her give birth like she's
freaking bursting look at that belly bro
there's kids in there and we gotta hook
him up with some maverick youth mercy
shirts for twenty dollars today and free
shipping over 130 yo you gotta have your
kids mama cyber monday we're gonna get
you the best deal such a dope creature
just preying on all the Mantis there is
we might have a new roommate
oh my god she's back what are you
talking about we brought in yesterday
what all of a sudden you scared
so it's mama come on she's cool
bro she's about to have kids she's been
pained be nice okay she's coming
oh she love you
oh damn new roommate
oh okay mama let's put you back there
you go mama
they grow up so fast all right mama see
you tomorrow here's what I'm excited
about whatever lo gangster's I fly out
here to ride at the red Challenger with
me oh come on get crazy with it bro like
I'm gonna try to safely
whip you guys out of the car I might
pull a little trip bro
Oh gonna be fun guys do not forget oh I
just go to looking ball that cop /op
grab your maverick my thanks go be prop
it but okay right now I'm Evan it's your
big day
dad you want to explain what's happening
like how this idea came about so today
I'm going to get my hair braided wha
like post Malone itch
no no no no post my little baby post
work for the day what week
yeah and I'm I'm just going for moral
support yep that's my boy he's my boy
there's my boy yeah boy hidden rear hair
braided like post Malone who is king
savage okay we gotta do savage thing
[Music]
oh my man Evans getting that special
haircut you're gonna look like that you
kind of already do actually I don't been
to a hair salon bro this is like I feel
like an astronaut you can get your hair
done and go to space what a big the
owners not coming today he's four years
old
oh well good thing you made that 2:00
p.m. appointment everything yes yes
do you guys braid hair we're trying to
make it look like post malala bright
hair that one four-year-old woulda
showed up we gotta find someone on the
streets bro someone with street cred who
knows how to braid hair let's try these
people you guys not a braid hair
actually I told you straight gray wanna
make him look like posting them a little
post Malone but the little version I am
as serious as a heart attack which my
dad had he didn't die good for him are
you down I told you so
you know why bro because I believe in
people believe you a few nice pro and
you spread good energy and good vibes
you're attracted to people with good
energy and good vibes no holding a
camera right in my chest pointing at the
faces said my friend yeah but yeah this
is amazing look they're behind us hey
you have about 1 mile to change their
minds but I don't think that's long
enough I we just got home can't imagine
what is going through these guys houses
a cool bus a challenge or a Cinquecento
Jeep with a tent on top hey was uh
welcome to the crib oh how you so cool
Lydia we need stuff Lydia we're in the
middle of a thing we need more of those
yeah she said you like the ladies the
lady the lady outside I'm Lydia
she's outside right outside first the
first thing their lady
why is she pregnant good cuz we just
father's don't be afraid bro we got an
attack dog attack ghetto Kong just
kidding I don't know I just went to a
dark place bro this is better than the
salon we were involved
got the vehicles you got her it's gonna
be amazing oh you look like such a
pretty girl did you see yourself doing
this today was in any world cool
calculator row you'd like Princess Leia
man I'm sorry that's what you look like
I put a picture next to you so everyone
could see yo you starting to look like a
full fledged ad okay we're in the merch
room let's see what we get it's on the
low gang oh here there perfect we'll get
him oh you good bro survey cuz he may
not be good bro yeah here you good bro
you good bro I know you may not be in
the low gang so I just wanna ask if
you're good bro it's definitely not good
bro Evan our new roommate is very
intrigued yeah this is no joke you've
passed the point of like oh I'm
frightened like I'm a fake thug like bro
who they're from
oh my you're getting into music yeah
this this yo so crazy we said you're
gonna be posting a little I think you
look like an upgraded version of little
pump dude no this makes me nervous last
time I did this I did cornrows and I
look I look like a thumb I look like a
skin phone
Evan you've changed for the better bro
you look like a scholar you should say
only like super profound things if heat
rises
why is our space so cold exactly Evan
yeah but somewhere so no coming back I
like how you guys are honest you guys
are both just like yo you're looking
ugly here's what I believe I think you
got to get ugly before you can be
beautiful fat and sometimes on occasion
you're ugly and then you're still ugly
which I feel like it's gonna happen
today but we'll find out oh my god doing
red because as you know we had just had
the Maverick red dry red raw chopped ah
so composure cops - ah hi guys the deed
is done yo thank you guys vana drew in
his name yes had a group hug I'm part of
the family now ever get in here bro it
happened so randomly you guys are
Mavericks that's what I preacher my
vlogs just like doing it ro just doing
it I gotta go look at how wack I am 80
oh man bro I'm gonna look so white and
disgusting what it's gonna be beautiful
oh you actually look like a thug No
[Music]
same thing is earlier just avoid the
glass honey what do with it no we're
doing it oh you know what I need bro
girls
my god we should never do this again
and actually no what no what you should
you know your don't mean this is the
last day it's not me
[Music]
currently no one on planet earth looks
as dumb as me I hold that pride on
tightly
all right title proudly yeah anyways
guys there's one more thing I want to do
today I mentioned it this morning we're
missing one person
Brendon it's me Logan I'm just eager to
get really good to get Wow yeah red
beads red drunk guys at Cyber Monday
free shipping on orders over $100 we're
not doing this again
20% of discount is up 20% discount still
applies i drowned the grill things many
guys it's the hottest softest merch in
the game no one's doing it who knows
what's in there even when they look dumb
nobody guys t-shirts for $20 30% off all
backpacks it's a big deal Logan Paul
dot-com / shopper link in description
join the maverick movement and also join
the love gang guys the strongest family
on the Internet
so subscribe for me hit the button in
the face for me a dad for meelo gang I
love you I'll see you tomorrow
take it easy fam please
[Music]
Stace Stace we hit the stage you ready
to raise we better up stand your place
we get in your face Wow saved our lives