warning the following vlog features
stunts performed by experienced
professionals do not attempt to recreate
or reenact any stunt or activity
performed on this show oh you guys ok
holy crap
[Music]
hey y'all good morning little gang would
pop it's not some Ohio she's lifting
logs and whatnot you guys know I got the
chaos a fight coming up right yeah man
you're somebody but no days off what's
good baby
it's that maverick lifestyle yeah I
could go camping and just relax right
take a vacation I don't think so baby
who's doing it make sure you join the
movement it is real everyday bro we are
here pushing ourselves changing the
world y'all know where to get the
hottest mercs in the game love all that
cops last shot oh my yeah I feel good
today you guys so yesterday he went
under they under his a yosemite falls
[Music]
very dangerous cold slippery had not
recommend trying that and we have more
fun stuff playing today guys oh man we
haven't even used a kayak yet so if you
guys do not make sure to subscribe sick
cartwheel guys we are the strongest
family on youtube so smash to subscribe
and for me like I'm a smash hit aside
face and ring the little bell next to
the button so you can be notified when I
post now your boys hungry and I need
some crowd
oh so funny I forgot we were camping not
much nutritious protein value in this
food yeah or spoons we don't have spoons
anymore I'm stay out okay when I'm 80
years old I want to look like this oh my
god oh we have spoons that guys can be
civilized okay first things first guys
we did buy a $600 kayaks we're about to
do a little minor Huck it's a major
major Huck yeah that's a fact well first
guys we have to find the river I gotta
get my Daniel Boone thank God my head
was anything wrong here what happened
what did you do tonight
obviously you did it oh you're right I'm
looking out the window I'm like why is
it why am I seeing the trail it should
be like directly behind the bus like nah
definitely swerving damn we are so close
to getting out of here we can do this
guy's
yeah big pearly not dysfunctional
trailer I can tell you that much what
dear oh my god dude this deer everywhere
here and all I got to say to that is oh
dear so I make it so when we drive the
trailer stays attached to the bus yeah
well we're low on gas which probably hit
it
we are longer leaving yosemite ghostess
Ovilus
I know what you expected Chester got
monopoly I came in but you out I'm not
sure either crunchy well with no
apologies I am okay guys we got gas
everything is looking pretty good
hopefully nothing else goes wrong
the issue is we haven't gone kayaking
yet and if you look here on top now
there's also a second issue what we're
dealing with here is a Class C grade a
level 10 red alert rapid holy Sh I just
I just don't know about the risk factor
here because the issue is right you come
from up the river you can't tell if
there's a waterfall down there this is
what I see happening there is somewhat
hope here if there Andy what's your
background and rowing again I mean I won
the national championship we're dealing
with a national championship row okay
it's like the waterfalls that are
waiting for it you never know the point
is I kind of trust being with em but
just this might not be the move I didn't
really want to get is that you mean
laughs well turns out the microphone
broke so here's the voiceover here's me
being [ __ ] but we found a river that
was less calmed it didn't appear to be a
red alert rapid we were kind of just
hoping there weren't any waterfalls but
didn't know for sure anyway so got the
guy act down Haydon as you can see
really helped out with that we got our
life jackets on then because safety made
a joke that I apparently thought was
funny shop the life jackets on nice and
tight probably too tight definitely yeah
too tight carried the kayak down to the
launching pad and then proceeded to plug
the hottest merchant in the game was a
good baby Logan Paul that got slashed up
the my boy Andy and I got in the kayak
and got ready to go
[Music]
I feel like now's a good time to say
I've never been kayaking in a river oh
my god you're we're going back
yes we took a lot of water on that one
okay I forgot this canoe doesn't release
water well I guess your only option
[Music]
oh oh oh you guys okay
oh are you okay what happened what you
guys okay holy crap this is did you guys
call for help you okay you okay we just
took it
oh yeah I'm just like in shock because I
just like hopped in the river like was
fighting for my life I come back here
and then these people are fighting for
their lives okay let's look at the sky
yeah
doing your we get it dude I know I get
this water and this so cool stay strong
put your legs
[Music]
of German
yo what's up bro you're wet turned out
it was a Red Alert rapid grades II class
I'll cold on you you look like you're
pretty warm definitely not warm hash Sam
spring cold shiver looks like it's
actually a little scary man you okay bro
ah yeah I'm fine here's the issue did
you see I saw it all the car crash I
didn't see the car bro bro happy when
you guys got a car crash who family's
like dude how about that English huh and
he's still with the car I don't even
know we gotta save and he broke he's
still out there
yo you look cold my cold if I was cold
they tell you we thought you and me
gotta save Andy and Annie we came to
save the day and your thighs are redder
than Santa Clauses has a lobster look at
my chin do know that one took a good one
yeah baby yeah took them hit I'm
freezing
we should get this on top of the bus and
go check into that family yeah
okay we're back here there's a ranger
right there
everything everything looks like it's
under control we just wanted to make
sure everything was okay dude what a
crazy chain of events like
we should have just listened to the
science bro we should get out of here we
should go back to LA right now
all right let's go and oh wow we're here
it's one I am pretty much everyone is
gonna sleep I got to tell you almost
drowning is exhausting whoa
what a crazy day guys we're back home
safe in LA and logging that is the vlog
if you have not subscribed yet go ahead
god bless support me join the strong
family on YouTube we welcome everyone
unless you suck then leave and also cop
your mavar merch the hottest softest
merch in the game to be honest if I
didn't have this after I went into the
Antarctica water today who knows I may
have gotten frostbite and lost some
limbs or more of your testicle low blow
Spencer sorry to bring up Logan pump
that cops last shot for the link in
description low gang I love you all now
see you tomorrow take it easy
[Music]