my dog eats fish my dog he likes to eat
yeah he likes to eat fish I know there's
a lot of fish in the sea but you're the
one I'm focused on welcome back to
another vlog if you guys saw the last
blog we got a new member of our family
the little young husky down in the front
because he's new to the family and I
like him more than you that's a joke
you're my friend we asked you guys to
comment tell tell us what you think we
should name our husky dog got a lot of
comment thank you for all those by the
way what did you spill what did you
spill you spill the Red Bull you big
that's why you're sitting in the back
listen hit that subscribe button if
you're not subscribed got a strong ass
family now we have a new dog named
Kimberly blue you haven't followed in my
Instagram cuz it's Chris Brody blue how
do you get so many followers so that's
right you stole your dead dogs in what a
piece I'm not gonna lie that that is a
little I think we're on the same page
there he was I didn't want to let kong's
page completely die and be a hundred
percent inactive rather have Broly here
carry on the legacy of young doggy is if
stuff kinda but I don't know I'm just
the boy with the dream the point is this
well he's a good dog he gave him a bath
his first bath yesterday and flashback
now it was super great and we got
Burrell he's super clean but the problem
is that fur guy he was a troublemaking
little shoe we give him another bath
then side note Mike lock his door
he's been locking his door I decided to
bust it open
look the point is this Broly has some
learning curves to do he's a great young
doggie except I quickly realized
something about if girls absolutely love
him I think it's probably the eye with
them why have I not used him to get laid
if I'm being honest just died and you're
using this dog's Instagram right you're
just an ass this was your idea
I feel bad I don't know if we even shoot
the video come on guys okay thank you
hit the like button we've done this
before with Kong Mike actually I picked
up girls may remember seeing it here I'm
falling for you literally way well while
your phones out do you think you could
text me not at all what do you do
actually I kind of do to be honest on my
back you gotta help me get these girls
probably you know I'm gonna feed you all
the best lot
hey let's test it out right now do you
like my dog jokes I swear to God that
was good that was good to go warm up
come on bro Lee
[Music]
I rather like your overalls you like
your overalls are you from
that's very cool I love Australia tell
her that your dog's Australian my dogs
apart Australian actually just uh after
she had a problem with dingoes you have
a problem with dingoes what about
wombats what about wombats Vanek laughs
laughs just like a little bit more
hey ma'am I see that you're moisturizing
your hands would you like to moisturize
this duper by talking to Mike because no
one here
his name is Broly I think it's a husky
like Siberian I'm not gonna hide now you
know now you owe me your phone number
[Music]
obviously cheesy I'm so sorry I've got
two girls coming along with a tote bag
I love tote bags that bags you you know
it's cute are you cuter you
I'm Sal follow-up God uh-huh laughter
there's laughter you've broken through
the ice I got nervous you just got to
say something else after that okay okay
okay I pay follow it up with another
sentence soon oh okay okay okay you can
pat him if you want you don't have to
I'm not making you Jenna oh my god I
knew a girl in high school named Jenna
it's funny because your name rhymes with
Splenda cuz you're sweet your name
rhymes with Splenda cuz you're sweet
Thanks
you like my dog I like my dog I got a
question Jenna are you into youtubers
yeah really like James Charles yeah he's
dope well maybe we could watch some
YouTube together sometime maybe we could
watch some Jeffrey star together
sometime we got a week to watch every
star be honest we could stand here and
do this all day but you only have seven
days so we should probably wrap this up
and can i maybe get your number we like
watched Jeffrey star together
you're so kind in the girl and stuff hit
me up all right we can watch them some J
star you know you're not old like that
where's your husband oh so there's a
room for me in the picture I love your
pants they're flowy like your hair I
love your pants they're flowy like your
hair and your whole vibe is flowy your
hair so long like my nevermind I see you
later
I blew it I blew it I blew it bro I know
I see a little seemed a little young and
stupid but maybe we could watch Netflix
some time with my new dog yeah he's a
husky sure you can pet him
only if I can paint you after
[Music]
did you say something to my dog in
Spanish I'm colorblind so ah what he's
really shy though like having to it once
he's really shy like like having to on
once is really kind of tough for him you
know but I could probably handle it so
man you wanna pet him
Broly tell them you were you were kinda
in the middle of getting this girl's
number
i'ma be honest guys I was kind of in the
middle of getting that number so no it's
fine it's fine just as long as she still
gives it to me we're good so hey what's
good okay so you're dressing all
white-looking I see you dressed in white
like my angel dog lady God
I don't know what they on what to tell
you I know I know I get it
right now he's cute i named him Broly I
was gonna name him destiny I was gonna
knew him destiny but it Burleigh seemed
better because I feel like you're mine
[Music]
group settings are usually tough for me
not always dogs help so your eyes are
helping too
I kind of get lost when I look at you
[Music]
my dog loves pink you know what else
rhymes with pink sing and I think we
look good together
[Music]
subscribe to impulsive ride subscribe
bolts
I got this boys
sorry guys stretching out your quads my
dog has quads maybe we could stress some
quads together sometimes all right
never never used the tree I I just use
this he seemed like nice but you see my
dog my dog he likes to eat yeah he likes
to eat fish I know there's a lot of fish
in the sea but the other one I'm focused
on from Russia we're going to Russia
soon you guys know Putin cuz you guys
are killing it you guys know Putin cuz
you guys are cute and I really think we
got off on the wrong foot during World
War two maybe we could try again yeah I
really feel like we got off on the wrong
foot during World War two and maybe we
could try again no you're historic you
got some baby right Cupid arrow
no just Cupid's arrow Cupid's arrow
children here got an entire school of
fish here
okay that was horrible yeah that was not
good at all I think I got one number
Jenna thank you guys for watching hit
that subscribe button
my dick I love you love gang also hit up
early blue on Instagram he's the new
member of the family he's at 3.1 million
followers it's almost like you took over
a super-sized the camera in a chess
setting know we was here stammering
appear like a deer when the car come in
here in the middle of the row bit of
beer you don't wanna ride but the man
hands off 50 grands counting up is when
I talk to the fans who I could champ it
out with some pin now anybody wanna be
friends yeah
[Music]
I may need to Rebecca