hey before you go can you feed me some
of the cucumber too just like a little
bit boy do I have news for you little
gang are impulsive podcast launches next
Monday we are doing three a week Monday
Wednesday and Friday it's going to be
incredible to make sure to subscribe to
the appositive podcast channel the link
for that is in the description also
another one we did it again drought new
maverick merch Logan Paul that cop slash
shop or link in description 95 what's
[ __ ] good the video you're about to
watch was shot about a month ago we had
to bank it you'll say I don't have the
beard but we've been incredibly busy
shooting other types of content such as
this podcast so enjoy Mike trying to
pick up girls hey yo what's up Logan I'm
gonna dive right into this okay so
getting girls is not easy right
especially if you're Mike today we're
down in Venice Beach
we brought conga savage as you know it's
got a whole little tongue problem going
on there and the newest member of the
family pearl Bingbing the pig now now
because if Mike needs as much help as we
can get we wanted to see how he could
collect more numbers with a few little
Pomeranian or a cute little mini pig do
me a favor
buckle up cuz we got a cutest buckle up
cuz we've got a cutest
like match lack it's awesome you get
those digits brother pearl you got this
baby
I just gotta walk wait what do you mean
why can't you hold her she squeals like
I'm tell her your pink love stripes your
pig loves stripes my pig loves strikes I
thought you meant I thought you meant
can you pet me say let's cut the BS
which one of you is single he's choking
yo Mike don't let those girls run away
you're letting him run away they're
leaving you you failed
oh hi Mike you got a pic in your hands
you got a pig in your hands don't forget
that's your ultimate lady getting tool
guys like pigs yeah she's been checking
you out so if you thought so bye though
to be honest with you she's taking a
picture say I'm a photographer I could
see us together I can picture us
together I'm a photographer too
yeah I could I could picture us together
[Laughter]
abort mission
hey girl and the white girl in the white
she's doing Instagram stuff hey you know
would make your picture a lot cooler a
pig okay
you know that girl Mike feels awkward
cuz he can't get over the pig what's up
what are you doing is that oh my dog we
chasing you guys I think he likes you so
do I call calling slow down slow down
he's pacing here he's chasing here I
think he likes you tell you drop a Lambo
walk cool bro let happen there you go
that's cool that's a cool walk you look
good you look great
that's my boy right though that's your
boy it's both of us rose
Instagram famous dog can get in your
pictures where you guys from oh you are
I was just over there for that uh you
know that youtuber Logan Paul say you
personally hate Logan Paul I'm not a fan
of him I the kid
he's a dude no no it's okay no I'm not
friends at least I hate him he's a
douchebag no it's not funny at all
pretty much yeah yeah let me and let me
take your number to jump up and down and
celebrate that you got her number say
say this is how we're gonna dance
tonight at the club this I'm gonna dance
tonight at the club so you're taking
pictures you want to take some of this
Instagram famous Pig
she's got like half a million on
Instagram I you guys have a good day was
your boyfriend
it was her boyfriend I was completely
wrong dude well I could tell the way he
looked at her and the way he looked at
the pig he eats bacon you wanna trade
dog for a skateboard for a minute yeah I
just want to skate around hey Paul Paul
a fall fall on the skateboard towards
the dead Oh
like say you scraped your knee falling
for her I scrape I scrape my knee for
you I'm falling for you literally wait
well while your phone's out do you think
you could text me like I hate you off
sometime not at all what do you do
actually yeah I kind of do to be honest
or like it could just be like a doggy
playdate for like your dog and my dog
yeah yeah oh my god it was good meeting
you he's amazed Matt he's amazed look at
him go look at him just running in the
grass that's amazing pretty sure you
said I scraped my knee yeah it's almost
like someone gave me I scraped my knee
falling for you yeah that's a pig
do you wanna powder what are you guys
doing tonight
we have no idea yes would you would you
want to hang out the pig tonight so
maybe we can call you okay sure so it's
a I'll put mine in right now hey before
you go can you feed me the cucumber I'm
a little hungry hey before you go can
you feed me some of the cucumber too
just like a little bit thank you thank
you bye call me
damn bro as much as I hate to say it it
looks like Kong to savages the winner is
that Tong bro just undeniable Tong you
did a good job pearl Bingbing I can't
help think it's because Kong has more
Instagram followers where I'm just
saying I'm just saying so go follow a
programming on instagram below that
subscribe button if you have not
subscribed yet at hey Big Mike there's
your plug is gonna go on some dates
tonight my dudes out there you guys want
to get some girls you don't have a pearl
Bing Bing or conga savage you are in
luck I have the news go to your keyboard
and type in logan paul dot-com slash
shop and cop your self the hottest
softest merch in the game with that said
guys I will see you next time low gang I
love you I messed up the order of that
outro I'm just gonna do this
[Music]