hey guys how are you okay I'm gonna
break this down we came to my brother's
house because as you guys know we're
having a 20% off sale on mattress this
weekend only Memorial Day weekend yeah
yeah we just got five new pieces to fly
together sure to be a maverick sure it's
a hottest merch in the game starting to
move me it's all across the globe people
who are doing themselves I like people
like you do you and I'm gonna do me like
I'm a maverick I'm over here I'm doing a
difference a movement of people who go
right when they go left like Andy's
doing right now okay look guys the point
is excited about it because fire bro
look at me give a quick pan up and down
bro oh my god I'm finna that's it Logan
fall calm /op or link in description
anyways guys I came to my brother's
house and I look around I realize he's
not here he's not here he's on tour he's
on his on his team tent tour the house
is essentially empty right now I
actually can kind of plan for this I
think I'm gonna be Jake Paul for the day
and I'm gonna call my brother's out
[Music]
classic blocking out the haters dab on
him glasses he's snowboarding goggles
that for some reason he doesn't wear
when he's snowboarding we're
front-facing they're always on the side
of his head I found that interesting and
then the team checked the hat to top it
up that Jake how you doing what's up
Jake you look like Jake
a little perturbed that my dad actually
looks good in this bro the winds hitting
him the perfect way right now
don't know
[Music]
Oh feels good to be no kitchen this way
I put food in my stomach
we got eggs oh not anymore
gotcha I won't be honest with you I'm
not believing him Jay Paul I'm really
not besides having blond hair what else
does he have tattoos sword on his back
oh and a tattoo you you guys saw
yesterday's vlog
Clyde Daniels interviewed some college
kids about who's gonna win the KS
average Logan Paul fight ksi versus
Logan Paul who's gonna win and why he's
lugging pool training I heard he's
training yeah there's a pretty general
consensus the people who spoken i'ma
beat can size ass sweaty back that's cuz
I'm urges so far
if you wanna be a Jaipur maggot a jig
that you had some lunch with aliens
Maine I would warm Oh super Ziggy what's
going on here
so I feel like if I really want to be
jig Paul I gotta get that infamous Jay
Paul back tattooed yes look oh my god
very infamous tattoo there right it's a
big sword and it's and it's big to live
and to die this war a broadsword do
never die by the sword
you really can't like see it we should
go to my room and check it out quick I'm
[Music]
damn it feels good to be a gangster I
got shoes on shoes I'm close I'm close
all my favorite my Gucci jacket that I
wore my video was gucci mane why are you
like you I'm Jay Paul I don't need your
[ __ ] cuz I have my girlfriend Erica
Jimmy up Erica she's Erica casa
she lives in herself let me go baby
thank you
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Jake you forgot your favorite hat
[Music]
I accidentally need an e in the face
yeah you mean the world to me how does a
cig be bro bien je crois is a lot of
work and I'm getting hot
[Music]
documented everywhere
[Applause]
[Music]
well that overall I think well I think
with pretty well and by well I mean that
was that was a disaster
well that was never really mad that was
half my I'm mostly my fault I feel like
there was definitely a better spot to
put the dummy not gonna live when you're
standing inside looking out it looks
much worse you guys do think Jake will
see in this video no I don't like being
JD the wall you said you could get a
shoe I don't know what the hell out or
outside Jake Smurfs store you can see it
says it right there
and I just figured I'd leave him some of
the hottest merch in the game you know
20% off on Memorial Day weekend this
weekend oh no Paul that console a shop
Jake you don't even have to go there bro
I'm gonna hook you up right now you
thank me
[Music]
I'm on the track
I don't forget
try to keep me
I'm all ready so don't fall asleep okay
now that that's done why would some
stuff for some manual labor and how did
this get here is if you're gonna do dumb
you gotta take responsibility for your
actions
Jake I'm sorry bro I didn't them gave
having the gun honestly looks better
than the original I agree I'm a glass
half-full kind of guy
or should we say a glass fully missing
hello gang that is the vlog if you guys
know the front of the lobby I do not
forget 24/7 this weekend only Memorial
they say oh we're not doing this get it
while the iron is hot before the glass
break that's what I'm saying the lesson
learned today guys is is only one person
I can be Jay Paul and that is shameful I
love you both okay I love you too and I
will see you tomorrow
a positive this now we know that Jake's
window is a potato proof so it's like
now we can get them way potato proof
windows don't fall asleep