what we can do because Aaron the car
wash please Aaron gonna do this
off-camera but I feel like I'm just
gonna do it huh uh-huh yeah sorry about
that
wow you guys have exceeded my
expectation as you know this past
weekend we relaunched maverick clothing
and you guys went crazy we are
officially sold out of the crewnecks the
hoodies and the shorts and I know I know
you're heartbroken so much we got to
understand I have not released like a
product clothing anything in over a year
so I didn't know how how well I do and
it looks like you guys are loving it I
also can't wait for you to actually feel
this stuff it is literally some of the
highest quality clothing in the world
yeah we're working on restocking so you
guys can get more of it the t-shirts are
still available and for everyone who
joined the Maverick Club that's like a
separate thing and I'm so excited to
curate very special experiences for you
guys you don't know what I'm talking
about where you want some of the drip go
to map clothing comm join the movement
because at the end of the day that's
what it is and I'm pumped to see
everyone rockin the clothes now we had a
pretty kick-ass Memorial Day weekend
this morning for example was great we
had dogs by the pool we had logs by the
pool and we even have skin hogs by the
pool he just loves whenever I kiss him
in front of other people Mike sister
looks like the female version of mine
they're identical David but I'm about to
prove it the girl felt they're on
snapchat that's gonna be my secret
weapon and sister and brother okay now
just face the camera oh my god oh my god
are you hurts more to get backhanded
forward you tell me okay and also stop
hold I'm a bad friend cuz he took the
sign down we got the sign in the first
place that's it AB you going the wrong
she deserved it
don't even get me started are you
kidding me don't look at him in the eyes
Abby don't look at her in the eyes Abby
quarters Oh ladies right there ladies
stop video mark oh that's awesome this
is like the only time I could ever have
because she may see like a drop off only
fans Erin I knew this would come in
handy
six months ago I bought this chastity
belt at the flea market actually with
Josie dr. Polanski's approved Wow no one
getting in there except me yeah take it
off you when you get back
have a nice day feel much better about
that the woman's made a massive mistake
and that is she left her dog here her
dog Ronnie you see Ronald's a wiener dog
so I think it's only appropriate if we
put her in a hot dog bun why is this so
natural for me yes cuz you were meant to
be a hot dog isn't as in pickles okay if
you're anything like me you've always
wondered whether a zebra is white with
black stripes or black with white
stripes
the answer is black base and I'm about
to prove to you think I got the chance
I ain't gonna waste and y'all know
zebras can swim people bigger than you
can just toss you around put puns on you