hey puppies I got that good good for you
today is a very special day for me guys
so six kids from the make-a-wish
Foundation have chosen to meet me that
was their wish which is absolutely
insane guys like I grew up hearing about
the make-a-wish Foundation seeing the
amazing things that they do that's what
I'm saying bro I don't know but they
chose me and it's crazy
most kids choose like LeBron James
real-life like big celebrities and like
I get it like I'm on my way there one
day but right now it's just like I don't
know it's mind-blowing and it's also
cool cuz my brother Jake is gonna be
there you guys know Jake yeah people we
tried to kill him yesterday here's our
flash the thing is he made me his
beneficiary for his life insurance
policy so if he died I would get his
money but that side story I'm getting
sidetracked anyways hey yo good morning
okay good Bob if you're not a part of
the logging you could make sure to
subscribe hopefully I can meet you one
day you guys know I love meeting you and
meeting these six kids today is gonna be
absolutely life-changing for me and
hopefully them I've never done a
make-a-wish before I've never been the
wish I've just been making wishes when I
was a kid in Ohio about filling these
crazy dream and it come true so I know
what it's like to have your wishes and
dreams come true my goal is to give
these kids with critical illnesses hope
and strength and something to look
forward to to beat and overcome whatever
it is they're going through with that
said it's time to dab a baby
yo we got the whole arcade to ourselves
apparently they lock like the whole
floor down also Dave & Buster's this is
not a free brand deal you owe me money
mother imma send you an invoice to the
maverick enterprises or you can get to
Mercer looking back on so yo that's
super cool but we got some kids in the I
don't know where my kids are but the
only person I really know here is
probably Jake I think um we'd like
yesterday we just like try to kill him
how are you I'm good you guys still
alive I see so as much fun it is to beat
up Jake I'm not here for you we're here
for the kids I know that it's a holiday
but I ain't the same without you BAE
it's been awhile since I saw your face
and not me seeing you remember when we
carved on me in December when the wind
came it's been a while since I saw your
face wish I was kissing you like cocoa
on a Christmas morning
skip the presents yeah oh oh oh I wonder
I was been in California do you remember
red challenge I'm having back real
maverick
I'm having a good day I'm gonna make
Logan comment below if we didn't see the
cool bus so we headed there we got
costume trouble we go be Mavericks
that's what we do bro this is quite an
experience
the lights are up if everyone could stay
here one second I have a song I think
you'd like girl what you tryna to cuz I
don't got a clue no I know Scalini
I just wanna get some food in you about
to kill me
I don't know if this is structurally
sound
we should literally all fall to the
ground right now thanks that was legit
eating all these kids on top of my bus
I'm just imagining like just how much
money I could be sued for absolutely
amazing oh well you guys can stay up
here I'm gonna go home
it was really nice hanging out with all
of you I love each and every one of you
hold on super tight especially you cuz
you look kind of tiny
help me help Tom just kidding guys we
set up proper goodbyes we dipped we're
back home he's pretty dope meeting those
kids I hope they thought the same thing
about me probably not though all right
Lydia I'm gonna do this for you okay cuz
I got just the guy long story short
Lydia's earring has submerged itself in
her ear I'm assuming cuz we're always
yelling Lydia and the earrings like I'm
out dip her earring is stuck in her ear
like cartilage I think you know oh yeah
you are and pull out the back yeah
no because how'd it go in through the
front so the hole in the back is gonna
be smooth so that is like an arrow when
it goes in like that you just got to do
otherwise you're gonna get infected and
die I know more surgical guys you see
the title of this vlog it's not about me
it's not about Lydia's ear it's about
young dog big day today's the day you're
gonna lose your virginity so guys we
found the female version of Kong
literally this dog looks exactly like
Kong but with the vagina and I wanted to
do this vlog for so long we send Kong on
a day look at him go
he's gonna go on a real life date with
this dog and it's gonna be absolutely
amazing she is on her way we got chef
Andy actually gonna cook pasta later
okay guys Lulu is here I will say her
owners are Brazilian they're pretty
spicy oh my gosh the female version of
the hatred thing going on this is
actually pretty cute he's disgusting
right now he's dirty he's been running
around in the yard all day listen guys
I'm not giving up just yet can you guys
come back later I don't want to bathe
okay okay buddy it's time to get sex I
want to do this thing that I like to do
with him cuz it's funny that's just a
good time for me no doggy likes a dirty
dog thing we need to add a little bit of
flowers you know he's gonna have a
romantic night you know what starts off
right ends up ha ha ha sex I've never
seen calm looking so happy ahh gotta get
the butthole not much to Kong Hong Kong
is mostly fluff
in the will you be an angel for a
helpless animal you'll help rescue
animals from their abusers
okay cogs not quite in his element he
has some cleaning to do so we're gonna
wait for him to dry off oh my god I was
in your ear oh my god that was gross
I realized a little boy okay that was
disgusting now it's time for young
doggies
yeah yeah
my boys ready to smash she's ready to go
look outside
we got the most beautiful setting for a
dog day ever the red roses the white
roses the electric candle surrounded in
a serene atmosphere full of love lust
and passion not to mention the best way
during the game yeah yours truly of the
Maverick Oh God okay here you go young
doggy it's your big day
my boys gonna smash
he's running he's a little shy you could
see him out there he's kind of he's a
little timid okay so Lewis here we're
gonna present her to Kong in the only
way we know how
Oh easy easy
Oh what the no he's going for
oh yes Lulu's not having it definitely
not having Kong you gotta take me out to
dinner first good thing we got the best
ship in the games on the menu no its
cogs big day just real quick there's
only one thing on the menu and it's
pasta so andis making pasta we got one
thing on the menu that's possible but I
would be a crappy server if I didn't go
check on my clients right now I'm sure
they're getting hungry
maybe that's why Lou is so sexually
frustrated so let's do this hey guys
just checking in on you
I brought the menus here there's one
thing you can order it's pasta I'm gonna
go ahead and set these down in front of
you and just let me know when you're
ready all right Luke's coat looks like
the chilling I feel like I know what
they want from the menu literally takes
a whole nother meaning to bone Appetit
others Marc perfect oh wow this pasta
weighs more than both of those dogs
combined yeah actually maybe not Lulu
she's kind of chunky we cut ourselves a
lot of Boston
hey puppies I got that good good for you
he's going on doggy
oh wow
hey Lulu I noticed you're not eating
maybe it's because there's no parmesan
tell me when just tell me when just tell
me when
guys because of indigestion reasons I
think you're gonna [ __ ] this also you
keep beating someone take this away oh
my gosh Wow who knows what's gonna
happen guys if you're not part of the
Logan make sure to subscribe who knows
but women have called baby's coming soon
y'all so smack the subscribe button in
the face for me and hop your maverick
merch the hottest softest merch in the
game no one doesn't like us there's
literally no family on YouTube that can
even capiche yeah Logan Paul calm slash
shop or link in description little gang
I love your nose
there's