hi I'm Jake Paul and you're watching a
bunch of [ __ ] so ride my ranch right
now it's like my favorite spot on the
planet I'll do a proper tour soon show
you guys everything we're still
finishing some stuff up but honestly
it's so beautiful here like the sky is
so blue the clouds are so pretty
sometimes you can like see certain
things in the sky in the clouds the
nature is just like untouched in this
water this is fresh stream water then I
got out of the stream earlier then we
put it in this bottle and I'm about to
drink you're in for a treat
that's [ __ ] girl
what what the [ __ ] did I just say you
trying to complete that sentence it was
more disappointing than my rock searcher
I've done this I've seen this I know
what you're gonna do squeezy square my
face and I'm I going and tick-tock
tick-tock there's like 20 million people
I don't even know why let's be nice
being this your dad just blue okay I'll
do my second favorite son cuz you love
Jake more you can tell me I don't care
mom's always like dig more divorce Birds
drama are you wait what what is that
what why I'm thirty twenty five and four
days twenty five years old I was getting
married oh no I'm such a failure this is
horrifying married at 25 years old
haha Jake's a little depressed why he
came to the race to try to like escape
the sadness and every now and then you
can hear him doing the whoop-whoop
effect all you're gonna do is woot-woot
clouds you come free time and then you
put a smile on your face or you'll end
up laughing it's supposed to make you
happy it tasted fury said it worked how
long to you depressed again social
distancing how you doing Dave girl yeah
you know that dance we learned when we
were kids try to approach me stop don't
touch me there this is my private square
so this morning I had my dad excavate a
little stream behind me so we could have
a boat race we each had about an hour to
build their own little homemade boats
now the winner of the race gets a
hundred dollars but unfortunately the
loser gets this gallon of green paint
dumped on there the first boat to make
it down the stream avoid all the
obstacles and make it to the finish line
win if your boat gets stuck you can
throw one rock to save it no cheating or
you get two points subtracted from your
score for you Jack Reese's that's pretty
much it so let's meet the racers this
macklin Bilski you got the little batty
here here's me captain the boat to
victory so watch out boys this is the
Santa Korn Tina's boat is built for
speed precision and self propulsion when
the water gets in this little bag it's
gonna act like an engine and at that
point I will win something for the first
time in my life I am Jay Paul this is my
boat the boats name is I'm hungover
depressed and heartbroken because my
girlfriend dumped me because I'm an
idiot Julia if you're watching this
please take me back as if you're in a
relationship don't take what you have
for granted
no no no looks like it's gonna be a
photo finish
just kidding it's not cuz um doh hey I'm
son congratulations you've got a 100
bucks
I just coming laughs this is Morgan the
[ __ ] fight let me down you go
this is literally the worst week of my
life
that sucks bro cuz I feel like it's
about to get much worse hi I'm Jake Paul
and you're watching a bunch of bull
[Music]
what do you came up here and you're like
what can we paint into a green screen
you're invisible oh I mean well your
heads not but you're covered in green
paint
now you're Julie race Jake I love you so
much I'll take you back I forgive you
nice do you think Julie is really gonna
take me back it's okay brother we're
gonna survive this quarantine together
yes we are
[Music]