you guys ever get bullied do you guys
ever have people make fun of you do you
ever have someone call you out publicly
like in front of everyone to her it
really does especially when it's from
someone that you love so I just want to
say I think a mistake has been made and
it's unfortunate that the beef not has
to be unleashed because this video will
be the death of Jake ball so I am amped
right now doesn't know why soon but I
can't tell you just yet come over here
yeah yeah yeah cause hi buddy
good morning pop good morning what are
you having your mouth Oh maverick I'm
coming hold on what sec I gotta stop you
I guess you can't go on this carpet okay
little up they had an audition this
morning well got deep almost crying with
him on that actor like hey I'm coming
I love hello yeah yeah that's calling I
said come on buddy you guys are gonna
bother come no more tomfoolery dawg I'm
maverick on my shoulder you guys can
pause I don't know I'm coming oh I'm the
pickle in the middle right now how come
you need a chill you need a chill I know
I know you got a stop puppy this is why
maverick doesn't like you - you're
trying to bite it he's just a bird look
looking at me so is the subscribe to me
bro us do anything ok I don't know what
his deal is I'll be honest with all I
know is you're my boy getting you the og
I give me kiss mmm yeah ok just this
this is what I was amped about earlier
than I kind of reference and it's live
now I'm literally looking at it Jake
released a diss track of saying the low
gang sucks
why straight-up he assaulted the family
like and I think it's bad okay while I
lowered it for Ella I knew this was
coming guys this why I was so high
because you know we're gonna hit back
harder baby he has no idea no yo
literally like it's gonna be better I'm
gonna take it way too far
oh so here's the hair thing before we
play this video Jake like nah man will
you treat your fans like shishun which i
think is bad and why would you use them
both well I would hope you're gonna get
yeah like bro you know I'm better to add
pretty much everything except YouTube
you're very good you to recognize but
when it comes to a creative talent like
music what a video
whatever it is like Rob's better and
like now I have to destroy you like
before I even watch the videos I have to
destroy it was a warning we're only
doing this because what if you did you
try to come back with another song we're
gonna roast you and all the way you come
back today after you watch this because
if you take two days to do it then
you're just a [ __ ] oh lucky for you
Jake Paul you have a rat on team ten
yeah someone told me you were making a
song so I could plan a day ahead you
better look into who's your friend who's
not I did salty over there hey but they
have more talent than you could ever
dream of a truly Incas man just get up
only thing worse than your song is on I
[Music]
like yo I don't get mad Logan this is
beyond me he's insulting us I don't I
don't get mad her don't but I'm not
gonna lie Jake you did good you you've
made you rat of me I'm I'm not sure but
I'm rattled and then I guess color let's
hope so because this is very rookie come
on Giggy dental okay okay this is better
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh it's getting worse as it goes I was
like not gonna lie almost sounds like
he's just trying to rhyme it bro it's
like he's trying Jake you have no rhythm
stop like imma put you to sleep
yummy yummy up go now I'm just announced
to harmful [ __ ] you up
can you watch running from the cops
nice simile Jake good rhymes Duke make a
better song [ __ ] no much that's the
hook myself Instagram I thought for like
20 minutes of how else I could roast
myself and that's all I got oh don't
worry I'll handle the rest yeah I'll
handle the rest to you they said help me
help you make a better song so why don't
we make a better song great why don't we
make a better song with why don't we
this song is going to be tasteful and
since this came out today we like I
think that's today's vlog I think it's
going to be the Jay Paul diss track in
the making of it so let's get started
off to a good start taking the rolls to
the writing session yeah yeah yo this is
fire bro yes the suicide doors okay so
I'm just like I'm found concocting
lyrics in my head he's so Jake is so ro
stable and one of the lyrics and Jake's
song he always it he's like yo I'm gonna
roast myself and I thought for sure he'd
lift like a couple thing but he said
that he has less Instagram followers me
of course I have to rap about allegro
there's so many things Jake I just I
thought we were brothers bro like you
made a crappy song and I just pointed it
out and I didn't I didn't need to you're
right everyone already knew we liked
bros what are you doing oh and we have
arrived we got the blue lights for
ambiance we got all the equipment we
need we got the key boy got a laptop I
hi guys I'm going to do hives over I
just like I'm I'm fired up this is all
happening today go beat the lyrics the
recording the mix the master the music
video in one day so we just got to go
Jake makes a big deal about making songs
in one day that obviously reflects the
quality of his work but like guys it's
not hard you can make a song one day
we're going to do it today and it's
gonna be nine times better than Jake's
so yeah bro let's do this see Jake this
is cus crafting our beats we're making
this right now I'm not going on YouTube
and typing in like freestyle
instrumental oh my god bro I thought
like this is perfect this is dope this
is it we're going with this low gang so
then we have a plan it's going to get
nice and I'm going to make up with my
brother why can't we just leave brothers
and love each other man that's how we
want to do and I get to sing a little
bit but then it's going to go back to
the road session because you upset me
Jake zero okay data fire yo thank you
for the ride I do have a meeting right
now and look who shows it's agent Paul I
need to join us do you know what's going
down right now what I do know is this is
me this is dope it's um it's a BMW this
is a Rolls it's like a definitely a
thing can I tell you something bro after
we do a bunch of movies together like I
will buy you a dope car on the vlog I'm
gonna hold you to this help me to it
roll right out let's go you're the agent
it's on you you can really move my boy
that's love ball did you see the roast I
respect it let me machine I told I'm
like it's good it's funny it's like okay
like I'll throw up this time bro the
Maverick we are Mavericks you're Jake
bro I'm writing these lyrics down and
they're good I think they're pretty good
anyway with her lid there okay I told
the jab they're pretty good because I'm
a creative and I feel like this I can
finally unleash my creative potential
but to be honest I feel I could go so
much harder I'm just going to keep it
like sort of like no no just unleash I
die with my boys
hey boy so I'm assuming you heard the
song and and did you see he called you a
Walmart one direction did you see it I
mean at least we can sell take it oh
yeah Jake you remember when you did a
team Zen tour and you could sell any
tickets
anyways rope messing with me obviously
in the low gang is one thing and now I
gotta bring in the assassins like come
on Jake I'm actually good at music oh my
god hosting we did but actually not yet
we have to go to a musically thing yeah
back in the car I'm taking every
opportunity I have today to write the
hideous heat ever and plus I got the BTS
beat ever yah oh this is awkward I
definitely the wrong song now we talked
today okay guys we are about at this
musically event I'm hosting it whatever
that means but regardless you know it's
gonna be dealt hey okay we were out the
music leave it bro I'm out yeah yeah I
can amount a lot of lot of users room
you guys can use it a lot of MU 0 so
it's like kind of popping out here but
we got to do some stuff in here for some
people say that I'm bad at math like
yesterday I taught myself Oh Jo Wow
say this again brothers looky here looks
exactly like using my joke this is it do
any Logan that yo wait like yo the
airport with your name Jesus Hunter you
have to think there's your hunter this
is that the French if he wants to do
sake this is me this is me that's me we
love pretty take marker no I
is due to its low game devices no that's
what I like to hear from how much work I
order my god got the merch on Zach bro
wait did you get any way to 20% off your
system our guy you can still get it link
in description shameless plug always fun
with your low back communist trim at
Logan fall on right now do what I was
going to do they all watch my blog you
haven't missed a vlog in 70 days I'm
watching everything you do without a je
crois guy like oh I have a fan page for
you I think take off he's like you
through my nose and Disney oh yeah I
don't know they put me on the world is
the wall of fame I'm gonna walk
but guys is my name hashtag be America
hello guys my name is Massimo I was
listening
[Music]
I'm taking these with the cake oh
they're gonna be roasting here bro why
do you know gang we are about to leave
but there is one thing I have to do
first if you look up top way in the
corner that's a picture if you look
closely it's a picture of my little
sister back at the boys house the Sun is
setting this is beautiful oh my gosh yes
such a good time of day to start a roast
session you guys ever get bullied do you
guys ever have people make fun of you do
you ever have someone call you out
publicly like in front of everyone -
hurts it really does especially when
it's from someone that you love so I
just want to say I think a mistake has
been made and it's unfortunate that the
beef not has to be unleashed because
this video will be the death of Jay Paul
I'm focused that's how I'm feeling
I'm very unfocused feels good I'm
excited to do it like I have not been
able to get creative like this and push
myself like this creatively like in a
long time so Jake I do want to thank you
for that bro this is fun for me did not
so much for you but this is going to be
done what happened Jake man we used to
love each other after all we came from
the same mother sometimes I wish my real
brother was dark but now I gotta go and
put you in the dirt yeah yes this yo
that's the radio I like that
that slow let me let me try a couple of
tho two hours later still doing my own
voiceovers okay guys back home I'm with
the man Kong I haven't seen you all day
buddy and apparently you don't give a
[ __ ] okay oh this song and like I
honestly don't have words for it I think
it's going to speak for itself and
obviously I apologize for the lack of
vlog today I had stuff to take care of
obviously tomorrow we are shooting the
music video for it I didn't want to rush
and try to do in one day and let Jake
like antagonize me because you guys know
this the quality of my work is not like
low I try to make it the best it can be
all the time and that does not exclude
this so yeah tomorrow we're shooting the
music video it's going to be awesome and
one last thing for us sign up as usual
be a maverick bro I said all the time I
love you guys like genuinely love
you guys you watch my content you
support me the jig's video has like
nearly a hundred thousand likes just
people from the low gang thing they
don't like it it means the world man
that you guys got my back like that so
if you're not family make sure you
subscribe and I will see you guys
tomorrow when the roast session begins I
take it easy stab bruised
[Music]
Wow
yes I'm just capable I'm not your dad
you don't do desert