[Music]
Dougy you guys know this car runs away
like every single day use my brain and I
got an electric fence so I'm done with
car running way that's gonna shock this
started buddy located okay look he
already knows feisty little dog listen
here's the thing calling we love you I
love you the low gang loves you I can't
have you running away Dubrow he's a
savage it's in his name calling to
savage oh I just don't want him to run
away guys it sucks seeing him get shot
but literally when he runs away guys
like I've gotten it's been a miracle
every single time that I've found him
hey Kong don't you want to come over
here and be free now I'd be a bad owner
if I didn't experience this myself
dangerous family on YouTube what setting
is this one on how it works
don't worry buddy we're in this together
the worst no I think we broke long
what's wrong you guys we walked inside
and he hasn't moved for like ten minutes
I feel so bad
Oh buddy why do you look like you're
gonna die it's okay mommy oh my gosh
I've never seen him like this he's like
a statue he's not moving I don't think
he knows where he can go oh god this is
a disaster
[Music]
yo terrified we got him tested for the
electric fence bro
yeah he's scared he doesn't know where
he can go but what do we want no dog or
a scared dog that's actually eight okay
I have a meeting to go to but obviously
I lost young doggies trust a little bit
this is the trust building exercise
three two one gotcha okay now my turn I
don't know if he can catch you get you
you mojo again okay it's time to connect
some business bro
the maverick enterprises he's terrified
bro we shot he needs time to recover and
he needs his daddy okay it's time to
make billions of dollars lo game we will
see what trillions of dollars logo
but--there they play it's later big
moves business moves so good stuff bro I
made a million dollars in that last hour
just kidding but one day hopefully I can
say that um okay yo Andy you guys
remember he's back and I know my boy he
wants to return with a bang Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so much guys Annie is the perfect
[Music]
oh it's good to have you back hindi I
thought I'm extra bro you might be the
most extra person I know what I love it
yeah so much fun that's so much fun
brother mariachi band oh oh you know you
know what you know what they're missing
[Music]
neon hoodie we'll keep all that cops
last shot crucial be a member
[Music]
go already playing batter I can
it's all good vibes good energy here and
he's eating snow that's fine don't tell
him that it's fine to tell he thought it
was over nope LP vlogs just getting
started Elijah last time I saw you was
it was rehearse your eyes for the og low
gangster high or ordained I didn't marry
you I married you to you officiate
officiated their wedding flashback I now
pronounce you husband and wife you may
kiss the bride
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I can legally do that in the state
of Nevada anyways these guys had an idea
today they brought what did you do you
cut off the top and we want to make this
vehicle iconic we want it to be like you
know you know it's something I'm very
good at yes you trust me to paint this
thing with you buddy I trust you to
marry my wife and I who did that are you
today and there's nothing to spend your
money on with Logan Paul Andy Andy paid
for the Mariachi band any bought this
this is the type of thing that just
makes the neighbors love me put this
thing on eBay so the links gonna be in
the box you're probably gonna make money
someone's gonna buy it but you're gonna
make some cash the logo goes hard
[Music]
this is actually cool the colors cool I
like these guys are great
[Music]
yo you mister your people were here
she's weights people they they were
Mexican hmm kind of because the music
originated from Spain they came over to
Mexico
see now racist lean Loganville evil
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't believe this actually looks good
I'm gonna be so rich afterward
one-of-a-kind masters not just yet Oh
[Music]
perfect done any idea what I'm gonna
write
I definitely ruin the whole thing it's
good yeah it's great Judy we think give
it a moment of relax
[Music]
subete not chess Staley got the freedom
to go be the man at the TV your mom are
you in the low gang
that's my girl cool
well that's we did their car paint
Leonardo da Vinci I what's happening
next okay time for the big to meet the
meat of the day no no your silly goose
I'm talking about the video that's my
bad if you guys don't know my brother
Jake he just released a Christmas album
homie ah I'm releasing a Christmas song
- it's a Christmas distress call make
sure that was the thing I copied you but
I did know I look the point is there's a
song on his album called the jingle Paul
like a play on words like jingle bells
jingle Paul's and he asked me to be on
the track anyways I said no Jake asked
me to be on his track and I said no I'm
not doing it Jake
and when I check out the Christmas album
last night what do I see jingle Paul's
featuring l0 Gann Paul it gets me bro
Jake what are you doing what I told you
know we're gonna listen to it and react
cuz I can only imagine what this kid did
in the cool bus cuz the acoustics in
here are phenomenal let's listen to this
song go oh god damn it
[Music]
[Applause]
gorilla what do you mean that wasn't me
no returning to be me
[Music]
[Laughter]
we talked about the fact that Jay Paul's
done something funny oh oh I bro I guess
that's the next best thing to do when I
tell you I don't want to be on your song
do you ever gone 13 I've never done that
I know what Jake needs honestly you know
any news bro this kid needs some a
verged I feel like it would just cure
him it would just make him just awesome
Jake Jake you know this bro you can get
your man of mercy look upon that cop
slash shopping okay that is a fun one
today you're surprised I'm actually
presenting a tie the Jingle Ball tonight
so you may see your boy on TV we're not
allowed to film that Brendon I'm sorry
they won't let you come oh I'm throwing
Demi lavato on stage Brendan just I know
you're not a part of the low gang I've
said this before you suck but the good
news is you can unsub as long as you
subscribe for real though copy maverick
so I can bother comes my shop it's that
hot itself this merch in the game who's
doing it baby the answer is no one so
many people have joined the movement at
this point it's like who's not a part of
the Maverick movement now I think the
best way to sign this vlog off leg dabs
to my brothers song to get a hand up
Brenda this guilty pleasure gotta get a
car alive
gotta get rid of this filth in sweat I
need all the order can hand over bulla
Burra never live together now look back
at that board show no grin fast-paced
when a crook back to Florida all wins
and a half your face got shook after
they feel supposed to put the pins back
in that last place and they stood act
like show but [ __ ] still sitting in the
glass Kate
[Music]