it's everyday bro
[Music]
I made all of us this morning comes with
Park other one feeling this morning
about the park I love the bar yo 2017
was absolutely incredible upon watching
this vlog I want you to make a promise
that you're gonna make 2018 the best
year of your life in fact attack every
single year trying to make it the best
year of your life
hey yo good morning we are here in Tokyo
Japan guys I feel so good right now last
night we went out there's a bit weird
starting the year like this first for me
that was weird if you don't know what
I'm talking about guys we found a dead
body hanging in the Japanese suicide
forest I planned on ending 2017 but
life's about the journey I'm glad you
guys get to live with me if you're not a
part of the love gang bang what you
could start your year off right join the
family learn how to work harder smarter
better faster stronger and smack the
subscribe button in the face the
movement that we started is no joke baby
bird
I said this in yesterday's video guys it
is okay to be different
in fact I encourage you to be different
because it's the crazy ones who changed
the world you don't want to end up like
a drone you don't want to fit in the
norm be the black sheep be a maverick
with that says Tokyo we got stuff to do
let's go take over Tokyo Lidia is
watching comm ya Gong hi buddy talking I
love you I'll see you in 2018 bye Lydia
you have a good New Year or else you're
fired
bye bye y'all 2018 is definitely the
year of the Maverick in the car right
here I was just thinking we have done so
much as a brand and apparently guys
don't forget I started
I have a friend on my birthday April 1st
of last year 2018 be crazy bro the
Maverick enterprises growing we're
different we're special past me we're
unique the point is it's real I cannot
wait for you guys to see the new stuff
for coming out with you just garden
everybody as we transition from merch to
apparel to big year bro you guys got to
make it big - big goals big dreams big
dick I'm geeking out right now when I
was younger this was my life the Game
Boy Color I'm actually losing my mind
bro Japan is like a king of anime and
games I'm sorry I'm just a vlogger and
the epicenter of Pokemon of Ziya love
book my so I'll take all your poke are
these pokemons
these are all the Japanese Oh perfect
how much 9,500 yes I'll give you my
I'm pretty good negotiator my gameboy
it's now it's like it's totally broken
my childhood it's not funny
ah why you could have returned it huh
the game seems to be malfunctioning much
Oh broken
okay forget Game Boy another model it's
a pocket model but I have a different
idea how does he feel my Pokemon needs
my man friend it was a little excited
he's already oh my god bro this is just
hilarious we need to bring these
costumes back to LA why am I still
talking let's get just up it's going
down we also got this pokeball before we
get started I want to say one thing
yeah sushi has a little secret no I know
you don't bro how's the dumpster what is
that what do you have why can I catch
him what kind of Pokemon gotta catch em
all yo this makes me miss maverick bro I
miss all my pad it's really an amazing
experience and with an owl in Japan hi
we're gonna be pokemons okay relax
yo we got to be active for the vlog I
know Snorlax sleeps and ain't no Andy
Andy what are you doing here in the
middle of street bro well so I wake up
Monday anak wake up we got trouble the
college merged itself Toyota I chewed
[Music]
now you'll never catch a mouse watch
this catch you okay got to go
honey get us oh you big guy in the
movies in the shows is different you
would throw the ball and they like get
caught by it like they go inside of it I
think this is defective pokeball
Charizard
wait is that imma catch you I choose you
yeah I feel like what can you do Melisa
Raney you apply right now
now and you're working Utah and I come
on you I will say and I've never seen a
Snorlax Gucci now I've been in
situations like this before
alright so we started with Pokemon
today's a bit of like a sentimental day
for me guys when I came to Tokyo like
two years ago to do a split I show up
it's midnight I'm by myself
I'm exhausted but I'm like yo I'm in
Tokyo I'm gonna go out and explore and
just see what I find it's crazy for -
country since the first spot I stumbled
right here right here on these signs
it's called kabuki here check us out I
took an Instagram picture oh guys by
myself I sent my phone I'm on a tripod
stood right here with my pants down
anyways I really like this place so I'm
gonna recreate the picture
[Music]
[Applause]
you know it's the grand bro man guys
were cute run in your space
run why Fiji Fuji Mount Fuji I'm here
look at ya tell me we don't look cutest
yo this is beautiful dude look at us
guys good friends I found this kid what
do you have nobody will recognize you
with one of your fans
exactly yeah this is crazy bro he tells
me yo is that is that Jake ball
I think it's me Jake ball it's everyday
guys we're gonna head back to hotel god
damn it Danny I gotcha I gotcha dude I
got it
come on Eddie
another fun day in Tokyo literally have
no explanation for poke one thing I just
feel I'm so happy yeah you guys can
probably tell I feel like my mind is
open my creativity my creative juices
can just flow and it's just amazing if
you're not a part of the low gang hey
I'm Logan Paul welcome to 2018
do yourself a favor to run the strongest
sexiest family on YouTube back to
subscribe bone in the face sleep on that
subscribe button copy yourself down out
it's marching their pointy H is gonna be
a big year for the Maverick Enterprise
the most comfortable clothing you'll
ever wear it's a revolution of
[ __ ] Mavericks those who are
gonna change the world with that said
tomorrow we're going to kyoto go gang
huh I love you you know that I will see
you tomorrow check it is bad
[Applause]
[Music]