like I throw away all you need
[Applause]
there you go baby wake up you guys never
fail to surprise me and show me just how
strong you are
this is crazy it's the Thursday
[Applause]
[Music]
every day it's a holy day every day bro
what a way to start the vlog do it all
god bless them but guys okay guys I love
you give me whatever you know I love you
we're leaving I love you why I love you
bro just literally really a mom yeah I
wish me luck we'll see you in the next
life today I was here next like oh okay
make sure you guys tear jump are like
pulling the people ah no solid weekend
no pretty good dude it's not a joke like
when I say low game for life like I
seriously mean that man I wish I could
meet each and every one of you back did
you come out here to support the pop-up
shop maybe see me rep the merch means
like literally the world to me so thank
you guys I know I'm getting deep at the
beginning of a vlog which is weird dude
but okay back to regular blog vlogs out
regular um absolutely Slade New York man
we had the second worst performance
obviously the pop-up shop is a boil
[Music]
the whole time bro on Oh
good news guys
Eila learned Evans name what is his name
again even no wait no no no no I am fine
alright I'm gonna get it right one day
ever sorry
sigh sir she does not a spell she was
just telling me you taking grade coming
around the mountain when she comes
she'll be coming around the mountain
when she comes she'll be coming around
the mountain to become nothing to be
comin round the mountain when she can ok
ok we came around the mountain we've
arrived on the plane calling made it
safely hi buddy
always so crying class I don't know why
I'm whispering so yeah man we're out
here in New York I never want to leave
this place man you guys have been so
good to me I promise I will be back soon
and when that happens gonna be for
something big I want to shut this place
down again do I rather I'm a good dad I
will provide a face for my dog to step
on when he need and off camera he calls
me daddy
every time I correct them that is
actually adapt and he nearly done around
here we come
guys we moved to Los Angeles I'm still a
lot of person here looking seven ever
have a head like at all okay oh wow okay
is that sup sup everyone calm down calm
down
can we talk about how hard these glasses
go oh my gosh my boy sure you get the
song obviously had a good flight cuz use
with it okay enough enough
Brendan how was your flight Ayla Ayla it
Ayla
you were crying why are you crying why
are you crying why are you crying
I'm just letting out energy that I built
up on the plane guys it can't be cooped
up in small areas for that amount of
time
I wasn't both of us I would built the
deal or something video
[Music]
in 84 years we're back in Los Angeles
and everyone needs to know
oh that's loud inside but yo everyone we
bring each other Oh feels good to be
home and it's a guy Oh maverick
forget the maverick it's exactly the way
we left it we got our Gatling gun right
here I cannot wait to use this in a real
vlog with mom on high what
over half of shop with rich I because
you can't come on a play cause you're a
bird also true no I know no the NYPD was
pretty cool pretty lenient I know it's
good to see you soon
I give me good oh yeah something about
being home that's just like maverick
versus Tom going down right now
Coe got that fire in his belly get a
call yet I scratch that bed into pieces
anyways we're sitting here I was
thinking like damn oh oh wow damn I'm
awesome but then I was like he'll we got
to do something belts to this vlog dude
whatever don't travel days make it hard
but I'm sitting here and looking over
there in that corner that teddy bear you
guys see that now correct me if I'm
wrong I feel like you're the same exact
size like bro this is perfect guys we I
don't even know how or why we have this
teddy bear oh my god bro we're gonna cut
it open take out the fluttering and
stuff you inside it evidence
this is hilarious how is Evan the same
exact cider this the evenings ex that is
so weird
yeah we're not going to work but it's
weird and a board dude I didn't say that
I know it's admit it though no I didn't
I was freaked
I didn't say Franklin I didn't say
anything he's just doing it you could
probably make a lot of money at the free
clinic find on the door
I can't I literally can't find I was
gonna say that there really honey
okay the surgery begins now oh yeah oh
oh you can change your mind
Oh what the heavens doc if I don't door
thought about that well sure
you're not even making any progress
you're living over here you go slow
after you method empty that bear this
bear has a lot of guts in the form of hi
this looks like way too much cotton for
like how tiny this bears dude the
physics just don't matter
oh it's gonna be beautiful yo this is
amazing Oh what up
can we get back oh my god are you using
your eyes I think you guys are just
invited a low over obviously we have to
scare the Schneider when I say like and
subscribe just freaked her out
huh I'm not doing anything not doing
anything
come on my house why I didn't even do
what you what are you just cowering in
the corner for
I'm not going to shoot you I literally
am holding a teddy bear please I don't
have a place to turn around I don't have
a play a left
why I'm holding a teddy bear can you
just walk in my house around this spot
here oh I'm not drawing a blue keep your
own plate I'm never coming back
I'm not a throwaway
all you need to do is like a Cisco wait
there's more okay why should take my dog
not only to say yet a clean is up
she took Toki dolls I'm not how to clean
bro man is going to like my life I
really do it's moments like these that
make me realize that come on margarita
pizza like the basil leaves on that too
so how you been out there better good
going up jimmy garvin right now do you
need help eating your pizza yeah here ya
go to a friendship look like there you
go right yeah no pinch pinch there you
are
[Music]
yeah yeah this is this was just idea for
sure I'll mail my copy came off you know
what else came off what my past cut Yuji
your topping come off my pants come off
oh that good evidence that was delicious
oh yeah gonna make one quick final pit
stop before we head back home but real
quick dad daddy okay we're at the store
this is actually where we bought the
original bear I feel like it's only
right to just put him back here you go
buddy
okay someone's gonna buy you and you're
gonna make some kid really happy one day
I can't wait bye oven I'm actually gonna
leave it with my best friend
[Music]
Wow okay guys we are back so glad to go
get my vision yeah we click wishes to I
start to leave here oh I did for comedy
hell I got nothing best friend
yeah I'm signing off so you can just
shut them what Oh Debbie stick I'm
sweating like dick off are you sweat you
dick off you don't have a dick in the
first place okay guys that is the vlog
type of thing Teen Choice Awards you
guys so many people are voting for me
for a male web star increased comedy web
star I love a man to link for that
description don't forget giving out
merge to people vote for me the winner
of today's is he ever always she used 7
devices and 7 Facebook accounts to get
me 70 vote today per category savage
girl yeah max all your votes to do that
Mauro's vlog is going to be so dull I'm
so excited something very big is
happening also going to be doing a big
merch drop tomorrow as well save that
moolah moolah get your maverick merch
link in the description subscribe to
under low gang and I will see y'all
tomorrow make it easy fast way
[Music]
holy