oh it's now okay ladies and gentlemen
the moment you've all been waiting for
this is by far the coolest room in the
house I give you the Maverick game room
for my first-ever fortnight live stream
on Twitch this Sunday at 2 p.m. Logan
ball was take it was good that was long
ok here we go 1 and I think for the
brand right now here's the thing bro we
got real-life models bro the brand's get
let's go
just drop new stuff we're dropping more
stuff these dare to fly shirts are
coming soon each cuz that's what we do
we dare to fly we challenge ourselves we
push ourselves we break the limits that
maverick lifestyle who's doing it baby
[Music]
it feels nice in my crotch oh yeah also
has you guys then we had the audio
problem but don't worry that is gone so
from now fine we got a new mic but yo
good news we found out the reason these
things go so slow they have a governor
on it basically that keeps you from
going a certain speed so we're gonna
take that off and Huck real hard but
yeah guys looking for my console a shop
or Lincoln disc really now it's time to
be a boy to be a model just one think
you're ready I hit it again this year
how bad is this pimple broke it's not
too bad it's not bad okay it's bad yeah
I feel like I've Mount Everest on my
face I'm not a model there we go I like
it like this what's the diameter of the
circle what do you think wider a little
boy no just I you know what she's got
some interesting tactics it's definitely
a little interesting but I saw something
fix a fire there good I think I think
he's a real deal okay yo this is crazy I
don't even know her name brothers good
what's her name
no no mr. boys name it's my name
no one good-looking Logan in the house
now okay I'm gonna do to you but I
actually made contact with the lens
there yes so the Hawks are inevitable
today you're looking good I just I don't
know is it the four nitrito speaking
about big news guys do you guys know
Sunday tomorrow you see the title of the
video we are revealing the game room
later today I spend a lot of money on
this thing is super cool yeah needless
to say guys it's gonna be all that trust
me you do not want to miss it tomorrow 2
p.m. PST that's your boy playing some
games now I think that was your idea bro
u-turn and that's like thanks yeah I
know I mean bro I'm out here was slim
waist
a TV still suck yeah we have no choice
we have to jump them seems legit yeah
built that myself so the plan is to just
pick up a heaps of speed and kind of
just hope that each wheel hits the
respective ramp the issue is you know
what we can use some duct tape hey dad
we have duct tape so since these aren't
like all like together I figure we'd
like tape them together and then love
your input on this we're just gonna kind
of Huck it over the ramp it's a good
plan with this extra added layer of
protection and safety a new high schools
yeah so why I got my diploma kids there
to fly baby we're about to take off
today baby let's go but just for
precautionary measures Devon you should
go first what I don't I just felt like I
was doing it got a lot more stupid of an
idea I admit I'm a little disappointed
in myself
why cuz you made the right choice to not
do it yeah wow you you actually are 23
now you're kind of like a grown up
wow wow you're right good would be proud
the way you've spun this is truly making
me feel great but I think
oh my god oh my god oh she was like over
the tire oh hi kids no more the fufu
show you what you came here to see yo by
the way this is all Evans idea Evans
inspiration he came up to me one day and
he says yeah yo man should do twitch man
like you could be really excited I
should PC for you my god yeah that's
what literally guys as soon as we cut
the vlogs Spencer and I and Evan have
just been hooking it on for tonight
because I want to be good at the game
for my first live stream it's been
pretty didn't work putting in work bro
yeah I was like doctors hours bro I was
like yo he's kind of late in the game
for real though we dedicated a whole
entire room my office is now the
official maverick game room and I'm
about to show you guys but first we are
missing one thing involving this is the
final addition to the game room I've
been waiting for this moment literally
I've been pushing I've been stalling the
stream yeah of the room I'm colorblind
you guys are gonna know we're talking
about in a second but I feel like it
really affects orange we're good yeah
we're good
yeah you guessed it I may be a
colorblind but I can't see that the
carpet is orange custom designed
specifically to match this room bro
actually you know what I didn't design I
just treat the color bro
to make it look like it's yellow I mean
it works no it does no I think it does
because the room the room has the yellow
scheme
all right well colors that orange I know
what is that door Inge oh snap okay
ladies and gentlemen the moment you've
all been waiting for this is by far the
coolest room in the house I give you the
Maverick game room for my first ever for
tonight live stream on Twitch this
Sunday at 2 p.m. Logan ball was take it
was good that was long okay here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah the wait is over I'm not he's gonna
ask I know you guys love this room honey
on my we have so much stuff going on
okay let's not over here here's me as a
fortnight character where's my gun with
my gun smells good and then we look over
here you got Kong a rocket riding cuz
he's a sad I do gotta say the
resemblance is uncanny first year and
then along this entire wall we have
these these lights right with the heels
they change color and not only do they
change color they can also be voiced and
sound activated watch oh look the point
is I am absolutely obsessed with this
room now the bread and butter let me
take you to the cockpit Jaime
[Music]
these two monitors here and that there I
actually know nothing about this at all
he built it for me
yeah this contraction right here is
Logan $6,000 PC that you see here
picture takes a picture oh so you guys
saw recently that I built a computer but
mine was only for streaming this is
specifically for gaming it's like
popping wine games always they even
every dress with a bathrobe and the best
robe maverick movement and then topped
off like Evan said with the monitor
behind it so that everyone on this side
of the room can see hey my favorite part
guys so when I'm not online on Twitch
this is my offline image it's just your
boy LP with the ground by the way real
carats of gold in here like the crown
and the glasses and even the shoe
buckles are actual gold flakes just say
by the way these work Lydia they work
here okay yeah they look good I yeah you
guys can see we got graphics like stream
starting soon and then when we go to
stream yo what's good it's your boy oh
but he was black oh this is so exciting
for me when I start something new and
dive into it I don't know if that's
gonna happen but that's obviously the
goal so yeah we about to light and then
check it we got a camera on the big TV
as well in the back there you can go so
when we win right into a wide angle and
the whole time like I said the idea is
once if I lose of course we go to the
gameplay angle here and then I get up
I'm angry right you know make a weapon
of choice we're gonna start off this
week with a slingshot and it's difficult
over fall we go right go play now this
is also important because I'm gonna
randomly break these plates but during
my livestream every now and then we're
gonna have a blue like coupon code show
up and I break the right play and you
guys gonna get discount so this one that
I was gonna be my first live stream it's
15% off everything on the Maverick my
local cost site what yeah you heard me
correctly the code is gonna be revealed
then and it's good for the rest of the
day so you've got to watch this training
bra and we're doing a new exclusive
merge strap Jesus Mother of God so much
amazing epic information I just think
it's so cool that a room can be
transformed like this oh wait there's
more Spencer do you want to show up what
yeah bro the whole squad gonna be
running up in the game room literally
we're all gonna be playing right here
just rolling heads on f9 I'm here dude
I'm happy also custom maverick chair for
sure well they weren't exactly like
custom embroidered so clean it's well
alright there was a brand there but you
know there's no free branding so I
covered it up with duct tape just
slapping a sticker okay little guy that
is the vlog boo this is gonna be good
guys if you're not a part of the low
gang make sure to subscribe also
important piece of information I'm
actually not posting tomorrow literally
the only spot you can find me and watch
me is on Twitch during the livestream at
2:00 p.m. Pacific Standard Time come
watch your boy are you gonna be playing
with me for a little bit oh it is going
down guys if you have not yet joined the
Maverick movement are you good bro make
sure to cop the hottest immersion in the
game logo ball that cops last shot or a
link in description every day we dare to
fly every day we challenge ourselves we
push ourselves try new things like
gaming for example guys might wish
handle is gonna be in the description
I'm gonna be able to even play with some
of you guys if you guys subscribe as
subscribers gonna get like super special
treatment whoo that's what's up baby
it's the low getting taking over so
again handle is local always taking I am
so pumped low gang that is the vlog I
love y'all and I will see you tomorrow
actually we'll see you on to it take it
easy
[Applause]
[Music]
this is great you know what my dog is
biting me oh cool