all right I got this when I was in
preschool I actually got expelled for
kissing every single girl in the class
when you send it it gets delivered right
hello gang I sent it and it is currently
getting delivered a yoga morning low guy
was mobbed you guys know we're having a
furniture problem right that rental
furniture was taking the houses to empty
right now so today's the furnace today
inside of that van that is obviously
having a hard time parking is a portable
Oh boxes nice so here's the deal guys
left updates number one if you have not
subscribed yet make sure to join the
loking the strongest family on YouTube
that's a fact hit the subscribe button
for me number two you guys know the
number song was released yesterday I
hope you're enjoying that singing about
numbers lastly oh no guys man merch the
hats off this person's name we have free
shipping on domestic orders over $50 and
we just drops a bunch of new stuff as
seen here Logan Paul back on slash shop
or link in description now why are we in
here because the pool tables got to go
right here
turning this room into a game room right
so you got the ping-pong table here and
then you're gonna be able to play pool
right there and then I think once put a
TV on that wall board exactly one of my
future ex-boyfriends yes how many
followers do you have on Instagram now
we made Suzy and Instagram it's at
neighbours Suzy how to the Maverick
Enterprise take fifty percent of
everything you make I don't know where's
my life you drive a hard bargain yeah oh
snap Suzy brought me some furniture
Suzy brought me a lot of stuff including
that guy yeah Wow truly remarkable the
things they have like this this is great
Suzy okay let's get out loud as you're
doing this be careful there is a killer
dog that we have running around so just
take it easy in which is watch out
yesterday Eagles
I like that and I can learn these lyrics
everyone knows Suzie's no more games
okay I'm kind of a big deal yeah of
course
oh you mean these ones hoodies available
now and looking for /i Suzie I'ma be
honest I you can have whatever you want
Wow I'm you tryna too small for you
all those muscles he's gonna stretch out
my hoodie yeah I'm gonna leave this to
users yeah you know how I can tell watch
the pecs bro
you shouldn't this shouldn't be thing
you should be able to see this stretched
it out yeah that's because I'm your eye
Suzy go ahead and do your shopping spree
imma go this way
[Music]
single day Vikas just gets more oh wait
a second no bro I bet this blue can be
used as a green screen bro
all right Ivan you're sleeping but
you're on the move anyways guys so since
today is about populating house cool
stuff you know the other day we got
something that I haven't shown you guys
yet I've been waiting for forever let's
do a little flashback to the other day
inside the wooden box there's more boxes
you guys this is material for the law
this could be the log of log yo y'all
don't even know it's clear to me you
guys have absolutely no idea what's
going on okay so just go live your merry
little lives all right I want to start
I'm a surprise job with the log okay I
respect your I have not been this
excited since I hit puberty you have you
ready yeah are ya did I got muscles now
we're actually behind the gym right now
I don't know if you guys know this place
sometimes see it we have this space here
I want to put a mini horse over there
before that it's also a great spot for a
log right I'm thinking right
here next to the rain barrel good little
patch of dirt I'm gonna let the boys
work and then when it's done yeah I
guess we're gonna check it out okay yeah
she'll be done by now it's dark it's
nighttime let's go check it out boy is
the log done so nice I actually don't I
don't even want to show that much of it
looking at me showing this right now hey
extra light Wow me showing this at night
is not gonna do it justice so let's cut
back to present day future Logan take it
away yeah hey thanks Pass Logan okay
yo this is a big deal the log is
complete ready to be used now I'm sure
some of you may have figured it out by
now the log okay check it out baby yo
you want to tell me what it is we do
without your boy come on go this looks
steamy bro come on in boys just a couple
boys in the sauna no big deal wait what
did you just say is my first time in a
sauna no it's at your house yeah
absolutely spacious in here like the log
change the room I hope you don't mind I
grabbed a couple of pair of the boards
yeah the crew woman those are the
women's performance shorts available now
in local bold icon slash outputs yeah
I'm not the only one who does come out
the number song yeah it's already on
actually so I also actually came up with
an idea for a new segment to do it here
solo gang I give you a song on a secret
okay these are actual secrets that
happen in our lives that's the rule they
have to be true all right I got this
when I was in preschool I actually got
expelled for kissing every single girl
in the class but you can't expel me now
mrs. buns
yeah that's right I can kiss any girl
who wants to kiss me back
I use my door face up to park in
handicapped parking spots technically a
handicap right you have a handicap think
about it if I park far away from the
parking lot and I'm walking and some
cars backing up and doesn't see me Oh
live in a world with no cell phones and
no internet I would choose that over
this world mad commendable Wow you're a
human I are you're up but actually I
watched Logan's vlogs and the sauna when
I'm at the gym
oh no no lay it down that's kind of
dough all right guys that is the vlog
thank you guys for watching as usual
Logan you guys know I love you if you're
not a part of us make sure to subscribe
smash the button for me all soak up your
maverick merch the hottest off this
mercs in the game whether you're a male
or a female or a male who wants to wear
female things or whoa man whoa man this
week only free shipping on domestic
orders over $50 Logan Paul back on slash
up [ __ ] bought that slice slow gang I
love you and I will see you tomorrow
[Music]