hey guys okay so before this vlog starts
I starks Tony Stark Iron Man I'm
recording this on the same day that you
are watching the vlog this is a buffer
or like a shield in response to Jake's
apology video which you may or may not
have seen we're basically he backtracked
everything and all this he talked in his
song you punch me in the face and I'm on
the ground and then you say sorry give
me a chance to get back up what are you
doing bro you're crazy enough to insult
me in the first place you're crazy
enough to insult the low gang in the
first place and now you put me in this
weird position where if I released my
full Rose track I'm going to look like
such a bully my bro congratulations
you heard my feeling like I saw red when
I when I watched that video my mind was
I couldn't believe what I was seeing oh
my god this whole vlog that you're about
to watch was us shooting the music video
for the song and like some other like
dope stuff cuz locating for life
I hate to do this like I don't want to
do this anyways the video is gonna be
out in a little bit I say it are two
times in this vlog the link will be the
description I still want to get a thumbs
up all right start the dance such a
weird note guys anyways enjoy the block
can you just give me one style oh my god
I was gonna start this vlog by saying
how I feel which was focused you know
determined unmerciful because as you
guys know today's the day we were
shooting the music video in retaliation
to my brother's diss track not only
against me guys but us the entire logo
what does he think you see crazy
he's gotta be cuz everyone knows you
don't mess with literally I have one
goal during this whole vlog and that is
to prepare you and get you to go watch
the diss track I'm doing against Jake
posted on this channel slightly after
this vlog as long I want the Logan to
smash the like button on that video so
many lies the link for that will be in
the description lots of go into over to
the mansion which is kind of ironic but
Jozef is a spinner in the back it's a
good size is it funny lovely salad you
want you you didn't even acknowledge it
it's a sign did it fall into your
butthole cuz I hate when that happens
Jesus Ayla are you blind oh okay I can
see why this is left in here yeah this
is dry okay guys we are on location
right now and there's like jqs right
wait we got the same house yeah Jake
it's not that hard we literally just
walked in bro you make one phone call
you get here yeah my will say this is a
big house and Ayla
you just look super tiny next to it like
like really tiny Oh God did a good job
choosing this house to shoot his music
video it's not that hard to get them
yeah this is a really cool spot infinity
pool red couch thing views on views on
view wait wait wait actually so why
don't we house is uh oh it's right up
there that's funny that's the boys house
and they will actually be here shortly
but let's keep exploring last window
paints this place is freakin beautiful
oh wait whoa what is this what do we got
a bastion we are co-directing this music
video today a friend you just joined the
wall or any we're in it bro
welcome to the load you know Jake shot
in the same house did you know that this
ain't like the same house I wanted to
flex on I'm gonna be like yo like you're
not that cool bro like shot a music
video one day and we don't really
shouldn't be that hard but that's what
I'm realizing is it slow getting you
guys if you watch Jake's stuff which you
shouldn't be doing because you're in the
low game but
you've probably already seen the tour of
this place you got calm what you got yo
this is his playground Kong if you hit a
million followers on Instagram tomorrow
I'll buy this house brother Kong -
savage if you want to follow him there
baby I've heard the song is live my
heart is this track of 2017 that part I
don't you should come in and just go how
many of you already know is bad ok I
will say is hot and you guys know this I
sweat easy some would keep it chill for
a little bit not number two my boy Jay
Alvarez supply in his G way the man the
myth the legend is my boy this is my boy
Wow also here's another thing in Jake's
video he had a white rolls and a white
Lambo I decided to get the same
literally the same white rolls and the
same way Lambert it's the exact same car
he made a big deal about making stuff in
one day it's not hard dude oh my god oh
it's just so sexy seconds later the cars
are now we got the Lambo we got J
alvarez's G Wagon
we got the Rolls Royce we got your Mario
Jake the no J was in the logo and you
guys know me I got a secret weapon in
the form of car
what up guys yeah lunch break my life is
good right now bro like look around is
amazing breakfast burritos rust and Jay
Paul I think good with that that low
gang Tang burrito you know and to
imagine it does give better kids number
two is fire boys no Jake is not ready
for these nice okay we're shooting over
there just pause real quick massage
their thing in the coccyx it's true he's
[Music]
number one on iTunes pop charts right
they just drop their new EP it's called
why don't we just and they are number
one on that when is popped we've been
number one all day Jake Paul maybe you
were near number one
[Music]
location number two we were actually at
the window we house it what up boys what
how did she get in dude you guys will be
with the band don't act like I'm not
know if anyone's gonna be with the bed
hey you guys look at Jonah right now he
looks like the kid who just lost the
Pinewood Derby okay for some creative
decision-making we have decided I don't
think we're actually gonna shoe here
because we're just chillin bro we had
some downtime so now we're just relaxing
making a music video where it's just
like performance shots is not that hard
like what help me help you there's a
story involved in everything thank you
bread every day that was awkward with
help me help you there was a storyline
right there was like certain beats we
had to hit so the jokes were here we
just get to like dance and sing and look
cool except it's it's not as easy for me
to look cool as the why don't we boys
also on the way home I ran into some
little gangsters and this happened
go ahead singsong will you add Jake
numbers don't lie you said it not me bro
well we are out to location I think it's
probably two and a half now what's up
Jay light me up bro oh okay thanks bro
you guys we have to be kind of quiet cuz
we are going on top of a helipad and
we're sneaking in the back way is how
you do it I love bunch of music because
we know we would know that's what we do
man we're grinders were hustlers we make
a head of the system do dumb millions
dumb millions Pro and locate how many
views do you think this video is gonna
give me enough twelve million give me
enough feed now a gang of stuff you know
that has a two point something billion
you blow gang help me help you get this
video this is what I'm saying bro we're
doing this we out here we in a parking
garage we sneak in seven billion views
go give the video a thumbs up
link in description get your maverick
merch always plug follow me on instagram
delcampo we're in an elevator I guess
you could say we're on our way up
do you see that are you see that our bro
I'm talking rooftop yo this is Joe look
at this bro yo do you guys remember this
area this is where I shot my 2016 recap
video oh hi dog I have one of you okay
talk to you later yo this place is
secret door hello I'm really excited for
this video guys like why don't I like
again I'll say it Jake you are crazy it
is just it is just why I told him
yesterday I haven't been this creatively
excited and so long hello open the door
open
oh yeah he is it a fact that we're out
here it's a fact it's a fact that we're
well this is a problem the helipad is
right there we are so close the doors
locked
where's my guy I know he's up there
somewhere come on honestly worst case
scenario I'm gonna have to climb and
jump over this right here I'm a maverick
you guys know there's nothing keeps me
Josh yeah your plan last along we just
have to open a door but they may be a
little harder than necessary okay but
the plan is still off Kevin by the way
he's the guy hooking it up oh my god
have to put your fingers enough to just
push the little thing I got big forearms
this way why can't it hop over oh my god
you sure yeah it's not dangerous oh
that's the only thing we're worried
about I'm going you sure about this
though don't try this at home guys
there's people up here bro oh thank you
just hope it was relatively Maddie how
are you do oh my god I freaking love
this helipad
welcome Sebastian welcome back one day
all of this will be mine I don't think
this is it bro this is where we're doing
the the helipad it's beautiful I'm about
to start singing the Sun is setting it's
a beautiful day here John I don't know
why I'm still talking let's do look at
the city guys oh my god Los Angeles I
love it okay we're gonna shoot it one
more spot here and then I think we are
going to get another cool car damn guys
with the other cool car literally it's
the same exact people just with cooler
cars it's called the McLaren and it's
silver and it's dope yo it's been a
really good day more we fill the more I
realize exactly how hard this diss track
is I want this to rattle the internet I
want people to be like why and then I
want you to be like well anyways we were
in the car on the way to the last
location we are listening to the radio
and the why don't we boy song I think is
about to come on rotation on rotation
bro it doesn't stop Logan that's me
dude I hear their song in the radio I'm
gonna flip though this is gonna be crazy
people just telling me things do
anything don't kill the messenger okay
guys we are at the location we were
literally just sitting here waiting for
their song to come on in the band and so
why don't we
oh these guys are just like they could
be like the next like thing like this is
such a mess
I directed this music video I directed
this music video
come on bring it in ooh I got good news
though I got Zach yes that car broke no
way that's yes yours yeah yeah that's
yours bro
100% your car definitely bought it yeah
borrowed on my vine money bro
[Music]
[Applause]
I want to give a quick shout-out to
hawkers for letting us use their amazing
mansion and amazing cars maybe one that
I can have all this stuff but yeah I
appreciate it thank you for helping me
rose j.lo gank that was epic that was
intense it still isn't ten that is it
for the vlog guys slight problem okay
this is a big problem I don't even need
to address it right now but if it
becomes a big problem tomorrow when we
go to post the music video or the diss
track I should say I will give you an
update and put it in this vlog I'll try
to wait because this this could explode
in my face because I'm a savage
otherwise the link for the diss track
will be in the description don't give it
a thumbs up and let's get a strong
comeback for Jake's diss track against
us not just me the low game subscribe if
you're not subscribed and I will see
y'all tomorrow
[Music]
so hard that one that was like that may
be the worst one Oh God