what's wrong what do you want away
freaking out did someone die Oh where's
Kong where is Kong no no it is weird I
woke up and I'm home alone this doesn't
happen aliens not here Brendan's not
here Evans not here but I do gun boy hi
hi hello game they're right there if you
want to say what's up now's the time
yellow gang I think again we are one of
the fastest growing channels it's not
the fastest growing channel on YouTube
where you going Brad its cousin was
savage it's cuz we don't give up we work
hard we never stop we grind ok the
Maverick spirit that's what this symbol
means it represents be a yeah I know
alias now yeah but you want to like
break a plate or something I really had
the urge to be right let's break a play
give it up and get the win here we go
break it break that fight oh Jesus
Mother of God these are some high
quality plates yeah we bought a bunch of
plates yesterday good for braking and
whatnot oh we gotta light up the
Maverick we got it here hold this and
number 7 I don't think that's accurate
as usual guys we have a fun day planned
for us and today is Saturday bro which
means Saturday's are for the boys are
you good
Oh mom mom is that you okay boys time to
get Chad lotion up boys there we go
that's that's I know them I know I know
them well that's 12 seconds later I am
sitting here and I see this girl walk by
over there with calm hey Lois supposed
to have Kong and gave him to her so she
could take him to the park tell me what
the situation is he's right there by the
way guys we have them in our possession
it looks good next to those oil dabs of
yours you're honest are you okay I'm
sorry
ale is such a bad stepmom okay so what
happened I got the elevator and sauce
cute little dog he's my dog he's calm he
runs into the elevator so I pick them up
the elevator yoga seven I think I'm up
and I walk out and I don't see anyone
around I'm like oh hello what are you
doing cuz guys i facetimed her and she
didn't answer so then I chased her
inside I'm like yo where was she doing
my dog and she's like it's running
around so hey thank you thank you be a
look currently has no idea where Kong is
I'm gonna call her and harass her a
little bit for almost losing my dog no
cuz he's mine
you but you might not lose and I respect
that okay Ayla what do you have to say
for yourself she's freaking out 100%
oh she's not answering oh this is gonna
be so much fun dude literally if I
didn't see this girl walk by with Kong I
would not have a dog right now
yo Ayla Ayla Ayla what are you doing
well yo doan't seriously him seriously
you know Halen a Latin Oh took him I
heard he was wandering because you let
him go bad amigo yo Ayla you lost my dog
you literally lost my dog and then you
come storming in here like it's our
fault are you good though yo someone get
this girl to survey how did you know
that we have yeah how did you know just
world is right here dog I was like yo he
ran in the Libyan experience what's
going through my route my heart is
beating so bad you you lost my dogs are
too high inches things start to the day
goodbye boys one slap freeze nipple you
know your problem is bro you don't have
one nipple otherwise life would be so
much easier for you I can't chase anyone
in my Gucci slippers but at least I look
good doing it now let's know this your
boys can be getting into music soon I
figure why not exercise that singing
muscle that as you can see it needs work
but I actually have a vocal lesson right
now I just wanted to come home so I
could do one quick thing really quick
oh I missed that purpose everyone just
calm down
get your freakin love this vehicle
actually still thinking about ways that
I can customize it I got some tricks up
my sleeve but if you guys have any ideas
make sure to comment down below I'm all
yours bro this is the collaborative
family of community of collaborative
miss what so I'm here at my vocal lesson
my guy Eric is in a session right now
look at this dog he has if this isn't
the most majestic dog I've ever seen yo
the coolest thing about him too is that
Eric didn't lose him like a lifted my
dog so funny hi puppy you're like a
giant q-tip huh okay didn't like that
joke see you later do you have any
interest in hearing my jokes why did the
chicken cross the road
how am i kidding he's not gonna answer
I'm not a singer but can you help me
sing I'm gonna try let's do a baby hey
guys it's me Logan Paul here's the
time-lapse of Eric helping me sing and
yeah that's pretty much it okay yeah
basically ariana grande mocha cappuccino
latte I will always preach this message
literally if you put your mind to
something and you really want it and you
really believe you can do it like guys
trust me I'm not a typical like singer I
wasn't born with natural singing talent
I'm just Logan I'm a chalk but mark my
words I am going to make a dent in the
music industry something I want to point
out you guys remember my boy zircon he
wrote a song about me okay you are my
year rose and then I flew out to LA and
we made a song together about heroes
Logan is my hero
what song about me so I snowing that's
really no thank you gift in the mail
Evan can you help me open it up yeah we
got gifts yo yo I just want to point out
my man was nice enough to send pillows
like bro look it like hospital quality
pillows like straight up I spill like
anything on this yeah you know I'm sure
Connor I gotta say I'm curious about the
pillows do you understand this this is
weird to me I'm not going but thanks
thanks for the hospital pillows buddy
anyways oh my god hell yeah thank you
sir Khan it's sad guys either was my
assistant as you know and she quit yes I
actually know I fired her for sure who
is also good on camera it's tough man
Hollywood he gave us like flash cards
Evan pick one what does it say Logan
when life's questions are difficult roll
the dice for your answer oh they got a
big pink dice okay let's ask a question
will the love gang rule the world and
buy other merchants Logan Paul calm /op
come on give me something good to eat
do something good come on pig dice come
on oh are you crying what is it what is
it oh no Aayla zircon means that oh no
there's no air
my guys you know al uh speaking of her
lost my skin dog this morning yeah bro
yeah you know what actually you know
what I let her off look way too easy
she's like one day oh I'm not Lois
assistant anymore let's lose club Halen
that's cold I need to get you back
ha ha oh you magic halo what are you
doing today can you not can you can you
can you not lose him if you take him to
the park please dog bro lela lela lela
can you come over later for the vlog I
want to do something all right I'll see
you later I'll see you later yeah that's
it bye no you know what I got from that
combo by the way hello well I just do
that cuz I'm Logan there's a park right
around the corner I think we post up at
the park and steal Kong from her and
then it will be like will be like you
lost cause again cuz Brent II don't know
this bro she lost Kong what's today you
lose the most famous dog I don't know I
see some girl walking with Kong I'm like
that's definitely not Ella and that's
definitely my dog and al is like she's
like let him walk out the door dude are
you kidding me like walking around the
ninth floor of the other building so
it's gonna be funny right like she lost
Kong twice in one day
good job Ayla - we can't have assistants
losing bugs broken pinkies shirt and
let's leave I want to look ok so we're
gonna go to the park like I said and try
and intercept they lie like a football
hopefully she's there hopefully she
didn't lose my dog we're
the way I think part of the challenge of
this is gonna be hiding the Yeti his
vehicle stands out a lot so we're gonna
have to like park around the corner and
then swoop in but I have a plan I have
every angle covered
and locked and loaded as you can see
guys i got GoPros on the wrist i got the
chest mount gopro nothing's getting by
me bro this is why i don't lose dogs the
park i don't really have a plan let's
just okay wait this is never gonna work
oh look at the g-wagen it's so massive I
mean that could be anyone's one of 300
in America yeah you're right you're
right okay four suits
[Music]
that's a good boy
how did she not see us it's just
terrible she's horrible at this is why
she loses comb she literally does not
even see us guys so we got the young
doggy I'm gonna want mr. whisper day I'm
gonna call Ayla and see what she has to
say for herself literally I can't
imagine losing this dog twice in one day
oh oh she's not answering he's not gonna
pick up brother Oh pick up either she's
on the phone and she's still preoccupied
or she knows that she lost him again it
doesn't want to deal with me right now
my guess is the latter so we're gonna go
back home and then call her again in a
little bit
okay we got Kong to pass some time we're
gonna fly this drove there's a party
happening on this hotel over here we're
gonna do a little recon see if it's pop
and maybe we go there later I don't know
we got Kong over here hey buddy how you
feeling nice and safe and sound that's
my boy can we call Ayla on your phone
yeah okay great I see she answers for me
okay listen while we wait for ailing to
answer we're gonna cut to the party
Wow what a fun time you listen listen
she's not even me yo she is I'm nervous
for her hey I feel like I'm gonna feel
so bad
I feel like now like I I don't even know
what to do cuz she's not answering
we're gonna poison back in town here we
go hello hey yeah why yeah sure I'll be
here hi bye
the cat is in the bag yo she's sad bro
devasting oh like how do you tell
someone that you lost their two million
followed Instagram famous dog don't
that's not like a conversation you
should be having it's not this poor girl
I was gonna we were just chilling
right now Ayla is on her way over Kong
is in this room
oh no no stay there's so Hale is gonna
be freaking out I'm just gonna milk it
like a cow until I feel like she learned
her lesson look at me I'm with that good
man
oh the doors locked I'm coming
Kayla hey bye yeah okay uh does this
work yeah unfortunately he can't stop
because vlog life we got a record for
which it wasn't anything like really
serious tell you she'll be vlogging this
no I'm gonna think I'm gonna do it
anyways what's wrong what's wrong what
do you want - why are you freaking out
did someone die
Oh where's Kong where is Kong
Ellen no what do you have no no stop
this is my dog I know I know I'm so
sorry what were you even doing
I'm sorry like I honestly I don't know
like I'm literally I don't know where he
went when he was just playing like
literally with your dogs like I turned
out really literally two seconds
yeah damn yo
that was fun the kind disorder part of
me felt back party was like not in
anyways if you guys are not subscribed
hit the button right now join the logo
Papa bro we're like literally the best
every plugin you're so cash also the
Teen Choice Awards for choice male web
star is for some reason still open I am
a nominee the rest of the categories are
closed I don't know why they left it
open you guys know we already destroyed
it but if you want to keep voting for me
you have like two weeks ten votes today
sought your votes tweeted at me I'll
follow you back Alfred tweet chat or
noted lastly guys get your maverick
merch Logan Paul calm slash be different
be unique be a maverick and push
yourself work hard to achieve the goals
you want to achieve so you can get what
you've always want I'll believe in your
low game okay I will see y'all tomorrow
take it easy
[Music]
Thank You shirt and let go I'm picking
this