how do I say this okay low gang YouTube
internet we are saying goodbye okay look
guys i'ma cut the [ __ ] alright I'm
back I'm here I'm ready to go hey yo
good morning okay so according to my
wristwatch here it's 6 a.m. very early
everyone in the house is asleep - my dog
and I figured I'd get up early today
start the vlogs back with the bank cuz
you know guys I have been gone and for
that I'm sorry low gang you guys know I
love you you we're the strongest family
on YouTube still and always will be the
squad the family of Mavericks the people
who aren't afraid to do things different
the ones who go right when they go left
the ones whose goal gets the great ones
who on their first day back to YouTube
in a while hire a drill instructor to
whoop their friends asses into shape
that's a fact yeah gosh this is George
Anthony here what's new his voice the
morning Jesus Christ it's very deep it's
very powerful here screaming for a while
we had to handle some things slow down
you know we were grinding so hard the
point is everyone got comfortable so I
figured I'd bring in George Anthony just
come in just what people's asses in the
[ __ ] look these blogs are simply not
gonna vlog themselves that's what I'm
here for
YouTube I don't know if you guys have
noticed it's been a bit boring lately so
LP has come back to shape stuff car
tires I'm a bit rusty it's been a minute
guys I have hello live updates we will
get to those later we got the case I
fight maverick just job some new merger
but again though I will get to that
later I'm dropping on the numbers song
this weekend which by the way might be
the best music video I've made ever
anyways guys I'm digressing I'm falling
apart like post Malone that's a song
reference let's get started but first
Jordan Anthony tell them to LIKE and
subscribe like share subscribe do it now
do it now do it now all right let's go
rere actually doesn't work for me he
just wanted to stay with me
the poor guy chose the wrong mother
[Music]
[Applause]
you got it all ready let's go blog this
is nothing personal bro it's just
business right we got to get back to
work YouTube needs us you almost punched
him today
okay well we're gonna go that way very
Paul's ready for anything apparently he
haven't had the pleasure of being woken
up by drill sergeant no long there we go
he must be in the Army National Guard
for in fact my bread balls that's right
I don't have to run yes good morning
Brendan wouldn't you maybe more than me
he's the other one no it's good it's
good we gotta get the vlog start it's
allocating the idea was we gather
everyone we woken up the entire squads
not here but we've been we've been off
the vlog for a little bit so I figured
George Anthony could get us back in the
rhythm right get us in the vlogs own
again go through some drills right I
have an itch cookie ow yeah yeah I'll go
get the cookie why you guys do your
drill all that he gets the fire let's go
get it rock stars
[Music]
it's done son this is you heard me talk
about this before guys we are building
and starting a podcast
it's called impulsive here are the
renderings right here so this room is
going to be turned into that yeah just a
big but if it was easy everyone would do
it guys just like everything we do this
is gonna be huge I think we're gonna do
it like once a week maybe
[Music]
I'm impulsive on the podcast guys are
gonna talk about every six tough you
don't see on the vlog risque stuff funny
videos viral posts Donald Trump hell
yeah talk about Donald Trump give you
can't wait till it's done they're gonna
have fun colors like blue Logan you're
colorblind yeah I can see blue bro I'm
reading green color bud this is great
yeah I swear to God Lydia and I had this
problem like this just looks like a
darker color of this and then my
assistant Lydia informed me that they're
not the same color look the point is I'm
colored by I can see certain colors I
can see like certain shades of red I can
see yeah just working we hired him to do
a job he's doing the job
oh so things have been going interesting
today hiring a drill instructor was
definitely a bold move I'm slightly
concerned George Anthony is kind of
taking things to his own hands
but needless to say he's doing a great
job also my assistant Lydia just showed
up and she actually has been doing a
good job lately so I think we're just
gonna shower her with compliments kind
of a theme of the day right we're a blog
Motors smash it in the face keep your
own [ __ ] I appreciate you it's time for
the drama it's the dramatic sit down
where you just talk to a camera how do I
say this okay low gang YouTube internet
we are saying goodbye to Brendan Brendan
so they all think we're leaving YouTube
now [ __ ] I'm staying right here no but
really though guys brendan has decided
to move on to the next chapter of his
life we have had amazing memories real
actually bro insane this this past year
a little under a year with Brendan has
been the best year of my life we have
gotten to do so many things together and
yes
and being being roommates all three of
us and Evan - he's pretty cool he's
right there he's cool hey well yeah all
of us have built this relationship and
it's not coming to an end by no means
but brendan is moving out and he is no
longer the official videographer for
logan paul fox is there anything you'd
like to say to the low gang I mean it's
been a wild ride with you guys thank you
experiences yeah and something something
you guys can all learn from Brendan
something you may not have known or seen
behind the scenes man works and works
hard not to not to mention he's super
talented but there's a lot of talent out
there something my brother always says
hard work beats talent if you have both
every single day every single day this
man's grinding not complain just up
shooting the vlogs and it's tough to
keep up with me and mother upstate I
know I might not be riding in the Yeti
if I'm gonna be in the car next to you
riding on the same street that's a fact
that's the fat guy so I just got so Evan
and I are gonna be living in the house
together which way I'm a good roommate
normally
if we could just give the next 30
seconds or so as a moment to cherish our
memories you want to do have to figure
out like where
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
by going to breakfast I grab breakfast I
got breakfast
[Music]
this particular moment I was very
confused with life
come in
I guess goodbye bro it's true it's true
it just doesn't live here anymore
before you go I actually have a couple
gifts for you one it's we just never
just dropped a brand new crop top for
the ladies I know you're not a girl I
think I'm not it's the gray goes across
the sleeves as maverick is nice and then
number two actually I got you this new
camera because I broke all of yours for
now yeah so there's that one to replace
those thank you well see you around
enjoy your crop top
[Music]
stay strong stay strong uncle work yeah
okay so now obviously guys we've got to
find a new videographer we got to find a
new roommate which is definitely gonna
be a thing guys there's so much stuff
going on that you guys meant starting
from like the chaos I fight and updates
on that which I will address in the
upcoming blog and then this weekend like
I said I'm releasing my song the number
song crazy-ass news video dangling from
a ladder dangling from a helicopter
great epicness that is coming Sunday so
just be ready to like it buy the song on
iTunes if anyone could get a song about
numbers to the number one spot on iTunes
it would be the low game but really some
people are saying this could be the
number one song in the world I don't
know about that but I can guarantee it
will be the number song in the world and
that's a fact also yeah I've been gone
so some of you may not know maverick
merchant of the game we did drop some
new stuff you saw the crop top buddy for
the ladies
we dropped performance shorts for the
boys and also for the girls no one's
doing guys being a maverick it's about
being yourself not being afraid to live
in your own skin and also working hard
to achieve your goals y'all know way to
get the merch slogan plot concise yeah
if you're not a part of the low gang
what subscribe for me smash the button
in the face kiss it on the mouth threw
yourself a favor joined the strongest
family on YouTube guys before I go I do
have to say one shout out and thank you
to my boy George Anthony man goes hard
lo que I love you and I will see you
tomorrow
one two three four five six seven eight
nine 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21
22 23 24 25 doggie we're looking at okay