we going to talk about last night
[Music]
this is the weirdest opening ever yo hey
i've been gone but i'm back yeah i just
needed a quick break you know i don't
feel like i am a blog
what obligated to make youtube videos
anymore
i do this [ __ ] because it makes me happy
and hopefully make some of you guys
happy and when i'm no longer happy with
my stuff
or like the things i'm doing in my life
usually a pretty good indicator that i
need to take a step
back for a second but it also doesn't
mean we're doing nothing in the past
week alone i [ __ ] directed
kid leroy's music video got a giant pink
yacht pulled by a crane
over my house and dropped into my pool
that muff air act just will not stop
and then we've been testing new chefs to
come cook for team maverick and this
morning i almost fought the one dude
like
he shoved mike bro he shoved the [ __ ]
out of mike
but apparently it was all a joke milk
coming it was his fault my boxing coach
he was a prank he knew the guy hey
listen logan got me
i told him when he got me i said i'm
gonna get you back was such a great idea
yeah yeah that's a great idea all right
carry on ladies and gentlemen this video
is brought to you by
lords mobile we got a sponsorship you
may have seen my brother playing this
game i decided to start playing this
game and now we partner
together a to not only promote the game
but give a quick 30k
30 000 cash to you guys so lords mobile
is the perfect way to kill time if you
guys are bored you probably are it's
quarantined looking for something to do
trust me this is a top mobile game that
is all about strategy why would you
spend your time playing shooting games
fighting games moba games when you could
just go on lords mobile and destroy
massive armies with one simple tap
to win you just build your kingdom and
continue to level up as you can see here
i just won that battle yeah in the game
you can choose army troops and hero
formations the way you want
create a badass city make the best
alliances to annihilate millions of
enemies yes they are real players and
it's considered by many people as the
best mobile strategy game with over 340
million players worldwide where
everybody in the world fights for the
throne there is a real
virtual world war going on in this game
i know it sort of feels like that in
real life too but
everybody creates massive kingdoms
armies and teams up with hundreds of
friends to fight for the throne every
detail matters city development
strategic troop formation hero upgrades
and more
click the link in the description below
you can see on the page there's a might
rank section when you can increase your
might by building your kingdom leveling
up etc so after the event ends the top
10 players will get a thousand dollars
each and besides the top 10 might
winners there's also going to be a ton
of other lucky winners to win a thousand
dollars cash each as well and you win by
building your kingdom and leveling up
also 350
lords mobile gift packs will be
automatically offered to participants
after downloading the game just download
the game from the link in the
description i want to see you guys
playing you could win
cash alright guys that's it enjoy the
video please don't comment i look like a
homeless man because my beard is long
i'm aware all right let's pounce and put
i'm sorry i said that first episode of
impulsive gone violently look at my nose
look what just happened
how did that happen well you were there
i'm bleeding from my face oh my god oh
yeah i saw what happened
what happened to the tv great question
what were you trying to do create a
disruption you literally frisbeed
a fan at joe biden's face and you say
you're on the left
you look like a thumb you look like a
sage film i don't came to a race track
today to drift and drift cars i feel
stupid
i feel kind of silly do you feel good
about this i feel like i look better
than i feel are you gonna try to shock
on a white claw oh yeah
[Music]
how can i get you inside my challenger
can you drift that
all right so it's not fully functional
but we're still gonna give this away
this is the first car i ever bought i
actually drove it from ohio to
california when i first moved to la i
haven't told anyone this but i actually
lost my virginity in the back seat of
that car i don't know if that adds to
the value but it happened but besides
everyone who's already in the maverick
club everyone who signs up in the next
48 hours gets automatically entered to
win my 2014 dodge challenger with three
wheels
but here's the catch i'm gonna fix it
and i'm gonna drive it to your house i'm
literally gonna hand deliver to you well
yeah link in description
mavenclothing.com sign up for the
maverick
besides there's a load of other perks
and benefits exclusive content weekly
zoom calls members dinners discounts on
maverick clothing
ten thousand dollar monthly giveaways
and a bunch of other dope [ __ ] okay
while you all do that i'm gonna go try
to fix my car suits me one of your car
but it's looking like a bit of a
show i think you were in luck all you
have to do is add air and should pop
right back up
oh really oh there you go
that was easy let's go
yo all the haters talking in the chat
saying i'm not friends with evan anymore
i'm best friends with him he's like my
best friend i mean [ __ ] bro we
practically finish each other's
orgasms whoa it's almost like i'm inside
your butthole
yes that's crazy [ __ ]
me nice wait a minute are we doing this
yeah we are mine comfortable wow
oh my gosh that's weird
we gonna talk about last night i knew it
i didn't want to talk about it i did it
one time one time only
and it helped me out this was you josie
last night
i felt the vibrations i had to check if
it was me he farts every day
throws him at me no i know i didn't know
you could throw a fart i thought it was
an urban legend i tried it
not successfully you were the first one
maybe it hit my mouth that's where i
threw it it's that dangly thing in the
back of my throat
sorry for throwing fart at you and so
you should be sorry for farting on my
dick hit that subscribe button we'll see
you next time peace
[Laughter]
[Music]