I've made a severe and continuous lapse
of my judgment and I don't expect to be
forgiven I'm simply here to apologize so
what we came across that day in the
woods was obviously unplanned and the
reactions you saw on tape were raw they
were unfiltered none of us knew how to
react or how to feel I should have never
posted the video I should have put the
cameras down and stopped recording what
we were going through there's a lot of
things I should have done differently
but I didn't and for that from the
bottom of my heart I am sorry I want to
apologize to the Internet I want to
apologize to anyone who's seen the video
I want to apologize to anyone who has
been affected or touched by mental
illness or depression or suicide but
most importantly I want to apologize to
the victim and his family for my fans
who are defending my actions
please don't they do not deserve to be
defended the goal with my content is
always to entertain to push the
boundaries to be all inclusive in the
world I live in I share almost
everything I do
the intent is never to be heartless
cruel or malicious like I said I've made
a huge mistake I don't expect to be
forgiven I'm just here to apologize I'm
ashamed of myself I'm disappointed in
myself and I promise to be better I will
be better thank you