dude
how did we get the most notorious rapper
in the world holding my best friend's
hand
on our podcast impulsive the number one
podcast in the world
sort of well just like most good ideas
it started with a good idea
six nine on impulsive
thought
i don't know hey you know what they say
ask and you shall receive wait i'm sorry
what the [ __ ] are you saying
you're interviewing this guy takashi six
nine i heard he's a big guy obviously he
threw a zoom call though yeah no no
they'll be coming to your house with ten
bodyguards
jesus christ
24 hours from now six nine we'll be
sitting where you're sitting right now
get lying
can i be here guess we'll be sitting
there and his name is six nine
[Music]
and you know there's another part of the
puzzle too you can sit in my chair
because i'm not doing it
i'm not doing the show yeah mike you
have to you have to that i can't be on
the show with a rat dude have you talked
[ __ ] about him in the past
a lot this mother has deemed it cool
to be a snitch you know deep down in
your heart there's no way you're
listening to that
because you're like yo this is a hot
song you imagine telling jay-z and naz
and biggie that this was now the
garbage man are the people that run the
rack said he comes on this show i sit
that episode out
do you plan on like pressing him like
are you gonna try to make him walk i
plan to just ask questions with not
loaded questions
good ask me questions why do you feel
the need to talk [ __ ]
and then run behind your body guards
like does that make it how does that
make you feel
like no no no no no i can't ask that
question
there's one rule when it comes to work
like no matter what happens you never
said i want to actually
setup
[Music]
are you doing what are those what are
you doing
traps bro they're just sometimes if you
have an infestation at your house
michael we're prepared yo you cannot you
can bro
he's gonna walk save it from the end all
right so i'll put the rat traps away
i'm sorry but i swear to god if i even
hear you so much and start sucking his
dick bro i'm gonna flip okay yeah yeah
don't you
hey man i just want to let you know
you're one of the most inspirational of
the dead
you said anything like that i'm flippy
[Music]
um trying to get everything done for the
album it's not
my mind it's just not all there because
right now we don't even have a [ __ ]
video done i was looking forward to
coming to meet you and i'm just like
this
dude cancels crazy yeah yeah just
that point was just like yo we got to
get that done i'm a big fan and
i definitely want to come and i i need
you more than you need me
i'll see you later all right sounds good
bro take it easy
you're all fired everyone's
[Music]
many many years ago the trojans rolled a
small
horse into a town called troy the people
of troy thought they were bringing a
gift but inside of that horse
were warriors hell bent on death
destruction
and most importantly [ __ ]
it's all right it's all right that's not
all right jre was supposed to be at my
feet now
suck his dick again
you know what i'm not even that mad
[Music]
well [ __ ] just like that there goes all
of our rainbow colored hopes and dreams
until
[Music]
[ __ ] six nine is on our way to his house
he flew back to los angeles from new
york to come on this
to his podcast you just said not the
best this is not a good start
listen 69 is on his way here right now
he flew here from new york to do this
listen we're gonna go right into it wish
us luck
[Music]
he's not gonna be able to go outside
though right first down
shot a music video on the block open up
your phone without seeing takashi 69
yeah that was before i went to jail you
just gave
me a moment if i was in that situation i
would have did the 47 years i snitched
and i did it proud why you stupid ass
popping willie's
well it was because of nikki it was
because of nikki
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah he kept it there and started
talking and i wanted to pull it
but i was like i can't do my boy like
that
i could pitch things i have never seen
him this nervous no nervous because i
could have died dude think about it
potential to be our biggest episode yet
and there's actual real-life dangers
after seeing his security that's pretty
comfortable i bumped into the wall i was
like who put this wall
i was like oh no that's just one of his
security guards subscribe to impulsive
we love you subscribe to this channel
too uh that was the craziest thing of my
life
it's cool when he started uh yelling and
you hear his
his rap bro i was just like it's fire
bro