it's a big deal this place is high
security guys I'm going to set right now
for my movie then maybe the second one
my drivers being a little pissy this
morning you're cussing you sound mad
you are kissing your cat see this is a
big facility guys like a factory thing I
think beer here do they make beer here
you still got it man you're the word
SuperDrive ever had I'm gonna give you
one star thing I'm not a new driver what
this is legit we're safety vests is that
what's uh no everyone guys I don't I
don't feel safe without your vest has
got the thinning merge the only other
merch I will wear besides maverick which
reminds me guys if you have not yet
gotten your maverick March just just
look at me real quick look at the shirt
and then look at the joggers and then
ask yourself why have I not gotten my
mind it's done how does much it the gay
obviously the softest most comfortable
clothing you'll ever wear and it's the
movement bros to join it Logan Poldark
on /op and they get it yeah I don't want
to be on the vlog are you ready 1 2
under the cool hat no way does Lydia
have to wear one yes yes to wear one
yeah
[Laughter]
he's crying right now because we were
stupid has to make movies very let's go
such a good way to start the day if you
guys haven't watched the first inning
you should it's on YouTube red you kind
of have to right now yeah bro it's tough
for your boy to become an actor baby
Oscars here if that wasn't an
oscar-worthy performance bro my name
isn't Jake Paul really hey Brandon how
are you I'm great hi it's funny because
in the movie like we're actually not
gonna be able to use any of the audio in
here all of its going to be 80-yard ADR
additional dialogue recording hey the
more you know about movies Logan I'm
going to bring Hollywood for you
[Music]
yeah this set has some weird stuff look
look duck under and like what yo so
funny check it out here's one Oh check
out that STD broom you can definitely
see the SCV cleaning you up just see in
tomorrow's vlog like it subscribe need
the STD broom I'm a good co-star I'm
gonna make sure none of the extras have
STDs
[Music]
oh my god so good you don't need some
life-changing yeah just take a bite you
know earlier I made sure all the extras
were clean from STDs Oh taking care of
me No so now let's feed them at what
point do we get the STDs back we want to
see I think so bro we gotta go quick
well I'm fine I'm fine Jenna I'm fine
guys I know I'm on your set I know I
gotta make a movie hangri producer sorry
it's our job you're the nicest angry
producer I've ever seen got that pink
murder though Logan fool.com / yo you
got lucky bro these sold out quick my
man's gonna do first
come on into my Sunday you're pregnant
I'm not right now no for the recount is
gonna count a video I saw her saying yup
guys are pregnant Lydia I'm trying to
help you you've got no STDs anymore
don't be upset you could be doing baby
commercials you could be the baby in the
commercial turn to think bringing Andy
to set wasn't the best idea
[Music]
my producers paid me I guarantee we
should've never hired a ski blogger whoa
different scene but guess what guys we
wrapped for the day clearly I've gotten
kicked out of me you don't look so hot
yeah Brendon you're ugly alright guys
it's time to go home hey we're home I
gotta say I like Andy's parking job that
is indeed my boy I know you have pedal
extensions on your car get rid of them
new Melanie
look at what are you making everybody
else is gonna eat that
[Music]
yo because I'm a good lager you know
it's dark right now and we're not doing
this machine justice so let's cut to a
morning montage of driving mini Yeti
next to big yet
[Music]
so Angie's making dinner and then over
here we got what have you been brewing
bro I haven't even told her looking like
they kind of know but not really
well we haven't slept for two days
because Logan said that he needed a
merch store sleep sleep when I die I'll
sleep when I die yeah for sure and so we
made a merch store while you were gone
shooting a movie do you guys remember
when our money ran through the wall
[Music]
[Applause]
and it was because we are going to
create the greatest smart store alive
for the greatest merch on the planet
that's right maverick merch the hottest
off his merch in the game you can only
get on local pub a cop / many have
joined the Maverick movement some people
have died no one no one's died no is
that so they made a merch store my mom's
in here that's gonna be crazy it's a big
deal
oh my god I felt like you needed to have
that like super exclusive yo this is so
so good how did you get this done yo
they got here last night this has been
less than 24 hours yeah yo and Logan's
like open I just like you guys he's like
yo I'm gonna make it today I'm like what
do you mean today
brother let's took one day how did you
that's unbelievable
in one day no no joke guys this is the
outfit I wore my Christmas diss track
music video honey I have no idea how you
did this in enjoy bro but we ain't done
yet mood right easy I got the red sock I
need to do the red drops thank you thank
you I was like you have exceeded
expectations I think that's one of the
most important values I've learned from
2017 done it bro you've exceeded my
expectations my man
it's beautiful
this is so good I'm so happy right now I
love dang that is the law not a part of
the logging like I said it many times
today subscribe if you have not gotten
your map of merch it do that guys the
quality of our stuff even the way we
portray and represent the brand just
like this is the highest level it
doesn't get any cooler than this cool
doing it bro the answer is nobody baby
Logan Paul that cop / shopper link in
description I'm so out here so thanks to
my mama everything bro the favorite
hoodies the red drop the chrome hoodie
the pink I'm done low gang I love y'all
I will see you tomorrow
[Music]
besides the fact that this is a beer
factory you could get hammered in here
ha ha ha