okay here we go I'm gonna be honest I
didn't want it to be like this this
video was supposed to come out a couple
of days ago I'm just I'm gonna be honest
with you I've been in Ibiza partying my
ass off and being a degenerate with my
brother Jake I'm fine I'm sure yeah here
we are finally making a video you may
have seen on my Instagram yes yes the
rumors aren't the true my leg is
completely bruised purple swollen and I
do have to unfortunately get it
amputated now you don't need two legs to
do every time just kidding I don't think
I have to get amputated it is tough to
go for lack of better verbage and yes it
is from the Challenger games which this
video is about I'm gonna show you how it
happened and what happened and although
the event was indeed a huge success and
we raised a bunch of money for charity
it does suck that I got severely injured
when I said this in my pre-challenge er
games video I'm willing to blow out my
[ __ ] leg for you guys I don't give up
I actually wasn't serious like you know
that wouldn't have been ideal I actually
I didn't think it would happen and it
did I don't know I don't know if this is
there's a good way to ship Hey
okay I'm making a video I'm making a
video me alone will show you the
swelling oh please don't flag me YouTube
how's it looking
I mean what's looking good bro I feel
kinda like an Instagram thought right
now but just focus on the purple on my
leg very best it's pretty bad so look
it's purple it's swollen know how I made
its way down my entire leg all from a
pulled hamstring you'll see me pull it
and then re pull it in this video which
I'm actually just gonna roll this
footage and then let's have another chad
the end of this video subscribe enjoy
I'll be fine we're probably good the
challenger games today one of the
biggest youtubers on the planet are
gonna be racing for $100,000 all goes to
charity you guys know I'm quick I'm real
quick bite I had a hamstring injury
pulled my hamstring guarding Snoop Dogg
in the game of basketball so this
morning started off right and I did some
rehab
[Music]
how do you injure a hamster no I'm a
hamstring Oh hamster but I'm feeling
good today I haven't been training for
the past week and a half I don't want to
use that as an excuse but I'm definitely
going to should I somehow into some go
Wonderland Fantasyland not win who knows
the Challenger games as you guys know
presented by halogen TV got two members
of maverick family competing today for
by one Mike is commentating that's
correct
Marty it back to you Marty I want to
raise a bunch of money for charity how
much a billion Oh smelly I think I'm
going for 1 billion dollars and I want
this to be an annual event so every year
we get together we raise we find it was
the fastest or maybe the events change
today the focus is on just being the
fast as I possibly can row I didn't go
on fox business and say I'm the fastest
man on the planet for nothing I meant
that running I could be the quickest man
on the planet
they also say do it I did but look it's
cured and that you were going bro yeah
hey listen the point is today's gonna be
awesome I love you guys thank you for
the support and I hit that subscribe
button now let's do this
you ain't a lose man I love this
attitude that are like 20 years old
running for 50 miles you have a broken
hamstring and you're mentally incapable
I remember this story about this bar I'm
down who are you are you what's your
name bro I like you no seriously no I
seriously do you know but today talk
you're just you're not my okay I mean
all right ask your mother who she thinks
is gonna win the race what's really good
[Music]
talk about why you already wrote erode
you're gonna blow a hamstring
[Music]
[Applause]
what's up guys my name is Logan Paul and
welcome to the first ever challenger
games presented by halogen we are here
in Long Beach California Veterans
Memorial Stadium to figure out who is
the fastest internet entertainer on the
planet I went on live television and
said it to me we all know it to me I've
had $100,000 on it all so today we're
here to benefit the Special Olympics
that's right we're raising money for
charity we have the biggest internet
personalities in the world in this
stadium today all ready to race to
figure out who indeed is the fastest
entertainer on the planet subscribe
hashtag at the Challenger Games on
Twitter every social media site let's do
this let's race good and they're off for
the first heat of this inaugural
Challenger Games mark donors suck it up
a little bit of gas there in the back I
think is good spend too much time at the
nightclub
[Applause]
and here we go let's see if your
prediction comes true and putting a
stranglehold early on to one
I'm thoroughly impressed I knew she had
the ability to do at fashion ova posts
on Instagram but I did not know she
could run that was quite impressive ties
[Music]
right now it's down to the wire it's
gonna be late for host a little slip off
there and the set Jake Paul Finch in
Jake Paul's the winter table dizzle and
second twelve point two six he 1.10 guys
I'm sorry that this is just the first
heat I move on to the final now pulled
through because I am the fastest
youtuber on the planet everything so I'm
gonna take home this W and Logan's gonna
give me a 300k thank you guys and it get
married tomorrow let's go
[Music]
and you can you can see Logan Logan's
face right now he is not happy this is
the last thing he wanted to see his
little brother Jake take the ice yeah it
looks like he's stretching out that
hamstring it's gonna be interesting to
see how he does on a 400 I know he's
running the 100 but the 400 also is
going to take a lot of strength and
endurance to power through this event
[Music]
I just thought attempted to sprint I put
my no you did absolutely what the oh
yeah I just pulled it again
I'm literally up right now same thing
same leg today way I pull much good just
like this now I pulled it again take
this as a life moment when there's
millions of people watching you and
wanting you to succeed and do something
you promise you to do and right before
you do it
employ your hamstrings I'm in panic mode
right now I have no idea what I'm gonna
do
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't do anything I'm immobilized
[Laughter]
[Music]
I feel so dumb I don't know this is it
for me I think so where are you gonna be
the rest of this this day I mean your
relay team like you said but just just
watching rooting for Jake now I hate to
say but I think so
[Music]
Logan i-i've never been more saddened by
an apparent injury you came out the gate
you looked immediately like a robot just
sucks man it just sucks I'm disappointed
but to be honest this event is not about
me it's about charity it's about
donating to the Special Olympics and I
think we're still doing a great job of
that and it's really it's really under
taming like I'm really enjoying watching
these races
you're hammy
happy birthday
oh I'm finished okay you actually should
run a little bit okay I can do what I
did with your leads like gold fast
asleep bro I really feel like Lo is
gonna be the reason we lose bro it's the
opposite okay okay is that quick I mean
quick enough maybe if I get this w you
will never guess the fastest man here
though bro
you can blow them away and they're off
raka raka actually with it's unclear
who's leading right now but lane seven
looks like they're pulling out in front
big time come subarray for the handoff
to Jake Paul oh wow we've got
out here winner right now
you angry
[Music]
third rule I was so dumb I miss so much
more babe he just recruited
[Music]
totally
Jordan
go ahead make some noise for your top
three finishers fastest email
entertainer on the planet and Charlie
Jordan she was gonna clean up that's why
I put her on my four by one team even
though we long as the fastest
entertainer on planet earth makes some
noise for your gold medal winner destroy
[Music]
thank you guys for joining us right here
in the 2019 Challenger games thank you
guys for joining us for a very special
event this has been the Challenger games
2019 we'll see you next time
that a mad star yet a rough race
whenever I start in a plastic chair for
four half hours have a drink of water
nothing I was treated like somebody I
was fasting and some sort of hindu
ritual here we are Rebecca so the
problem was I shouldn't have ran on it
at all but my pride and my ego a little
bit was sort of affected and I was
embarrassed and I wanted to at least
complete the race and so I did I ran
sort of the hundred meter dash and
phousi actually carried me I'm sure you
guys saw across the finish line which
was awesome but I think the real problem
was me trying to run the relay with
summer Charlie and Jake and hopping down
100 meters just like hold and reap old
and reap old and then next thing you
know slowly but surely turning into
Thanos but everyone got hurt at the I
made a list here the Challenger games
literally just collected hamstrung King
batsh a sensei Charlie morally model Roz
a sensor Daisy key joseline and Austin
McBroom everyone in some way or shape or
form got hurt related to the Challenger
getting one of the hundred meter mens he
three people in this same race got hurt
like just ridiculous we're all right
we're getting tools for this next year I
don't think the Challenger games are
gonna be a track-and-field me it's gonna
be a different type of epic event so
comment below what you want to see think
like maybe American Ninja Warrior think
like gladiator type war a nice friendly
harmless game of golf with that said
right now I'm focused on recovery that's
not true at all I lied I'm more focused
on partying
well I'm sure everything's fine thanks
for watching this video if that's
subscribe button [ __ ] love you guys
if you donated it if you sponsor if you
participated to all that athlete
seriously thank you guys challenger
games was so much fun and I cannot wait
until next year's 2020 challenger games
I'm gonna rally my brother and we will
see you next time target