that is what it looks like when your
main parachute does not open guys that
is a real video I am still alive
hey yo good morning okay what's up so
yeah we're gonna get into that later
like that was the day I should have died
but it appears as if I got like addicted
to skydiving so we are actually at a
skydiving store right now to get a
custom suit you know go rock down
maverick baby it's time for the birds to
take flight no no your Julio yeah guys
when you're going skydiving obviously
the goal is to a survive but be look as
dope as you can so that's why Julio is
gonna help us my goal is to just be
falling from the sky and just sell as
much merch is Bravo oh he's a good Logan
Paul Khan's last shot she's like tapered
on the inner thigh so I can just frog
down I did that before
here's a picture look inner thigh bro
always plug always play everywhere your
body articulates you have a neoprene
articulation okay and you can use
hitting the tone you can use it in the
sky okay sounds good so this is where
the magic goes down there's so many like
sewing things here that I just have no
idea you can print a suit I swear less
embroidery you guys can do anything dude
Julio I'm so glad we found him bro it
was Jeff yo yeah just in case I don't
die skydiving I can definitely flip a
car on the racetrack I'll make it better
yeah we're go why a little small in the
chest hit the bicep what are my biceps
my big what yeah
no no they're not yeah no you're lying
those are six teens bro I got 17 18 19
if you're not a part of the low gang I
feel like now's a good time to say you
should subscribe because your boys got
some super to you the strongest family
on YouTube and we skydive who's doing it
I don't know buddy guys we are back at
home I noticed this I'm not sure if he's
gonna do it Kong smiles
such a good dog okay we're back home
let's see what's popping
[Music]
lady has picked up sculpting okay are
you making stuff out of clay this is
mine that I made the woman of many
talents anyway speaking of talent you
[Applause]
need to start a plate factory and then
you know you can just break I could make
so much money
come don't move don't step on the plates
you're in a minefield
don't move yo so if you guys remember
yesterday we got new koi put in our pod
Joe what the heck was that
I don't know I was trying to show my
excitement I am a geek for koi and fish
and they look so beautiful right yeah we
got sick Evan look you remind me of that
fish all along all by ourselves no
friend at least a tiny F check out the
big one his name is daddy I did take him
busy we should do a boxing match instead
of KS Ivor's Logan Paul every versus
daddy daddy
[Music]
Oh what else can we throw Lydia no you
have any ideas I'm gonna throw up the
idea was to get rid of our old stuff by
throwing it the issue is old milk smells
like ass no code now though I will say I
do feel ready to talk about the
skydiving accident okay I feel like this
could get a little deep and I actually
forgot that I haven't even shown this
video to my parents guys no one has seen
this video i ding OH a lot is going on
right now look guys I was slinging a
knife around actually cut myself I
stabbed myself yeah that sucked it's
very painful so now my dad's all decked
out in maverick mercy I load and pull
back on slash oh hey so you guys may
have seen this during my social media
blackout cuz I did talk about it a
little bit basically like I went to go
skydiving and when I pulled my main
chute it did not open there were plenty
of articles about this well now you get
in the first-hand live skydiving
accident Logan Paul the day I should
have done I need to adjust my goggles
and put diese it doesn't matter I'm not
gonna wear these when I'm in the ring
with CSI oh ok addressing that really
quickly CSI denied the fight with my dad
and he if you actually want to fight me
on down there I am you can tell I it's
me because I have the Mavericks on my on
my
I'm a beast and stuff so this was the
first time let me go okay by myself okay
[Music]
deposit one second you guys good maybe I
need to flash back to this morning
because there's a crucial piece of
information I think you guys should know
Spencer manager Jeff they were there on
the day I did not brief them I'm just
gonna have them speak honestly cuz this
is what happened that morning when we
were in class what conversation took
place first off I got to start by saying
you spoke this into existence literally
it was my fault there's a hard time at
all at the beginning of a skydiving
class we get into harnesses and they
basically run you through some checks
right so we're doing the emergency
procedures casually yeah nothing but air
II gotta know this guy starts starts
kind of like letting his imagination
loose the wrong way I'm just like yo
like what what are the chances actually
happens like why would I why would I cut
away of my main treats that kind of open
Logan says yo I feel like a lot of crazy
stuffs been happened to me this could go
wrong the teachers like basically just
like no there's no way you're gonna be
fine you got to know it but you're fine
I'm like I'm like lady you don't
understand weird things happen to me
like you have no idea she's like you're
fine and cuz when you skydive you could
die the whole day I saw I brought my 360
oh that Julie fence came up to us right
before the jump Ian he's like yo you
guys gonna wear this 360 camera I was
like uh I don't know no really he's like
dude just do it I was like so our
instructor put it on because we cannot
wear cameras yet without the camera
never caught it was your jumped right
after so I didn't see any of this happen
you've got to see me splat on the ground
bro
yeah I know we plan if I am in my
parachutes don't open as I'm falling to
the ground it's gonna be a DAP and I'm
gonna go boobs this is gonna be a sonic
sonic boom across this yeah yeah guys
this was my first time jumping alone
this is my seventh jump my instructor
has jumped 2,000 times she's had to cut
away twice okay so anyways I go to the
plane here she pushes me out I do flips
I send it like a boss or whatever it's
360 camera looking beautiful during the
free Falls I'm fine by the way also
notice China that that suit is like
trust me the suits are gonna be much
cooler that's what we did this morning
gotta spend it I'm gonna play this real
time and then I want to talk back and
dive into exactly what was happening
before what could have been the last
moment
whoa yeah dude oh dude my heart is even
party this is freaking me out for real
no [ __ ] idea cuz you literally look
like you flipped like okay let me
explain let me explain your main
parachute takes three to six seconds to
open I go to pull the pull the ripcord
but he was right as I pull it it gets
stuck in this like little square shape
so I'm like okay cuz you're still going
right so I'm like I'm gonna give this a
second like it could still open up it's
happen before it takes like a second
longer to open up but I'm also spinning
right the cord is wrapping around I'm
getting a line twist they call it and
about four seconds in I realized the
pears are still nasty opening so I
started tugging on it I'm like oh okay
remember three to six seconds for this
thing to be fully open real time I'm
gonna play exactly how long it was when
it wasn't open
it's like not it's like 9 seconds I
think I don't know but we showed you a
building yeah so eventually I'm like um
I am gonna die I'm gonna die first up I
can't believe this is happening cuz I
talked about it this morning literally I
had this conversation this morning
verbatim the only thing I said was oh I
look red I grab red I peel pool just
like they taught us and my main
parachute detaches and I'm like hole
well hmm I hope my reserve works
literally crossing my fingers that my
reserve parachute works because this is
my last chance
peel pool is like you are in your mind
next to death next to death yeah you're
fully prepared walking the line you're
fully prepared that this pool that is
gonna change your life one way there
yeah there's one part here where you're
free falling y'all right here yeah yeah
I'm upside down and you listen closely
you can actually hear my instructor she
goes holy dude and your reserve chute
was still y'all up you dummy
yeah yeah you know why I your reserve
comes out and I'm twisted one time or
I'm like so lit I'm in my hammock no oh
I'm not doing this right now I'm living
so I grab my my risers I pull them apart
I spin around everything safe and I'm
like well I'm I'm I'm still alive yeah
this is good there's a good thing
honestly and I'm proud to say this and
it sucks that I have to go through
situations like this to learn this about
myself I think you're gonna go I'm okay
it's Nana I'm okay exactly there was no
panic it was like this is the steps I
have to do to live peel pull all right
like no panic there was no time there
was no like holy s--t I'm gonna die it
was just like this is what I gotta do I
want to live that's what I'm doing like
total glass half-full type of mindset
yeah but I also I heard this quote today
glass half-full half-empty
yeah there's water in the cup drink - to
stop complaining reserve parachute is
out I'm not touching it bro I'm looking
at it I'm like there's no holes every
single cord is attached I'm good I'm
good I'm not dying right now barely
touch me I was like say ladies oh god
that's right posted guys the Maverick
loser I'm still here skydiving okay with
that said low gag oh thank you guys for
watching if you're not a part of the low
game make sure to subscribe cuz my name
is Logan Paul I am still alive and I
love each and every one of you we are
the strong family on YouTube that's an
actual fact there will be plenty of more
fun skydiving videos assuming I lived to
tell the tale with the new suits to
helmet yo it's about that maverick life
we're getting it all customs out it's
tough this much in the game Logan Paula
calm / shot the maverick lifestyle is
not being afraid to do the things you
want to do like skydiving and just live
life to the fullest every single day
okay I love you
[Music]
yeah whoever told you love as simple is
Alaia whoever told your piece is easy
don't admire I wanna hold you but I
can't control the fire
go find a spirulina putting out a light
ya desire you turn to the side your turn
to Tula try it all there for the white
hand but we had
[Music]