Jenny lo gang yours is all about mental
strength no matter how many tears your
eyes no matter how much television exit
your mouth as long as you gets a cup
good morning where you going where you
going be my vlog be my cameraman for the
day no I'm good though I'm good I love
Brendon bro no we're perfect come look
at my wood good job dad what's wrong
with these rotting as beams father my
dad he's the one who birthed me I was
once a sperm selling his penis
right now we're unloading wooden beams
for actually my bed frame like everyone
buys use like expensive la like
Hollywood ass bed frame dobry I'm gonna
lie oh boy I want to make them out of
like literally just wouldn't be like yo
that's a beam if I've ever seen one 1898
sit mace or some old that's beating now
I'm no beep so listen my bed frames lit
my dad's lit I'm lit the loading is lit
that's you if you're not a part of the
loading you could subscribe right now
smack the button in the face during the
strongest family on YouTube now I will
say today it's gonna be an interesting
vlog because my cameraman / roommate /
friend Brendan took today off Brendan
right boys and grindin so I what I got
Fraser my yeah he doesn't know how to
work a camera here's the hot working
phone but I don't want to complain guys
here's the situation
I literally shift my dad out here help
me find wood and build my bed frame as
the furniture company was gonna charge
too much like for once in my life I was
trying to save money and this is what I
wanted I was going for something like
this look you barely tie my shoes that
all I know how to do is plug murciélago
ball that got slashed shop and get
people to subscribe you know just don't
look like the Big Sur dog you're not
stained yet if you want to do the top
part silly your color by match what I
got the same color what do you mean you
buy a vehicle i remand you have bought a
vehicle
scope you did not buy that you bought it
the Eddy looking sexy and his sister ah
must be na ha ha it's a convertible I've
done 24 hour challenges inside cars that
would be challenging the yeti is so sexy
it's just missing one thing
oh my god we've done it the Mercedes
sibling no joke guys team maverick is so
out here like when Jeff and I roll up
places like in the Yeti and whatever he
decides the name here oh the competition
shakes yeah
FedEx you can wait made us wait enough
times now you wait for us if it takes
five to seven days man gonna marry this
girl haven't seen her like do we all
true hand cream yo that's why her hands
are so tiny
yo dough job my wood it'll break cause
it's cheap no I'd like to wake up in the
morning have a nice piece of wood
Bob break take a stupid angry
get back in your car Frank before my boy
does the universe on your face what are
you doing dad picking slivers out of my
hand oh my god you mean to tell me
that's the cheap wood you bought leaked
in your skin you don't say [ __ ] Jeff a
splinter would put those splinters in my
hand myself because Mike said I wouldn't
do it yeah your cookies suck but thank
you Liz yeah you go Mike there we go
I'll take these I'm sure they're okay
[Music]
yeah no no cleaver here
let's go gross Lydia take this disco
ball yeah I love my life yeah we got
your riddles I think it's pretty clear
the best spot to put this meat is right
on Lydia's windshield she's in for a
surprise
get it off okay you owe me a car wash
I'll get you a car wash I just want to
see how you're gonna remove it you won't
do it you will drive with that meat on
your car you are driving honestly my
cars already disgusting so it's a [ __ ]
talk to me about your hand cream Lydia
it was popped open like a tube of
toothpaste
yo your head cream is gone it was
already broken right it was reduced base
ground yeah mad respect
tell them the Falls neighbor Susan
neighbor Suzie yeah
neighbor Suzie on Instagram I see why
you do that Lydia if I were you I just
wouldn't put it on the floor of my car
open like a tuba dude you're my bro is
it where is it that doesn't look like
that's a fact look oh oh that's right
buddy what are you doing out are you
outside
no okay you wanna plug the mort's okay
yeah how to stop this merch in the game
you know it is that maverick lifestyle
where can they get it tell them no you
know you're not supposed to be out of
your cage hey Bri okay guys now on the
vlog we're gonna see what's happening
outside Briana
oh yeah the neighbor brought you again
okay never mind
come on friend look at my friends to the
ball that's my boy oh that's so much fun
and my dad in the rocking chair he's
getting old he can't move much but I
actually do you guys want to bring Lydia
out here and make her feel bad for a
tripping Mike into the pool what did you
put at the bottom of the pool I know you
did it with your hand cream balls
no it's on that side no no it's on that
side no no he's shouting he's drowning
no Lydia I gotta save him quick dad hold
this video camera
[Music]
so welcome to my house bro I got rocks I
got crystals
[Music]
Oh God either showered by fluffy blonde
hair is back one day he's back with me
oh wow
they're getting married for us a lot of
commitment I or enough me but it'll be
as cute as I luck good luck guys hi
listen guys as if this day couldn't get
anywhere we just set up for the one chip
challenge we got milk bread avocado
chairs for everyone who's gonna die
today oh there's the guy the one chip
challenge what is this basically you can
only eat one chip it's impossible I mean
if you're a maverick right yeah which I
am so I might just eat
I listen this is the one chip challenge
look at it literally the chip is in a
coffin Jesus Christ the [ __ ] one chip
challenge [ __ ] is not paying me money
you owe me money you mother we get a
little background on this because I
actually have no I do not eat this if
you are sensitive to spicy foods are
pregnant I'm pregnant so I'll see you
guys it's made with the hottest pepper
in the world the Carolina Reaper nobody
doesn't like they're doing the Carolina
I think the best way to do this is just
not think about it I heard this this
will literally like make you cry and
like burn your insides for like days
actually you're not supposed to touch
the chip there's like gloves but we're
gonna touch it no joke ladies and
gentlemen and it's packaged oh my good
any last words the Reaper is waiting
parties the Sun is setting so we have to
do this we have to do it now forcing us
into this I'm going boy little bite
Oh right up there let's go baby
[Music]
Aven ship no what are you doing are we
living oh my god no see the thing is
like David affected me I would be I'm
telling you I'm on you ever drink some
elephant oh you'll mind starting to kick
him
Andy you good I don't know anything
Oh
tears streaming down my face you too I
thought today we're gonna make Logan
Paul cry huh I'm not crying I'm sweating
from my eyes it's getting worse okay no
at this point the only thing I can think
to say it make sure to get your merch
Logan Paul back hop / not be a maverick
you know how it is eating chips that
have no dick known to kill people who do
it like demons in my mouth
low gang this is all about mental
strength no matter how many tears your
eyes no matter how much television exits
your mouth as long as you gets a cup
[Music]
I'm I'm fine I don't know about all my
friends but I'm chill the first time in
his life look and Paula's crying I'm not
sorry oh my god I'm not crying
just wet from my eyes is a big
difference no my fingers are tingling
this mambas you're a baby you're not
close of your size because if you're a
guts to do it
no way tell me look applause but I won't
see you oh you're a savage if you do it
oh my god yo your boyfriend's can be
pooping on you tonight we're good
we're definitely chai I know that's fire
my god this is so hot but it's still not
as hot as the hottest this is much
easier
all right okay there's the blog just one
chip challenges no joke if you're not a
part of the low game make sure to
subscribe we risk our lives - for your
entertainment
we all got busy life sometimes but
that's what we're here to do distract
you from that just subscribe for me copy
stuff the house Logan Park on says yeah
he's hard to talk coming up Vice
Families tumor hello guy I love y'all
take it easy
[Music]
now that slightly Oh