and I never thought I was saying this
but Logan Paul vlogs I was up low again
you guys missed me what is up guys
hey yo good morning okay what's poppin
as we were back with yet another vlog oh
my gosh I have a lot to explain so let's
start off with the title of the video
right the end of Logan Paul vlogs I know
what you get I'm gonna get into all of
that later but I know what you guys are
thinking loggia how if you're not
posting vlogs how am I gonna know when
you've got dropped the new merch the
hottest march in the game hold this dawg
look I'm gonna decline to comment I will
say look about that concise yeah it was
good
maverick movement is still alive it's
always gonna be alive we're out here
doing a different route changing the
world every single day boy I do
understand your qualms I unconcern which
I will address I always miss some stuff
right here's some updates I got my other
job is my last leg know yeah you know
yes look okay all right guys you just
show them Sona i'ma get into it I just
want to give some updates on some other
stuff that went down doesn't see your
tweets guys we were the fastest channel
to ever hit 10 million subscribers it
was daily vlogs for like four hundred
sixty days in a row and then had like a
month social media blackout and then
came back and daily blog for a little
bit so I know you're confused and I see
the tweets logo happen in the vlogs
where the vlogs that we'd like you being
savage blah blah I'm missing the vlogs
bro now I'm stuck with Jake and his
goofy friends etc etc we're still gonna
be making waves we're still gonna be a
run in this platform because the low
gang is the strongest family on the
internet that's a fact by the way imma
get into it alright here's what you
missed so this is cool I got carved mr.
beast carved me out of an ice sculpture
there's me in ice
yeah we get the Yeti back today ma'am no
seriously guys I've missed the Yeti so
much it's not the same Yeti you know and
love this thing has monster truck tires
on it ho honey yeah how tall you bro
they might the literally might be taller
than you that'd be a nice wear bro yeah
so we've been shooting sketches uh Evan
and I are making a sketch I think it's
actually coming out tomorrow it's all
right I got started I'm fine and so we
figured we get back into comedy a little
bit kind of like the best friends
scheduie shot yes but no gang I'm
rambling look the point is when you see
the sketch on Instagram at Logan Paul by
the way make sure to drop your boy a
follow it make sure to give it a like
and also maybe comment
speaking of my favorite supervillain ksi
JJ as you guys know we have a beat-down
scheduled for August 25th or I guess
it's technical like a flight but I don't
know how much of a fight it'll be okay
as I was back at it again don't know how
whenever he tweets he always manages to
sound like a Dragonball Z character like
an evil okay this is actually impeccably
tweeted uh August 25th would be the day
I end another youtubers career not true
I'm gonna do second second off Vegeta
YouTube is not my career this is a hobby
I hopped on this platform like two years
ago I've been making YouTube videos
since I was like 10 I have diversified
bro got my tentacles spread out in a lot
of industries third of all bro if
anyone's gonna end my career
okay it's gonna be me I almost kind of
did it once twice not anymore
anyways guys it's time to go pick up the
big Yeti oh she's my baby i'm missin'
earth's the moment you've been waiting
for an actually speaking of it's a
little Yeti right there was good a part
back you see into the alleyway Ivan just
took a spin and in his Yeti I can see
everything I didn't think that was that
steep alright and go two miles an hour I
thought I could get it I went up on the
ramp
okay this is great fun the mini is
absolutely amazing but it is time we
gonna pick up the visual
[Music]
just be careful now heaven wouldn't want
your crash in this car to go up a hill
then flip this car i'ma sit here in
these car rides I'm thinking too
literally the only thing that's bad
about this maverick much time to do it
different shirts you can't see cuz it's
on the bottom what do you we have tilted
over backwards probably not yeah just a
foot flip I must have missed that
[Music]
hey Evan do you think I could try mm-hmm
hey Spence read the title card for
always it's a dry me whenever I Drive
you to spins
[Music]
oh hey there guys I don't think this
would be a logan paul vlog if something
didn't go wrong yeah yeah the audio cut
out in the car so here's a voiceover but
it's not that big nothing really amazing
happens here except oh my god what is
that oh it's my baby the Yeti okay this
is me reacting to seeing the Yeti for
the first time in forever that's just
like when you break up with a girlfriend
and you meet up to have makeup sex
that's how I'm feeling right now anyways
guys it turns out that the tires were
literally almost bigger than Evan this
guy a victor he told me that my G Wagen
what's the only G Wagen with tires this
big in the world 40 inch tires
oh man not to mention the ladder on the
back Evan climbed up on top of the roof
rack which we also now have and even
came with an axe and a shovel for
whatever reason you're gonna use a
shovel for but anyways this cool also
has these these wires these cables on
the front of the vehicle for extreme
effort actually have no idea what
they're for but I could talk about how
cool this is all day but I just think
it's better if we doin a bit more job
[Music]
it's like spinning a wall right now Road
no it's just showing nothing and
combined with the little voiceover mic
issue we had that we literally just
found out about that because we went
back and look at the footage and you can
hear I leave it over here this one out
well we got good news oh it's that way
all right that driveway and climb up in
there I think we can find it bug sick
all right so who wants to do the
trespassing me are you ah okay so you
got a lock on that signal but we're
closed I think if you stick your ass out
a little bit more it'll elongate the
signal I know just clearly until we're
in Jurassic Park
baby what's that when t-nuts saw these
[Music]
do you think that has something to do
with the problem you like that would
affect like probably we got the footage
though let's go got it do it dude
perfect trail we gotta get the yeah guys
I want to you know talk about the title
of the vlog and everything I want to get
the Yeti up here doing a cool spot
there's just one problem I'm seeing
Spencer you see it down there
all right you referencing that huge pile
of dirt yeah put in the divot find it's
a big old pile of dirt here the divots
right here and I definitely see how it
could be a problem to get over we're
forgetting something specific follow me
here cuz I got a shovel I was like I'm
never actually gonna use it it's been 30
minutes
like they put dirt here so people
wouldn't do this most vehicles don't
have a shovel included with them there
you go keep going I think you're about
two and a half percent there I think
that's good
nothing to it but to do it there's a
high chance that the same thing that
happened to Evan in his mini Yeti today
could happen to me right now I
definitely don't want that that's a
steep hill bro chances are this could
work I don't 90 69 percent something
like that you
[Music]
okay pro hockey
so top-heavy on this thing yeah go slow
Hey
you need more speed
I know my baby could do it
whoa
oh yeah
let's go
[Music]
the view right now is absolutely
breathtaking
if we overcame that little hill pushed
ourselves a little bit Oh forgetting the
challenge we would be gifted with the
universe with doll that Oh baby look
around
golden our goals and our bro life is
beautiful right now
[Music]
alright guys the title the end of Logan
Paul vlogs honestly I feel like this is
a great spot to talk about it while I
explain how I'm feeling so if you guys
are in the low gang if you're subscribed
you can you know this I kind of hinted
at this in the vlog the other day you
guys mean the world to me you are the
reason for my success and YouTube my
success in general the reason I'm able
to enjoy views like this or purchase a
vehicle like this we have started a
movement in the form of maverick I joke
and I and I make jokes about looking
bald like I was shot but I attribute
most of my success a lot of my success
to not only working hard to not only get
up over the hill but to do it different
to look at a situation and be like ok I
see where everyone's going I see how the
path has been paved how can I throw a
little spice on it a little salt bay to
make it both true to me answer to my
passion so basically where I'm going
with all this is thank you the vlog life
has been absolutely incredible I don't
want to get emotional I don't want to
get emotional bro from the first pop-up
shop we had in New York City
- shutting down the Dubai Mall
I could literally go on all day to all
the incredible things we've done but
it's a fan driven channel and I never
thought I was saying this to sit down in
front of like a desk or something
they're like well it's the end of the
book right now I bet no ok well kind of
it is the end of the daily vlog that
word daily yeah guys I have done a lot
of logs every day in a row and not
blessed and I'm thankful your boy wants
to exercise this creativity in different
ways you guys know we have a talk show
coming soon it's called impulsive we
just built a studio in my house it's
sick and that's gonna be a vlog for next
week I don't make these hits bro I want
to dive into music I want to start new
business endeavors and you guys know we
got the ksi if I coming up so not only
that but I'm training as well just a lot
of stuff so the vlog is not finished and
I will and I am proud to say the vlog
will never be finished as long as my
heart stays something on this goddamn
planet Earth blog is my two feet around
this here soil but like I said daily
vlogs it's not every day
[Music]
and if this disappoints you the good
news is the pink hoodies pink maverick
hoodies are back in stock so that's good
for a little bit they're gonna sell out
quick so looking for that comes slash
out oh I'm just it's a happy day
honestly I haven't been this happy in a
while and it's such a good way to end
the day on this beautiful mountain with
my brand new car and Spencer quick
request huh can you please stay this tan
like the lighting it makes you look like
a goddess sure thanks man but there's 0%
chance of that happening I'm as white as
mayonnaise oh my god I love gang that is
the vlog if you're not a part of us make
sure to subscribe the vlogs are gonna
keep on coming your boys gonna get more
and more and more and more and more
little babies back we go hooking up
hills getting back over that is another
story but we'll see what happens low
gang I love you guys
[Music]
you said tomorrow do you want to say
I'll see you next time but there is a
vlog tomorrow okay all right see you
next time is what I gotta say from now
on
but I will keep that all right
[Music]
anyways guys JJ is back at it yo can you
shut up