[Music]
conspiracy theories we've all heard them
global warming to kill John Africa but
even crazier people that actually
believe that
I'm gonna say this as a friend do you
think the earth is flat the earth is
flat when the earth is flat aren't its
flattened straightest line structure
that we're living it has been
misdescribed what shape is the earth
flat think that the Earth's flat because
if it wasn't flat and we would all be
falling off of it
[Music]
it gives me great pleasure to announce
for the 2018 3rd flattered of
international conference this many
people to start questioning the reality
the truth set you free
the evidence they presented at the
get-go space is nonsense do you
acknowledge that other planets around
I don't know acknowledge that other
planets are planets you think that it's
round is because I could shake your eyes
we don't have toilet water flying out on
people in Australia because of gravity
when you're taught that you just came
from nothing because the scientific
narrative is nothing exploded and
created everything more crazy I didn't
know any of this stuff before I came
here and like yes sir letting me to set
you free I can teach you some things
it's tough because you've been told
something your whole life and you didn't
a certain way right
how becoming a fire I'm not saying I am
Robbi I just don't know what to believe
anymore the truth set you free
my name is Logan Paul and I think I'm
coming out of the Flat Earth closet
[Applause]
and we are being separate
[Music]