I don't think you realize what you've
walked into
[Music]
murder that you I finish you off and
Angel Korea okay wait pause what the
[ __ ] is that
what is your face dude are you pooping
Jay Jay are you pooping your pants it
looks like someone gave you drugs and
then ran your face over with a Russian
tank and then me what's good with me why
do I look so skinny I'm like a little
[ __ ] look at me a real-life zoom in I'm
gonna I'm a beef stick bro
anyways back to business go rematch
round two just ladies and gentlemen
that's right it is confirmed bro I am so
excited one year later and I finally
finally get to avenge this disgusting
draw that took place in Manchester
mmm-hmm not this time hahaha
Jay Jay I am gonna knock you the [ __ ]
out this time I am NOT leaving up to the
judges and it's here in Los Angeles at
the Staples Center one of the coolest
venues in the United States and it's
gonna be on the disown app which has
basically been Netflix for combat sports
so look November 9th the mark of the day
if you're here in Los Angeles or
anywhere flying it is gonna be the
biggest sporting event of the year I
guarantee it's gonna be sick I've been
training we are professional boxers bro
no headgear I remember I complained
about this last year I did not want to
wear headgear they made me wear headgear
and this year we're going down to ten
ounce gloves last year was 12 ounce so
that's gonna be super violent awesome
Eddie Hearn is promoting he's one of the
biggest boxing promoters in the world
and again we are actually legitimately
professional fighters like when people
asked me what I do now I don't have to
say oh my videos on the Internet I could
actually say that I Pogan law I am a
professional fighter and look guys I get
it last year and the year before that
and the year before that and also the
year before that I've been pretty
controversial sort of a polarizing dude
not everyone likes me that's okay for
those of you who are not on my side yet
stay tuned because here are 12 reasons
why I'm gonna be ksi in the next fight
and last year's way in case I wore two
pairs of underwear and stuffed his pants
to hide his micro penis however I have
an incurable case of be de my laughs is
cute as [ __ ] here's proof your laughs
makes me want to ride an ostrich into a
volcano
sound like a [ __ ] ambulance
while I was training hard this year you
were on tour making soundcloud music if
your songs were half as good as your
music videos maybe you'd sell out 50
person venue Logan that's my name and
it's a real name your name is just
letters in the past year I grew a
sexy-ass beer looks like you grew a baby
hope you don't about this one it's been
over a year since we last fought
remember that time you hit me after the
bell yeah you do cuz you're a scumbag
meanwhile I am a charitable man here you
go kind sir just look what I did to this
guy with the closed hand or this guy
with an open hand we dreams wanker you
couldn't even beat me in your own
country this time I got the home-field
advantage
welcome to America [ __ ] I still get
along with my brother the last time I
saw your brother he was my podcast I
leave my bedroom often jayjay still
films all his videos in a rolly chair
who knows maybe he's too sick to get up
I'm stronger I'm taller I'm faster and
I'm better-looking in fact I hooked up
with his ex girlfriend in Ibiza what's
up it's true in the past year both
maverick and Kong have died just like
your music career yep so that's that
thanks for coming to my TED talk really
though I'm excited guys this is this is
the biggest thing in my life ever
probably and it's gonna be fun to to mop
the floor with JJ's face here in Los
Angeles I'm absolutely stoked for this I
want to see all you guys there and if
you can't make it it's gonna be
available to watch on the disown app JJ
bro I I hope I hope your training
because last year when I barely knew how
to box you couldn't beat me this year
with actual training and by the way I've
been training this whole past year while
you've been doing your soundcloud rap or
music tour I'm rolling heads dude I'm
collecting skulls
I'll give you 90 seconds hey guys thanks
for watching the video I will see you
next time November 9th
save the day but not subscribe to my
channel no problem you don't got to do
that you don't got to do all that it's
time to make history I'll see you guys
next time