Logan why why are you crying ready you
know IRA crying why is your fault how is
it my fault you leave me Thanksgiving
okay Freddie's leaving me for like four
days yo but you wasn't reporting your
family yo guys I had to hire three guys
to replace you cuz you're the equivalent
three Mandrake oh that's man who the -
she's calling me a Mike what's up Jeff
anyways here's why it's a big deal
Brendan today's the biggest that's right
now they're just job red joggers bro
who's doing it the highest most softest
quality mercs this gets me so excited in
fact I'm so excited my brand-new house
is going to shambles didn't even break
okay maybe these bottles are Mavericks
on the booty you a maverick you maverick
I respect you need to get some job guys
today is our red drop we are dropping an
entire red collection of maverick stuff
including I know you guys have been
seeing it and the red maverick hoodie
homey homey how can one person tell her
to get the red panties and go to her
favorite spot for dinner I'm buying
yeah guys you know Black Friday's coming
up Cyber Monday is coming up so we
wanted to do something special for you
not to mention bro for the next like
five days yes five days we're doing a
20% discount on the site I was doing it
guys we are not doing this I think again
for like ever so make sure you get your
merch while you can little ball that cop
/ shopper link in description join the
maverick revolution like my room heaven
is a wiener out why I mean it's not but
like I guess just so much stuff going on
be free young and he's off yeah
hopefully we don't lose confidence guys
also the best part about this is if you
go to the website and grab your merch
between Wednesday and Monday I'm picking
two of you to fly out here hang out with
me at the Maverick I'll ride in the
vehicles Pat Kong help me find calm when
he runs away yeah there's just a lot of
stuff going on I have to eat Andy's food
very important for growth growing boy
you know me six foot two blonde boy Josh
let's go serious for a second Andy got
you some flowers for your mother
[Music]
don't forget about the red drop
so you guys look pretty cool hey hey how
you doing
one question what's up at the bags boys
like why you have bags like you're gonna
Airport or something yeah like what do
you mean like I don't need three extra
roommates no offense okay
sick now yeah you're right okay y'all
replacing Brandon might as well you're
gonna join team average you gotta be a
maverick brawl I gotta get you a Nemours
brawl
I need you to pick up some of the finest
merch in the game it's good stuff it's
the merch closets currently under
renovation needs some work
yeah yo it's red day oh I'm not gonna
lie we're all wearing this brothers
Sabbath oh it's gonna be high all right
you guys put those on imma be uh
touching but there's my butt touching
butts waiting for the ball
[Music]
yeah okay so we're here at West Coast
Customs I pull in and I noticed
something little brother Jake is here oh
this makes me nervous
why is all me here don't be his car's
right there what is the blood shard
doing here oh whoa hold up first off the
squad okay we're blood it out we're red
dude let's go maverick super boom let's
make the blood shark a real blood sure
look sharp hey vocab all the counselors
shop flippers up for the next I did
separate money black rhotic but I'm
actually nervous because like guys I
prank Jake yesterday
you saw I had my painters paint my face
in his house and he told me he's gonna
prank me row selection my car is here
and it's just like I don't know all
right so I don't know how this is gonna
look I had this idea and I just did it
it could look stupid broken coffee all
jokes aside we're about to see what this
actually it looks like rather Jake is
nowhere to be seen so we're good there
Henny bro
[Music]
I saw coming I saw coming he put them
everywhere what you're wearing red shoes
I don't need shoes there are kids in
Africa there's kids in Africa it was I
just thought you needed a naked Jake I'm
preaching on your windshield bro red
drop drop looking up dope with the local
ball that cop slash shop your boy is
happy guys do not forget from now Black
Friday until Cyber Monday it's like five
days I'm not very good at counting
yourself bro site-wide discount it's the
red drop we got the new hoodie the red
joggers my boys got them shorts are you
Oh
oh snap oh you look good Hey so grab
your murse go to the site and I'm gonna
pick two of you to fly out here and take
a ride in this puppy with me man you
guys know I love meeting you in person
so when I fly two of you out here it's
gonna get nice and personal we'll get
the box we'll get done yeah I need to
throw things elidio we can prank ever do
the possibilities are endless
yeah copy Mercer and the guys are gonna
be talking about it the next like five
days because this is a big deal we've
never done this type of dish done before
ever Joe join the maverick revolution
logo ball counts last shopper link in
description guys it's a movement of
people who are doing stuff differently
ie
imagine me driving down the street in
this but it's kind of no I think there's
only one thing left to do bro let's go
with this
[Music]
yeah yo tell me if you're down for this
idea so we get in our vehicles and then
drive home so we don't get arrested yeah
let's do that skit that no damn
literally have had this thing for less
than an hour and extremely dirty despite
how dusty this is guys I have the
perfect solution yeah yo so crazy I just
got my car wrap and he just got so dirty
all of a sudden I was wondering if you
could take it to a washing station
that's the kind that's my god okay hello
gang earlier this morning when I asked
Mac my brand new wall with the
sledgehammer there was a method to my
madness
I was loosening it up from a boy Armani
okay naughty party from the ATO um this
wall has to go if you haven't noticed
look we put a giant bullseye on the wall
if you come to the other side this is
ready to beat the mob okay so this all
jokes aside is gonna be turned into a
merge room locum Paul back home slash
shop so the wall has got to go my man
Armani is literally gonna bulldoze
through this thing we gotta prep my boys
so we brought in some protein and
hydration materials it's new cameras pan
in prosciutto it's a good high in
protein there are some water that's good
okay guys safety has no quitting time
we're gonna put a helmet on the boy
ignore the fact that it's literally
pretty much only plastic and let's just
a little piece of padding
this is actually like this is beyond
stupid we're lining it up in cones
making sure he knows exactly where it
goes
we got the bull's eye so it doesn't miss
oh just to make sure my boys are going
too fast cuz you know Armani's fast we
put a parachute on him just jump
aerodynamic baby my boy Frank is gonna
toss him the football guys this is no
drill this is real life like college
professional NFL football like a DB my
god
[Music]
[Applause]
it's a blog a lot of good stuff today
we're wrapping cars we're breaking
through walls the Maverick red jump is
going down guys the biggest drop we've
ever done christmas came early for five
days but like now through cyber monday
20% off site-wide discount guys we're
not doing this again
man we dropped a long sleeve all kinds
of stuff guys i promise you it is the
hottest softest merch in the game join
the maverick revolution I'm gonna play
two of you out here to riding a brand
new
I feel like why are you who are you