oh this is actually gross all right this
is kind of cool you can so guys right
now I'm doing ADR additional dialogue
recording for my movie valley girl look
there's me right there aha super lip
yeah you can tell the movie's gonna be
great no seriously though guys it's
coming out a June 29 the next year oh I
wouldn't know because I'm not there yet
but I'm on my way if you're not a part
of the low gang make sure to subscribe
guys were poppin we're super live we
sing songs about being awesome my voice
is gone bro I scream way too much in
these words well okay that's cuz I love
you man it's all about energy come here
okay
yo they know me bro I requested a gym my
idea wow thanks valley girl also real
quick this morning I was looking in the
mirror I was like damn my head is shaped
like a lemon but then I looked in my
clothes I'm like but it's all good cuz
this merch I'm not even like I'm not
just saying this I'm so happy and proud
with what we've been able to create in
the form of the merch should we get a
quick like know who's doing it really
it's the softest merch ever and it's
swaggy ask you to do yourself a favor
cop yourself some map of Mars guys it's
the movements to revolution literally
the word maverick means someone who's
different and we're all different some
people think that's a negative thing not
me bro I think that's special I think
that's what makes everyone unique and
that's what makes us special and
everybody be hopping on the train guys
Logan Paul calm /or Lincoln disgust
anyway as usual guys we got an epic day
ahead of us Hey okay guys so in about
two days we're releasing my 2017 year in
a review video though last year bill
this guy hates bro has like ten million
viewers and I wasn't even like vlogging
hard but now I mean you guys have seen
it 2017 so funny vlogging in real life
cuz like I'm just like so out here bro
hello my children children actually
scare me anyways guys a lot of thought
is going into this video we want to get
like the most epic locations right so
we're at the Griffith Observatory uh
honey son brenneke Zuma son I move our
way Freddie go
Wow so beautiful I really had though I
think you guys are gonna love this video
hey that's great he's from Scotland you
can scroll in accent issed that's
anyways I'm so hyped for this video
promise me when you see this tap a like
on it like I'm filming this vlog two
days in advance what where did you buy
it from we should take a picture bro at
Logan Paul
thank you serving happy holidays
my daughter is in love with you but she
won't hug you so I'm going to yo respect
brother you're the coolest dad I've ever
seen in my life besides my great father
and there you go
hello gang I spent the whole day making
the 2017 year review video the best it
can be and this vlog is nowhere near
done I'm Frost yet hey Lydia give me a
plate okay that definitely helped also
though I do have good news
I have roommates to help me keep my
vlogs
started it wait no dogs can't tell if
it's a good thing what he jumped off
this row I like snap my neck and my
whole spine crack like it might be
broken or it might be like their
beautician she's leaving she's going
home for the holidays you know a
Christmas do something nice for everyone
in the house you included
Brendan included Brendan you're included
really there is so you're gonna get your
gifts separately but Lydia you know go
home for the holidays it's Christmas
it's the giving season
no it's $2,000 cash really yeah
you got it haven't you went this morning
that's smart as a businessman okay tell
me when he gives to what do we get is
absolutely none
by Lydia i'ma leave this here for you
destroy the joke I tell them to run away
why are you running same direction
how dare you destroy my joke oh forgot
to mention my dad's working to everyone
at the maverick house is hard at work we
got stuff that needs to get done before
the holidays guys its grind time my dad
I was once a sperm cell in his penis the
holidays yes it is all right it's a it's
the giving season yes it is I'm working
hard on my house trying to go I got you
a gift
you did oh boy $2,000 cash you spend how
you want it got you you gotta work for
you so I'm gonna bring my family no he's
keeping that let's talk about my merch
room for just one sec look it's
incredible young but that's not the
point okay the guy who built this is the
guy who painted me on my Jim he's
actually building something in there
which I'm gonna show you later no I
can't see a problem but y'all know him
y'all love him he broke my wall
flashback
our money AKA is adi party yeah what you
got here roses interesting uh I'm back
in town yeah and I'm cooking up some
stuff okay
as usual it's not my process works bro I
just I just put it together I come to my
lab I figure it out respect actually I
have no what barban I wouldn't get to
the stuff I bought ten times the amount
of anything they said to get I would
hope so cuz let me just disclaimer this
is all kid stuff like for school like
literally I'm looking at the supplies
young scientist for surface that I'm not
young like I'm gray aging you can tell
by my hairline but oh my god it's going
down this looks cool alright it's pretty
you got the vials you got oh sparklers
watch that smoke bombs things are
bubbling things are bubbling but does it
work oh it works that's a good thing to
be doing at midnight but respect our
money respects safety first thanks good
job where's mine oh well that's simply
because ya know you know what the dopest
part about these bubbles are you're
ruining my brand-new patio oh this
reminds me of like when I drink way too
much is like what happens to my body
like right before I throw up
learning alcoholism know that kids don't
drink like you'll you'll die I've seen
it look young scientist oh this is
actually gross oh damn
Wow why are you busy why are you here
this time well uh we are building you
the world's greatest bunk bed that's a
wrap what don't we have in the house the
answer is a bunk house guys when and a
was staying here by the way Andy Andy
it is dead nope no no he went back to
Washington but I missed some guys we
left early I got up early so this is a
tribute to Andy who I think is still
alive
we love you Andy but yeah the point is
guys we had nowhere for people to sleep
and smash so we had no choice but to
build a bunk room oh well I dry ice you
don't think it will you'll think both
muchos better
that's accented yeah hey mister you know
it's funny you bring that up can you
help me you won't help me I'll get
manager Jeff oh so I kind of put my
pants in away
sort of you this out all right guys all
jokes aside we do have a problem my
kidneys failed just kidding no the bunk
room is not done tonight so we've been
in this situation before I'm a good
vlogger literally I've made a commitment
to give you guys the best content in the
world that's what we've done since day
one of vlogging so we're gonna cut to
the morning when the bunk room is
complete and do the reveal event and in
all fairness it's something that should
probably take over a week no joke all
jokes aside again these guys do things
so look they built this entire okay no
we didn't I don't Armani doesn't do that
Jeff respect guys cut to the morning now
right it's the morning are you doing so
guys I forgot they're actually taking
some of my stuff today this is all
rental furniture and we got real
furniture that we own coming today
actually um
two couches their Mercedes couches stop
for the buck just kidding bad news low
gang something went awry last night yeah
all right a WR why what's the sitch
they're Armani
well you know things happen nail guns
break other people come in and they need
a nail gun broke last night it never
broke that we're actually hammering
nails one by one is not the best used to
be a sign so the bunkhouse they weren't
able to complete it they didn't nail it
regardless Logan I'm still gonna show
you the progress because I feel like I
owe that to you today's vlog has been
weird trust me even today I have to film
the video the big video which is coming
out tomorrow by the way to be ready to
like it but yeah let's go check this out
the thing about the crew right yeah like
they don't stop and so it's physically
impossible great so in sleeping in there
they're basically on the normally see
that part but you definitely see what's
gonna happen here like it's dull there's
bunk beds for dolphins four-way smashing
with a nice view of the house
everything's poppin it's just not done
so weird one today bro but it happens
you I do this every day guys give it a
brag also sorry for those guys leaving
if you're not a part of the lugging make
sure to subscribe we have the most epic
video ever produced on this channel
coming out tomorrow
be ready to like that for me turn your
notifications on and copier maverick
merge literally the hottest softest
warmest March in the game it's winter
it's cold not anymore with your Matt
Logan Park I'm slash shop or they give
with that set low gang I'll see you
tomorrow which is actually just my today
check it out
the guy