[Music]
when you're in high school you either
love or you hate the squeeze dances
personally I love them right I love the
dance offs I love dancing with the girls
I loved watching people who grinded too
hard get sent home for being too horny
it was the most amazing [ __ ] show of the
year now in our school there wasn't much
of a limit on grinding like I swear to
God I saw girls go from slow dance to
standing-up grinding to bent over grind
to upside-down grind all in one song
especially the girls in the grade above
us they could dance like a twerk and
[ __ ] another important piece of
information this was right around the
time the lonely island song GZA my pants
came out which is when I learned what
jizz is and that it could be done in
one's pants so keep that in mind anyways
it was homecoming dance and little horn
ball Logan is dancing his ass off when
all of the sudden he sees the notorious
Trisha Michaels through the sea of
equally horny teenagers motioning for me
to come dance with her nutrition
michaels was a senior she was the
hottest girl at the dance and she was
also the best dancer this was gonna be
the best day of my life so I wattle over
to Trisha erections safely tucked in the
belt line like every other boy at the
dance she grabbed my hands put them on
her hips and started grinding harder
than a single mother working three jobs
in a low-income neighborhood it was
everything I had ever dreamed of was
coming true seeing your girl dancing
with me
freshman noodle armed Logan got it and
it felt great but suddenly it started
feeling too great I felt some type of
euphoria and wasn't sure what was
happening
[Music]
the song was over so Tricia hugged me
and walked away but alas as I looked
down I had realized I had used my pants
it's true I was standing there in the
middle of the dance floor jizz in my
pants but I didn't give off [ __ ] I just
danced with Trisha Michaels I was the
coolest kid on the planet so cool that I
thought it was a good idea to tell all
my friends exactly what happened oh my
gosh she was so good in fact I think I
just my pants wait what yeah I dude she
was so good I actually jizz my pants
wait are you serious um yes
I think so oh yeah actually definitely
yeah I blacked out and it just happened
I couldn't help me within minutes
word spread and no female would step ten
feet close to me I was the kid he chased
his pants at the school dance little
preview best
it was horrible but come on this was
just a one-night thing right wrong at
school the next day people gave me
toilet paper to shove in my pants
through new underwear at me made all
sorts of cruel ejeculate some jokes and
this lasted for my entire freshman year
i far one of the most embarrassing times
in my life so listen the moral of the
story is under no circumstances do not
dance too close to your school dances
because you will jizz your pants and
ruin your high school reputation like
and subscribe
[Music]