can i get some logan
ksi v logan paul tickets no it doesn't
look like it's gonna [ __ ] happen
because logan's too [ __ ] [ __ ]
logan's too [ __ ] [ __ ] can't be
talking about me right
not me i'm not a [ __ ]
what's good i'm just saying and mind you
this dude he's good at manipulation
that's his tactic the first three videos
he actually made of this year were about
me
and the fight just an ample amount of
words coming from his mouth and i've yet
to weigh in on what's happening with the
rematch and i want to
finally say something because i saw this
video today and i found it uh comedic
logan's too [ __ ] [ __ ] me [ __ ] was
[ __ ] good
so listen i felt about a month ago jj's
team
seemed sort of uninterested in pursuing
the conversation around the fight and
actually making progress to make it
happen
i was unsure if he was gonna still do it
because guys i'm still training and by
the way i'm not training for no reason
not to stay in shape i'm training so i
can beat ksi's ass so this doesn't
happen again
in fact the other day we had our gym
rearranged
to train more efficiently oh no oh my
god
oh my god this is incredible shut the
[ __ ] up
so i'm taking this very seriously i want
to make this happen not only for
for me as like a sort of finish what i
started type thing but for the fans
obviously like you guys want to see the
rematch so i'm training and then i go
online and i see um
ksi's is is making videos where wow wow
you my friend are looking a bit sick
what what what happened what i mean are
you even trying and so i'm wondering if
he's like losing motivation if he
doesn't want to do it like
here's what i will say i am fighting
someone this year and we will have a
venue
in the united states jj i would love
that for you to be you
so i could push your face into the
ground
i'm not good at talking
[Laughter]
i'm not a [ __ ] bro what i'm saying is
this
i'm gonna replace you if you don't step
up and one other thing that i know
you're going on
a music tour to promote those amazing
tunes of yours
gonna be a good show i feel like you
should hit up nick crompton and he could
open for you i'm the english ever this
saturday night
mini cooper and you chick to my right
and i love nick this is all coming from
a place of love but also [ __ ]
you i'm not a [ __ ] no no seriously
though [ __ ] you
because here's why you either a aren't
gonna have time to train or b
are no longer interested in actually
fighting me again i've said this before
publicly um we were supposed to fight
this month in february and after the
last fight when we proposed to
to fight in december or yeah even
february
ksi refused he did not want to do that
and he backed out
you already broke the contract i mean
i'm just saying yo who's the [ __ ]
compulsory
you could stick to wii boxing ultimate
i got one question for you ksi
you're good bro not to mention it is
actually much harder to get an
unsanctioned boxing match approved
in any of the states in the usa i feel
like england is
just a bit more lenient with the rules
what do i know i'm just a kid from ohio
we're working to make it happen we're
talking to
big big big production companies and
yeah it does take time my team is making
moves internet youtube i can assure you
that everything that comes out of jj's
mouth like this
his team ain't doing [ __ ] bro i'm sorry
it's all talk end of the day let's take
action right let's make an action plan i
made this video you can make your videos
we can go back and forth uh let's sign a
contract
with a date or at least like one to two
months that are set in stone that we
cannot back out of preferably with some
sort of repercussion
so if one of us does back out the other
person gets xyz whether it's like
monetary or like
i get your youtube channel which by the
way i'll just delete and do
the internet a favor i'm here i'm ready
i'm training so
let's get god bro with that said logang
love you guys thank you for watching hit
that subscribe button get your murders
from every merge how to softest merch in
the game all my mavericks out there the
low gang i will
not let you down on this fight i promise
i would rather die than uh not win this
fight
with that said i love you guys
[Music]
hey for those of you who watch these
little clips at the end of the content
hey thank you b
i know you're the real fans see i hope
you're enjoying uh my new animated
cartoon series cha
shales comes out every thursday next one
is about how i [ __ ] my pants at the
school dance
and also best friends comes out every
tuesday so yeah give those videos thumbs
up when you see them thanks guys