I know I'll be alright I know for a fact
I'll be i I've snow understand bro like
I'm my [ __ ] boys up that's not doing
it [ __ ] up like that [ __ ] these boys
[Music]
day three last day of the 72-hour
military training combat boot camp I
can't feel my forearms you saw my
Instagram story I have bruises and
scrapes all over my leg needless to say
I'm in a lot of [ __ ] pain we just
drove two and a half hours to Virginia
Beach because Dom the ex SEAL Team six
member has his facility here so he's
gonna run us through a workout today bro
a little nervous I kind of just want to
go back to Encino and pet my dog
Broly so I'm just kind of crossing my
fingers that we do not perish here we go
what's Tom's goal today like you see
China kill us none of what you're gonna
do today will be more difficult than
what you did yesterday unless it is more
difficult and the [ __ ] logic is that
you don't know what you're gonna face
just be ready for anything
aye-aye captain I don't use doors doors
are for [ __ ] you guys better than you
were yesterday nope so much pain pain
always makes us better you know that
yeah sure so we're at the Dyna
misalliance headquarters in Virginia
Beach this is a private facility what we
do here is extremely confidential
anybody that walks into dynamesh my goal
is to take them from a liability and
turn them into an asset so I hit that
ocular and I move to the side
[Music]
five four
bihaan that bag my boy he'll make me
paranoid okay we're getting ready to
start scenario one am I gonna have to
put it on after this okay wait what's
going on 40 Cal for Tom yeah what the
[ __ ]
40 count time this is part of our
standards constant Rho is APM Mexico
these all the reps I need this no time
starts now
[Applause]
it's Logan the best version of himself
right now that's a question that we all
have to ask ourselves pride ego all
those things it's about humility here
you're always the student and if you
walk in here without that mindset you're
gonna be one step behind you're gonna be
behind the power curve you have got to
open your mind every single day with is
what I'm doing the best version of me
are you the best with your mindset and
are you approaching life in every bit in
every way to the best of your ability
not give it up for you I never
[Music]
I know how bi I know for a fact Albie I
ice tourists and rollin I'm what [ __ ]
your boys up no they're not doing it
[ __ ] up like that [ __ ] these boys up
photos they got me to a place
no I'm serious bro like they got me to
100 and if I I'm trying to bang right
now bro everybody wants to bang but you
have to be smarter you have to use the
tactics cuz they don't have those the
people that come up to us I want to
fight us or whatever wherever we are
they don't have this training you have
to stay under tactical [ __ ] no matter
water not [ __ ] ready no [ __ ]
problem let's [ __ ] go coconuts
[Music]
well these are fun the first one was
just [ __ ] miserable here hey they
said they said here go walk in this room
where 7 guys are gonna jump you know
didn't even say that I wish they said
that I had a [ __ ] open the door and I
had one second to just go and I take it
cuz I don't know what the [ __ ] to do
here's why I'm mad bro they they took me
dude they took me to like 110 I've been
there like like four or five times in my
life and then the next girl was like a
like a walk through like I was ready to
kill people bro I was ready to hurt all
my friends that I just trained with in
the past two days
it's also it's also lonely as hell bro
[Music]
[Applause]
you did a great job with Brian I was
super impressed because you waited there
was more than a beat
you're like what the [ __ ] do I do with
this guy but you didn't shoot Brian put
makeup on Rodney
I saw his bone I understand who's
spraying blood romantic that's your
shirt you took it off and stuck it in
the blood right now you have more
training than 99.9% of the people in
this country and that's a fact
100% you know the last three days you've
gotten stuff that people never get
exposed to I think you guys ended really
strong
[Music]
you know obviously the first thing you
see when you come up is honor but every
star represents one of the guys that
were killed in the community this
memorial is dedicated to all those guys
that have been fighting in the shadows
never asked for recognition never wanted
any anything they don't want to pat on
the back they just want to do their job
and most of these guys step up on a
daily basis and they care about this
country they care about everybody in it
they care about the freedoms that we
have they look at one of these stars I
knew a lot of these guys and I think
it's 30 plus guys that I knew personally
worked with deployed with that I'm
getting killed
[Music]
means a lot to me that you guys are even
here Logan especially you you know and
your whole crew you know you guys are
out there making a big impact on the
world so I want to present you guys with
something this is a Revere blade present
this to you because I feel like this
weekend you earned it I feel like it's
just a start and hopefully it's the
start of a journey for you that helps
change lives and change the future of
the world being around a group of guys
to all of a common goal is we're all are
dedicated and passionate this is this is
a circumstance that is comes few and far
between in my life being around do to
have a mission I didn't know I didn't
know if it was gonna happen I didn't
know if that the evolution was gonna
happen so I got to thank Tim for pushing
us to get out here and and and truly
truly change changing me as a man I
don't think I changed you as a man I
think you changed you I think I think I
think it's zero times a new birth
[Music]