children I don't give it you guys know
yesterday was my big day today's my
first day we gonna I know I'm gonna
teach all right I'm going there what we
going I'm going with RJ I'm saying here
with my favorite son Oh see you later
mom okay this is why I think of that oh
man you know it's crazy we hit 10
million subscribers yesterday and we're
already at 10.1 like a column do you
think we need to go out and buy like a
point one okay cool yeah probably not
well we got our own car and everything
that's not the car ground in his
business on this one same car door Teen
Choice 2017 carpet arrivals don't mind
if I do
I would be a disgrace to the low gang if
I didn't show up to the Teen Choice
Awards the my couch is super feel good
I'm a goofball wait guys I think the
plan is to go get makeup put on my
[ __ ] outfit no this is not it
although it is fired and then walk the
red carpet open up the show won a few
awards and kick flex pay ha ha ha feel
like Conor McGregor whoa ho ho I'm here
so I'm in my room
I just know that this officials woman
but I'm actually a man are you good bro
so I have to pee bro but this is no
urinals do it's only stall the bathroom
to do it do either this do I sit down
okay no more distract after all it is no
big dog gonna try to keep it happy and
positive time for your boy to become
[Music]
my brain I'm not gonna interview
I ignored painless I feel like a mask
over there like in a movie with my Robin
maybe oh yo that was crazy looking
seeing you guys in real life has got to
be one of my favorite things on planet
Earth and just so you guys know how this
works so we did the red carpet and kind
of hot so obviously that's what we're
doing right now I'm in here cooling off
thank you David and then we are going to
go open up the show and it needs us to
say it sounded in the green room about
to run some other good song Thank You
Man oh we're getting you same color too
wait we gotta get to fill out lies you
make you have more subscribers than me I
know I just wanna make you a little
better one day one oh yeah there's a
chance we go on stay together good
you're up for choice female I'm sorry
I'm up for course mail web oh my god I'm
a girl oh my god wait somebody else is
there for no but she's so humble well I
mean I could learn a couple of things
from logic oh she luckily I get a
teleprompter this was a good idea love
the ball welcome to teachers came out
tonight with this it's not moving all
along
[Applause]
are y'all good
[Music]
[Applause]
your boy is blowing up we got award we
got Justin Victoria Justice that is
tough stuff
job and we're all through on this break
we'll be back in 30 seconds the low game
two phone bill you can't dump oh look
mom I'm tell about it how to use a real
kiss themselves I'm so proud I love you
I love you row did you say every day bro
is singing I mean yes I would yeah yeah
yes okay I gotta say it is so cool to be
here with my parents a lot i frickin
love you guys this is a tree it's a long
way from a mile man no weird you know
five years ago I was watching the Teen
Choice Awards on MTV I followed my
dreams I did what I wanted to wasn't
afraid to be different or make stupid
videos on the internet now I'm nominated
for three and my brother's nominated for
two I got to open the awards oh my
parents are here oh sure okay okay mom I
don't think that's what step-dancing is
we'll leave it to the professionals
younger
that's why you want a CD with jaqen at
me so cool mom and so I'm just relieving
myself right now and I'm filming it that
this is what bonding looks like I think
I think the one awards at him up for
choice male web star is coming up soon
just getting out those pre 3p nervous
jitters what am I going to say for my
speech dude you gonna come up with some
quick probably just like
so I think my award is coming up but
I've been here a while like I'm kind of
getting tired
[Music]
I think this is it bro I think this is
the moment or else before my friend
Bella and Melo are presenting the award
I like marshmallows I like marshmallow
what yokai strikes him on the mouth
Martinelli's yeah here's another man I'm
gonna kiss melon you've been voting
online for your choice web star
and the winners holder in my hand guys
right here
[Music]
Liza
[Applause]
[Music]
looking for me we're definitely out here
research it's my big day
you cut me off before I can take the low
gas before we get to surf born from
Venus to the Sharks so the Phoenix and
so strong it won't be the last one ha ha
ha ha Bree next year we're going back
we're going to be honest isn't the more
time that passes I'm like yo it's just
they cut me off took us to was probably
some like commercial probably like like
a shake weight commercial assemble I
didn't get to thank you sorry but we're
going back up I'm not getting let's go
buddy
I don't give a damn hi guys
I just want to take this time to thank
my team Jeff I'll be Jack Paul a man
hated hey you know who you are I love
you bro hobbies and Brendon obviously
sorry the good thing this isn't life I'm
supposed to show you guys you can
achieve whatever you want man four years
ago I was in Ohio on the couch watching
the Teen Choice Award and now I'm here
and I want to teach or sweep
also I have to give a safe to the
stronger family on the Internet
[Applause]
being different keeping really keeping
passionate D life through the lens of
possibility Bey because that's what we
do see am Arabic logos life I'll take
this acceptance
okay grant no you do you would win I
want to on a budget can't do it my vlog
loose in here locket ball my we want me
we cleaned up to do it does anyone ever
Brewer howdy us yo does anyone ever
believe you know please be a smoke yes
if you say yeah they please they preach
I got him
I'm proud of you
[Music]
[Laughter]
wanna go eat food okay yeah sure king
baby king don't mind if I do I'm not a
king yet I'm cataloging where's my
brother
yeah guy that's not Jake okay guys
Jake's nowhere to be found
now that everything is calm down guys
legitimately I owe that award all to you
thank you to everyone who voted
I am truly salty that I didn't get to
thank you on you know live national
television but I'll do it in this vlog
it's going to get more views than the
Teen Choice Awards anyways but it's all
smiles at the end of the day got to open
the show got to see you guys in real
life and if it isn't my brother behind
me brother
oh man such a good way to end the night
someday
guys I'm gonna enjoy my steak but yo
Jake all graduation I'm very product
they don't want year's winners what we
call stay winning son also thank you mom
yeah thank you Dad but without you guys
I I would not be alive so thanks I know
seed okay let's go home back to the crib
oh yo lo getting we had a pretty good
day today yo call what about you but how
was your day nah anyways guys there's
not much else to say other than the fact
that just I just know I am extremely
thankful I'm grateful I'm humble and I'm
honored that this and vloging the low
gang has allowed me to live this this
crazy life but more honored that you
guys get to do it with me okay do not
forget guys don't be afraid to be
different be unique be passionate the
crazy wants to change the world I get
your maverick March on local folk on
/off for linking description I love
y'all don't see you tomorrow check it
isn't bad
yeah
are you I said