[Music]
big moves money moves business moves
stock just went up 10% guys we were in
Dubai I'm slowly but surely falling in
love with the city I had a business
meeting this morning but first you see
some location
[Applause]
a business meeting we're still here like
this is often barely the employees all
invited their kids
[Applause]
this is how we start our mornings and
divide that long
I love Dubai and shelling my her baby's
good stuff just real good stuff manager
Jeff quick question yeah what's the
question how high can the stock go
before it's too high there's no limit
does it stop in Dubai we're going jet
skiing yo but just a guy naive he's been
part of the security team if you look to
your left this is a seven star hotel
literally the nicest hotel in the world
normally stars are you guys know like
five stars now they added two for this
one I literally think the toilets are
made out of gold which makes me wonder
why not have that in my house anyway
something to think about we're going
there later it's just so much yellow my
hubby these guys I'm basically Middle
Eastern one quick thing I want to point
out still plugging bro I know it's faded
though well yo real talk you haven't got
any mercy at Logan Paul that kind of
slash job or the girls would feel like
at this point there's few people who
like don't have their maverick Marge
yellow like get too much yellow on my
hobbies let's do it
[Laughter]
[Music]
Oh yo I love jetski you know what bro
since the Ohio boy has been in LA I
actually haven't been on the water also
makes me think I've won a jetski for our
house like we just put it in the pool
anyways look outside its have been stars
bro how is that possible he's toilet
[Music]
wait what is the poisonous what are you
doing rose water this is a ding see
something I never get in America single
life
no way I saw her fighting me most often
saw him this sort of makes me hate
myself you know I feel like even the
guys falling like in the thin the image
he's flipping he's slipping in gold
we'll go upstairs to the Presidential
Suite
oh and then from there you'll see
everything okay amazing you know what
this reminds me all this gold and lavish
things that no one really needs spend a
lot of money I'm so stupid while I'm
here but I've been good
[Music]
I feel like now's a good time to remind
you this is a hotel how much does it
cost to stay here I feel like you don't
yeah hey this week these windows you
need these this is not for one for is
this is for like throw parties open the
business row why was the walking here
like a big blues go why this would make
them the chestnut that I grew up on what
[Music]
I just flushed a gold toilet
goodbye haters writing a lion is nothing
against
no joke I thought I was a big guy yeah
you're a machine here we're gonna move
the couches yeah I'm good I'm girl stick
blogging uh I've seen you rip people's
heads off is what we do for a living can
we get a flashback can you just give me
like like just like a load to your your
hands registered as weapons you should
do that bro just in case you do kill
someone you won't get in trouble
boxers talk talk talk talk talk walk
around as if there's Sam but I keep my
business in the ring outside the ring
you know keep myself as a general low
gang take notes that's the mindset
another professionalism hello gang I
added a G to my name
[Music]
cool things can you have no speaking of
cool things like I said earlier I got
this the guy at the seed idea in my
brain when I go buy some cool things
baby let's do it hey Shiraz yes now oh
my god he's God keeps bringing the table
they asked me what I bring to the table
I bring the damn table and that's a fact
ok yeah so this is good go to the mall
buy something I shouldn't be buying and
swim with a shark ok yo I hope this
isn't as crazy as the other day you guys
saw the meet-and-greet yeah and this
mall is like literally as big as the
city so it's we have to keep it low-key
it's gonna be hard
what okay try it onto me Josh
Oh easy this cage is no joke
yo this this is cool cuz I've never done
do you guys know this I love doing
things I've never done before I can't
believe I've never done this what a
better place to do this then Dubai look
at this there's an eel that's wrapped
itself around the cage it's a big go you
got a dip bro my turn in the cage you
wish me luck guys
[Music]
you're gonna helmet for me and
everything
[Music]
oh don't do it it's cool because inside
the helmet my hair stays flawless no you
know what I'm kind of salty about haha
salty about so let's start water no no
it's good I didn't get eaten by a shark
imagine the views if I got a there's
everything what is this just stop
hanging from the ceiling there she is
over yonder the Gucci stove also Gucci
you owe me money bro
I plug you way too much you plug Gucci a
lot all the time I'm gonna send the
invoice to your team CEO manager no it's
like it's like a cat just looking at you
in the face oh yeah you get some shoes
bro actually yeah help me spend my money
I hate shopping whoa whoa got the top
yeah yeah you like those yo they look
sexy Brendon I'm not gonna lie about
your stock just went up yeah I got two
now so to really look like a pirate
I met Brendan's got his new Gucci cakes
oh wait hold on I'm gonna the camera my
god hey oh yo I also got this Gucci belt
these pants actually don't need a belt
just put it on the show you it's kind of
plain but like I tried to tell him about
like it's glossy it's but I'm not always
trying to flex can I not just be a
normal human being
I'm Thomas you okay low getting that the
hug I'm gonna end it like I started it
money moves baby power moves we are all
dressed up because we're going to be
Arabian business dinner award meeting
show Festival Coachella type thing which
oh yeah God okay if you're not a part of
the low-key make sure to subscribe this
Dubai trip
honestly that's a great question I like
I don't know I just say just cuz like
you know like I want them to subscribe
if you mean they're not but then it's
like are you good and the answer's no so
subscribe for me join the movement be a
maverick of revolution of people who are
not afraid to be different unique past
those who are willing to work hard and
wear a suit and be an adult for a couple
hours even though they don't like it
that's rizona copy map emerge the
highest most softest quality best marks
in the game
lope all that comes slash shopping
description
[Music]
another way friend you're getting
awfully close to my face and I just got
this acne pimple but I hear they don't
look at it for just Dubai's been so much
fun my pimple just wanted like join the
party is just like I'm here