[Music]
Hey our YouTube channel we're gonna do
supercool pranks ever been done before I
roommate Mike is in the shower so we're
gonna dump flour on again never been
done before on YouTube super original
super cool sorry Mike I love you dude
like it subscribe I'm so sorry
hey what are you doing it looks like
your shower doesn't come on is your
shower where we got stuff to do morning
Mike take some money today
[Applause]
I'm always spending money right and
that's not cool 100k in Vegas come on
90 k podcast room gone 60 K on a dick
upgrade gone wait when did you get that
what what did you get your dick hungry
okay well anyways no more no more
people need to see is saving money so
that's what we're gonna do today but
first before we do that if you're not a
gangster if you subscribe and give this
video a thumbs up in fact get in the
habit of just giving my videos a thumbs
up want to get these views though I want
to get back on Google preferred
[Music]
[Applause]
listen if we don't stop spending money
we will lose the house no but really I
don't want that to happen so I came up
with an idea you know when you go to the
movie and you say I'll take you know two
tickets imagine if you only had to pay
for one ticket how's that possible oh my
let me tell you with this human right
here imagine if me and my best friend
Evan which by the way guys I hope you
enjoyed yesterday's episode of best
friends of his best friend from home go
back and give that video a like and
thumbs up like seriously if you have you
seen the classic like the trench coat
where two people are on top of each
other and they wear a trench coat and
they go into the movies as one person I
think we're gonna make this happen all
we need is disguise so we go and Evan
you be the you be the head and you say
one ticket and we save money we only
spend money on one ticket instead of two
quick question how much is rent here a
lot of money bro 10 to 20,000
potentially a month yeah yeah so movie
ticket us how much like 12 bucks and
$0.50 my calculations are correct boys
we're looking at 36 bucks a month save
if we make just a few more cuts we could
even think about starting to eat again
listen are you Roy there's only one way
to do this actually for real and that is
we needed a very large trench coat a my
wonderful assistant Danny okay you can
walk in and show your face that my
wonderful is Danny got for us thank you
how much was it 160 bucks do you think
it's big enough it was the biggest I
could find so let's hope it's big enough
because that's one question
you spent 160 dollars to try to save 12
dollars
let's draw on the trenchcoat how tall is
he pushing right now definitely I have
never been this tall in your life oh
yeah
no I can't see anything oh my god we
could do a dance through the hump
[Laughter]
[Music]
Devin's not actually a part of me in
real life you have to move your arms
that you are wouldn't work but I think
we should test it out first by the way
we got spire glasses for Evan they're
legit now it's believable as hell
was it oh great I can spread my long
legs out these long legs he removal have
you these legs somehow now that I get
back over to see I'm coming I'm oh god
listen guy is there any way you can give
us one ticket we're trying to save some
money okay I want to buy one get one now
deal it's not possible one is worth the
bras removed from Google preferred this
man I will not stand here under my
friend and get swindled and pimped by
this business appreciate you for your
time let's try something else
[Music]
that's why I was like no no he you tried
to swim over the pit box and I will not
be won over by business I will not be
played by the system I won't how's the
movie bad news Mike what didn't work
what I mean they knew we were one person
to stack on top of another person they
discriminated against your size I'll
just say from here I'll have you know
that my 2 foot one friend is two frets I
will
[Applause]
I listen bro we have to try something
else and we gotta get creative this is
gonna how many people do you see here
[Music]
[Applause]
hi John we can take a hard left we're
gonna take a hard left grab my hand -
John right here here we are here we are
[Music]
going boy yeah gully yeah yeah do please
how you doing man lamo Laemmle alright
let's go let's go Lou all right Thank
You Laemmle I'm gonna go left now and
now we'll go straight into the theater
tuck those legs in tuck those exit all
right no way that's a do not enter Oh
[Music]
what is that a third ticket no these are
my regular lanes I like to write
China source track syndrome yeah long
legs short short arms you got short arms
you could see who this guy oh I was so
what's happening is he was born with an
incredible deformity lower head demand
it's where most abdomens are he actually
is a head there right think thanks guys
wolf here we go we're going straight now
to leave take take a hard right in the
board the work
I got two things what do you mean so
close they almost wanted it really I
have another idea
I feel like the reason we're I feel like
the week weezing weez no way the reason
we're not getting let in like I don't
know about you but I'm feeling a bit of
like sexism type thing going on sure
so I brought a girl you're gonna be our
girlfriend Jackson our or mine
your girlfriend cuz I'm part of you I
guess
[Music]
I know thank you for taking me no right
left right no left left right hello
brought me down here let me get over
this
whoo thank you so much
[Music]
what is the words upstairs still going
straight
[Music]
for what reason in my body my boyfriend
yeah they're just coming see how
handsome you are so this way to the
right no no there right there right you
going
[Music]
oh my god that was amazing the movie was
great we did it yes we got a new couple
on our hands that's incredible if you
guys are not a part of the low gang make
sure to subscribe I hope you enjoyed the
video today run there subscribe button
get your Mercia live all the cup size
shop
[Music]
I love it yeah they do they just ran
away
[Music]