and not to get hella cheesy but this is
definitely a life moment I've waited my
whole life to do this I see Jean Claude
Van Damme do this watch so he was in
between two semi-trucks
[Music]
well I literally felt my scrotum just
ripping down the center I'm God i'ma
nailed it we'll be doing that they're
gonna both be sprinting 50 miles an hour
down pasture
conversation $30,000 later in two weeks
of sawing drilling and pounding at 8:00
a.m. in the morning and this has got to
a place I really like much obviously
more efficient than the Mercedes couches
that have now been Oh to shreds anyway
I'm a can idea to put a bridge across
saying until we get the cushions here I
don't know what to do with this space I
mean you could put a pit bull on the pit
I could put pit bull in a pit
now it's an arm pit animals [ __ ]
[ __ ] dude I'm gonna be honest while
riding this horse around the
neighborhood is one of the coolest
things I've ever done in my life I want
you guys to know I'm terrified right now
the animals scare me immensely they're
so big they could do whatever they want
look I'm not telling do is he's doing it
his spine is turning in full-on zoo I
got two dogs to pay to real horses one
fake horse a turtle some fish more fish
and ex drug addict who's now a
best-selling author and a Paris where
the guy's about to be Noah's Ark in this
[ __ ] and as you guys know we'll be
choosing one person from the Maverick
club to come to our ranch and ride the
horses with us as well as the copious
amounts of other benefits we provide to
our members our VIPs for example today I
had a zoom call with a member named
Tyler great guy we actually played smash
bros against each other and he won yeah
he beat me good [ __ ] sorry to say this
Tyler I'm actually gonna kick you out of
the club
just kidding me I head over to Matt for
clothing calm signed up and join the
most exclusive cool best ever curated
special experience on the Internet you
yeah go whack job I'm a psycho and
straight-up batshit crazy yo the Apple
does not fall far from the tree Greg
yeah tavar let me buy her a $2,500
saddle if ever you like the saddle okay
well if you like it everyone sign up for
the math club so I can afford this
saddle for my girl comment below how
much y'all would pay to see one of
Josie's nipples are we gonna test this
out on our horse outside this is great
feels good feel safe very sturdy man
okay damnit are you gonna be pissed
kids raised by me they won't be wild
hooligans that are out of control
yeah Josie can make me buy that saddle
for her
I'm mr. horse now that we're all clean I
told you to trust me and you did in the
past I got the horses in the back but
now I got the horses in the pasture I
can't I can't deliver I [ __ ] be free
little horse
[Music]
[Applause]
and not to get hella cheesy but this is
definitely a life moment I have these
every now and then and I definitely
dreamt of a moment like this when I was
a kid
next step we just gonna have real kids
all right guys half a million likes and
Joe's you'll have my babies yeah more
like hi guys you sign up for the
Maverick club I'm giving away my future
children I don't really know what the
[ __ ] I'm trying to say right now all I'm
trying to say is it's [ __ ] beautiful
[Music]
signing up where like $20 manage it yeah
but like that I was like your club is
like so worth it I love that so much
[Music]