you're gonna be alright yes all right
guys I don't know your quarantine is
going but mine's been somewhat
uneventful and I'm slightly bored to
come numb to most things so sometimes
I'll do things like literally anything
so I could feel something this is the
fourth time I've done this here we go
[Music]
hey QWERTY
I hate the coronavirus oh no my pets
have really been getting me through this
quarantine I love you I love you I love
you who's gonna perish because it sounds
like he's saying it back to me I love
you whoa that was three syllables means
sir I've been working on this new trick
where you hide to my mom do you consider
yourself cultured yeah I just want to
put you to the test I'm gonna show you
pictures of celebrities and I want you
to try to name them 6:9 Katy Perry Wow
she's just have to reckon below you
talking about Miley Cyrus yeah but
that's not Miley no you don't say Riley
I didn't remember her face but her lips
look for me okay yeah yeah yeah the guy
with the claws yeah cabman jack jack
klugman oh that's jack yeah Jack Sparrow
yes Rodney here there's wide hangs down
to his knees you stick your arm down the
toilet and then you flush it you get
sucked into the sewage we welcome you up
boy let's make a little wager last time
I shot an arrow at a spray paint can I
miss what do you say if I can hit the
can this time you stick your arm down
the toilet and if I miss I'll stick my
arm down the
gambling I'm taking a leave on high
stakes are you sleepwalking right now ja
[Music]
how are you a real person no way that
came out of it's on top of the rock over
there oh my god failure I know
Oh order destruction hey you know what
this means right
oh you are the barren the toilet y'all
seen this before wheel actually Mike and
I have done this before
no charge no babe you have to Mike I'll
tell you I love you eat the chip Wow
I've seen her do that before we lost
rice that's good you practicing social
distancing I know you're struggling my
face stop trying to act tough or you too
wouldn't it be fun or deque no cuz your
brand is like tough girl must be nice
[Music]
that's okay it's okay to hate me because
I love you you're gonna be alright
yes my insides are sweating my stomach
is doing triple axels but I wouldn't
wish this pain on my worst enemy
this is ridiculous