[Music]
who's the best head you've had i've seen
your dad fried who
is the best head you've had you've seen
my dad greg
head you've had she's got the shoes dave
get as tight as you possibly can
just just get in there she's feeling a
little sick is she pregnant
oh oh are you pregnant is this in a now
video
i gave in he sold me on the powerpoint
oh my god
his name is hold on a second
that's not my [ __ ] baby joe's been
telling me she thinks she has corona i
don't think i have corona i just have a
headache for three days and all i want
to do is sleep no i know you don't have
it because we got tested yesterday
it burned burned a little that sounds
like chlamydia babe
baby i think something's wrong with your
dog why did you do this are you worried
when she's digging her ears are flapping
so much she'll just like take off like
the dumbo of dogs i wish that one day
she does because she's a lot of
responsibilities
wow you're gonna be a great mom what the
[ __ ]
give me some [ __ ] input here come on
where do you want to go i think it's
switzerland i swear to god i would
get to switzerland tomorrow
switzerland's closed okay no problem
what if we went to
david's home country germany
germany's close okay so i couldn't come
to us for 200 we go to heaven yeah
[Applause]
poland saudi arabia
how did you do that wow we are on a
podcast together what if we just like go
to the airport with the suitcase and go
somewhere guys let's be honest i'm not
going anywhere we're going somewhere
mike i can't [ __ ] take it anymore
i've been stuck in this multi-million
dollar mansion for too long i gotta
switch up the vibes i hit like a
creative wall
if i don't do something to stimulate me
mentally we're gonna be in deep doo-doo
there's no way you're actually pissing
me this idea are you [ __ ] serious
they want me to take laxatives with her
and see who shits first
who wouldn't want to watch that our
videos used to be so fun
you would do tricks and then i would
stand there and get something shot off
of me or you throw knives at me she's
like okay one idea
i could shoot a can off your head the
second one we take last night's first
yeah chances of you [ __ ] your pants as
you shoot the arrow at my head
i'll take those out yeah this is about
to explode i'll hold it over my head
then you shoot it off
upside down with your feet please don't
miss don't aim too low sophie please
oh no selfie please just be
[Laughter]
dave careful sorry no none of this is
good so because
that is about to come out of my butthole
hey guys so josie and i are going to
play that game where you put headphones
on and listen to really loud music and
try to decipher what your partner's
saying can you hear me right now
yeah i hope this doesn't ruin our
relationship i think you're a cute girl
you thought it was cute you pooped you
pooped today yeah
i believe in you you're gonna leave me i
believe in you
okay good i'm not lying i love you
you're not leaving
i'm not i'm not leaving you who did you
[ __ ] before me would i plug a butt for
you
who did you [ __ ] before me would i [ __ ]
a goat for you
for me did i come before you yeah
usually bro what the [ __ ]
what are you saying who did you [ __ ]
before me oh
you like happiness i like your penis
yeah i love your penis i want to have a
kid with you
oh no you don't i know what the [ __ ]
you know i have a kid with me i went to
rite aid to get your birth control with
you today
one day who's the best head you've had
i've seen your dad fried
who is the best head you've had you've
seen my dad grab the best
head you've had who gives the best blow
job you've been yeah
you give the best blow job
gonna lie no
hey the best [ __ ] ever can we go to
the next one
i don't know if that worked at all i i i
don't know if it worked you want to
watch it i know
okay you can catch it on youtube at
youtube.com
stay away from my butthole i'm not going
to stay away from your butthole
why are you so good at this game