that's the countdown with the results
that's horrible why does it do it like
that in 7:30 in the morning
every morning I wake up to this shit's
is ridiculous I'm telling you I write a
very strongly worded letter that's the
idea
oh god I don't have to give these guys
the taste of their own medicine
see yes there that's eight hours of
screaming goats you guys like yeah up
you're awake now I don't make the rules
boys yeah Dave let's go back to bed so
it's a bracelet and it has it like a
shocking mechanism you could train your
behaviors to shock you when you do
something dumb you're gonna hit a
cigarette instead of heating the
cigarette you shock yourself shut the
two of them because I want to hook them
together and put them around my staff
snack you can't do that to your
employees if I did they'd hate it and my
life would be so much easier but I can't
how bad is this gonna hurt oh it's
nothing oh I'm starting to like this 30%
zap oh wait you say 200 I don't know
what button does it so it's like it's
gonna be a mystery to you as my Fitbit
kicks your [ __ ] ass curse you put this
app in the maverick Club and I'll wear
this and they can shock me whenever they
please sign up for the metal Club right
now you get shock the [ __ ] out of me man
for not calm say for example I go to
smoke marijuana
wow this weed is gonna be good let's say
I go to text and drive driving on the
highway Martin my business
Oh my girlfriend sent me a new damn she
looking good accidentally hide I'm
pissed I'm so [ __ ] mad instead of a
CVD cds/dvds
says it right here but someone clearly
mix today because if it was CVD I wanna
be as high as a [ __ ] kite look at me
Dave
does that look for SIBO to you the day I
try to stop smoking weed now look at me
try pothead David
[Music]
sorry you're driving a truck you're
driving a truck got you you are driving
a car or
- I bet I saw that on Twitter uh some
actress got stabbed
know what the knife you ever ever SED no
no no why no why I was just focused on
the corona desde touch her brain okay
tickle her cranium is this good makes me
want to sneeze well I woke up on the day
of my fight you know how many times I
sneeze three times you have to count
down with the results up-and-coming
youtubers would send me DMS when they
were up-and-coming and then when they
made it they all unset the deal what's
good oh you unsent him though it was
because I was meeting Jay and I didn't
wanna [ __ ] him look like a little [ __ ]
did you win send yours yeah shut the
[ __ ] up so he got the merchant he goes
guess what I did it he comes into my
room and he goes I bought maverick merch
and he would go around telling people
he's a maverick I love what you're doing
with your life and you seem like a
really built person to hang with I come
up to LA almost every week it would be
dope to me that was such a lie we never
was on Twitter that stabbed who got
stabbed something oh yeah what's Reese's
last name I don't know what the [ __ ] is
this joke bro what the [ __ ] is a joke no
no y'all salvos wooden
unless you're TMZ or are you a sociopath
[Music]