hey you think you let me off this leash
bro absolutely not
come on just let me have to leave what's
hey no you know trust me I'm gonna try
it yo y'all know I got this cute dog
little bro Lee blue the other day if you
saw the vlog we actually took him on his
first day
[Music]
whoa yeah bro Lee lost his v card so
that was good if you guys are not
subscribed that's a seven I figured
though broadly like everyone seems to
like him he comes over the girls patter
nice try to steal on Jake's Tola think
it's cuz he's so good looking like y'all
know he already hit 3.1 million
followers on Instagram like two weeks
which is crazy I'm cheating though you
know kinda cheesy what a mere old gamer
you had a dog
[Music]
but well you're really milking this one
I'm really milking broadly for content
I'm not gonna lie so anyways I oh I
horror transition so I figured what if
there was a way that I could be as
good-looking as Broly yeah so y'all hit
that subscribe button because we got
some epics today
oh my God look he's stopped eating that
you know how asparagus grows no
seriously I'm asking you have any idea
asparagus grow like someone's trying to
prank someone into tricking them how
asparagus grows little sticks in the
ground actually just grows like that
disgust me pop the pimple this morning
you know what that means there's gonna
be no sex for a week anyone wants to
have sex with you period
hey guys this is Lanie she's the makeup
artist who's gonna make me look like my
dog what have you got you have ears you
have cocaine am I allowed to talk about
George doing that when I was looking for
a makeup artist for this shoe and I
messaged this dude George too cuz he
painted the Dolans wing I asked him to
pay me and he was like nah dude you talk
circus he must be a cat person ever must
not like painting dog that's incredible
hey George bro so I hope I hope your
life's going great
what's the first steps to make this
happen lens is that you're gonna put in
custom for you to look like brollies our
eyes okay we have some ears to put on
okay then after we get to contacts and
ears on then we're gonna full body paint
your upper torso okay how long is it
take probably around two hours okay
these were a hundred and forty bucks
each they're so creepy holy [ __ ] dude
don't you mean bro leash oh I'm crying
makes me blind I do it spats I noticed
we had the same hoodie on guys do it
different maybe today we do it the same
you maverick could mean oh my god so bad
you look good thanks man here's the
thing bro I'm gonna be looking like a
dog I am a dog Oh doors back when my
wife is pregnant bro
around here for sure I know what I need
oh my god of thunder is back really
comfortable it's not as soft as maverick
merge but it's all right from this angle
bro it looks like Burley has been slain
his legs sticking out behind asparagus
oh hey man it's me bro Lee come on
oh god I'm still human I had no real
urge to chase that toy I don't want you
boned it
[Music]
yeah keep forgetting I'm a human I've
even seen what I look like yet oh my god
this is amazing
you're the detail on this is incredible
Wow you're so cute guys follow us on
instagram at burly blue what's for lunch
yeah yeah yeah I'm still Logan a
discrimination issue racist you have to
go to the bathroom
I'm saying you're racist you have to go
to the bathroom you're being raped
she did such a good job I'm looking at
my nose in the mirror you see how the
detail there bro with the air pots on
the nose just like Broly yeah good thing
this bro he's driving the car am i right
i real talk though not that I'm a dog I
could really got it be a dog so I got a
place we can go get on my way huh get on
my way
get out my way huh get out my way that's
right buddy that's a good boy ya know
what's good
so what's good what's really good hey
easy bro hey yo what's good
you're watching smoke no we don't want
to that mom burly come on bro Lee come
on Logan come on come on come on here we
go we're doing it this is perfect
this is efficient it's effective
I like Huskies you know let's get my
cellphone for the kill
I have the worst news I pee right there
we came to the dog park cuz I'm a dog
he's a dog we like being with other dogs
that's a dog get stay stay
last time I was here we covered myself
in peanut butter it was confronted by
the cops this time I'm just like a dog
what's the worst that could happen
come on come on dogs have a voice box so
I can use English to talk hey you think
you let me off this leash bro absolutely
not come on just let me have to leave
what's hey no you don't trust me no so
I'm actually not a dog lady looks like
you're holding like dead salmon you're
actually happy I finally eat your treat
gotta take my Invisalign out no problem
speak hi
who else and again lady I'm not actually
a dog oh my god hey good to see you must
be nice being a real dog I don't wanna
be a dog anymore
listen thank you for watching the vlog
listen thanks to you poisoning me it has
an ounce of scotch make sure you
subscribe hit that button join the load
can't gain skirting me up on Instagram
at Logan Paul my boy
we're only blue on Instagram a truly
bloom don't forget copter maverick merch
do something different today push
yourself outside of your comfort zone
Apple do you think I wanted to be a dog
today actually kind of did ya go but be
a [ __ ] you have lick feel average
logo Pollock on /aa or link in
description I love you guys the state of
art take these bamboo know what that is
supposed to be done guess what
I'm number one they don't know Melissa's
only begun really we're just having fun
play play
[Music]
Shane Oman inefficient but my life is a
weight on my shoulders it done against
me I don't even know if we on haters
should use this part because it might
just be better as they go reveal you
know I think so might be right yeah but
hey this could be at the end of the vlog
they do submission but that message that
you got the game in the Chuck they lose
and they prob I set up three level no
debris when they say they was so real