Oh lime you you I've never been inside a
pumpkin I was just dancing lo gang come
on [ __ ] I just find out we have eggo
waffle with no toaster god bless it so I
was dancing till like drying away my
sorrow anyways yeah yeah good morning
good morning cog there's no toaster okay
oh yeah all right you guys know what I
open vlogs like this like you ready bro
it's a big day for the vlog called go
run away how do I say this you know you
saw the title of the video um I I
ordered California's largest pumpkin
2,000 pounds cost me $4,000 and it's
kites being delivered to the house today
I'm an idiot right and I'm not gonna get
to see the state's biggest pumpkin look
who knows in how long in my life so I
swooped it up just thing yo it's [ __ ]
huge it's gonna be epic so if you're
watching this vlog and you are not a
part of the logging are you good hit the
subscribe button smack it in the face
god I'm gonna get back here no come be a
good dog god bless Nick Carr get back
yeah he's still learning commands yeah
and his name in his name yeah anyways
yeah join the low gang the stalk his
family on the internet hit the subscribe
button for me and let's get the day
started with the bang also I want to say
guys I think actually I know I know it's
official today is the last day of the
moustache finally I know it just it
served me well alright we shot the no
handlebars music video a couple days ago
in fifth gear I'm a ten-speed not my
fault she's text
made a human bicycle handle in the stash
it just worked but now that I'm back to
normal normal life order in giant
pumpkins and just I think it's kind of
this dog best be careful bro I saw a
coyote last night in the neighborhood
Kong would try to make friends with it
yeah but coyote wouldn't like that
because his dope as the views would be
on a coyote ate my dog video I don't
want that to happen
are you fully clothed cuz I'm sad what
you do you shower really clothes on
yourselves yeah you know it's funny I'm
doing like the dopest stuff with Evan
him and I on the pumpkin like overnight
challenge please bring you love me not
to mention you leave me
he left me last night and I genuinely
had no idea he was leaving last night
hey future Logan it's me past Logan not
feeling so good right now uh what did
you tell me just now I don't even at
6:00 a.m. oh yeah I told you multiple
times yeah hey bro I don't I forgot yo
you have no idea it's the biggest
pumpkin in California I told you my
schedule we can go and you got my camera
Gracie
we're going were you going Evan when you
get back you get back the day of
Halloween and you want to make a vlog
with a pumpkin after Halloween are you
good I got the carrots
I mean he warned me not to what did you
say if we decided to replace you with a
minute or two leave Eve I'll bust your
knees okay cool
need my knees need my knees necessary
these are good I mean you know it is the
biggest pumpkin in California you can
fit but you know what you go do your
thing of Maryland bro I'm going in the
pantry all right I'll see you oh yeah
because it's a walk-in pantry and I can
do that bro cuz I just bought me a house
buddy I'll give you a nice Tony proud
like you used to like yeah I'll be
coming to custom milk
[Music]
I'll leave you in here and out but I
don't know I think you might have
snapped them essentially it's his fault
that I'm wet like broke my bottoms are
working the math assures dropping
November 1st to be ready but in the
meantime you can get to merge and look
up all that got a slash shop or link in
description and so as you can imagine
when you're dealing with a 2,000 pound
pumpkin you can't just pick that up
unless you like me and you know what
most people aren't so I had Lydia she's
so fun order a forklift and it's here I
thought you I thought you shaved your
moustache I couldn't do it yeah it came
down to the wire I was like I'm just
gonna leave it for now I think it got
thicker yeah so anyways yeah the
forklift is here Oh yo Lydia what the
forklift this is like a crane fork to
tell you guys as you can imagine it's
not easy getting a pumpkin this big like
you can't just buy this out of pumpkin
patch so I went to the pumpkin guy his
name is Chris his sons and daughters I
think daughters are in the low gang
actually so he made his way out from
drinking God knows where to get this big
old pumpkin and he's been like teasing
me bro Chris you son of a [ __ ] you've
been teasing me bro first he sent me a
picture right look at this bull um she
was just big ol giant 2000 pound pumpkin
so at this point I'm like oh that's a
big punk there's no joke hence the
reason we needed that we if we bought
this how much would be good look at it
boss you need to think like that more
often that's what we do here on local
pawn logs bro where's the pumpkin
how's that oh this is dope what is it oh
how far do you think this thing reaches
amazing Oh vodka - oh this is the
biggest pumpkin in California biggest
pumpkin in California oh honey oh yeah
it doesn't make any sense also who are
you guys
there's so many things we can do this
bouquet so many endless Andrew vote we
could make the world's largest pumpkin
spice latte just fill the whole thing
with coffee with the most basic of
[ __ ] bro you guys seem pretty basic
so like if we made like a pumpkin spice
latte in the pumpkin would you be into
it yes yeah would you get into it okay
flowin let me tell you about my forklift
this takes precision and accuracy both
of which I don't have
so much work for one time now go dude yo
I feel like a dad and not because of my
stache I'm just being responsible I just
like I'm a little salty I couldn't be
the one to actually pick it up but
whatever with your hands yo my head's Oh
Brendan don't mind if I do
don't mind if I do come on Kingston hop
on pumpkin put eggs makes me miss Abbott
how it's all you bro
50 for Evans 50
[Music]
what are you gonna do with it now that
you have it we should cut a hole in it
oh my god it's exactly like cutting a
little pumpkin
it's a giant pumpkin it's crazy how
these things grow Chris can you bless me
with some this pumpkins 88 days old
this pumpkin gained 50 to 60 pounds a
day yeah could get stuck I get like some
sort of liability claim sounds like a
pro okay honestly see you later in this
scenario better than Evan like I don't
know if Evan would have done this oh my
gosh Oh
some of the guys selling it depends on
how popular they become but anywhere
from a hundred fifteen hundred to seed
remember doggy I told you when I got you
you would live the most insane life ever
and this giant pumpkin is a part of it
yo what what was that what was what
would you must ask
[Music]
my moustache was fake guys hey no you
won you're literally gonna you might as
well eat $1,500 mr. Dubrow yeah tastes
like just like a bum it really does
probably cuz it is gonna make this
little powerful conversation uh-huh
take it up top
we're still a why'd I come up here but I
don't know cuz dove huh look down we
could start at legit business about like
I know they say I wanna they want to
keep the seeds yeah are you gonna start
growing pumpkins we could grow pumpkins
I got big yard the games dead looking
good
I used to be local Paul what's up dude
so how are you I'm good I used to be
good reason I'm no longer good I don't
tell you this but I didn't order that
pizza much happier than the guy yes okay
thank you ma'am big biggest one in
California this is gonna be a problem
story me pizza I appreciate you guys
you're Mavericks to grow giant pumpkins
it's a good thing you get marks okay you
know where to get it local Paul back on
slash up Wow one big happy family all
wearing their merch
hey you text guy alfredo and ask if we
keep the forklift for another day oh
yeah so we want to pick the pumpkin up
over the house and put it in the pool
yeah cuz barely can float okay very nice
family I hope one day to raise a family
like that my cell but we got a while for
that right now I'm gonna focus on this
puppy right here okay so the skin inside
is very thick so in order to make room
for like overnight challenges etc like
hopping in it got to carve it out by the
way when Evan gets here it's probably
gonna be like destroyed and squishy but
I don't give a [ __ ] 7 you're getting in
my pumpkin breath anyways let's clear
this out broke time you messy got my
utensils
[Music]
okay so just it's not making much
progress at all I'm a white guy
[Music]
made some necessary modifications to the
pumpkin made the hole a little bigger
tend to do that often California's
biggest pumpkin possibly the world and
I'm about to hop in keep in mind I'm six
foot two but to ten oh here I go you
I've never been inside a pumpkin this is
pretty cool dude
hey guys know this I like to make it a
point that in my life I want to
experience as many things as possible
and fitting inside the giant pumpkin is
one of those things oh it's crazy bro
like my head just fits here
okay we're inside of a 2,000 pound
pumpkin
actually crazy oh my god it's not bad I
think honestly I need to carve out more
but yo the vlogs in here okay look at
that is the vlog I'm gonna sign off from
the inside of this pump because this is
though if you're not a part of the Logie
make sure to subscribe we are the
strongest family on the internet ed
copier maverick merge or low gamer
slogan fall cops last shop or link in
description yall already know it'd be a
mess be a maverick go out do something
different today like buying a giant
pumpkin life is good load gang I love
y'all I will see you tomorrow take it
easy I need a pumpkin spice latte hot
chocolate
yes to the whipped cream on top
I need a venti soy mocha just me little
mocha but at least I won't be cautious
bye Lydia good boy