[Applause]
good morning okay was Bob the Maverick
decided to get a little running this
morning I've been feeling lazy lately
which is never good as you guys know we
just got our gym painted but there's no
gym equipment yet probably and I wanted
to give our new Maverick performance
shorts a test run yo these babies are
fight guys guys listen I'm not even
kidding when I say this these are like
the highest quality shorts I've ever
worn oh wait did you you forgot we
dropped maverick bottoms hey don't
forget yeah two days ago the merch game
was changed forever when maverick
apparel drops bottoms jogging's leggings
jogging's leggings joggers joggers
leggings shorts
it's no joke okay look it's room /aa
poorly in description and do not forget
if you buy some of this new heat in the
next 24 hours
let's choose five of you to like
FaceTime and talk to you on instagram
live in front of probably you like
probably like 60 to 100,000 people no
big deal I read you guys comments or
read your tweets and you're already
losing your mind over the bottoms as am
i you're buying them you're loving them
this southern I can't God sure it's
gonna be let's go join the movement
okay yeah okay welcome to our vlogs hi
i'm logan paul that's dwarf Mamba and
this is Brendan Norris if you're not a
part of the logging and you want to be a
part of the look and make sure to
subscribe smack the button in the face
to me kind of like Evan just hit me in
the face I panic I just okay one day be
as cool as me but no I'm tall yeah you
look [ __ ] sexy
yeah what can I say it's me dwarf Mamba
this is terrifying huh the house is
becoming a home we've been adding like
flavors of our personality to it like I
said you guys saw this yesterday but
this is the gym we had it painted
everything on these walls means
something you guys already saw I'm just
obsessed with it like the dead the
universe is written backwards because
when we get mirrors that we put on it's
gonna reflect off the wall and then he
could read in it's just this little
creator and then the infamous Kong the
savage looking by the way oh
damn it come come here god bless he's
got stuff to do
alright guys we showered I cleaned off
and I'm not gonna lie it's a little dark
outside it's so it's getting darker
earlier as you know wait wait by the way
step that sucks
savings time ends baby bro maybe one day
we'll start a petition but
what I'm saying now is with the drop of
the Maverick bottoms I'm putting a lot
of time effort and thought into it so in
between takes what you guys don't see is
like I'm doing emails and then firing
off creative ideas blah blah blah and it
kind of sucks like don't get me wrong
it's fun but like my mom's in town she's
at Jake's house and I realized I haven't
even seen my brother's house yet that's
weird he's lived there for like how long
would you say maybe like a month almost
a month right so I'm like dude I'm gonna
go to Jake's house maybe bring him some
frickin joggers and just be like yeah
what's up and just check it out and you
can bet your ass I'm making Evan come
with me my brother the brother oh I love
you I'm how how are you I'm good I'm
driving in my Yeti to Jake's house
actually so I was gonna ask you did you
tell Jake security guards not to shoot
me in the face
cuz I need that ah yes I will be sure to
tell them not to shoot my son in the
face thanks mom
that's how I know your that's how I know
you love me that's a good mom I will be
there
yo where are you you're not I'm getting
a beauty treatment you don't need a
beauty treatment because I think we all
agree that you are flawless all right
bye mom okay so I guess my mom is not
there which kind of sucks I love that
woman she she she birthed me out of her
yep
[ __ ] you thought it was gonna save
vagina you just did just Tom Brandon are
you thinking about Evan you be your
quiet if a vacuum isn't good
turn left doesn't suck
[Music]
yeah do whatever you need to do she told
you not to shoot me in the face we're
loyal to Jake but mom lay down the law
and she says okay
[Applause]
I was joking about shooting me in the
face bro they have handguns oh you know
what now I'm a parkways belongs like in
a bit bro
yams illness me switch it up like I feel
like it belongs you good you'd be good
like we did good but this is second
oppressor bro and he's 20 years old how
old are you Evan 20 where's your house
bro where's your house your house with
you tips over on to the Eddie I could
see my brother's house from here you
recognize that
because like I said in us you son of a
[ __ ] you're getting dark early I said
we'll come back to this but I gotta say
bro I've seen some doors in my life
dope door oh the difference between
Apollo and Kong Kong doesn't eat rocks
yeah this is a rock you can't digest
this so I'm gonna take that away from
you
Jake well I'm proud of you man they got
us beat on the view the view is nice but
do they have a tree don't go to my house
is your house yeah
Ivan Brennan both be thankful this is
what Jake does do his roommate Zoey has
me in a box I get with Jake meant when
he said his backyard had a backyard this
is Wow you could do all sorts of things
here you could skip rope
that's terrifying yeah yeah we're gonna
yo are the six you check oh oh oh damn
son I know for a fact my mom made this
pasta games I guess technically could be
made in here you ain't got no mama snake
on the wall this is all cool but where's
Jake's room
little brother big brother advice you
need furniture bro
cuz I'm looking around here and I'm like
my friends get better gifts how you
doing with that Rolex you got a little
lucky you they let us rent our furniture
in our house like our house probably
would look like this we just have to
choose this stuff but oh honey the view
again it's nice little brothers not
playing any games Oh
okay I am in like one of like look
there's three guest bedrooms and this is
a kitchen like bro this is a different
house we're in the same house
I think rose look at me can you find his
way back we're good okay no this is a
little like sacrilegious but if you guys
have not gotten your mavar about him yet
you have to do bro I'm not even kidding
bro it is the dopest most quality most
versatile comfortable apparel you'll
ever have so we're get them apparel
I'm loadable that comes last shop or the
link for that in the description we're
gonna head back home before Jake gets
here but y'all I was thinking the
obviously the joggers sweatpants coming
soon enough plugging in Jake's house
here's what I was gonna say security
guards a dog tied with me we're pretty
much scissoring light with height so
y'all I'm like yo raking just give me
like one like raise I got access to the
house bro solo gang comment like a prank
or something I should do to Jake's house
maybe like steal Apollo or like paint
the whole side like Logan Paul calm
sighs yeah so many things we can do cuz
doodling chillers let me in okay she's
she kind of cute girl she's kind of like
got some kill you she could kill me any
day like if there's one person who's
gonna shoot me in the face perfect
alright I know there's pity on Jake's
hot security got talked back to the
Maverick at home with my two boys three
Brendan this is definitely the squad
right here Jake you did a good job bro
your home is dope and I'm proud of you
you're a good brother you're a little
bit my brother and I will kiss your
security guard on the mouth one day but
until that day low gang that is the law
literally just blog to the bottom so I'm
not gonna plug again but uh don't forget
guys I'm gonna face
five of you on instagram live if you
purchased merchants the next 24-hour cop
your bottoms cop you show your hats
whatever you want looking Paul that cop
/ chopper link in description guys it is
a movement a revolution we know where
we're going and if you don't you know
get out of our way
cuz the Mavericks are headed to the top
baby also smack the subscribe button in
the face for me if you're not a part of
the Logan lokay I love y'all I really do
like you guys don't and I will see you
tomorrow
[Music]
my pride