oh
hello everybody i'm just a blonde white
boy from ohio here to cause trouble in
your country hey yo good morning loki
what's
up guys it is a beautiful day to be
alive on planet earth why
low gang you guessed it my voice is
coming back
you guys know for the past week or so
i've sounded like an old lady named
deborah who's been smoking since he was
seven
but not anymore guys logan paul is back
when i was enjoying the quiet
sorry brendan no more quiet guys i'm
back and stronger than ever
if you're not a part of the make sure to
subscribe yo how does my blood look from
this angle looks so good
thanks bro so yeah guys we're in tokyo
japan if for whatever reason you're not
subscribed
you good hit the subscribe button for me
smack it in the face
and join the strongest family on youtube
a family of mavericks people who are
doing it differently
people who walk on the street instead of
driving in cars hi how are you
okay it's really funny guys they drive
on the opposite side of the road in
japan hello
hi sushi i'm
sorry bro i'm a lot to handle he's got
my back though so guys today he has two
flashlights
what's up guys oh my god is that kong
kong
where's kong hi i have a dog like you
except not it's fluffy oh this is crazy
kong i'm with your grandpa
thanks for letting me touch your dog
okay
first tokyo fish market now we heard
you're supposed to come here much
earlier in the day yo it feels honestly
brandon it feels so good that my voice
is back it's bad like bro i feel good no
like i said fish market
hey how many what how many subscribers
15 million
she's just up and
[Music]
he has down idea hello hi
how you feel okay have a nice day
use my feet when i don't have to it's so
easy to get around your ubers bro
free look learn a lesson from me if you
want to see the fish at the fish market
in japan
don't party with thoughts the night
before yeah i'm also not giving up hope
see now that's what i'm talking about
shrimp guy always goes hard he's the
last one
first one here i just want a giant fish
to smack andy with like how funny would
that be
[Applause]
yo i thought we went hard last night
these guys are still going hard
they've been drinking since 8 00 a.m on
my instagram account you won't let me
leave look literally i'm locked in
your family now
i don't know what this is it's a red red
merch
it's an octopus yeah yeah it's an
octopus
it's kind of like a fish we get it it's
funny it's what
it's funny it's gross that's funny
i want to buy this i'm not going to eat
it though it's just for content
what are we going to do with that hit
people with it that's gross
man yeah i saw him in spongebob he comes
out of the screen sideways and he talks
sucks that he's dead now rest in peace
[Music]
guys we're in shibuya i got my squid leg
i got a fish
hey guys you want some fish okay does
anybody want a squid leg
okay it's good oh okay respect you
almost hit him in the face with that
i would never purposely hit someone in
the face
oh not the murderer oh not the bird but
it's so
funny
[Music]
how can a fish poop after it's dead
that's so disgusting learn a lesson from
me logang this was not worth it
i should have never disrespected the
merch like that no this actually makes
me
sad bro not them ever
[Music]
we'll be collecting tips or you can just
get some merch to login for that
slideshow
that one
the best way to clean the merch is with
more merch
all right back to business there's
real-life mario kart so we can't do it
because we don't have an international
driving license but look this is amazing
tokyo is just a giant playground maybe
it's not
maybe i should stop probably not
[Music]
oh who lives in a pineapple under the
sea
i'm a messed up human being fun fact um
when i did the splits here in japan
this was another area i went to i feel
like i'm definitely having more fun this
time though
[Music]
how are these people filming us oh hi
are you guys in love
yes we are yes
you want this fish is a token of your
love definitely
is that real yeah and look you can
combine them whoa
it's like a megalodon you sure you don't
want this yeah
yeah let's go get drunk where's your
family respect respect
[Music]
japan is all about the hottest fashion
it's the freshest in the game
just like the fish these are kind of
nice again like i don't know if i find
myself wearing jack as often i already
got the hottest merch in the game
actually what do i do here bro i'm good
bro
[Music]
honestly bro i'm done with these fish
we gotta do some others hey so it's a
bit later we're eating pizza as you can
see
i do i just want to say one thing though
japanese people
are so nice literally everyone first off
they put up with me
second off they laugh with me oh so
sometimes at me i think most of the time
most of the time but it's just like like
i just i love tokyo i love japan and the
culture
is so nice i'm not even kidding
americans we could learn a lot
like watches hi hi hey
they always smile
everyone's always smiling it just makes
me so happy so japan tokyo specifically
uh thanks for putting up with your boy
and from the bottom
of my heart uh it means i love you
[Music]
cultural
i'm falling in love with japan literally
we just came to this waterfall so i
could be
by waterfall it's a fountain what far
away you know today is only day two we
have so much more time and [ __ ] yeah so
do me a favor if you're not a part of
the vlogging first off what the [ __ ]
[ __ ] are you doing my voice is coming
back the channel's getting lit again hit
the subscribe button for me
smash it have sex with the subscribe
button cop yourself some of the
strongest hottest
far the best ever merch in the game
maverick logan paul dot com
slash shop our link is good luck dude
we're doing it we're changing the world
every day mavericks being different i
don't want to be the same as everyone
else
in fact i'm never going to be you're
unique and that's what makes you special
lokang i love you and i will see you
tomorrow take it easy
like it's this guy in all that shaver if
i cannot hear it
i'm just i'm really happy i'm talking
about it