oh that's daddy's gonna love it his door
shut maybe he's playing video games
what's poppin I'm being quiet cuz Kong
is really weird
hey buddy we gotta get you a real
girlfriend yeah Oh gross
Oh No let go no no no you do your thing
we'll get back to you later
is this top look what is what you got em
macaroni and cheese yeah Evan did you
put this here but what oh no I need you
didn't put that there
I mean I can't even reach that first off
it's just kind of weird I'm good I'm
good oh that over there yeah I got I got
Evans watch appraised Ashley you guys
remember I bought Evan the Rolex well I
had it appraised which means I got the
actual value of it worry about it later
anyways men's rolex submariner watch
right there oh that's just estimated Mr
sair comparison $30,000 oh I was about
to go into Evans room and show him and I
looked to my left what does is he good
girl why do you why did you send the
watch out here is this not good not like
bright like I thought it was $20,000 and
apparently it's about 30,000 broke hello
no oh my what he loves his video games
no cars time to show you there's your
watch yeah estimated MSRP comparison oh
yeah bro so what
yeah cuz it's diamonds it's expensive
there are kids in Africa anywhere okay
okay let's talk to Dueling number one
one year vlog over Surrey yeah coming up
on September 12 I will have been
vlogging for one year baby 365 days
straight which is in I think ten days
what also my brother's been saying it he
wants and thinks he's gonna be the first
channel to hit 12 million subscribers in
12 months we're at like 11 point one and
we have 10 days to go we could do it
like we could definitely do it it's
gonna be tough I will say Jake you had
200,000 subscribers before you started
vlogging I'm just sayin it I'm just
saying anyway she's killing it I'm
killing up all mothers ha ha ha so for
some reason if you're watching any not
part of the low game subscriber oh we
are making history bro the fastest
YouTube channel to grow and hit 10
million so be dropping an exclusive
awesome amazing piece of merch on that
day and some other stuff in about four
days or so keep an eye out for that okay
number two calm tooth yeah so while he
was doing way look at that tone bro like
dog his tongue is unreal that's not real
bro while he was uh getting it on I
guess you're gonna call it this morning
yo he was going too hard I don't know
like you know some people when there's
like sexy time they like to like buy it
and stuff like if you don't know that
some people do that should I not say
that
I know his comas going too hard he must
be like bitey or something I lost a
tooth well that thing that is Kong's
tooth his actual tooth that fell out
this morning buddy you know what this
means right we got a the Kong tooth the
doggy tooth fairy bro so far how this is
gonna work is we're gonna put this under
your pillow and then you're gonna go to
sleep and then when you wake up the
doggy Tooth Fairy will have come and
giving you like a gift or money or
something
needless to say come it's your baby I
don't believe
to the comms a bit tired he's been
running around a lot while he sleeps
kind in the mood for like frozen juice
it's like frozen yogurt but juice right
check it out bro food your juice easy
I think it's breeze that makes sense
this is healthier than ice cream yeah
I think same frozen yogurt yeah my jam
no this is your freeze crazy yo so I
don't know where most of you guys are
from but in LA right now it is so hot
this has got to be breaded what do you
think the hot hasn't been here yet oh
yeah guys it's like a hundred like here
the other day was 110 like you guys know
this broiling I'm at all times out here
but like at this current moment I'm in
here bro
like inside of my house because there's
too damn hot outside I will say bro it
looks like the Tooth Fairy came there's
something under kazekage do huh well we
got what is heavy
wait what everyone what are you doing
bro solitude so you just won under my
dog's bed yeah I want to see what it was
you're not the tooth fairy no I'm a nerd
oh okay well can you leave the tooth at
least watch out there's a cage there can
I please get the tooth brother you
robbed Kong of a potential gift from the
Tooth Fairy for my collection dude
what collection what it's pretty serious
collection Steve are they your teeth or
dog's teeth this is this is ridiculous
really just give me the tooth
Wow
Thank You Starling I thanks for giving
me this tooth did you order food local
pulse I won't believe that out coz no
free brand deals Brendan are you hungry
yeah damn oh man told you I'm about to
order food any Chaka Khan just watching
some tagging instead of ignored me I
didn't know you I was keep taking teeth
from my dog never listen to me you never
what if he eats it and for some like
miraculous reason grows like three feet
that would be amazing
hey party's over you steal again if you
don't believe me my friend has something
to say I'll call the police
I know a guy I'm still all your girls
kiss all your life yeah yeah I'll catch
your wires have seem do it hey kiss my
wife I also got a pregnant full of I
didn't know that that's too far bro my
wife pregnant bro Shady oven door came
out of her progress like God doing is
possible you were pregnant with my wife
it was like one night I thought I pulled
out hold on I don't even have a
boyfriend II mean I said we're gonna go
get some food ourselves but look what
we're bringing the official candid
teacher of the official candid t-shirt
with the golden maverick and the logo
they say it's the worst signature in
Hollywood I don't think it's that bad
it's pretty bad what skew Brendon
anyways if we see someone in the logo go
ahead oh just launch the cannon at them
yeah I think I see some low gangsters
remember guys the only way to get one of
these is if I fire it at you remember
there's only 50 of them three two one
[Applause]
remember guys in like four days or
dropping some new stuff is I am I used
to be I guess I still AM you go guys
what two for two but anyways yeah guys
four days Logan Paul calm /op the
Maverick merch the low gang merchants
we're gonna be amping it up these next
two months man if you haven't copped it
already go to the site link in
description join the movement baby it's
all about being Mavericks being
different bro that's how you make waves
in the world
let's effing go so we're getting some
food right now and I don't know about
you guys but when I see pictures of the
food like that that's that's what I'm
gonna get because I see with my eyes it
looks good and I don't depth this is why
bro it looks exactly like the picture I
know exactly what I'm getting at you
anyways um Evan I know you're part of
the low gang I know you watch my vlogs
mo we don't need your stinkin food I got
my own food Brendan got a salad we
chillin as we're at the pet store I'm
super bored if you can't tell till we
get a pet maybe for Evan Evan needs it
heavy needs a pad he needs friends hey
buddy you want to be friends with my
roommate Oh what do you have it's a
snake no I'm a wrapping around my wrist
like a watch this is cool dude what's
his name
look I'm Paul oh no fear Brandis here I
[Laughter]
got you a new pet guys we got him a
betta fish oh he's gonna love it his
door shut maybe he's playing video games
he's snoozing so hard is he good we need
to give him two things hey dude I see
you're sleeping with your Rolex I like
that
here's a you good bro survey cuz you
snore like a lion but most importantly
bro
look what we got you is that that's
Oprah
it's your new pet Oprah Oprah the betta
fish she's better than you yeah you
gotta take him on walks it's okay you
can do it it's your big day all right
well you can't walk something else I've
been excited for waiting for it all day
my man cog in the Tooth Fairy Oh what
did she bring you bro oh wait what you
know is just weird is that a fidget
spinner yeah it looks like she brought a
few spinner and uh katana do you think
she's good Wow what is he gonna do with
you
who knows maybe he'll fit just spin and
cut things I don't know anyways guys
with that said that is that was an
interesting day guys
whoa gang I love y'all if you're not a
part of this family make sure you
subscribe join us cuz we pop advanced
wonder your vlog reverser is coming up
make sure to subscribe copy or maverick
Mirchi oh that bird logo a change in the
world bro every single day we're out
you're grinding working hard following
our passions chasing our dreams that's
that maverick spirit baby Logan Volcom
slash shop a link in description I love
y'all I'll see you tomorrow
take it easy
[Music]