gotta stop having unprotected sex I
don't have unprotected sex alright I had
at one time what's the problem right now
my which so much worse let's go do bad
yo here's the deal there's some kings on
YouTube right now no we're not inspired
by anyone to do this we're gonna do it
doing different but better cuz I watched
david ovaries blogs they're so happy all
the time you know why cuz they're not
like just like real people you don't
have ever that live in their life that
come 23 years old I want to do that
stuff
I've just been censored and I gotta keep
my stuff I kind of tame right now boss
we got a major problem we've started a
whole new series of YouTube yeah bro you
know how we live like pretty crazy lives
but we don't show it like we have to be
like all tame and censor like why can't
we do that
just like fun-loving kid oh we do some
crazy yes we just got to live our lives
and no want to say but like you guys are
like all wild by this idea
this is literally made you famous still
with your life you just don't record
anymore because it got too explicit yeah
now you have smart people around you
you're on tinder and you think Christian
mingle is gonna be better yeah ladies
and gentlemen we've lost Olga's Safari
I'll find you a nice boy via vlog if you
guys want a day old girl follow me on
instagram at logan paul yeah yeah no
hold on oh they're not Olga Olga this
vlog this whole vlog is about us
escalating and maturing our content so
you're gonna get a nice of aged
boyfriend no these are the people I have
to pick from
here's nobody laughs all ten of us no he
looks like he what about the cross-eyed
guy problems from Long Beach whose eyes
point different directions heart beer
dude before you know what a stud you're
in older that's perfect my blog just
turned into a commercial cuz you're
maybe i'ma send you an invoice Oh since
we're getting a clean start on our
content
I figure we go and get a clean start on
our wieners as well it's that time of
year guys we are going to get an STD
check Oh Mike and I are betters clean
yeah my decks clean is mostly nice I'm
95% sure I'm good but it's always good
to check on 10% sure if you don't get
tested you can't ever get an STD but
thanks Beth I'm urgent-care this is most
definitely yeah no one's taking a look
at your wiener last name Paul his name
Logan how did you hear about us
Mike Thank You champ sex Allah you look
like you're in death row right now stop
having unprotected sex I don't have
unprotected sex all right I had at one
time
I started roughly on a trip to Denver
baby you gotta stop you think you are
exposed you had sex with two girls nah
he just put that you had unprotected sex
and you wanna be tough can you write
that sentence twice though cuz he did it
twice by what are you doing why are you
already back in the game keep the funnel
filled look at this row perfect
opportunity oh my god I'm not gonna lie
I have the worst news ever I came into
the bathroom to pee in the cup that's
right there and instead I just I went
pee and now I don't have to pee in this
is all I could muster out I have the
worst news yeah I forgot
just open the toilet pee I literally
forgot dude I swear to God I forgot I
don't know this literally the only
reason we're here even if I tried for so
long I was in there for 17 minutes I got
this I just inhaled water right now this
whole vlog is about a fresh start
for example we're having interracial
double penetration babysitting can't
show your mom porn check this one
stepsister riley reid
ambushed in black males oh yeah why
yeah we'll look stupid what's so good
about this this is literally so oh I
didn't teach you this there's no one no
ha I feel like as long as sex is being
talked about and handled in a safe
manner for example Mike and I got tested
today for STDs like adult you took the
thought with the bathroom and held it in
his hand willing peed in the toilet I
can't believe this Wow it's so
ridiculous that little chin here
time bro I'm done being depressed all of
the beard was okay it signified my
depression now I'm happy man look that
face
like you know proper shade down
[Applause]
[Music]
back it up and so let's line beard we
have enough for everyone we're gonna
sell the individual hairs but if we do
run out of hairs you can buy the hottest
off this person the game let's go ok I'm
doing things we have to we have to get
our STD results back so fingers cross
fingers and toes on my burgers but yeah
fun vlog I do I do want to try to get
more real from now on and then a little
getting gang skirt make sure to
subscribe I will see y'all next time
take it easy man
Christian dudes are yeah they do they
love anal