right now I'm wondering like at what
point have you taken YouTube too far I'm
just gonna start off by saying this low
gang don't hate me please don't hate me
you know this I say it every day we just
hit a year
yeah hit a year of vlogging we got the
diamond play button for hitting 10
million subscribers oh that was a lens
that was a camera lens okay okay great
anyways 100 percent thought you're gonna
drop it anyways we just hit that kind of
a big deal and we also you know I've
said it for the past few days released
these 365 Mavericks that you've assured
guys I'm not even kidding I cannot
fathom how much of a God church they're
selling like no no
what's more than a God Church Brendon a
lord bro a Lord Church it's the Lord
charger and the drop is over you cannot
get these anymore
but I was like wait this is such a thing
I need to call my team the conversation
look like this how hard would it be to
make this shirt white and make the white
parts black like to reverse everything
is looking at me funny an exclusive like
24 hour drop you can do it just like 25
like I don't even know if anyone's gonna
get him bro
yeah yeah there's now a white version of
this only available for 24 hours it's
like the even more exclusive 365 shirt
that's why I'm sorry because if you like
got this one and you want to get the
light one too I just um pricketts I had
to do it again only gonna hit one of
your so yeah those look like this right
here as you can see they still got the
sexy dent the universe on the back cuz
that's what we do every single day and
you know where to get it Logan Paul calm
slash shop link in description I where
is my boy ever
dan you look good Mambo 1/2 because
you're like shorter exactly oh you want
to go downtown with me am i driving oh
[Music]
god we can't do driving with having this
like a little lip into tires blighted
she represents like your career just
like falling flat on its face yeah yeah
totally
now we'll be good will draw well we're
gonna go we're gonna we're gonna do
driving with Evan to the tire store now
okay apparently not get in the car
Evan you're crazy right all right we're
gonna determine if we can do this I
think I've done this I don't think that
it's because the tires well I think you
like those tested drive like a little
bit skimming like it just give it the
tip of driving welcome to driving with
evident mine are you hungry
I'm so hungry that way out of here yo
this is no longer driving with Evan this
is this is sitting here with Evan
[Music]
if you like someone is slashing my tires
this happened two days ago we didn't
vlog it but Lydia a fact you replace my
tire someone slashed me I'm so was gonna
die if it's flat you still have a rim
that can like work as like a tire it's
not good for them but haven't slowed
down haven't slowed down haven't slowed
down good okay do the thing before you
leave do it okay Lydia can you fix can
you fix my car while we go eat we love
you Lydia I think she told us she hates
us really yeah I'm still hungry
yeah me too let's go eat can I do a hot
chicken and a smoke shack and Logan
Poldark on /op and link in description
and subscribe this aren't things on the
menu I'm just making it up yeah but
really yes no you did it no it was too
late you were too late how many times
you guys have texted me and it's been
too late and I walk my aspect wait yeah
I was gonna say you all my fries you got
you you might hate me but more
importantly how's the car how's my baby
without a car just so you know there's
no driving with Evan low gang if she
messes up eat your fries and enjoy
are you less hangry nah bro life is good
that's that's my boy confirmed that's my
boy Holy Mother of God Lydia
Harlan you did it oh my gosh look at it
I'm gonna get you some food to make up
for me not getting you food okay I'm
gonna take the the almond butter cookie
my friend Lydia here who's a doll is
gonna get the B I don't know yet on this
one almond butter cookie yeah yeah yeah
sideways do Thanks hey Lydia
thanks for fixing my car and I'm sorry
I'm such a charge no it's my least
favorite part of the day we gotta give
congas eyedrops for his conjunctivitis
titus prudish might his status Depp
nothing hi buddy hi no air jail
air jail air Jail coming back down I
don't like doing that man there's
nothing more I detest than watching my
son cry be free car yo you know what
that reminds me uh all this talk of Kong
being sick and stuff like dude we should
get an STD test
what do you mean we Mia doesn't really
just like looking at me like okay they
rose what about yo come on it's a good
idea
yo hits response it's a responsible
thing to do we could also do a little
like learning lesson with this vlog bro
yeah well the kids can learn from us a
little public service in our exactly
hello low gang I'm here to talk about
STDs otherwise known as sexually
transmitted diseases yucky
nowadays kids are fornear than ever they
go around dry humping pillows and socks
like the apocalypse is coming something
you might not know almost everyone has
multiple STDs and they're going to die
just kidding but it's possible yeah so
make sure you practice safe sex with a
condom as shown here like you put on you
and if you don't use a condom you run
the risk of getting an STD from a ho no
way no even worse sometimes there are no
symptoms even worse sometimes your
condom breaks the good news is that you
could use it as a bracelet in conclusion
wrap it up and have lots of safe sex as
long as it doesn't get in the way of
your homework like and subscribe I feel
like this is horrible
let's go kiff is having to take the SCD
[Applause]
do you want to get an STD test with us
what sexually transmitted diseases like
see y'all I told you you never know man
just like some of these girls bro in LA
like friggin no you pee next to me yeah
I do yeah
from the air that's how you gonna sneeze
oh no it's just like I feel like it's a
responsible thing to do it might be that
time in my life but here here's the
rules if it comes back and you have an
STD or brenden as well
oh god you gotta tell the internet bro
that's that's their like not how
confident are you bro I'm confident too
I'm gonna do
Oh so our girl Lydia has I found us a
place to get checked what is this place
living you just walk in and get checked
for STDs the Hollywood walk-in clinic
I guess it's a serious matter oh dang
okay do you think you have your free bro
not for your daughter ism other than
that it should be good
hey get up if I do end up having an STD
I won't give it to you you know you're
my boy so I will gladly accept that just
getting real you get an STD you die and
it's a fact how did you find out about
us my assistant Lydia me it's my big day
I'm positive I'm not positive just gotta
roll up my sleeves on the March why do I
feel like I'm on a freakin like spy
mission right now like everything is so
undercover so low-key this is a weird
process especially since I have like
rave music playing right now okay I'm in
the bathroom no rave music in here buddy
I gotta this is urine test as I said
it's a good thing I got the bladder of a
camel bro I gotta pee right now I'm
wondering like at what point have you
taken YouTube too far like what's the
difference between private life and
public life anymore I do it for the low
game bro I know for you guys
onam I should show this maybe I should
blur it but I peed in the cup and now
yeah give me all of it holy oh you're in
cups I need Evan so in the meantime you
don't go ahead and pee in your cup and
I'm waiting for Evan right now I need to
get a thumbnail with all three of us
Evan oh she doesn't get YouTube's you
don't know I need a thumbnail go get
mama that's never how you feel bruh I
haven't peed in a cup in a long time hey
there it's been a minute bro I feel good
about it me too she do yeah great it's
important bro
it is important kids don't have sex what
no you just got to be responsible that's
the only thing that's what we're trying
to do right now we're in the STD
bathroom the hospital STD man
Yeah right I don't know this probably
has to be somewhere in here drop it in
the box
my urine Evan here's the password for
your results my password two to three
business days
oh you stiff these are a stiff thank you
okay you good you got the fresh air wake
up wake up you fine okay Wow
so I'll okay we got that to look forward
to two to three days of just waiting to
see if we have sexually transmitted
diseases yeah okay hello gang that is
the vlogs and it was fun today was
definitely interesting and educational
and educational Brendon no we have like
I said the STD results to look forward
to in the next couple days and like I
said no matter what happens no matter
what happens we're gonna say the results
out loud online for all the internet to
know whoa I'm not nervous I'm chilling
okay yeah the white maverick 365 double
universe shirt again just a little salt
Bay on the internet drop in the hottest
merch in the game logo ball calm slash
shop link in description you have 24
hours to get that should you decide to
do it and subscribe if you're not a part
of the low game alright guys I love
y'all and I will see you tomorrow take
it easy
[Music]