be careful dude all we need to do is get
over there we're in splat right there
think we'll be good
[Music]
okay thirty degree water your seventy
national parks they're gonna stay clean
now eh oh good morning Loghain what's
poppin I'm gonna make this faster this
breezy oh oh
have you got a part of the locate make
sure to subscribe boys good baby yeah
not a good time yeah another epic day
here in Yosemite Fresno yesterday was my
birthday I'm 23 now right we celebrated
with the low gate we hooked it pretty
hard
[Music]
[Applause]
and today is gonna be equally as amazing
what's up guys my name is Logan Paul if
you're not a part of the Logan make sure
to subscribe because we are the most fun
litte weird crazy family on YouTube that
is a verifiable facts oh yeah subscribe
join the family we welcome anyone unless
you sucked and get them out about the
little Bell next to the subscribe button
so you can be notified when I post my
job guys I want to make you happy you
want to make you smile I want to
distract you from your busy life for the
next like 10 to 15 minutes or so now
let's see what the camp is doing good
morning party people good morning young
man what's up guys what we got we got my
god I love it I do I swear to god this
never gets old
[Music]
good morning cars camo and putting her
in the woods that's all good what we got
going on in here oh hello there Hayden
hi here
this cantaloupe it's an American fruit
yeah pretty nice okay no more foo-foo
what's the plan today people okay I
think we are gonna hike it ours we can
do oka what like no yeah yeah yeah for
sure definitely Wi-Fi hack for sure yeah
it's a fact cuz you're close to the
satellites in the space real talk though
I made it like a goal to assemble the
most odd group of people think everyone
is just so different has like a
different set of skills makes for some
lettuce content anyways where's my boys
even and speeches I gotta find my boy
are they have you seen my boys where are
my boys
even speed sir oh my god it's my worst
nightmare
pull up with my ceiling missing four
wheeler stay oh damn oh wow this is
beautiful Half Dome village I don't know
even what that mean I'm assuming it's
like 50% of a dome you have you seen my
boys my not my balls just mocking me I
don't have my boys or my balls even
hello my boy here adventurer halfway
across the United States to find you
guys why you come here bro I showered in
the lake it's a man hold on okay I'm my
voice but I don't forget to do your
hygiene guys
well I got you guys again here you go
fresh cantaloupe it's dirty but it
surprised all right well let's go back
and see if we're gonna hike oh wow you
look really LA right now damn bro that
thing rips dogs here we are I can't get
over our bougie ass setup right this is
the tents posted on top of the bus
coffee right campfire Starbucks for all
good campfire Starbucks no it's good
campfire Starbucks what's it a thousand
times I wonder when the Joe : how about
now hey guys let's go okay here are the
details guys this is no joke this hike
is about eight thousand feet high you'd
see we're gonna go up that way towards
the waterfall oh you know oh my gosh it
looks so beautiful there's two
waterfalls one right here one right here
okay so the goal is to make it up there
with the entire crew all of our limbs
and not hating each other there's
definitely a savage hike we all I
believe in this crew right y'all
maverick sorry I'm about to put these
performance shorts to the test I was
immersed in the game by the way it's
that maverick movement whether I
congrats to everyone who got the merch
over the weekend you got the new world
wide hoodie they just drop you had the
$10 t-shirts then we said huckett that's
not enough $5 t-shirt hello yeah we
definitely need these guys it's
important that we stay in communications
right cellphones don't work here but
yeah thank gosh Vince did bring up we do
have pine phones we give them a little
test before we go yeah you good okay all
right let's try a little farther back
yeah it's getting a little low you'll
get a little scratchy in and out type
thing but maybe go let's try a farther
it's getting worse and worse but I think
when we fire the closer we get with the
better I'm sorry I saw this sign here
I'm a little worried um each year over
200 people finish their hikes like this
being rescued I have a feeling that's
going to be you Olga
well I mean I didn't bring any water or
food
okay well exhibit a listen guys have no
fear especially you miss I've done this
before I've definitely made on this
before yeah yeah I have this whistle
just in case things happen okay let's
get hiking
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my god this is amazing it's just
water this mist just going across the
bridge
Oh
[Music]
evan is the waterfall this feels amazing
Doug O'Connell anybody you know this is
a moment I've been waiting to do since I
bought home
that's my boy we're too next I got this
five knots
southeast it's down Oh God
are you sick
quick kiss me no can't do that Logan not
now
she's something old man coughing take
these keys go back to the bus save
yourself okay okay
see you later get better no not Logan
the brook Titus yeah they weren't cut
out for we're the hardy losing half the
group we've a better even bloody started
yet so y-you know I get it I get I did
I'm not even mad it allows mad you know
good bye guys have fun if there's any
emergencies just call me on the PI phone
she's so basic
all right guys three down yes go you can
see some deer right we should tell him
that hey guys you're looking a little
cold and that you're not not lit but you
could be more or less so we're about to
go huh get on a trail but if you want to
grab some maverick mercs you can go
ahead and do so real easy just go to
Logan Paul calm /op and got the hottest
merchant the King was good
[Music]
Wow let me help something with you this
is no joke holy Sh we're also getting
started way late according to my watch
here dude I don't want to be one of the
people in the signs bro
[Applause]
upper yosemite falls 3.5 miles no dogs
allowed right so there's a good thing
kong left human walking okay
human walking spine yeah no mini dirt
bikes yeah definitely not all jokes
aside bro are pine phones and our
whistles might save our lives
[Music]
any chance we end up like the people on
the side let's hike you know we're
Mavericks everywhere we go we are really
like on the trail we're kind of just
like hugging them directly up the
mountain that's all we do a row we do a
different beat see you never
oh my Mac goodbye Silvana it's okay you
boys like mountain goat
here we go rock formation how you doing
yeah you got this bro use the
performance joy stuff yo yo yo real talk
you need a drink of water
oh my god it's so good probably not the
best for me since I'm still a little
sick but here's the thing I don't give
up I'm not a Spanish if you guys can't
keep up with your pace please do it
I depend more on my pace so you get the
straight you want us to slow down yes yo
yo you got a place you got a mental
toughness bro
[Applause]
[Music]
oh damn oh wow we're getting closer it's
already made it worth it you're doing it
bro is that mental strength I'll just
chill here hey touch my others two and a
half hours thank you for like three sure
though it's all about that mental
strength right Reshiram in two shakes
this is amazing I'm getting this like
weird earn everyone's going to the top
right that's like I it's cool and we
could do it for sure
but I want to see if we can get like
under the waterfall you guys remember I
went under waterfall in Hawaii one
fourth of this one yeah another fact
that was in Hawaii
yeah that's snow little colder here
nipples we'll definitely be able to cut
diamond it's looks right I don't know if
it's gonna happen but I'm saying it's an
idea okay see it has been planted the
idea
hey there Andy hey hey there Hayden hey
good question
thoughts on going under the waterfall I
mean we would be crushed by the fooling
water and our rain Jackson I'm just
saying bro everyone's going to the top
it'd be a real maverick move to not do
that I say we check it out miner Huck
see what happens
yo well it's definitely it's definitely
a little bit wet in here yeah bro when
they go right we go left we go left side
way we go left
[Music]
oh my god this is the move brochure this
is incredible damn son
I mean we have to breath Suns going down
so if we get cold there's no Sun or heat
no it's okay we have each other
yes let's go with duck should we hug it
over there be careful oh mylanta
what is Rakhi that's what I live for man
you guys aren't exploring the world
trust me that will make you the most
knowledgeable experienced person and
your hat you have to you absolutely have
no there's only like a 20 percent chance
this is a 100 percent
sketch yeah go get us some day
Oh be careful
oh dude all we need to do is get over
there where it's flat right then think
we'll be good
[Music]
we did a voice to dinner today
Spence ow yo all jokes aside guys it is
absolutely freezing just explain where
that water's coming okay let's go
historical over the past hundred billion
thousands of years a glacier I'm talking
snow I'm talking ice - four hundred
thousand degrees that water is no joke I
will say it's a good thing I got myself
some of the honey shot this merger
dictate having real talk though is about
to save me Oh roses but it really think
you want me taking my shirt off on
camera that trouser trousers these are
trousers so there's one of those things
you use the farm grapes for pants oh
[Music]
it's a good thing I have more bananas oh
just kidding
- merged in the game yes wanna go out on
it before we get hypothermia
who's that I am let's go in the cool bus
is waiting for you have no idea what we
just did most people right they go on
top of the falls
who went under and bro I would have been
down I mean you weren't so get out I
feel so good hi doggie what's up what
have you guys been doing
no YouTube we went under the waterfall
not on top of it I was doing is pretty
one college rower and you're just the
guy from London I prove everyone wrong
no I'm dumb addition right okay get him
Kong all right guys that is the blocks
I'm gonna sleep like a baby tonight guys
if you're not a part of lo game make
sure to subscribe
bring the notification bell next
subscribe button and join the most lit
family and YouTube guys thank you so
much for watching I love you I love you
I love you I love you I love you go so
it's very clear that our performance
shorts do indeed perform the Maverick my
local Paul clothing line is by far the
best merch in the game you already get
low-balled icon slash shop so join the
movement it be a maverick oh boy that's
it for today Logan I love you I'll see
you tomorrow
[Music]