oh no it's actually working thirteen
million thirteen million low gangsters
y'all it was so loud Wow favorite hoodie
it was restocked today yeah big most
power moves only ow you know the favor
hood you're still got my favorite hoodie
and you need to give it back Shay
Mitchell loves the favorite hoodie I
love to pick the low gang love the
favorite hoodie everybody loves a
favorite yes back in stock today that's
like one of our hottest selling items I
don't know just coming back so smooth oh
I can't look about like on /a poorly
description yo maverick bottoms are
dropping on November 1st if you saw
yesterday's vlog we actually just got
done filming with the other chair and
the forklift outside oh okay here's how
I feel about this chair tech technically
right it's ugly cuz it's like a bright
like vibrant color but I could see and I
love what murse
I was loud to whose house kind of echo
we need more furniture it's unusual I
know Brenda had the idea to shade our
giant pumpkin remember guys it's the
biggest pumpkin in California and it's
gonna start rotting soon so we have to
we have to exhaust all our opportunities
with the pumpkin well so today uh
already know by the title of this video
we have something fun we're gonna do
with the pumpkin oh yeah chicken just
moved in right is so many things we're
doing that doing do the house including
security cameras everywhere I was in the
kitchen yesterday I just do my thing and
barely Brendan was watching me what did
you see
I was watching Netflix and I got a text
from our security camera boys dancing
like an idiot owes me I was dancing as
yeah okay she's dancing I like I was
okay I joined her a little bit whatever
listen to some Kendrick and dancing bro
you don't do that Ren didn't like come
on I was in bed it's never slow guys
there's always projects going on here so
as you guys know my house came with
another house in the back I said white
wagon one house when you could get to
turning that into a gyms gonna be dumb
freakin youngness I wanted to paint the
inside so if you guys remember the tiger
video with Kong yo this is so oh okay
little backstory there was this guy
there named Nick Nicky was like yo my
boy is painting a mayor his team is
painting a mansion right I said that's
not a thing people don't normally paint
manages this guy mr. job turn up here's
my man
[Music]
it's a big deal it's imagine it's huge
these guys are so capable of painting my
gym so they drove here from Vegas these
guys we could one-30 a-m work throughout
the entire night his team is sleeping my
house there's one on a lawn chair here
yeah so we taped off the gym and we got
a few things going oh let's go a few
things first thing you're gonna see is
that you're going when I took this
picture I don't think you had I'm gonna
get abs look my boys been doing 12 sets
of 20 let's go if you're not a part of
the low gang and you're watching this
are you good bro subscribe button in the
face for me yo toward the strongest
family on YouTube but yo my mom low gang
is about to be here and she has never
seen the new palette my dearest mom is
about to be in for a surprise
we got a forklift we got the Yeti
everybody needs a portlet that's what
I'm saying here
everyone says guys so apparently house
looks smaller than it is I'm camera
every single person that comes here says
it's bigger in person forget about the
dog the house look at my yard we did
good you did good raising me yeah you
don't cry it's your house it's a
fairytale cottage it's true I'm
definitely already started building I
already started smashing too had a ball
too little maybe like three to five
girls just last night did I need to know
that no Nikki Lydia what do we have to
do this thing where she forgets what
she's saying halfway through her senses
one more time in merch model pics we
brought a model because she's actually
good-looking oh yeah no handlebars music
video coming soon to a theatre new you
would say I do have bad news someone
outside it was like they were like in
the forklift and they broke two plate
yeah
he was an [ __ ] but trying to blow dry
brush [ __ ] you just wanna just can't get
you out - just kick you out of mine I
just can't get you out of my bottom ah
yo can we whose idea was this can we not
have Jackie Natori work Jack your
maverick Oh God okay all right that's
superboy yoga so white it's disgusting
wait I'm not white what yeah what are
you yeah
I'm not even kidding go look at these
right now the merge game is about to
change forever like I could tell you
they have pockets on both sides I could
tell you they have a back pocket here
here's the pocket it's super secret for
the secret things you put in your butt
they're dropping on November 1st
I'll promo it alive then so just be
ready bro just save the money aspirin
for Christmas Thanksgiving it doesn't
matter okay I think I think it's time to
do the thing that this vlog is all about
so if you look around girls here right
for any quick sidebar so y'all they're
pretty basic it seemed a little basic
yeah I don't know how to make a pumpkin
spice latte me neither bro but I'm sure
they do we have the biggest pumpkin in
California yeah I think we take them to
the store get supplies to make the
biggest pumpkin spice latte in the world
with the most basic of girls so we get
this like world record certified I think
so I think so watches do you guys like
pumpkin spice lattes we have this idea
we want to make a giant pumpkin spice
latte but in the big pumpkin but we
don't know because we're dudes with
penises how to make a pumpkin spice
latte you actually know this is
incredible first off look at look at the
girls back there
this is your first ride in the Yeti it
certainly is it's your big day I've had
a lot of first set first today are you
having a stroke because you're on that
age do you know that your grandmother
your dad's mom died of a stroke at 5600
perfect how do you fifty-four
that's just great mom know if you mom I
swear yeah did you die I'll kill you
making it work we're crafters were
artists I'm already so annoyed it's
incredible yeah we ate all of it I need
all the milk would you get ridiculous
coffee okay flavors flavors alligators
it doesn't matter this has got to add to
the flavor huh little grin dear Papa
Papa Papa you owe me money pumpkin
butter phenomenal oh okay pumpkin spice
non-alcoholic I put it back oh there's
so much pumpkin spice goodness look it's
my super spicy spice its pumpkin it's
going yeah for sure it's going in this
slot they have a pumpkin like that
Brandon pumpkin pie spice I should do it
oh I look like Princess Diana
[Music]
okay so this experiment cost us four
hundred and thirty seven dollars it's
gonna be worth it it's gonna be
delicious I think for sure okay we're
about to make the world's largest
pumpkin spice latte in the world's
biggest butt towards the clean up look
like on this somebody get it milk all
over my new driveway know that it we're
out of milk no but in the coffee
[Music]
[Applause]
mahjongg can't do it I don't know the
pumpkin pie parts there was a box do you
want some pumpkin spice time look at my
pumpkin spice latte
quick side Barbara she's not like a
basic white girl
yeah or spiced drinks I'm all drink so
just looks like dirt and hey it's gonna
be so good we should just do a shot I
poured I worked hard to make this Brahma
beast
you're gonna project off on it
[Music]
[Laughter]
well yeah it's just it's solid it's only
coffee grass hot what hey basic [ __ ]
gonna be basically you also be a savage
it's like being basic isn't it solid
it's solid available at Logan Paul calm
slash I think that is the vlog if you're
not subscribed make sure to subscribe
because we risk our intestines for you
okay so smack the button in the face for
me and Gus saw today if you have not
copped your maverick merge yet make sure
to do so Logan Paul's icon slash shop or
link in description there favorite
hoodie is back November 1st we're
dropping bottoms big things are
happening bro power moves only our
neighbors blog hashtag I don't know how
we're gonna get the milk out of the
pumpkin the cleanup is gonna be a [ __ ]
but I love y'all now see you tomorrow
take it easy
[Applause]
[Music]
you're racist against almond milk yeah