but Anthony did you let him in here I
don't suppose a guard what is it hey
Logan here iPhone vlog classic Brendan
still sleeping guys um how do I say this
Hong Kong right away again this is now
becoming a recurring theme and that
first I thought it was my fault like I
have my eye on this dog he's in the
backyard I'm watching it and there's no
stopping this dog like it's like I know
I have a hole I have a really bad
feeling about this like I feel like I
feel like we've gotten very lucky with
finding Kong in the past not not feeling
good about this bro this is horrible
what's up what what are you doing I
think Kong's gone what do you mean I
think he's gone
yeah gone gone yeah gone gone like you
guys have seen we haven't clicked baited
Kong legitimately runs away what am I
doing wrong
quick like a cheetah shut up stop bigger
things to worry about Frank my dog just
ride away all right I saw the dog going
this way the dog went this way excuse me
so so we found Kong okay let me show you
what I saw in the security cameras you
guys understand what type of dog this is
okay look so I'm watching the cameras
here look how fast this dog is like you
see him bolt through the frame all the
way up the side of the house and then
guys I'm playing this real time I follow
him and I'm literally right after him so
that home he goes sprinting up the side
of the house without hesitation hops
right through the fence he doesn't stop
you doesn't looking at something Douai
they knew exactly where to go the hole
is this big this hole he just squeezed
through this hole like he already knew
where to go my man straight prison-break
to me nine hundred percent this was
predetermined and I bet if I put him
down right now who do the same thing be
free oh oh yeah now he stays oh look at
me I'm just a dog I'm just sitting here
being cute I've never been here before
hello good morning okay was good if
you're not a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe we are late we are the
best family on YouTube and we got a fun
flog today
no not not kong contry thank god little
brother Jake what I'm gonna be honest
with you guys I'm sorry to think there's
only one way that we can actually just
control call call it doggy on coach's
doggy Alcatraz so the theory was guys
you know Alcatraz is a prison like in
the middle of the ocean it was ocean
what's the body-worn francisco bay guys
only like two prisoners have ever
escaped Alcatraz the ones who did like
died on the swim in so we figured if we
Alcatraz Kong's will never be a little
scape I think this is gonna work guys
but um okay there's sort of an emergency
going on right now here's here's what
this vlog is about here's what we did
last night last night guys we just
pulled up to brother Jake's house we
gotta be quiet cuz he does not know I'm
here no one actually on team ten knows
I'm here the security guards know me so
they let me in but I told Andi and Mac I
don't want anyone to actually know what
I'm doing
so here's what's happening so the guy's
repeating in my gym they're called the
a-team they're here painting Jake's
generally they're doing some sort of
Sistine Chapel on the top and I'm like
you how funny would it be if like I can
paint something Jake's Tim like super
secret Jake's not a tile right now he
comes back he's going home this is sick
action we got what can I like mess up or
become a part of like how the hell you
got baby what if you make me a baby or
paint my face my big obnoxious my
profile picture there's just like you
painted on a baby so every time Jake
comes in here he goes that's my daddy
[Laughter]
[Music]
this prank is rooted in fun so please
don't hate me but I am gonna pay myself
on your wall it's all I broke whatever
could I see two babies without heads
together bro I need you to put your face
on that baby it'll be like a double
prank
put your face on that baby I'll be on
this baby these babies are great it's a
done deal
brother Jay came back early it's like 10
a.m. so our Monty calls me and he's like
hey dude the team 10 manager just called
me apparently some of the kids in team
10 snitch that we were there which I
understand my fault for being seen I
thought I was stealthy what the manager
texted Armani and she's by the way I've
never heard of this girl she must be new
cuz Jake's manager is the guy so he was
a conversation that took place ah good
morning can you give me a shot when
you're up
Armani says good morning and then she
sends a picture of my baby with the
thing over his face mm-hmm and she says
is that Logan if so I can guarantee that
this will not go over well and that's
coming from his best friends in there
[Music]
bro I don't know worried about drip for
Jeff ah yeah drama with brother Jake
tomorrow we have a huge merge drop like
a Mart shop that's gonna make history
one more shop that's gonna dent the
universe it's a big boy we're releasing
no handlebars this week don't worry
about drama guys so
laws throw we lost that race true so
Jake is I don't think he knows what's
going on obviously no one from Team
Tennis told him but I think the dialogue
is that I just came with Andi to have
fun and then when he shows us the
painting I'm a bit whoa that's so cool
wait what is that what that's not me
like I'm play dumb bro yeah I'm like a
Switzerland
you know neutral country here and like a
both brothers are yeah oh snap I see
Armani
I think Team Tennis pissed oh we gotta
go we gotta go
what you don't know anything you know
that's definitely the girl that texted
Armani just text in Jake just like me
they're here they're at the house dude
it's her first day on the job she wants
to be a good team just like leading us
in it's kind of weed I don't feel safe
all right so Jake's not here Q the
waiting montage
and the good is going down Andy Andy
what are you doing at this oh well I may
or may not have gotten a text that said
Logan's face is painted on your wall
what did you do that our money did your
trade sides down no I don't know why are
you here
jake has never seen this room he seemed
to paint for the first time thank you
bro like this yeah yeah yeah why are
these faces covered here why is he
vlogging it - what this is my moment my
story I don't know baby good luck dude
Anthony did you let him in here
I don't do sister Paula Gardner what is
it
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone's fired hold up now I can
explain I said to myself I'm your
brother and I want to be your brother
and baby for so I painted myself as a
baby and then he came over and he had
yeah there was something happening he
came true why can't I just ever have a
nice thing homey homey homey worry about
this in a sec row just like this just
something else you should see I think
please please bro
what is this no I don't I don't this is
that is that you in here about to throw
a [ __ ] fit hold us with your security
our security security they go they go
you're his brother I go yeah
[Music]
no in the dark
you can run but you can't hide I know
where you live
[Music]
you been I've been good how are you I
think I'm gonna go home what ending the
vlog with Kong in my possession that
makes me happy also makes me happy that
brother Jake wasn't actually mad
surprising but I'll check it so after
this right now actually we're gonna make
some music guys yes I'm recording a
Christmas song hey no handlebars is
coming out this week either tomorrow or
on Thanksgiving Day I have to decide if
I want you guys to listen to the
following lyrics I can ride your girl
with no handlebars around your parents
at Thanksgiving just not sure how like
the family would would accept that Jo
the point is if you're not in the low
gang you suck and you can unsub if you
subscribe that's all that fire I'm
putting now burn also to Maverick squad
the Maverick revolution growing everyday
we just out here changing the world and
smell a bomb slash shop looking I love
y'all now see you tomorrow
[Music]
my god