no Logan what is happening oh good boy
that was weird
okay guys so it's really earlier so I
have these sunglasses on because so kind
of sleeping actually and me and the why
don't we boys are taking the jet back to
Los Angeles
what's some number door hello oh yeah oh
yeah Amanda - Jeff - so let's do it
goodbye casino by piano by lion goodbye
reflex goodbye hooter and hello good
morning boys good morning boys good bro
I want some money I gambled got I won
$2,000 I forget Harper's next on deck
more snacks on deck yes is the move go I
don't feel bad for Jack what happened
buddy what you doing back there
you know the coolest part about this
shot is I could see my boy Jeff ain't
never done rubble Wow nice private jet
are faster and more better and we are
take all these look at all the builders
look at a ferris wheel look at the law
all I gotta say is likes me
I'm gonna take this yellow nappy -
laughs OH
look around guys I'm back in Los Angeles
and you know who I missed that you guys
probably missed - my boy hi buddy off my
mom next what sure kind of someone who
missed me hi god I love a gaga buddy
oh my boy welcome to this little bit
dinner oh man I missed this little fur
ball don't flop me all the night oh snap
I forgot you know what today that's
right buddy
hi darling
okay I'm going to tell you guys are
teaching today it's all about the smart
- Oh smart we got the smash honey time
you guys would you put this on one thing
to do that smash whether its food
whether it's a tap whether it's a female
or male doesn't matter the point is you
don't be smug way towards maverick
inception so yeah guys we've got this
mastery these are lit at there's also a
dope tank top and t-shirt make sure you
get that stuff yeah that's right
maverick ocean Paul calm slash shop or
link in the description and you know
what this is good because don't forget
I'm doing the free iphone 7 plus
giveaway all you have to do is buy
summers and you're automatically going
to be entered in the contest so go on
the side get some maverick merch get
some smash gear and you could be entered
to win an iPhone bro yeah anyway so
interesting thing before I started
recording this I had had this
conversation with my mom what did you
just say to me mom this is ridiculous
and I hate this apparently I just read
300 pounds of subscribe know you guys
understand you should not have 300
thousand subscribers I'm sorry
I agree 10 to 18 years old I did YouTube
for eight years and I got four thousand
subscribers that's it they left me the
penalty speaking of this what was your
next thing you asked me whose beauty
products I know
pooty pyres she goes with PewDiePie
we love right there that's a fake
account problem you had definitely shake
account pewdiepie did not follow you on
YouTube I'm sorry about I thought I was
really good
yo but then this brings me to my next
thing my mom asked me to do something
for her vlog what is this a face man
this is the new mask that I want Logan
to Tron just come take my face at turn
black or something yeah because it's
kind of a get out all of your impurities
well I'm perfect so I
doesn't work I'm playing seven seconds
later I'm doing my own voiceovers woke
up [ __ ] would you judge me ma boo
take it off did you know my peanut hi
guys I would take this [ __ ] mask off
and we're gonna play the con a little
bit get my boy a little exercise match
guys okay it's so cute this is what
needs to happen more for them to bond
icon eazy-e all yo were you doing
calling you still go see maverick you
just want to chill ha ha ha no what's up
man one day guys are gonna be friends
and it's gonna be Rome 8c good prop you
good
you got this buddy you got it feel like
most parents would help their child but
this is hilarious today you got it buddy
nothing mahboy so now we're playing
fetch with calm we realized here watch
though it go get it no damn it anyways
we realize when he goes to get the ball
he reaches a certain speed where he'll
tuck his ears back for ultimate
aerodynamic purposes watch I come took
it and watch carefully
hey watch my gosh ears back
I would look that I'll go good thing so
when my boy wants to poop
I bought him some grass because as you
guys know I live in the middle of
Hollywood I'm talking about no grind
until now we got the brilliant idea to
have grass brought to our house switched
out twice a week will up board and
ticket yellow grass no this is authentic
astute you know it's hilarious my my
vlog channel youtube.com slash Logan Bob
Wallace make sure you like this guy's oh
my gosh it's going yo guys real grand
I'm bringing the jungle to Hollywood ma
I'm gonna be living large my boys doing
we'll have to put you in this puppy jail
cuz you'll be potty trained and you can
experience the joys of life oh we got
probably the first is at my parents
blogs actually hit I'm watching my
brother's vlog he's stole clogs your
phone you gave him gone you did he's
soaked all it took good care of no
you're not
they're all there like humping Kong and
everyone just putting their hands on a
dirty paws honking they all do and they
made it into chemical it says Wong is
average so act like Monica long is
average team Zen puppy I love my owner
Jake Paul on the low game sucks you know
what the who I'm genuinely pity I knew
this was coming I knew when I got this
dog there's going to use it for
subscribe what can I do this is bad bro
I have an idea what we put some kind of
huge animal just bring it in their house
and leave it really right like a cow
wrap in Logan yeah we're good cow or
something uh we don't want to get it go
like you care like I do I go yeah come
on let me find she can finish gate to
keep it I need to have a go we have to
buy a goat goat Sarah I'm sure there's
some no that's a good that's a good
praying I'm like Connor piss right now
I'm not just like stop smiling but I
want to kill G so here's the plan first
steps for paper everyone go ahead and
report Wang as a ver let's do it's
inappropriate
I believe this account violates
instagrams Community Guidelines profiles
pretending to be someone else a
celebrity or public figure please enter
the name of a person being impersonated
Hong the savage submit hey guys future
Logan here I'm actually on set right now
so right now it is the next
des and I checked it for the longest
average account and it's gone it's gone
guys it's not on the internet meaning
either Jacob the account and he's gonna
bring him back later when he steals Kong
again or B you guys allo game reported
it already without even me telling you
to yo you guys are amazing if you did
that thank you and I just appreciate
love you quick little I love you okay
back it along I'm sorry I watching this
long it's actually really sucky they put
them on the room that's what Kong on the
roof guys this is animal of you this is
Bennett stop long this is all your fault
let me rewrite you guys okay I respect
Jake I will say he's a good youtuber he
is creative I will say I think he lacks
talent and actual acting ability he
laughing Jesse knows is true yes it is
because he's a Disney actor Oh guys
let's do this big photo joke I'm a real
actor bro movie star
valley girl cuz however I still have to
[ __ ] him up hey buddy I'm sorry
those kids are real jerks huh yeah I
know buddy I don't know why they put you
on top of a roof a little [ __ ] up I
know you could have fallen but it's okay
at least you fine hey I got a question
for you bro do you by chance have to
poop call nobody right in the corner
there's a new grass you can poop there
like me I mean no way what I I don't I
don't never poop there oh my gosh oh
thank you I think of my wife you got a
buddy be a maverick and go poop on the
girl that's a new poop spot go potty
Carlo Bobby go Bobby babe I wonder if I
need to take that on me personally I
hate pooping with clothes on someone
take it off now let's try go potty : no
don't eat the grass go potty go potty
don't no no no snack home potty is weird
okay guys the little stickers not going
potty because a tongue but you know why
I think he knows that I was going to
collect the poop and throw it at Jake's
house and he's like bro why don't you
just have me poop at Jake's how I like
that idea buddy would you be down to
like poop on is better suited yeah okay
cool wait Logan what are you what are
you doing right now
no let me introduce you to christen
hatch the queen of music from Logan
you're gonna be am user now musically
bro apples and balls you want a little
sour
help Wow I forgot to mention the boys
are here Jeff is doing a thing
I just bet this man 25 you bet 20 bucks
that he can't yo what's this bet what is
the bet Jeff this is one drink
Oh straight straight straight I put 200
no we're on a road shake my head bro be
a minute oh are you my boy are you my
boy yup I'm vlogging one golf like you
have to stay on go go go oh you know
everyone is filming Jeff oh I have faith
in you I want us to do it go this is 1.5
liters of waters and crazy yo you're
gonna have to see a lot every ya know
you're gonna gain so much respect No
where's the money
Geoffrey $200 for you my back how did he
do that oh man got no stomach ready to
debit credit or debit card some ringing
[Music]
nice oh it's been like probably a month
I'm not even kidding I shaved my face I
can tell that I painted my toenails that
doesn't make you look extra serious that
makes me disco Daniel my boy stop I'm
ending the vlog you shouldn't have three
thousand two thousand subscribers yeah
guys kill him smuggling to death got
sick I want to pee on his bed let's move
out oh yeah George Jones was a prank
with Jacob are you leaving
I am okay great absolutely for you yo I
want you to have this this is female
maverick merch she wears it you'll be a
maverick Kristen because you are a
maverick Mona doesn't follow the path of
others sue and acne the better they
write whatever one goes right we were
left and you're a maverick I seen you on
that musically yeah yeah guys watch out
for our collabs calmly pop in and George
has just met calm oh my God thank you by
the way Daniel employs a bro Saten
Savage broke Kong diss a baton and
screams you wanna follow me Oh yo I know
right he's like the little Simba from
Lion King oh yes oh Jesus plug help me
help you we go me Paul Hogan so screw
your [ __ ] but I love you saying and yeah
if you guys have not seen help me help
you go watches and - bro link in
description tell me help you
or what's your trouble - oh I don't got
to know I know tell me help you cuz I'm
hungrier than you I just want to get
some pudding you all nothing - oh yeah
we're about to go make Kong poo but
Jake's house but yo my dog just died on
me bro this is a problem we need you
mmmm savage guy yup he hasn't movies are
you hear what I said I do this okay so I
got the ammunition me my mom and George
you're going to play with George what
one more Hey look wait mark George whoa
George it's green bro he just mother of
god no okay so what about the savers we
got George we got mark apparently now I
mark what's my okay yeah uh we need we
need parkland Greg I got others people
like that beers like John tests that
match the fence
you notice how Jake only has two fans Oh
your fans mom
guess who got kicked out of their old
apartment because fans would why not
have a whole cavalry of low gangster Wow
okay guys we're sneaking up on Jake's
house right now now we're not gonna do
that they know you're not you're lucky
what I'm genius what up G what up G oh
you got a bucket water water
you got water go you got water yo
Oh
[Laughter]
Oh y-you guys animal abuse in bro
here's I'm wondering George's up top
George do it ah Wow yeah bro waters
that's my boy these guys just get
physical my boy uses his brain yeah you
PMS pianist dahi on his bed and film in
George's ass AB gosh how do you say
thank you too far and we are Hollywood
fit we laugh okay let me just say I
think prank wars is actually becoming
Wars like they had a different water run
George you had a bucket of their
different parent ever I didn't know
every son hanging people we broke on us
before his windshield
does that's great man destroying people
stuff I'm trying to distract him right
now on George pees on his head no give
me one finding Victor give me one you
guys always have people here only to
those I got kicked out of my last leg
driving a lot more than two low game for
life I was like they stole Kong I got to
get them back with clay I was going to
have Kong like Wong poop on your bed but
I was like yo if I distract him long
enough and my boy George is still in the
house he could just pee on Jake's bed
himself Shawn enough said don't he's
doing it right now okay for life
yeah touch done did my eggnog hard I
know we go the real mark always bug mash
look upon flesh nothing in this case our
enquiries another hey yo he's locking me
a mom I go no Logan what is happening
code oh no god damn it don't move that
truck right now
mom has spoken that's enough Oh guys the
Queen has spoken
oh come on Dan oh are you a neighbor
here what's going on these Kitab say
what is it every day bro yes man I
recommend filing a complaint
salty neighbor
closer salty neighbors don't get in come
on get in we got hella salty neighbors
too salty neighbors we up the whole
street is lined with neighbors George
si yo I think we just won the prank war
you have the P go I got here you know oh
my god oh my god that's my boy you guys
already seen this footage this is just I
love you had to bro I don't know
I sleep in that bed just I had you to
leave with your son Jake yeah yo who do
you pick from buddy Greg block yo I
think we won because like he faces like
real-life consequences like he's gonna
get kicked out to God and we're gonna
give him a final to buying way out did
you expect
[Music]
yo no gang you know we did today smash
what a day bro yo this is my boy like a
firm that's my boy it's been an hour
together like every time we rekindle
it's like it's amazing and while we're
best friends
I guess that's it for the vlog couple
things hey I won't give away two enough
for Gager maverick Moriches mask t-shirt
Tuesday Oh sunny now yeah to really go
report Hong Kong as a breach on
Instagram
can't have him a boy being impersonated
he's so cute over there and then three
subscribe if you're not subscribed to
your new Jake Potter I understand
welcome to the family but also Jacob
your bed smells what's up man don't mess
with the squad don't mess with tool okay
that a dog with you tomorrow
take it easy van please
good
[Music]
hey hey let me ask you something here
a-team tell you where people say you
serve over look what's what is going on
well