planning something Logan what are you
sure I'm on your side should we get back
got it dumped water hold before come on
boy quick week this Friday May 22nd
after a year and a half a rebranding
we're finally dropping the new line of
Maverick load and I want to make one
thing clear this is no longer murse this
is clothes high-quality garments in fact
I am so confident our product I'm gonna
make a tether right now and swing on it
like Tarzan hey I really believe in this
so that's what I'm essentially risking
my health and safety to prove how dope
this new shoes really put my money where
my mouth is if I'm buying a t-shirt I
want to know if I can swing it cross
clothing smacking clothing calm this
right
proud of us has an organization leveling
up once again changing the game raising
the bar from here to here when it comes
to high quality you guys combined to one
Wow he's going for it also know what the
fresh waffles I like this new day the
other day that seems excessive
damn I'm used to like 30 to 45 seconds
well right mates we're gonna class the
case of some influences in the wild like
in Lana I'm making a tick-tock how it
looks pretty exhilarating from being on
storm water in cups in OneNote to Philly
I cannot think of anything more exciting
oh my god oh my dog he just dumped a
bucket of water on his girlfriend I've
never seen Lana that way that's a yeah
that's so funny
[Music]
[Laughter]
six months my roommate Evan you guys
know I haven't you love Evan he's been
having a problem with his arm like I
think he's got like tennis elbow or
something and this week I saw him
running around with the brace on what
are you doing do you need a new arm yeah
I heard really bad I got you you said
you wanted a new arm so I got you three
Wow
it's like I don't have to use this arm
anymore ah people with no arms people
would don't aren't you dumbass well how
its arms use this then ha ha ha ha look
this is great now whatever you want to
use it just pull this can we do it oh
you know like surgery come on bro I
spent $500 on arms for you would someone
do that I think we lost Evan officially
hey come on man they're using that thing
a little differently than I would yeah
will you lose this dick little
differently I would too
[Applause]
[Music]
somewheres looking at your vlogs right
now and they're like what are what he's
doing right now is millions of dollars
beautiful women around them and this is
what the [ __ ] you're doing I'm not proud
of myself man come on guys this is
getting out of hand
[Music]