[Music]
okay welcome back to another video if
you're not a part of the low gang the
strongest family on the internet make
sure to subscribe there's this challenge
going around it's the acrylic nail
challenge mind you I know nothing about
critic nails that's why we have Olga cuz
she's like kind of a girl me and my boys
want the longest acrylic nails you can
possibly give us so we came to get the
longest acrylic nails possible for me
and all my boys let's go blue to match
the hottest sauces merch in the game
full set no are you saying full send I'm
like absolutely well said well said well
if these ripoff are my real-life nail is
gonna rip off no this is already so
different I literally just can't answer
my phone for manager Jeff how do I this
I can't hello I can use it uncle using
uncle I'm getting really long acrylic
nails can we talk later dope for vlog
actually no what no this is for me
personally can you hang up though cuz I
can't really is your nails I can't
impossible apparently you just don't do
it I just can't move no you can you just
can't wait that doesn't seem effective
how am I gonna do that nothing you're
saying makes any sense look at my hey I
look like Wolverine
[Applause]
yeah I mean yeah just doing anything you
know bring one shot here we go
I have the worst news I have to pee I
really have to pee in floor mat this
extraordinary creature it's a slice like
I feel like a slime that's what's gonna
happen to you if you live on nothing but
leaves this is horrible this is so
difficult I can't shake it
all right no problem no you're not doing
it right
we're friends we're all friends here
welcome Mike you gotta get my zipper I
can't do it I'm so sorry you had to go
through that no seriously I I panicked
please tell me how I take out my fing
Invisalign there's no chance
Harvey B do this she has these nails on
like regular the difference between you
and her she's a bad [ __ ] look at
acrylic nails what are you doing out
you cannot you guys can buy this now in
Logan Paul calm slash shop you have to
use the middle of your finger when you
swipe or anything got to poop yeah good
luck soldier update man how long are you
one step at a time this is the disaster
this sucks
what do you got we mean what do we got a
long acrylic nails damn your or a vlog
there's my Clarice how'd it go what's
going on horrible how was it how'd you
do it horrible I did it
but wiping is impossible trying to
upload a YouTube video I just want to
take a momentary pause if you're a
female and you rock these this is the
hardest thing I've done in my life my
friends can't even wipe their asses dude
- but I hate this so much
yo yo I realized when we clap it's kind
of funny but we need something to clap
at right so I brought a guy he's up
there his name's Pasha
[Music]
it was really great Oh we'll worry about
it later
shake my hand
Oh No Oh
smells so bad in questionable places I
want to be a bad [ __ ] thing honey I
feel like I want to do some magic so yo
let's go work out get with Stan
oh we do it's not all we do is done yeah
we start all we do is done all we do is
done yeah we start all we do is done are
we doing stunts your stunts are we doing
stunts are we doing
all I do is be stopped 8 YT dudes be
Friday hit the mall about what I wanted
you touched it or we jump in a pop Allah
we dump it reset base up in this bump it
we do this like it's nothing why dates
off but they bluffing
I broke a nail my job I'm breaking yo ha
I'm falling apart so many nails I break
boys not breaking I'm calling it quits
lo gay guy I thought I'd give you 24
hours now shout out to all the girls
that can do this I'm gonna try break
them right now feel like it's on branch
just like hold it and rib Oh
we kind of did it low gang we left some
broken nails in a hurt level of
testosterone go skiing now yes go skiing
guys if you are not subscribed make sure
to join the little Gang Gang Gang pick
that bus and for me for all my max out
there keep doing you yo you want to get
acrylic nails you can do and if you
feeling a bit weird today embrace that
yes you would be proud to be you cuz no
one else isn't that some other fast
Jewish man oh we doin started
oh we do it's done
all we do is we start oh we do it's done
oh we do it's done it's done oh we do
it's done oh we do it I broke all my
nails I told you you would I know you
were right for once I leave