[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
people are making million dollars after
one game it's gonna take at least a four
oh gosh good thing my upper-body
strength is on par my face I'll be fine
all right all right okay
maybe a lot a part of the low game make
sure to subscribe guys the fortnight
that's which thing is happening first
off I got a twitch it's at Logan Paul
was taking Logan Paul was taken
literally user named Gus subscribe to me
on that I'll pull them up by these
maverick bottoms so the strongest
version of the game so good Paul that
kind of side shot as the hats motion and
get out baby nuts was good make sure to
join the low game that I say that but
also subscribe to my channel which I now
have as you can see I'm working on it I
gotta get better at the game
what play
[Music]
yes that was me I witness I'll see you
may have noticed my brothers here look
at me when lo are you actually good at
this game bro I'm gonna get this w I
don't think so bro I'm the for tonight
King had Logan fall was dig no this is
crazy
this game is sensationalizing I was
taking over the world pretty soon Trump
is gonna be playing it he's probably
already done yo you guys want to go do
real life stuff like talk stock s I go
work out yes speaking of JJ I'm sure
you've heard fight has been confirmed
the contract has been signed August 25th
London I am officially fighting ksi it's
gonna be a fight no shots fired I'm not
gonna underestimate the kid ray I'm
taking it very very I'm not gonna
underestimate the kid I'm taking it very
seriously in fact a couple weeks to go
before the contract was even signed I
went I got boxing equipment bag I think
we're in the right place time to get
fitted boy they have quite the selection
of things used to be people's asses with
Exhibit A look at that guy he looks
defeated this guy looks like my brother
Jake but better-looking oh really oh
he's sexy oh this feels good this feels
I'll take them oh these are nice hey
what no free brand deals already don't
hang on them too dang yeah for sure
Wow look I never feel like a boxer and a
dancer these are for the classic the
speed bag when you see the boxers going
like that right make some cool noises
for rhythm pypi okay this feels good
I'll take five I'm gonna need this
uppercut bad for them uppercut oh these
are stable environment
okay get it boys Wow good work we have
so much stuff we're really putting those
shots to good use these are tight right
here they're normally not that close
hope we don't break down on the way home
and we back and that's looking good all
of it no I mean I got tires - boy this
I'll be so ready for this fight kiss I
bro you see the title man you just you
you don't have a chance of winning and
then later I'm gonna break it down for
you why like first off bro I know for a
fact you can't handle this power you'd
like I've been hit in the face by Logan
ball before and like it is not a joke at
all break it up break it up hey I know
what we can do in the vlog I could talk
just about his little brother oh now
that's happening COO I just want to let
you know buddy you're going down oh not
just anywhere you're going downtown
oh that did my chocolate no this might
be the best blog I've ever made I'm not
any case' so good so many meaningful
moments you're going down the number two
reason you can't beat me JJ my awareness
is I'm take to my awareness is awareness
take free number two reason my awareness
you know number three JJ this is not a
joke I know you're scared bro when we
met up in person or more like when I
caught you sitting on a couch during
your training you could just smell the
fear and I'm not just saying that I saw
a video of you making eye contact with
your last opponent Jo Weller during one
of your face offs right like you were in
the zone like man's feeling good and I
get a rose kind of badass but the thing
is I'm not Joe Weller and when I met up
with you my dude would not look me in my
eyes like I'm in your head bro and I
know Jake's in Daddy's head he's
dangerous he's a fighter he'd been doing
it for years he's still been doing it
for a while and exclusive daddy's going
down
with special wanna film the special
Spencer down [ __ ] y'all ain't ready
alright yo actually have something to
tell you what when I made my first video
about this boxing match I said to que si
that kiss I bro
I'm not wearing headgear dawg I don't
want to do that that's the last thing I
want to do I think it's the silliest
thing in the world in the contract I
signed because they were had they had a
time limit on me bro they're like
putting the pressure on so I signed it
and cuz they would not change this
little kiss ILP agree these fight rules
approved headgear open cheek I swear to
God I swear I wouldn't
I'm not fighting anybody with heavier
that's so I thought I literally
guarantee you I'm not fighting anybody
without your I know yes I you say you
want to be a pro boxer you look you want
cute little fluffy man take off that hey
[Applause]
we gotta work on that
no one wants headgear nobody and your
man is your Stewart I see you by the way
Stewart about the can throw you in the
ring with my manager Jeff regardless
there's gonna be a lot of fights know
what pop is Nick Crompton fighting put
them on oh my god when we prank Nick
Crompton and he fires back at us real it
is lethal yeah that's a lot of weight
coming at you though okay
we've been talking for a while now I
think I it's time to Train see that dude
you see that bring it back
see that one
[Music]
they never seen some stuff like that
never seen it oh my god yo I am looking
forward to this fight guys mark your
calendars it's gonna be August 25th it's
gonna be streamed live from London Bob
wants you to watch it with your friends
this is going to make YouTube history
mark my word and we gonna show the world
just how strong the low gang as the Jake
Pollard's are the Maverick movement is
in the jig Palmer that's what's up bro
make sure you copy yourself some Logan
Paul yeah join the movement people doing
a different every single day and
whatever reason not part of the low game
make sure to subscribe smash the button
for me kiss it on the mouth
yeah birth to it anything you want
really just make sure that button says
subscribe
whoa gang that is the vlog I love you
and I will see you tomorrow
[Music]
Ceyda
London is my country