Gordon Blanc or some longtime yo what's
up guys it's your boy LP so I went on
the good old internet today and I saw
our good friend kiss I uploaded a video
he said why I beat Logan Paul that's
interesting cuz I don't think you did I
thought we'd tied I'm pretty sure we tie
I know we tied here's a picture of us
you're on the right side as you can see
both of our hands are raised commonly
referred to as a draw but okay I see I'm
actually gonna be making one of these
pretty soon to is like a round by round
analysis saying like why I thought I
should have won the fight so if you guys
have not yet subscribed make sure to hit
the button for me but I figured I would
watch this video and see what chaos eyes
commentary and perspective is on the
fight and see how he interpreted the
fight before I do my full analysis so
let's dive in why I'm here to explain
why I won the fight Oh was a time but
okay all right judges got it wrong
stay out like absolutely biessed know
scooby-doo laughs it's coming back to
his brain he doesn't understand why I
was wearing the mask coming from the
dude wearing a full mask nice jobs see
him was that doing a few frames just to
see what he does whenever I try son it's
interesting cuz ki is definitely more
technical than I am um at this stage in
my boxing career anyways that's one of
the pros he had over me his um
experience and his ring knowledge really
really helped him in this fight because
I think he's been training for about a
year and I'm I'm I was like four months
in well you know he had a really good
job that's a really good job I gotta
give him an thanks man yeah I know my
tweet I'm pretty quick and I discovered
that I have a pretty lethal jab
literally a week and a half before the
fight so it's gonna be cool in the
rematch being able to build things
around the jab sort of just relying on
like one punch he takes his time he
really doesn't want to attack but he
taught me that was good right obviously
I I I can eat punches today's I did
notice that about ksi I was impressed I
wasn't because I hit I hit pretty hard
didn't seem to faze him too much who's
got a chin OC he was getting me so
he started being a bit cocky but you
know that wasn't gonna face me I don't
know that never affects me I disagree
that's the one thing I noticed after the
first round
I'm telling you his spirit change his
demeanor changed wasn't like King ksi
that he portrays on the internet I think
he realized that it's this was a real
fight and like he says he wants to go
pro right but you have this like dude
who like barely learn how to box
who just whooped your ass and is now
taunting you in front of millions of
people I know that got in his head I was
a few good punches that so yeah he got
he told me he got me there pretty good
so I was there like come on let's go
after I hit him like with five five hard
punches in a row man I was trying to be
a showman like you can see I'm standing
there with my arms out and in reality I
just have attacked him but yeah first
boxing match got a lot to learn still
your boy always first up first up on the
ring like my stamina and condition is
always on point so I always made sure
that Fitness is number one because that
essentially is what wins you fights
that is so true and don't get me wrong
we condition our asses off like I've
never been in that good of shape in my
life like we would run for so long so
many times during the day and I just
wouldn't get tired but something about
this boxing match you know being in
front of the people being at my first
fight for the first time it's different
dude like it just drains you and he
knows that and I think next time for
sure definitely gonna up the fitness
physique stamina game give him that job
in the cross and then uh I've gotta
admit man this boy loves to clinch oh my
gosh you'll see I get so frustrated with
it and the referee tells me off for
because I'm flooring him across he did
not like the clinch the clinch is like
when we would get close and I would kind
of grab him or hold him or like he'd do
the same to me yeah I know he did not
like that I [ __ ] hate is pissing me
off a lot more friends to try and get
him to jab just so I could slip under
and you know create some create some
openings so I was really wild with our
right hand but I realized that the
overhand is working because he's
probably used to very traditional
way of flying so if I made it scrappy I
knew you wasn't gonna be able to deal
with it that is very true that is very
true this dude came in here fighting
like a dog like he uses terms like
overhand right or like hook but he's not
throwing like these punches they just
they're crazy coming from Timbuktu and
he got away with it in this fight you
want to go pro man you're gonna get your
ass kicked it thrown like that so okay
so now you're probably wondering yeah
why did I yeah him off to the ball
Wow ladies and gentlemen it's because
this model hit me twice after the bell
but you don't see it what what do you
mean bro first off that is false second
off you don't see it dude there's a ref
in the ring millions of people watching
it's on video what are you what are you
talking about the bells wrong he's
hitting me once and then he's hit me
again with his fright and I'm there like
nah dude dude dude this is boxing if the
bell rings and my arms in motion and it
happens to hit like tap you not even I
don't want to say hate you that's just a
sport that's how any sport when the bell
rings the action then stops well you
don't got to be like a sport about it
and blatantly hit me after the bell by
giving him hard line it's a little job
it's a little job like it doesn't matter
dude if you like stab someone with a
pocketknife versus like a large-scale
knife you still stab someone okay
horrible analogy but you see what I'm
saying right ah wait what guillotine ha
ha let's go oh gee stopped himself
bralla curity didn't even hold it well
again you see go talk to Merrigan sand
and that's when he clinches so whenever
oh this mother okay listen
true totally true but I will say a
clinch is a very it's a pretty mutual
maneuver like when I clinched I go over
he goes under we're kind of like hugging
I'm not holding you there that I would
be wasting my energy I'm kind of just
like leaning out a little bit that's
part of the sport I don't hear any other
boxers complaining about it if you
didn't like it you could have pushed out
and tried to hit me with you
did sometimes but yeah it's definitely
the wrestler in me kicking in another
right so there so I threw him bad
because this model was constantly
clinched me I'll stare like fun stop
punching me yo yo you're a king scumbag
of a fighter like you fight dirty bro
and I'm trying to like box this is one
of the big problems I had with the fight
he's fighting dirty and he's doing
things that aren't legal in boxing and
for some reason this is not being
accounted for in the score I think why I
won and why I would have given me the W
is because he's fighting dirty and no
points were lost for that apparently I
knew Logan was very tired you know he's
got such a large frame so much muscle
that I knew all the lactic acid etc was
getting to him suddenly ksi is a
biologist I knew the lactic acid
combined with his white blood cells
would create a foam and a window of
fatigue like the only way to win this
was to be scrapping wild I needed to
just get up in his I respect that I mean
it's true it doesn't really like I can
see here like mock his fighting style
and say he doesn't look like a boxer
he's just like going out swinging his
arm but at the end of the day like it's
part so no no room to talk really for me
cuz it was working and he got up in my I
needed to just get up in his just
because he hates that he hates it when
people are close to him Chloe he
clinched to save his life he knew as yo
to be honest with you quite simply if
you don't like the clinch pick a
different sport
pick a sport where you can do something
if your clinch to make some martial arts
for example by me in the Octagon
actually fight me I would love that
a boxing stand crazy hard but it's half
a fight I use half my body
there's no submissions there's no
grappling there's no throws ro if you
don't like it pick a different sport
like stop whining and do something about
it alright we go again look again just
he would do this often he would like
duck under like this and slip his head
in my cubby hole and then whine about
being in my cubby hole I don't know what
he was doing here
what was he there now that's some
illegal move that I should have I talked
about this in my video my analysis I'm a
good sport man I literally probably
could have broke his ribs right there I
should have done it I should I really
should keep because he was just laid
back right here and there was just full
torso exposed ribs my hand was up oh
nice guys finish last ladies and
gentlemen or tied you ain't [ __ ] oh
another right there another right I came
again Oh another right he's getting so
excited oh there another right did you
see it right there
another right there again another hold
on a second did you guys see that there
was another right another one if I did
more left hooks I in the van 15 inch
dick I'd be a porn star to a pathetic
old man I mean hopefully we can all
agree that round 1 and 2 Logan has won
I'm three and four I have one like let's
accept that as a fact I can get behind
that I could see I could see that okay
Logan was definitely told here he's come
back you're gonna need a prayer pressure
on so that's why Logan came in straight
off a good quick Oh God I can't wait til
I get actually good at this sport
overseeing round five though he did miss
a law for argument's sake I'm gonna say
this was Logan's well I appreciate that
that was my round right so right now
Logan is winning round 1 round 2 round 5
and I'm winning round 3 around 4 okay I
can get behind that I him with a job and
another right there and another right
there another one boom I'm throw in
there so referee says break
what I
threw him off me because he's clinching
me fam no go let's get the Octagon baby
if you want to throw me and you want to
do these like you want to fight I can do
that I can get behind that yo
oh how crazy would it be if the rematch
was in the Octagon and we did MMA I bet
you won't do it JJ oh my god it would be
fun I don't want to fight me you want to
box me you want to box me this guy is
tired let me finish him off look at this
boys sitting down look at it look at it
sitting down who said something the
folks in much drooling around I do [ __ ]
let's get one thing straight if I feel
like sitting down I'm gonna sit down
another right did you guys see it it
happened in the boxing match bonus all
right there this mother I know I don't
remember doing that he has nothing he's
just holding me for dear life that is
that is so true
I was like I'm going down you're coming
down with me I'm father by myself this
is definitely the round where I first
sure lost brain cells you watching it
back dude
I were just getting rocked but I told
you guys I have this issue I don't mind
getting hit it doesn't bother me at all
so I can get hit it was [ __ ] that
money's gonna draw out I'm the contrary
the match was a tie but your dogs
fighting style and cheap fouls and were
unaccounted for
you're lucky you're lucky they were they
were not kind of hearing the score so
low did you load them you all finished
the next I might get you
your business it's so funny hearing him
say that I know you know that's not true
bro I know you know I'm gonna be
standing over top of you you're
literally gonna be looking at my nuts
I might teabag you I honestly - oh that
muscle bleeding from the nose and
everything he's finished it's like nine
days later and you're literally still
bleeding from your eyes like your eye is
bleeding dawg look at your wrist if he
was meant to be the Challenger to take
away my belt that definitely wasn't a
champion showing dawg I've said this a
thousand times I'm not a boxer I was in
a boxer I was pretending I like force
myself to learn boxing in four months
this dude has had over a year of
experience and he looks like Shh I
promise I think I'm gonna knock him out
in the first round and the rematch I
don't see I'm literally gonna be so good
by then Wow okay
all right all right guys so that's the
video yeah like I said I'm gonna do my
analysis soon hit the subscribe button
if you're not subscribed trust me it's
just way better being subscribed to this
channel and if you haven't yet guys top
your memories local ball that concise
shop or link in description you know how
we do it we do a different baby example
if I feel like sitting down in a in the
middle of a boxing match on the ropes do
it I'm pumped
also I'm gonna I'll say this now one
other Jeju he made a comment that he
wants the rematch to happen in May of
next year into that I say no no that's
bro that's so far from now who knows I'm
gonna be doing in May I could be
shooting a movie making music who knows
I want to rematch to happen in December
of this year stop running
trust me it's better for you brother
less training that I get under my belt
the better it is for you let's just get
it done bro we got the momentum I know
the Logan wants it this year guys that's
it I freaking love you guys and I'll see
you that's good
[Music]