Amani weather is this is very good you
know I wasn't always writing domestic
abusers like a horse and buggy but today
it was a bit different it started off
like any other Tuesday
[Music]
after raging our faces off we hopped on
a 5 a.m. flight exhausted as hell to
meet this guy Pat email patty is an
experienced bail enforcement agent
otherwise known as a bounty hunter
a person who captures fugitives or
criminals for a bounty
now today my brother Jake and I were
going to become bounty hunters and we
actually captured two other criminals
earlier that day which you'll see in the
near future so make sure you subscribe
but yeah this was a last one of the day
which is why my pants are ripped so
please ignore my wiener
but first obviously we had to get
briefed almost I'm gonna give you a
little bit different direction that one
okay I want to fight the biggest do you
got that's what we're gonna teach you
sadly if our suspects here and you have
a visit you have a position of advantage
over him and you're behind them and I
look at you and I go like this that
means I want you to go hands-on with
this guy I give you the signal you it
and that's exactly what happens oh look
that was easy just let me do it well
done and that's all the training you
need no no no no no no I don't but then
I have to be dry stun just can I Drive
stun him we gotta get you certified here
[Laughter]
all right yeah it's time to go catch
some bad guys just got the brief this
will be a third apprehension of the day
broke my finger and the first one should
be okay but today this guy's name is
Freddy he looks like this he was
apparently a violent offender
and not just any kind of violence
apparently when he beat his wife that's
not cool at all Freddy
now I'm frickin mad and I'm going to
apprehend you violently and aggressively
so also they're kind of like gonna put
us in charge for this one because we've
been doing it all day and at this time
we're pros
we're not doing a Reve occasion based on
failure to appear we're doing a
relocation based on a report of domestic
assault the wife calls the bail bonds
company says my husband who she
co-signed on the bond with assaulted her
again and so we're revoking the bond
based on that as soon as we identify her
we'll make sure that she's okay
first and foremost and then we'll locate
the male and as soon as we locate the
male and identify that he has no weapons
we send you guys in for straight-up take
tat the dogs you know send it the guns
time we gotta wait for the I don't want
him here I'm a single mom I am taking
care of my kids I want nothing to do
with him okay at what point were you
gonna call and tell us that he wasn't
here because we called you not 30
minutes ago and said we're on her way I
told you guys I was like hey he him and
I are done you don't want anything to do
with them I don't want any of this drama
if he's in the house for you to tell me
right now you're putting a lot of people
in danger he's not if she's so he's in
house you're going to jail you
understand that you think she's lying on
Freddy you think he's here I think
Freddy's here
buddy come on I'm operating we know
you're here Fred Freddy are you sure you
want this smoke before we really do it
like this are you feeling froggy Freddy
[Music]
in this apprehension we're more just
like the executioner's you know yeah run
if you're upstairs thank you so now I
still think I still think she's [ __ ]
right
[Music]
how about that oh boy
I'm not seeing them in here drafts of
work address where he is right now let's
go let's go
sorry buddy here's the situation the
white free ticket right gave us a work
address
apparently this dude is still at work
we're gonna just show up at his
workplace you only went there because
she told us not 30 minutes ago yeah he's
home
come on bye
[Music]
with that
hey hey who's in charge who's in charge
where's your supervisor Patti just walks
around with his dick out who's a
supervisor who's in charge here what's
your name you know you don't say
anything don't say anything you want to
catch a felony charge for harboring a
fugitive one of your employees why does
no one want to cooperate say nope one
like that one more time I'm gonna show
that sausage so far up your ass no
here's the deal I'm going to start
pressing charges on people harboring a
fugitive cuz I have information they put
a felony fugitive here right now hands
on the back your head on that this
little girl I'm sure you're in the low
gang obviously where's Freddie you don't
know yeah where's Freddie okay what do
you do what are you doing here this is
tough this is tough
betrays you're 18 years old you're like
oh these guys look like some good guy
throw some sausages down with the bullet
just so you know you know you're
protecting a woman-beater right Patty's
not happy with anymore if I'm being
honest just having very small tolerance
for [ __ ] I have a very small penis
huh I said I have a very small penis
laughs what
with us right now yeah man why is
everyone protecting this dude this ain't
easy what about this shutter right here
he's gonna be in the shed we appreciate
your participation and cooperation you
seem like a good kid you just got the
chainsaw you could be an accountant but
now if you're trying to saw people in
half where's Freddie man just tell us
you don't know then why you come at us
with the chainsaw seems a little
aggressive don't you think hey you know
we're coming in hey guys we're cutting
the door Freddie you got about t-minus
ten seconds I heard you punched your
wife not cool no excuse me a second give
me a second through the time no it's his
first time using bolt cutters he's he's
a strong kid in pound for pound no you
got you could do it he could do it
coming in we can do it he's gonna take
him a second come on all right Freddie
looks like you're safe today Oh we'll go
with it nope never put you back to a
door Oh
never put you back to a door Patti why
don't we get the real saw Jake Jake Jake
Freddie's here yeah I think he's in the
barn
you goddamn right I do I'm creative but
it's just a little thing there you go
that was nice of you Jake you didn't
have to do that though yeah you did it
that was first top of you man it's
always destroying anything
[Applause]
how is the sausage date they go over
juicy okay
he's not in here [ __ ]
holy I see him he's a real human he's
got a shovel only come out of that side
of that side leave it there bro bro hey
what the [ __ ] are you doing bro since
when do you drink beer
I don't bro come on Freddie hands first
it could be real easy I'm riding with my
hands
this is crazy hey I'm putting you to
sleep now oh he's bleeding red he's
bleeding come on Freddie
don't resist stop resisting stop
resisting stop resisting put that right
here behind your back sir
we've got your good eye it's done Fred I
know it's done Fred
[Music]
yeah yeah oh my god yeah we like Oh
Freddie so home we bled all over me all
over me
this is disgusting Freddie why'd you do
that man hey it's all fun and games
until you're riding a domestic abuser
like a horse then it's not fun that's
just what the first spin
Freddie brought your friends make a
great sausage link yeah you know this
dude I'm not gonna lie
might be the strongest dude I've ever
felt in my life get a beer over here
point man bro Savage are you stressed
out
yes necessary completely do you think we
have a future and bail enforcement I
think you guys would be kicking ass
anytime you want on nice thank you yeah
I would have I be I'd be happy to have
you guys back as my partner anytime Oh
drinking on the job
yeah hey if you're not subscribed hit
that subscribe button I'm cooking love
you give the video a thumbs up he want
us to do more with Paddy mayo and the
team okay I'll see you next and bye
he could do it you could do it