doesn't say no diving so hey guys it's
me hello again I'm just gonna say it la
has been on lockdown for like a week and
I'm already over this I can only do so
many ping-pong ball trick shots
I can only shove a leafblower and my
friends faces and then my face so many
times I can only make so many tick-tock
before I start to lose my mind I want
you to know I'm doing my best to try to
keep you guys busy distracted from the
bush y'all know we make podcasts
impulsive and you get on time for that
we do the impulsive clips channel blogs
Instagram taking doing it all so before
we get into this video just subscribe to
those channels and then you'll never be
bored again the links for those are in
the description with that said let's go
your mouth nothing I'm sick of being
stuck in the house I decided to bring
the beach to Encino
[Applause]
Logan's luau the party I spent seventy
thousand dollars on for no [ __ ]
reason he says so what are you really
afraid of slugs
who's afraid of slugs we're gonna be
social if someone were to take this slug
and like toss it on Evan
[Music]
this is exactly what the virus want it
wants to turn us against each other
they make us hate slugs you see this guy
special guy right here what do you think
he's thinking right now oh I know
exactly what I like to watch the fish I
like to vote the pigs and swim in the
pool and chase the bar and I take naps
and if I really have to pee but the
outside is too far I will pee on the
world not just one more this world this
one in this world all the things I like
to do
[Music]
oh you are for me today their name want
me to call my ports today
look at the carpet I've ruined it
this is Mike's room no he's in here
somewhere hey hello good to see you Mike
I can't wear it no one with me right now
[Music]
hit a point of quarantine well put a
pool in my garage yesterday I've lost my
mind
give it up Mike still mad about take
care of it still there bro there's no
way well the wood yeah it's way God this
scared of oh it's a slob it's a slob