alright look gang this is something I
want to address the Lenox it's extremely
expensive
ten thousand dollars go talk to this guy
here all I talked to this guy really the
guy trying to sell it to team maverick
drives a hard bargain get the case idea
then just we gotta know we're getting
the best deal you could never make a
faster dollar and profit and the dollar
that you know again air conditioners
great we have an hour acting class no
Dan gonna be a great actor is acting not
arts and crafts have a neck and road yet
bang what's the difference between
gettin yeah what is it you good actor
thoughts bad actor Oh what's a bad actor
thought am I wasting my time
oh good to know good to know handle it
keep those bad thoughts out of your mind
but continue trying to get a new air
conditioner saying that maverick merch
just drop new woman's like here I have a
package inside we just dropped these
brand new maverick blue leggings for the
ladies they're super comfortable
they're super stretchy wait how do you
know they're comfortable do you think I
give them a test drive huh yeah they're
comfortable Spencer Oh comfortable bro I
could even use them as a comforter for
my dog ya know it's like a blanket yeah
it's kind of a big deal by the way
before we go back out there if you're
not a part of the low gang do yourself a
favor make sure to subscribe if you
haven't subscribed yet go ahead and do
so hit the subscribe button for me and
money will show up at your doorstep for
sure yeah we're gonna go ahead and leave
it in the editor okay yeah go ahead and
subscribe
make me famous yeah you're gonna be
famous bro you gotta have an Instagram
you guys can follow him on Instagram at
Logan Paul that's what you were talking
about right there accessories yes we're
saying also this free shipping this week
for $30 or more domestic orders you were
lovely friends yep squeeze my boss hard
willing to give you 5% oh you want to
compare apples to apples to sweet this
isn't the first time I've compared
apples I will say I'm very impressed
both of these apples are very good okay
we're getting sidetracked guys where's
my dog no the AC guy
she's getting some pop zooms bro what on
the pop zooms yeah yeah like that just
stop just stop it one sec one sec this
is something I've been meaning to
address in the video the other day bro
the comments about your pops so many pop
zoom comments let me read yourself does
anyone else notice that the cameraman
zooms in every two seconds I don't hate
the new camera guy but the zoom is this
cameraman drunk hey Chuck I don't think
so
okay tell your cameraman to chill out
hey Spencer chill out
perfect thanks guys Oh God Logan
Paulette does his brain have more than
three brains yes it does this one
actually is good follow-up it's funny
how much he plugs his merch
Logan poo all.com sized shot who cares
about Logan fighting care side we need
to know if a hotdog is a sandwich I'm
slowly falling into insanity guys I'm
getting sidetracked
hey adventure just gotta push the brakes
under the constant pop seems right told
me to pops it yeah I know you are first
time you could stop even when you're
holding a camera is the pop zooms are
good for vlogs genuinely but like I
think you're doing a little too much
typically on a pop zoom it's cause like
you're overcompensating for something or
something's not funny or just like spice
it up say a joke is not funny check this
out why was the cow mad at the chicken
because it was in the bed
[Music]
300 having this conversation Oh what
those oh honey no oh God look ease but
bro
looks horrible this looks like one of
those things inside a car wash one of
those things that no wonder he's
checking someone's mud and yeah Kong's
been a dirty dirty dog maybe partially
my fault
we haven't groomed in a while but I have
an idea when I bought is not going to
work for that I thought it's for you I
know bro just like his daddy
oh how you doing Carl just shaving my
dog's butt like a good dad okay I think
I did a good job pretty nice-looking boy
it's not bad right I wish my butt look
that clean what the Oh Lydia I don't
know how there's like a pile of hair
next time I think would you mind
grabbing it no it's blood hair no no
it's not know that that's in my written
someone's butt here in this room and
it's not - aw Spencer's it might be that
one look the point is I just don't want
butter on my sink also are they come on
Oh more I realize I really messed that
up
I feel like we need to take into a real
group work I think you might be right
[Music]
now go to the groomers but needs to be
waxing
[Music]
alright low gang uh this is something I
want to address you may have noticed the
vlog has been slightly off today it's a
little slow it's because this morning I
got an email that sort of set the tone
for the day for me and it's it's this is
odd because I've never been affected in
this way and the way I'm about to share
with you uh so a while back maybe a
couple months ago I did a make-a-wish
event kids who are suffering from
terminal illnesses I think six of them
chose to meet me as their their
make-a-wish so I went to Dave & Buster's
with these kids I hung out with them I
spend one-on-one time with me every
single one of them and one of the kids
Nick he was from the Netherlands all
right so this is Nick and Aaron's from
the Netherlands yeah you guys flew from
the Netherlands just to meet me yes you
good
anyways I got this email today it is
with great sadness that I have form you
one of the kids Logan met in December
recently passed away
Nick vanderlin from the Netherlands lost
his battle earlier this month
normally I would keep this private I'm
sure his family is grieving plenty but
this next sentence kind of I felt like
Nick would want this we've been told
that in his final weeks he talked about
Logan a lot and how big the impact of
his wish was on Nick stayed up every
night waiting for the new video Nick
would have wanted us to let Logan know
of his passing and how much does it wish
experience might
can you please pass along our thanks to
Logan once again for granting Nick's
wish the family would be comforted
knowing that we're making you guys aware
so I'm gonna go ahead and dedicate this
vlog to Nick bro thank you for being the
little gang for your dedication and and
in strength in your battle you're in a
better place man you're a maverick and
yeah thanks for riding with this bro I
think you said this is weird for me cuz
I read this this morning I started
tearing up because this has never
happened to me before and it's so weird
because again just there's so many signs
is such a weird day we made a bunch of
jokes that day about Nick Nick brought
us like candy from the Netherlands and a
weird I was making a joke about like the
way it sounds I forget what they're
calling Stroupe crook ins or the strap
strap Krakens or something oh they
brought the cookies they're called
Stroupe tokens this is weird sorry I
just I just looked at this video when
after the event inside of Dave &
Buster's we took all the kids to the to
my cool bus we wanted to show him what
the cool bus was like in real life
battery's been dead for like the past
month now III have no reason to go in
that bus this morning I went in just to
go see if it would start and then I saw
something which just validates it like
some crazy energy going on today
let's go i'ma show you
[Music]
oh and sitting right where Nick is
sitting is the candy that he left me I
still have it it's sitting right there
they're just you know the Stroop
cooking's mind-blowing like Nick bro
rest in peace man when the little time I
got to know you your energy was palpable
it was contagious and and I'm glad to
have a party living on
[Music]
odd but I felt like part of this vlog -
I said it before is to share my
experiences in my life with you I want
to distract you from your busy life
whatever stresses you have going on if
you've lost anyone I am here to make
your life better hopefully that said
that is the vlog this vlog is dedicated
to Nick and his family stay strong guys
and Nick the Logan is thinking about
your problem
[Music]