are you really gonna use this I think
you do oh snap okay guys this going down
hey oh good morning low gang was Bob I
just picked up the cool bus from West
Coast Customs guys cuz Sunday as you
guys know is my birthday your boy is
turning 23 want to be the doll head god
guys there's also the anniversary of the
Maverick brand wheat we are out here
every single day changing the world not
being afraid to be ourselves in fact I
encourage you to be yourself that's what
makes you special we do a different
camera app today big no we just drop
these brand new Maverick worldwide
hoodies guys these are the nicest things
we've ever dropped anyways guys yeah at
the bottom here it's the year I was born
in Roman numerals and on top it says
world wide with the Mavericks all around
the globe because as you guys know the
movement has gone global and a matching
a worldwide t-shirt to go with it
doesn't matter go sit down and have a
talk about the merchants a new legging
shacks word of right now oh my god honey
honey yet ladies don't worry we got you
covered already know where to get the
hottest merchant game logo ball my
console a shop board link in description
telling you guys not just saying this
you have to go fast we only have a
limited supply these three different
hoodies and then you guys know as well
we have $10 original t-shirts now for
Monday only guys it's selling like
hotcakes well you can't oh well you can
now guys the reason we're driving the
cool bus and the reason it's all so dark
out we have been running around the city
all day collecting supplies because for
my birthday every year it's not April
Fool's every year this is not a joke it
is literally the worst day of the year I
actually hate it because somewhere down
the line I missed the memo that everyone
just wants top squid Logan no honey not
this year I am getting the first out of
here yeah but what if I know bro please
you guys remember two years ago when
Jake did his little Lambo thing
[Music]
that was the worst day of my life so
this year we're gonna go ahead and hock
it all the way up to Yosemite National
Park we're gonna get a camping trip in
with the boys and Jack the one girl I
feel so bad she's got a penis well look
enough genetalia tom we obviously need
materials for a camping trip right the
seven of us crammed in a bus for like
three days
first things first guys we knew on a
road trip right you have to Huck it you
have to so this morning we hit up a dirt
bike an ATV store so flashback to that
oh my god this is heaven for the Ohio
Board oh yes absolutely here's the thing
I want to stay mini because yeah I've
gotten seriously stopped on dirt bikes
before in fact this this car right here
and I'm a little like emotionally
scarred so if we stay small it's safe no
they said small over the bike making a
Huck happy facts we want to hawk it so
we're just looking at some quas we want
to give me what exactly are you trying
to do okay
oh whoa there's like some things in life
that you like just need like food water
many ATVs are definitely now on that way
in that order in that order food water
mini ATVs yeah we're gonna get these on
top of the cool bus road because I
actually don't have a trailer I have an
idea we need to buy a rope I stand on
top and just Huck it all the way up it's
the only way I'm yoked bro and if you
don't think I can pull these then our
friendship is over I like you you know
what you come in ten dollars this week
only and a new hoodie drop get your
mercy sure it's getting hooked but but
y'all by the way speaking of the
merchant or mele we shoot in the day
right it's nighttime we didn't really
give you a chance to do a montage and we
just drop the hottest we ever have we I
have no we're in a store right but it's
not too late to do a montage we could
doing here
[Music]
and
don't spend it and I said
[Music]
Oh super-tight ever seen someone buy
this many blankets yeah hey you should
man yeah honestly should okay well I do
so let me we can stop making fun of
looking now have you ever seen somebody
with this many pillow oh well looks like
my uber is here so I'm gonna stop
getting roasted by going that way there
camping stuff is all in your car and we
gotta unload it put it in the bus okay
yo let's go on the trip I'll be more
than welcome to come
okay barely in wisely because the
bathroom oh that is a situation I'm a
girl
how do girls use the bathroom if they're
interested Thomas outside wait I don't
do that okay we cannot film it it's just
she doesn't take a dump or she's mad I
am taking Kong he's absolutely coming
that is the dumbest idea ever why you
don't think my pretty cake okay I'm
gonna get there and you're like oh wow I
don't actually have time to take care of
it Oh Lydia hey calm was around much
longer before you and I did it by myself
I'm 23 now I'm gonna dog he just doesn't
want Kong to spend time with me in bond
he gets so jealous look out Joe I'm not
just watching my dog like Lenny more
than me that's not cool
bring Matt Rick let's go ask him bro
what's up I know sorry to wake you
I was just wondering if you want to go
camping no what yeah yeah I mean I guess
Kong's going why does it matter
oh whoa I didn't know it was like your
dad I didn't think he was gonna take it
back or definitely not coming bro we'll
see you later
guess not nice throw Olga next time try
hugging
I can't focus on how cool our merch is
because my penis hurts so bad take it
easy on the budget I'm telling you okay
it's gonna be fun there's just a lot of
testosterone and we might need your help
with that estrogen you guys okay
me and my confident are talking about
tying you up and throwing you in the
back and bringing you anyways fine we'll
do it the legal way nope that's still
the illegal way we're gonna invite you
like cordially you like to come we'll
come back Monday
oh that's really neat
yeah you do I don't know
where am i sleeping we got a tent for
the room I'm not going if there are
bears well well do well yeah yeah yeah
for sure next to who like here look Oh
No
you could sleep next to Evan for all we
care right just to let you know the spot
next to me will be open you can't do it
with that bro evan is a sick big spoon I
would know all right what about what we
will do that activity by using our
mouths and digestive system Wow
at this point I am really dragging this
vlog out yeah yeah we should cut to the
next scene
No you'll be safe we have these
sunscreen bug lotion what lantern coffee
pot it's like Starbucks Yosemite Edition
flashlight whistle job oh wait there's
more Wow you guys are the answer to that
is none of us guys I'm really insecure
about my knees and I think they're just
really thank you might need some pants
Zach you're like a needle in a haystack
Oh guys getting dressed up we always
were slowly breaking her down dude yeah
here hold this map hey hey oh gosh joke
respond even I was like my boy knows
this song by a heart well Olga I guess
we'll see you tomorrow if you're coming
or not hug me and let's say goodbye okay
okay that's the blog these next three
days or so really so exciting man I even
wanted to go camping in the cool bus
from the day I got it but there's not
only my birthday but the one-year
anniversary is also the Maverick read
whoa we just dropped these new t-shirts
today and the new hoodie you guys saw
and ten dollar t-shirts that last
through Monday join the movement guys be
a maverick do it different don't listen
to other people talking just to [ __ ] a
snack whatever they want to say you do
you you focus on you stay true to your
heart that's how you succeed baby that's
how you hock it bro Logan Pollock on
slash shop or link in description lastly
if you're not a part of the low game
make sure to subscribe you do not want
to miss what's gonna happen on this epic
camping trip and also ring the bell next
to the subscribe button so you can be
notified when I close because apparently
if you're subscribed like that's not
always enough Oh YouTube silly goose Wow
okay that's it I'm gonna play some for
tonight low gang I love going I'll see
you tomorrow
[Music]
y'all ready no way