now seriously I've lived through this
moment right here
all right let's go welcome back looking
at gang skirt I love you guys got a big
day planned today I invited a few people
over for the Super Bowl we've been
setting up the house you leave late if
you who I'm gonna people are coming like
a hundred got a lot of people but listen
we got the game room set up we got the
drinks and alcohol we even put some
stuff in the garage for people to sit on
oh that girl is cute
hey what are you doing for the Super
Bowl wanna come to my house have a party
she had heard about our party they said
we got chef Caitie at the house ready to
make the world's biggest hamburger
because we survived sober vegan January
and we are celebrating with the lots and
lots of meat we got the jet ski sitting
outside but there's one crucial crucial
thing that I missed for hosting a Super
Bowl party I really messed up I dropped
the ball
we have like three hours you know this
is gonna be so expensive oh my god oh it
is the beginning of fatal February which
is the exact opposite silver meeting
January lots of meat alcohol you might
not make it through this month but
that's the point that's exactly so we
figured we'd start off by making V
world's biggest hamburger how many
pounds of meat is you get that's bigger
than Andre is vegan you'll be back to
the light siding leaves every day step
number one is making giant buns
I heard we started you're caressing the
dough with your sensual with it what are
you doing hook your elbow under bro oh
my god
sorry if my vegan friend Oh more meat
this is a lot of me this is actually
like one entire cow where it came from
biggest supporters remember that layer
is breaking down because of cows part
the methane hey cow if you cow reducing
the farts hobbies that help I'll tell
you exactly I know supplying the man the
last demand the last supply okay well
what about when the demand spike relates
to the lower inversion of the equators
lower spike for sure just to think I was
making
[Music]
oh that would sink it looks so good by
the way this is amazing giant flat
potato it looks like the earth people
are starting to trickle into this party
but it's a good thing we bought a TV for
this because there's no internet here
just a bunch of frozen pixelated
football players young like we must stop
dude this is a serious problem something
about it doesn't seem right we can't
watch the game frozen did nothing's
happened No
do make a giant cheeseburger on your TV
will freak oh let's go by the way I'll
have you know I'm tipsy hey we're also
making the world's biggest hamburger
today so this party was getting fun
slowly but surely but I knew if we
really wanted to get lit I had to bring
in my secret weapon
[Music]
okay fun party but also let's not forget
what we came here to do and that is
create the world's largest cheeseburger
[Music]
as much thicker than I expected this is
the leaning tower I've waited my whole
life no seriously I've lived through
this moment right here
[Music]
43 pounds we made a forty three pound
hammer
we really did it wow this is such a dumb
idea to begin with goddamn we made it
work welcome back Mike
just I'm meeting life
[Music]
yeah
wait what are you gonna do my sign-off
hey listen okay I appreciate you guys
thank you for staying with me for the
world's biggest hamburger this is heavy
I hope you guys enjoyed that video
make sure to subscribe if you're not
subscribed during the locating the
strongest family on the internet and for
all my Mavericks out there sometimes you
feel like building the world's biggest
burger you just do it don't be afraid to
be different local icon slash shop I
will see you guys next
[Music]
I feel like I've got a baby