[Music]
welcome back
to another vlog
all right listen guys how do i say this
uh today's vlog is gonna be great it's
also gonna be a little sad
as most of you guys know my best friend
my homie kong the savage was taken from
my yard by a coyote
last week and uh i i've been wanting to
do something
about it so i came up with something he
was actually taken right over there
where we planted those flowers and it's
almost like he
never even left wait a second what what
is this wait what
what is that how that is that you buddy
okay no it's not him it's not him but it
is
a pillow dedicated to conga savage oh my
god it's so cute
it's so cute bro it's so soft the tongue
his famous little tongue
it's soft it's so soft this pillow is
actually awesome so we have these
specially made guys
on loganpaul.com but here's the catch
are you trying to profit off your dog
man no not quite the opposite actually i
have something in mind
if you guys buy one of these conga
savage pillows from now until next week
we are going to be donating all the
money
to the west valley animal shelter if you
guys remember they're also the people
who helped us out when we found huck
huck the duck oh he's so cute
oh he shook his head no
[Music]
basically we're going to raise money and
awareness about coyotes in los angeles
to make sure
a the people are safe but be more
importantly our pets because i do not
want this
to happen to anyone and eventually we're
gonna build a kong to savage coyote
awareness program for the people of
encino and la residents and it all
starts with the people of
west valley and the l.a animal shelter
now before you do anything else
copperpillow loganfall.com shop kong can
be preserved forever
you can snuggle with them what are you
doing somehow got up here
oh okay now i need help yeah no
it happens land on this pillow it's
really soft i don't think that's a big
enough landing spot
but i can try
oh i got a pillow was there that's what
i'm saying bro yeah that's a quality
pillow a lot of value
all right guys so fun fact about young
doggy he loved peanut butter like most
dogs they like peanut butter but that
tongue was just
always just i figured what better way to
commemorate him
than cover myself logan paul and peanut
butter and go to several dog parks
and try not to get arrested except first
you got to get the peanut butter guys
welcome back to today's vlog
yeah we're already rolling so hold on
let me hold
we can't go anywhere in public bro
eventually i'm going to be banned from
life i thought about it what if i get
banned from the united states
oh the peanut butter section and they
tell you how to say in spanish
the big one it's a lot of big ones the
giant the giant one the giant one
gavin please you're happy bro you're
like a [ __ ] brick please got it
just a quick note there's like 40
containers right there yeah
[Music]
we're gonna make a giant peanut butter
and jelly sandwich out of me i guess i
thought it was peanut butter for the
dogs though yeah but how funny would it
be if you covered me and peanut butter
and then got like a model to get covered
in jelly
and then you stick bread on us i'm 24
years old and this is what my life
diluted to i hate myself hey welcome
back to youtube today we're covering
myself peterborough go to dog park
[Music]
are you out of your mind literally bro
dog freaking palace there are so many
dogs so many bro
it makes me miss kong i used to have a
dog myself
[Music]
stay positive those are crazy dogs
all right i wanna give my back away [ __ ]
that dog's dick is bigger than all of
ours
[Laughter]
those are some dope tigers bro there's
kind of a gatekeeper over here just has
this like outfit on and he's like
opening and closing the gate
what if he's like yo you're covered in
peanut butter you're not allowed in i'm
like no i'm not
this is my skin i have a rare skin
disease where cream of the kakawa
takeover is my body
all right should we just uh start living
you up
should we do this bro let's see how this
works
this is amazing i think we bought too
much peanut butter i never said that
you called it you were right can you
imagine what this phone call to the
police would be like excuse me 9-1-1
there's a man covered in peanut butter
running around the dog parking encino
you're not really going to do that are
you flapping it oh my god you're the
youtubey guy you're going to do it
aren't you not in it maybe not my demo
but i'll take it
oh [ __ ]
hey nothing to see here uh it sucks when
i meet like
real people that i work with he produced
the thinning like he was the producer
great like he knows me as an actor and
here i am like yo what's up welcome to
youtube
large dog area not recommended for small
dogs absolutely no food allowed
i wonder if a human peanut butter snack
counts
[Music]
hello look i'm a human snack oh my god
this dog is like i hit the jackpot so
many big dogs
i don't understand bro are you sure your
dogs are dogs you dogs like peanut
butter
man why don't dogs like peanut butter
what's happening right now
[Music]
[Laughter]
this one's licking my butt bro i don't
know how i feel about that oh my god
hello i brought you here for a reason
today dogs coyotes are running rampant
in this part of town
watch your back and check your six you
should be okay you buy this kong pillow
from loganpaul.com shop and you raise
money for coyote awareness
have you seen this dog
[Music]
get him
oh my god hello hello
hello oh [ __ ]
they're getting they're getting about
the peanut butter
[Music]
thank you lady i like you as soon
i like this dog he's different
oh watch out oh no guys if you see a
coyote
call authorities immediately or more
importantly
call logan paul dude you're freaking me
out
it's crazy over there i like you
i like you you're so cute i had a dog
like you once except he was smaller more
golden and had a lot more tongue
[Music]
oh this is good
i told
guys i've been summoned by the police
i'm not running if i go to jail
why would you dress like this i gotta
admit i'm not
proud of myself i'm not i'm not this is
it's
all right with the filming yeah we're
done our dog was killed by coyotes last
week that's okay
in encino and so we're raising money for
a um
a local what's the name of it west
valley animal west valley animal shelter
you have that uh youtube channel yeah i
guess but now i'm kind of just really
embarrassed like
you're covered in peanut butter
[Laughter]
yo when you say that out loud i now
understand the gravity of the situation
wait did someone did someone call yeah
yeah well
can i ask what the call sounded like
what do you say mel covered peanut
butter
thank you thank you guys donating
proceeds to this
shelter the peanut butter i don't really
i thought i thought that was it bro my
mug shot just like this like posted in
jail like this
i wasn't ready for that smoke wrong only
twenty-five call was just what i said
though
when the color-covered got the call do
you think they were like we gotta go
handle this
oh no the ride back to the house
all right we're gonna load you in here
you got [ __ ] everywhere i'm trying to
cover it take the sheet out yep
completely okay so remove all the sheets
okay now what's next what's next [ __ ]
genius
this is why i'm moving to the cloud
house you morons 34 year old peanut
butter backup dancer
world's number one podcast you're
[ __ ] right don't even take youtube
views into consideration mike is
having an existential crisis and we've
captured it here on film and logan paul
vlogs hit that subscribe
button all right just get in there but
don't touch anything
ah that's actually pretty good here just
stay tight stay safe all right
thanks spencer
it's hot back here bro it's hot bro i'm
a melting reese's cup i'm a peanut
butter mess
whopper bro i'm another butter in the
back seat i hate you
all right man all right i can get it
hey yo stop stop stop [ __ ] oh stop bro
oh my
yeah it gets worse too olga it's in his
ass oh it's delicious
hey mike i got lately bro and i know
you've been
feeling kind of underappreciated and you
were like screaming earlier and uh
expressing your frustration with some of
the content lately
no and no no i just i'm not done yet and
no i get it
i get it bro i i hear what you're saying
and i want to let you know
i value you and more importantly i love
you bro
a piece of [ __ ] i just wasn't fast
enough
i just lost you fast i hate myself
i love you he knew what i was doing a
second before
evan i want to tell you you can hit the
dick i don't care why what are you gonna
do what are you gonna do which way are
you gonna go ahead
oh i got nut this one you're gonna nut
that way so
i love all the team maverick here
especially you evan i don't even get
paid
like you do that rolex one guy one rolex
well i love how she says wait and takes
off her clothes
i don't want this i don't want i don't
want it
what's wrong i don't know logan i don't
have to do it myself
we can settle this easily you don't have
to do anything dumb and aggressive and
violent
we're best friends you punch me dick
i'll be very upset
[Music]
this is this is the first layer oh you
want me to get on top of you yeah
lay the same way as me though like her
head should be herself
so bad shut up and mount me
[Music]
i kind of want to call the cops on
myself excuse me 9-1-1 i'm disgusting
please help hop on you
[Music]
[Laughter]
bro
how do we look bro well you guys look
like a full-fledged sandwich
someone's got to eat us you know that no
who do we know that can eat anything bro
i know i know someone yeah i got
something in mine too
[Applause]
you can eat me anytime pearl hi little
gang that is the vlog thank you guys for
watching
if you are not subscribed make sure to
subscribe join the low gang the
strongest family on the internet
and also head on over to loganpaw.com as
you guys know we're selling these kong
the savage memorial pillows all profits
go to the west valley animal shelter and
we're gonna raise money for a coyote
awareness program
rest in peace kong i still love you i
miss you buddy logan paul.com i think i
already said that well i don't know i'm
covered in peanut butter and we're going
to san francisco so hit that subscribe
button that eventually's going to be fun
little gang i love you guys and i'll see
you tomorrow take it easy
come on danny there we go