wow what a fight man what a fight what a
night I still have a black eye from the
fight I don't even know where to start
this video I guess I'll start with this
after my first ever amateur boxing match
your boy is undefeated I also have zero
wins that's right oh oh and one oh and
water what is that a draw was a draw oh
my gosh ah I hate that so much I hate it
so much when they raised our hands you
can see by my face my mouth dropped I'm
I was absolutely stunned ksi has the
exact same reaction on the other side
it's weird because you don't know
whether to celebrate or be disappointed
like you didn't win but you didn't lose
and after talking to you guys in public
at the airport's the general consensus
seems to be if you wanted ksi to win you
think he won and if you wanted me to win
you think I want it's it's split I
personally think I won and I'm gonna be
doing a fool round by round analysis in
the upcoming weeks so guys if you're not
a part of the Lowe game make sure to
subscribe there's gonna be a ton of
content around the fight you don't wanna
miss it so yeah hit the subscribe button
turn on the notifications DiBella
whatever and let's just dive into this
video so I guess first off I want to
start by saying this thank you to the
fans y'all you guys are looking amazing
to everyone who came to the Manchester
Arena it supported me and Jake to
everyone who watched online legally have
you watched illegally you this whole
thing was a demonstration about how
powerful we as an internet culture as
like a young people culture can be and
it worked it worked
immensely we did it that's why it was
the biggest internet event in history so
yeah thank you guys whether you love me
or you hate me or you just in-between me
we're all human beings floating on a
rock in the middle of an infinite
universe and we were all part of this
amazing collective effort so you guys
are number one to thank I love you thank
you and for all my Mavericks out there
yo team maverick King showed up me
included wearing this brand now has a
totally additional new amazing meaning
to it I wanted to demonstrate what it
was like to fight like a champion keep
pushing forward no matter what like
this whole thing was a crazy long
journey I went through so many personal
changes public changes one point you
guys know had the whole entire world
against me but I vowed that I would
never ever ever give up so thank you
guys for supporting me everyone who
wears this brand every single day it's
the Mavericks baby the one who go right
when they go left the ones who think
outside the box the ones who refuse to
take no for an answer
warms my freaking heart also that hurts
if you guys can't tell I'm sick had a
little rest and relaxation period in
Paris with my girlfriend Chloe Benny
who's right there say hi Chloe you're
kind of Lois to put a hand up or
something
there she is okay yeah I've had a lot of
crepe a lot of sugar so just sick as a
dog
so yeah guys we're celebrating a little
bit this weekend maverick hoodies are
25% off all maverick hoodies and female
Maverick merch is 50% off you already
know where to get it I don't even need
to say it but I'm going to Logan Paul
calm slash shop or a link in description
now finally I'm going to dive into this
video let's talk about something I would
like to skiing address some people are
saying the fight was raped or that it
was staged or that it was faked from the
bottom of my heart literally suck my ass
JJ and I put our hearts on the line
everything we had we were warriors out
there beating the [ __ ] out of each other
we all worked so hard so and for anyone
to say that was fake also another thing
in addition to that last one Oh God made
new you the doll about the fight so Rick
I've read articles that have said ksi
and I have walked away with 30 to 40
million dollars each I cannot stress how
false that is and how each one of the
fighters involved was absolutely not
doing it for the money
let me explain I might make an entire
video on this if my team lets me but
between all the expenses on god I am NOT
just saying this for the internet I am
not a hundred percent sure I came out
positive
on this event that means I'm not sure if
I made money on the event think about it
there is no this isn't like an official
boxing league the pay-per-view unlike
boxing pay-per-view events and UFC
pay-per-view events was not $100 right
it was $10 there was no official major
big sponsor there's no Al Heyman checks
coming in this is a couple youtubers
doing this four year entertainment who
are yes trying to make money I think we
severely miscalculated the expenses
examples including 30% of the revenue
goes to YouTube right away then I split
the remainder with team ksi then I split
that with Jake accordingly then out of
that another 30% goes to my managers
lawyers agents everyone involved from my
team we paid for venues our full-time
boxing coach we flew like 30 to 40
people out to Manchester and provided
them with lodging for like two weeks I
could go on and on and on and like I
said I might make a full entire video
about this in the future if you guys
want to see it so yeah again subscribe
and let me know in the comments below
but okay as far as the fight goes let's
talk about the fight oh oh man my first
ever amateur boxing fight with really
only four months of training under my
belt good I want to say I was pretending
to be a boxer cause like I had the
fundamentals down but people you know
they worked their whole lives to be good
at this one thing good to be good at
this sport and I was going in there
right as a youtuber first not a fighter
or not a boxer and no one told me how
different it is from sparring in a gym
to competing inside a ring in an actual
fight with 20,000 people watching and
millions on the internet night and ski
day and I am pretty sure that's why I
gassed out in the later round but I will
say after leaving the ring that night I
finally now feel like a fighter I
finally feel comfortable saying I am a
boxer and the sport is so fun dude like
just two dudes seeing the shot of each
other it's a beautiful thing that
experience is valuable but I did walk
out of the ring that night finally
feeling like a boxer and if if I got
that good after only four months of
training I cannot imagine how good I'm
gonna be by the time I fight ksi
or whoever I fight next now with that
said I thought I won the fight I thought
I won 4-2 I thought I won rounds 1 2 3 &
5 ksi hands down took the fourth round
and obviously the 6th round where he'd
just he [ __ ] me up back in a line that
was me just trying to stay alive I was
completely out of gas and I was a little
disappointed that his cheap shots his
throwdowns his fouls like you guys
remember when he hit me after the bell
dog thing to do man like that was just
shady fighting ksi is like fighting a
dog dude became animalistic not a boxer
after the first two rounds something his
coach must have said stuck in his mind
because he turned it on but he was just
throwing haymakers from down here none
of them were like legit boxing punches
and you guys can imagine when I spar I'm
sparring professionals not dudes who are
head down just swinging for the fences
so again first boxing match on my part
great you can get away with the sloppy
bulls but for the second match I promise
not a single one of those is going to
land so yeah I think he was able to get
away with the cheap shots because we
were in his country his hometown not
gonna be the same when he comes to
United States in fact I'm not going to
leave it to the judges I just simply
won't and now that I know what I'm
missing
and I know what I'm good at the
improvement is only gonna be there I
think you can sort of see can't sighs
demeanor after the fight and during the
fight there's like a underlayer of
disappointment I think it's because he
knows he missed his chance like that was
it you had a chance to beat me and you
almost did if there were more rounds you
might have beaten me I'm not sure you
might have beaten me cuz I was
completely out of gas but there wasn't
and it's over now like I'm only gonna
get exponentially better but regardless
again it was a phenomenal fight ksi mega
kudos to you dude you have the heart of
a skiing warrior and I told you that
after the fight both you and I know that
six round a bro you took me for a ride
that round my goal was to just stay
alive which I did my issue at not issue
but when I get hit and case I was
hitting me a lot that round with
lot of big strong fast powerful punches
this happens in sparring - I don't
register it I don't mind getting hit in
fact I like it unless you knock me out
like I am NOT falling to the ground
which is good but at the same time
there'd be times in sparring where my
coach is like yo what the [ __ ] you doing
like we we have to stop because I'll be
so tired my hands will be down and I'm
only using my face as as a weapon and
it's not a weapon literally I'm just
getting hit in the face repeatedly I'm
sure I'll suffer brain damage later in
my life for for doing these things
that's part of it I guess but I gotta
say I think the warrior blood runs in
chaos eyes family cuz Deji tangi you
impressed me bro you impressed everyone
I don't think a single person thought
you were gonna last five rounds bro good
job to you
hats off I think you proved a lot of
people wrong that night including myself
but of course brother Jake came out with
the victory I love Jake it was so nice
to see all of his hard work these past
couple months pay off and Jake man it
must be nice having a belt like that and
having an official win you [ __ ]
I'm just kidding kinda anyway the best
part about this event hands down was
afterwards the sportsmanship the fact
that we four dudes are able to get in
this little square and beat this of each
other and then shake hands and look each
other in the eye afterwards that was
invaluable
those were the special moments those are
the moments that I'll never forget
cuz as much as I like fighting it's the
last resort always why would I ever want
to do that I'm all about spreading love
and positivity and happiness and the
fact that we were all able to squash the
beef one night right them right there
was incredible and then for me obviously
this year has been obviously you guys
know like what it's been after the fight
Jordy asked me a question and I was able
to answer it in a way that I felt
encompassed and represented what this
fight was about for me
[Music]
that was definitely the most important
part of the fight for me just just so
many emotions and yeah crazy crap I
don't even know this is it's a crazy
life man 23 years old youtubing acting
singing writing producing rapping boxing
vlogger chat boy who knows what the list
will go on to say but overall um I don't
want to say I feel cheated or
disappointed I think the word is
slighted I feel slighted but that tells
me that I have to work that much harder
the taste of not winning is absolutely
disgusting I promise the next time I set
foot in that ring I will be so scary
good I will be an actual boxer and I'm
not going to leave it up to the judges
I'm talking knockouts and in my country
with my fans the low gang the Mavs
are me no jet lag great health I am
pumped with that said guys I hope you
enjoyed the video if you are not a part
of the low gang make sure to subscribe
also all maverick hoodies are 25% off
through the weekend join team maverick
you guys know it's a hottest softest
merch in the game and ladies March is
50% off Logan Paul calm /op or link in
description I freaking love you guys
thank you for watching thank you for
making my life exactly what it is and I
will see you next time take it easy bad
[Music]