yo what are you doing this does not look
good what are you doing doesn't seem
like nothing
Logan bro Logan stop stop bro we all
miss Kong you missed Kong - yes we all
missed some more than me this is not
gonna make it any better though this dog
rheya is so timid and I don't know why I
wish you would just like love me all up
because as you guys know I don't have a
dog anymore rest in peace Kong hey I'm
your friend it's me uncle okay no please
don't run away from me all need love is
it's not like that bro okay maybe it is
like this I'm sorry dude I don't know
what to tell ya I know it said I've
missed him too buddy
I really do every night my can attest to
this I go to my room I go to bed and
every night I go come on Kong and he
never comes
[Music]
I don't know if this is like some it
just doesn't feel like him oh my god
he needs more he needs a tongue there we
go it's Kong man I can't believe it it's
like you never left
man I got good news I got good news for
you finally got dobrik for the podcast
nope and we're still not on Google
preferred oh I all get these donut holes
closed finally one of you know you guys
are joking someone in this house today
is getting a car this morning it's got a
lot of issues so I really hope it's me I
know really oh who do you think the best
roommate in the house is best roommate
gets a car did a roommate or is it
someone at that it's a roommate I've
been on this team for four years I still
have no car and can't afford it I know
bro I was gonna say I went to hook up
with a girl the other day she said
because of something on my body she can
never hook up with me again it was cool
yeah it's because I know a girl you're
talking about she says she wouldn't
because of my tattoo thank you boy oh
[Applause]
yeah we're in the right spot and it
looks about right
yeah I think my dick just grew oh who
would have inches now I told automatic
door
why don't we get one of these jet skis
so just a sea of jet ski dude this is
the manly oh my god a lot of while I
want to buy a car for my friend his
birthday's coming up I think I know
which one he'd like I want to buy one
for him the slingshot oh yeah this is
sick he's gonna love the print yeah you
guys you guys know oh is that kids that
good a lot of people would say the same
thing why do we not have that how much
for the whole tell me I don't need this
in my heart like look at these these
pecs but they said triple e here this is
the thing usually advise you on making
good decisions this is an excellent
decision
oh we done something right
didn't have a car and the exact same
color scheme I think so did I already
pay for this I like it yeah but it
doesn't matter where I think I think
he's gonna love it
this thing is nasty real question are
you a fan are you a fan I know of you so
you're not a fan
oh yeah this car for my roommate for his
birthday what you think you know that's
not the roommate okay when I was driving
around in Hawaii in this thing I was
having so much fun and I know this kid
and I know him very well I feel like he
had one more his own use I don't know I
just feel like he's really gonna
appreciate it you guys have a really
crappy one the guy really sucks oh this
is too nice he's that bad he's just a
[ __ ] this guy told you not to look
at my car right right it was from art
it's a gift the muffler in the middle of
the ass cheeks right mmm hit with that
one - that one - and scoop it's me dig
Paul bro
but beyond flat no stop no keep going
okay stop Sabra keep going I mean your
eyes I mean at this point just do it a
[Music]
few different types of straw drink the
first is the host slurp it's that second
is I drink with a straw I'm not overly
using the straw
I just nd half the cup with that one
slurp
what's going down most different yeah
he's gonna love this yeah is happening
new keys
[Music]
yo I am so pumped right now he has
wanted something like this for so long
and he deserves he's a bit of a
douchebag kinda cocky to make some bad
decisions sometimes but he's a good kid
he's got a warm heart no no I'm just
excited to see how he reacts to this
puppy and Mike's bringing out Go Go hey
man um okay I got you a little something
I know it's your birthday and it's not
my birthday bro okay how was like 20
days ago yeah tomato tomahto anyways man
you've worked really hard for this right
you're 24 years old now so uh yeah I
think it's time to give it to you Mike
can you remove your hands yeah you know
you're lying
no oh my god that's right yo listen no
no look what you gave you your lie tell
me is this a prank yeah it's not a prank
bro
it's real life and I want you to enjoy
it it's wrapping fries I'm gonna go this
place y'all All Right see you later self
I love myself this is amazing what the
flaw I still need to like act like I
didn't buy for myself no no no we bought
this slingshot
this is the new whip I think we came up
with the name for it I think I'm gonna
call it the skunk cuz it looks like the
skunk it has those two white lines down
the middle
Oh Frankie bro damn I think there's only
thing what did ya I wouldn't take it for
a spin bow I hate you not really no
listen bro I mean it I hate you bro I
hate you both please just cut to the
montage
mrs. Munt attentive to do 10 of the dad
there are their drums buh-buh-buh
drums ah yeah montage yeah okay listen
we're back home this thing is so much
fun skunk
welcome to the family wow that's it look
egg thank you guys for watching the vlog
happy belated to myself I bought this
actually you couldn't tell like at the
beginning of the month I don't know why
I'm just shooting this vlog now but even
out part of the low gang make sure to
subscribe and if you go and look up all
that house slash shop pick up any piece
of merch we give one to a kid in need
for every time you get one might get it
back this year a guy that said I hope
you guys have a wonderful day don't
forget be a maverick do it different
I'll see you guys next time take it easy
[Music]
to the ball everybody know that I'm
positive
[Applause]
wait a sec you know what I just realized
how dope we are no this is gonna make it
in the fly but we're just shooting the
beginning of yesterday's vlog that we
filmed about the [ __ ] slingshot I
thought something was actually
[Laughter]
[Music]