I'm going to go with solar lady with
stroller Oh lady with God I have been
hearing one sentence in LA this week and
it goes a little something like this are
you going I was invited last yeah
because this height restriction 88 the
next two weeks when Coachella is
happening the level of basicness as you
know guys Rises exponentially except
mostly by the basic gas concept I want
to make a song about Coachella and every
year all the LA girls can play for their
friends hey guys maybe a little
something like that hey leave him be
what you guys but you got something to
present to us yeah well I can see my
presentation doesn't see they want to
take it seriously no I want you I'm down
can you show me again Danny's prepared
something for us I think it's a big deal
I figured out how to get vengeance on
corn bandits on Kong he's dead so as you
guys know this is calm yeah
Kong is dead it was killed by a coyote
coyote vs. calm is what fair that's so
true unfair what else declared is like
they like that's the rat from kim
possible no yes yes stop interrupting my
presence
so the plan is Mike Logan we round up
five rats in a white box you put the
black box in the front yard
okay and the cave smell this occur like
in hides in the bushes we man the
security camera we tell them in the haze
approaching load comes out shoots the
cable takes a photo with the dead body
posts it
take a photo partial the internet let
them know hey you can't just come and
Nick my dog and there won't be vengeance
we can throw Australians as much as we
want but we have something serious
coming up Alex Jones unimportant that
still happens today yeah and I have one
question that I really just want to ask
him I want to park here it's just a
little tight we're like on top of a
Lambo it's that McBroom some people park
like [ __ ] yeah no you got it
the doors go up right you know why I'm
doing this right cuz that was your car's
mic it was my Lambo I love Austin don't
be wrong but Jake was that not my
vehicle that is literally your
Lamborghini from the factory you gotta
just go straight yeah you got it now you
got it you got it you got it are you
going to hotel yeah artists I have gas
carry of car Bell
what [ __ ] happy year last night it was
so windy and my tree just fell apart
this is so heavy
last night made a video midnight it's
12:05 a.m. and the wind outside is
blowing chefs weird feeling I feel like
someone's gotta come down to my tumblr
this Junction was a minute I was right I
mean brothers like a stick though
Spencer it doesn't just start here next
thing you know the whole tree is falling
I wonder if they're gonna catch on yo
did you take a peek out well the wig is
blue
yeah yeah come back and hit you hit me
no you take a peek outside when the wind
was blowing no I was it crazy doing
exactly ice is really only one possible
thing we can do
I see why I fell off the tree now not
much structural integrity in my nose you
want to be more like me oh my god I'm
gonna get you right quick crack it back
in your septum is obviously dislocated
I'm gonna go slow and if it if it does
like an excessive amount of pain to stop
me nothing happened it's still
completely crooked I have an i panic
this is bad guys this is how am i
smiling why'd you play this guitar for
me bro the shadow just doesn't look I
think I think we could stop now I'll be
honest with you today this week has been
absolutely crazy we have Alex Jones on
our podcast yesterday its Biden groping
Biden it's a joke it's not a joke sorry
no that's good by the way I've stayed
off Twitter bro because mind you if you
stay off Twitter you can't get hated on
it's not gonna empty if you never get
tested so for the haters how you doing I
still love you guys like it subscribe
get your merch but we just got off
another podcast with the call her daddy
girls yes every guy has had that moment
where you're like I Loki him down about
sex cuz she's gonna be so sweet on my
over I'm gonna be like getting it and
then she also knows she has to leave I
literally laid facedown in a pile of
sand for 10 minutes my brains about to
finish floor
I don't even know if I want to make this
a part of the blog I just wanna say like
I finally feel like I've got a little
footing in the podcast space I feel good
here brah guys haven't checked out the
episodes on impulse to make sure to do
so this may be the first time ever where
I feel like three times as we've said
the world's number one podcast we
[Applause]
anyways all this good stuff that's
happening there's only honestly only one
true thing that matters and that is for
all the dudes and girls who every year
ask those same questions to the same
purple this one's for you
DJ run it back
[Music]
cars I got my ticket janitor what am i a
[ __ ] time
you have a plus-one
yeah
I just have one question for you at-bats
listen closely i guard you gotcha
[Music]
ha
of course I have artists I'm a
[Music]
a bike bike bike