hey good morning little gang what is
poppin okay guys the title of the video
it's not clickbait this time is for real
man I sort of feel bad cuz I mean I do
feel bad obviously Kong can never be
replaced and that's the title of the
video but I've been sort of I don't see
like depressed but like lonely and down
try without Kong like I lost a homie
it's true homie and I've said it in the
video I don't want to be one of those
people that just like replaces a dog
with another dog but first guy I guess I
am oh yeah we got a new member of team
maverick he's so cute I couldn't not and
the way it all came about is incredibly
spontaneous and weird and you know like
that's what I that's me that's what I
like to do oh [ __ ] dude anyways guys do
not forget it be a frickin be chop your
besmirch shot mr. beast calm got some of
the brightest merch in the game mom I
got the hoodies t-shirt the t-shirts
dandelion yellow the hoodies butter
yellow and the hats or mustard yellow I
would we make them all the same color
that doesn't make any sense so we made
them all three different shades of
yellow gotta get it so I can keep giving
away money anyway let me flash back to
yesterday when we introduced a new
member of the family to team maverick
yeah hell is your problem right now like
all the time hey by the way we love you
Logan
awesome all the times a lot of creators
say it's just like harder your best not
to do ours you know get the cage I'm
gonna f this man off what are you gonna
do Spencer present yourself in front of
them say hello to this for how many more
fans are gonna watch this exact video we
just all say goodbye to him yeah yeah be
careful
people that follow you on our team and
we didn't want to step on any toes or
anything we understand it's a hard time
since she just had a pub gone and so I
just want to see if you wanna check him
out he's at home he's a rescue it's like
a super dope dog I'm sorry you you're
saying you brought me a dog yeah so we
brought you a dog or a dog to my house
brought a dog here huh so you think this
dog can replace Kong he's exotic super
crazy-looking so much energy
oh by the way let me through three times
I already don't like him he's not calm I
know it's not how many times a week
getting delivered a puppy
oh my oh my oh my what you think oh my
god oh this isn't a wolfdog what kind of
dog is it no he's a husky but he's an
exotic cousin how long is your tongue
always stay in his mouth it never just
hangs out well he's just chilling but on
the drive up here we like that we like
that cuz with my lad I thought a tongue
probably look at his nose bro
they look like it looks like air pops oh
my god oh no we have a real problem
Oh yo trying to bring us his dog to make
us feel like it was grow we kind of made
out a little bit and it just seems like
fate - how he just showed up here like
in a Maserati with a guy that
[Laughter]
oh my gosh oh my god that was close
let's see what he does next to Kong's
gravesite let's see how dope you really
are gorgeous this doesn't even look like
a dog he's like more grass anymore grows
you hold this dog for a second I can I
do a little rendezvous with my team yeah
you guys want to talk inside real quick
what do you think and also so fast I
feel uncomfortable potentially too quick
so we've got a lot of opposing
viewpoints no like we got to get this
dog you know say we can't get this dog
[Music]
he looks great on camera it's like he's
a Content dog I'm not gonna lie but I
don't want to get a dog for content I
didn't get Kong for content I got clone
cuz I loved having your dog yeah issue
lonely now he's very lonely I would say
yeah is she looking for a younger
brother yeah she gets along great with
boy dog that's a pro this is a husky
outside that looks like a lion they are
taken from the team
although you already look like a new
biggest thing is that this is a rescue
dog so maybe we like hump the brakes get
it checked out George
rescue George I'm with Logan and the
rest of the team we've got a dog outside
you give us one about the dog that's
outside I'm having a real internal
struggle right now yeah I said this in
the podcast I don't want to be one of
the guys that like their dog dies and
you just replace him in a second but
I've been feeling lonely I'm not gonna
lie I feel like I lost at homee and I
said like Mike kinda sucks having he's
alright but I need like a you know one
of my boys I need a homie who's gonna
have my back and I think like we kind of
got the same color eyes those are a
little lighter he's better-looking oh
hey we should we just had the logo help
us decide to because the song was a dog
of the people and and this unnamed dog
would also be a dog about the dog of the
people do you remember what Kong kept
doing we gave him the keyboard he kept
doing the same number Kong had a
favorite number two hundred and eighty
thousand seven hundred forty seven
hundred eighty-seven this log it's two
hundred eighty thousand seven hundred
forty seven likes which by the way was
Kong's favorite number he wants to be
bought two hundred eighty thousand seven
hundred forty seven like low gang you
decide oh my god
does this
[Music]
okay listen man
random guy Ricky you showed up at my
house I want the dog sure man he's yours
oh my god
you're gonna do great things in this
world I know it you speak up oh whoa I
don't think he's trying to kiss him I
know you say oh actually one thing me
and mavin agree you can't just like
replace his brother like Kong and
maverick we're brothers funny just
didn't see him like that see more like
they hate each other if I hated each
other I feel like maverick hates
everything
never do that again
oh no you stop sucking your own dick
dude it's been at least five he's young
he's even bored of himself oh I guess so
this dog he's so cute ah oh my gosh
she's chewing on my finger it's weird
like having to raise a dog from like
puppy age again I haven't done this in
so long the last time obviously what's
up since con I'm positive he is gonna
into bed and pee everywhere but you know
what that's a risk I'm willing to take
if I can cuddle with my new puppy oh
this is kind of crazy I feel like he
smells we're calling used to pee or he's
peeing right now oh god i extremely
miscalculated that whole thing what's he
doing advise why are you doing this bad
dog does he even know yeah come on put
your back into it
no you can't get up there you go get
those back legs up yeah you got it yeah
you need to be careful you're right on
the edge oh no oh my god he doesn't
understand physics this is horrible he
is gonna be trouble I can tell Hey it's
past your bedtime dog
be honest I went to see Avengers today
you got to stay up late it's 1:30 a.m.
you gotta get your [ __ ] together dog I
have early morning oh I'm a dad all over
again
Chase is pissed okay
I may have made a mistake I I don't know
if he's ready to sleep with me being
honest this is a complete total [ __ ]
disaster okay I think I found a solution
and I placed the dog in a cage next to
my bed this seems promising I feel like
this is a good idea if it's not please
tell me in the comment section with that
said I'm gonna take my snow leopard and
try to go to sleep I'll see you guys in
morning aah
[Music]
now if you look closely you'll see a
snow leopard in his natural habitat and
Encino California
yo this dog is being awesome we took him
to the vet a little bit ago and the vets
like y'all I've never seen any husky
like this ever a real maverick dog stop
eating grass please welcome to the
family young gagging you're gonna do
great things guys thank you for watching
this vlog I meant down below what you
think we should name them cuz we still
haven't quite figured it out yet
and if you're not subscribed you know
the drill hit that subscribe button
that's not least cough your merch shop
mr. beast comm you know how it is we got
Donuts spelling beasts but they're
different than regular Donuts they're
melting the melting donor so so a snow
cave Lincoln by oh and you suck you're
plugging other people's merch I mean
there's not other people's does my merch
how did I hear Logan Paul back home so
this is my merch ok I'm going out my new
puppy logo I'll freaking love you guys
and we will see you next time take it
easy family
[Music]