hi three do what dumb little bird
maverick the parrot he's gone you know
how much I hate these dramatic sit-down
videos I hate watching them I hate
making them even more you know first it
was Kong not was maverick in the same
way actually maverick was murdered he
was eaten you'll hear about what
happened and find out in the in the
remainder of the video but life has been
a [ __ ] lately to me it's this has been
one of the probably just weeks of my
life
and I've just been trying to stay
focused on the positive because there
are a lot of positive but obviously and
you guys see the positive but obviously
there's still a side to me that I I I
keep in my personal life and as you guys
know I was in Sweden for the past like
two two and a half weeks or so I got a
call from my roommates and my friends
back here in the United States and I
just started filming me and mind you I'm
just enjoying Sweden the meatballs the
energy the the people or so beautiful
inside and now I'm having the best time
in my life and I get this call and Andre
like I said starts filming and he
doesn't do that often so I knew
something was up and
yeah the rest of the rest I guess just
watch for yourself but this is this is
uh it's another curveball it's another
curveball in life I love this little
bird so much he's been my best friend
for the past six seven years and it
sucks I had to happen like this you know
so yeah here it is
[Music]
what up Oh what's going on
why is Andre filming me [ __ ] all my
heart's beating what do you say what bro
I'm losing my breath bro what's going on
I don't think I can get much worse than
it is not that I know
the bird the bird what do you mean the
dog ate a bird
- me what what's what's graphic
where's maverick yeah
yeah this is a joke right
no I decision are you with me right no
no you definitely are because I remember
before we left you told me that you're
gonna practice saying this you told me
this you said you said this those are
feathers that's oh don't bro that's soup
[Music]
god damn it bro oh my god Oh
well why does this keep happening what
the dude
[Music]
oh so you're telling me you're telling
me that my Tibetan Mastiff ginger killed
maverick the parry
[Music]
what the
first call first calling it now maverick
the iconic maverick ferret the
inspiration behind the maverick brand
maverick by Logan Paul all started
because just one little in Sun Conure
parrot the pet the pet that I've had for
the longest time in my life seven years
at maverick parrot on Instagram 1.3
million followers 2.3 on the brand
account dead the bird I've had since 18
since I was a senior high school before
I started internet you're saying that
bird is gone and killed by my other pet
ginger you're supposed to kill coyotes
she's supposed to kill coyotes not my
pets
[Music]
well what them why do all my animals get
murdered when I'm gone literally get get
murdered an aggressive murder and their
bodies just disappear bro oh yeah I
gotta go talk to you later
this can't get any worse
[Music]
bro the og hoodie I happen to wear today
what doubtful what nothing
oh no this is horrible this is
[Music]
well I don't know what to make of this
yeah I'm not I'm not going definite all
that mine goes into this weird spiral of
confusion and then I can I feel myself
wanting to like make a joke and deflect
with comedy which is my defense
mechanism and it just it's so it's
unhealthy it's weird
ha I don't know dude feels like death
has been like a teacher over the past
year of yours just like trying to say
something over death is trying to teach
me a lesson
bro I swear to God I don't know what
lesson I mean you know in a roundabout
way it definitely matured me put the
whole Japan thing like I think it's
pretty obvious that I'm not the person I
was to two and a half years ago but it
just sucks that it has to come through
death I think I'm such like an extreme
person that thought that the only way I
I learn lessons and make big monumental
moves in my life is through big
monumental events which inform
unfortunately has been through the
passing of X Y Z
this thing with maverick is weird it
literally feels like a like a piece of
my life has died which is why I said it
might be symbolic
[Music]
you found maverick like this Oh Oh why'd
you show me that you sick oh my god
I'm sort of glad we didn't find Kong now
oh my god what he's saying listen he
just oh my God look you won't believe I
got god dammit and she's like go figure
he's got a figurine of a Paris what time
is it about now 11 p.m. it's only Street
a store on the street that's sleeping
only store that's open to the whole
street in Sweden in a dark alleyway we
walked by every walk by the story I was
like what you guys find stupid this is
where you get the magical adventure
[Music]
look at the bird oh it died was it sick
or he got an accident he's sort of he
got eaten by my dog my Mastiff consumed
my bird for no words
[Music]
dad hey man good to see you yeah your
bag oh [ __ ] they removed the sand man
moves have been made so much has changed
bro the sand is gone and so is the bird
well how am I gonna like I'm actually
really excited to see ginger like really
excited I really missed her but she also
killed the most beloved animal of my
life how am I supposed to greet her it's
not gonna remember if I discipline her
so do I just act like nothing happened
that's tough you know yeah I can't be
mad
[Music]
oh hi baby I see you mr. promised bra
have you have to go upstairs and see the
empty cage does everyone here know about
maverick yeah which one you discovered
it like somebody made a maverick
smoothie in your room like ice cream
[Music]
okay I can't do anything right
oh no no look he looks more like
maverick now so we saved some feathers
of maverick we're gonna go around and
give them to you but we're gonna share
story our favorite memory of I was gonna
say those are his actual feathers it's
pretty [ __ ] up you know but I what
ginger did with the other feathers is
pretty it's a little more I the first
time I met you at 600 fine maverick me
thanks for sharing we go across the
country maverick so mean you and
maverick drove across the country to
move to Los Angeles good to speak to the
hotel Oh Mike carrion under a blanket
and like oh that one hits me maverick
was when he was a meth dealer oh that's
right yeah we started the vlogs make
sense
I used to drink wine together you would
sit on my shoulder and drink wine did
you get [ __ ] up
no I only gave a couple tips he liked it
my red wouldn't let me go to sleep
that's why I fell asleep in Sweden the
first photo you and I actually ever took
maverick was perched on your shoulder
just real quick you know I have a lot of
memories in there a lot of memories I'm
starting to know where to stop the one
that sticks out specifically you know I
didn't post it on social media I
remember I was getting hammered 4:00
a.m. one morning after a club plastered
and I tried to make myself throw up
I remember maverick was on my shoulder
the whole time while I was trying to gag
myself my boy had my back and that's
when I knew he was my homie for life
roll the clip
[Music]
it's disgusting if the clip is
discussing Ron like I was alone in my
apartment just like oh and Matt was like
you you got that you Matt was like get
him oh come on no hangover tomorrow you
know he he was more than a birdie at
personality that was definitely a moment
that sticks out in my mind
amongst the thousand others that I'll
show you guys right now
[Music]
oh hey ma'am good morning hey buddy I
want you today that's what's going okay
how you do
going on a date tonight do I take her
somewhere fancy romantic but whoo-hoo
both and you shut the door your feet
such a blackberry
[Music]
[Applause]
you cannot hallmark race from me
you cannot take my family
[Music]