oh
[Music]
we come a long way from ohio bro it all
started with an idea that manifested
into merchandise that's now clothing and
to see it all on a rack
although only the first couple
iterations this is one of the coolest
things in the world
and not only that this shit's high
quality these are one of the items of
clothing you wear
and you only wear this i haven't taken
this off in days i should probably watch
it soon it's fashion forward it's
comfortable
it's sexy and if you have a torso this
could be for you
your torso you can find yourself wearing
this
i'm not so good at this i'm proud to say
that
it's it was first an idea in my head and
now it's come to life and actually i've
been on the line all day working hard
preparing it for you guys you know from
screen printing to drying to folding
really making sure these clothes are
made with love
and we are doing a couple of bonuses as
well put it some polaroids of me in some
of the packaging here not that you'd
want it but it is packaged by yours
truly get it out of here
it's my first ever maverick we just got
it from the factory
all right so if you guys saw my last
vlog you know i've been dying to get the
[ __ ] out of los angeles i've been stuck
in this multi-million dollar mansion for
too long i actually think i found the
place
unfortunately i can't say where it is
yet because what happened in yosemite
this is where it gets tricky because i
want to leave today and there's only one
person i know that has an rv look i know
i [ __ ] up your rolls royce when you
gave it to me
i know when you let me drive your can-am
i flipped it going four miles an hour
but i was wondering uh can i borrow that
i won't you know i don't think listen we
got this on camera
you can take it anything that happens
from this point forward he's stolen i
don't know what happened
yes yes when this thing opens up it is
[ __ ] paradise turn the generator on
wash it and then you're done it'll go
back to green
clips right on there and you can walk
right up and plug them into here push
arm out
entry step keep it on yo it starts motor
needs to be on when these go
up or down everything's very similar
simple
it doesn't seem too complicated
oh my god this is a big [ __ ] i know
what i'm doing no
that's a lie this thing is [ __ ] huge
real slow watch the god amazon prime
thank you for your service
are you [ __ ] kidding me i just
decided i actually don't want to drive
this five hours to do
all right so i hired a driver his name
is chris and he looks like a good guy
like real good looking kid but i don't
know if that always translates to
driving a 36 foot long rv
and so it's kind of just like a fingers
crossed operation does this thing
actually fit in one lane it's like one
and a half how do you drive it on a
phone you don't you don't
chris does who's to say that he's even
driving chris can we confirm that you're
driving this vehicle who's driving one
vehicle
the good news is we only have five hours
left
all right guys pulled up to our
destination it's [ __ ] seven a.m in
the morning right now i'm sure you can
see this guy behind me the sun's coming
up i don't even know if we're allowed to
park here i'm sure someone's gonna wake
us up in the morning and tell us to [ __ ]
off but we're all pretty exhausted until
then we'll try to get like two three
hours of sleep so wish me luck
oh holy hell we've had a crazy [ __ ]
day i haven't really found a spot to
illegally park this rv yet we're working
on it but it's fine because there's
really only one thing i want to do while
i'm here i just want to catch a fish i'm
from ohio i love catching fish except
the problem is i talked to some of the
locals and fishing's not looking good
have you caught a fish here i have not
cut it
have you caught a fish not one have you
caught a fish here no you caught a fish
today no
fishing's been bad there's no fish no
fish yeah they haven't stock since the
night
oh no one's catching fish then i met
these two nice young lads and they said
this you're telling me to guarantee
catch me a fish
guarantee you oh [ __ ] i'll bet you 50
bucks 10 minutes
kid let's get it catch me a fish boys
come here buddy
bro what the [ __ ] i've been scared in a
while
i can't have you doing that no more of
that okay we're in the middle of a lake
used to swimming in a pool in encino
it's a big difference okay
take it easy from now on promise me hey
the good news is
this place is beautiful
about to catch the fattest fish and
you're just gonna be like damn that's my
mans
yeah that's what's gonna prove your
worth to me
[Music]
[Applause]
nah nah nah there's no way bro what you
got it bro you're gonna be famous on
youtube
you better get this fish
[Applause]
[Music]
you think you think it's okay if i tell
these ducks to shut the [ __ ] up
[Music]
you