Oh what is this kid doing now okay so a
while back we did the basket treadmill
well recently a bunch of my friends been
sending me a video of some girl doing it
but into a pool and they're like yo
Logan you should do this now granted I'm
25 years old I'm a grown-ass man I don't
want to be doing this well I'm a man of
the people so if I'm gonna do it I'm
gonna take it to another level
literally I suits a little wobbly but we
start to call ambulance 26 years old I'm
done with this also I forgot to mention
we had a little bit of an issue when we
were grabbing the cabinets baby mouse is
a hoarder baby mouse holy [ __ ] 6:9 I
understand it's not ideal we're doing a
dumb YouTube little stunt I'm gonna
relocate you and your family got nothing
to worry about giant rats oh wait that's
snitch-ass had it coming to him oh my I
can't have another rat scandal on
channel I won't do it used to tase rats
on this channel now we save rats on this
channel they mean well and they're
really cute gonna save their life you
should auction these off for the
Maverick on what the magic club will be
winning our rats we could do that
legally alright so this is a bit of a
weird loss we're just doing things that
have been done before but better a while
back we did the the chocolate milk
explosion and then there was this
youtuber named Ryan Trey Hanna I mean
well he bested us
are you Ryan that's pretty good and then
he said this okay Logan if you top this
will all join the maverick Club well I'd
love to have Ryan and his team as part
of the maverick Club so we're gonna take
this to another level again I don't even
know if this is gonna work great you
guys no context that sentence can weaken
it's really close
Tanya it's compressing - that's like
4,000 rubber bands
bro so it didn't work I'm embarrassed to
be honest we've run out of rubber bands
3,000 of them so I think we're gonna
have to improvise
[Music]
well I guess alright Trahan welcome to
the Maverick Lee Oh what is this kid
doing now
what are you doing man what you don't
why do you get the dog in the backpack
he likes it I don't know like we do this
every Tuesday it's like me time I mean
what gives me you got a fight coming up
just be training August 25th Staples
Center that's 2018 Mike that's two years
ago is 2020 Connie is running for
president you know the [ __ ] we want
actually you know I'm thinking for me
carry on with your day Mike yeah we'll
see how you look in round three hi
goddamnit
yeah I'm not gonna lie this is probably
literally one of the best dogs on the
planet he is so chill and I'm in love
with him I gotta say I'm Josie or great
my girlfriend you're awesome well you
got some competition with this little
palm ski I doing big man you okay
anyways guys I hope you like the blog
bit of a weird one today I'll admit but
hit that subscribe button turn those
post notifications on and keep thumbs up
man we hit like yo half-a-million on the
last video that is insane anyways we
love you guys now see you on Friday
[Music]