vape nah bro laughing guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
these girls laugh she's screaming
excuse me oh you keep your cheeto
fingers away from me miss i don't even
know you what are your thoughts on
donald trump
do you listen to joe rogan oh she
prefers impulsive
oh damn i feel like i should run off
this boat and tackle him while he's on
the board i already took your slushy
machine the least i can do is break one
of your legs too
what's up dude not a good day to be
friends except
my friend would never ruin my sleep
everyone hates parallel parking but
that's because i think y'all are doing
it wrong
maybe we shouldn't be doing all this
guys i got a fight coming up august 25th
manchester arena
right no i think i got cte for my last
fall
oh holy [ __ ] mike what's wrong with your
legs they look like
popsicle sticks really last night he
went psycho and then he said that if we
break up he's going to go on your
podcast and talk
about me yeah you guys can watch that on
paul's consolationpolicy.com you guys
want to see more [ __ ] content we're
going to show you more content
right now for a youtube video we got
this idea from mr beast he said open a
dictionary to a random page pick a word
then brainstorm off the word three
two one [ __ ] yeah pose
oh no that was pretty good
china go to wuhan boys quick thorn
by the way mr beast came up with all his
ideas via this
hand clap a clap of the hands imitative
ah imitating others like mr beast using
the dictionary
piano accordion and according with the
melody played on a small vertical oh
that was actually cool we hired someone
to get a piano recording and then do
something i bet it'd be great
this is great
[Music]
oops what that's the same feeling i get
when i wake up
is the ending sound every day i wake up
like another day of this [ __ ]
play more please
ma'am i'm aging i'm aging so quickly
look at my face looks like there's been
an earthquake on a playground parking
lot i want people to touch my face and
think i'm a toilet full of porcelain can
you all inject enough botox in my face
to make me slender man
i don't even want to have a face do you
hear what i'm saying that's why i love
hollywood baby
mike did it better than you did drugs
for 10 years
[Music]
hey so we actually aren't a lot of post
needle stuff on youtube so for some
reason if you want to see me getting
stabbed in the face
sign up for the maverick club link in
description is the cost of being
beautiful huh it gives you a little bit
of a tangle in your brain and your penis
and what's better than this huh
guys being dudes
bro this can't be legal it hurts
oh my body all right give me give me
more laughing guys
[Music]
your face is so red i don't want to be
beautiful anymore sucking laughing gas
out of wally's nose