pull over pull over you heard the pop
right Wow look at us just a young couple
stranded on the side of a highway
oh my girlfriend's bear fine and she
thinks I heard this black I was gonna
pick up a flat earther they're weird I
have good news
I brought my rollerblades I'll just put
them on it go find help
bear fire so this whole thing happened
the day after Josie and I got in a
little fight and she wasn't crazy happy
about the timing of everything I'm sorry
I'll make it up to you so today I'm
keeping that promise and taking Josie to
do her favorite activity in the world
baby we're going horseback riding what
she doesn't know is that we actually
already visited these same horses last
week took them for a test ride and
really really liked them so I decided to
buy both of them one for her and one for
me look barb we're done horsing around
we want to buy your horse can you
imagine if we got here and she didn't
like the horses that we already bought
so something about a girl on a horse
[Music]
so cool baby you look so good in that
horse yeah I'm a better duo yeah
how long you been riding horses you've
never had your own personal horse
definitely the nicest gift I've gotten
any girl ever
do you like the horse I'm glad you like
them baby cuz I'm gonna be honest I
actually already bought them for you
[Laughter]
actually bought that one for me too to
the house yeah yours even if we break up
you can keep them between Danny
just-just-just nope literally only earth
[Music]
you guys knew you carry last week we
test road and we like them you did go
yeah yeah and you
[Music]
[Applause]
Logan you're the man you're the man barb
I mean the woman barb that horse is your
[Laughter]
horse bought me another like month to be
able to say you know yeah yeah yeah
we're second out sound like two of my
animals in the past and perished hey I
know this is all new to you you gotta
trust me I'm a good dude I swear to God
he's like I have you know my dad
[Music]
I'm so looky here folks it goin hard as
[ __ ] on the maverick Club it is the most
intimate curated special experience on
the internet we're gonna keep doing that
so we're gonna fly one of our members
out we'll ride these horses with us at
my ranch head over to maverick loading
calm to become a member and if you don't
like horses we got a ton of other
benefits including $10,000 monthly
giveaway equally faced times I've been
doing to add a periodic members dinners
exclusive content limited edition
maverick clothing discounts on literally
everything on the site and as you know
I'll be giving away my Dodge Challenger
to just a lot of dope oh yeah head over
to MAV of clothing com sign up and yeah
I'll see one of you guys on a horse ride
give us a hee-haw