I'll miss the thousands of miles of
memories with you you kept me safe you
kept me warm there's no way you're
crying right now so the girls were doing
some gardening with some hose a
gardening tool and they found this giant
bug here dude this thing is massive
oh he's touching me I'm touching him too
though will you eat this bug for $100
it's crunchy oh my god oh my god there's
remnants of bug congratulations your
$200 rooster nothing to say a couple of
vlogs go Jake jumped in this little pond
right here or puddled pond Pippin have
you look now it's full of like wood mud
sand I don't know what I've set him in
but now I have reason to believe this
could be quicksand there's only one way
to find out guys I don't think this is
quicksand I dig your back I think it is
quick saying it's quicksand here's the
deal we drove a bunch up to the ranch
this weekend and this like nice bar
thing broke I don't know how bad it is I
know you ate that bug but I'm actually
not gonna pay you $200 and you only
actually have a good idea how
you killed that big snake real prank is
hoping to plant it on the ground and
then hopefully scare the [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] snake wrangling this the first
time we ever came to the ranch
cheapy fought a rattlesnake to the death
now on behalf of the snake community I
think we should get him back hey dad dad
there's like uh there's a snake by the
logs alright take care because I'm
already so we're gonna get one of the
dogs or something behind you right right
you're right what are you doing you saw
I bought Danny a new Jeep because her
old one is real oh he's been kind enough
to let me roll it off a cliff and then
shoot it a lot I understand you've
prepared a eulogy
nice nice do my Jeep whoo I've spent
seven faithful years with you've been my
first love my first adventure buddy and
there's so much that I'll miss about you
I'll miss the aggressive sound when you
start if you start in the sound of the
mysterious piece of metal that clanks as
I Drive you I'll miss that I can't go
over 60 miles an hour unless you warm up
first I'll miss the garden hose used as
a replacement part in the radiator and
I'll miss the way that the floor fills
up with water when it rains but most of
all I'll miss the thousands of miles of
memories with you you kept me safe you
kept me warm there's no way you're
crying
we don't have to do this teary eye - I'm
not good you kept me safe kept me warm
you took me places and you're always up
for an adventure may this last memory be
as crazy as the rest
[Music]
jeez
[Applause]
no I mean like do we just shoot it and
leave it on the hill forever
[Music]