hey welcome back guys so before this
vlog starts I want to say according to
my YouTube analytics 40 percent of you
are actually not subscribed so do me a
favor
hit that subscribe button and I will
love you forever
oh yeah that's my bad just looking at
this thing you could probably still use
it
I am I put it right Crona serious Felton
has a full gas mask on as he's driving
that dimension look at my hey can you
shut the [ __ ] up for once
they're sort of mating dance I could do
wait where are we what why what you
gonna do I'm nervous
500 bucks of shoot spitballs for you
guys thought about Beauty the majority
of it lives with it we'd be here for 15
minutes your guys hey you know we have a
dinner to go to
can you please what are you doing oh I'm
so sorry it didn't I yeah
continue sorry I don't know I mean I'm
eat your dinner this morning we came
here to the UFC Performance Institute
apparently they want me to spar a guy by
the name of Paolo Kosta he's not a human
he's a bear he's a 30 nano undefeated
UFC fighter I don't think he liked the
way I looked at him at dinner last night
or something but it's a good thing I'm a
professional boxer now who's oh and one
god damn it I put the headgear on me and
not him and that's how you know now this
could be the future the UFC
we see them in the Octagon only time
will tell he's with Paul Acosta this is
Logan Paul and definitely he likes to
brawl
we'll see how MMA goes in his life you'd
never know but look at him now
he's ready I did good great kid if he
won you won you was
you know how to fight you'll know how to
fight 9% of guys who go to go show me
may have good technique but not hot
speeds not big hard you know all have
big heart don't have a good tech they
have booth thank you thank you
hottest thing I've done all day man
[Laughter]