she's our new roommate she's my roommate
she's your stepsister this is kilo
looking for a status update from alpha
alpha come in not feeling so good kilo
over here confirm at the meeting with
the doctor did happen basically told me
and I spent the last two hours fixing
this bowl with a 3d pen over alpha can
identify how the bowl actually broke
yeah that's actually the worst part I
was the one who broke it as well I'm
kind of just trying to stay busy over
board bro it works just great all right
so I'm not too happy right now
y'all may have seen I've been fed on are
a little bit like painting and stuff and
this morning I woke up to find that a
piece of art in my house had actually
been vandalized it looked like it was
done with stencil and a spray-paint I
said Banksy wasn't here obviously my
first thought was cool banks he came to
my house to vandalize my art but then I
was like this it's most likely not
actually Banksy so I checked the
security cameras and at 1:24 a.m. you
can see a tall skinny man entering frame
with his face covered putting his
stencil up and ruining my masterpiece
and the worst part is I'm pretty sure I
know who did it I just don't know why I
know you vandalized my painting you
piece of [ __ ] it's just crazy because
that stencil art resembles a lot of your
art too let's propose that it was back
see it wasn't [ __ ] Banksy you've
analyzed my art that wasn't me if you
can prove that I did it retribution huh
he was mad have you seen the video he
walked away like a person who walks like
Mac is trying to not walk like that
black spray-paint playing this Mac these
are my stencils this is my are you
stealing - that's - I got a question Mac
explained these brand new Nike Air Force
Ones that it looks like the perpetrator
was wearing as well
the most common shoe in the entire world
literally will go out there look at the
rack of airforce ones that are in this
house we're close we're close to busting
your ass all the art in the whole entire
house why did they only hit Logan's and
missed all of math he had a motive if
y'all remember previously Mack's art was
hanging in that spot no I took it down
and replaced it with my father he was
upset that the swap was made and wanted
to destroy my image yes my art is
priceless but now to have more presence
because Banksy was it wasn't Banksy it
says on it that he was not here I know
what you want me to think you want me to
think banks he came here and said he
didn't come here oh really it was you I
don't know where's the stencil I talking
all you do is [ __ ] now that's it this is
the time you realize if you like your
partner and I finally get to spend time
with your loved ones and you realize you
can't hate them holy Sh the mayor of LA
just said I'm issuing a safer at home
emergency order ordering all residents
of the city of Los Angeles to stay
inside the residences and immediately
limit all movement outside of their
homes beyond what is absolutely
essential by LA is on legit lockdown
right now like like you can't leave what
is essential I'm going to be able to go
to Liechtenstein to get my haircut she's
worried about her dogs and her hamsters
Mike are you moving in oh my god I have
no friends except are you a Sara
liability does this mean she's our new
roommate she's not a roommate she's your
stepsister
[Laughter]
you remember Eve she's the girl who slit
of my DMS Wow is it
loving the beard look Dave our German
videographer has taken quite the liking
to you
you convinced him to tattoo your name on
his leg but then I convinced him to
tattoo Christmas over it I'm talking
about that right so we're gonna get him
back yeah okay
you may have seen a one vlog Dave I'm
just gonna say it yeah you borrow some
Plan B and in the vlog we mentioned that
he didn't see her take it
congratulations your father I don't know
how to say this but we can't let our boy
suffer anymore come on
my reaction it asked the audience if I
did not already know we didn't know you
were scared my life seems someone less
willing to admit that they got prey good
stuff robber plus 4e that was amazing
she miss it on purpose just to get the
green card also I could insufferable
right honestly I did not fall for prank
but if I did fall I said this [ __ ] is
trying to get green card I was scared on
the how did she just continue her
sentence
[Music]