all right listen first so you subscribe
good second have you turned in
notifications on good yesterday 10:30
p.m. my assistant Danny loosely hints
that today is her two-year anniversary
working for team members now am I an
[ __ ] he doesn't forgot yeah maybe but
obviously my mind starts racing cuz I
had nothing planned absolutely nothing
so I started thinking back and I
realized that I've known Danny for like
four years
basically heard a few other people
randomly linked up with my dad when I
asked him to drive my school bus from
New York to California she has been a
badass since day one she's literally one
of the best people I've ever had the
pleasure of working with somehow she has
not quit after two years of this
[ __ ] so today I'm gonna get Danny
her dream vehicle the only problem is I
have no idea what that is
have you talked to Danny do you know
what her dream car is a newer version
yeah it hardly stars but it works which
means a better one a new one yeah yeah I
think it might be but we better find out
yes I'm gonna ask her brother so then I
did that and then I called her mom and
they both confirmed that Danny indeed
wants a 2020 Jeep Grand Cherokee okay
great
so I called my financial manager to see
if we could even do it your investment
portfolio because of coronavirus are you
I mean the ideally we find a sponsor so
that brings me here guys today this
video is brought to you by no except me
myself maverick clothing we couldn't
find the sponsor in time but also I
don't know I preferred promoting my own
it's not even just mine anymore it's not
maverick by Logan Paul anymore it's
maverick clothing calm and we spent the
past year rebranding coming up a new
creative ideas designs etc they're
simple they're sleek they're cool
they're low-key still keeping the
meaning of the brand which obviously
means the world to me hopefully you guys
do the idea of using and embracing your
differences to fuel your ship it's a
very simple concept I think being the
kid that was laughed at being the kid
that was undermined that no one thought
was gonna do the thing who did the
[ __ ] thing it just resonates with me
so excited to launch this the bad news
unfortunately he can't get any of it yet
it's not available yet if full launch is
coming mate
the second so mark the day I [ __ ] up a
lot in my life I've made a lot of
mistakes I've also had a lot of
successes and when I was at bat low
point in my life you know I never
thought I'd make it out but I am living
proof that it can happen and the launch
is gonna set her around the idea that
you can and even even though you feel
like you've gotten beat down by life it
starts right here started there for me
and it worked so May 22nd mad for
clothing calm yeah sponsors none let's
continue this video I love you guys so
here's the problem
Danny literally like does everything for
me if I need something usually she gets
it done so today to distract her from
what's actually happening via text I
asked her hey Danny do you get the
chocolates and flowers and card very
important obviously not for you she said
yep by God I said okay great not for you
obviously do you have the flowers and
the chocolates that I asked you to get
[Applause]
every two year anniversary a team
maverick Danny after the most
intentionally awkward interaction I've
ever had in my life it was time to get
to work are we buying a vehicle right
now at this moment or is this just a
preliminary a little scout I say we roll
back there with this dude no [ __ ]
you're lying right now oh no bro you
know me I'm always the guy that says
Logan don't do it Logan don't spend the
money Logan don't buy that hot dog not
today Logan I like Danny and I think we
get her a card
do you know what it's like to get
someone a gift and you're not sure if
they're gonna like it or not I'm doing
due diligence because I do not want to
[ __ ] this up
let's get him something that they will
like I like that idea
Mike you hear that it's been a big
learning her brother said favorite car
color is charcoal slash don't graze it's
our great
[Music]
I just want to say hi Lisa we want to
have somewhere for me
[Music]
I've never got anyone on the team a car
oh I know I know
IBM Danny's brother and I said is his to
life
he said that's perfect
[Music]
administrative work being a great girl
on what not hey Danny full transparency
I did have a little more plan than just
the flowers that you got yourself I got
you a song so I'm gonna reach into
Mike's pants to get it when it be the
first time last year
you'll get Danny that's you from Logan
that's me my hands get nervous quicker
than anything else
all right so once you follow me out
front
[Music]
[Laughter]
that is your brand-new 2020 Grand
Cherokee get you a better one I know
what it's like to get a gift that you
don't want Joe Mike whatever color you
want whatever accessories you want that
is also included in this game your
brother and your mom told me that this
was the car you wanted in his didm them
this is 1,000% yours this was not only
for the vlog I know I'm feeling that we
have a [ __ ] you deserve the [ __ ] out of
this like you really [ __ ] deserve this
and I'm so appreciative of everything
[Music]
you're not in here it stop dropping the
key
[Music]