Oh Oh No
David what happened notice it when
you're writing game old headset it's our
4k some people cheat and they try to
walk through walls to get people it
could be a real wall and you'll walk
right in you have a video of my boxing
coach running into a wall and I see this
video roll the clip jelly's knows they
got my nose but look at the
videographers nose was a cable what can
we make love in the video game well I'd
be balding in the virtual reality world
as well they're gonna see Jesus in their
day I know there's a door handle around
here somewhere is that the door handle
stuck like that hi in this corner let
you look you can see the fruit of wall
the best thing I've ever done in my
entire life
do you think I can throw the lawnmower
from the top of the house to the pool
like if I spin like this fast enough you
think so he doesn't think I can do it I
don't think you can throw a lawnmower
off the roof have you not seen him do
this
boom boom boom Hayden like quick caught
like 20 different crazy things he's done
I got over it
what'd you see
[Music]
as you know I've been through a lot of
[ __ ] this is one of the worst things
ever no matter what I do someone's
watching me I can't even get thicker
hair without in someone watching that's
my girlfriend's bathing suit well eyes
are titties I see the most concerned
with it toilet was thought I was
beautiful but now I know plan is to ride
my horse butt ass naked with only this
wig on litter how I'm opening the next
vlog not prepared to see that you
[ __ ] ready for Monday's vlog what's
happened David what did you do David
David why isn't raining in the house
David a light is leaking vlog oh you
want but in three minutes they're gonna
have to deal with this oh no David what
happened
oh I do at work I wouldn't listen to
import like a one episode of impulsive
like three times that's horrible
[Music]