[Music]
I drove back here in a Berber driver
with the camera my face put it on my
face touch me Dave I don't feel good
when I cough I feel like my head's gonna
explode and you know what serves me
right you only make fun of the virus so
many times before it comes back and
bites in the ass you people for your own
safety Milton you're more susceptible to
the virus than most of us million you
are old that is true but gotta go home
milk mill you're making this harder than
it has to be man we love you million no
the code on the game whoa whoa slow down
there Speed Racer what closed off yes
congratulations bro you safe I don't
think so here take this take this press
the button to talk take food paper so
give me a now women are coming here just
to steal my TP can I cut you matches and
gasoline to the washer we're gonna burn
does it look like a so this is my friend
Steve you've seen him consume enough
food and alcohol to kill the average
human being but today he's going
head-to-head against my Pig pearl
Bingbing in a burrito eating contest
and don't worry there's no meat on
pearls
[Music]
she did oh my god it's a big doing well
you gotta eat it Steve is fast I highly
underestimated Steve let's go baby
that's a good girl oh my god
and the rona holy Sh bruh she got really
close she's done I spent the last three
hours trying to be dude perfect this
one's called the three-point shot to a
vaccine that we have not discovered yet
[Music]
you know how many ping-pong balls I
threw dude you are perfect
yeah but real talk watch three-point
shot boy sure three-point shot
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]