i thought you said this new electrical
system won't cover power yeah what the
[ __ ] i got to watch
all right here's what happened as you
know one of the many benefits from being
a member of the maverick club you do
weekly zoom calls and this was a zoom
call i had like two weeks ago if we
traveled across the country from chicago
we would vlog our journey
to if we could meet you in person you're
in the maverick club yeah yes yes yes
let's go let's do it really yeah
yeah i got a lot of love from maverick
members as you guys know if you're not a
member yet maverick clothing.com or link
in description but these boys ryan and
his friends have literally
driven across the country and i think
they're outside right now coming all the
way from chicago
it's riot in the boys
boys thanks for being part of the club
i've got so much love for you guys and
uh we're actually about to head to my
ranch i suggest you
come i am down i am down
all right boys welcome to the ranch you
can do whatever the [ __ ] you want just
stay away from greg paul
i heard you got kittens yeah somebody
dropped them off at the game shut up
they just left them here yeah with a
little note it said
we understand you guys have a farm we're
moving out of state we know it'll be a
good home
that's how i got passed off to my
parents we know you're middle eastern
you have hummus here you go
oh my god a little oh my god
oh my god they're so scared oh my god
dad someone just dropped him off dog
i mean cat i can't believe someone
actually left his kittens here welcome
to the country man
hey honestly i've never seen you this
happy of course he's happy he's happy
every time he gets free [ __ ]
because you usually pay for it you own a
razor yeah
you want to ride it yeah you're gonna
[ __ ] yourself up no i just want to get
that on video
i feel like this is a bad idea is this
stupid did they sign waivers
yeah no that's good
these kids
how would you feel if i was like under
you don't want to be the kids who killed
logan paul
honestly there's a lot of people there
where's the nearest hospital that way
you sure you want to do this
oh my god i always trust him have a club
admit your adrenaline's rushing
nah psychopath i could take a nap
are you kidding me that's probably the
most expensive target we got you spent
twelve hundred dollars on roses
you do when you're in love man yeah so
dave got this heart rose for his
girlfriend eve but she got stuck at the
canadian border
now his heart is broken we're about to
break his heart again
you feel any better she actually brought
my heart through herself oh [ __ ] you eve
for breaking dave's heart
the fridge is out the food's gonna get
bad we're all gonna die greg told me the
upgraded solar system would never go out
so he said we have a solar system
we got the whole universe
there's only one man who knows how to
fix this problem
all right
besides him and his two buddies that
came who else knows he's here
surely you know where all these buttons
mean
[Music]
man greg paul says there's a lake on top
of a mountain we're in the middle of you
know where we already traveled 30
minutes to get to this spot
we have to leave the sprinter here
because it's not going to make it up
this rocky path tanner fox is driving
we're stuffing in the back of his pickup
truck kicking my girlfriend in the
vagina accidentally this should be
interesting
i hope this is worth it everyone's
pissed at me turned out to be a little
longer hike than i thought
my legs are hurting i didn't even pay my
taxes yet or kids
what do you mean these four kids for me
really gave up
watch the victoria's secret one runway
can't walk up a mountain
yeah do that do the runway walking be
fine okay maybe not
home stretch let's go thank god
holy [ __ ] this is insane this is [ __ ]
crazy
just at the top of a [ __ ] mountain
does it feel like water yeah it feels
like water okay that's cool
let's go
thank god i bought these whitey tidies
at the store the best day of my life
literally like a mountain heaven top
five best swims of my life dude this was
so worth it all that complaining
so worth it this is crazy guys we are
eight thousand feet in the air on the
top of a mountain and they're swimming
in a little oasis right now
[Applause]
[Music]
well listen you guys survived the
weekend more importantly you survived
greg paul
really nice to meet you you guys can
find it that was that was weird
you guys could i also feel like now is a
good time to say
thanks for 22 million guys we hit 22
million that's a big
yeah i guess let's just keep going let's
keep growing this family hit that
subscribe button or don't if your
notifications aren't on turn it on hit
the thumbs up i see you guys hitting the
thumbs up we're hitting like 300k on
each video real impressive guys i got to
say that i'll see you on wednesday i
love you bye
come on dude get in the water is warm
bro come on all right
it's a beach whale and tiny whities