pull over milk what did you what did you
hear yeah it's nothing it what if they
flew away probably it was Oh
no but he hit me I know obviously didn't
hit him biologist that's really
unfortunate oh no no he hit me so hard
Gregg would do right now is I don't I
don't I know I know I know daddy me what
if he's not dying you guys are
misinterpreting yeah but I got a
headache
it could be fine he might just yeah he
might just I've got to be I've got a
concussion he's good he's good you got
it you got it boy come on but he's not
in the right state of mind right now
and so he's vulnerable out here if we
can move through the house I can someone
give Milton that uh just for animal
control it's closed today
it can't be closed today hey buddy come
on you got this I've been through some
hearts my life just like you're going
through right now so I feel your pain I
relate to you we're tough throughout you
ain't pitching you out you ain't a bird
you are power and you toss
[Music]
is that a hedgehog or now Oh where'd you
find it it found us millon hit it and we
thought it was a bird okay we don't know
the Sprinter van mil tonight he loves
you you saved his life
well let me tell you I am in a second
ballot coming up with it but they
described your name for this to cover
this is how it's done huh I am so
hopeful that he's gonna be healthy and
well in the morning all right it's the
morning I have my mom on the phone for
moral support I'm really hoping this owl
is alive I know they're nocturnal so I
kind of feel bad I'm just gonna take a
pee in there what if he is we can call
animal control today and then we can
ship them off to somewhere safe whoa
he's so cool
not really we hit him with her car well
he hit us but the good news is it looks
like he's still alive he's not 100% in
the right state of mind yet but he is
healthy fish I was giving pep talks last
night last night yeah that's good at
least take me out to dinner before you
[ __ ] me Millie
wasn't me just like with the owl bill
you know you can hit the coffee we would
have something hit our windshield found
what appeared to be an owl on the cusp
of death gosh damn right I am
hold on my parents freaking out sorry
uh you guys will take it sweet all right
goodbye we're gonna do this we're gonna
be heroes Dave you and I Dave just me
and you hear us forever hundred years
hundred years men more hey heroes
[Music]
stay with me
one final wishes good luck for our
friend who have decided to name hoot cuz
I was hoot it's the home stretch yeah
you're gonna make it through this
so I guess that's it you didn't say
goodbye you hid remember we have to Alan
that's leaving us notice I have my bird
mask nice promo mil nice yeah I feel
like it's a good time to tell you
May 22nd the new mattress drops coming
change the Instagram handles no longer
at Mavericks by Logan Paul it's at
maverick clothing the tricky part about
this is that like none of this needed to
happen right like he didn't need to hit
it it's like because I feel good like we
did something good but we also did the
bet the thing that we needed the best
thing that any human being could ever do
I mean I was gonna drive off
[Music]