- This looks amazing!
(pops) Oh my gosh!
(laughs)
New challenge, we have to do another DIY prank
because this one was what, like, a cake balloon?
- Yeah! - So, right now ...
- Hey Collins, you want a Whopper?
- Yeah, sure, thank you. You're welcome.
- Ah!
- (laughs)
- Dude!
- It's a cheese ball Whopper, bro!
(gags)
- Devin, pull my finger.
- Okay?
What?
- Yeah, we do need that. Okay.
Ow, geez, now that's cheesy (laughs)!
- Hah.
Alright so here's how you make it.
Now we got our chocolate
we're gonna melt these down to make the Whoppers
so we gotta do it quickly cause I can feel it, it's burning.
I can smell it, I can sense it with my senses.
Tadah! There we go, boom, nailed it.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Olive oil, bro, you forgot!
- Oh, right, right, right! Alright there we go
- What? Ow! Dude, how's it stuck to me?
Dude, what is going on?
- Eh, eh, eh.
- And go! I gotta break it! I gotta ...
I gotta just crush it down, crush it down,
Come out, come out! Okay there we go, boom!
Tear it on it's side. Yo, it is like legit
burning and roasting right now
look at this, look at this!
This is how you make a crumbled chocolate bar.
Doesn't that look delicious to eat and like a lot of fun?
Oh no, dude!
- What?
Oh, (groans) what did I do?
- Your moves are weak!
Yo! This is coming together nicely.
Okay, here we go just gotta mix mix mix mix mix mix
per usual your elbow is very close to my face.
- Well yeah, I'm right handed bro, so uh ...
- Devin, hand me one of the skewers.
- There you go.
- Here's how you retrieve the cheese ball ...
... you gotta bam! (bag crinkles)
Oh, I got two of them! - (laughs) Nice!
Uh, eh, ooh, ow! (laughs)
- Scratched your finger. Ow!
Ow. Enough of that,
You're gonna mix in the chocolate
on top of your cheese puffs.
Now it's time to empty out our lil' cheeseballs
or, should we say, disguised Whoppers.
Oh man! I made a steamy amount, like it's a lot there.
That looks really ... - That looks like something
- Looks like something to me!
- Yeah, pretty much spread them out one by one, for sure.
- That's for sure! So right now we're gonna do that,
pop these in the fridge and then
do a little taste test.
Bam! They're all done now, and that is what they look like
so right now, Devin, it's time for you to do a taste test.
I already had my experience.
- Alright here we go. Three, two, one.
- Wait first! A 5 second subscribe challenge
we want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channels post notifications
in 5 seconds. Are you ready?
- Done. Now if you can do that comment down below
"keyper squad" right now
and Devin, I wanna see if your reaction is as extreme
as mine was, so go for it.
- Alright here we go. Three, two, one.
(crunches)
(coughs on repeat)
Holy cow!
- It's bad right?
- Way worse than I expected.
How could these two delicious things taste so bad together?
- I don't know!
Alright so right now guys we are on to the next round.
- Hey Collins, want a piece of gum?
- No, no, I've seen this before
if I pull the gum it'll shock me.
- What? No, not at all. Dude trust me.
- (screams) Oh my gosh!
It didn't shock me so,
you just gave me a piece of gum?
- That's the prank there, bro.
- Alright, shocking gum.
This is some weird looking gum.
(Devin laughs)
- What is that!?
- It's PlayDoh, bro!
- Now the process to make this ones a little bit
extra!
- Oh gosh, I did not know what you were about to do.
- 'Cause we got Extra bubble gum.
This is not enough gum, we're gonna need
Extra!
There we go, we got some extra gum
get it cause it's literally Extra gum.
This is how you do it, you juggle bro.
- Yeah, all right.
- Yup. All right lets do this!
We got PlayDoh and gum so first up we gotta remove a piece.
- Already done.
Dude, what? (laughs) It's not ...
- I got two pieces
and now we gotta unwrap it with your mouth
- What? That's not safe dude you should not-
bro, what are you doing?
Dude your teeth are turning like silver, bro.
- Yeah, for real, you might want to spit it out. Hah.
- So first we're gonna pop another round
and easier way to open it which is bumbumbumbabumbum.
- Really dude?
- So basically you gotta unwrap one of the gum pieces.
- Or a ton of them.
- How did you do so many?
Alright so basically, you just need the wrapper
and then you can get rid of the gum so, yeet.
(sad, slow music)
YEET!
There is only one thing that can be done, Devin.
- Okay.
- A feet!
Alright let's pop open, YEET, this here, wait Playdoh.
Woah, can we get a replay on that?
It popped out a very cool way.
(banging)
- Okay so now we're gonna take it- splet.
- You know what, Collins, you can have some of mine.
- Thank you, man, I appreciate it,
so now you just have to roll it out.
- That doesn't look like you're rolling it, dude.
There ya go! Nice!
- You just gotta really get it kinda flat you can use
actually, your PlayDoh roller - Okay.
like this to kinda roll. - We need a roller!
So we just had an idea, basically if you
take a real pice of gum,
then you're gonna lay it on top like this
and then you're gonna trace the outline
yo this stuff cuts like PlayDoh! (whoa sound)
- And you just gotta give it a good ol' sleecity slice.
- Now it's time for the big reveal
of what the gum looks like. Ready?
- Three, two, one, tadah!
- So now you're gonna place it inside
of the wrapper very carefully
and now you're gonna actually hide it back inside
of your gum container, just like this
so now you can pull out your piece of gum
and then when you go to offer a friend
they're gonna eat some PlayDoh, which is disgusting.
So right now we are on to the next one.
So Devan I wanna start this off on the right foot
so I brought you some cookies.
- Oh, awesome! Thanks!
- Yeah. They're home made so tell me what you think.
(coughs)
- Yeah well I-
are you insulting my cookie!?
(laughs)
- No, they're actually made out of
mashed potatoes and black beans.
- Oh!
- So for this, we're gonna need
some water and some butter, so woohoo!
- Oh, dude! You almost messed me up!
(banging)
That' doesn't look ... (trilling sound)
- Whoa! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Bro. What are you doing?
Great now we just let that heat up and boil and
- Next up we add the mashed potatoes
so Collins I'm gonna let you do the honors.
- Alright we got this here ... Okay.
- Ow! (laughs) Dude you okay?
Okay maybe you can't.
- Oh dude, you're getting it everywhere, Devin!
- Do you see this? This is not coming out, bro.
Tada!
Whoa, dude, your elbow.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What? That's more than two cups.
- It says two cups, look at it, two cups.
- No, that's way more than two cups!
- Oh wait yeah, that's a little bit more.
It's like two and blahblahblah. Alright here we go.
Alright let's see how this goes,
now we're just gonna mix it up in there.
Oh, you that's actually kinda satisfiying. Smoky.
- Whoa, it smells like mac and cheese.
- Yo, it smells like it's burn- (screams)
- Oh. Dude you okay?
- It looks like it's burning.
- Alright so I'm gonna turn it off here.
- Okay, okay, okay, yo, all right.
No, no, no! No, no! (yelling)
- Boom! Now it's done, oh my god that's pretty hot!
So now we got the mashed potatoes which are steaming
and this is gonna act as the cookie dough
so now it's actually time to make the chocolate chips
which we're gonna use black beans for this
so now we gotta pop it open. - All right.
So now we're gonna pop it on here,
I've learned from my mistakes, - Be careful this time.
All right here we go (sings). - Oh, nice.
So now all we need is something to strain the beans with.
Uh, oh, where did that come from?
- (laughs) You need to work on your magical skills, brah.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Unless you want me to, BAM! Devan, Devan!
So we got the beans and we dump it out in- (screams)
Alright Devan, what is going on!?
Yo, I did I clap wrong or something?
Maybe it's like- (claps)
- Collins, help!
- Hold it up, hold it up, hold it up!
(grunts)
- Boom. Oh my gosh, okay.
Now we're gonna add the beans which will look
like the chocolate chips, into the mashed potatoes.
Boom, and now, time to mix it all around.
- Next up we add dollops of this.
- There's an extra step to it,
you gotta mush it together. Oh, oh, oh.
- Dude, what is the point of that?
- Heres a better way you can roll it in your hands first
and then I call this one
Whoop-dee-doo! - Missed it.
Whoop-dee- missed again.
Whoop-dee-doo!
That was a great technique!
So right now we're gonna put all these on here
and then pop them in the oven and bake them
just like some cookies.
- Whoop-dee-doo!
- He-hey!
- Whoa! (slam)
- So you're going to go eat
a nice chocolate chip cookie and-
like it's all dry and crusty
- What?
Alright guys! Next round, lets go.
- Collins, have you seen my phone?
- No, why? Have you tried calling it?
- Uh, no, let me try.
(phone chimes)
Oh wait! You found it?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah I think it's in here, I hear it.
- No! Bro! What did you do!?
That's my phone! That's not a joke!
- Well I may have gone a little too far.
- Whoa, why!?
- Well, here, try calling it, make sure it's the right one.
- (laughs) That's my phone! Which one is this?
- I'll show you guys how to do this prank right now
because you can break a phone like that so here's how you
do it the safe way, where you don't break the phone.
- My heart is going so fast. - You're gonna go,
Yo it's jello time!
We got this here for the jello
Peanut Butter Jello Time!
- Yeah.
First up we gotta add the water.
I've got double whisks 'cause I'm a double whisk action.
- Whoa, be careful, be careful.
Oh my God that was close. Great job, Devan!
Next up we're gonna add the jello in and then just kinda
- This smell never gets old. Every time.
- Just add a little bit more jello
Alright, all of it in, done, all right,
mix, mix, mix, whisk, whisk, whisk,
whisk, whisk, whisk. whisk, whisk.
(spits) Time to get some food coloring
so we're gonna want to go for, of course, red for this one.
- Oooh. - Whoa.
now that we've made the jello, kinda put this to the side
- Ugh. - Smells disgusting!
Now the DIY really begins
so Devan I want you to take this
I want you to cut out the phone.
We have some dental floss and we're gonna need some tape.
Where is the- where's the tape?
Boom, there we go.
- Why'd you stop?
- Nothing. So now I get to take all the dental floss.
We're gonna go like this and guys,
the reason we're cutting out the phone right here
is because of the fact that we don't want to put a real
phone in jello, otherwise it'll break it.
Actually wait, hold on one second.
All right, there we go.
- What!?
- Just plucked it straight out of thin air.
- Yo, how did he do that, dude?
- You're gonna put the tape right here on the side
and I literally have to create
basically a hammock for the iPhone.
So we're gonna take off some dental floss
we're gonna lay it over the top like this.
- There you go, it is all cut out
now you put it into the phone case.
- Okay, is it too big?
(laughs on repeat)
- Bro, you didn't print it out on the right side
- Well eh- blalalalalala
Okay, thanks!
- And next up you put the case right on the dental floss.
- Yup, and now you're gonna pour in the jello
and because it's suspended it will not sink
all the way to the bottom
it will literally be stuck in the middle.
- No! Bro, you remember what happened last time right?
- Oh! - Oh, no, no, no, no ...
- It was an accident though.
- What? Was it?
- I'm nervous this time, this is a pranks video
so you cannot spill this on me, that's not a prank, Devan.
No! - All right.
- Dude, ow, ow, ow. - Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
- And, okay, I think with that.
- Hold up, hold up, holll ...
- Save some, save some, 'cause we're actually doing
an extra prank we're gonna be doing with the left over jello
but right now, lets submerge the iPhone. Do, do!
All right and now we're gonna stick it in the fridge
and then the prank is ready to go.
This looks absolutely insane
so this next part here is the most fun
so we gotta remove the tape first.
- This tape is rather ... adhered. I got it!
- Alright so here we go time to flip it over.
- The best part!
- Oooooh!
- That looks so cool!
Alright next up is Devan's gonna remove the dental floss
so pull it.
- Oooooh.
- This is so satisfying.
The dental floss is literally just running through the jello
this looks amazing
I think at the end of this video we should take
a bite of that jello cause that looks delicious.
- Ah! Dude, really!?
- All right so how do you do this prank?
- So first you blow up a balloon.
- Okay.
(air inflating against balloons)
- Think that's good?
- Next up you tie the balloon
- Done.
- Oh, all right.
- Yay!
- Ah, got 'em!
- I thought it was gonna pop.
I'm really not liking the-
(balloon banging)
- Next up we frost it.
- Frost it!
So I'm gonna take out some of this frosting. All right.
This is the way to go.
- Ugh, it's way messier though bro.
- Dude, that feels super weird!
- Oh no! (laughing)
- It got stuck to all the balloons.
- No!
- Okay, yo, this is actually working out
way better than I thought it would. Wow!
Now it's time for some pink stuff
it's looking like a strawberry swirl of sorts
- Oh, that looks so good!
- Oh my gosh! I wanna eat it so bad.
- Like look at this bro, I just leave it
alone for a second, and it-
- It's because it's top heavy! - Look at that!
- I think what I want to do with mine is I'm just gonna like
get all the edges except for the bottom, chochochocho.
No one would ever think twice that this is
actually a balloon because
it looks like delicious cake, it smells like one
it's gonna taste like one at first
and then all of a sudden, pow!
- You know what's better-
- Oh no!
- I got it on my key! Not happy!
Oh my gosh, it's just not staying still.
- Oh!
We're gonna get this rolls, okay here we go, squeeze it out
get it all over the top here
and the final step, time to add some sprinkles.
That looks amazing! Oh my gosh!
This looks like a legitimate cake!
- Dude!
- That looks delicious.
- Whoa!
- Now it's very important to not pop this before
you get to the person you're trying to prank
because when they try to go and slice a piece
it's gonna pop all over them, as you saw
so right now guys we are on to the next round.
So for this one here
all you're gonna need is the left over jello,
some whipping creme, and some green food coloring
'cause that'll actually change the red look of the jello
into the kinda like, murky brown color
and this is awesome. So what you're gonna do.
Pull out a straw, Devan. - Ooh.
- And then look at this. I want you to pinch the end of it,
it's gonna push it forward like this. Okay?
- That looks so gross!
- Ugh, that is so disgusting.
And this is how you can make edible earth worms
and really freak people out
so I'm gonna grab a whole bunch of them at once
here we go, that's really gross, oh my gosh!
Literally, look at all these, bro!
- They actually feel like worms.
- I know and they look like it too man, ugh!
I guess we're just gonna give these a shot.
So here we go, Devan, pick up a worm.
- No, we have to eat them?
- Ready, three, two, one
Wait, first, three second like challenge,
we want to see if you can like this video in
three seconds, all right here we go,
- three, two, one, done.
- All right so right now I gotta get a new one so here we go
- Three, two, one.
- Wow - Yeah, they're delicious.
- Yeah, now you can prank people and they will think
that you are literally eating an earth worm
which of course, is just jello
now's the fun part, time to pull this phone
out of the jello so here we go,
three, two, one.
- Oh, mine actually went in!
- Mine went in a little bit too.
Okay we're gonna try it again,
three, two, one.
Ow! Oh it feels so weird.
- Oooh! Aaaaah!
- The phone is just like perfectly sitting in there
it made like a perfect impression of the phone
so now the fun part, we're just gonna take it
and just kinda give it a tear in half
you take that side, I'll take this side, ready.
- Three, two, one.
- Holy cow this feels crazy!
If you want to see another video click right over here
and right, you have five seconds here we go.
- five, four, three, two, one, done.
- Love you guys so much - Bye!
- Yo, these are very I- you have to be careful
with these so I'm gonna put a bean thing on top of them
- That's not the- - They're gone and ... !
- All right, I'm time!
Or, I'm time
- I am father time.