(screaming)
- Hmm, I'm thirsty.
(record scratch)
Mm.
- Wengie! That's Windex, you can't just drink Windex!
- It tastes really good!
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
- No!
(screaming)
- It burns!
(T.V. beep)
- What just happened here?
- Well, my bottle wasn't actually Windex, it was Gatorade.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- Oh yeah.
- Tastes good right?
- Oh yeah. That's nice.
- Pranks, guys.
(laughing)
- The next prank is extra spicy.
Basically, whenever someone asks you for a piece of gum,
this is the perfect prank to pull on them,
and no one will ever ask you for your gum anymore.
'Cuz basically, this prank involves
- Wasabi!
- And trust me, it's spicy!
- Let's do it.
Alright, so we're going to open up the package of gum first.
- And I'm gonna open up the wasabi so we can get it ready.
You know what? We should do something.
- What?
- Loser eats wasabi.
- Oh! Like a rock, paper, scissors at the end of the video,
the ultimate showdown, what are you doing there, fam?
We'll find out who has to eat wasabi at the end of the video
that's a great idea.
- A full tablespoon.
- What?
- Yep.
(sniffing)
- Oh...
- Oh my gosh, it burned my nose hairs.
(groaning)
- It's so bad, oh my gosh.
- I never thought smelling it would make it just hurt.
- Like, I felt the burn.
You just, smell it through your nostrils, man.
My nose hairs are singed.
So guys, basically you're going to take your wasabi,
and you're gonna kind of put it on the top. Oh!
- This looks like a green worm booger.
- Oh, that's kind of nasty in it of itself.
- It's like sticking to my knife.
- Oh yeah. This thing is like very pasty.
- They're not going to notice this when they open it?
Like, are we gonna give it to them a certain way?
- Yeah, you hand it to them upside-down so they can't see it
and then they bite into it and they just,
it will mess them up for life.
- Oh.
- Oh my gosh, I am not excited about eating some wasabi.
That's something I'm not looking forward to.
Next step's, once you got a spread on there,
you're going to take it, put it in the freezer,
let it freeze or dry or harden,
and then you scrape off the excess
and then you won't even be able to tell
there's wasabi on the gum.
- That's really smart. I didn't expect that.
- After it's frozen, this is what it looks like.
You're now ready to hand this to someone,
and they're gonna take a bite of it and freak out.
Right now I think it's time for me
to actually taste what this is like
before we go for the full tablespoon
of wasabi at the end of the video.
Oh my gosh, I'm not excited about this.
- You know what, that looks so real guys.
It's literally quite real.
- Uh-huh. Here we go. Okay. Three, two, one.
Wait, wait, first I'm gonna challenge,
I wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
You got this? Here we go.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one. Done!
If you can do that, comment down below "Keyper Squad"
right now. And now? Time to take a bite. Oh my Gosh.
I don't like wasabi at all.
- Alright. Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
- Oh my gosh!
(screaming)
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Oh!
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
- Oh my gosh, if I lose at the end I am not going to be good
because I do not like this, it is so hot! Oh my gosh!
Alright guys, onto the next prank!
My mouth is on fire! Oh my gosh, it's so hot.
- You're red. You're literally red, it's crazy.
- Yeah. I don't do well with spicy things. At all.
Okay, next round. Let's go. Whoo!
For this next prank, basically we are going--
- Collins?
- What?
- You kind of smell.
- I smell? Oh, okay.
- What?
- It's just cream cheese. And it's super frozen.
I did not think it would be that frozen.
(Collins laughs)
So guys this prank here--
- Ew, this smells too!
- That was so gross! Everything about this is disgusting.
Okay guys, now we're going to show you how to make this.
(laughing)
(T.V. beep)
Well, that was a bad experience.
But we're going to show you how to make this
so you can freak everyone out. So, we got some deodorant?
- We've got one deodorant.
- Oh, we have to share? Ow! Okay.
Oh jeeze, there's two layers.
- Oh yeah, there's the--
(spitting cap out)
- How do you get it out?
- Oh, you've got to turn it.
- Oh, three, two, one.
(clinking of plate)
(laughing)
- That didn't work.
- Yeah, nope you've gotta keep going!
(clinking of plate)
Totally meant to do that. All part of the--
it's on the floor! Whoa! This thing is slippery, man.
Alright, so where are we gonna pop this?
I'm just gonna stand it up right there on top of that.
- I'm still going, I'm still going.
- Let's see if we can grab it and pull it out.
Oh, no! My fingers are all slippery.
Here, I've got an idea. It's called the two spoon approach.
You just kind of clip it and spoon em!
- Whoa! Like, literally that worked guys, look at this.
- Yeah but now it's all over me.
So, next step here, we're gonna kind of clean out
the top of it thoroughly,
because you do not want any deodorant left in there.
(magical tinkling)
Done! We've cleaned it out,
and now time to add the cream cheese
and make it look like deodorant.
- It's a little bit soggy.
- Yeah, mine's a little soggy.
I wonder if you push it from the bottom like this, Oh!
- Whoah!
- It's like a popsicle. Hey guys,
I've got a cream cheese thumb!
(sqwawking)
So you kind of take off a layer off the top of it.
- Okay.
- Like this, and then you're just gonna start kind of
spooning it into the deodorant.
- I see where you're going.
- Alright. So we're just kind of
gonna push this down in here.
- So I'm gonna do it much cleaner.
I'm gonna just stamp it like this.
- Oh, that's really smart.
- It's in a nice blocky shape.
- Just gonna kind of stuff this, oh yeah.
This is, I'm getting saucy with mine. Oh yeah, this is nice.
- I love how you're looking at it like it's a piece of art.
Like sculpture. He's just like, like totally, mmm.
- Oh yeah, I'm crafting a masterpiece right now.
- This is the masterpiece. Look how smooth that is.
- Yeah, yeah. That is pretty much a masterpiece.
- I'm just glad you're not like using the tongue technique
where you're just actually like, eating it.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Alright, well mine's looking good.
This is really convincing guys.
I would fall for this.
- Mmhm. And there you have it!
Now you can either put this in the freezer
if you want to keep it in this shape,
or if it's cold enough it will just stay like this.
And now you can freak someone out and be like,
oh you want some deodorant? Hold on for a sec.
(bite)
Mm.
- It's literally weird even though--
- It looks so weird.
I've seen it before and it still looks weird.
- Alright Wengie, we've got some orange juice for you.
- What? That don't look the same as my orange juice.
- Oh no, trust me, they're exactly the same.
Yeah. Just enjoy.
- Ew!
(laughing)
- Yo! It's macaroni and cheese!
Oh my gosh, okay yeah. So this one is actually kind of,
kind of disastrous because they think they're going
for orange juice when in fact it's only
macaroni and cheese cheese packets.
- Ew! That was disgusting!
- So all you do for this one is just take some
orange juice and just empty it out.
Oh, I hope it doesn't go everywhere, how do I open this?
- What are you doing?
- So I'll give you the honors on this one.
If you wanna dunk the packet of macaroni and cheese in there
yo, it's kind of like, it's kind of chunky, right?
- It's so orange! We don't have this orange cheese
in Australia! I've never seen cheese so orange you guys.
- America, with the orangest of cheeses. Ha ha!
Let's see if we can, oh.
- Ooh!
- What a perfect pour.
- [Wengie] That's really good.
- [Collins] Yo, this actually looks really good.
- That looks like orange juice.
- [Collins] This is the perfect prank for breakfast
when you guys are all eating food together.
Because everyone thinks they're going for the orange juice.
- You could totally prepare it in the kitchen
and put one orange juice that's like pranked,
and you put normal orange juice for your own.
- And then voila!
I can't believe how much it looks like orange juice!
- I can't tell.
- Yo! Check out what I found! These were in the fridge.
- Yeah, I made them earlier can I have this one.
- Yeah, for sure, what are they?
- They're caramel covered apples.
- Oh I'm so excited.
- Yeah, alright, cheers!
- Cheers!
- Ah!
- Whoa!
(screaming)
What is this, it's an onion?
- Pranked.
- Oh my god. Caramel doesn't taste good with onions.
What the heck is going on?
- Oh that smells so bad!
(screams)
- This was the nastiest thing
I've ever had in my entire life.
And it's so confusing!
'Cuz at first you're like, oh, delicious caramel
and then you bite into it and you're like,
oh! Nasty onion.
- Well, mine's an apple.
- So how would you do this?
- First, you take a packet of caramel
- Okay.
and you melt it over a pot.
- Mmhm
And then you cover one apple with the caramel
and one onion with caramel.
(groaning)
And then you take it to your friend.
- Okay, gotcha.
So then the friend has no idea what's going on.
- It even smells bad from here!
(choking)
- This was a diabolical prank to say the least.
This next prank actually involves toothpaste. Yeet!
- Okay, I like this one.
I can't wait til you brush your teeth because
that onion though. Yeah. Yeah.
- Yep, it was your prank okay?
You're the one who pranked me on this one.
- No bad idea.
- First steps first, you gonna take your toothpaste,
you gotta empty the entire tube.
- Oh no! I can't keep watching this. Ugh.
You can fit a whole tube of toothpaste in your mouth?
I'm impressed.
(laughs)
- See? No more bad breath.
- Alright. Now after you've emptied your tube,
you wanna make sure you do this thoroughly,
I didn't do it thoroughly, we're gonna keep going here.
(T.V. beep)
- That kind of looks like slime,
you could make slime out of that.
- That would be like really cool. Toothpaste slime.
That's the next thing.
Now I'm going to try to inflate my tube.
- Oh!
- And for the next step now,
you're gonna take some mayonnaise,
you're gonna open it up now.
(glass shattering)
Perfect. And I got one of these handy-dandy syringes here.
So we're gonna pop this in.
- [Wengie] Ooh! Ew!
- [Collins] Oh! That's crazy!
- That looks cool. What?
- Oh my gosh. Alright, so now we pop the syringe like this.
Oh! It like literally fits perfectly!
And then we're just gonna...
- [Wengie] Oh!
- Whoa!
(laughing)
- [Wengie] That's satisfying. Whoa! That's perfect.
(screams)
(slow-motion deep voice scream)
(laughs)
Oh my god.
- Are you okay?
- No! I'm covered in mayonnaise.
- Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
- So that was the real prank.
- Oh my gosh. I'm in so much trouble for this one.
Y'all better go subscribe to her channel
because she just got like, splattered with mayonnaise.
Oh my gosh!
(T.V. beep)
- Alright, I'm all cleaned up.
- I am so sorry, oh wait.
You actually still have of mayonnaise still in your hair.
Look forward really quick? Okay, here we go, hold up, um.
(hair clippers buzzing)
(screams)
- What!
- It's an app! It's an app!
(screams)
(laughing)
- You guys, that's another fun prank.
There's an app, it's like a razor app.
It sounds like you're about to buzz someone's hair off.
And like her hair is iconic.
- I know! My hair!
- Alright guys, so right now I don't think
we're gonna add anymore mayonnaise for obvious reasons.
(screaming)
But that's basically how the prank ends up
where someone goes to squeeze out their toothpaste,
mayonnaise comes out instead of actual toothpaste.
- [Wengie] Ew!
- It will not leave your teeth clean,
it will leave your breath smelling nasty.
- It don't smell good.
And I keep remembering that at the end of this
one of us is going to have to eat a whole thing of wasabi.
- Oh no!
- We've only got a few pranks left so.
- Yes.
- I guess, let's see what else we've got in store.
- Alright, we've been filming for a while. Are you hungry?
- Yeah I'm actually really hungry.
- Me too. So I've got two things,
this is a chocolate egg, apple. Which one do you want?
- I actually love chocolate eggs
so I'll take this right now.
It's like one of my favorite foods.
- Mm.
(Wengie laughing)
- What is this?
- It's a chocolate egg, you know it's chocolate--
- Oh, literally a chocolate egg! Okay.
So wait, how do you do this prank? I don't like this one.
- Okay well, there's some chocolate, you basically melt it
and cover a real egg with the chocolate.
- Oh! I saw all the eggs here and I was like,
this is kind of suspicious.
(screaming)
- It burns it burns!
- So we're just gonna unscrew the tops right now,
I've actually got a little bit of left over Windex.
Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew! Oh! Whoa!
- I'm kidding. I got nothing.
- Well it's turned off so hold on. Let me just.
- Oh! Safety switch. I like it. It's Wengie proof. Oh!
- Whoa!
(Wengie laughing)
This is like continual pranks, man, I cannot catch a break.
It's a very effective way to remove it.
- Are you serious? Can't you just pour it?
(Collins laughing)
- Yeah.
- What? What are you doing Collins?
- Yeah, no, no that will not work. Oh!
- Whoops.
- Oh jeeze. Well, I guess the benefit
is that if we get this on the glass it's no big deal
because it's a glass cleaner I guess. Ooh!
- Look at that foam.
I was like trying to make it like a bubble bath.
(blowing air through container)
Aw! You made bubbles!
- So make sure you guys get all of it out.
- And wash it.
- Yes. So we're gonna go do that right now,
we'll be right back.
(magic chimes)
And now, you just take a blue colored gatorade
and fill up your bottle of Windex.
- Ooh, this smells really good.
- This would like freak everyone out.
Like especially for like back to school,
even in class, like anywhere, with your friends.
This will like, just trip people out.
- It looks almost similar.
Oh no! It's making my hands slippery!
It's slipping, it's slipping, it's slipping!
- You got it? Oh, okay there we go.
So now we're getting the Gatorade on the table
I don't think the Gatorade is meant to be on the table.
It's not like Windex. Won't clean it the same way.
- No, it's gonna get sticky.
Literally, oh, how does that taste?
(coughs)
- Awesome. So whether you're at home, in class, or anywhere
with friends, family, you can then
take your bottle of Windex and do this.
- Mmhm.
- Or it can be with the top on,
and you can squirt it into your mouth.
(liquid squirting)
(Collins screams)
Oh! Oh my gosh, I
forgot to clean it out!
I forgot to clean the top out! There's Windex left over.
- Oh! Yeah. We forgot that part.
- Alright guys, onto the next round. Holy cow!
- I'm so glad I didn't put mine on.
- This is perfect if you want to prank your siblings.
So basically for this prank, grab their bar of soap
you're also gonna need some clear nail polish.
Now you're gonna open it up.
- [Wengie] Alright. Oh.
- How do you...
- That's, oh. I've got it, I've got it.
- Oh there we go. That was difficult.
And what you're gonna do is you're gonna cover it
in clear nail polish.
I've gotta say, I don't think I'll ever
get used to the smell of nail polish.
- No, it's overpowering. I can smell it from here,
and I'm already like trying to move back.
- Oh yeah. So once the top side dries,
you're gonna take it, you're going to flip it over.
Whoops! And you're going to do the bottom side.
That way, when they go to use the soap it will never sud up.
'Cuz the clear nail polish, for some reason,
it stops the water from touching the soap.
So they're going to be washing themselves
thinking they're getting super clean
when they're not at all.
In fact, it is probably going to smell like nail polish
when they're all done with their showers.
And now. I think we can put this down.
Because it's time for the moment
you've all been waiting for.
- Oh!
- The big finale! We've got the wasabi.
- [Wengie] Mmhm.
- And whoever loses this rock, paper, scissors,
is going to eat a giant squirt of it.
You say it differently, right?
Because in Australia you say--
- We would say scissors, paper, rock.
- Scissors, paper, rock, that just feels so weird.
- You guys say rock, paper, scissors, right?
- I'll go, we'll say scissors, paper, rock,
because that's cool.
- Ready?
- Yep. Scissors, paper, rock. Oh!
- Oh no!
- Alright, so now the moment has come, we're about to--
it just shot everywhere! It luckily didn't get on you.
Don't worry. But guys we also filmed a video on her channel
so make sure you guys click
right over here to check that out.
Also down in the description, and subscribe to her channel!
Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Three, two, one. Oh my gosh!
(screams)
Click here, click here, click here! Ahh!
Alright, bye!
- Bye!
- That was terrible.
(Wengie screams)
Holy cow that was intense.
(Wengie laughs)
- My nose!