- What's up everyone, it is Collins Key
and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Today I'm joined here with Teala.
- Hi.
- She has a beauty guru channel.
- Yes.
- I'm a big watcher of the beauty guru channels--
- Clearly--
- If you guys couldn't tell by the eyeliner.
- You're like winged eyeliner, you got some blush going on.
It's on point guys.
- I actually have no idea about
any of that stuff you just said.
Today we are doing two truths and
- [Together] One lie - Challenge.
How this challenge works.
- You say three things and two of them are truths
and one of them is a lie, and if we get the lie correct
then the person gets one point.
- Okay.
- And if the other person doesn't get that correct,
they lose.
- [Together] Oh!
- The winner gets to tweet something
off of the loser's phone.
Cool, let's do it.
I'm gonna go first.
I can do a double front flip.
I've been stung by a bee 14 times in a row.
And a fan tried to eat my key necklace at a meet and greet.
I tried to pick the best ones possible.
- What?
These are crazy.
You've not been stung by a bee 14--
- No, how did you get that?
- Really?
- What?
I should have gone for like six.
- 14 times, that's like, (laughing)
'cause like what if you were allergic,
you would've like died.
- Just like (convulses).
I got stung on my middle finger one time,
- Really?
- I didn't know what it was, so I was like whaaa.
- Yes, one point for Teala.
Okay, here's my turn.
I've been the same sue shies--
- [Together] Shoe shies?
- I've been the same sue--
- Haha, you did it again.
- I can't do it.
I've been the same shoe size since I was 12 years old.
I still have a Club Penguin account.
I had a pet hamster when I was nine years old.
- I've been like the same shoe size
since I was around that age, so I think
I'm gonna say that's a truth.
I think our feet develop faster.
I'm just making that up, I have actually no idea.
But actually-- - Actually, the fact is--
- You're actively on Club Penguin,
or you just never deleted, you're actively,
that's a lie, you're not actively on Club Penguin.
What the heck, is that for real?
- Yes, last time I was on Club Penguin
was like a month ago, but that's still pretty active.
- That's pretty active.
- No shame my people. - That's crazy.
- The lie was that I had a pet hamster.
I did not have a pet hamster.
- Okay so that's two points for Teala.
Man, I am losing.
I threw a rock and hit a car.
I was detained at the airport.
- What's detained?
- Like, taken in the backroom.
- Oh, okay.
- When I was eight years old, I fell out of a tree
because I was dressed as a tiger.
- I believe the last one.
It just sounds something that Collins would do.
- Hope this works.
- You didn't get detained at the airport.
- No, what the heck.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
- I am so good at this game.
- This is so sad.
- This is pathetic.
I'm allergic to cats.
I was afraid of the little troll in Dora.
When I was younger, I used to hate playgrounds.
Not hate them, but like I didn't like play on playgrounds.
- I don't even remember if there was a troll
in Dora the Explorer, so I--
- There was.
(whispers) There's a troll.
- I remember, like, Boots
(sings) Boots and Cats and Boots and Cats
and Boots and Cats and Boots and Cats.
I'm gonna go with you're allergic to cats.
Is that the lie?
- No, I am.
- No.
What the heck?
- The lie was that I hate playgrounds, I love playgrounds.
- That's what I thought,
I'm like, who doesn't love playgrounds?
- Should've went with your first instinct.
You have no points Collins.
- This is terrible.
- This is so bad
Come on Collins.
- I ran onstage and hugged Demi Lovato
in the middle of her show.
I once ate 22 full plates of food at breakfast.
I pushed my friend off the swings and he broke his arm.
- The lie is that you
hugged Demi in the middle of a show.
- Nope.
- Really?
- That is not a lie.
On the last show day,
I ran onstage in the middle of Demi's set
and I gave her a big hug.
- Oh I guess the lie is that
you pushed somebody off the swing.
- Yep.
- Dang it, I was gonna say that.
- Yes, one point.
- One point, one point.
- Turn up for one point.
I'm gonna put your little points over here,
I'm gonna make my one just like super big over here.
So it's very clear that I have one point.
I have one point.
All right, cool, your turn.
- I don't have an answering machine on my phone.
I was always afraid of Chucky from Rugrats.
I used to have a robot vacuum.
- Yeah, I'm gonna call the lie on that.
- The vacuum?
- Yes, is it?
You've gotta be kidding me.
- I had a robot vacuum.
- This is messed up--
- I literally had a ro, those like things
that like talk--
- I know, but like it was so random.
- That sounds so made up.
- I really hope this one stumps you
When I was young, we went camping and I got lost,
it took the park rangers three hours to find me.
I've gotten a back massage from a WWE fighter.
My dad proposed to my mom on their first date.
I so totally hope I get a point right now.
- You probably did get lost at camping.
Knowing Collins.
Your dad did not propose to your mom on the first date.
- Yep, he did.
- What?
- Yes, yeah yeah.
My dad is a straight-up boss, like on their first date,
he proposed to her and asked her to marry him.
- What, that's ama-, that's crazy,
I've never heard anything like that before.
- And like 20-something years later, here they are.
Two points, oh yeah, woo.
And the lie was that I got lost when I went camping.
- Really?
- Yep.
- I believed that.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause.
- 'Cause, you know--
- Collins is Collins--
- My favorite fact in that one was the fact
that I got a backrub from a WWE fighter.
Okay, your turn.
- I'm still not allowed to play with matches.
I used to have these, what I called, special rain boots,
I thought they like gave me good luck.
- Is that what you're wearing right now?
Are these your lucky rain boots?
- No.
- You said you had the same shoe size
since you were like nine or whatever,
so these could be the lucky rain boots right now.
- You never know guys.
- You never know these days.
- I really jumped far for that conclusion.
- You really did.
I can't have spicy foods,
like I don't like hot sauce and stuff.
- I think the lie is that you hate spicy foods,
I don't think they bother you.
Did I get it?
- Yeah, you got it.
- Yes, finally.
I kept a black widow spider as a pet.
I was Spiderman for Halloween.
And I've been bitten by a brown recluse spider,
which they're like super poisonous.
I tried to keep it all spider themed to really mess you up.
- Spider themed.
- Spiders.
- I want to say that the lie
is that you kept a black widow spider as a pet.
No, you got bitten by it, was that the lie?
You dressed like Spiderman is the lie?
What?
- Never for Halloween.
I dressed up as him on like normal days,
but not, never Halloween.
- What, that's even more random.
- I know.
- I dress up as Spiderman on normal days.
You kept a--
- A black widow spider as a pet and--
- Why would you ever?
- We actually kept, like, two, because one of them
we don't know what happened to it,
which is kinda scary.
But, we put it in like a jar.
And we would have to like, literally,
find flies around the house and with the jar,
unscrew the top and try to catch the fly under the jar.
If you guys enjoyed this challenge,
let me know by liking this video.
And also, I want you guys to comment down below
what other challenges would you love to see me do?
I did a video on Teala's channel.
- Check that out, it's really funny.
- It's pretty spiffy.
I'll put the link like right in front of her face.
It's like magic, what?
- It's magic everybody.
- Make sure you guys, of course,
subscribe to this channel.
- That's so cool.
- Yeah.
Once again, I'm Collins Key, this was Teala Dunn
This still is Teala Dunn, I don't know about was.
Peace.
(electronic music)