- Let's see this watermelon turned into jelly.
Three, two, one!
You challenged us to make spaghetti noodles out of juice
and right now, let's go.
To turn this juice into noodles.
We have to use what's called sodium alginate.
We're gonna use two teaspoons right here.
And what if they work immediately.
Like the moment it hits,
and then we're gonna be blending these up,
and then we're gonna be turning them into noodles.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh, there we go.
Like a little smoothie almost.
My guy has a little hat, oops.
And done.
Alright, it got super thick.
Wait, is yours as thick as mine?
- It's really milky!
- We're gonna dump them out and let 'em sit
and that should get rid of a lot of the bubbles.
This looks delicious, it's turning into sludge, man.
- Dude, mine got rid of all the bubbles.
- And mine got even more bubbly, it seems like.
Next up, we got huge trays of water right here,
so we're gonna put this on top.
The final thing we need is calcium chloride,
and this stuff looks super crazy.
It's like a whole bunch of little balls, check this out.
Now, we're gonna mix 'em up.
Wait a minute bro, mine are like all gone,
they're fully dissolved - Oh yeah!
So now it's time to add in the juice.
So, we're just gonna suck off some of this juice right
(painful groaning)
Oh, that's so cool!
Yours looks way better than mine,
Mine did not go that well. - Oh yeah!
- Now the moment that this juice hits
the surface of the liquid,
it will immediately turn into the noodles, aight here we go,
- [Both] Ready, set, go!
Oooooh, what!
- [Devan] Wait, I can't even see mine!
- It turned into noodles!
Does that mean that yours don't work,
or maybe they will work , we just can't see them yet.
- Oh, man.
Oh, that popped off.
Dude, I wanna see if I can get
a couple of little drops going in.
So here we go, a little drop right there.
Here we go, gonna go underneath the surface here,
just like this.
It's like a streamer!
Three, two, one, oooh
- How does it feel, dude?
- All the little bubbles in it, man.
- It's weirdly spongy.
Yo, what if we take a whole bunch of this stuff
and just pop it in, right there
- [Both] Ooooh.
- [Collins] It's no longer liquidy,
it's kind of separating from my fingers a little bit.
Dude, it's kinda like a jelly fish,
like especially if you put the little legs on it,
and the real questions is, how did yours turn out man.
Let's see how it goes, ready?
- [Devan] Woah!
- [Collin] They worked!
- [Devan] No way!
- [Collin] Those look insane!
- [Devan] Wow!
- [Collin] Bro, those look like real noodles!
- Look at how long this noodle is.
Time to see how these noodles taste.
W-w-wait, we'll be doing this at the end of the video,
and right now, we're onto the next one.
- Oh, I can't wait.
- You challenged us to make
a healthy jelly watermelon,
so let's go.
Yo, dude, alright, now it's time
to gut these things out
and turn them into some hollow watermelons.
- [Both] Oooooh.
- [Devans] Dude, that's a whole bunch of it.
- Look at that, bro.
- You can hear bubbling.
- Wait, why is it bubbling though?
- Cause I got a potato masher in here, bro.
- Here we go, gotta mix it up a little bit
Oh boy, it's shooting up, oh boy, okay, here we go.
Dude, you made like watermelon soup in there, almost.
- Yeaaaah.
- Dude, try taking a little drink from it,
that looks so good.
Time to dunk out the melons, I'll go first.
Here we go, three, two, one,
- [Both] Wooh, yeah!
- [Collins] The watermelons are gutted,
and now it's time to create the gelatinous substance.
We're gonna be using agar-agar,
or agg-ar agg-ar, I don't know.
- Powder. - [Collin] You need
some water, oops, little bit too much, little bit too much,
alright there we go, ooh boy,
that's a lot, okay, whew.
Alright last one right here,
you know that should be about good.
Perfect, and now we gotta heat it up and mix it.
But in the meantime, it's time to mash up some watermelons.
Oh, for the juice, man.
Just gotta mash down like this,
so the goal, we wanna get as much of the juice
out of the melons as we possibly can.
Alright lt's see how this stuff is turning out.
- [Devan] That's gonna mix with the watermelon?
- Yeah, how is this really gonna work, man,
I'm kind of confused right now.
Next up, we gotta strain out these bowls,
but I gotta move my watermelon
off to the side over here, like this.
Three, two, one, midair,
- [Both] Oooh!
- [Collins] Yes!
I saw that going a lot worse in my head.
Now it's time to add in the agar
and turn this into gelatinous goodness.
Just gonna put it in like this.
I think yours might actually work better,
mines gotten pretty thick, I gotta say.
I wanna see if the agar's gonna mix in
with the watermelon juice or not
'cause mine's staying rather clumpy right now
- [Devan] Yeah, I know.
Right now, it really doesn't mix at all.
- [Collin] Wait, wait, wait,
these look like hardened chunks of agar
- We may have missed a step.
- Dude this stuff is not dissolving at all,
so you know what, I think the solution
is to pop it back into the pan over here,
and then reheat it all,
so, no no no, I'm talking about
all of the juices, everything.
Yo, dude, it totally worked,
the agar is now melted into the watermelon juice.
So be very careful with this,
and do not try this at home.
- [Both] Three, two.
- [Collins] Five second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel, both notifications
in five seconds, you ready?
Here we go,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one, done.
And if you can do that, comment down below,
Keyper squad, right now,
- [Both] Ready, set, go, aaaah!
- Oh no, no, no. - Oh!
- [Collins] That was catastrophic.
- Oh, oh, oh
It's overflowing?
- Wait, is it already filled up,
I guess so, I guess so, here we go,
we're just gonna lift it up a little bit.
Yo, it just got plugged in the bottom, somehow.
Just tilt it in, a little bit, here we go, like this.
Time to close this off, we'll be eating them
at the very end of the video.
You challenged us to make edible glow-in-the-dark slime,
so right now, let's go.
Vitamins were made to glow in the dark.
Next up, we do eight teaspoons of psyllium husk.
Alright, well there's a little rinky dink teaspoon.
I guess, we'll get a whole bunch of those here.
'kay next up, we need the water,
then we're gonna get, kinda like the high pour on it.
I'm going for the low, safe pour,
Woah, dude.
- Oopsie.
Here we go, low pour, like that.
Here we go, ta-dah.
Nice and civil over here.
we're gonna mix it up a bit.
- Why is mine like, so congealed already?
Dude, your hand.
- Yeah, I know. - Turn it around,
it looks really funky. - I know.
- Is this what it's supposed to look like right now, man?
'cause yours is all watery, bro.
You know what mine needs to fix it, Devan?
- Water. - Nope!
More vitamins, so let's see this.
oh, wow, oh wow!
The mixture right now is just,
sorry, I'm trying to do two things,
I'm not ambidextrous.
I can't do two things at the same time.
- Woaaah!
- Let's see, we're gonna put this here.
- So now, it's about to fling everywhere, dude!
I don't even know why, oh my.
- Vitamins are in, so now let's mix it all up.
(pounding)
And then just.
Alright, so we add it onto the hot plate like this.
- You're using the pan, you know, right.
- Okay sorry, gotta get it off this thing right here,
so let's plop it in here like this.
Can I have some more water,
I think that's really what it needs.
I think you were right from the beginning.
And the coolest is that we get to eat this, bro!
- You're excited to eat that!
- Now it's time to turn this into slime,
so we gotta turn this up,
as it boils, it's going to turn into slime.
- [Both] Oooh!
- [Collins] Okay, okay, I see you.
Dude, look at this!
Oh man, it's definitely getting a lot more slimy,
that's for sure.
The heat is turned off,
and now it's time to pour this onto our frozen marble slab.
- How is this thing gonna glow in the dark?
I can't wait to see how this turns out.
(Collins screaming)
- [Both] Ready, set, go!
- [Collins] Oh man, it's coming out.
Dude, what?
- [Devan] This is not a pretty slime.
- We gotta cool this thing down quick.
The real question is, is it going to glow in the dark,
and how is it going to taste?
we'll be trying it at the end.
- [Devans] You challenged us to make
glow-in-the-dark oobleck out of potatoes.
And do not try this at home.
- The potatoes are peeled,
and now it's time to dice these things up.
- [Both] Oooh!
- [Collins] Bro, this shot out.
I've learned this cubing technique
from all the cooking shows I've watched, man,
'cause this is exactly how they do it, man.
Time to dump it all in, so here we go,
gonna balance it up like this,
dump it in just like that.
Boom, and now we're on to the next step.
Yo, these got super murky,
so right now, we gotta strain out the potatoes
and get to that good old juice.
- [Devan] I think I got it, I think I got it.
- Yeah, the biggest thing is that we need
the starch from the potatoes,
so that's what we're doing with this process.
Next up, we're gonna use this strainer right here,
over the top like this,
three, two one,
- [Both] Ooooh!
- [Devan] Just a little bit has overflowed.
- Yep, just a smidge, nothing too crazy,
there we go, boom,
and now, I've got the ice laden potato starch,
and now it's time to make the oobleck.
All the way to the top.
Here we go, almost there.
The potato starch is all settled at the bottom,
and that's what's gonna be the oobleck
so now we gotta pour out the liquid at the top.
Wait, why is it dripping down the side?
I gotta go very slowly right now.
- [Devan] I got it. - And done,
okay, there we go, boom.
- I wonder if it turns into oobleck
the moment it hits the bowl.
- It really is oobleck.
- [Devan] No way! - Dude!
Here we go, ready,
- [Both] Set, go!
- [Collins] Dude, it doesn't mix, it's fully oobleck!
For those of you who are new to oobleck,
basically it's a substance that's a liquid when you hold it,
but it's solid when you hit it.
Yo, wait, I just realized this is fully edible!
- [Devan] Dude, you're right!
- Oh man, we can give it a try
and see if the oobleck actually tastes any good on this one.
I can't wait to see if this oobleck glows in the dark,
and of course, to see how it tastes.
We'll be doing that at the end of the video,
and we're on to the next one.
You challenged us to turn orange juice
into a delicious, frozen delight, so let's go.
Just gonna fill up my baggie
with some orange juice right now.
Here we go, Devan, if I hold mine like this,
can you pour a little but more into it,
- [Devan] Yeaaaah!
- A little bit more, more, more, more, more, done, done.
I can't seal it bro,
you've left me in a very precarious situation.
- [Devan] Alright, here we go.
- Dude, you gotta get some of it,
pull out just like that.
Oh snap bro, little bit more, into yours?
Alright, so now let's see if I can close it up.
- Did you get it? - No!
- I got it, I got it, I got it!
- You got it?
next up, we got the ice, just gonna add this in,
so here we, uh oh.
- Maybe we should help each other out.
- Yeah, okay, yeah, that's a good idea, Devan.
Teamwork is the dreamwork.
- [Devan Why do you make it so difficult?
- Why do you keep raising it up, Devan, Devan.
- So I can catch it!
- Flawless.
Alright, so now it's time for me to add my salt in,
so here we go, I'm gonna fill up the spoon first,
and the reason the salt is in here
is to actually speed up the freezing process.
It's time to add in our bag of orange juice.
Devan, smash!
(drumming)
Next up, I've got an innovative idea,
I'm gonna coat my bag in salt, right now,
so pop that in there.
So if I have any extra salt here,
just gonna dump this on right now.
Now gonna lift this up and pop this into the bag.
Now it's time to mix it up and shake it up,
so here we go, turn it up like this,
and then just
(Collin screaming)
Salt in my eye!
I smacked-ed-ed it.
And then boom!
Aah, I'm gone!
Dude, I think that my bag is broken up in the inside.
Drop it from hand to hand
and just really mix it up, here we go.
There is no more bag, it is all one.
- It really has kinda filled up,
and I think your bag popped.
- Ohh, wait which one?
- [Devan] I think it's working.
- Oh, dude, dude.
And now let's see if this actually worked, bro.
Yours looks amazing.
Mine, questionable at best.
How did all the juice escape the middle bag
and leak into the second bag?
Alright, here we go,
just gonna have to pick it up,
lift, and drip, and drop, and go.
- [Both] Ooooh!
- [Collins] Yeah, and then get a little bit
of juice out of there.
- It actually kinda worked!
- No way!
- Other than the big leak in it.
- [Both] Oooh!
(laughing and screaming)
- [Collins] Bro, but I spilled over your lap, dude.
But let's see if it turned into a frozen delicacy.
- [Both] Oooh.
- [Collins] Ooh, no way!
That looks so delicious.
We'll be eating this at the end of the video,
and right now, we're on to the next one.
You challenged us to try sushi art.
- [Devan] First up, I'm gonna slice up some carrot.
- And as you do that, I'm gonna make
my green, spicy, wasabi rice, right now.
Ooh, I can smell it bro.
It's making my eyes water already.
- Oh yeah.
Dude, we just started, why are you using your hands?
- The chopsticks weren't doing good enough
so I gotta get my hands in there and you know,
make it all green and make it all good.
Art is important, Devan,
and hands on art is the best kinda art.
Alright, gonna add a big chunk
of the wasabi rice right here, boom.
I call this the splat and pat.
Splat and pat.
- My carrots are done,
and now it's on to the nori sheet.
- Is that like, too much rice, you think?
- Uh, yes.
Now I'm gonna wrap my carrots in some nori sheet.
- My panda's gonna have some red eyes,
it's gonna be a fusion panda,
it's gonna be a red panda
with some black spots on it.
Game changing idea!
The cucumber's going to be the mouth.
Alright here we go, gonna take the cucumber,
and very carefully, gonna slice of a side
over here like this.
And last but not least, we got this last side over here.
- Some might think this is a tongue,
but nope, that's the whole mouth.
- We're gonna take the beet,
and first of all, we're gonna drop the beat.
(funky dubstep)
- Nice. - Thank you.
- Time to wrap my second carrot in a nori sheet.
- That's a pretty juicy beet right here.
Oh, man, alright, it's all red on the inside,
which is perfect for what I need.
Check this out, I'm gonna take this thing of beet,
and I'm gonna insert it inside the cucumber
so there's a tongue inside of the mouth
'cause Devan doesn't have that, so I'm gonna win.
Gonna put a little hole here at the top,
this is where the beet's gonna go.
Yes, boom!
Yes!
I've like, conquered this challenge so far,
and my art challenge is going through three-dimensional.
Alright, time to roll up the first layer.
Okay, I need a second nori sheet.
- It actually kinda works, dude, look at that.
- I'm gonna smash my beet, all right, here we go.
Oh boy.
Oh yeah, this turned to some nice pink rice, man.
Yo, the pink rice is totally working.
The only issue is that I forgot to take off
the chunks of beet.
Three, two, one, splat and pat, pat, pat, pat, pat.
Gonna give it a little bit of ridge
in the center just like this.
I'm gonna have to use these nori sheets
to create some dark eyes and some stark contrast.
Art words.
- [Devan] You're really picking up this artist thing.
- Oh no, my panda's opening up.
Alright here we go, gonna fold like this,
and then gonna lay it down like this,
press it in, press it in, boom, perfectamundo!
Alright, just gonna pack it down with rice
here at the the top of it, man.
Just gotta keep the nori sheet down, right now.
Aight, boom, eyes are in place.
So add a beet nose, which you probably
won't be even able to tell
in the final result, doesn't matter.
Here we go, last but not least,
we got the mouth.
Here we go, gotta push the mouth down a little bit,
boom!
Gonna pop this over the top here
and just gonna kinda mold this one here.
It's called triangle sushi.
All in the name of art,
so my top sheet is kinda crumbling a little bit.
And to get this really in state,
you really just gotta combine the hands like this.
Here we go, boom.
Alright, gonna move my triangle sushi off to the side.
Now for the final step here, gotta take out my green rice
to finish up my panda art, here we go.
Real question, how is that gonna be wrapped up in that.
The thing about art, you never ask questions,
you just do it.
The real question is how I'm gonna eat this in one bite?
Gonna do a side rollover, here we go.
Boom, side rollover upside-down triangle!
Boom, there we go, mine is done!
Oh snap!
I can't wait to cut it open,
see what it looks like on the inside.
Bro, you're taking forever, man.
Dude, that is huge, and it's got
a ton of spicy wasabi in it.
We're gonna cut these open.
You get to comment down below
whose panda you think turned out better.
We'll be eating them at the end of the video.
You challenged us to turn milk into rock art,
so right now, let's go.
Step one, we gotta heat up the milk
and do not try this at home.
The goal is to heat it up
right before the part it where it actually starts to boil.
But we're gonna be adding in the vinegar
and the milk has a crazy reaction.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Oh, dude, look at it,
immediately, immediately.
Dude, it's like curdling!
Wait, it's like totally separating!
Next, I'm gonna strain out all the excess liquid
and get the curds inside the milk.
So Devan, we're gonna pick this up and go very slowly,
- [Devan] Very carefully.
- [Collin] And be very careful, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, ooooh.
- [Collins] Dude, I nailed it, bro.
Here we go, just going to strain out here.
Oh, man, dude it's all jiggly and funky lookin', bro.
Bro, looks like its own little ball of cheese right now,
like goat cheese, or something, man.
It's milk, and milk comes from cheese.
- Milk does not come from cheese.
- Sorry, its the other way around.
Next up, we gotta get the last bit of liquid out of these.
So here we go, just gonna place them down right here.
- [Devan] Oh man, it's so warm.
- All right, and now it's time to make the art
and fill these molds.
I don't know if we even have enough for this.
All right, here, just gonna pull it down
and press it in a little bit.
This is gonna create some really cool art,
and the best thing is that after this sits for a while,
it turns rock hard, like you can't break it.
Comment down below whose you think
is gonna turn out better.
We'll be testing them at the end of the video
and we're on to the next round.
You challenge us to make a vegetable trumpet,
so right now, let's go.
So here we go, boom, the body of a trumpet.
If you're doing this at home, be very careful.
The next step, gotta make it hollow.
And for mine, I've got this little white
Christmas tree looking thingy over here.
And this here, Devan,
Qthis is traditional cucumber coring techniques, bro.
This is how the ancients did it, man.
- The ancients?
- People who've been around a long time.
Maybe if I rotate it all the way out,
oh, it's dripping out juice, okay, here we go.
(groaning)
- [Collins] There we go!
- Yeah, I think mine's cored, look at that.
- [Collin] It's like a telescope, bro.
- [Devan] So next up, you put the carrot in like this,
you gotta mark an inch out, just like this,
- Here we go, we got the two things here,
and just kinda wee.
So now, just gonna put the two coring things
together like this and it's a little bag, Devan.
You hit the mall, you know.
Ooh, I made it through!
Innovation, core through one side over here,
oooh no!
Bro, it breached the side of it.
I hope this doesn't ruin the trumpet, bro.
All right, next up, I have to hollow out the carrot.
Oh jeez, there we go.
The cucumber has a huge slit on the side of this now.
Lemme see.
I'm gonna have to cover that.
In an attempt to rescue my cucumber,
I brought along some nori sheets for sushi.
Just gonna go and lather it up a little bit.
Get a little bit of liquid on it,
and I'm gonna use this to seal the opening.
Gonna slice open the bell pepper, yum!
- All right, I think my mouth piece is done.
Now it's time to put it in the cucumber.
Yeah, look at that, dude.
All right, gotta cut off a little bit here at the back,
and Devan, be very careful when doing this at home,
cut off a little amount.
This is where the cucumber's gonna go, okay.
- Now it's time to see if my cucumber fits,
and no, not quite.
And I might have messed up already.
- Oh dude!
- I mean, look at that.
- That is definitely not your best work, Devan,
I gotta say.
- Hey, let's find out if this really
plays like a trumpet, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- [Collins] Oh you know, we should actually try
this at end of the video,
so right now, we're on to the next one.
We've got all the food hacks,
it's time to test to see if they actually worked.
We've got the slime, and now it's time to see
if it actually glows in the dark,
and of course, we gotta find out how this stuff tastes.
So right now, let's turn off the lights
- [Both] Yoo!
- [Collins] Dude, this fully glows in the dark,
dude, this is crazy!
- [Devan] This looks so cool!
I had no clue vitamins glow in the dark.
Dude, if this stuff glows,
I wonder if it's gonna taste any good.
Well these things definitely glow in the dark,
and they look so cool,
but now, let's see if they taste as good as they look.
I guess we'll go for a bite at the same time.
You ready? - [Devan] Alright, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, oooh.
- [Collins] Wait if you wanna win
a fifteen minute video call with Devan and I,
text the word "try" to 81800 right now,
so pause the video and text the word "try"
to 81800 and you'll automatically be entered
in to win, and right now,
let's see how this tastes.
- [Both] Three, two, one, ooooh.
- [Devan] And it's like, weirdly spicy.
- Oh man, not a fan.
Just cause it's edible, doesn't mean it's good.
All right, we got the juice noodles
and dude, these things would taste so crazy.
- All right, here we go.
- [Both] Ooooh.
- [Collins] Man, I'm dropping chunks.
I'm just gonna take a bite out of it
and you're gonna go next.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Devan] How does it taste?
- They're actual noodles, but like juice flavored.
I mean all in all, those were super bizarre.
Like, I don't know if I liked it or not.
- All right, here we go.
Oh, and these things were liquid on the inside,
dude, I wonder if it stayed the way.
- I don't know, man, you should try
taking a bite of it though. - I know.
Three, two, one.
- Oh, they crunched!
What they're not good? - Uh uh.
They're coated in something weird.
- Oh, oh!
- And the apple juice doesn't really help.
- Yo, those were disgusting.
Time to reveal the sushi art
and see how these things taste,
so here we go, ready,
- [Both] Three, two, one!
- [Collins] Let's see if we just give this
a nice little slice here.
Oh boy.
- [Both] Oooh!
- [Devan] Oh, that smells horrible,
- [Collin] Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait,
here we go, there you have it.
I think it's upside down.
It's meant to be that way.
Three, two, one.
Bro, I think you nailed it perfectly.
I wonder if.
- [Both] Oooooh!
- [Collins] The wasabi rice came off!
No no no no no no!
It's looking crazy.
- [Devan] Three, two, one
- [Both] Oh yeah!
- [Collins] Bro, even this one,
even this one looks like a little panda!
You nailed it bro!
- [Devan] Wait, he actually kinda looks a lil' sad.
- We got the sushi, let's see how it tastes.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(painful groaning)
(agonizing Wailing)
- Whoa.
(incomprehensible mumbling)
- I've got the magic, man,
and now it's time to see if it glows in the dark,
and also how it tastes.
Now let's turn off the lights and see if
this glows in the dark.
(crying of wonder)
- [Devan] Dude, this is so crazy.
What, this looks awesone!
- [Collins] And in the blacklight,
it looks really crazy, man, cause the way it falls.
(shouting)
- [Devan] It looks like some sort of creamy delight.
- [Collin] It smells like an alien substance.
- [Both] Ready, set, go!
- [Devan] Oh!
Whoa, that's kinda sweet.
- Ohh, what is going on?
It's bizarre cause like, I take a bite out of it,
and it like, falls out of your mouth.
I recommend you never eat this one.
We've got a frozen orange delight right here.
Let's see how this tastes, we're gonna pop it open, woaah!
Oh yeah!
Here we go, take a big spoonful like this,
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Ow, it's so good but like, so cold.
- That's so good!
- I wanna see if yours is colder than mine, though.
- Okay, all right, it's decided dude, wow.
- All right, we've got the vegetable trumpets,
and now it's time to see if they really make some music.
Who'll go first, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(Collins blowing veggie trumpet)
- Sounds like a really frustrated man.
(blowing veggie trumpet)
Collin, it sounds like you're yelling into the trumpet,
not playing it.
All right, here we go, ready, set, go.
(Devan blowing veggie trumpet)
- Oh man, I can't tell if that's your spit,
or the actual stuff coming out the cucumber.
- Seed.
- Did you like inhale a seed?
- Yeah, I did!
- We got the rock-hard milk,
and let's see if it actually turned rock hard.
- Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oooh.
- [Collins] Dude, wait wait wait wait wait,
before you touch it, it's time for me to get mine out.
Three, two, one,
how did my crab fall apart?
- It's a lobster.
- Let's see if it's actually rock-solid.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Devan] Mine is!
- Mine's like all crumbly.
- It's a little crown!
- Let's see if this watermelon turned into jelly!
- [Both] Three, two, one!
(crashing)
(screaming in wonder)
- Oh my god, dude.
Dude, it like, totally broke apart,
but the watermelon's like stuck
inside on the rind, right now.
Now it's more like sandpaper.
It's not as smooth as I would have liked,
but look, it's breaking open.
Oh my gosh, it's so satisfying!
That looks so cool!
Oh snap, it's such a big chunk and it's so jiggly!
All right, well mine totally works,
let's see what yours looks like.
- [Devan] All right, here we go.
- [Both] Oooh!
- [Collins] Yo, dude that looks so cool.
- [Devan] It looks so awesome!
- [Collin] Dude, it looks like it's gonna taste amazing.
- Mine is breaking off.
- Oh no, there's a little but of funkiness to mine,
and I just wanna see if it's juggle-able.
Wait dude, can I hold it?
- [Devan] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wanna try for a second.
Oh my gosh, it's like totally see-through, too.
This is so wild!
- Dude, this turned out so cool!
- I know!
Let's see how these stuff tastes, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two.
- [Collins] Oh wait, oh yeah,
we just launched our brand new Keyper club
and if you become a member,
you'll get exclusive access to live streams,
merch discounts, loyalty badges, custom emojis,
and exclusive content you won't see anywhere else,
so click the top link in the description right now
to claim your membership,
and let's see how this stuff tastes.
Here we go, and actually, you know what,
I'm gonna use this one here, so
- [Both] Ready, set, go!
Whoa!
- [Collins] Dude! - [Devan] Oh my goodness!
It comes out so easily.
- It is completely watermelon flavor man,
this is absolutely delicious.
Well thank you so much for watching.
Comment down below what is your favorite food
you would love to see us use for a hack
and if you wanna see another video, click right over here.
You've got five seconds, here we go,
- [Both] Five, four,
three, two, one, done.
- [Collins] Love you, - [Both] bye!