(toy horn)
(laughs)
Well, what's up guys?
It's Collins Key,
and welcome to the Thursday Vlog.
It's gonna be a very different video today,
as you can tell,
and to start things off,
I need someone very special to help me out.
So, everyone, please welcome to the, uh, adjacent chair,
Devan Keys.
Ay!
- What's up?
- So, yeah. Welcome to the video, and today--
- I thought he was going for a little handshake, but nope.
(toy horn)
- A hand--
- Nope.
- Left him hangin'.
There we go, and then hit him with a (toy horn)
For today's video,
it's going to be, like I said, a little bit different.
I was actually inspired
by some other Youtubers to go to the 99-cent store,
which I've never done before,
get a whole bunch of random products there.
And now, basically,
I'm just going to test them out
and see whether or not they work
or do what they're supposed to do
because they're from the 99-cent store,
so I don't know if that changes the quality of 'em at all.
(toy horn)
And also,
make sure you guys watch til the very end
because at the very end,
I'm going to post some bloopers and outtakes
from this video.
So, make sure you guys give this video
a big thumbs up
if you're excited to see
what random things we've gotten.
And, yeah.
Let's jump into the video.
So, we're going to be starting off with a bang,
and we're going to be--
the party poppers with confetti.
- I didn't know you'd be going that fast.
(laughs)
- Let's see if this is a--
Oh!
Well, it opens very easily.
I gotta say that.
There's this gun round cartridge,
and then the party popper.
Dude, wait, wait, wait.
I don't even know what we're doing.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
We have to be like, coordinated.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- I'm moving faster than you.
- Dude, you don't even know what you're doing.
- Oww!
That actually hurt, dude! Oww!
- There's no face shots.
But a nut shot.
- Oww!
(laugh)
You are a savage.
- No face!
You shot at my face!
(laugh)
- Oh well! My bad!
- Dangerous!
- Do it again! Do it again!
(laugh)
Alright,
well the verdict on
this first party popper gun with confetti.
- They're awesome.
- This was amazing.
- If you go to shoot each other in the face.
- Now, the next item is a golf club,
and these are very plastic.
They look pretty cheap and they feel pretty cheap.
Like, you can just like-- (yelling)
And just like break it.
But we're gonna go outside and test them out for sure.
- You're not gonna win.
(laughs)
- Yeah, let's go do it.
Teeing up for the shot.
He's placing his golf ball
on the proper position for him to be able to
hit the golf ball at a relatively high speed.
There is a, umm, 400 mile an hour wind
coming at us in this direction.
- Gotta shake my booty.
No!
(laugh)
- You missed so bad.
- Oh, gosh.
I gotta get myself out of the way.
- Yeah!
- You totally--you suck!
Hole in one!
I win!
- These are a fail.
- Yeah, I gotta say these are kind of a fail.
Umm, and look at these.
They like, they break so--
It's like a nun chuck that's like-- (screeches)
So, yeah.
These are are definitely a fail, guys.
Next, we have very masculine glow sticks.
What are you doing?
So, umm, yeah.
Let's see if these work, or if these completely fail.
- Oh, it smells so bad.
- Yup!
This is definitely not chemical or toxic.
And now, to finish it all off.
Ta-da!
- Sword fight!
- Whoa, dude! Chill! I am zee winner!
I gotta say I'm a little bit disappointed
that this part here doesn't actually glow.
I thought this was gonna be like
a glowy thing in and of itself.
Overall, the verdict is a fail.
(play fighting)
This is actually a really pointy tip. I probably--
- Stop!
- So, this next one
is one of the only items Devan picked out,
and you'll know why for a reason.
I don't-- what is--
Would you explain to them why you got that?
- He told me to pick a brand.
(laugh)
- Like, what is this?
- Apparently, it's to hold clothes.
- I guess, let's go for it.
So, we were going to try this product out inside on drywall
which is what it is intended for,
but we wanted to go above and beyond for this video,
so we've got this, umm, this wood over here.
It's a nice, solid wood.
We're gonna try it out.
These are like razors almost.
So, let's see.
I'm gonna just try to put this in the wall real quick.
It doesn't penetrate the wood
as easily as I thought it would, but, umm, there we go.
It's kinda-- It's kinda in there.
Actually, we don't have a hammer with us right now,
so Devan--
- Found a rock in the house.
- Take it away.
(hammering)
- So, now we have this thing,
which I think we just stick that there.
- Oh, perfect.
- Perfect!
Exactly how it was intended to be used.
Let's give it a shot.
Hey!
- It works!
- It actually worked!
Holy cow!
Alright, cool.
So, yea.
I give this a, umm, a 10 out of 5.
This is a 10 out of 5 right here.
'Cause look at this.
You can-- Oh!
Next item is called the power ball gun!
Ooh!
And it comes with targets and everything,
but we all know what I'm gonna use as target practice.
- Not my face!
- I think how it works is you pull it back like this--
- Lame.
That was lame.
- This is--
Okay, so this product is right off the bat,
this is-- 'cause if you don't put your hand here,
it just falls right out,
so this product is a massive fail.
- And next up,
we have hand drums.
Yay!
Man, I'm gettin' purple!
- First of all,
I gotta say that this is not really a hand drum,
'cause there is--look at this compared to my hand.
Like, this fits in my hand.
- Mad beats!
(laughs)
- Mad flow!
- You look so funny with--
They're not a win,
but they're not a fail.
And the only other product that Devan bought is--
- No. No.
- Yes.
- This is actually something that he bought,
and just really wanted to try it out.
(laughs)
- No way, dude!
Regardless of whose idea it was,
which it was his, let's get into it.
- It was actually his.
- Let's do it.
- Whatever.
- It's basically like a picture
with just a whole bunch of numbers on it,
and there's like different--I feel like a magician.
So, we were gonna do this
until we found out that sparkles are involved.
- Get that outta here!
(grunting)
- We are not a fan of sparkles!
This was a massive fail.
We are not a fan of this
because it included sparkles.
Big, big fail.
So, onto the next one.
I forgot, Devan did get one more thing.
He comes up to me, he's like,
"I don't know what this is."
It's a toilet freshener.
(laughs)
He literally brought me a toilet freshener.
(sniffing)
And it smells
like one of those disgusting porta-potties.
Look--smell it.
- No!
- It's totally disgusting. Yes.
- That's so gross.
- You were the one who bought it.
Okay? Smell it.
Smell it.
(gasping and coughing)
This is a massive fail.
I don't know why you would want your toilet
to smell like another toilet.
So, this is a massive fail.
Now, for this next one, we're gonna be makin' some noise!
We're testing out, umm, the trumpet
and a whole bunch of flutes.
(toy trumpet)
You sounded like a dying duck just now.
(laughs)
Go for it.
- I can't, man. I'm laughing too hard.
(toy trumpet)
- There you go!
- Ay!
- What were you doing? You were like (toy trumpet)
(laughs)
(toy trumpet)
- I was not!
(toy whistle)
- It's like really late right now,
and people are trying to sleep.
(toy whistle)
(laughs)
And these are definitely a win.
(toy trumpet)
- That's not as bad as the whistle.
- Yeah, so--
(toy whistle)
(laugh)
- He's just not good at blowin' things.
So, for me, the verdict is, these are a huge win.
These are a massive win.
- No.
(toy trumpet)
Fail.
(laugh)
So, next up are something called "wall walkers,"
which are basically little blue men that are--
look how disturbing these things are.
Look at this!
Like, you could literally pull them apart, and-- oww!
- Ay!
- Whoa!
- Hey!
- They're all-- see, yeah.
They are walking.
That's really cool.
Okay.
Look at this one right over here.
Whoa!
Oh!
Ah, man.
He died.
Oh, no, he's alive!
Okay, these are actually a massive win.
- No look.
- Yeah, that was nice.
- Did it work?
- Yup.
- Whoo!
- Now, this final item is the most expensive item.
It is actually a dollar, 29.
They are rockets, so let's open 'em up.
I think these are gonna be, like,
too explosive to do inside,
so we are gonna go outside and try 'em out right now.
But, umm-- (squeaking)
I like the sound of it so far.
So, yeah. Let's go try em out!
(laughs)
Oh, man!
This is the rocket test. Ready, aim, fire!
Ah! Dude!
- Oh. Are you good to go?
(Bleep)
- And now,
to settle this once and for all, the quick draw.
Two steps, ready, and begin!
The final verdict
on the most expensive item in this video
is that they were a win.
We had fun with these.
Don't point that at my face.
Please stop.
Ah!
- That's right.
- No!
Not again!
What are you doing, you crazy man?
Ah, no, what are you doing?
Okay, yes.
So, umm, if you guys enjoyed this video,
please give it a thumbs up right now.
Dude, this stuff is so nasty and, like, so toxic.
And also, share with your friends
if you guys want me to make even more just, like,
randomly testing out products and items video.
Umm, dude, you're done.
And also, comment down below what other random items
you guys want me to use in, umm, in upcoming videos.
Dude, stop!
You're getting my computer.
Dude, my computer!
And also,
make sure you guys check out all of Devan's links.
His links are all down in the description below.
So, be sure to go follow him
on all of his platforms,
and the Keeper of the Week is Becky, aka Living Musically.
I love you so much, Becky.
You are always super active
and you are such a hardcore keeper.
So, shout out to you, fam.
We love you so much,
and if you want to be the Keeper of the Week,
and be featured in one of my videos,
all you have to do:
just be super active on Twitter,
on Instagram, on Snapchat, on Youtube,
liking, sharing, commenting.
Basically, the more active you are,
the better chance you have
of being featured as the Keeper of the Week.
But again, congratulations, Becky.
We love you.
Oh, dude, chill!
Thank you so much for watching,
and make sure you guys subscribe!
Yay! We held them in our hands. That was a terrible idea.
- Oh, man!
- Alright.
Cool.
See you guys again next week.
Love you.
Bye.
Ah!
(bleep)
- Not the face, not the face!
- Okay.
We're done, we're done, we're done, we're done, we're done.
Ay!
Chill!
I'll see you guys again next Thursday.
Bye!
Ah!
Geez!
You're scarin' me! (bleep)
Here is the aftermath. Look at all this.