- What's up guys.
It's Collins Key, and welcome to the Thursday Vlog.
Now as you guys know,
April Fools' Day is right around the corner
and you guys don't really know this side of me,
but on April Fools' Day,
ever since I've been a little kid,
I've always been crazy mischievous.
I've always planned these crazy elaborate pranks
to pull on my parents on April Fools' Day,
and it was the one day, no matter how crazy it was,
I never got in trouble.
It was awesome.
Today I'm actually doing something that magicians,
we're not really supposed to do.
I'm actually gonna reveal to you five
of my top favorite April Fools' pranks.
These are easy things, fun things.
You can do this with stuff around your house.
Don't have to go out and buy anything.
Oh, and one more thing,
I just saw a screening of DreamWorks Home,
and it was such a cute movie. Oh my God.
It actually comes out this Friday, March 27th, in theaters.
So you guys gotta go check it out.
But without further ado,
I'd say let's just jump into these top five crazy pranks.
Let's do it.
Prank number one.
I call this one the die in toilet prank.
Now this one doesn't actually have to do
with you dying in the toilet because that would suck.
This one actually has to do with food coloring.
Remove the lid from the toilet,
and I found that Jell-O works the best for this.
Open up a pack of Jell-O and pour it in.
This might not be enough, so open up another pack of Jell-O,
pour that in, and one more pack,
because you know, we're awesome.
Grab out a whisk and whisk away.
Whisk, whisk, whisk. It's pretty fun.
Now you gotta put the lid back on and you're ready to go.
Now when someone goes to flush the toilet,
they're gonna be in for quite a surprise.
And let's just say the people coming in after,
they might be, um, wondering what just happened.
Prank number two.
This is a fun prank to do to someone in the shower.
All you have to do is just take the bar of soap,
and paint it completely with clear nail polish.
That way, when they go to use the soap,
it will not sud up at all,
and basically they're going to be left
with not being clean after a shower,
which kind of defeats the whole purpose of taking a shower.
Prank number three.
This one I actually learned from Demi Lovato
when we were on tour together,
and it's quickly become a personal favorite of mine.
For this, you're gonna wanna grab your friend's phone,
go into Settings, General, Keyboard, Shortcuts, New,
and then type in a funny word like poop,
or use your imagination,
and then type in a word this person uses a lot, like hey.
Hit Done.
Now when this person types in hey,
it will autocorrect to
(dramatic crescendo)
Prank number four.
If you've got a friend or family member who
is always watching TV,
this one will be perfect for them.
Grab your remote and look for the LED on the front of it.
Then, cut a piece of tape that's approximately the same size
and cover the LED with the tape.
Whoever tries to use this remote is going
to be really frustrated to find out
it doesn't work at all.
And, prank number five.
Now this one is great if you're lazy,
but you still wanna scare someone really bad.
Leave a note warning someone they're getting pranked,
and then don't do anything at all for the rest of the day.
And those are my top five April Fools' Day pranks,
and if you thought any of these pranks were clever
let me know by liking this video
and also comment down below,
which one are you most excited to try out?
And also, go add me on Snapchat because on April Fools' Day,
my Snapchat story is going ham.
So go add me right now, @CollinsKey.
I love you all so much.
I'll see you guys again next week. Bye.
Woo! Yeah. Jump it up. Whoo-Hoo!