(audience applause)
- Now, earlier today on Twitter I asked all my
fans what is like your favorite magic tricks I've
done during the season?
Now, the two most popular was the first one,
where I took the bill and made it appear
inside of a bag of popcorn,
and the second most popular was the book
trick I did in Vegas.
So, tonight I thought it's my final show,
how bout I combine the two acts and try something new.
But of course to do this I need two very sexy assistants.
(audience screaming)
So, I thought...
Now I did have two very sexy ladies in mind,
Kathie Lee and Hoda.
Give em a huge round of applause.
(audience applause)
- Thank you.
Come on darlin.
- Hi everybody.
- I'd keep it goin for them.
(audience applause)
- Hi. - How you doin?
- Hi sweetheart. Love you.
- Hello. Thank you so much. - You're so kind.
- Alright you guys, let's go over here.
So Hoda, if you want to take a seat right here.
- Okay.
- Kathie Lee over here.
- Alright.
- Great, so basically we're gonna start off,
got an empty envelope. Alright?
- Uh huh.
- Gonna seal it up. Let's see here.
- Watch him closely.
- Uh huh, I got my eye on you.
- This is gonna be tricky. Okay. (giggles)
- No littering in New York.
- Sorry. I'll recycle it later, don't worry.
Okay, here we go.
Let's see here.
So Kathie, what I'd like you to do is I'd like you
to stand up, take this envelope,
sign it, and then sit on it.
(audience laughter)
Alright. Now, while you're doing that, Hoda...
I brought along a copy of your book.
Excellent, right? (applause)
Yes, promotion.
- Her New York Times bestselling book.
- Uh huh.
- That's what Howie said. That's exactly what Howie said.
- That's right.
- Hi Howie.
- Alright, so Hoda, I'm just gonna go through the book
and you say the word stop whenever you want.
- Okay. Stop.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
- Great. So what I'd like you to do.
I'd like you to, this is very important.
I'd like you to read aloud the page number.
- The page number.
- [Collins] Page number.
- The page number is...
(audience laughing)
Kathie?
- [Collins] You got any glasses?
- 90.
- [Collins] What is it?
- 96.
- [Collins] 96. Okay, great.
- My age.
- Geesh (audience laughing)
- And what's the first word there on the page?
- No indeed, it's sucking.
- Sucking.
- Of course it is.
- What? (audience applauding and laughing)
- Of course it's sucking. - It's my book.
- What is in your...
Here, take your, that's great.
- Okay.
- Hoda writes books like that.
- Quit it.
- This is awkward. (giggles)
Okay, um.
(audience laughing)
- Alright, so I've got some just random bills here.
- And now Kathie, can you just confirm these are all
like difference serial numbers, right?
- Ah, well let me look at em.
(audience laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yes, they are. - There. Yeah, they are.
- [Collins] Yeah, there. Okay, great.
So, I'm just gonna go like this,
and basically I'm just gonna like deal down bills,
and your job, just whenever you want, say the word stop.
- Stop.
- On this one?
- Uh hmm. - Yeah.
- Okay. This will be the bill. Take it.
Now, I want to show you, if you went one bill earlier
you would have got a completely different serial number.
One bill later a completely different serial number,
but you happened to get that one.
Alright, can you just show it to the camera really quick?
- Which one?
- Right over there.
Get a shot of that.
Oh great, and let me see the bill really quick.
I need to memorize it. Got it.
Okay, great.
I'm gonna try and do some visualization now, so you guys,
I need to concentrate for this, alright? (giggles)
- Okay. - Okay.
- Here we go.
I'm just gonna close my eyes,
I'm gonna visualize taking the book,
tearing out page 60...
No no, sorry. 96 right, 96?
- [Hoda] Uh huh. - [Kathie Lee] Right.
- Okay, turn that page 96,
writing the word sucking on it...
- [Hoda] Oh. (audience laughing)
- Turning it around, I'm gonna write down the serial
number on the back, and then insert it inside the
envelope that Kathie Lee is sitting on.
- No way. - Uh uh.
- Okay. I think I should have done this.
- Here. Can you please take the book,
and open up to page 96.
- This may take a minute. (audience laughing)
- You should have gotten younger models. (laughing)
- [Collins] (laughing)
(audience laughing and applauding)
- Oh my god. - Oh my.
- [Hoda] 96.
- Your one page has actually been torn
out of the book like that.
Alright, now Kathie, you've been sittin on top of that
envelope the entire time.
Is that right?
- The entire time. And I have not done anything to it.
- Okay. Can you, uh... (audience laughing)
And I, I want to confirm, you never at any point felt my
hands go near you or the envelope.
- Oh honey, I would have felt that.
(audience laughing)
- Well, you know what they say...
- And I would have been arrested. What are you 17?
- Well, you know what, yeah.
(everyone laughing)
- [Collins] It's a little bit illegal.
Um, well you know what they say,
magicians do have fast hands.
So, here. Can you please stand up for us?
- I've got a lot of stuff going on here Collins.
- You've got a lot of stuff going...
Okay, just take...
- Okay.
- I'm sorry that you had to multi task.
Alright, so here, we're just gonna take the envelope,
just gonna cut it open here.
We'll try this. This is, um...
Let's see this.
- [Hoda] How is that possible?
- [Collins] Magic.
- [Kathie Lee] Are you watching closely?
- [Hoda] I am. I'm watching closely.
- Okay. Just like that.
Could you please open the envelope?
See, is there anything inside of it?
Just open it up.
Okay. You go it?
Yeah, is there anything inside?
- Oh my god.
- Is it your missing page?
- The page, look at it.
There's one word on it.
- With the word sucking on it.
- Sucking. (audience applause)
- Are you kidding me?
(audience cheering and applause)
- If this is the serial number...
- I can't __
- There, yeah.
Well, let's see if this is the serial number,
this would be pretty crazy.
Can you please read the serial number off?
What is the serial number that you had on your bill?
- K13805733H.
(audience cheering and applause)
- Yeah.
- That's unbelievable. - That's amazing.
- Thank you guys so much.
- Wow. (audience cheering and applauding)
- What's up guys?
It is Collins Key, and welcome to my YouTube channel.
(techno music)
- [Howie] I think that you are the new face of magic.
- There every week I'm posting new videos so be
sure to subscribe to this channel to make sure you
can see them first.
And, also, if you guys enjoyed this performance,
it would mean a lot to me if you could share this
video with all of your friends.
My social medial links are all down below,
so be sure you go check those out for all the latest
updates on tours, performances, and everything else.
Peace.