- The last time, I kind of like,
I tried to use magic to get a girlfriend.
- They said central park.
- Central park.
- Oh my God.
- Thank you so much.
- [Collins] I think something went a little
bit amiss in the magic last time,
because I guess she had a boyfriend.
And so I'm still single, I don't
have a girlfriend anymore so, I never had one.
(laughs)
- So the Collins that's on stage
is the Collins that's at home with us.
And so when people meet him on the street.
- Can we have the picture?
- Yeah, let's do it, yeah, yeah!
- It's the same kid, they're not
getting something different.
- [Collins] I almost gave up magic,
just 'cause like peer pressure.
When you're doing something that
not everyone else is doing, it's
definitely that pressure of like,
well what are you doing out there
you should come back here with the group.
You should come back here with everyone else.
And so I almost gave it up and
it was really my parents who, like,
encouraged me like, no if you like
to do it, go for it.
- [Anne] This means the world to him,
and for something that can set him
for the rest of his life, doing what he loves to do.
- [Collins] I think to win the show
would be incredible, because not
only would I be the youngest magician,
I would be the only magician.
I'm gonna do literally everything to make it to the finals.
(clapping)
(cheering)
Tonight, I'm putting 250,000 dollars on the line.
Now it's not my money, it's Nick's.
(laughs)
Nick, are you able to just take
that, ridiculously expensive watch?
Yeah, alright, great, just take it off for us.
I promise to be very careful with it, very careful.
- Hope y'all got insurance America's Got Talent.
- Alright, alright, here we go.
Alright, it's chill if I change the time right?
- No!
- Alright, alright, here we go, check it out!
I'm gonna place it over here, very carefully.
Alright great, we've also got some cheap watches.
(thud)
Can't do that with Nick's.
Awesome, now Howie, please take off your watch.
- My watch?
- Yes your watch, pull out the stem
and change it to a completely different time.
- Alright.
- The renaissance period?
- If you've got the power?
Alright, Heidi, I'm gonna try and
mentally influence you to choose a bag
with a cheap watch, so this is very important
Heidi, I need you to look at me.
Bag one, two, or three?
Name one now!
- One!
- One, okay.
Alright, Mel B, same thing, one or two?
- Two!
- Two, are you sure?
- I'm sure!
- Alright, bag number two, here we go.
Watch.
(crash)
- Oh my God!
(gasps)
(laughs)
- You have my watch!
- Alright, Howie, can you please
tell us what time did you change the watch to?
- The watch is changed to, read that.
- You can't read it?
- Read it.
- Hold on.
(laughs)
Five o'clock.
- Is that rounded, or was that the exact time?
- Is that the exact time?
- No, it's 4:40, 50.
- What?
- Is it eight?
- 4:40, 50?
(laughs)
- I like that, 4:40, 50,
what do you guys say, yeah?
- 4:58!
- Sorry, what was it?
- 4:58.
- I think so.
- Alright great, everyone remember the time 4:58.
(laughs)
Especially you Nick, you're gonna
remember 4:58 for the rest of your life.
(laughs)
(crash)
- Whoa.
(gasps)
- That doesn't look good.
- Okay.
(laughs)
- So Heidi, Mel B, let's see if
you guys destroyed Nick's watch.
Alright, Nick, here's your watch.
Now this is the craziest part,
you stopped your watch at 4:58.
- Correct.
- I set Nick's watch to, 4:58.
- No!
(cheering)
- Yeah, come on you guys it's time to make some noise!
Yeah!
(clapping and cheering)
- Wow!
- He had it upside down, it is 4:58.
(laughs)
I don't know how you did it, but
you lucky, if you would've broke
my watch I would've broke my
foot off in your you know what.
(laughs)
- What's up guys it is Collins Key
and welcome to my YouTube channel.
Now every week I am posting new
videos so be sure to subscribe to this channel
to make sure you can see 'em first.
So if you guys enjoyed this performance
it would mean a lot to me if you
could share this video with all of your friends.
My social media links are all in down below.
So be sure you go check those out
for all the latest updates on tours,
performances, and everything else.
Peace.