- Yeah, yeah.
(crowd talking)
So now it's impossible to duplicate this card.
So check this out right here.
Take your eight...
Put it like halfway in the middle right here.
This is where it gets crazy.
Watch this card right here.
It'll find your card that's in a card watch.
One,
two,
melts all the way off the top right.
And it goes all the way through the deck.
And look at this find your card
and you signed the front of it.
So watch if you go through,
one card has a bite out of it.
Do you see that?
- Who did it?
- Right.
- That's the card I thought.
- You picked the card you signed it right?
Okay.
- What?
- And that's not even the best part,
look at this.
What happens when you eat something,
where does it go?
- Stomach.
- Stomach right?
Well this is a cannibal card so watch this.
This right here, watch.
- Oh.
- It's inside of this card. - No it's not.
- Look at this. - Okay, I don't like this now.
I'm afraid. - Pull it out, pull it out.
pull it out take it all the way out.
It's really in there,
yeah take it all the way out.
Here's a little bit more here.
Make sure it fits that card exactly.
- I have to go.
- I don't like this, I don't like this.
- Crazy, right?
(techno music)