- [Boy] Dude, dude shut up.
Oh gotta hide.
That's the car right there.
Our dad's driving but our mom is in there.
Oh it's getting real.
Turn around, shoot.
(laughing)
Oh my god, that was horrible.
Alright, here we go, they're walking in.
Alright here we go.
Okay so this is like, it's terrible.
I'm not even in my costume and they're already here.
Okay, here we go.
Cut the camera off.
Setting up the shot.
- [Camera Guy] Dude don't look like that.
You look creepy.
- It's time for the mask.
This is the mask, mom.
I'm so sorry.
Alright guys, so I'm getting into position right now.
You have camera number one right over here.
So this is the angle that this camera is getting.
So I'm gonna turn this on.
You guys good?
You good?
How do I know when they're coming?
Tell Lindsey to text me when they're like
a few feet away from the car.
No sign still?
Alright.
(police sirens)
How are you?
Before we go any further, I just wanna clarify something.
Number one, I had no idea going into this
that clowns are more than just
a social media trend that was happening.
And number two, I didn't get in trouble for doing it
but also we can just tell that,
I just absolutely suck at making pranks.
I didn't get in trouble luckily for this.
Everything was completely fine.
Everything worked out.
That being said, Devan and I right now
are gonna watch a whole bunch of clown sightings
and clown pranks and kind of see
what's going on with this whole trend.
Give this video a thumbs up for
the fact that I tried it, I went for it.
I tried to pull my very own clown prank
but yeah without any further ado,
let's jump right in right now.
A little bit nervous, but right now let's just--
- Yeah let's do it.
- Let's get it started.
- I don't like this.
I don't--
- [Both] Oh no.
- [Man] No.
No.
No, no what are you doing bro?
- What is going on?
- [Man] Oh (beep)
- [Both] Oh.
- [Man] (beep)
- Yo.
No way.
I would freak out so hard if
this was happening on my property.
He's destroying their pumpkins.
- What?
- This man is strong.
He literally just punched a pumpkin and broke it open.
- [Man] I look up, then I see this clown right there.
Which freaked me out bro.
How do you even get up there?
- That's the wildest one of all.
Why would you do that?
(honking)
- [Man] What the (honking).
What the (honking) you (honking).
- I thought that was a clown with a horn.
They're bleeping out what he was saying.
(country music)
The music fits so perfectly, oh my gosh.
- [Driver] No no way.
- [Boy] Dude get outta here.
Back up back up.
Oh my god.
He's just going.
- He's going back to his home.
If you go fast he's not gonna be able to get you.
- [Boy] Oh my god, what the.
- Yo come check out shot man.
Are you serious?
Yo go around it bro.
Yo go around this fool bro.
- No.
- [Man] Go around him bro.
Go around him.
For real man, go around him.
Get away.
Run him over dog.
- That's what I was thinking.
- [Man] I'm not getting out the car bro.
- That driver's the worst.
- And now an actual recreation of what happened
after the guy stopped filming.
Ah.
(laughing)
Hey kid, want a balloon?
Don't think I could ever try to blow this thing up,
it's a lot harder than it looks.
It takes so much cheek strength.
Hey kid, what do you want, a dog?
Good thing that's what it ought to make.
Here's a dog.
- [Woman] This cannot be real.
Hold on let me slow down.
Roll down the window, roll down the window.
I wanna talk to him.
- Why?
- What?
- [Man] This guy's on Twitter too much.
- [Woman] Hey, oh god he's running, he's running.
He's chasing us.
Oh my god, he's (mumbles).
- These clowns are gonna get hit one day, I swear.
- [Girl] I'm scared.
- Well yeah.
- At least the movement is a little bit different.
The rest of the clowns are wide,
this guy is kind of like,
he's kind of iguana crawling around.
Iguana crawling.
(suspenseful music)
They added the music.
- That music is just too much.
- Why is he doing yoga right now?
This is the first yoga clown.
After all that build up, he doesn't explode
or multiply in multiple clowns.
- [Woman] Turn this stupid radio off.
Justin, no get back in the car.
- He's like the guy in every horror movie who dies first.
The opening scene of every horror movie,
he's like, let me go check out what this is.
And then he dies.
It's that man in real life.
No, no.
- Why roll up next to him, man?
Why?
- Wow.
- Oh okay good.
- I'm not buying the whole Slender-man act.
- Uh uh.
- [Man] I just wanna finish dude.
- Wait, did he say, do you wanna finish?
What did he say?
- I thought he said, just let me finish.
I thought he was using the bathroom.
He's like please let me finish.
- [Man] Clowns walking around Allen town, look,
on hover boards, look.
- They're still creepy.
- Haters gonna say it's fake.
- How does he know where to point the camera,
that's my question.
- [Man] Get it on Snapchat, get it on Snapchat.
- [Man] No this can't be real.
- I agree with the man who's like,
this can't be real, because guys,
this can't be real.
It can't be.
- [Girl] Okay so we think we just saw
a clown go into the bushes.
- Ya did.
- [Girl] We're not exactly sure,
so we're gonna go investigate.
- [Girl] Delaney I know you're scared, bug off.
- [Girl] Shh, you guys be quiet.
- Oh.
(screaming)
- The clown's way faster than those girls.
- Oh my god.
- They're not gonna, they're not gonna,
yeah that clown's way faster.
- [Man] We're here in Ohio and I think we just saw
one of those killer clown things.
- And so we're gonna go investigate, brilliant.
- [Man] So I'm out here in Palm Springs, California.
And my brother said he just saw a clown somewhere
in my apartment but I really don't believe him.
- I thought he was gonna turn it
and there'd be a clown right there.
- [Man] I'm out here looking at sun down.
- [Boy] He had red hair.
There, there look look, he's right there.
Go.
Run.
- Yeah I'm that little kid right there.
- [Man] We saw a clown.
That's him, that's him.
Bro oh my gosh.
(crashing)
- So a couple of those were pretty creepy,
but for the most part, Devan and I are still
rather skeptical about the whole clown sighting thing.
We have a bunch of news clips here
and this might change our minds.
So let's just see.
(screaming)
- [Reporter] This Snapchat video of that creepy clown
standing right outside Shareeta Maston's apartment.
It waved what looks like a knife,
before it skampered away.
Shareeta says she was with her 11 year old cousin,
when she spotted the clown at the BP station across
the street, so she ran home.
- I left her and then by the time we got here,
we turned around and was closing the door.
It was standing right here in front of,
right here, with the knife just waving it at us,
through the window.
- [Reporter] That's when they took
this video through the blinds.
They took a second Snapchat video
from a side window as well.
- [Shareeta] It was scary.
- [Reporter] He called out the helicopter
because this was so serious, to help
search for this clown, but they couldn't find him.
They're looking for a clown with orange hair,
white paint on his face, red lips
and he was wearing a rainbow suit.
- These clowns are terrifying.
- [Reporter] A clown wearing white with red hair
came out from behind some trees near her house.
And was staring at her.
A deputy tells us another man called from
that same neighborhood, saying a clown had chased
his child and some friends when they got
off of their school bus.
- [Reporter] You are looking at cell phone video
of a person dressed in a clown suit,
trespassing at the Rosehill cemetery in the dead of night.
- It's pretty sick, it's creepy.
- [Reporter] Julia Graham was quote, freaked out,
when she figured out what the image was
that she saw running towards the cemetery main gate.
- And when we get closer we realize it's a clown.
- The first picture her husband snapped
was of the clown scaling the main gate
at the Ravenswood avenue entrance.
Not an easy climb for anyone,
let alone someone in a clown costume.
It happened around 10 o'clock,
when the cemetery was clearly closed
and locked for the night.
Cemetery officials wouldn't go on camera,
but CBS two did show them the video--
- Dude what the--
- What a ending technique, wow.
Special effects on fleek, it looked like
the clown was really there.
- [Man] Oh my god.
- [Reporter] Videos and photos of creepy clowns
surprising people on the streets of California
at night, went viral last year.
- [Man] Oh my god.
- [Reporter] And in New York, more of the same.
But again, for some reason, in cemeteries.
Eventually the clown was caught in the headlights
of Grahams car, turns around and without saying a word,
takes off into the darkness.
- What if he just said one word, was like, pandas and ran.
- Eek eek.
- The creepy clown sightings
have been increasing across the country recently.
Due to recent social media threats
from anonymous clown accounts,
Suffolk County school districts
are not taking any chances.
After one of the anonymous Long Island clown
Twitter accounts threatened Lindon Hurst Friday morning,
the students here at this elementary school
weren't allowed outside during recess.
The clowning pranks a disturbing trend sweeping
our area and the country with violent threats--
- Those eyes.
- [Reporter] And countless accounts.
- Well.
I don't quite know what to make of those videos.
Some of them are definitely fake--
- I'd say there's probably like five real ones.
- If that, if that.
Some of those seem like they could very well be real.
So let us know what you guys think
in the comments down below.
And if you see a scary clown,
please be super safe.
- Just run, reverse.
Listen to your other friends who are in the car.
- Do not film it.
Oh my gosh yeah, whatever you do, just get out of there.