♫ And you'll never wanna leave my side
♫ As long as I don't break these
♫ Promises
♫ And they still feel all so wasted on myself
- [Melanie] How do you do it?
How do you do it?
How do you bloody do it?
- [Howard] You're a terrific performer.
17 years old. Let's remind America of that.
- [Collins] And for the the trick
I thought of-- - Whoa!
♫ And they still feel all so wasted on myself
- [Collins] Now, what I'm about to do,
most people say this is absolutely impossible.
I want to make magic fun for my generation.
Right now, open it up. Open up all those 20s.
- Oh my gosh.
- [Collins] Retweet if Collins Key blows your mind.
(people chattering)
(screams)
♫ And they still feel all so wasted on myself
(energetic electronic music)
- Mind blown! (energetic electronic music)
- Right now, I need some of you to help me out.
(energetic electronic music)
- [Howie] I think that you are the new face of magic.
You have just stepped into your future.
(audience screaming)