- [Collins Key] What's up guys? It is Collins Key.
Now I am here in Dallas, Texas for the
Pop Tarts Crazy Good Summer concert tour with Demi Lovato.
Now, it's Pop Tarts' 50th birthday, so to celebrate,
they are throwing all their Crazy Good concerts for free.
Now, as you guys know,
my favorite flavor of Pop-Tarts is cookies & creme.
But today, we're gonna be finding out what Demi's is,
and I want you guys to comment down below right now
and see if you can guess what her favorite flavor is.
Now as you guys know, I went on tour with Demi
on the Neon Lights Tour and I haven't seen Demi in a while.
So I'm really excited to be able to catch up with her,
hang out, and talk about some cool things.
Now right now, I want you guys to go to
poptartscrazygood.com to find out all the details
about this tour and also to find out how you guys
can see EMBLEM3.
I'm really excited to be here with you because
this is Pop-Tarts' 50th anniversary.
- [Demi] Mm hm.
- And this is like a crazy party for them.
And so I wanted to ask you, when you turn 50,
what do you want to be your crazy, like, blow-out birthday?
- Yeah, something that's totally stereotypical.
No, I don't know what I'd do for my 50th birthday.
I think I would skydive or something like that.
That'd be cool.
- Alright, so I know you've been traveling a ton
and I always see your Instagram posts, you're everywhere.
So what has been the highlight of your
crazy good summer so far?
- The highlight of my crazy good summer so far:
I got to go home for a couple of days, almost a week,
and spent my Fourth of July here in Texas.
- Oh, that's awesome.
Okay, so of course, what's your favorite Pop-Tart flavor?
- S'mores, which is right behind you.
- S'mores? Right behind me.
I brought along your favorite flavor.
- Ahhh.
- Hey, actually, hold on.
I want to show you a magic trick with them really quick.
Check this out.
- Can you crack it open and make a $100 bill come out?
- Watch. You want a $100 bill?
- Yeah.
- Which? Like, do you want the
new hundreds or the old hundreds?
Oh, shoot. Which one?
- Uh, new!
- New hundreds?
Check this out. I want you guys to see this.
Look at this.
- If you do this...
- Look at this.
- I'm gonna freak out.
- That would have been awesome.
- That would have been really cool!
(laughter)
- What's like your favorite song to perform?
- You know, it's whatever the crowd is most into.
So I think right now, it's "Really Don't Care."
- I want to give a huge thank you to Pop-Tarts
and Demi for the amazing show tonight.
And also, I had so much fun talking with Demi
and re-living what it was like to be on the
Neon Lights Tour.
And if you guys have any questions that you
would love to ask Demi, let me know what they are
in the comments down below because next time I see her,
I might ask your question.
Now, this has definitely been the highlight of my
crazy good summer.
I want you guys to right now, go to
poptartscrazygood.com to find out
where the next stop of the tour is.
See you guys again soon.
Don't forget of course, subscribe to this channel.
Peace.
You signed the Joker that you put in your mouth.
- Oh my God!
- What?
- What the heck? I want to try!
- Mind blown.