(upbeat music)
- So basically if we could cut this, be quiet!
- You need to do some magic on that bowling!
Oh!
- Hey what's up guys it is Collins Key!
And welcome to another tour diaries.
And one of my favorite parts about
being on the Neon Lights tour
is being able to hang out with Demi.
So basically, we had a day off,
so she took all of us bowling, went
to our own private bowling alley.
Knocked down some pins, let's check it out!
(upbeat music)
(pop music)
Alright if you guys enjoyed watching us bowl,
make sure to give this video a huge thumbs up!
And that's about it, so once again you guys,
my name is Collins Key and have a fantastic day!
Peace.
(snaps)
(funky pop music)
- Yeah!