- Yo, it works, eh the sourest
fidget spinner in the entire world.
(yells)
You guys challenged me to make edible candy fidget spinner.
I have a whole bunch of candy here
and at the end of this I'm gonna be making
the first ever world's sourest fidget spinner
and I'm really nervous 'cause two things are gonna happen.
I'm probably gonna knock out a tooth
trying to bite into it and also,
it's gonna be so sour, like this, I've got malic acid, guys,
you know what's gonna be goin' down.
And I have no idea why you think
I'm gonna be good at playing with fidget spinners,
but I mean hey, let's give it a try.
Three, two, one, go.
(rock music)
Now it's time to get rid of the card,.
And now the part you've all been waiting for,
yes, I will be spinning this every single time
I begin a new section and right now
we are gonna be deconstructing the fidget spinner,
so RIP buddy, I've had a great time with you
but we just pop this off here.
Don't they look like balls inside of there,
what's up with that.
Umm, how does this work, do you?
(clatters)
I think I broke it.
Let's see if it works without the covers on it.
Hey, it actually, well wait wait wait.
Do these actually do anything here,
these little ball things on the end,
I'm gonna pop these out, just kinda curious, let's see.
(spins)
I think it has no weight so it probably
stops a lot sooner, yeah.
So, oww.
(blows)
I sound like a plane when I'm doing this.
(laughs)
This next part is gonna be one
(clanks)
Most scientific things I've ever,
that's like a bottle flip challenge.
I'm breaking so much stuff.
(beeps)
And shout out to Stephen Cheer
because I would've had no idea
how to make these molds, make sure you guys
go check out his video, the link is gonna be
down in the description below.
But basically you take these two different colored putties,
mix 'em together, and then you have one minute
to put it down and then put the fidget spinner on it,
make a mold of it, and then you can turn it into candy.
That's what's gonna happen, it's gonna be magnificent,
and I'm gonna try not to mess this up.
All right we're taking this (mumbles)
boop boop boop boop boop boop boop boop, mmm, mmm.
You gotta get this out super quick
because otherwise this stuff is gonna
go away and it's gonna get hardened
and it gets very very very hard.
Okay here we go woop, bam, boop.
Yep, mix it all together, yooey!
That's like makin' edible slime again.
(coughs)
I'm not sed to workin' with a time constraint on
these sort of things, just kinda get to mess around.
But now I literally have 60 seconds
to mix this all together, otherwise it's gonna harden
and then the whole thing will be ruined.
Gonna go baker mode on it, oh yeah, la la la la.
Grrr. Oh boy.
It's actually to getting a lot harder
to mold and squeeze now so I think it's startin'
to harden now, so now we're gonna place on the plate.
Gonna remove, oh no there's stuff on the plate.
So we're gonna roll it now into a ball.
Perfect, here we go, we're gonna take a place down here,
just kinda flatten it out.
(clangs), great!
Now we're gonna take the fidget spinner,
oh we gotta pop this out, yay.
All right here we go, gotta push the fidget spinner in here.
(whimsical orchestral music)
All right, and then I think you kinda
wanna mold the edges close to it,
that way you kinda get a nice like fidget spinnery look.
So it's been 25 minutes and this thing now is really solid.
It looks really squishy but you guys
can put this in the microwave, it won't melt
and only the candy will melt.
So we're gonna pop out the fidget spinner now.
Yay, that's the mold right there.
(children cheering)
To kick it off we're gonna be tasting the rainbow,
with some skittles right here.
So I think what we do is we take the skittles.
I'm gonna get roasted so hard in the comments
for how I just opened this bag of skittles.
Like that's not the way you open it.
All right gonna kinda put 'em in there.
Now time to pop this into the microwave
and create a beautiful fidget mold,
once I rearrange it all, so let's do that.
- [Man] A few moments later.
- These skittles did not work out,
there's actually more like an egg that cracked,
but you can very easily crack this, watch.
This did not work, there is no way
that I could fidget spin one of this.
Just not gonna work.
- [Man] Time for a cool fidget spinner trick.
- Spin, flip, catch, drop, another spin, hooh!
Flip, catch, drop, flip, catch, caught.
(beeps)
Now this fidget spinner, even though I don't like it a ton
actually has these things which keep it in place.
So I made a mold of it, you know the feeling you get
when something is gonna work?
Well that's the feeling I have right now.
Jolly ranchers.
(clatters)
Let's go.
You guys, I told you this was gonna work.
I think this is it, here we go three, two, one.
Yes, this looks so good.
Okay now, the moment of truth.
We have put now the fidgety spinner wheel,
whatever the heck it is that makes this thing work
and then we're gonna see if we can spin it.
Ooh, I'm nervous but very excited.
The moment of truth.
Will it spin, three, two, one.
Yo, it works!
Guys, we did it, it finally worked.
Oh my gosh I'm so hyped.
This is like so, so, so, cool.
And now it's time for the first ever
fidget spinner lick test, here we go.
Yep, this tastes delicious.
- [Man] Time for a cool fidget spinner trick, again.
- This just seems like a bad idea.
(splats)
Ow.
Yeah that actually could get hurt.
That that this is that that really hurt.
And we're gonna start off right here with one fidget spinner
and then we're gonna get another
fidget spinner going on top of it.
And let's see if we can get one more goin'
on top of this, there's no way.
Yeah! (cheering)
Between the bean boozled challenge or starburst
I think more of you guys suggested starburst would work
and then the bean boozle challenge would probably fail.
I am not on my a game when it comes
to throwing things and catching things today.
And that wasn't even a throw, that was a drop.
But um, let's go, yeah, I'm joking, yay, yay.
Whee!
All right we're gonna crack open,
gonna crack open some Starbursts.
- [Man] One eternity later.
Oh that was so difficult.
All right we're just gonna, perfect.
But now I have to color code it,
unwrap all of these, which can get kind of boring.
So we'll just fast forward until
the part where I have it all made, yeah.
All right let's see if it worked.
Oh dude, this worked out so well!
Oh my gosh.
Now the true test to see if it can truly fidget spin.
But first I have a challenge, I wanna see if
you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video thumbs up in seven seconds.
Here we go seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you could do that, comment down below
keyper squad right now.
Let's see if we can pop it in here.
(dramatic music)
(groans and sobs)
Fail, we were so close, what happened.
I'm so upset right now.
It's all about movin' on though,
gotta stay positive and let's make
this next one the best one.
- [Man] Time for a cool fidget spinner trick, again again.
Two fidgets at once.
I see these people with finger strength
they're like (yells) and it's like
it spins like crazy.
I can't do the thousand mile per hour finger spin.
I need the two hand, yaiy.
We're gonna try with the bean boozled challenge.
And first I'm going to try some beans
and just see how this goes.
(rattles)
(chomps)
(yells)
Horrible, I got all the worst ones.
Help me, okay.
Well that was terrible.
So now we're gonna add these in here.
I can smell these ones are all bad
and now we're gonna add these in,
microwave 'em and let's see if this fidget spinner works.
I gotta mention, out of all of em so far.
This one I gotta say is not the prettiest,
but I mean it kinda works and this thing smelled
so bad when I was microwaving it.
It was horrible so if you do this at home, be warned.
It's gonna smell terrible.
So now we have part of of the fidget spinner
which we insert over here.
Here we go and then we have part two of the fidget spinner
here and they do not appear to be
compatible with this mold it all.
Let me see if I can get this though, oh my gosh.
Here it is, the moment of truth.
See if it will spin.
I mean this is not as satisfying as I wanted it to be.
I wanted the (low pitched moan)
But there's definitely room for improvement,
and luckily we're not done yet
because we still have the most sour one in the entire world.
With that one, I have so much faith that it's gonna work.
But first, we'll take a bite of this one,
just kind of try it out.
Ah.
Yeah, nope.
- [Man] Time for a cool fidget spinner
trick, again, again, again.
- Ow.
It's so hard.
Ow, my lip.
We're about to make the sourest fidget spinner in the world
but first I wanna give a huge shout out
to the keyper of the week, Ash.
If you wanna be the keyper of the week,
check the description at down below
and right now it's time to eat
the sourest fidget spinner in the entire world.
I brought the one and only Warheads so here we go.
(tape scratching noise)
Let's open these up and then we'll microwave 'em.
I'm not lookin' forward to this.
Yo this one actually turned out so cool.
The other ones were all a solid color but this one
looks tie-dyed, there a ton of little holes on it.
And this one looks sweet, kinda innocent, but it's not.
This is gonna be intense, and what we're gonna do right now
we're gonna pop this in, it's so close to breaking.
I have to hold it upside down, otherwise
there's no way it's gonna work,
it's so close to breaking, how do I do this.
One finger balance, if this doesn't work, nothing will.
Three, two, one.
Hey, the sourest fidget spinner in the entire world.
I'm gonna take a bite of it, three two one.
(gasps)
Oh my gosh it's so sour.
(beeps)
In the extreme sourness I forgot to add the malic acid
so for those of you guys who are like
where's the malic acid, there's the malic acid.
Oh.
(beeps)
- [Man] Time for a cool fidget spinner trick.
I'm sorry, again, seriously?
- Hooh.
(crashes)
The one trick I really do wanna get
where you toss it up and then you
catch it in the other and then you go back,
oh and then you, that's part of the trick, I promise.
And then we'll try one last time here, ugh.
Egh, ooh and then back again, oh.
(clatters)
(rock music)