- You challenged us, Oh my gosh!
To make DIY edible Christmas presents
that you can literally eat.
Right now, we're kicking it off with Christmas trees.
(spits out food)
Gotta open up the butter.
(spits) Yee!
- I got em!
- Yee!
So basically we need three tablespoons.
As you guys know, this is how you cut a stick of butter.
(thud) Ow.
You cut it and there you go.
Ah, the paper! - Ah no!
- Grab the paper,
grab the paper. - I don't want to touch it.
All right now time to add the marshmallows.
- All right, you're only supposed to add at handful.
- Handful.
- Yup.
- Okay, cool.
- Wait, no, bro!
What are you doing?
Just a handful.
- That's about a handful.
- No, this is a handful. - I have big hands, Devan.
- [Collins] This is the bonding ingredient
for Rice Krispies,
which will be the base of our edible Christmas tree.
This smells delicious.
Oh! Let's do this, Devan.
It's called the quick pat technique.
- [Devan] Whoa, bro.
- I've never made this before
and this looks just, oh the butter!
Bro, it's getting super gooey!
Holy cow!
This is melted marshmallows with butter.
We're making a Christmas tree, it's gotta be green.
But right now, we got some green food coloring
and, as you guys know, I'm very good at moderation.
Check this out!
- No, bro!
- Dude, it's bubbling up.
It's bubbling up, - I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
- It's shootin' everywhere - I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- It's starting to smell a bit singed.
I'm feeling rather spontaneous
and so I'm gonna add this entire thing
of food coloring right now. - Wait, what?
No! Why? Really? - Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Okay, now you're gonna have to mix it all up, Devan,
go for it!
- [Devan] All right, I'm going for it.
Go, go, go, go that's so fast, bro!
All right, so guys, next up here we got a pan.
And then we also--
- Ow.
(both laugh)
- I'm sorry we also got Rice Krispies treats.
(screams)
- I don't feel safe right now - I'm sorry.
- Move it over.
(vibrations)
(both laugh)
Okay.
- Rice Krispies Treats!
(laughs)
Yee!
- Bro, oh no.
Oh no!
Nope, no!
- I'll be very careful. - No. No.
- I'll be very careful. - Be very slow.
- Okay we're good, - Nice.
- We're good, were good.
Yeah, so you can just do that.
That'd be easiest.
All right, it is time to pour this in.
- Whoa, dude, that's awesome!
Call me the scooper diver!
(bubble sfx) - The what?
- [Collins] These are starting to come together
really nicely.
I get so excited about these little
DIY creations we do, man.
These are cool.
- Wait, bro.
I just realized I been sitting here doing nothing.
- Wait you just realized?
I've been well aware of this.
- I can actually be helping out so here we go.
(claps) (bell glissando)
Nice.
All right, - Okay, great.
- I have a spatula and I'm here to help you out
- This stuff has turned out really, really cool.
All right, time for a quick pat.
(two clunks)
Don't!
All right, I think we are good here.
Woohoo!
To construct our Christmas trees.
We got nonstick spray
for our hands that way we can mold it and shape it
into the perfect tree.
So bro vs. bro.
(spray) (screams)
So now I guess we kinda just grab in.
- Whoa!
- Your tree is gonna be huge!
- No no no! - Yes I want a big tree Devan!
- I need some more.
- So Devan is going for that strat.
My strat is to make the biggest Christmas tree ever.
Stop stealing!
(low pitched laugh)
Time to shape the tree.
Oh my gosh, I do not have enough.
Ugh!
- Are you good dude?
- No!
Holy cow, I feel like we should've done this
when it was like not as like firm.
'Cause it's very firm.
I feel like my shape is not as good as Devan's is at all.
How is yours so good?
I'm going for a new strategy.
I'm just going for pure height.
I want this thing to be reaching into the sky
like a massive tower!
- All right, that looks about good.
(can clangs)
(high pitched tone)
- Let the decorating begin!
Ow!
Oh no, oh no.
Let's see it's gonna get a whole bunch of it.
Perfect!
We got stars for days!
Whoa, dude, yes!
- Bro, I need some though.
- We got some gold fairy dust.
I think mine looks pretty fantastic.
- Tada!
- That's it?
- Yeah, dude, that's it.
- Do you have anymore finishing touches?
Because mine,
I've locked it in, boom, its done.
This is it.
- I do have one.
- Devan just made a crazy change to his.
Here we go the big reveal.
Three, two, wait, wait, wait.
First, five seconds subscribe challenge!
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn of the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Ready?
Here we go!
Five, four, three, two, one.
Done!
If you can do that,
comment down below - Comment down below.
"Keyper Squad" right now.
And here we go, the big reveal.
You ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Tada!
- You added a base to your tree?
- Yes, I did.
I added a tree trunk.
- So comment down below who won this round.
Is it my beautiful super tall tree?
Or Devan's hyper-realistic
actual Christmas tree?
For this round you challenged us to some how make
hot chocolate into edible slime.
So to kick this off we gotta roast it.
(crickets chirp)
Roast it!
- So we're gonna turn it on.
- We need two tablespoons of the olive oil.
The next measurement is very exact.
It needs to be...
(grunts)
- No!
You ripped some of the marshmallows, dude.
- I know, dude, I tore a marshmallow in half.
We have never made slime like this ever before.
- Ever.
- Especially edible slime.
One, two, three.
Marshmallow trick shot!
Nope!
Spoons out.
Time to mix it.
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Devan] Bro, this even sounds fluffy.
- [Collins] This is getting melted so quickly,
but like it's turning into goopy slime stuff.
- This stuff smells incredible.
- Now two tablespoons of this stuff.
- Bro it's all coming out!
- I got it in my eyes!
There's chocolate literally everywhere.
Now we need two tablespoons of this hot chocolate mix.
Boom.
There we go.
- all right. - Final one.
- Spoon? - Spoon!
Probably the most delicious slime I've ever smelled.
This is gonna be so delicious!
Why have we never done slime like this before?
- I know, seriously. - This is the greatest way
of doing it.
- [Devan] Bro, you dropped your spoon.
- Then don't cover my spoon!
- I got it, I got it, I got it
- I can't touch it, it's all hot.
I know how we can do this.
Candy cane rescue mission.
Okay here we go.
Oh, oh!
I gotta hook it, I gotta hook it.
I broke the candy cane!
Next up we gotta add some cornstarch and some sugar.
Okay, so a little bit of powered sugar.
- That's it, that's it, that's it.
- Now time to take the melted down marshmallows
and hot chocolate powder.
- It's not really coming out at all, really.
- All right, we need more, Devan, I believe in you.
- I know, I got it, I got it.
It's slowly but surely.
Slowly but surely.
- Whoa!
There's a giant scoop.
Whew! - Whoa!
- I'm feelin' it needed to be heated up more.
(Devan laughs)
Okay, change of plan, Devan.
Flip it over.
We gotta put it all back inside man!
- All right, all right, all right.
- Look at this. It's not heated up enough.
(Collins and Devan squeal and shout)
Whew, man.
That got stressful.
So guys we gotta reheat it up right now.
We made a big mistake.
Dude, it's burning,
its burning! - No!
- Just dump it out.
Oh my gosh.
- Is it dumping?
- It's dumping.
- This went from looking delicious
to looking like something else.
All right let's grab this here scoop-a-doop-a-doop, oh!
Gonna mix it, mix it, mix it.
- This place smells burnt now.
- Holy Cow.
It's on the hot plate, Devan.
- Oh no.
- Get it off.
That's gonna set off the fire alarm for sure.
Oh man.
I don't even know if this is gonna turn out good.
Here's what we're gonna do.
Got some cups here.
And we're gonna kinda drizzle some of this.
- Is it hot? - Oh yeah, yeah.
It might even melt the plastic to be low-key honest.
There we go.
- Oh it's hot, it is very--
(cracking plastic) Oh.
- Guys this round was a fail so comment who won.
Is it mine who actually made it in a cup
or Devan's on the spatula?
Again, we're gonna eat these at the end.
I still hope it will taste good
and right now we're on to the next round.
Have you ever wanted to be able to eat an ornament?
- Wait, what?
- Like chomp on it?
- No.
- Well, after this DIY you'll be able to do that
because we're making ornaments
out of chocolate.
Eee, no! - No.
- Let's make some edible ornaments.
Woohoo!
We melted down three different colors of chocolate.
And then, basically, we're going to take
these little paint brushes
and then paint and decorate the inside of our ornament.
First, we gotta make sure nothing sticks,
so we gotta spray it.
- Nice.
All right, that's one.
- Don't spray me!
Don't spray me, dude!
Oh, geez.
I think we did way too much oil.
- This isn't even really working at all.
- Yeah, I think that we definitely did
way too much oil.
Oh well.
All right, guys, so I got white coated on
the inside of some.
I got polka dots on the other.
All right, guys, getting a huge glob of chocolate.
So, now I guess it's like paint on the inside, pretty much.
You'll be able to freak your family out
because you just put this on the Christmas tree
and then one night you just like pop it off
and be like, "Oh, guys, I'm kinda hungry."
(chomp sfx)
And your family would freak out.
Next step, pop this in the freezer.
It'll harden and then we turn it into
the actual orb.
Like, we attach two separate things.
Boom, one thing.
It's pretty crazy.
It's now come out of the freezer
and it's the moment of truth.
Can we get the chocolate out
without cracking it.
- You go first.
- Mine's actually kind of easy, because this one here
as you guys can tell,
it's kinda like full of chocolate.
So, this one shouldn't crack.
Oh, yeah! - Ohh!
- All right, let's see if I can get this one over here.
This one's a little bit thinner.
I hear it but I don't know if it's cracking or not.
Oh!
Please come out.
Yeah, ohh! - Ohh!
- Dude, that like popped out!
This green one's the last chance I have.
It's looking good.
It's looking real good.
(cheers)
I think the green ones
turned out the best.
- Yeah.
- So, here's what's gonna happen.
Gonna drop this on here.
Quick slight burn.
Oop, looks good.
Oh, no, no, no!
Get it!
There we go, it's done.
And then put it down over here.
Same thing, slight melt.
Okay, there we go.
Oh, no! - No, no!
We're gonna put them together like this.
(laughs)
It's not round.
That's bad.
I will be amazed if you get that out
without cracking it.
- I'm going for it.
- Oh, oh no!
- So close! - Oh my gosh!
- Look at that.
(both groan)
This is my last chance to even get one of them right.
- I believe in you, Devan.
I believe in you.
You ready?
(cheers)
It looks like wrapped present with a bow.
- Oh, yeah, that's what I was going for.
- Dude, look at that!
- Three, two, one.
(gasps)
(cheers)
- That worked.
All right, so now you've gotta put them on top.
Go for it, go for it.
- Not a lot.
- Oh, done, there you go.
- Ooo.
(claps)
- Now the really fun part.
Time to decorate it.
Oh, that was actually pretty awesome right there.
Just a slight mist.
- That's a light mist?
- Perfect.
You gotta get some silver on there.
- Bro, there's no gold left.
- It's golden on the inside.
One final element left.
The top of the ornament.
Here you go. - Oh, okay.
Oh, I got it. - I haven't got it.
- Oh, no. I thought I had it, but I didn't have it.
- And those aren't gonna work,
so let's just forget that ever happened.
- Oh, I got it!
- Hook it, bro.
- Tada!
I really think that spray made it worse.
- We're actually going to eat these right now.
We're gonna be eating the rest of them at the end
of the video.
But we just can't wait.
All right, here we go, three, two, one,
but first, three second like challenge.
Can you like this video in three seconds?
Ready, here we go.
- Three,
Two,
One,
Done.
- All right, here we go.
Ahh!
(screams)
Are you sure this is edible?
- Oh! - That was disgusting!
Oh my god!
For this round, we are making Santa on a sleigh.
- Yes we are. - We will be making an edible
sleigh.
The first thing's first,
you gotta crack your candy cane open.
Oh my god, it cracked open.
Ahh!
Woohoo!
Yee!
We're basically going to be hot gluing a chocolate bar
to these two candy canes to create the sleigh.
It'll doesn't look like a sleigh,
all it looks like is little elf boots, now.
(Devan laughs)
I think I'm going to remain a basic dude.
And just use these.
- Really?
- Yup.
Oo, it's smokin'.
(screams)
Oh, that's really smart.
Guys, that looks like an awesome little
sled right there.
So, again, for this I gotta crack this
thing open.
Or, should I say, chop it open.
(metallic slashing)
- There we go. - Hey, you got it open.
- I would definitely not recommend opening it that way.
Yeet!
(clang)
That was pretty easy.
You basically just take the candy
and you arrange it on your sleigh.
Yo, we got even more chocolate.
So, I'm gonna put a little dollop of hot glue.
Boom.
Chocolate will never go anywhere.
Santa does deliver a whole lot of sugar.
Hot glue gun on top of a Butterfinger,
another Butterfinger.
Bam, boom, four Butterfingers.
- Bro, that is not aerodynamic at all.
- Top it all off, a bit of chocolate.
- All right, my sled is finally done.
It's not symmetrical at all,
but that's okay.
- I wonder what happens if you put hot glue on chocolate.
Let's fine out.
It like literally melts it.
But, like, you can't eat it because it has glue all over it,
so there's that.
The only finishing step we need is,
of course, the dude who owns it.
I'm sorry Santa, but I gotta put some hot glue
on your beard.
(Collins cheers)
It stays!
Holy cow, I am so proud of myself.
All right, I'm gonna pop a snowman on here
because Santa can't be alone.
And then, of course, you've got the reindeer.
They have a mandatory 15 minute break every
100,000 miles, so.
Chillin' over here with Santa right now.
- This is so far what I have going on with my sleigh.
The bottom of it is actually suspended from the ground.
And then I got these candy canes for support.
They're like the railings where he holds onto, you know.
All right, so I'm dumping all of these out
and I'm actually using this as my present carrier.
This is the bin where all the presents go.
- Well, I think you're making a huge mistake
because there's actually another use for this.
Santa's gonna be riding around in a jacuzzi.
This ain't no one horse open sleigh.
This a jacuzzi, boy.
Now we just gotta hot glue this thing like crazy.
Boom!
There you go.
And I only have one finishing touch left.
On top.
It stays, man.
I am an architectural genius.
Oh, it's kinda slippin'.
- All right, I have just added some
turbo boosters.
(Collins laughs)
Onto the back of mine.
Look at those babies!
- That's crazy.
Yo, Santa's gonna be like, "Let's get them the presents!"
(shouts)
- That's why it has to be hot glued
to his seat.
Next up is the finale
and we're going to be eating all of these delicious
edible Christmas gifts.
But first,
guys comment down below who won this round.
Is it my Santa in a hot tub with ornaments.
- Or my turbo jet Santa sleigh.
- (high pitched) blah, blah, blah, blah.
All I want to do right now is eat this
but I gotta be patient and wait until the very end.
But right now we are on to the next round.
For this final round,
we are joining forces
to make the greatest edible stocking of all time.
We've got so much candy.
So many marshmallows,
so much butter,
whatever this stuff is.
And right now, let's begin.
There we go.
Now we've got the butter melted,
time to add the shmellows.
- Yeah!
- Whoa! - Whoa!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be very, very careful.
Bag number two!
This is so many marshmallows.
You gotta give it a quick pat.
(vocal percussion)
They're starting to get mushy,
but I think it takes a lot longer
when you have a lot more because these
are not going quickly this time.
(clock ticking)
Since this is a stocking,
we're gonna make it red.
Woo, that's a very deep red.
- So, I'm doing four and a half cups of
the Rice Krispie Treats.
Actually, I'm not even gonna measure it.
I'm just doin' the whole box.
- Dude, woo hoo!
Time to add it.
You ready?
Three,
two,
one,
- Whoa! - Whoa!
- This is absolutely crazy!
- Dude, this is so much.
- Holy cow.
- Gotta tip it more, gotta tip it more.
(shouts)
- Time to mix it up.
- Bro.
- This was not big enough at all.
- It's overflowing.
- This is turning out absolutely incredible.
Like, it's the perfect shade of red.
I think we got it mixed up enough
because this is like
oh my gosh.
Ready to go.
So now, let's make this stocking.
All right, so I'm just gonna kinda follow your lead on this
because I have no idea what's going on.
These kinda look like hot Cheetos.
Like little, tiny hot Cheetos.
- They do.
We're makin' one that's really big
so you can put a ton of candy in it.
- This stocking is insanely big, bro.
- It's bigger than any stocking I have ever received.
- It is fully stuffed with all the goodies.
- So, I'm gonna start with the top of the stocking.
- These Gummy Bears smell amazing.
- All right, so we need a boom, gummy bear.
Gummy bear.
- Bro, I think we need some for the actual stocking, dude.
- Gummy bear.
We're gonna line it with some
green gummy bears here at the bottom.
Because I have no other ideas.
I'm gonna be tasting all of these
to make sure that they're up to our quality standards
on our massive stocking.
Ooo, these are little hearts.
They're super sweet.
- Yeah?
- That's awesome, I love that.
All right, these ones smell a little bit sour.
They're like little Batman.
Well, I think this might be a lime flavor,
but let's hope it's not.
Eww, it's sour!
- It is?
- Oh my god!
Why is it so sour?!
(shouts)
- Here, try this one.
- This one seems just as bad.
(screams)
Oh, it's worse!
If these taste like cherries,
I will be super happy.
These are like little gummy balls.
Holy cow, they're strong.
Let me see how this thing tastes.
(angelic voices singing)
It's cherry.
Oh my gosh I love this so much.
I want all of it.
Mine.
- No, I, we need it.
- Mm-mm
- Bro, we need it.
You're just supposed to taste it,
not take it. - Yeah, but it's mine.
- Bro, no. - It's gotta go in my pocket.
- I kinda wish you weren't on my team at this point.
- Where do I go?
Oo, green balls.
- Whoa, whoa, before you eat it, bro,
you have to promise that you will not steel these,
like you did the last one.
You gotta pinky promise me.
- All right, I pinky promise.
- You promise?
- I promise.
I think it's green apple.
(claps)
Mmm!
That was so good!
- I want to try some.
Mmm, bro.
Bro, what're you doing?
- I'm putting it in my pocket.
- No, you can't. - Saving it for later.
- We pinky promised.
- No, no, no, I crossed my fingers.
- What?
- Now I got cherry in this pocket.
I got green apple in this pocket.
What other candy do we have?
- I can't believe you.
Oh!
I think they're licorice strings.
- Let's have a competition.
Whoever can get it all up in their mouth first, wins.
- All right.
- Three, two, one, go!
- Wait, wait.
I wasn't supposed to suck it.
(lip smacking)
- No, no, no, without your hands.
Without your hands.
- Done!
That was not in the rules, and I won.
- You cheater.
- (low-pitched voice) A prize.
- Oh, I've got little game called "Walrus Boy."
Arf, arf.
We finally finished the stocking.
This thing took forever. - So long.
- But it looks incredible.
We're about to eat all the different candy
that we made throughout this video
right after this.
So stick around for that.
But, right now the big reveal.
- Three,
Two,
One.
Ta da!
- This thing turned out so good.
And it looks incredible.
Like, if this showed up underneath the Christmas tree,
I would lose my mine.
So, right now guys,
time to eat the DIY edible things we made.
Starting off, of course, with the Christmas tree.
This Christmas Tree is gonna taste amazing.
And guys, comment down below.
What everyday items should we turn into
edible foods next.
So, right now, let's eat these Christmas trees, bro.
- How do we even do this?
- Mine's stuck to my plate.
Dude, it's stuck.
There we go, okay.
I'm gonna kinda dip it in like this.
And then you just got to take a bite
like corn on the cob.
Three,
Two,
One.
- That's so good.
Tada!
- Bro, I completely forgot about this one.
- I know, it's supposed to be hot chocolate.
It turned into this.
So, this one right here, we'll have to be careful.
Because, I don't wanna like, chip a tooth on this thing.
- It's actually gotten really hard.
- Oh my god!
- Cheers.
- No, I don't want to eat this.
- Three, two, one.
(crunches)
- That was so disgusting, bro.
Do not make that one the way we made it
because it tastes burnt and gross.
(blows raspberry)
Oh, man, I dropped Santa.
No, Santa fell out of his hot tub.
That's not good,
so how do we eat this thing, man?
- I don't know.
- I think I'm just gonna kinda like tear it apart.
- Whoa.
(screams)
- Oh, snap.
Let's see how this thing tastes.
We're gonna toss this up.
- Ooo. - Oh, that's good.
This right here is by far the most elaborate
mint dispenser of all times.
- Oh, yes.
Wait, you got Santa in there.
It's an eraser, bro.
- Santa, no!
I hope he doesn't see that.
Devan, where'd you put that stocking at?
I want to eat that next.
Where's that?
- Oh, I hid it.
Because I'm going to give it to you later.
For Christmas.
- What?
- There is no way you will find it.
- You're kidding me.
- Nope.
- All right, guys, well I'm sorry.
I guess you'll just have to wait til Christmas
to see what it looks like.
You can check that out on my Snapchat.
Boom, right here.
Or Devan's Snapchat.
Boom.
Right over there.
You guys, if you want to see another video,
click right over here.
Right and we have five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Love you guys, bye.
- Bye!