- What's up? It's Collins Key.
And for today's video I'm back at it again
with a brand new DIY.
And today I'm doing a DIY Rainbow Pasta.
And I made the very poor decision to wear a white shirt
while doing a rainbow DIY video.
So there's gonna be a lot of food coloring,
so hopefully I don't mess this up
because I literally put this on for the first time today.
And I like it, and I don't wanna mess it up.
So yeah, that's what we're gonna be doing for today's video.
We have cheese, so yeah, we have cheese!
If you want me to do another DIY video on my channel
let me know by liking this video.
And if this video gets enough thumbs up
then I'll do another crazy DIY video.
Also wanna let you guys know
that I'm giving away an iPhone 7
and all you have to do if you want to win this
are two very easy steps.
Step number 1, you have to download an app called Live.me
which is a free live-streaming app
that I like to stream on all the time.
I'm gonna put the download link for that
in the description down below.
So make sure you use that link in the description
otherwise you will not be entered in to the giveaway.
And for step number 2
all you have to do is just watch my live broadcasts
which happen every single Sunday at 4PM PST.
Without any further ado, let's create some amazing,
that's too high expectations.
Let's create some really probably pretty good DIY pasta.
Rainbow pasta, oh wow I messed that up bad.
This DIY is actually really simple to make.
All you're gonna need is just pasta linguini
food coloring, Ziploc bags,
and if you wanna be extra fancy
you can make some parmesan clouds.
And you guys know me on this channel, we extra fancy.
(dinging)
So what you're gonna wanna do is take your entire box
and you're gonna wanna heat up a full pot of water.
And once it starts bubbling, pro-tip,
that means it's boiling.
(gasps) Mind blown!
And yeah, so actually there is a pro-tip here.
While you're bringing the water to a boil,
if you add olive oil to it
that will prevent the pasta from sticking together
when you add it in there.
So I think the pasta needs to cook for like
around nine minutes
so yeah add the pasta in there
cook the pasta, and then we are on to step number two.
While the pasta's cooking, the fun part begins.
For me, this is the most dangerous part of the DIY
because this is where the food coloring comes in.
And my shirt is at jeopardy
of becoming completely destroyed.
So all you need for this, some Ziploc bags.
I don't know how you open it,
so I think I'm just gonna go like.
(loud bang) Ow.
That's not working at all.
Next, remove a Ziploc bag, that was actually kind of cool.
Right now I have a challenge for you.
I wanna see if you can subscribe
to this channel in five seconds.
So let's try this, five, four,
three, two, one, done.
Were you able to do it?
Were you able to subscribe to this channel in five seconds?
If you were, you're a true Youtube Ninja.
But right now let's get in to this.
And now the most difficult part of the challenge
getting 20 drops of the food coloring in the Ziploc bag
without messing up my shirt.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15,
16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
(gasps) Ran out of breath there.
And that was actually a lot easier
than I thought it would be.
Alright, look this stuff actually kind of looks like blood.
(intense music)
This DIY is going in a very different direction.
But now the next step is
you have to add two tablespoons of water
to what's going on, so I have,
that's not a tablespoon, that's like half a tablespoon.
Probably have to do four of these, but it's two tablespoons.
There we go.
Two full tablespoons right there.
And now we have blood bag number one.
Once you're done with all your colors
your pasta is probably done cooking at this point.
So next you guys need to strain the pasta
as I've done here.
And now we're going to add the pasta to these bags.
This is the moment where my entire life
could come crashing down around me
if I get this dye on my clothing.
So, let's see here.
Oh I've never like really felt spaghetti
just like with my hands.
It feels pretty funky, so um,
I'm kind of eyeballing it here.
Don't know exactly how much there is.
I'm actually getting really excited as this DIY goes on.
This is gonna look so cool.
So now what you do is you just kind of
mix it all up in there.
And then you're just gonna let it sit for one minute
as you add all the other colors.
Yo this looks!
Okay, actually it looks kinda like kale.
(rustling)
This looks so cool!
So, next all you can do is just take your completed bags
of colored pasta and strain them under cold water.
And hopefully they'll still remain the same color,
so I guess we'll just find out.
No rainbow would be complete without a cloud.
So right now we're gonna make our very own parmesan clouds
and this is very important
that you watch every little detail of how I do this,
because if you don't do this properly
it will not turn out right.
So step number one, you need to coat your pan with oil.
(quiet buzzing)
(soft coughing)
Next place the parmesan on the pan.
Some chefs will spend upwards of 10 years
mastering the technique.
If you don't get the same results when you first try this
don't worry I've been practicing this for many years.
Nah I'm just kidding, this is probably the easiest part
of the entire DIY and somehow I managed to mess it all up.
So the real question is
do you wanna eat boring pasta like this?
Or like this?
Oh my gosh! I can only, yeah definitely not on that pasta!
This pasta looks amazing!
I gotta admit the cheese clouds actually turned out
to look really really cool.
So now this right here is DIY rainbow pasta.
So give this video a thumbs up for the fact that
I think this is the first DIY I've ever done
that actually worked all the way.
So right now it's time to make the rainbow.
We're about to mix it all together and just give it a try.
Before I mix this whole thing up
and turn it in to a giant rainbow,
make sure you guys subscribe to this channel
that'd really mean a lot to me.
But right now all I need is just a fork.
Whoa no, that's way too big, get that out of there!
We can not use that.
This fork here is a little bit more manageable.
So right now let's create a true rainbow.
Let's see, let's just kind of mix it all around.
Oh my gosh this looks so so awesome.
Alright guys, well this has been a super fun video
and now bon appetit!