- Mm.
- What?
- They're edible candy crayons.
- Dude, that's awesome.
- Yeah, they're really good.
Wait, bro, that's a real one.
Dude, what are you doing?
(yells)
Spit it out.
Why would you do that?
- It doesn't even taste good, it doesn't taste good at all.
You challenged us to make a whole bunch
of DIY edible back to school supplies.
That way, when you get hungry in class, you can eat.
There are two ways
to make candy crayons.
One involves Skittles.
- The other fondant.
- Step one, you gotta open the bag.
- Woah, bro (laughs), bro, what did you do?
- [Collins] (laughs) I don't even know.
Hey, at least I got two of 'em in there.
- [Devan] Nice, okay.
- I think I have one in my hair.
- Wait, I wanna check.
(laughs loudly)
I think there's one in my shirt, too.
- Oh, on the back of your shirt (laughs).
- Yep, there it was.
- Step two, gonna separate out the colors of my Skittles.
- And I'm gonna start cutting this fondant
into crayon shapes.
- Let's do it.
(whimsical piano music)
(Skittles clicking)
- Woah, woah, woah, what are you doing?
- Well, I had to divide 'em into only the red ones.
- Oh.
- [Audience] Oh!
- Next up, gonna melt these down
and then turn it into a crayon.
Now, I'm just gonna try to poke 'em and see if they break.
Oh. - Wow,
that looks so cool!
- They look like little flowers or something.
So now we're gonna peel these off.
What are you doing?
- [Devan] I'm rolling it.
- Look like a little DJ, like,
(record scratching)
Now I'm gonna take these
and then I'm gonna turn these into a crayon.
That looks like, not enough for a crayon.
- That does not look like enough.
- Like, in comparison to this,
I dunno how that's gonna work.
Ooh, dude, yeah, - You're pushing it.
- This is actually gonna work!
- Whoa, it's actually working.
- Oh my gosh.
Now I'm gonna kinda like, turn this into a point here.
I've made a crayon.
It's like the pointiest crayon of all time, bro.
You will get some fine defined lines with it.
Ta-da!
I made a crayon you can eat!
- Man, did you just grab one of my wrappers.
Seriously?
- Yeah, but I want to see what color crayon you made.
Bro, did you really have to make like five different colors?
- I mean, uh, yours took a long time.
- You ready, we're gonna eat 'em, here we go.
Three,
- [Both] two, one.
- No, wait, wait, wait, first I've got a challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
Here we go, you ready for it?
- I'm ready.
- Seven,
- [Both] six, five, four, three, two, one (laugh)
- Time.
If you can do that, comment down below,
Keyper Squad, right now, what are you doing?
- (laughs) I forgot how to count on my fingers for a second.
- And this is a back to school video, Devan.
Here we go.
- Alright.
Wait, what, you actually caught that?
Alright, here I go.
- Oh my God.
Oh. - Mmm.
- This is the greatest tasting crayon of all.
- Mm, this is so good.
- What's up, dudes?
My first day of school, man, how you doing? (laughs)
(spits)
You are about to learn how to make an edible glue stick,
so, - Yep.
- There's gonna be two different versions of this.
Version number one is gonna be with the frosting.
- And the other one is gonna be with Starburst.
- Step one, you need to dismantle your glue stick.
- You just have to remove the glue from the glue stick.
- I like the way the word dismantle more.
Just twist your glue stick a lot
and then just, whee. - I dunno if this,
I can't tell if this part was supposed to be (laughs),
did you throw it?
- No.
Alright, next step, you're gonna wash out your glue stick.
And we're back.
- Next up, I'm gonna start unwrapping my Starburst.
What are you doing?
- I'm about to open this up with one finger.
- Oh!
- Aw, man.
First step for me is punching this Starburst
into this tube.
Three, two, one.
(yells)
(groans)
You have no idea how hard this is.
Okay, I think I got it.
Nope.
- I'm about to fill myself with fro, I mean my (laughs),
Bro, I'm crying I'm laughing so hard right now,
this is not good.
- (groans) Oh, why is this not working?
- (groans) Sorry, bro, I'm messing up.
- Oh, no, that doesn't look like it's working.
Ooh, this technique is working.
This works really well.
- [Collins] Oh, you got it?
- Yeah, you just don't do it on the table,
'cause it gets stuck.
- A little bit of excess on the edge, so just,
- What?
- It's done!
While Devan's finishing his,
I'm gonna pop this in the freezer for a few minutes,
so, yeah, I'll be right back.
Whoa, jeez.
- Did you almost fall?
- Yep.
Bam, got mine out the freezer.
Yo! - Whoa!
Look at that!
- [Collins] Oh my gosh.
- That's so awesome.
- See, the thing is, mine actually looks like a glue stick,
so in class, I wouldn't get in trouble.
But Devan, on the other hand,
- Yeah, I didn't think about that.
- This was suggested by the Instagram Keyper of the Week--
- Oh no!
Oh no! - What was that?
So if you want a big shot
to be Instagram Keyper of the Week,
check the description down below to find out how.
But right now, Devan, grab your glue stick,
- I have to find it.
I think I broke the five-second rule.
- Three,
- [Both] two, one.
- I'm just gonna glue my paper over here.
(sputters)
(laughs) - Mm.
- Oh my gosh.
- So good.
(mumbles)
- You said, what was that?
I'm sorry, I can't understand you, what?
- This is a lot of frosting.
- Huh?
I think you're saying we're moving on to the next one?
Got it.
- Now, you could prank everyone
with this next DIY edible food,
right, what, oh, dude, this is so cool.
- I know, right?
- I've always wanted to eat this.
It's so powdery.
It's so delicious-looking, bro.
- Mm, I think I did way too much.
- I wonder how many of these I can fit in my mouth.
- No!
- Mm-hmm.
I've seen this on every Instagram not satisfied compilation.
- Whoa.
(slurps)
(gasps)
- It's my tongue.
(spits)
You literally just spit all over me, Devan.
- It wasn't on purpose.
- Well, ya did it!
Fun bonus, ow, life hack,
is that if you wanna get super muscular cheeks,
which I'm not saying you do,
But if you do, this is what you do.
Grab yourself one of these long balloons,
- Okay.
- and then try to blow it up.
So Devan, go for it.
It's actually really difficult,
like it's, - I'm literally trying
as hard as I can.
- But if you keep practicing every day,
someday, you'll be able to do this.
- What?
Wait, how?
- Yeah, it's just extreme cheek muscles.
Don't pop it. - Oh, I tried to pop it.
Bye-bye, balloon.
Alright, so what you do
is you just take this little part here,
and you just wrap it around.
You good there?
- I'm so good.
- What are you doing?
- I've got an idea.
Gonna roll it up and then toss it up, 'cause it's a gumball.
(gum thuds)
Ow.
Here we go.
- [Audience] Yay!
- Oh, nailed it.
Right as I finished, too.
You ready for this.
I'm pretty sure this goes this way.
Put it down in there.
Whoa, look at that.
I guess you just pull it from here,
and then you, ooh, that actually worked.
- Mm-hmm.
This is an awesome prank you can pull on your friends
when you go back to school.
Basically, if you take a glue container, you empty it out,
now you're gonna wanna go to the sink and wash it out,
because you want no glue left in here whatsoever.
Once you've emptied them out,
now it's time to fill them up with a liquid,
so Devan's got some water for his.
- Oh, this is going well.
- Oh, yeah, that was not smooth, Devan.
- Don't make me laugh.
- Alright, so I've got some milk for mine.
Look at that precision. - Ooh.
(slurps)
Alright, there you go.
- (coughs) I tasted the glue, bro.
Now that it's prepared, you're ready for the prank.
So here's how it works.
You're sitting in class chillin'
and you're a little bit thirsty.
Hey guys, any of you have any water?
No one's got water.
You're like, what?
And then you pick up your glue and you go like,
yo, peep this out, fam.
(splutters)
Not that aggressively.
- No, no, no, no, don't shoot it straight up.
No, that's not a good idea (laughs).
Now we're gonna make an eraser.
- Wooh.
- No, no, no, no, I want it, bro, what are you doing?
No, no, no, I want it, wait, what?
- Again?
- Seriously?
- Well, I guess we're gonna grab out three red ones each.
There we go. - No, no, no,
the pink ones, we're making a pink eraser.
- Oh.
Just keep in mind, you're not a yellow Starburst.
- Mm-mm.
- You're a pink one.
This next part may sound very difficult,
and it probably will be,
but we're gonna try to make it easy.
You're gonna have to like,
meld three separate Starbursts into one.
How?
Where's our blowtorch when you really need it?
- Wait, no, no, no, no, no, you can't do that.
- Devan had the brilliant idea to first put it into a ball
and then, from there, mush it into the eraser shape.
- Ooh, this looks cool, it's like a marble ball.
- [Collins] Oh, that looks really neat.
- Alright, I feel like it's a bouncy ball, no!
- It's not bouncy.
I'm gonna try to stretch my Star, oh,
I'm breaking my Starburst.
- Alright, my eraser is, what is that for?
- I knew rulers had to come in handy
at some point in my life.
- It's just gonna get stuck.
You're gonna have two rulers stuck together.
- Shh.
- Sorry.
- I have a great idea.
Let's uh,
- You can start over?
Oh, okay.
So for this next part, I'm going to use an X-Acto knife.
- So for this part, make sure you have parental supervision
if you're doing this at home.
- (groans) That didn't work.
- I have a life hack, I have a life hack.
- No, no!
- I'm sorry, Devan, it had to be done,
and right now, we're moving on to the finale.
A notebook, let's do it.
This is the big finale.
It's an entirely edible notebook,
like every single thing is edible.
That way you can write notes to someone,
pass it to them, it's like, if the teacher calls you out,
you can literally just eat the note.
This right here is something called sugar sheet,
so it's like paper made out of entirely sugar.
Can you get the pens open?
- I got it.
- There are also pens that the ink is edible.
I guess you can, like, decorate food with it and stuff.
- I wonder.
Don't bump me.
Don't, I see your hand.
Alright, I'm making one more red line right next to it.
- Jeez, these pages are gonna be looking so spicy, bro.
- Look at that! - Oh my gosh.
- Ooh, it looks so good.
- Alright, so next step is the lines,
so I have the black pen for you, so I'm gonna,
- No, no, no, they're blue.
It's a good thing I'm making this.
- While he's doing that, I've got some Twizzlers
I was gonna deconstruct right now
and turn them into the book pages.
Yo, these are cool.
(whimsical piano music)
- You're not eating it, are you?
- Of course not.
Devan's gonna punch holes out of the pages
as I decorate the artwork on the front of it.
I know you're thinking I'm not an artist.
But I'm about to be.
- I cannot wait to see what this turns out like.
- Bro, it's gonna be legendary.
- I'm just realizing that I did this in the wrong order.
This stuff is supposed to be done at the same time
that we have the cover and all of the other pages,
or else none of the holes are gonna line up.
So, yeah.
- Before I reveal to you guys my masterpiece,
I just wanna let you guys know
that on a completely unrelated note,
I recently got stung by a bee on my finger,
which really hurt, and here's my cover.
- Wow.
- It's a giant foot, and it's a dude saying,
oh no, and he's like, it's a bee, and then there's a bee,
and then it's like, it's a foot, it's a foot,
and it's stinky.
- My favorite part is the foot is saying it's a foot.
- The bee's looking mad, dangerous, bro,
it's coming in hot with that stinger.
- But I think you nailed it, you did a really good job.
Okay, I'm gonna try to peel this off.
- Okay.
- It's so weirdly flexible.
- I know, it's like, paper.
- Think about that, man, rolling through the school year
with this all year,
you'll be the most popular kid, for sure.
- If you don't eat it before you get
to the end of the school year.
- I mean, 'cause it just, what's more delicious
than a bee about to sting, it's a foot.
Oh, I nailed it! - Woah.
They're like sprinkles.
- [Collins] Alright, next step is the binding.
- I hope the pages don't crack.
- And here you have it, the coolest binder of all time,
'cause ya can eat it! - Wow.
Yeah!
- So right now, guys, we're about to take
our very first bite, but first,
if you want to be featured in the next video,
comment down below right now and let us know
what school supply should we turn into an edible food.
You ready to take a bite of it?
- I'm ready.
- Three, two, one.
- Whoa.
I'm gonna take a bite of yours.
Mm.
- Yeah, this is (mumbles) tastes really good.
- This is so cool.
- (mumbles) I gotta eat the gummy.
(laughs)
If you want to see another video, click right over here,
and right now, click right over here, I dare you,
click right here, I dare you, do it.
- Ya gonna do it?
- Right now, go click on the video.
Alright, we love you, bye! - Bye!