- You want to see me eat the sourest slime in the world.
(howling)
You challenged me to make
DIY edible candy slime.
And first of all, I had no idea you were even able to eat
certain types of slime.
But we are doing three types.
We're doing the gummy slime, we're doing the candy slime
where we mix a whole bunch of candy into the gummy slime
and the last one, I have to eat sour slime.
I didn't even know that was a thing.
It involves malic acid, toxic waste,
and my taste buds becoming destroyed.
That's happening at the end of the video
but right now to kick things off,
we need to melt some gummy bears.
That is a lot, that's like the most amount
of gummy bears I've seen in my entire life.
And one thing to be cautious of
is when you melt them in the microwave
only do increments of 10 seconds,
otherwise it might burn.
So, right now, let's go heat 'em up.
One thing that I think is very important,
is that you learn from my mistakes in these videos
and I just made a massive mistake,
I had this brilliant idea that if I combine
all the colors, it would make a beautiful rainbow.
Instead it looks like this
and guys this does not look appealing.
This looks kind of like caramel,
kinda a little bit like something else.
I'm not about the color of this,
it's not aesthetically pleasing.
So for this, I went a little bit extra
and I actually divided out all the different colors,
so this can be for the basic slime,
this will be for the candy slime
and this will be for the sour slime.
Colored coded and everything.
I just melted up all the blue gummy bears
and this looks so much better, like this looks so cool.
It looks like the ocean is in gummy form.
Like this looks delicious, I'm so excited.
Next up is the corn starch and then the powdered sugar
so I'm going to add an equal amount in here.
Mix it all around, put it in here
and that's what's going to create the slime.
So, the powder sugar is
what's going to turn this into a, no!
I'm so bad at this.
Wow, my DIY skills are not good at all
I'm definitely not Grady Garcia, that is for sure.
The cornstarch is really cool because it actually
makes it were the slime won't stick to you.
And I remember this stuff
from when we made that giant pool of Oobleck,
and so, yeah, I know the smell of cornstarch.
Hm, very well.
(upbeat music)
- [Man On Left] Oh my god.
- Holy cow.
And John's in it for real.
- So we're gonna dump a little bit in right now
I really messed this up because you're supposed
to put them both in this bowl
and then mix them together, but
(laughs)
I think I'm gonna do away with the spoon right now.
We're gonna go in with the hands
and just go crazy.
Alright, so get the last of the slime off the spoon
Ooh, this already feels so weird and so sticky.
It doesn't feel at all like slime.
It literally just feels like
well, of course, like melted gummy bears.
But, I don't know what to do with the spoon,
so I'm gonna just leave it over here.
A little bit of cross contamination
never hurt anybody (laughing)
said no scientist ever.
So, alright, I think I'm gonna have to
go with both hands here
We're gonna try to work it through.
The great thing is it's not really like sticking.
No, it's sticking to me.
It's definitely uh
yeah, it's all over me.
This is not good.
Okay, this is not even like candy.
This doesn't look appealing at the moment.
How does this look?
Not good.
This is just a hot mess, man.
It's just a hot mess.
It looks like an alien substance, too,
I mean, it doesn't even look like an appealing slime video.
Like ya know when you see the videos on Instagram
where they're playing with it?
It looks so beautiful, like aawww?
And it looks so gorgeous?
Yeah, this...
that doesn't look good.
It's getting there a little bit.
I just need a lot more of the powdered sugar
and the cornstarch.
I'm gonna, aha it's on the back of my hand,
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can we get a little more of the powdered sugar
and then we're gonna go from there.
I think I need a bigger bowl, though.
Alright, now time to transfer into the bigger bowl, so
Ah, it's dripping, it's dripping,
it's dripping, it's dripping
Ah, ah.
It's so stressful, okay, now it's all in my hands.
So how do I get it off my hands?
Like, I need.
I don't know how to do this.
Melted gummy bears is a very sticky substance.
It's getting even worse.
Okay, yeah, that's not happening.
Oh, it's actually turning into slime.
I cracked the code.
I'm a genius.
I had no idea that would work,
so now we take it to the next level,
and I'll now put the powdered sugar and
cornstarch in my hands,
and I'm going all hand action right now.
This is just
you can use the thumbs to kinda mush it in.
So, look, I open up a little bit and
then we push together like this,
and then, kinda, squeeze,
and manipulate, and it all falls out, man.
It's the issue that's not combining it
That's my issue with it.
It's just, and then gets stringy.
Fam.
Hm.
Why stringy?
So let's make this, Eric.
I was gonna go back to this technique
it's just so much powder.
So much powder in the air.
So we go here, and we're
gonna try to use like the high-five technique on it.
(gasps) It's getting so much better, actually.
Look at this.
It's getting, oh my gosh, yes, yes.
Bless, yes.
Here we go, I'm gonna take a handful of it now
I'm gonna retrieve some more of it down here
Okay, there we go.
My slime gonna eat it.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
This is like a real work-out, too, man.
I've gotta do this two more times.
Holy cow.
I wonder if I can make a giant bubble with it.
'Cause you guys know I'm great at blowing bubbles
when it comes to the slime.
(blowing)
Nope.
It's starting to peel off my hands now
which is kind of like what it's supposed to do,
but at the same time, its not like,
it's getting more slimy.
But this looks actually
really, really, really cool.
Aw.
Aw, man, there's so much powdered sugar everywhere.
The, ugh.
It is getting better, though.
It is getting a lot better.
This takes a lot of hand strength.
You've gotta see the full extension of this, like.
Ah, what's up.
(light-hearted music)
Oh!
That just shot everywhere.
That was not good, you gotta see this.
We're starting to get sliminess.
Okay, yeah, 'cause it's starting to come off my hands.
That's a good sign.
Oh, yeah, mmhm.
Turn up, it's my party time.
Next up I'm gonna be tasting it
because I think it's kinds getting to
like slime levels.
If I can just get it off my hands
and not as sticky,
then we'll be in very good shape.
That didn't work.
It's all over my hands,
but we're gonna go with it.
(coughing)
Eventually.
Alright, guys, I think we've gotten into
a really, really good place now.
Look at this slime, it looks so cool.
So right now I'm about to taste this
edible candy slime,
but first I've got a challenge.
I wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel.
Turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up
in seven seconds.
Here we go. you ready?
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one,
Done, if you can do that,
comment down below KEYPER SQUAD right now,
and we're gonna be going through and replying to people
who are able to do all three of those things
in seven seconds.
By the way please don't comment
about how bad that hand countdown was.
I've slime on my hands.
Here we go.
I get to eat this candy slime that
looks so delicious.
It looks like cotton candy.
Here we go three,
I'm just gonna go.
Two, I'm so excited.
One.
Mmm.
That was really good.
This stuff is like super sticky as well.
And you put it in your mouth
and it's like sticks to every area of your mouth.
It makes you feel like you can't talk.
Like this is the inside of your mouth.
You try and talk and like, oh man.
(laughing) This is so cool.
Right now we're taking this to the next level.
(laughing) I love how my hands look.
High five.
They don't stick.
What happened?
(laughing) It's so cool.
This is when things get really exciting because
we're doing the exact same thing
with the red ones,
only this time we're adding a tonne of candy
and then for the last one
we're doing a tonne of sour candies.
Right now, lets heat these up
and lets make, let's make that slime.
Woohoo.
Now this looks so delicious.
It literally looks like strawberry jelly.
And I wanna eat it right now,
but I have to us patience.
I have to first mix in everything.
Last time we did this, that was
my first time doing it,
and it definitely didn't go according to plan.
So this time we're gonna be much more precise about it.
We have the mixing bowl right over here.
So we're gonna take the cornstarch first
add that into the bowl.
And then next we take the powdered sugar,
gonna add an equal amount into the bowl as well
Feel like a true baker right now.
And this time instead of playing with my hands
I'm gonna be professional
and use a spoon to mix it all up.
So we're gonna dump it all in.
That's a lot.
And then we're gonna just kind of go for it.
Here we go.
Yo, that looks so crazy.
Yeah, so I think this is, okay note to self
this is definitely working a lot better
than what I did with my hands.
So, I've pulled a lot of shenanigans before
I don't know why I didn't do it
the way you're supposed to do it before.
But this, it almost looks like a candy cane right now.
Just like the way the white is mixing in with the red.
I'm gonna mix it up a little bit more.
Oh, you know what this reminds me of?
It reminds me of those deserts,
What are they called?
They're like,
you find them in like Japanese restaurants.
Oh, mochi, that's it.
It's called a mochi,
and it's like this ice creamy kind of desert
that looks like it has the same texture as this.
And I think it's like powdered sugar
or flour, or something.
I don't know, some mysterious substance on the outside,
but, man, it's getting really tough to move.
Okay, here we go.
Oh my gosh.
My hand's getting so tired.
Oh my gosh
I like, want to get my hands on it.
Okay, I think
I'm done with this spoon, guys.
I wanna get my hands on this stuff.
It looks, looks so cool.
Hopefully it won't be as sticky as last time.
'Cause last time, ya know, it was pretty intense.
But here we go.
I'm gonna pick it up.
Let's see, oh.
It feels so cool.
It's like really stringy,
really hot, but definitely not as sticky
I think because it has like a tonne of cornstarch
coating it right now.
I'm just kinda like mix it up, oh.
This is so cool.
Yeah, it's definitely very sticky.
I should've coated my hands first.
What was I thinking, No, no, no I need to be a baker.
Think baker, think baker thoughts.
No!
Here we go.
Rescue myself.
Remove, remove, okay.
This hand only has a little bit of slime on it,
so I'm gonna try to coat here.
I'm gonna try to coat this hand in cornstarch.
Here we go.
I should have definitely done this beforehand.
But here we go, okay.
So if I coat my hand in cornstarch,
theoretically, the slime won't stick to me.
Yeah, my theory didn't work, it's still sticking to me, so
I went way too early.
I should've been patient.
I should've used patience.
It smells really good, but I should've used patience.
Two hours later.
Well now it's turned into more like
a snowball than anything else
cuss it's like whee. (laughing)
This stuff is crazy, but it's looking
like slime as well,
and so now it's time to add
the candy into what's going on.
Right now what I'm gonna do
is I'm actually gonna take this
and then I'm gonna open it up
and use it as kind of like a bowl.
I'm gonna dump all the candy into it.
And then, after that,
we're gonna mix it all together and
taste it to see
how the candy-gummies slime tastes.
So first I think we're gonna add in some
good old jelly beans.
Oh, way too many jelly beans.
Alright, we're gonna use a few Gob Stoppers,
Okay, perfect, oh, no.
That green one, man, that was uncalled for.
I was not expecting you, you are not supposed to be here,
But I'll let you stay, you're cool.
Next we'll add some Pop Rocks,
and these things kinda trip me out, hold up.
Ugh.
(fireworks exploding)
In my haste and excitement,
I kinda used up
kinda all of them.
At least we got to enjoy them one way or another.
And then next we have these
Are these Pop Rocks as well?
(bleating)
Nope, okay.
We'll add these in here.
That looks so cool.
Also got some Razzles we're gonna add into the mix here.
Perfect, and then we have some of these things here.
These are Cookie Dough Birthday Cake Bites.
I've heard that these are amazing,
so I'm really excited to add these.
That was a lot of them.
But that's eh, that fine.
Alright, we're gonna kinda squish them in.
This is looking delicious.
I think we've also got some, um, some Nerds.
I'm gonna add these in.
Perfect.
We have now entered the Nerd zone.
Alright, here we go, the moment of truth
to see if we can mix all this candy into it.
So, I don't know how to do this.
I'm just gonna kinda squish it together.
This is not gonna work at all.
I have little faith
Little to no faith at the moment.
We're gonna use the thumb technique again.
The thumb massage is kinda thumb it over.
The thumb technique comes in handy, man.
Very versatile if you can master the thumb technique
you're good, so I'm just gonna kinda like turn,
implant them all inside of it. (gasps)
This is working, oh my gosh, yes.
I literally thought there was no way this would work,
but this is actually working.
Hold up.
This is crazy.
As long as there all stuck in there,
that's the most important thing.
(grunting)
Yo, that's like looking so cool.
Yes!
Woohoo!
I'm hyped right now.
This was a massive success.
Now is the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Time to taste the candy, DIY edible slime
here we go, three, two, I'm so excited
There we go.
One.
Mmm.
Alright, I'm gonna take another bite.
This stuff is so ow.
Ow ow.
I'm sorry, there's a lot of crunchy candies involved
And like I don't expect that.
It's so nice, like fluffy, slimy
and you bite into a candy and it's like. (imitates cracking)
Ah.
It'll attack you bro
I wish you could taste it right now.
It's like all the best candies mixed into one.
My mouth is glued.
I can't, I can't talk.
Now we are moving on to the final one
which is the sour slime.
(chattering)
Now this looks like slime.
These Gummie Bears melted
and this literally looks like sour slime
without even adding any sour candy to it.
And the process of making this into slime is gonna be
a little bit different this time
because we're still gonna use cornstarch
but instead of the powdered sugar,
we're gonna be using malic acid,
which is the sourest thing ever.
This is the stuff they put on sour candy.
This is, hands down, the worse.
So, again, we'll kick it off with the cornstarch right here,
And now comes the fun part, adding in
some malic acid.
Oh, my gosh.
I get chills
just from thinking about how bad this stuff is.
I've had some terrible, terrible experiences with it.
(screaming)
Alright.
Let's mix it up.
(light music)
And it's back in my hands.
I've got a tonne of cornstarch
but this stuff is still super sticky.
So I was saying out of all them so far
this is like the hardest one
to get to the right consistency.
I think it's because we used the malic acid on it.
But hopefully this will turn out.
But at the moment it's just
it's crumbling.
Malic acid, man, always ruining everything,
across the board, twenty-four-seven.
(screaming)
Well that's kinda cool.
(blowing)
(laughing)
This stuff looked like the most slimy stuff
out of all of it.
Like this, it looks kinda toxic in a way.
Ya know what I mean?
I've created a bowl with it
and now it's time to add all the sour candience.
Of course we're kicking it off
with some toxic waste right here.
I gotta add two more of these ones,
as you guys know are intense.
Gotta pour some Cry Babies.
Personal favorite.
There we go, a couple of Sour Dots.
I'm not looking forward to biting into this.
And then we also have some sour Warhead spray.
My fingers are stuck together, this is so hard.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, okay,
Alright, here we go.
(coughing)
I breathed in some of that mist from the sour spray, man.
That went down the wrong way.
Okay, we're gonna take this and close it up.
Hoo.
Oh, no.
This stuff is going to be so, so intense.
I am not looking forward to biting this.
Oh my gosh, look
It's not even like sticking into it, man.
This stuff's so sour
It's like, we will not become part of the slime.
Here we go, I'm about to take a bite into
the sourest slime in the world,
but first, if you want to be featured
in the next video,
comment down below
How many pounds of slime
should I fill a pool with.
Also, congratulations to the keyper of the week, Claudia.
If you want to be keyper of the week
check the description down below to find out how.
You wanna see me eat the sourest slime in the world,
here we go, three two one.
Ooh!
It looks like a little like a little like a hammock.
Dude, it looks like a little hammock.
Ha, That's so cool.
You (clears throat)
You challenge me to make soup.
Nope.
(laughing)
(coughing)