- Yo I can't believe it worked.
You challenged me to make DIY gummy fidget spinners.
One of them's going to be a normal sized fidget spinner,
like ow, like this.
Another one's going to be a medium sized fidget spinner
and the last one is going to be the world's largest
gummy fidget spinner.
But right now let's have some fun and do
some fidget spinner tricks.
(upbeat rock music)
Let's go.
♫ Three, two, one, go
♫ Go
(crashing)
Yeah so now that I've officially mastered
the fidget spinner tricks it's time to move on to making
the first gummy fidget spinner.
It's actually really easy to make gummy fidget spinners.
All you need are a few things.
You need some boiling water,
which you are going to add into a bowl.
You're also going to need some gelatin.
You are then going to add that into a bowl.
(sniffing)
(coughing)
You're actually going to take a whisk
and you're just going to want to whisk it in there
and mix it all together.
Uh oh.
Okay you've got to do it quick 'cause otherwise
it's going to get all messed up.
Whip it to the sauce boy.
Now that we have the water and the gelatin mixed up,
it's time to add the food coloring.
And the Instagram Keyper of the Week suggested we add blue
and if you want to be shouted out as the Instagram
Keyper of the Week check the description down below
to find out how.
Now we're only going to use two drops of this
so here we go.
We're going to do it from a high distance
because I'm feeling very dangerous.
He's lined up.
The tension's building.
(dripping)
Oh kind of missed it.
Drop number two I gotta make this one more successful
so we'll start off in the bowl and we'll do
a direct lift strategy.
I'm going from even higher this time
because I feel super dangerous.
I really hope my calculations are correct.
(dripping)
Yay a direct hit!
Okay now it's time to mix it up.
Whoa!
That got blue very quickly.
It took like a whisk and a half to get very blue.
Now we have the gelatin, the water, it smells terrible,
we have the food coloring in and it's time
to pour it into the mold.
And this right here is the mold.
If you want to know how to make this just check out
the video I did on candy fidget spinners.
We're just going to dump this in so,
this looks really weird.
It's kind of like gushy if that's even a word.
Okay I think I need to stop there.
Oh it's over spilling.
(shrieking)
Now we're going to be putting it in the fridge
and we're going to see whether or not we can actually
make the gummy fidget spinner spin,
that's a lot of spins,
but let's spin into the next part.
(slamming)
Oh geez alright guys well now it's ready.
That probably didn't work because you can like
see my hand drop it.
And now time to see if it worked or not.
Let's see if we can pop it out of the mold.
Well it's definitely very gummy.
Fam, this is looking real floppy.
It's all wet too.
Oh gosh I need to kind of like dry it out a little bit.
(breath blowing)
Gonna flip it over, kind of like roast it on both sides.
Boom, roasted.
So now we need to add the center
of the fidget spinner to it.
So to do that you have to take
one of your original fidget spinners.
You pop out one of these things.
And then (imitates pinging).
Tutorial.
And then we're going to put this in here.
Now it's time to find out
can we make the gummy fidget spinner spin.
But first I have a challenge.
I want to see if you can subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds.
Can you do it?
Here we go.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
(laughing)
Done.
If you can do that comment Keyper Squad right now.
Let's forget about whatever that was
and let's try to make this spin.
Well the camera stopped rolling for like one second
and then this happened.
So I don't know how I'm going
to recover this off of the table.
Help, please don't break.
It's so close fam.
It's starting to split.
What happened?
Gummy fidget, no!
(crying)
You had so much potential.
Alright well, no way we can make it spin
but I do have a solution,
an innovation I think could make this work.
Oh my heart, it breaks as my fidget breaks.
Here's what I'm going to try to do.
I'm going to see if I can actually get this.
I'm going to get one side over here, sheboimps,
get one side over here, sheboimps,
and then whatever's left of this side over here, sheboimps.
Oh no, hmm.
See how it's kind of on there because there's no way
it's going to spin on its own.
Let's see if I can get this to spin.
The moment of truth.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Oh no my fidget.
(crashing)
Well I think now we move on to the medium one.
I look at it this way.
We're learning from the mistakes.
This did not work at all but moving on to the next one
I think I'm going to add a lot more gelatin
and so this medium sized one I have a really good feeling
it's going to work.
But at least I get to try it, though.
(gagging)
(coughing)
Oh man, it's like straight gelatin and water.
It's like an aftertaste.
Alright for the medium one, to make sure it's a success
I'm adding 20 packets
into this container.
And check out this trick I learned.
Are you ready for this?
(pan clattering)
Alright this water is very, very, very hot
and just like the little version of this
there's a lot of steam.
We are going to be adding a whole bunch of hot water
into this pan, so let's hope this goes well.
Oh boy.
Yay we're doing good.
This is so far a success.
This is very hot, like I can feel the heat coming off of it
and I think we're good right there.
Alright, I didn't burn myself.
Mission accomplished.
Now that we've added all the water it's time to add
the gelatin packets.
Now I've opened them up as you can see.
I want to keep them as far away from me
'cause they smell disgusting
but this is 20 packets of gelatin all in one container.
It's going to be so bad when I mix it with the hot water.
Okay I'm going to be mixing it as it's going in.
Oh no this is not working.
It's clumping.
(coughing)
Oh it's spilling.
Oh my gosh okay yah I definitely put way too much water.
I'm going to go for this technique.
Oh my gosh this is just a disaster.
No it's so much gelatin.
Work with me fam I need to make this cool.
This smells horrible, this looks horrible,
and I did a horrible job at mixing it together
so hopefully this turns out not horrible.
And last but not least I can't forget
to add the food coloring.
It smells so disgusting right now
but you guys all suggested pink for the medium sized one
so we'll add this in here.
I'm going to be a little bit more liberal with this,
just kind of distribute it evenly.
Just one, two.
Yo this looks so crazy and like my eyes are really
enjoying the visuals of it but my nose is suffering
so much right now.
You guys have no idea how toxic
and it just smells so, so bad.
So hopefully it looks good though in the end
and let's pop it in the refrigerator.
- [SpongeBob's Narrator] Two hours later.
- Fidget spinner versus Jello.
Three, two, one.
(thud)
(crickets chirping)
Yeah that's probably going to get cut.
That was really boring.
And then I'm going to leave it in.
The Jello is now ready and this is the most dangerous part
of this entire video because I cut out right now
a mold of the fidget spinner so we're going
to place this down and then use an exacto knife to cut out
the gummy into a fidget spinner.
So if you do this at home, be very careful.
Make sure you have parental supervision
with the knife.
I was about to say cuts through like butter
but it actually cuts through like Jello.
(laughing)
Almost there, we're coming around the back side now.
Coming close to the beginning again.
Boom, done.
(thud)
Ow almost broke my finger.
Let's see if I can get this out.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Yo this looks crazy.
(laughing)
On the bottom of it it has the words
from the bottom of the tin printed into it.
Now it's time to cut out the hole in the middle
and this one looks like it has the potential
to be able to spin unlike the rest of them.
We're just going to have to eyeball it,
going to have to go for it, just use my instincts.
Channel my inner gummy.
Here we go, alright.
(upbeat music)
I'm feeling good, I'm getting good vibes.
Oops.
(ominous music)
Here we go.
The moment of truth.
Going to pop it out.
Yay we did it! (cheering)
There we go, it's a fidget spinner made out of gummy.
Uh oh it's starting to crack so we're going to
pop it on a fidget spinner just like this,
kind of position it properly.
It's touching the ground.
That's going to be very.
(gasping)
Sorry I just got very excited for a split second.
This might work, it has potential.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Yo that's about as close as we're going to get.
Now it's time to see--
No!
If we can get it to spin on its own.
It's not going to happen.
The big one has to work.
That one cannot break at all but I'm going to try
a bit of this right now.
I think it's going to taste disgusting
but it looks delicious, but the looks can be deceiving, so.
Look how disgusting this looks on the back.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(gagging)
Okay, we're good, we're back.
Back in action.
This just tastes so disgusting because you've got to know
what's in Jello.
Google it or don't, because you'll never eat Jello again.
We're moving on right now to the final one
which is the massive gummy fidget spinner.
(crashing)
Ow.
Instead of showing you the exact same process
for the third time by filling it with hot water
and then gelatin, I thought let's just fast forward
right now and then you guys wanted me to make
a blue version, a pink version and green version
and we're going to be fitting these pieces
into a massive gummy fidget spinner.
I've got a whole bunch of cutouts right here
and right now I'm going to place a cutout on each one
and then we are going to cut it out.
- [SpongeBob Narrator] One eternity later.
(laughing)
- This looks so funny.
It looks almost like a little hairy beard
that I have around my face like hello.
(screaming)
And there you have it guys, the final piece
of the gummy fidget spinner.
And now it's time to put it all together.
This next part is kind of like a puzzle
because we're going to take each of these pieces
and fit them together, see how they all go.
Place a blue one here, oh I get it, I get it, I get it.
It goes like this, yeah.
It goes like that and with the, aha, yup, yup,
the blue one here, yeah.
And then we do the pink one.
Nope.
What combination am I missing.
There's literally three pieces.
It's been brought to my attention that I had it
flipped the wrong way.
So now let's try this, let's see.
(cheering)
This is now, guys, the largest gummy fidget spinner
in the entire world and now the moment
you've all been waiting for.
Time to go outside and make it spin.
Let's go.
Now because I couldn't find a giant version of
whatever it is that makes a fidget spinner spin,
the thing in the middle, I don't know, it's like magic.
I don't know how it all works.
I had to get one of these here which is a giant
cake spinner and now I'm going to be putting
the fidget spinner on this,
spinning it around and then I also have a giant
cake mold over here.
It looks like a ninja throwing star.
(thudding)
It's over there now but we're going to grab it in a second.
I've now reacquired my ninja star.
I got it from that way.
No, no, no, no, no that way.
Okay let's do this.
The ninja star goes on the spinner
and now we're going to be grabbing the gummies.
So first we're going to grab the blue gummy.
Have to remember how this goes.
I think the blue gummy goes over here.
(ominous music)
Oh no, don't get grass on you my friend.
Now we've got the red or pink gummy.
I can't really figure out which one is which,
and I'll pop that right there.
And now we have the green gummy, the final piece.
Here we go, guys.
We're about to spin the world's largest
gummy fidget spinner but first if you want to
be featured in the next video, comment down below
what should we make our next fidget spinner out of?
But right now the moment of truth.
Will it spin?
Three, two, one.
Alright now we've got to spin it up a little bit.
No!
You know guys I'd say that worked
and that's it.
I love you all so much.
This is like my tongue.
Bye!