- ( Collins Key ) This is the largest melted gummy snake
turned into sour slime.
Three, two, one.
You challenge me to melt giant gummy food
into edible DIY candy slime that you can actually eat.
And so to do this, I got my friend Natalie
from Natlie's Outlet over here.
She is the queen when it comes to pranks,
when it comes to DIY, so she's gonna be helping me out.
Today we are making three types of edible candy slime.
The first one is out of a giant gummy worm.
- The second one is watermelon flavored slime.
- And the last one...
- Oh.
- And for the last one, we are melting
this eight foot long giant gummy snake
into the sourest candy slime in the world.
And then we're gonna eat it.
So right now, let's get started.
- How to does this work?
- Make this super rare slime.
First we need to melt the giant gummy worm.
So let's do this.
- Ready?
- Yep.
Okay, go towards the bottom.
Oh, that looks so cool.
We're like burning it.
Try to keep it like--
uh-oh.
It smells really good though.
Alright, it's kinda...
- It's catching fire.
- Oh yeah, it is on fire.
It's starting to drip though.
It's starting to drip.
Come on, I believe in you.
Oh my gosh, there we go.
That's a lot of it dripping out.
Oh, that's a lot of smoke.
Oh, we don't have time for fire alarms.
Okay, inside is getting kinda burned and kinda charred.
If you do this at home be very careful.
Make you sure you have parental supervision.
But it's kinda working a little bit.
We are melting the gummy.
I'm gonna try this really quick.
Just kind of see how it's tasting so far.
It taste delicious.
- Hmm.
- But this is not quite working how
I thought it would, because look at this.
It's like a crusty mound right...
Ow, that's hot.
It's working, it's working!
Yes, woohoo!
- Woohoo!
- This is so cool.
This literally reminds me of when we were doing
that liquid metal fidget spinner.
The way this thing is melting is crazy.
- It's bubbling.
So now that we've melted it, we're gonna add
some cornstarch.
Kind of eyeball it and then we're gonna make some slime.
- Yeah!
I done this before one time where I accidentally used
my hands prematurely.
Bad idea.
Ah, it's on the back of my hand.
No, no, no, no, no.
So we're gonna use a spoon for as long
as we possibly can to make it.
Oh my gosh.
It's starting to get stringy, so I think we need
a little bit more cornstarch.
And then we're also gonna want to add a little bit
of powdered sugar in.
This is how we'll make it taste good.
Now we're gonna switch of stirring duties.
Not 'cause my arm got tired at all,
just because I think it would be great to share.
Everyone gets to have a little bit
of the experience.
These videos are never clean.
Ever.
So ladies first.
I'll let you...
Let you do your thing.
I'm a gentlemen when it comes to candy slime.
I've learned that to have good slime it shouldn't
stick to your hands, but like it's stuck to my hands.
It's like my hand is sneezing.
Oh, there's still more slime left in the bowl
that has not been mixed yet.
Whoa, this spoon is covered.
Yo, I've got a new idea for a candy.
It's called the sugar spoon.
Stick it into powdered sugar...
Like the cinnamon challenge.
Quick, high five.
Oh! - Oh!
- We're like stuck together now.
You know what's missing right now?
- What?
- Some nerds.
Alright, so we're gonna add some nerds in
what's going on.
- Woo, party.
- Yo this is so...
(Collin sneezes)
- Ew.
- This looks so, so cool.
'Cause now it's not only candy slime,
but now there's like this little bumps here
where you can see the nerds.
- So you wanna taste it?
- I think yeah, it's time to taste it.
But first, I have a challenge.
I want to see can you subscribe to this channel,
turn on the channel post notificatoins,
and give this video a thumbs up.
Seven seconds, here we go.
Seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Done.
If you can do that, comment down below.
Keyper Squad right now.
So now for the taste test, you ready?
I'm gonna go for a giant chomp.
Here we go.
Three,
two,
one.
- Crunchy, slimy.
Every kid's dream.
- It taste delicious.
- Kinda tastes like gum.
Wow, Collin.
- Let's melt this watermelon.
- Woo! - Woo!
That was very unsafe.
- Yeah, it was.
It was a little too close to my face.
We're gonna be doing the hot knife
versus the gummy to melt it.
We're gonna give this a shot right now.
So first.
Let's heat it up.
It's glowing.
There we go.
Three,
two,
one.
Let's see if this works.
- There goes.
- Yo, it's working!
Oh no!
No, no, it's so smokey!
Oh gosh no, what've we done?
It smells delicious, yet very toxic.
It's working, there we go.
It's almost like slicing off the gummy.
Yes!
I've got a new start this time guys, though.
Watch out.
Gonna slice it off.
- [Natalie] You should slowly slice it off.
- Yo, I wonder if you can slice right through it?
Get so smokey so quick.
Yo, but it's actually melting it, guys.
The way I'm holding this, this flamethrower
in my face is not a good idea.
I'm just like...
Well without smoking up the entire house,
I think we're gonna pop this one again
in the microwave, but this actually works.
Like this actually melted.
The hot knife was definitely a better strat
than just the blowtorch.
So right now, pop it in the microwave and let's go.
What started off looking nice and pretty,
and now it's just kinda...
It looks like grease or like an oil.
- Pour some in.
- Let's do it.
- Slime.
- Slime!
Whip it, flip it, sauce boy!
YO, this looks so nasty, fam.
- Ew, it looks like hairball.
- I was going somewhere else with it.
I'm like this doesn't look like a watermelon.
It looks like peanut butter.
Go away.
Alright, so now we're gonna pick it up
with our hands and go...
Oh my gosh!
I got it on my shirt.
Aw well, that's part of it.
But now I have an edible candy shirt.
- You've got skills.
- Yo, this looks like a makeup that you would put on.
Like it looks like a foundation.
- Wanna pour some on?
- I'm good.
One more step to make sure
it's the ultimate watermelon gummy.
- What about me?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Collin share.
- I think mine are just kinda disengrating.
Hers look really pretty, and then look
what happened to mine.
Mine just kinda splattered everywhere.
It's definitely turning red now.
So we didn't have the color before,
we definitely have the color now.
Oh man.
So let's see if this actually tastes
like a real watermelon gummy.
And if you wanna see me do a whole bunch
of crazy DIY's and experiments live
every single Saturday, 1 PM Pacific Standard Time,
I'm partnering with Live Me as summer long.
So yeah, the download link is down in the description below.
Come join, it's free, it's superfun.
Tell your friends and also comment what should we do
on our livestreams, 'cause we're gonna be doing
literally whatever you want.
So right now, you ready to try this?
Here we go guys.
Three,
two,
one.
Ho, ho, it's stuck to my teeth.
Alright, so final verdict on this.
What are your thoughts?
- I don't like it.
- Yeah, I thought it was good at first,
and then I started tasting all of the corn starch,
and that really is terrible.
So right now, we've been melting the eight foot
gummy snake into the sour gummy slime in the world.
Let's go.
This is literally an eight foot gummy.
Oh my gosh.
It's so heavy.
It's like 20 something pounds.
It's almost like it weighs 30 pounds.
We're gonna make it sour.
We also need the bucket.
Alright, so I think I had it for like a second.
Can we get the bucket?
You're gonna take the snake...
Ow.
It smacked me in the face.
Where'd the eyeball go?
Ah.
I want the other eyeball though.
I want to try this.
- Good?
It's so heavy.
- Use your muscles.
(Collin and Natalie cheer)
- This is so cool.
Fashion is my passion, but I'm gonna
release my scarf now.
Almost fell over.
I wonder what it's gonna taste like.
- It's lipstick.
- What?
You wanna try to hold this thing?
- Yeah.
Oh.
- That was like choking me.
Because this is eight feet long, we can't pop
it in the microwave.
So now, we're making our own microwave.
You know what, what I think we're gonna do
is let's just chop it up, pop it in the microwave,
and then put it back in here.
Because there's no way we can melt this down.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
Oh my gosh.
There we go.
Oh jeez, oh.
Alright here we go.
Time to make some...
Yo, that was a powerful mix.
- Stir, stir, stir, stir, stir.
- This one is going to need a lot more corn starch,
because right now you can tell it's super, super gummy.
Oh my gosh, she got it all over me.
It looks like a bizarre alien substance for real.
- Yay!
Now we can do this.
Now the corn starch won't get in my nose.
- Yo, this stuff looks crazy.
You good?
- Yeah.
No, I really can't breathe.
I can't see.
- I think this slime is getting pretty good.
And now we're gonna add the sour candy into
what's going on.
So right now...
What kind of a sound was that?
We're doing a lightning round with the sour candy,
and to kick it off, this is Cry Baby Soda.
- I never had that.
- I've never had it either.
So you have to bite off the top of it, apparently.
It's like wax.
Cheers. - Cheers.
Oops.
I missed my mouth.
Eww!
That's sour.
- Next up, toxic waste.
Cheers!
I've got some Warhead Chewie Cubes.
We got like two left.
- [Natalie] I never had these.
- They're sour, but not too bad.
- Yummy.
- Got this, I don't know what this is.
Oh, it's like a roll?
Three, two, one.
Oh no.
- Are these like Pop Rocks?
Yeah, sour power.
Alright, here we go.
Sprinkle a little bit of 'em in here, and then...
Holy cow!
Alright, I think we got some of this stuff here.
I don't know what this is.
Looks like some spray stuff.
You like that?
(Natalie screams)
- It's in my nose.
It burns.
- Yo guys, so we're adding some malic acid
and she wants to try this stuff.
- I'll do it for the Keyper Squad.
- You got it.
Before you try it, guys we also filmed a video
on her channel where we made slime.
It's as crazy as it sounds.
The link is down in the description below.
So go check it out, go subscribe to her channel.
Give her video a thumbs up and comment Keyper Squad.
Oh!
Yo, I told you this stuff is crazy!
- My tongue, my tongue, my tongue.
It's still going!
- It's still going?
Alright, we're gonna do this.
We're gonna do this quick.
We'll sprinkle the malic acid.
That's so much!
That sour stuff is so intense.
It's so intense.
There's so much malic acid everywhere.
This is the largest melted gummy snake
turned into sour slime.
We're about to eat it right now.
But comment down below what's another giant
gummy something that I should melt into candy slime.
But right now, you ready for this?
- Yep.
- Here we go.
Three, oh-no,
two,
one.
(Collin and Natalie yell)
(Collin mumbles)
Okay, bye!
It's not a joke.
It's not a...
You're like, "Yeah I'll give this a shot."
I'm like, "Fam!"