- Oh my gosh, I'm sorry.
- What was that?
- Three, two, one.
We've got puppies.
And you challenged us to let puppies pick
our slime ingredients.
My dog's name is Cuddles.
- And mine is Puddles.
And he's off to the races.
- And we also got a baby Corgi named Bubbles.
So right now, are you ready to pick some slime ingredients?
All right here we go, three,
two, one. - Two, one.
- Go for it buddy, go for it.
Get some slime ingredients.
- [Devan] Do it, oh they just wanna hang out.
Hanging out, trying.
This is slime time.
- [Collins] Let's get some slime.
Bro, okay, see.
Your brother's like he's ready to go, bro.
Let's get some slime.
- [Devan] High five, high five yeah.
Yeah.
- [Collins] Yes, we got contact solution.
All right we got clear glue, perfect.
And, wait, Orbeez, what?
- [Devan] My first one's baking soda?
Vinegar.
Yes, activator.
- This is Bubbles, the corgi, and he's gonna be choosing
our last slime ingredient.
You ready, bro?
All right, here we go, three,
two, one. - Two, one.
- Go for it bro.
- [Devan] Go for it. - [Collins] Go get
some more slime ingredients.
- [Devan] Go, go, go, go, go.
- [Collins] All right Bubbles, what have you got for me?
Oh, I'll take it, a blender.
- [Devan] All right Bubbles, red glue.
- Now what's interesting, is that Puddles actually
chose baking soda and vinegar.
- Oh yeah.
- But you know what that creates right?
Oh what is this, what is going on?
- What is it?
- Oh no, oh no, run.
(lava crackling)
(screaming)
- All right, well right now, let's sell, let's go.
To kick things off we're gonna mash up
a whole bunch of Orbeez right now.
Whoa. - What, dude?
- Yay. - You're already
getting them everywhere.
- All right, wait, wait, wait.
Hey.
- Sorry, I just wanted to try (laughs).
- Let's relax, these are mine.
And add them all here like this on the pan.
Perfect, okay.
We gotta figure out how to mash these up.
So I think this here.
(mashing loudly)
- [Devan] Dude, oh, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Keep 'em on your side.
- I'm sorry, I was.
- [Devan] I think I'm gonna add some vinegar here.
Dude dude dude dude.
How am I supposed to make my slime?
- Ho, ho, ho, ho, hew.
This is game changing.
All right, here we go, add these in, oh, yes.
- [Devan] Ew.
- The thing is I don't wanna waste this stuff.
So, here we go.
We're just gonna put in a little package here like this.
Rr, there we go.
- What?
It's like a taco.
- It's a little container.
A little taco container for my Orbeez.
- It's an Orbeez taco.
- We'll pop it right in here because I am going to be
blending up my Orbeez.
Perfect little funnel.
There we go.
Back to normal.
It's to go for round number two, here we go.
The uneven counter kind of made this
a little bit more difficult.
I'm gonna use this thingy here.
This thing's pretty cool.
See, check out.
(loud clanging)
(Devan laughing)
I know I lost parts of it.
Here we go, I'm just gonna scoop it in like this.
Yo.
(mixer winding)
- Really?
Wait.
Oh.
- I thought I lost it all.
All right, we're gonna add this in right now.
- So mine's looking pretty cool, but man I wish
there was more colors.
- I got you bro.
I'm the master of colors.
- [Devan] What?
Really?
- So here we go.
- Ah, sweet.
- We're just gonna use this little pot right over here.
- [Devan] Okay.
- Just grab yourself a neon vest like this.
We're gonna have to ball it up a little bit.
- Okay. - Three, two, one.
Ah.
- All that for just that?
- Boom, check it out man.
- Nice, All right.
- Enjoy your neon juice.
- Sweet man,
thanks. - Yep.
- Got some safety gloves on, and here we go.
- [Collins] Oh. - [Devan] All right.
Dude is this stuff gonna glow in the dark?
- [Collins] Oh.
Now we're just gonna add the rest in very carefully.
Oh.
- [Devan] Oh.
- All right, time to blend it up.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(blender whirling)
Perfect.
The blender really turns it all to mush man.
Here we go so this.
Oh, hoo-hoo.
In me eyeball.
- That's not good.
- No.
All right, my Orbeez are all mixed up, and now it's time
for the final step, which is to add the glue
and the contact solution.
So first of all, for the glue, is we're gonna add
about this much right there.
All right, time to get my hands in
and see how this stuff feels.
Oh my gosh.
It feels like hair.
- My slime has baking soda and vinegar.
Does that mean it's gonna be a volcano slime?
- I have got an idea. - Well, what is that?
- We're gonna summon my friend, his name
is Tickle Me Tiki, and he is the expert on volcanoes.
Here we go.
- Okay.
- Three, two, one.
(ball exploding)
Oh, there he is.
And he looks really angry.
Well, no he's actually very happy,
but he loves to be tickled.
- Coochy-coochy-coo.
Whoa. - Pretty cool, right?
- Um, yeah.
- Let's tickle him together, here we go.
Ready, set, go.
(vocalizing)
Woo-hoo.
Eventually it gets really crazy because we tickle him
for three seconds, you'll love to see what happens next.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
(tiki exploding)
(Devan screaming)
Oh man, he's gone.
- Dude, that was one temperamental tiki.
- But here's the great thing Devan, he did say
you have a 50% chance of it working.
- Only 50%?
- All right, now it's time to add the contact solution in,
and see if this Orbeez slime actually works,
but I really hope it does.
- Oh.
- Yo, it's starting to work.
- [Devan] Not quite the most satisfying slime,
but I made visually.
- You know what, Devan?
I think it needs a little more Orbeez.
So here we go, I'm just gonna place it down here.
- Wait.
- [Collins] It's gonna pick up some Orbeez
off the counter just like this.
- Dude, you got it all over me dude.
- Ah man, I'm like picking up spoons.
- All right, as you figure yours out, I'm gonna see
if this vinegar can turn this into volcano slime.
All right, here we go, three, two, one.
- Wait, 5 Second Subscribe Challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you can do that, comment on the Keyper Squad right now.
- Three, two, one.
(water pouring)
- [Devan] Oh.
- Mix it, mix it, mix it, mix it, mix it, mix it, mix it,
mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix, mix.
- [Devan] I gotta mix, I gotta mix it, I gotta mix it.
I'm mixing, I'm mixing, I'm mixing, I'm mixing.
I think it's going, dude.
- [Collins] Dude.
Whoa, snap. - Whoa, dude.
- When you get the comment down below,
who's slime is cooler?
We're on to the next one.
- Great job. - You guys did
a great job, you picked some great slime ingredients.
- I know, great job. - And right now.
- Ah, he's so cute (laughs).
- Oh, the kisses.
- I know.
- The kisses.
- It's the kiss attack.
- (laughs) Are you gonna pick some more slime ingredients?
My guys ready to go, he's ready.
- I think mine's ready too.
- Go get some more slime ingredients.
Go for it.
All right, first up we got the clear glue.
All right, now we got a little bit of contact solution.
Nice, we got baking soda.
- [Devan] Wait, are you thirsty?
Or, oh that's my ingredient.
All right, glue or activator?
Okay, activator.
Puddles, ice cubes, really?
- All right Bubbles, you're gonna
be picking some new slime ingredients.
You ready buddy?
All right, here we go, three,
two, one. - Two one.
- Go for it bro.
No way dude, it's gallium.
- [Devan] Come on Bubbles, yes, yellow glue.
Oop, startled himself.
- Dude, I love gallium, and my favorite thing
is what happens when you touch it.
Check this out, you ready?
- Whoa, what?
That's never happened before, has it?
- [Collins] Ay.
No, that has definitely not happened before.
- [Collins] Bro, you should try it man, it's so much fun.
- All right, wait, nothing's happening.
- [Collins] What do mean?
A toaster? (laughs)
What?
That makes no sense.
- [Devan] Why'd you turn me into a toaster?
- I didn't do any.
It was the gallium.
Bro, I did nothing.
Maybe it's just like your true self being expressed here.
I don't know.
(gallium moving through Collins)
- Whoa, I'm back.
- Yes, it worked.
- Yes. - Okay, great.
- I'm back bro, thank you.
- Dude, I'm so happy to have you back.
Yeah, for sure.
I was kind of scared you'd be a toaster forever.
- Yeah, that was weird.
All right, well right now, let's make some slime.
I'm gonna pour this stuff into my hands.
So, here's the crazy thing.
Even though it looks like liquid.
Oh my Gosh,
- What? - It is literally
as heavy as metal in my hand right now.
- [Devan] So cool.
I'm gonna try to pour a ton of it out of my hand.
Are you ready?
- [Both] Whoa.
- [Devan] Oh my gosh.
- [Collins] Oh man.
And look, it like leaves metallic residue bro.
It's so cool.
- [Devan] How are you gonna make slime with this, bro?
- All right, so I'm gonna play with the gallium
and add that to my slime.
But the first step, I gotta add the glue.
And unfortunately, I don't have my glue,
and I think that they actually took my glue.
You guys are being sneaky.
So I gotta tap into the secret glue reserve.
So, let's ah see where they're at.
Okay. - What?
- I think (tapping), nope, um.
Dude, how do you know when you find it?
- Oh, trust me, you'll know.
(tapping)
Nope.
I know it's around here somewhere.
I think it's, oh, maybe, maybe.
(knock)
Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
(knocking)
- That's definitely it.
Okay, here we go.
- Okay.
- We got the faucet.
- Okay, we're also gonna need the collecting bucket.
- Okay.
- And here we go, so we're just gonna have
to get this perfect.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Nailed it.
That's perfect.
Okay, here we go.
And super easy, just snap. (snaps)
(water boiling)
- Whoa.
- Yeah, I know right?
Yo, it's almost overflowing.
- Ah, snap. - There we go.
And to get it to fall down, we just have to give it
a little (claps), just like that.
- Whoa. - Perfect.
- All right. - Okay, so now,
that's all, is add the glue in.
- Okay - Here we go.
- [Devan] Oh, and that.
- [Collins] Yep, there we go.
I love the secret glue reserves, but you cannot tell anyone.
Let's get some contact solution in this thing.
- [Devan] I don't know how many I wanna add.
So I know I just add some water, but I think I need
to get some more.
- No, no, no. I got the water for you.
Here we go. - What, really?
- Here we go, three, two, one.
(water pouring)
- What?
- Ah, perfect, done.
- Whoa. - That's all you need.
- I was just gonna grab it from the fridge,
but that's awesome.
- Why grab it from the fridge when you can get it fresh?
(frame clanging)
From a painting?
- Yeah.
- Mom's not gonna be happy.
Let me go ah (banging), put this back.
And here's the twist.
The puppies' are actually gonna be the ones who can mix
up my slime, if they press the right buttons.
So right now, Cuddles, I need you to press
the green button.
Stay away from the red button, very bad.
- Collins.
- What?
- I think dogs are color blind.
- You're kidding?
You know what happens if he presses the red button, right?
- No clue.
- It activates a trap door.
- What? - Trapdoor.
- Um, okay.
- Yeah, we should not have had this thing installed.
Okay, so here we go.
- Why are you leaving it to a dog?
- Eye contact.
Right here Cuddles, right here Cuddles.
Green button, yay.
Red button, (grunts) no, no, no.
Just focus on my thoughts, All right?
(buzzer buzzing)
(yells)
- Collins, you okay?
My last step is to add my activator,
and I think I'm gonna measure it out
like a responsible person.
- The moment of truth.
Time to add the gallium into my slime and see
how it all mixes together.
So, here we go.
This is gonna be the craziest slime I've ever made.
You ready, okay, here we go, three, two.
- Yeah, oh. - Wait, first.
3 Second Like Challenge.
We wanna see if you can like this video in three seconds.
You ready, here we go.
- Three, two, one, done.
- [Collins] Three.
- [Both] Two, one, oh.
- Dude.
- And now the moment of truth.
Time to mix it together, you ready?
Here we go.
Gonna fold it over like this.
- [Devan] Look, like it's already.
- It's escaping out,
it's escaping out. - Dude.
- We gotta get in.
- Ah.
- [Devan] Oh my God, it looks like a chunk of--
(Collins and Devan screaming)
It's so heavy
it broke through. - It broke it.
- It's not gonna mix.
- Here we go, so we're gonna
put it in here. - I think I won this.
- Gonna add this little bit in.
- [Devan] It's so heavy.
- I'm gonna put the slime all around it.
So here we go, it's gonna be very careful.
Here we go, look at it.
See, it's right here at the bottom.
- Oh, it's so heavy.
- What is going on?
- What?
- What, there's no way? - Oh my gosh.
(Collins and Devan screaming)
It's like a teardrop, bro.
- That was so crazy.
- What? - Oh my gosh.
- All right, it's time to mix it up.
- [Collins] Oh, that look so cool.
- [Devan] Dude, what?
- Oh my gosh. - It's like honey.
I love this this stuff.
- All right, well you get to comment down below.
Who made a coolest slime?
And right now, let's go back to the puppies
and get our next slime ingredients.
All right, you guys have been doing amazing so far.
- Yes, whoa. - It's time for
some new slime ingredients.
Ready?
All right, here we go. - Go for it.
Three, two one, go for it bro,
get some more slime ingredients.
- [Devan] Mines already so ready.
I can't even control him.
- [Collins] We're kicking it off with some clear glue.
Nice cuddle, contact solution.
Baking soda, okay.
- [Devan] Ooh, shaving cream, yes.
I love shaving cream.
Sta-flo, awesome.
Yes, clear glue.
Ooh, look at his little toes.
- All right Bubbles, you ready to pick
some more slime ingredients?
You did a great job last time.
You ready buddy.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Go for it.
Ooh, silly string.
- [Devan] Oh wait, for slime?
All right Bubbles, what you got for me?
What, crayons?
- I have never heard of silly string slime.
You what, let's give this a shot, let's see if this works.
Uh!
- Oh, oh snake. - Oh, oh, oh my gosh.
(Devan screaming)
- Is it gone?
(Collins laughing)
Is it gone?
Dude, it's not even a real snake.
- Fleet.
All right, so right now let's make the slime.
- Dude, I don't even know how I'm gonna use crayons.
Will this even make slime dude?
I'm first gonna try
to break it up and see if this works.
I don't know this, ah.
Whoa, dude what was that?
- Nothing.
Time to add the silly string.
I broke it.
- Whoa, I think you broke it.
- Ah, I broke this one too.
Oh well, I was gonna ask.
Whoa, oh my gosh.
(yelling)
- Enough with this, I'm gonna try using a hair dryer
to see how this works.
- While you do that, I gonna add in my silly string.
Whoa, this is a powerful one, bro.
- [Devan] Dude.
- Now let's see if this turns into slime.
I'm gonna add some glue.
- You know what Collins?
I think I actually need some more crayons.
- No, put it down Devan.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, why?
- All right, I'm gonna add some more here now.
Perfect.
Long-distance shots.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Over Devan's head. - Whoa, whoa, why?
- Back this way.
- Whoa.
- Bro, it's actually working.
Dude this is taking forever.
I can do it way faster.
Put that down, step aside,
and here's how we're gonna do this.
Ready, here we go?
(lasers shooting)
- Whoa, okay.
- Yeah.
I can tell you're impressed.
(laser shooting)
Whoa, what?
Dude.
- Ah-choo.
Ah man, I'm falling apart.
Gah.
- It's like you're sick.
(lasers shooting)
Whoa.
Oh.
No.
Oh. (laughing)
Whoa.
Ah, tell me what is going on.
- All right, I'm good.
- Am I safe?
I think I'm gonna add my glue next.
- [Collins] This is pretty sweet.
- [Devan] They're not like mixing at all.
- This is super bizarre, man.
Oh, wow.
The silly string stopped becoming stringy
and just really turns into like mush.
- Ah, Collins.
- What?
- I don't think this is working out.
- [Collins] Dude, yours looks awesome.
It's like a dance party happening all in your slime.
What's really crazy is I though yours would be
like all nice and rainbow colorful, but it's dark.
- [Devan] Dude, it's like a ring.
Look at that.
- Bro, you're married to the crayon.
- Yeah, I'm married to the crayon life bro.
- Crayon life?
- All right, I think I'm gonna add some shaving cream next.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, bro.
That's expired, you can't use this.
- I didn't know they had expiration dates.
- Yeah, this is not fresh at all, Devan.
- Oh really?
- I'll show you how to get some fresh shaving cream.
Do you smell this?
- [Devan] Ah, yeah.
- See how it doesn't smell fresh?
- No.
- And there we go, perfect.
- [Devan] Wait, what?
- Brand-new, fresh, shaving cream.
Smell that.
Fresher, right?
- Sure.
As you add, I'm gonna go wash my hands.
- Collins, that's not how you wash your hands.
- It's pretty clean compared to what it used to be.
- [Devan] That's smearing your hands.
- [Collins] There we go.
- Yeah, you might. - Now you're cleaning
the fridge.
- Oh, it looks great to me.
That's like art.
I can clean your fridge with art.
- [Devan] You can't, oh, you just did that.
- [Collins] There we go.
Bump, bump, and then huh, huh and then ha.
You can't do that if you don't have
that stuff on your fridge.
Guys, don't ever do this to your fridge.
It's not a good idea.
I do not endorse it (laughs).
Now time to be responsible and go clean up
the mess that I made.
Dude, see this?
Dude, this comes off easy man.
Don't do this at home, but still it comes off easy.
- It's also nice and fluffy until you get
these chards of crayons stuck in your hands.
- Puddles, man.
Come on, you should have had the foresight to see
that it wouldn't work.
- [Devan] I know man, come on.
- [Collins] All right, I guess we're gonna add
some of this in here.
- [Devan] Sta-flo.
- Dude, this is just so bad
at coming out. - What, no, no, no, no.
Get that away from me dude.
Sta-flo is still not doing anything dude.
- Here we go.
We've got some contact solution for the final step.
Oh, ya fleet.
The air really tastes like baking soda.
Ah, I burnt my nose.
It burns.
All right, just gonna add some contact solution.
I feel like a mad scientist right now.
- [Devan] Dude, the worst about this is the bottom.
There's just hard, fragmented crayons on the bottom.
- All right, just need a little bit more silly string.
(bells ringing)
Oh dude, oh, oh, oh, this is not good, this is not good.
- Whoa.
- I got it.
Dude, bank shot man, with a pan.
Look at this bro, master at the chef.
(pan clanging)
- Oh.
- Okay, I've got all the ingredients in here.
And now it's time to see if silly string slime
is actually gonna work.
So Cuddles, I'm counting on you to be able to win this one.
Let's see if this happens.
Here we go, three,
two, one. - Two, one.
- [Collins and Devan] Oh.
- There's so much silly string bro.
- Is it gonna work out?
- I don't know man, oh.
I can kind of feel it.
It feels like it's starting to come together a little bit.
Ah. - Ooh.
- It's just like juicing everywhere though.
The real question is, will I be able to mix
this silly string into it?
It feels kind of like styrofoam almost,
which is really weird.
Yo, it worked I win.
You can get the comment down below.
Oh no.
- Dude, really?
- [Collins] Oh no, well you get
the comment down below, who won.
Ah-huh. - Oh, they've got it all.
- They've got my leg, he's got my leg.
- [Devan] He's got my leg.
- It's going down.
It's so heavy. - They're bringing you down,
Collins. - [Collins] It's so heavy.
These pants won't make it.
- He's got my leg, he's got pant leg.
- Oh, one of them got your leg too.
- [Devan] Ah, he loves the legs.
- [Collins] Look at that little face.
- He's ready to go.
Let's go race. - Dude, he's so ready
to get some slime ingredients.
Are you ready buddy?
We're just gonna be watching over here Devan.
- Huh? And just observing.
- [Devan] Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go for it.
- All right, we're gonna do this, we're gonna go for it,
we're gonna go for it.
You ready?
Three, two, one, and go for it.
Get some great slime ingredients.
All right, in order to see
the slime ingredients, it's that way.
- [Devan] They're this way, whoa.
- [Collins] That would be yes.
Love the energy, but let's get some ingredients.
Bubbles, perfect, I love bubbles.
Nice, clear glue.
Love it bro, Sta-flo.
- [Devan] Ooh, All right clay, I love clay.
Nice, shaving cream.
Thanks Puddles.
And hair gel, kind of slimy.
All right, here we go, wee.
- All right, you're a good boy.
You're a good boy.
Ah, you're such a good boy.
- [Devan] Oh, he wants to go that way.
- [Collins] With a nice little leap over the leg.
Metallic blue pigment, sweet.
- [Devan] DohVinci, I don't think
I've ever used DohVinci before.
- Out of all the crazy things I've done,
this is by far the wildest.
So Devan, how you feeling right now?
- Dude, this is super weird.
- I mean clearly you're just stuck in a bubble
and I mean I can tell the dog's getting kind of
tripped out right now.
So, let's do this.
I gotta get you out of here.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(bubble popping)
Holy snap - Oh.
I actually feel solid again.
- All right, well right now let's make some slime.
Yo, these great bubbles, you can literally hold
in your hand, bro.
This is crazy.
- [Devan] It's not working.
Oh, what?
(gags)
- [Devan] Dude.
- Bro. - What?
- Look at a bubble you can literally hold in your hand.
- Wait, I want it, I want it, I want it, I want it.
Ah. - Oh my gosh.
What? - Pass it me man.
Pass it to me.
- All right, here you go, three, two, one.
(bubble bounces)
(Collins blowing)
(metal tinging)
(yells)
You gotta be careful with that stuff man.
- Why?
- 'Cause it's magic clay.
Set it down for a second, you'll see.
- Okay.
Whoa, wait, what?
Where did it go?
Wait.
How did it end up over here?
- I told you man, it's magic clay, it's super easy.
- Um, Collins, it didn't let me grab it.
- Oh, right over there, yeah grab it again.
- [Devan] What?
Dude, seriously? - Sike, it's magic clay.
(laughing)
- Is that all it does?
Wait, and now it's in my bowl?
- Exactly man, it said magic clay.
- This is really peculiar.
- Let me see it. - No, no, no, you can't.
- I wanna see it for a a second.
- Okay.
- Are you kidding me?
- It disappeared.
All right, here we go.
Yes, dude.
- Oh dude, I've got an idea.
Check this out, here we go.
(bubble inflating)
- Dude, that's a big bubble.
Um, ah, Collins.
What are you doing?
- I gotta get mine.
I gotta get mine.
- Ah, what is this around my head?
Did you pop the bubble on my head?
(collins laughs and vocalizes)
- How do we get out of this?
- The only way to get out is to blow out.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(balloons popping)
- I think we need this DohVinci stuff next.
So, I think you add this in here.
- That actually looks pretty cool man.
Can you make like a.
Oh, dude like a little art piece, midair.
- Oh.
- Do it right over here, do it.
- What, how do you do that?
- Just kind of squeeze it.
- Three, two, one.
Whoa.
- That's so cool.
- Yeah, but what is it?
- That's Katy Perry.
- How do you know that?
- It's clearly Katy Perry, I mean look at it.
- It's just a stick figure, dude.
- No, you'll figure it out in about two seconds.
- Okay. - Here we go.
One, two.
(fireworks exploding)
See, that was Katy Perry.
- I guess so man.
- All right, well right now I've got some slime I'm making.
Oh man, oh that's cool I can.
Oh. - Oh.
(yells)
- Ah, where's a nurse?
That's not gonna come out.
Let's take a quick pause, so I can fix my shirt.
- I'm just gonna add this DohVinci for some color, I guess.
- [Collins] And I've got some blue pigment I'm gonna
add to my slime.
Whoa, look how the pigment mixes into the glue.
- Bro, this is like mixing neon noodles.
- And mine looks like metallic right now.
All right so now. - Whoa.
I can gotta make a couple more bubbles, then we're gonna
be adding it to this and literally making bubble slime
we can just crush, which is gonna be awesome.
Huh, you know what?
I'm gonna put a secret message in a bubble.
- Wait dude, wait.
What are you saying?
Collins, I can't understand what you're saying.
- Here we go, you ready?
- No, no, no, I have to know what that says.
- Hi Devan.
- That was too weird.
- Yeah.
That was it.
- Okay.
- To complete the slime, I just gotta add some Sta-flo.
So here, we're just gonna add this in.
Oh, you know what?
I'm gonna add in the first preliminary bubble.
(bubble inflating)
Well guys, there we go and we're just gonna drop it in.
Bloop, bubble's in.
And let's see how this works.
So I guess, I don't know, we just kind of use the bubble
to mix it up, mix it up, mix it up.
Dude, this is pretty wild.
- [Devan] Mine is not mixing well at all.
- I'm gonna get my hands in.
Oh, this is weird.
No, it's turning stringy.
- Oh no.
- Bro, I gotta. - You gotta save it.
- I know, this slime is like, it's super close
to not working.
- Nothing about that is because of Collins.
- Yo, I fixed it bro and this looks so crazy.
This is gotta be the greatest slime I've ever made.
Yay.
- Dude, it's so tough.
- Oh man, it's like super cool.
- It's mine now. (laughs)
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- [Devan] What?
- Whoa, ah dude I love this stuff?
Wait, how did I end up back here?
- [Collins] I'm confused.
- Did you just put me in a loop?
- I think so, I don't know.
And now the moment of truth,
time to lay this over the bubbles
and create the most satisfying bubble popping ever.
Here we go, three, two, one, and then drape over.
Come on, oh, there we go, there we go.
- I got you fam, I got you.
- [Collins] We gotta put it over like that.
- [Devan] With the assist.
- Time to reach in pop all the bubbles.
This is gonna be so satisfying.
Here we go, ready, three, two.
Oh wait, if you wanna win a 15 minute video
with Devan and I,
text the word "DOGS" to 81800 right now.
So pause this video, text the word "DOGS" to 81800
and you'll automatically be entered in to win.
And right now, let's do it.
Three, two, one.
- Oh.
- Oh my gosh.
- What?
That was so cool.
- Oh my gosh, next level.
I think I absolutely won this but you get
to comment down below and let us know who made
a cooler slime.
And right now, back to the puppies for our next slime.
All right, this is the final slime.
Are you ready to get the best ingredients yet?
- You ready bro?
- End on a bang.
All right, here we go guys.
- Look at his arm.
- Classy man, go the arms crossed and everything.
- He's ready.
- All right, three, two, one, go for it bro.
Get some slime ingredients.
All right in order to see the slime ingredients,
it's that way.
- They're this way.
Whoa, whoa.
- [Collins] First up we got Sta-flo, nice.
No, not glitter glue, come on.
Ear plugs, what?
- [Devan] Baking soda, unconventional, but usable.
Weird, a blender.
At least I got white glue.
Oh, and Sta-flo, nice.
- All right Bubbles, you have the most important job,
you gotta pick the last slime ingredient.
Are your ready buddy?
All right, here we go three,
two, one. - [Devan] Two, one.
- [Collins] Wait, chapstick.
- [Devan] Ah, Bubbles picked squishies.
- I do kind of feel bad, but I think my first step
is gonna be to cut these things up.
- That's so wrong.
Oh, no, no, no.
- [Devan] Start with an ear.
- Oh.
- [Devan] And maybe a little foot.
- This feels very bizarre.
I kind of wanna join in though, so her we go
we have panda squishy. - No, no, no, no.
This is my slime.
- I wanna try something. - What?
No, no. - There we go.
- No.
Dude, this is far more satisfying than you think.
(yells, laughs)
- All right, I've got my cutting board and the chap stick.
So, here's what I'm about to do for.
(blender blending)
Devan, I'm, okay, there we go, thank you.
Now for the.
(blender blending)
Are you kidding me? - What?
- So I'm gonna be using the chap stick.
(blender blending)
Devan!
- What?
- I'm trying to explain this.
This is out of control.
(blender buzzing)
There you go.
- Dude, I think you broke my blender.
- No Devan, I made it better because now,
it can't cut me off anymore.
So instead of it being a blender, you now have
a hand-crank blender.
You just spin this little thingy over here
and what you're gonna use for your blender.
- It's old-fashioned dude.
- So it will give me time to properly explain.
Gonna empty my chap stick down here.
Ah, you hear that?
Silence, I love it.
All right, it's time to mash it up.
Here we go.
(hammers pounding)
Whoa man.
That's enough with the hammers.
Right now, let's grab this little thingy here.
I don't know what this does, but that works really nicely.
We can finally add it in, we're on to the next.
- No, I have to mix my glue first.
I mean my slime. (laughs)
- You have to make your glue.
All right, and the chap stick is in.
All right, next up, here go, I've got my glue.
No, dude, it's glitter. - Ah.
- [Collins] Bubbles, why would you choose glitter?
Come on.
I've never heard of chap stick working in slime before.
So either this is gonna be really cool,
or this is the worst slime I've ever made.
All right now, we're gonna mix up the chap stick
and the glue together.
Now it's time to add them in.
My slime is now fully soundproof.
- Now it's time to add my squishies.
I'm gonna do it very slowly.
- [Collins] Whoa.
All right, and now time for the Sta-flo.
Oh, oh.
- [Devan] This is the best thing ever.
- Oh my gosh.
My slime is like it has a whole bunch of baby carrots
in it man, like all these ear plugs
are not helping it at all, but.
- [Devan] Dude.
- I don't know if this is a win or fail or what,
but you get the comment down below.
Who won this round?
- Mines a total win.
- The only person I've ever seen make slime
with squishies is simply me.
We're outside, and it's time for the slime dump.
- How about this, we do a double slime dump?
- Oh snap, we've never done that before.
And now, we have Devan back to perform
the double slime dump on himself.
Two buckets, two hands, one dump.
Here we go.
Ready and.
I swear we were like this close.
- While I was away, I got you a chair.
- Wait, is this, what's up with chair?
- There you go, 'cause you're getting dumped first.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How me first?
How about we do a rock, paper, scissors battle
to see who has to go first.
- I don't like those odds.
- Rock.
- Paper, what is that?
- I'm thinking about strategy, okay here we go.
- [Both] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
(bell ringing)
- Hey!
- Two out of three, two out of three.
- [Both] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- No!
- Yes!
- Sit down, the chair is all yours.
- Oh, I just had a crazy idea of how we could do this, Boss.
- Oh sweet.
- Let me show you, so basically, sit down.
- All right.
- So imagine I'm gonna sit down first,
and then you're gonna pick up the bucket,
and then you'll be back here like this, okay?
And then you're gonna countdown.
You're gonna go three, two. - Whoa whoa whoa, wait.
Wait wait wait.
This is not right.
- What do you mean?
- What are you about to dunk that on me?
- No, not at all.
I know how we can do this.
Two chairs.
- Okay.
- All right, so we will both sit down this.
- All right, yeah, we're sitting down.
- No you're not.
- What?
- Sit down now.
So basically like, imagine you would take the bucket
and you would go three, two, one.
- Whoa whoa whoa, okay, okay, that's.
Got me a little nervous there.
You know what?
I think if you just sit there, and I just take it from here,
and just like three, two.
- No, Devan. - What?
- Stop it.
Do you know what?
I don't think a chair's gonna work.
We can kinda like, scratch this off.
Here's how it's gonna go.
You're gonna stand regular, I'm gonna dump it on you,
we'll get you a little step stool, you can step on that,
then you can dump it on me.
So you get slime dumped first.
- [Devan] Sounds like a deal.
- Why are we shaking on it?
- You get dumped first.
All right. - What?
- Hell yeah. - Oh come on.
- It worked.
- I got duped.
All right, so if I'm getting slime dumped first,
that means you need to get a step stool or something.
- I was actually very prepared for this moment.
Very sturdy.
- So I don't know, can you dump it from here.
- Yes, I think I got some height.
Maybe if you come down a little bit.
- Like this?
- Yeah, like right there, that seems about right.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yeah, positive.
All right, I'm gonna grab the bucket.
You ready for this?
- No. - All right.
Three. - Oh gosh, no no.
- Ugh.
- What?
- Do you know what?
I don't think I can do it.
I think you need to be in the chair again.
Here we go for the slime dump.
You ready for this? - Oh, no.
Wait, you're not gonna do it from that side?
- What?
- I don't know.
- Here we go, slime dump. - Oh no.
- Three.
- God, not again.
- Two.
- Oh no.
- One!
(slime pouring)
(yelling)
- It's so cold! - Oh.
- It is so cold!
And it's so slimy!
It's in my eye!
- You okay?
- No!
Well now it's time for you to get slime.
- Yeah, that's right, dude.
- Oh.
(stammers, yells)
- That's the scariest part, dude.
- Dude dude dude dude.
- You okay?
- I feel like I'm ice skating.
(both yelling)
I'm like doing a little dance, it's like (yells).
Every which way.
I got a lot of.
- It's getting over me now.
- I'm gonna rotate this way.
- Okay.
- And then kinda like, pull my arms.
- I'll pull you, yeah, go a little this way.
- I'm gliding.
- Switch, no no no, this way.
- All right, Devan, you ready to get slime dumped, bro?
- I'm ready, I'm ready.
- Gotta take in my surroundings here
before I slime dump you, I gotta.
- Really?
- Gotta little scoot around here.
- Seems like you're having way too much fun with this.
- And then a little, little scoot around over here.
- Is it because it didn't get on your face?
- All right, Devan, are you ready to get slime dumped?
- Yup.
- This is a ton of slime, bro.
It's like sloshing around man, it's just like.
- Dude dude dude dude. - Look at it, bro.
It's just sloshing everywhere. - I get it.
I did it to you.
- See, you have slime dumped, Devan,
in quite a little while, so.
- I know.
- It's gonna be a different feeling for you.
All right, here we go and comment down below
what color slime should we use for a slime dump next time.
And Devan, we're gonna go slow and slimy on this one.
- No no no, fast and quick, get it over with.
- Nope.
Oh my gosh, I'm sorry, bro.
- What was that?
- I did, that was not on purpose, all right.
- That was a little bit premature, all right.
- You can't do two slime dumps.
- That's not two slime dumps, that's just a little bit
of the bucket. - Really?
- I'm gonna dump it on your right now, here we go.
- My lap is freezing.
- Three, two, one.
(slime pouring)
(yelling)
- Dude, it's so cold.
- All right, well that is it.
Thank you guys so much for watching, we love you guys.
- [Both] Bye.