- Slime dump!
Three, two--
- Oh no. - One!
We've got puppies and you challenged us to
let puppies pick our slime ingredients.
My guy's name is Hans.
- And mine is Frans.
- So right now, you ready?
All right, here we go.
On the count of three, three, two, one, go for it, bro.
- There you go. - Pick some slime ingredients.
- Let's do it, come on. Go this way.
- There ya go. - Go that way.
- See-- - There we go, yes!
- He's on it. - They're off to the races.
- [Collins] First ingredient, here we go, Sta-Flo, nice.
Great job, great job, let's see what we got, glue!
Dude, this is awesome, perfect, markers,
okay, I don't know how I'm gonna use that.
Is that chalkboard paint?
- [Devan] First up, I got food coloring, yes.
Glue! Yes, I could totally use that.
Styrofoam balls, no! No styro--
Sta-Flo is great.
Alright, I'm gonna start off with my styrofoam balls.
- Did someone say bouncy balls?
- No! (spring sound effect)
- Yeah! (bass party music)
- No, no! I said styrofoam balls, not bouncy balls, bro.
- Wait, did you say bouncy balls?
- No! - I got you bro!
(bass party music)
- No! - Alright guys, let's make
some slime right now. - Bro, how did you get th--
- Oh, oh, almost got it (deep laugh)
- So like I was saying, it's time to.
- Oh, sorry, I did not mean to do that.
- It's time to crush up my styrofoam,
so I'm gonna use this little mallet here. (thumping)
- Bro, that's gonna take forever.
Here we go! - Oh, jeez!
- Boom! There we go bro that is awesome.
- What? - For my first ingredient
we're gonna use some of this paint right here.
We don't wanna get any chunks in the chalkboard paint
'cause you don't want a chalky chunky chalkboard,
know what I mean fam? (hooting)
- Look at mine, this looks insane.
It actually looks like popcorn, I'm so shocked.
- [Collins] And it's becoming creamy too.
- I'm making popcorn slime.
- First ingredient is in. - Wait, that's your first
ingredient? Dude, I'm almost done with mine.
- What? You know what?
I didn't want to have to do this, but it's the only way
I can slow you down, Tiny Devan.
- No! - Three, two, one, boom!
- Hah! You don't have your powers anymore! (gasps)
- Oh my gosh! - What did you do to me?
- I'm so sorry. - Look at my hands!
Oh, I'm feeling a little faint.
- Whoa, whoa, Devan, Devan, Devan, Devan.
- Collins, hold me, please, please, please, Collins, please.
I can't live like this! - Devan, stop!
- How can I paint with these hands?
- Oh my gosh, you're so heavy.
Dude, it's not that big a deal, I can fix this.
- Just gonna fix my hair, sorry.
Dude, I can't even make slime, look at this.
How am I gonna make slime like this?
I can't even clean off my hands, I can't even clean--
Oh, Collins, I'll never be able to pet Frans again.
- I don't mean to laugh, I don't mean to be insensitive,
but this is the funniest thing we've ever done.
- I can't live like this. (slow piano music)
Change me back, you have to, I beg of you.
- Hold out your hands like this.
It might be more helpful to close your eyes
so this doesn't shock you anymore.
- Okay, just do it. - I got you bro.
Here we go, three, two, one, bam?
- Are they gone? - Technically yes.
- What do you mean? (screaming)
What kind of joke is this?
- Okay Devan relax. - Bro, change me back!
- Third time's a charm, right?
Three, two, one. (magical chimes)
Oh no! - What?
I don't even have opposing thumbs now,
these are the hands of a sea creature!
- Okay, Devan, relax, calm down, I need you to
stay with me bro, one more time, this one's it.
Three, two, no more horsing around, I promise, one!
Bam! (magical chimes) - No!
What did you do to me this time?
- I think I used the wrong choice of words.
- I don't even have hands, I have hooves.
- Okay. (Devan screams)
- I'll take the small hands, bro, just take me back.
I'll take anything but these.
- I forgot, I need the extendable hand to fix you back.
Stand right there. - This better work.
- Three, two, one, boom! - Ah!
Oh yes, oh my goodness, it feels good to feel again.
Bro, thank you, thank you, I mean wait, no,
you did this in the first place.
Get off of me bro, you're gonna have a
time out for that dude.
- Well now that that's over I can resume making
my glue and that really gave me no advantage whatsoever.
I'm so sorry bro.
- Need a breather, bro, oh man.
- Alright, here we go gonna add my glue.
(silly whirring sound effect)
Nailed it.
Now it's time for the Sta-Flo, so here we go.
Gonna open it up and we're gonna
make some chalkboard slime.
So my real question is, will I be able to actually
write things on my chalkboard slime?
Time to get serious about this mixing so I've got
the official mixers, and that's about all
I'm gonna use 'em for.
I forgot to mix the glue with the paint, though.
This might not be good.
It looks like a shredded garbage bag.
This thing is an udder fail. - Yes.
- This is horrible. - You failed? I love it.
- So here's the true test, will it write?
Here we go, oh!
I can't believe it literally worked, that is so cool.
- That is really awesome.
- You have slime that has writing on it, woo!
Oh, snap, now you can mush it back up
and you're back to regular slime.
You get to comment down below, who made a cooler slime?
Oh snap!
Okay, it's time to get the next slimes.
You guys are doing a great job, buddy, yeah.
- Crushing it.
- Look at his little arms, he's like, "Yeah, I love picking
"slimes, I want that one, I want that one--"
- Hi five? Yeah. (laughing)
- Are you ready bro, Hans?
It's time to get it, here we go, three, two, one,
go for it buddy, go for it.
- Be free. - First up, Sta-Flo, dude,
great job Hans. No!
Glitter glue, I hate glitter.
Wait, are those plastic fish?
Okay, and then, are you thirsty?
No, that's my ingredient, okay, water.
- Go to the white glue, yes, next up, neon glitter.
I can work with that. Neon paint?
Alright, this is gonna be a fun slime,
and Sta-Flo, perfect.
(bell rings) - Devan? Devan!
- [Announcer] And now the continuing adventures
of Tiny Devan! ('80's keyboard music) (Devan screaming)
- Collins, I'm down here! - Here he is, hey!
- I was literally about to become Puppy Chow.
- Oh my gosh, bro I am so sorry, here go, three, two, one.
(chimes) - Yes, I'm big again.
- Kicking it off right now with my glitter glue.
- Oh, almost dropped my glue.
- Here we go--
- Next up, I add florescent tempura paint.
Alright now it's time for me to mix it around.
- I'm feeling extra confident, so I'm gonna
go for a long shot with my glue.
- The what? - The long shot with the glue.
- How? - Just, and then just go p--
and then it'll be perfect, three, two, one. (splat)
Oops. - You know what?
I'm not actually feeling this blue,
so I'm actually gonna add this yellow instead.
Now it's time to mix it around.
Whoa, dude, this looks insane!
Now it's time to add my next ingredient--
- Fish attack! - Whoa, wait, what?
- Awesome. Alright, glue is in.
Next up I've got water so I'm shouting to Hans,
I know what you're thinking, always stay hydrated. (slurps)
That's how dogs drink water, is that how dogs drink water?
(slurping) Alright, word, bro.
- And yo, Frans, why did you pick glitter?
Dude, I hate glitter, c'mon, he's trying to
sabotage me or something, jeez man.
- Oo, snap, I filled up my bowl too much.
I mean my ball, it's not a bowl.
A little bit of water, just gotta do a beach ball serve.
Three, two, one. (thud) That didn't work.
- That was like a beach ball hand switch.
- Now I'm gonna do it for real, here we go, three, two, one.
(thud) Oh, oh no.
Here we go, I'll give it a little squeeze. (splash)
- It doesn't squeeze. - It does!
- No it doesn't, you're getting water every--
- It's squeezing, it squeezes. - But it's not.
- I'm trying to show you, you said it doesn't-- (splash)
Oh my gosh! - That's not a normal squeeze.
- We actually popped the little ball open.
- We? You're dragging me into this?
- Team effort Devan! - No, it was not.
- My shirt's soaked. - It's this guy.
- The water's in, next up, I gotta add my fishys,
so just pop 'em in there, oops, I missed a couple.
Thing is, I need a lot more fishes, so,
I am King Poseidon, king of the Seven Seas,
and I summon thee all right now. (waves splashing)
- What is going on? - Ah, my kingdom and kinfolk.
There we have the leopard mantis seal,
the beluga whale fish. (both laughing)
You've seen them before in Discovery Channel.
- I have not actually.
- Ah, one of my kinfolk, Dolphindigulus.
(high pitched sounds)
- Wait, bro is that even a real trident?
- How dare you question the authenticity of my staff!
Shar-keesha! Get him? - Shar-keesha! No!
(muffled screaming)
- Shar-keesha! (garbled speech)
I'm gonna finish up the slime with the Sta-Flo-oh!
Just gonna pop some in right now.
All the fishys are in there right now which should help,
'cause they're gonna be swimming around
and helping out as well. - Nice.
- Dude, mine is not working, looks like noodles.
- Oh, I'm gonna try to write something in the air
with my neon slime, bro, here we go.
There's one letter, two letters, three letters and four.
Oh, dude let's check mine out under a black light.
Here, take this flashlight, turn it on,
and we'll turn out the lights, you ready?
- Yep. - No, mine, dude,
what are you doing? - The fishes do glow though.
- What? - That's super cool.
- That's so awesome. Bro, I can't wait to see
if this works under the black light.
- Alright, I'll turn off the lights, three, two, one (claps)
Wait, first, five-second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, are you ready?
Here we go,
- [Both] five, four, three, two, one, done!
- If you can do that, comment down below,
Keyper Squad, right now. (sounds of amazement)
We need to get the lights back on now, so here we go.
(claps) Now it's time for you guys to vote,
who made a cooler slime? - I think it was me.
(grunting) I got it, I got it.
His tooth is on it.
- Dogs did a great job last time, so for this round
we're gonna see if they can create even crazier slimes.
You guys ready, here we go, go for it.
Wait, you have him like a little baby.
- It's so adorable, it just wants to snuggle in my arms.
Oh, he's ready, got some quick snuggle time
and now he's at it.
- I've got contact solution, perfect, glow in the dark glue,
that is awesome, great job, and then beads.
- Alright Frans, Sta-Flo, good choice, cotton balls, what?
Alright, and then white glue, perfect.
- Let's make some slime. This is glow in the dark slime
whoa, whoa, whoa, don't ever bring a pillow
to a Tyrannosaurus Rex fight. (yelling)
- I won that thing. - No you didn't.
Collins, I think you're cool.
- Back to what I was saying, this pink slime
is really cool 'cause it's glow in the dark.
This could be glow in the dark slime.
- Oh, that would be so awesome bro.
- Gonna add it in, it's got little sparkles in it,
what's up with that? - Dude, what are you doing?
- Working on my forearms, bro I gotta get buff.
It's my new workout plan, called Glue 90 Flex.
- Dude, your arms! - Whoa, I feel pumped up
right now bro, that stuff is crazy.
You didn't believe me when I told you bro but
these things get crazy. - Oh.
- These workouts are the best--
- Can you just let off? - Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry, I don't know my new strength.
Umbrellas! Nothing. (grunting)
- You're like one percent stronger.
- What? - It's all look, no function.
Dude, you good yet? (snap)
- Oh! - Bro, these muscles
are changing you. - How do I get rid of 'em?
- Jut pull 'em off. - Oh, that was easy.
Woof, man, I feel a lot better, a lot more level-headed now,
so I'm just gonna take this more calmly now.
Gonna add some stars to this.
- Alright, got my cotton balls now it's time
to add these in here. (shaking)
- Perfect. - Was that really necessary?
You were almost better with the muscles.
Dude, with these cotton balls, I don't know
if my slime's gonna turn out, bro.
Dude, why are you doing such a risky maneuver?
- Time for my super-special new technique.
It's called the boots and boots.
- The cats, oh. - There's no cats.
♪ Bloopah bloopah bloopah bloopah ♪
♪ Bloopah bloopah bloopah bloo ♪
- Dude, it's like a kid playing in the rain.
- This is basically Collins playing in slime right now,
this is great.
Boots are out, now it's time for the pecker staff.
So the pecker staff just goes in like this
and just pecks away the slime (sneezes) man!
- Bless you. - Thank you.
Alright, I've been mixing my slime now
and it's not turning out so well at all.
- Dude, it looks like marshmallows, bro.
My slime is coming together nicely, but it's not getting
milky enough, you know what I mean?
I'm sorry Hans, you did pick some great items,
but unfortunately the, oh, pick it up!
- It's not even a problem, bro.
- That was close.
I was gonna add some Sta-Flo.
Ow, okay, note to self, might not be the best idea
to add in these super spiky stars because you're
squeezing it and all that, it's like (throat static) oh
and like (throat static), you know what I mean?
- No, I don't. - Alright, you know what?
I think my slime is almost done, how's yours looking?
- It's looking great. - Dude, this thing turned out
so cool, but the real question is, will it glow in the dark?
Hold onto this for a second, Devan,
I gotta use the Clapper, here we go, three, two, one (claps)
- [Both] Yo, this is so cool!
- [Collins] Bro, I've never juggled glow in the dark slime.
This is crazy, oh snap, I dropped it again, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one! Ah!
- They're eating my hair. What's up, hi, hi.
How are you guys? I love you man, so cute, bro.
The best dog partner ever.
Look at this one here, think we're gonna pick
some new ingredients, you guys ready?
- Ah, he wants a little belly rub, so cute.
- He's been doing a lot of hard work,
just wants a little belly rub to relax.
Bath bombs, okay, we've got cornstarch, alright mines
going for water, how can you make slime out of water?
- Gold leaf, interesting, okay, contact solution,
I can definitely work with that, clear glue,
could not get a more perfect slime.
- Alright, so I've got my bath bombs and so first up
we gotta add some water to the bowl--
- Hey, Collins, you're a winner, you want a trophy?
- This is like some sort of joke.
- No, you're a winner, dude, there's not trick to it.
Just take it, dude, you're a winner.
(whooshing, thudding)
Oh, wait, what? I didn't think there was
a trick to that but apparently there is, alright,
I'm gonna try to use this, three, two, one. (clunks)
- Hey, there you go! - Wow, I'm back.
- He's back, alright. - That thing was terrifying.
So now it's time to add some water--
- Hey! I've added my glue and now I'm gonna
add the contact solution.
- You do that, now it's time for me to drop in
some bath bombs, which one do I want to go with first?
I'm gonna go with the gold one first, three, two, one.
(splash) Oo!
- Why would you drop it like that?
- Look at it go! - Dude.
- We're just going all of them at the same time, bam,
put this one in there, we'll go with this one here,
another one, alright, we're going with that one there.
We'll go for this one here, and then we'll go
for this green one, and then we'll uh--
- Oh oh! - Maybe if I mix it up.
That's not helping. - Use the broom.
- We gotta use the big spoon, to scoop, oh!
- Dude, you made it worse.
- I'll get a little broom off.
- Ow, my foot, you dropped it on my foot.
- I'm sorry, bro, but I'm panicking, bro.
- We should have done one at a time.
- Yeah, you're totally right. (laughing)
Well, you know what, first ingredient is in.
Maybe a little bit too much, you might say,
you'd be wrong, 'cause this is the perfect amount.
I'm a hold this under the water and see what happens.
- It smells so good right now.
- They're all still full, my hands are so slippery now
I can't even pick up anything.
But next up, gotta add some cornstarch into my slime.
Just, oh, so hard to grab it bro.
Here we go, three, two, one. (thud)
Oh, that worked, first time. - He acts shocked.
- Bath bombs mixed with cornstarch is not a good smell.
Hopefully this stuff makes some Oobleck
bath bomb Oobleck cornstarch would be kinda cool.
- Oh, what?
- I'm just gonna try to make this slime
as quickly as possible so we're gonna try to
squish up a whole bunch of bath bombs along with the
cornstarch and hopefully this turns into
some sort of slime, oh boy.
Oh, snap, there's a little toy in it.
That or a random fish came to live in here.
I don't know what's going on with that, so we're gonna
let him live in this habitat, bloop, just pop him in there.
It feels so weird, I gotta say, it's not slimy yet.
I must say it is the most beautiful mess I've ever made.
For sure. - Very true.
- It's now time for the voice-changing microphone,
good evening, I'm Collins Key reporting live,
and Devan Key. - Hey, what's up.
- Is going to be putting some gold leaf into his slime.
This is monumental, this has never been done before.
Slime, what do you have to say about this? (blurps)
Fascinating. - It came out clean!
It came out clean! - Word.
This is my show, Devan. - I have something to say.
You're not doing a very good job.
We'll take it, back to you Frans.
(crickets chirping)
And we're back, Frans didn't have much to say.
So he reaches for the gold leaf,
he places it on top, whoa, the puppies wait in suspense,
Devan goes for sheet number two and now, folks,
I don't know what to tell you, but it appears
that actually looks pretty awesome.
Wow, alright, the gold leaf slime looks pretty awesome.
Bath bomb slime, what do you have to say about that?
(blurps)
Fascinating, alright, we're getting rid
of this microphone now, and you get to comment down below,
who made a cooler slime for this round?
Is it my awesome bath bomb slime or is it
Devan's whack gold leaf slime which is
actually pretty awesome.
Now it's time for the puppies to pick some new slimes.
- We're almost at the final round and Frans
has deserted me, what's going on buddy?
- He's already picking ingredients, bro.
Hans, want to join him?
Go get some more ingredients, Hans.
- We gotta pick this next slime.
- You got this, you got this.
I've got clear glue, fake snow and Sta-Flo,
fake snow, Sta-flo, it rhymes, great job, bro.
- Alright Frans, pick a good one, wait, toothpaste, what?
Shaving cream, okay, I can work with that, wait, dude,
not Sriracha, Frans, I thought we were friends.
There's no way I can make slime with this stuff.
(sneezes) - Bless you.
- Sorry, I tried to control it.
- You scared Frans.
- Bro, we've got snow in a can!
- Wow! - You do not seem excited.
- I don't think it's real snow, it's just powder bro.
- What? - Ah, dude, the smell.
Oh, I can't stand Sriracha, it's too spicy for me dude.
- Here we go, it's time to add the water.
You ready Devan? - Uh yes.
- Let's see if this turns into snow,
here we go, three, two, one. - Oh, what?
- What? - Yeah!
- This keeps getting bigger! - That's so sweet.
Wait, I wanna-- - No don't touch it.
This is mine. - Uh, jeez.
Dude, there's like no way, this is like goop.
- How does all of this fit into this?
Doesn't make sense, does not add up.
Oh, that smells so bad. - I know uh.
- I've got an idea, three, two, one, oh!
- That's so cool! So fluffy, oh my goodness.
- I think it might be expanding too much.
- Yeah keep it in. - Keep it in, bro.
- There's so much snow. The snow is done.
- Feels so crazy, it's all squishy, no way.
- I think I added way too much, I forgot I was supposed
to make slime. (laughing)
- Just add some to mine, mine's already ruined.
- You want it? - Yeah, I'll just take it.
- Just shoveling snow, you know, a huge mound of snow
everywhere so I gotta unload it a little bit.
We're back to the nice, fluffy, powdery snow.
- Dude, mine's yellow snow now.
- Uh oh, that's not good--
- It's warm and yellow. - Bad, very bad.
- Dude, just when I thought mine couldn't get any worse.
- Is it worse? - It looks so gross.
You will not live this one down Frans.
I'm done mixing mine, bro.
- Dude, it just keeps getting bigger and bigger and bigger.
- You're getting it on my gloves.
- It's literally like a winter wonderland right now,
it's not even Christmas yet, bro.
How does all of this fit into this?
It's already full, just that little bit.
Literally keeps growing-- - It just doesn't stop.
- We should fill a pool with 10 thousand
pounds of this stuff. Snow angel.
We're gonna add some glue next.
Whoa this is the weirdest feeling slime I've ever made.
Oh, what, this is so bizarre bro.
- Dude, what does it feel like?
- Oh, it feels like, gah, uh, ah!
- Somehow I know what that means.
- Oh, that's weird, that's not nice.
You get to comment down below, who made a cooler slime,
but that one's pretty awesome.
Yo, we are outside, it is time for the slime dump.
You've been commenting down below,
who you think lost this challenge--
- And I'm the winner!
- Wait, you are not the winner, that has not been decided.
No, I am too, we're sharing the bucket, Devan, we both are--
- So what, we're both dumping it on each other?
- I have two hands on the bucket, okay?
- I actually have them on the bucket,
you have 'em on the handle, therefore, I'm the winner.
Whoa, whoa! (laughing)
- Here we go, on three, two--
- Wait, dude, there's no, wait.
A chair, (laughs) just for you Collins.
- It's like a throne almost. - A loser's throne.
- What? I am not sitting in that throne.
You are gonna sit in that throne, oh that's heavy.
I don't like the name of this throne.
- You have no idea how heavy this is,
and it's so slippery too, you ready for this?
- Oh man, I'm not ready, gotta sit in my throne,
gotta get a little man up over here.
- Alright, here we go, slime dump, three, two, one.
- Oh, and if you wanna win a 15 minute video
call with Devan and I, text the word dog to 81800
right now, so pause the video, text the word dog to 81800
and you will automatically be entered in to win
that 15 minute video call.
- Three, two, one. (slow speed yelling)
Oh, dude! - Oh my gosh!
Hey guys! (shrieks)
(slow speed yelling)
- Dude, it missed your face!
(laughing)
- Well that's totally fine with me, you guys get to comment
down below, who won this challenge?
We'll be doing another slime challenge coming up here soon.
Shout out to the puppies by the way.
Click over here if you wanna see another video right now.
You have five seconds. (exclaiming)
Three, two, one! - Love you, bye!
(exclaiming) (Collins laughing)