- I am over 140 feet in the air right now
because Elmer's asked us,
"What if we made slime in the most extreme conditions?"
So you challenged us to make slime upside down,
in an earthquake simulator, and a 140 foot bungee jump!
So right now, let's take the leap.
Here we go!
This is the jump.
Bro, my heart is beating so fast.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one!
(screams)
Got all the glue, - Yes
- And now it's time to make the slime
that we are gonna be using
when we go off of the bungee jump drop.
That is a whole bunch!
Of course, there's gonna be a whole bunch
of different approaches that we have.
- Yes.
- I have a couple of specific slimes in mind..
that I think are gonna be perfect,
get the perfect stretch.
- I'm honestly already very nervous for this jump!
My slime is probably gonna be way cooler
than your slime. Just sayin'.
- What?
- I think it's gonna reflect in the light and everything
- What?! - as I'm like falling and
plunging towards the earth.
- All right well here we go.
You add that in, I'll keep adding in mine over here.
- I think I might've added too much glue.
Do you need some glue?
- Um. No...
(talking over each other)
- Whoa whoa whoa
- Do you need this here?
- Hey, hey, hey this is my magical liquid, Devan.
You can not have this stuff.
- Fine. I will stay with my very special
metallic magical activator here.
- Wait, can I have that?
- No, no it's mine.
This is actually a super new, cool,
metallic, magical liquid.
Your slime is not gonna stand up to mine at all.
- I don't believe you.
Okay, here we go, it's time to mix it up,
we've got the net of glory over here.
Let's just pop this in here like this.
- Yes, that's looking great.
- Oh man, alright, well that's enough with the net.
I hope that's not a foreshadowing
of what's gonna happen with the bungee cord
'cause that's not very good right there, so here we go.
- Oh, I think I added way too much glue, dude.
I forgot that we're making two of these.
- Yeah, we're making two slimes
'cause we're gonna be mixing them midair,
and then depositing them down
into the "what if" Elmer's bucket.
- You know what, I think I'm gonna use some of this glue
for my next slime here, so I'm just gonna
transfer the buckets.
- Oh you're gonna add like different magical liquid into it?
- Yeah, exactly Dude, this looks awesome!
- For a second, I thought you were a superhero there, man.
Your hands turned all metallic, and I thought
that your whole body was gonna turn metallic
or something man.
(metallic whoosh)
- Yup, I made my own sound effects.
- What? I think this is gonna be
the winning color right here, for sure.
I mean you can just see, it's obscuring Devan,
and that's how good it is.
Whoa, first bottle down.
- Dude, look at my slime, it worked out so good!
- As you know it has to be Collins-proof,
that means it has to be able to make it through anything,
so right now it's the make it through anything test,
so here we go.
(slime jiggles)
- I hope I make it through this test, jeez!
Got it in my slime.
- It made it through, alright yeah this is definitely
bungee jump ready, so here we go.
- Now I got some holographic powder I'm gonna add in.
- [Collins] That's gonna get everywhere.
When you're falling, bro, there's gonna be
so much light hitting it, it's gonna look insane.
- I know it's probably gonna be the coolest slime
I've ever made.
- You can hold my bowl, I want to do a practice round
for when we actually go for the bungee jump,
and I gotta make it into it.
If I miss, please move. Alright you ready?
- [Together] Three, two, one.
- Like that. And then, you got this.
- Here we go, here we go.
(dramatic music beat)
- Devan! Devan, you missed!
- Oh! Are you kidding me? What, you said please move.
- I meant like move to catch it.
- Oh, oh that's what you meant, I'm sorry, my bad.
Just do it one more time and I got you.
- Unbelievable, pinky promise
you're gonna actually catch it, okay?
- [Together] Three, two, one
(guys yelling)
(dramatic music beat)
- Are you kidding me?
- That had so much force to it.
Do not try this at home, this is not safe yet.
- All I gotta say is, if that's any indication
of the force that my slime will be coming down with,
it may shatter the Elmer's "what if" bucket.
Click over here to vote right now if you think
that's what's gonna happen.
And let's make the next slime!
- Now if you thought my first slime was cool,
this slime is gonna be even better.
- Not to flex, Devan, I've got color changing slime bro,
with this glue right here.
- Oh yeah, you do?
And as you can tell, we've got these watermelons over here,
and here's my idea:
I wanna test how high
that bungee jump is by yeeting these watermelons
off of the top of it.
Alright so right now let's go test these out.
Oh my gosh.
- Dude, just you getting harnessed is making me nervous.
- Holy cow, okay so they got the giant cord now.
All right, this is getting
realer and realer by the second.
- I can confirm, it has been clicked in,
and it's screwed on.
It's looking good.
- I can't see it though.
He did one of these on it.
- I hope this isn't a prank video.
You promise it's not a prank video?
- I promise this is not a prank video.
- Okay, that would not be good.
- I promise you.
- Alright, yup, secure.
- That didn't seem like you checked,
you barely touched it!
- He checked it first!
- Okay but bro come on.
(Devan and Collins talking over each other)
- You like barely touched it.
- We've got watermelon number one
And watermelon number two.
We've got wo friendly watermelons,
as you guys know we love watermelons.
We've definitely smashed a lot of them,
so let's do something we've never done.
- And today we smash some more!
- Exactly!
- Initial predictions, Devan,
how far do you think the watermelon's gonna splat?
- I think it's gonna go all the way to the outer ring.
- Alright so here we go, this is happening.
- This is getting real.
- Hello. Alright so let's see, all right.
- I have to say, this is where I'm happy
to be the younger brother.
- I knew it was a cage, but I gotta say,
it's definitely a lot wobblier than I thought it would be,
especially with two watermelons, man.
- We're going up, man.
- Oh man.
- Dude, it's definitely getting real now,
'cause we just, yeah, are ascending.
This feels like a ride you'd find in an amusement park, man.
I can like see all of LA out here. Holy cow.
- Can you hear me?
- Yes, and you're gonna want to move back when I drop these.
- I couldn't hear him at all.
- I thought I was prepared for this.
Fam, I don't know if I'm prepared for this.
Yeah, this may be one of the scariest things
I have ever been a part of.
This is like, so nerve-wracking.
Like, if you just look up, it's just a crane!
- Oh my gosh, I'm like lowkey
starting to shake a little bit.
Don't tell Devan, though, shh, we can not tell Devan,
I gotta be brave big brother, okay?
- Collins, can you hear me?
I see a hand waving, but I think that's Ron's hand.
I don't think he can hear me.
- I'm starting to shake. Devan's gonna freak out, bro.
Cause here's the advantage that Devan has, bro.
I'm the older brother so he gets to see me do it first.
- Collins, I'm gonna step out.
- I've got the watermelons, so let's see how this goes, man.
Ready? Here we go, hold it over like this.
Alright here we go, three, two, one.
- Oh man, it's coming down.
(watermelon splats)
(guys yelling)
- Oh my god!
- What? Did you see that??
It like touched that building and that building
and that building.
Oh my gosh
- Did you see that? I saw that.
- Are you going for another one?
- Alright, guys, I've got the second watermelon
'cause I gotta test this.
This is scientific method.
We've gotta see if it's really that big of a drop.
Let's see. Three, two, one, yeet.
- [Devan] Oh, it's off. Here we go!
(watermelons splats)
(guys cheering)
- [Devan] Oh, dude!
Alright, we've gotta go back down there, get my slimes,
and oh my gosh.
- Are you kidding me? There's no watermelon left!
- My heart's beating so fast right now.
- Ohh, man, I'm real nervous.
Dude that went literally everywhere.
- [Collins] I thought the impact would be big, I gotta say,
and now being up there for the first time,
very nerve-wracking, Devan.
This space feels pretty large, when you're up there,
it's like this little tiny hole, you have to jump,
like pencil dive into.
- Oh man.
- So let's keep making the slime, but I gotta say
that I do think by the-
- Hold on, I gotta take a second.
- You good?
- Real nervous.
- For what?
- For the bungee jump, dude!
- I thought you meant for like another watermelon smashing.
I'm like, it's not that big a deal.
Now it's time to add in the color-changing glue right now.
This stuff is literally like magic.
The UV rays change the color of this glue.
That's very cool as well.
- Tt's a metallic slime dude.
- Now time to add in the magical liquid
into the color-changing glue.
Oh my gosh, look at that on the inside!
- Whoaaaa
- Because the sun layer wasn't covering it.
Here we go, we're gonna go for the one hand around,
then switch stance, switch stance, switch stance.
It's the stance switch that makes a huge difference.
Dude it's crazy, look at how it's all yellow,
and it starts to change colors, man.
- Alright well now it's time to add this all new, metallic,
magical liquid.
- You're gonna add it to me, Devan, that almost got
all over me, bro.
- It's gonna be double metallic.
We prepared the perfect slime for bungee jumping,
but now it is time to prepare ourselves.
I've been told that bungee jumping is like
surviving an earthquake while being upside down.
So we've simulated both of those extreme conditions,
and now let's make some slime in them.
In preparation for our 140 foot bungee jump,
you challenged us to make slime-
(screaming)
(bottles rattling)
(Collins and Devan screaming at each other)
- I've got to add some glue!
- Whoa, the tremors stopped.
Okay, wow. This is going to be intense, man.
The point is that as we jump, we're gonna be shaking,
going all over the place, so this is a good preparation,
you know?
Alright got all the beads over here-
(screaming)
(bowls rattling)
- I caught some for you! That's for you!
- Thank you!
- If this is any indication of how shaky
the bungee jump is gonna be, bro this is going to be insane.
(Collins and Devin screaming over each other)
(slam)
- Whoa, what was that?
- I was trying to get more of the beads.
(slowed down yelling)
Alright I think I gotta start working on my slime over here,
I'm gonna add in some more metallic glue over here,
I enjoy when it's very stable in here, it's very nice.
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
Now we just gotta get some things to mix all this around,
we're going to add some of this metallic activator.
- Wow, I am kind of nervous.
(screaming)
- It's so slippery!
- I will stabilize you, Devan! You got it!
- I got it, I got it.
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
- Well, at least in the bungee jump
there aren't gonna be a bunch of beads flying everywhere.
- Just check out that stretch.
- Yo, that is perfect man, that slime is gr-
(screaming)
(low rumbling)
(Collins and Devan yelling)
- The pencils are on the ground!
- I've lost it.
- You're good, you're good.
I'll help you. I will help you.
Whoa, no. No.
- If there's one thing I've learned,
it's that whenever the tremors start, you just gotta chill.
- I had a bucket on the table where did it go?
- Okay, it's down over there.
(screaming)
(items clattering)
- Save me! Save me!
- Come back. Come back.
- I've got it, I've got it. Thank you!
- Where's my Elmer's glue, bro?
- What do you mean? It's down there!
(Collins and Devan arguing)
(screaming)
- Fine.
- Oh no, no, no.
I got it. I got it. Pull me back. Take me back.
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
- I never thought I'd say this,
but I think I'm actually prepared for the bungee jump.
- We're gonna put on this helmet.
- Why did you just put the helmet on, man?
Take the glue. Let's do it.
- If the earthquake simulator starts, Devan,
I'm just sayin', this might get all over you.
- I don't think it'll start.
- Three, two, one
(screaming)
- I'm trying!
I'm trying my best!
I'm doing my best! I've got it. I'm doing a great job!
(screaming)
- I'm doing such a great job.
Okay, there we go,
And, I think we got it!
I mean in terms of where the glue ended up,
in terms of his proportions, not totally inside there.
- You didn't get it in at all! What are you doing?
- Look at this.
- Bro!
- That's quite a bit all things considered.
- What if this happens to me on the bungee jump.
- Now, while we're here I'm just gonna dump it
into the water, and hopefully it'll absorb on the inside.
This is gonna create a very cool texture.
Ta-da! For the slime!
- Yeah! Great job.
I really think this is gonna make a big difference,
so here we go.
Gonna add that in.
I'm gonna grab some of my slime, and use this slime
to hold you in place.
So here we go. Boom.
I'm gonna put this slime like a little backpack.
A little slime in the backpack, there we go.
And then mix it, mix it mix it.
(screaming)
(objects clattering)
There goes my slime, but don't you worry,
See that little bit on my finger?
That's all we need. Here we go. Okay.
(Collins and Devan cheering)
(triumphant music)
Look at that! This is perfect!
Oh, how about you grab a side, I'll grab a side,
we'll both stretch it.
- [Together] Three, two, one
(Collins and Devan yelling)
- Let's see how the slime looks. Ready?
- Yeah, here we go.
- [Together] Three, two one
- (Collins and Devan cheering)
- We've got the perfect slime, the experience
of being in an earthquake simulator, and now,
the only thing left before we do the bungee jump,
is to make slime upside down, so let's go!
- In preparation for the bungee jump,
let's see what slime ingredients Elmer's sent us.
- Holy cow, that's a ton of ingredients,
and Elmer's challenged us to make slime
in the most extreme conditions.
- What, like upside down?
- Exactly, so right now Devan let's um-
(Collins and Devan talking over each other)
- [Together] We'll figure this out
- Yo, I've got my slime dude, this is nuts!
- Oh no, it went down, I lost it all.
- The only difference between this and the bungee jump
is that I'll be making slime while hurling
towards the ground.
That actually doesn't help me out at all.
This is metallic teal glue and confetti magical liquid.
- And this is orange glitter and metallic magical liquid
- We're gonna add some ingredients, here we go
So we got this, we're just gonna pop the top off.
- Wait, lemme try to catch it.
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
- Oh, you missed, you missed!
Okay there we go, there we go, dude.
This is insane.
- We'll just grab some of this, aw that was a miss.
- Oh! You missed! What are you doing, fam?
Grab some activator, just a little bit of activator.
(guys cheering)
- Just a little bit more.
Holy cow, this is wild.
(Collins and Devan talking over each other)
- We can go fishing a little bit, you know?
Yo, yo, let's trade slimes.
- [Together] Three, two, one
(slimes splat)
- Wait, let's try to get it in the bucket.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
(Collins and Devon yelling over each other)
What just happened?
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
- Let me add this, let me add this.
- Whoaaaa
- Holy cow.
- This is crazy
- Alright well you know what, I think this is uh-
- This is like a dream.
- We're making some new slimes here.
- It's actually way harder than you think
to make slime while hanging upside down.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, three, two, one
(guys groaning)
(slime splats in slow motion)
(uptempo electronic music)
- Alright here we go. Look at my balloon.
(Collins and Devan exclaiming in confusion)
- Dude, wait get the balloon back, get it back!
Can you get it back?
(balloon pops)
(guys exclaim in warped slow motion)
- Alright check this out bro, here we go.
Take the top off, it's a magic trick.
- [Together] Three, two, one
- You can't hit me bro, you can't hit me.
Look at that, look at that!
(dramatic music beat)
- Ohh, you actually got it on me, what are you doing?
- Alright well I think we got the experience
of being upside down, so now it's time for the next thing.
(slime clatters)
- We've made the slimes, we're back here
about to bungee jump.
Do not try this at home.
We have trained professionals here helping us do this.
First thing we gotta do right now
is just get into the harness.
- And you're going first.
- [Collins] It's a new fashion statement guys.
- [Devan] You're gonna look good Collins,
you're gonna look good.
- Thank you, man, I can tell
Alright, so guys, for this part, I stick my arms out.
Okay, this is the second harness
because again, the bungee is gonna be on my back,
so I'm gonna be going stomach first.
So all I'm seeing on my way down is just the ground
rushing towards my face.
- And the slime that's in your hands.
- Exactly.
- I'm feeling the tugging, so we're good?
- We got the thumbs-up.
Here are the slimes that you made, it is getting real man.
- So, I guess these are the slimes
that I'll be mixing on the way down.
Time to board the machine.
This is my last time on the ground
before I bungee jump.
Devan, any final words?
- Good luck!
- Thank you, man.
- Climb up here.
- Alright dude here you go.
(Collins and Devan cheering)
- And again, huge shout out to Elmer's
for sponsoring this video.
There is no way we would've been able to do this
without Elmer's glue because their glue
is what makes the slime able to be mixed
as we're beungee jumping.
So we wanna see what you can do with Elmer's glue.
A whole bunch of crazy things.
Maybe not bungee jumping,
but we know you can make some awesome slimes.
So right now it's time to go up, and make some slimes.
- Don't tell him we're talking about him,
but, uh, he doesn't look so good right now.
- Alright, we are going up.
Right now, I got all the slimes here.
I've already had to be up here once, so I'm already
a little bit scared of what this is gonna be like.
Oh my gosh, bungee jumping is one thing,
trying to mix slime and bungee jump at the same time
is a whole different ordeal, man.
That's like a whole level of concentration,
and the ground is getting smaller and smaller.
- [Devan] You good? Are you doing okay?
- I don't know!
- [Devan] Can you hear me?
- I can hear you. It's pretty scary up here bro.
- [Devan] It's really, really, real now.
- Oh, it's really real now, Devan.
There is no turning back.
- Exactly, and worst of all I still forgot,
I still have to try to aim for a bucket.
- Can you wave to me?
- Hi!
- He's now a tiny little speck in the sky.
- Help me, help.
It's a whole different ballgame up here.
When you're down there, you're like,
wow, what a large space we're in.
When you're up here, you're like oh, it's not that big.
Feeling like a little hole you're trying to jump into man.
Alright guys so the moment has come.
Time for me to pick up these slimes,
and we're just gonna be jumping off.
Bro, my heart is beating so fast.
Holy cow, I am so nervous right now.
Dude, I think I can see the beach and my house from here,
This is one of the best views in all of Los Angeles.
Unfortunately, the only way to get down is by jumping.
- Oh jeez, I'm nervous for myself 'cause I'm gonna have to
do this in just a moment.
- Alright here we go, about to grab the first slime.
Boom! There we go we've got it.
Here we go, about to grab the second slime.
Boom! Here we go.
- Oh, he's stepping towards the plank.
He's stepping towards the platform.
- Got the two slimes, as you can tell, and now
this is the jump.
Yeah, this is nuts.
Alright here we go, three,
two,
one!
(Collins screaming)
Oh my gosh, this is the scariest thing ever!
Oh my gosh!
I can't even see the bucket! There it is!
Oh my goodness, I was not ready! I was not ready at all!
Holy cow! Yeet!
- Ohhh, and he missed!
All of that, and he missed!
- I did my best bro.
That was the scariest thing I have ever done.
When you get up there, you will see.
It is very hard to hit the bucket, okay Devan?
Like, I gotta say, that was actually pretty close.
- [Devan] I believe you.
- I'm surprised I got that close.
- [Devan] You are very brave.
- Thank you
(clapping)
(people cheering)
- Bravo, bravo.
- So this is it, this is the slime, and I gotta say guys,
I know, it looks like quite a large margin,
but when you are that high in the air,
I'm shocked I even got it this close.
- [Devan] That was actually pretty close.
- That was actually pretty close!
I think I have a different method, though.
I think I'm gonna try something different.
Yeah, if I do it at all, 'cause that was terrifying.
- It's a different ballgame when you're up there.
- I'm already not a fan of this, you know.
Like that feeling that you get when you're falling?
Did you get that feeling?
- It's more the psychological element of it,
'cause you're just watching the ground rush towards you.
(Devin groans)
I was just trying to do my best,
I lost some pieces of it bro.
- You lost like half of it, it's over there, over there.
- In my defense, the wind is rushing past you.
- Look at how far that went.
- In all honesty, that could've been the slime that I aimed,
but instead I got it, like that's pretty close.
I wanna see you do closer man.
We're leaving that there to see if you can do closer.
- Oh jeez.
- So guys if that's where mine landed,
and I'm the one who just kinda jumped headfirst into things,
where do you think Devin's slime is gonna land?
Comment down below, will it hit the tarp,
will it hit outside, or is it gonna hit
somewhere completely else in Los Angeles.
So comment down below right now.
- Alright it's my turn, here we go.
Oh man, the heart is just going so fast.
- Oh my gosh, your face looks a little pale,
I do have to say right now.
- Well I did put on sunscreen, so maybe it's that.
- Hopefully it's just that.
- [Collins] You have a separate strategy
on how you're planning on mixing your slime.
- You know, I think I'm just gonna have to wing it, man.
It's gonna be crazy, I don't know how I'm gonna
concentrate on that and also not concentrate,
I'm about to, you know, smack the ground.
- If I can give you one tip, it's when you go out,
it's like the whole kind of thing is like moving.
It's swaying a little bit,
so it makes it feel even a little bit scarier
because there's this whole added motion.
- Thanks. Appreciate that.
- So you go, these are the slimes.
(Collins and Devan talking over each other)
- I think I did a good job, right?
- He did a good job on the slimes, but now the question is,
is he going to be able to mix them?
- Hold on, I gotta tighten my helmet. It's a little loose.
- Safety is extremely important as we're doing this.
(Devan screams)
You good?
- Yep, it's gonna work.
Alright here we go.
- Alright Devan's hopping on.
- Give me a high five!
You got this bro.
- Thank you very much.
- I believe in you Devan.
- Thank you, I'm actually not nervous yet.
- Just let me know when you start to get nervous.
- Okay, do you have the bullhorn?
Grab the bullhorn!
- Okay, grab it.
- Devan what's the verdict?
- You guys are lucky, you get to just watch.
It's terrifying.
So far, this is a beautiful view.
Just look over the edge real quick.
That is just terrifying, and it doesn't look as scary
on camera as it does in real life.
- Is it getting a little bit scarier, Devan?
- Not a little bit! Actually, quite a lot a bit!
- Yeah, you're getting pretty high up there now, Devan.
- Uh huh, and we're not even to the top yet.
- When I got to that point, I was like tripping out.
He seems to be handling it a lot better than I was.
- Dude! I am terrified!
- I can only imagine what's going through his head right now
- Was Collins this scared? This is like mind-boggling.
Just look over the edge real quick.
I got people in like apartments watching me.
What is going on?
- Right now I'm sure he's getting instructions and stuff.
Bro, I was just stalling up there.
Everything I could think of,
like how could I possibly stall this situation
just a moment longer?
- Is it good to go now, even though my heart's going crazy?
- Oh yeah, absolutely.
- Alright here we go, I am about to jump.
Collins, can you see me?
- [Collins] You got this bro!
- Dude, this is crazy.
Comment down below, "You got this Devan!" 'cause I need it.
- Devan! Devan! You got this bro!
- You ready?
- Just his little head pops out over the edge, oh my gosh.
Devan, you got your slime right?
- I got my slime!
- Cause otherwise, you're gonna have to do this again.
- All right, I'm grabbing my slime right now.
It feels very unstable, I have to say.
- He isn't ready.
- How long of a drop is it? Like two seconds?
Three seconds? Four seconds?
- 140 feet of fun.
- Here's my slime.
- Alright he's going for it. This one's for real, guys.
- Here we go, three, two, one.
(Devan and Collins screaming)
- [Collins] Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
- Oh my goodness!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
- That was insane!
- I got a little of the slime, NO!
That was the scariest thing I've ever done.
Can I make this little bit of slime?
- See if you can get that little bit of slime in the bucket,
You've still got a chance, Devan.
- See if I can make it, see if I can make it.
Oh man, that was close.
Dude, you were right, that was the scariest thing
I've ever done.
- I gotta give you credit bro,
that's a super scary thing to do, man.
So nicely done.
- Hand me the slime, thank you, I'm gonna dunk it.
(Collins screaming)
- That is cheating! You cannot do that man!
(Collins and Devan yelling over each other)
- That does not count, no, no, no.
- Are you good?
- No, I'm not, it's slippery.
- Well, I gotta say, I think my slime barely
got a little bit closer bro.
- [Devan] I think it did. You did a better job.
- [Collins] But how was that?
- [Devan] That was terrifying. What was that, man?
- [Collins] Was it fun, though?
- [Devan] It was super fun, like once you're weightless?
Man, that was super fun.
It's just getting over the first hump,
that's the craziest part.
= So how about this, since we both were not able
to get the slime into the bucket,
let's combine our two slimes, mix them together.
Brother power, like this.
On the count of three, we'll both dunk it in the bucket.
You ready? All right, here we go, here we go.
- [Together] Three, two, one
(slime splats)
- Yes! - Boom, there we go, guys.
So thank you so much for watching, and a huge thank you
to Elmer's for making all of this possible.
What if Elmer's challenged you to make extreme slime?
What slime would you make?
Comment that down below right now,
and if you want to see another video,
click right over here.
You got five seconds, here we go.
- [Together] Five, four, three, two, one, done!
Love you! [Together] Bye!