- These are real life zombies,
because you challenged us to play hide and seek
with zombies here at Two-Bit Circus.
But here's the twist, if the zombies find and tag us,
we get turned into zombies and join the herd.
Last man standing wins and the clock starts now.
(bell rings) Let's Go!
- [Ben] What? - Alright guys,
let's find some hiding spots, let's do this.
(group exclaims excitedly)
- [Nina] Oh my gosh, this is amazing.
- Holy cow!
Alright well, everyone's going that way,
I'm going this way.
No one's gonna find me.
- Look at this, what?
What do you think?
Can you tell that it's me?
- Look at that face that is insane.
That's really cool.
- Maybe I can do something where I can like
hide under the chair, maybe under this?
That would be kinda cool. (door creaks)
- I heard someone.
Let's find the others.
(screams)
- [Alexis] Please! - Hide!
- Oh my gosh, he needs to help us Lindsay.
- All right we're going upstairs.
No body's gonna find me up here.
Oh man, I don't know what to do.
- Yo guys, Yo guys, behind here
I think I may have found my hiding spot.
(leaves rustling)
- And one other thing I forgot to mention is that,
whenever the siren of terror goes off,
we have to switch hiding spots immediately.
- Wow, this place has so many hidden treasures,
this is crazy.
- Whoa, what are you doing there?
- What are you doing here?
- Money's on Bella,
she'll be the first one turned into a zombie.
- You're super tall, I'm little n' speedy.
- [Lindsay] That's like not gonna work.
Oh oh can you hold this?
Guys I think I found it.
- [Nina] Okay, no.
- I mean I can hide in the trashcan.
Throw myself with trash, that may work.
- If you can hide up in here, that would be nuts man.
Just like spider-manned out. (screams)
- Oh maybe behind the box.
Nope, but I could get a soda.
I don't want a soda but I could if I wanted to.
I know the object is there.
- [Devan] Ben, look at Ben, he's just running man.
(silly noise crashing)
- Oh sorry!
- If we both come in here,
it'll be like we're both in the womb again.
- [Lindsay] I can't fit under there, let's go.
- Oh, maybe I can hide behind the pillar.
Yeah, you can probably still see me.
Okay guys, we're running really out of time,
so I'm gonna go hide here
'cause it looks super promising.
Oh, okay I think I can fit in it.
Bye guys.
Don't tell Collins, I'm gonna win this.
- Oh, this is the place.
Squeeze in back here.
Okay guys, this could actually work.
- I wish I could hide in one of these things.
That would be awesome,
that would be some like James Bond level stuff.
I might, do i able to like hide in here,
if you kinda like knot up
and become curled up into a ball or something?
- [Collins] Oh, I forgot to mention that all the zombies
are wearing ear plugs,
which means meaning they will not be able to hear us
and can only find us based on sight.
- I'm running out of time.
I have no clue where I'm gonna hide.
(bell rings) (zombies grunt)
- [Ben] Guys, they're coming, they're coming.
- I feel like you don't have as much adrenaline as me.
What's in here? - [Nina] I do,
trust me, I do.
(both screams)
(grunts)
- Oh, check this.
You can see everything that everybody else is doing.
Oh geeze, there are so many zombies.
I think I'm just gonna stay up here and hide.
- Alright guys, so I found the perfect hiding spot.
It's around this corner.
There's no way that the zombies
are gonna be able to find me.
Alright guys, I'm gonna hop in, come on.
Okay. (screams) (zombie grunts)
- Shh! (zombie grunts)
- Yo, come on in here and check this out.
We have like a control room.
Dude, I'm like so scared
a zombie is down this hallway over here.
But this is a great spot.
(zombie grunts)
- You need to use your brain now because I...
- We have the same brain! - I have tried everything.
Wait that's scary.
- [Lindsay] Woodshop?
- I don't like it in here.
- No one's ever gonna find me in here.
- [Nina] Can I fit?
- I think there's room for both of us.
- [Devan] Dude, there are so many zombies.
I am so glad I'm up...
No, that's the siren (siren blaring)
and it means I have to change my hiding spot.
(zombies grunting)
- Alright.
- [Collins] Okay everyone, listen up,
zombies are coming but I found a hiding spot.
We would go down that way right now.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, go go go!
Come on!
- Alright, alright, lets go, quickly.
(group chattering) (zombies grunting)
Close the door,
close the door.
Alright, let's turn on the lights
and see what's going on here.
Is the switch over here?
- [Ben] Yeah, that's...
(group exclaims)
- Alright guys, so here's the thing.
This is a great hiding spot
but the only issue with it is that
once the siren goes off, we're gonna all have to relocate
and find another hiding spot.
So how about this, we'll create some defense weapons
that way the zombies cannot tag us,
we'll be able to get away.
- I think I found a really good thing
out in the kitchen area.
So I'm actually going to go out there-
- You're going to go into the kitchen out there?
- I'm gonna try to find it. - Are you crazy?
- I'll be back guys.
- Devan. - I'll be back.
- And if you see Alexis out there, let us know
'cause we need to know if she's a zombie or not.
- I will definitely let you know.
All right, see you guys later.
- All right, so the goal is to find a weapon
and I think I found one over here.
Just have to check for zombies.
Okay we're clear.
(metal clanging)
- Okay so here's the thing guys
I'm gonna try and make like an ax.
- What if we liked taped it?
You should do that 'cause I don't know how.
- Oh, guys I found it.
Oh!
- Oh wait, Ben what are you doing over there dude?
- [Collins] Put that down, dude put that down.
Alright let's test that thing out.
- I really want to try this.
- Get an arrow over here dude, I'm super excited.
- All right, I got it, What am I aiming for?
- [Collins] You're gonna aim for that can
that I set up for you.
Alright here we go, three, two, one.
(group exclaims)
(zombie grunts)
- Here we go, we're gonna use this
to see if we can line this up properly.
- That can work.
- That's what I'm saying.
Oh it's upside down.
- Alright guys, so far I gotta "p."
- Dude find a corner or something, like not just here.
- No, no, I got the letter "p," the big "p."
- That's not a "p' dude clearly it's a nine.
- It's a six
- Oh it's a 6?
Quick Maths.
- Let's see if this can crush some zombies.
Safety goggles on; do not try this at home.`
Alright here we go, three, two, one.
(Collins exclaims)
(zombies grunt)
- Oh, dude I think I found a room, I think I found a room.
Alright come on, come on, come on.
What?
No way!
But before I show you want I found,
we have a huge announcement for you,
because on our last video we got over 40,000 comments
saying that you would be super hyped
to play a challenge created by Collins and me,
so guess what?
We took the best parts of your favorite videos
and turned them into our first ever line up
of challenges, toys and games you can play at home.
Comment down below "I'm in"
if you wanna play the challenges.
It's here dude, look at this thing.
Holy Cow!
I just gotta grab this, take this back to the group
and this is gonna be way better than anything they have got.
(zombies grunt) Oh no no no!
- So I have my PI paid "p" shooter.
- (laughs) That guy has the most lethal
p I've ever seen in my life.
(all laughs)
- Nina and Lindsay, what is this?
Shh, I think I hear a zombie.
Hold on.
Go back there and hide.
(tense music) (zombie grunts)
(plank clanks) (group exclaims)
(door bangs)
(door slams)
- Dude, it is so crazy out there.
- What is that?
- This is my trust friend I found on the way.
All right, I haven't tried this thing yet,
so let's see how this works.
- And do not try this at home.
- Do not.
- Here we go, you ready?
Three, two, one.
(group exclaims)
- That's nothing compared to ours.
- What?
- [Devan] How did you guys make this?
- Oh, it was easy.
- Are you guys gonna launch it like at the two big cans?
- [Nina] We will right there.
- You have goggles on.
Do not try this at home.
You guys ready?
Here we go, three, two, one.
(cans clanging) (group exclaims)
- [Collins] Oh, that's the siren.
Okay, we gotta find new hiding spots.
Get caught and you turn into a zombie
but right now we gotta split up.
- [Ben] We gotta go, go!
- [Devan] Come on this way, follow me!
- Ninja rolls at a time..
- I'm not joking around.
- Fudge, they're everywhere.
(mumbles)
- This thing is way too loud.
Okay, hold on I gotta to take this thing off.
- [Bella] Okay.
- [Devan] We're good?
- [Bella] Yeah, okay so this says break room.
Should we go through it?
- I mean yeah, it might be a good spot.
Let's do it, let's do it.
(zombie grants)
Dude, oh god.
(tense music)
My phone's down.
- Oh (indistinct), oh, this is it.
(tense trombone)
Oh, no!
(artifacts crashing)
- Sorry, sorry.
- That was all your fault.
- I know, come here. (zombie grunts)
This way, this way.
- Wait, I here someone...
(zombie shuffling)
- Okay go go go, come on, come on, come on.
(Ben screaming)
- Where you going?
Where we going?
Alright I have enough
for the five second subscribe challenge.
If you want to, you can subscribe to the channel
and turn on the post notifications in five seconds.
You ready?
Here we go, five, four, three,
two, one, done deal.
Dude, you alright? (screams)
Yo dude, I think we gotta make a run for it
like over that way, okay?
Let's just go go go go go.
(zombie grunt)
(tense music)
(dramatic music)
- I can't take two at a time, Devan!
- [Lindsay] Whoa, this is insane, we found a spot.
- [Nina] It's cold in here, okay.
- [Lindsay] Wait what about in here?
This aint gonna work-
- [Nina] I don't think I'll fit in there, what's in there?
- Wait I think I have found something in here.
(scream) (zombies grunting)
- Is this a secret door or something?
Wait.
Perfect.
- Ooh.
I think there's something over there.
Don't look this way, don't look this way.
- [Ben] Is that a wheel?
Yeah, it's a wheel, go get it.
- Hold this, hold this for a second.
- Be careful.
- Dude we can sneak behind this way.
Crouch crouch crouch down.
On the count of three you go.
Three, two, one, let's go go go go.
Okay Okay.
- I hear them everywhere.
Let's just try it, okay.
- [Bella] Where are we going?
Where?
(zombies grunting)
(tense music)
- Okay, okay!
Come on, here we go (indistinct).
- Oh my God! (laughs)
(both mumbling)
- Wait a second.
Look at this, we're gonna hide in plain sight.
You ready? (screams)
- It looks safe up there, I can see the sky.
They will probably never find me up here.
This is the best spot ever. (screams)
- We gotta find a spot dude, we're running out of time.
Do a little duck walk over here.
A little duck-walk over here.
Slick.
Behind us. (zombies grunting)
- I'm not thin enough for this.
I'm not thin enough.
(suspenseful music)
- Bro they are so close right now.
- Did you hear them?
- That was so close.
- You're gonna crawl underneath?
- Can't fit.
There's a door.
- Dude no way, check it out.
Dude yo!
Dude that's perfect.
Go go go go.
(Ben screams)
(siren ringing)
- Wait no, that siren means
we have to find a new hiding spot.
Okay, run run run run run.
- I'm just gonna find a new hiding spot, I think...
(bricks crashing)
Aaugh!
(indistinct)
- Okay, we are clear. - [Bella] Go go go go go go.
- We still haven't found a spot yet
so I'm thinking the kitchen might be a good place to be.
- Okay, that would be good. - Go go go go go go!
- (Collins screams) Wait a minute!
- Wait a second, wait a second.
Keep your distance.
Are you a zombie? - [Bella] Don't get near us.
- [Collins] Do I look like, do I look like a zombie?
- Yeah you're really pale right now.
- [Collins] I don't get a lot of sun.
I make YouTube videos all the time.
- Okay, all right.
The real question though is,
are we the final three at this point?
(zombie grunt)
Okay, they are leaving.
- Okay well I guess that answers that.
The twins have been turned into zombies.
I know Ben was for sure turned into a zombie.
I don't know about Alexis,
like she's been hiding this whole game or she's a zombie,
so I think, we might be the final three.
- [Devan] There's probably other zombies in here.
- I don't hear anything.
- What is this?
(group exclaims)
- Why is this here? - Why is it not?
This place has got literally everything bro.
This is the answer.
Today's game plan
is that we're trying to find the place to hide
in plain sight and make ourselves look like zombies.
- What, I like it!
- Dude, that is absolutely insane, I am not sticking around.
- Go go go go!
I'm out, I'm out people.
- You gotta tell us how to make us over.
What is he thinking?
There's a lot of zombies here, so how about this?
We gotta make one more item we can use
'cause now we're a team.
New team alert, let's get it.
Alright, check the freezer.
Yo, look at this.
There's like a hand in here.
We can probably make a candy arm out of this.
We got the head, the candy arm.
There's like doughnuts over here
that we can use to build the arm.
(zombies shuffling)
- We'll grab some doughnuts.
- So I still haven't found a spot but gonna try it out.
Okay coast is clear.
Dude, they are so many zombies out here.
Holy cow, I'm gonna try to go here.
- We gotta do this fast, they're gonna find us here.
- I need to break this.
- You need to break this, leave that to me.
Here we go.
(plastic crashes)
Oh!
- Shh.
- I don't know, it's resistant to drop kicking.
That was strong man, holy cow.
Oh it's like an elbow for the arm?
There we go by the way.
No no no, that's a twig.
- Oh, I thought it was pretty similar.
(exclaims)
- Oh wait a second.
I think there was something over here.
I just found the best spot ever.
Dude, no one's gonna find me here.
(screams)
- Okay so here we go, we got the glaze over here.
No,
oh no!
We are so close!
Okay, we gotta manage to look like zombies
like real quick like right now.
Just pop it on your face?
No way.
- Do more. - All right.
Okay ready?
- Three, two, one.
(Collins laughs)
- That's gonna be a meme.
Are you good, is that enough?
- I gotta do it to you.
I don't know, three, two, one.
(lady laughs)
- Okay, we need to get going.
(indistinct)
- Why is it acting all like rubbery?
Dude they are all out there.
We're gonna be like full on zombies.
- Okay.
- (indistinct) Best of luck.
Cheers, ready, here we go.
- And if you want the chance
to get a personalized video message from Devan and me
and early access to our first ever live
of toys, games, and challenges;
click the top link in the description right now
and join our keyper club. It's completely free.
- Three, two, one, let's do it.
(both grunting)
Ooh, right there.
(all grunting)
(screams)
- And that sound means the game is over guys.
That's it.
All right guys,
say hello to all our zombie friends over here.
Huge thank you to all of our friends for being in this video
and a massive thank you to Two-Bit Circus
for letting us go here.
If you guys want to have some fun,
this is the place to be.
You want another video,
click right over here you have five seconds, here we go,
five,
four, three,
two, one, done.
Love you, bye.