- What's up, guys?
I'm Collins Key, and I'm here in the dressing room with
- [All] Fifth Harmony!
- I am really excited because today
I have a super special video for all of you.
Every video, I ask you guys to comment down below
with who you guys want to see me do magic for.
And when I was looking through the comments,
the number one name I saw was Fifth Harmony.
If you love Fifth Harmony, let me know
by liking this video.
And let's get to the magic.
- [Camila] Any card?
- [Collins] Any card.
- Boop!
- [Collins] The joker.
- Yeah.
- [Collins] All right, cool, so take it out.
And what I want you to do, actually,
if I can get your autograph.
All right, you can just take the card and just sign it.
- Okay.
Sorry I write like a Third grader.
- [Collins] It's all good.
- Heh
- [ Collins] Cool, cool, Alright cool.
So basically the reason I have you sign it
is because, that way, there is only one card
like this with this exact signature in the entire world.
It's impossible to duplicate it.
So this is going to be your card.
So you can feel it, the ink won't come off?
- Nope. Won't come off.
- [Collins] Check it out so we use your joker.
Check this out.
I'm going to try to fold it up a little bit.
And I want you to actually open up your mouth.
- Okay. Well!
- And I want you to bite on the card.
Cool, alright here we go.
So here, I'll use my own card here.
Jack of Hearts.
So here, I'll sign the Jack.
Get a shot of this.
Like that. You saw my signed Jack.
Alright so what's going to happen here,
- [Camila] Tastes funny.
- [Collins] Tastes funny, right?
- Yeah tastes like Sharpie.
- Blue cards taste better, actually.
Check it out, watch.
See my Jack right here? Check this out.
Put it down.
Alright, so watch this.
(techno music)
- [Ally] It's so cool.
- What's going on?
- [Camila] Open the card!
- Check it out, you signed the Joker
and put it in your mouth.
(gasps)
- [All] Oh my God!
- [Normani] What the heck?
I wanna try!
- Mind blown!
- Give this video a huge thumbs if you enjoyed
Fifth Harmony's awesome reactions.
I've got great news for you because there's
actually a part two video.
I'm going to put the link right around over here
so be sure to click that right now
if you want to see even more crazy magic
and ridiculous reactions from Fifth Harmony.
And I want you guys to comment down below
and let me know:
Who should I do magic for next?
Don't forget, of course:
Subscribe to this channel.
Once again you guys, my name is Collins Key.
Thank you so much for watching this week's magic video.
I'll see you guys again soon.
Peace.
(snaps)
(techno music)
- Can you make one of us disappear?
- Yeah!
- Normani, please! I'm kidding!