- My parents will be so upset when they find out about this.
- [Together] No!
(tone) - What's up?
It's Collins Key and today we are doing another DIY.
And today, get ready for this, we are doing
a giant glow in the dark glitter slime stress ball,
that's made out of a giant Wubble.
No, it hit my brother's painting!
I am going to literally die.
This painting is absolutely gorgeous
and the Wubble may or may not have just hit it in the face.
I've had bad experiences with Wubbles
and this is just one more of those bad experiences.
Like when I did the testing As Seen On TV Products video,
well yeah you guys, you know what happened there.
(whooshing) - Ahhh!
Uhhh! (laughing)
- [Man] Direct hit.
(Wubble popping) - Ohhh!
- [Man] K-O.
- [Collins] My God dude that hurt.
- [Man] Look at what's on his face.
- What?
- [Man] Look at that.
- What happpened?
- Wait, what happened?
- [Man] Look at that.
- What happened?
- [Man] Oh man.
- That didn't hurt? - Wow!
- That hurt a lot!
Today I'm going to be attempting to conquer
my fear of the Wubble by turning it into
a giant DIY stress ball.
And if you want me to do a super messy slime challenge,
let me know by liking this video.
And if this video gets enough thumbs up,
then I will do a crazy challenge, probably with Devan,
where we just dump a whole bunch of slime
all over each other.
So yeah thumbs up this video right now
if you want to see that.
Now there are two parts to this DIY.
Part number one is where I'm actually going to make the DIY,
and part number two I'm going to slice it open
and pour all the slime all over myself.
If you want to see that, I posted it on my Instagram
so go check out the link down in the description below.
That will take you directly to that Instagram post
and if you like the post, comment Fluffy Bunny
and then follow me on Instagram,
like turn on my post notification.
I'll be going through your guys' photos,
liking a ton of them.
And also I'm going to be following some of you guys
on Instagram who do that.
So go check that out right now.
And I'm super excited because I'm doing a free meetup
this Saturday in LA at 6:00 p.m.
on the 3rd Street Promenade.
Basically I just want to hang out with you guys,
give you some free stuff and also do some crazy magic.
And this is all because I'm teaming up with AT&T Hello Lab,
and we're going to be filming this meetup as well.
So if you guys are there,
you're going to be a part of this video.
It's going to be crazy.
All the information is down in the description below.
I got to give credit to Corina Garcia
who inspired me to make this video.
So go check out her videos, I'm going to put them down
in the description below.
So without any further ado, let's jump right into the video.
All you need for this DIY are just four things.
Number one is the Wubble.
(rising reveal music)
Yike!
Heeh!
You also need some measuring cups,
you're going to need some glue,
some liquid starch.
Don't you ever disrespect me again.
And last but not least, I like this glue more.
We're going to kick this off by making the slime first.
And all you're going to be doing for this
is adding equal parts glue and equal parts water,
mixing them all together.
Whu hu ho, this is going to be so so cool.
If I didn't know better I would say this looks like yogurt
and I would try to eat it right now
because I haven't eaten yet today, it looks real
(gagging)
Tsk tsk tsk, does not, (gagging)
it does not tastes like yogurt at all.
We're just going to forget that that ever happened.
And no screenshots please guys.
(dings)
You guys I'm a genius because instead of
using one cup each time,
which was kind of slowing down the entire process,
I could dump this entire thing in there all at once
and then all I have to do is just fill it up with water
because that will make sure it's equal parts water,
and equal parts glue, I'm a genius.
Here we go.
Yo ho ho, this is a lot of glue.
If you are a slime critic watching this,
you probably going to say at the moment
things are looking a little bit too bland
and I completely agree with you.
So right now we're going to spice up.
We got some blue, we got some pink, some red,
we're going to add some color into this
and just kind of see how it looks.
Alright here we go guys, we got two colors at once.
Let's see if I could actually like swirl them mid air.
(liquid squirting) (laughing)
I can't, guys I'm sorry.
(mumbles) (mimics sneezing)
(laughing) It didn't work.
I have like one here, I have a whole bunch of these like
glitter tubes which we are going to be using.
Here we go, you guys ready for this?
This is about to look amazing, here we go.
These are literally just like tubes with glitter in them,
like that's really all this is right now.
One more thing of pink.
(liquid squirting) (laughing)
If you were to look up how to do this
normally they would suggest you use a spoon to mix it up
but personally I'm extra fancy man,
I know how to use chopsticks and so I'm going to be
using chopsticks to mix this whole thing up.
So let's see here.
Okay like I was completely joking, like I didn't know
this would actually be good.
This actually looks super cool with the chopsticks.
Here's the thing about DIY, you never know exactly
how it's going to go and at the moment
this is just not colorful enough.
So we've got some food coloring here
so hopefully this will really make a huge difference,
'cause if not this not going to be
a colorful slime at all.
So adding the green food, that was literally the best thing
I could have ever done because now
it actually looks like slime.
And now I just need to add a whole bunch of water.
So without splashing this everywhere,
we're just gonna kinda go for it, let's see.
(liquid pouring)
Contain yourself water. (gasps)
It's getting out of hand.
It's getting a little bit out of hand.
And I was like no, no, stop it, stop it!
No, no, no, stop!
Alright there we go, it is starting to look
real funky now man, real funky.
We're getting a spoon upgrade right now
because now I need to mix this stuff all together so.
Yeah so like it's not really mixing together that well.
This table means a lot to my parents
and so I cannot get it like messed up at all.
So that's why I'm just trying to be super cautious right now
because I will lose my DIY privileges.
Next we are adding the liquid starch into this container,
so let's go for it.
(liquid pouring) (chuckling)
This stuff looks weird.
So next I'm going to be adding a whole bunch of the water
and glue into this and hopefully it'll turn into slime.
We're going to be using this bowl here to scoop
the glue water and them dump it,
oh ho ho ho, that's so heavy.
Yeah this getting real slimy now.
You know what, using a spoon is not that much fun
so we're gonna go with my hands right now, let's just.
Yuh awww. (chuckles)
This feels so good, oh my gosh yo.
(slime dripping and splatting)
(laughing)
Look at this! This is so wild!
(slime squashing)
(laughing)
This next part, I feel rather innovative.
What I've done is I've actually taken the glue container,
chopped off the top of it and we are now
going to use that as a funnel.
I'm using my brother, so here are Devan's hands,
his lovely model hands.
So now we're going to take this, (chuckles) it's so heavy.
Basically just go take it, (chuckles) it's so heavy.
The goal is, take this and dump it into here,
and I will funnel it into the Wubble.
Here we go, ohh yup.
Casual, okay.
You ready Devan?
- [Devan] I'm waiting.
- [Collins] Dude hold it.
- [Devan] I am, I am, I am.
Oh my gosh.
(Collins gasping)
It's on my hands.
Dude it's on my hands. - I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm fine, I'm. - You just need
one of these to stabilize.
- Alright so we are like in crisis mode right now
because we need to figure out,
I'm going to, we need more water
I think is what the issue is, excuse me.
- Nah nah nah nah nah nah no, it's not attached.
- We're going with a different plan here,
it's called the Shove Slime Method.
This isn't going to work.
- I'm going to break it. (giggles)
- Ow! (panting) Help!
This does not smart, this does not smart.
Oh no we're breaking the Wubble!
I think I literally just snapped the Wubble.
This is hands down the greatest fail I've ever had
at a (laughs) DIY ever, ever.
Uhh (slaps) uhh (slaps)
♫ DIY
Oh this is going to be so perfect,
this is going to be amazing.
This is going to totally work.
Yes, I might've actually added too much water, shoot!
Guys we got one more friend to help us out,
his name is Mason.
- What's up Mason?
- I'm gonna like bring up a lot like this
and you gotta like cut it off at the bottom
and like put it in there.
Alright so I'm going to lift up like this,
cut off at the bottom, and then, and then dump it
in there, dump it in, dump it in there, okay!
- [Mason] Oh that was nice!
- No, Mason's good at this!
Let's do it again, okay here we go.
Ooop, cut it off, cut it off.
Yeah, ninja chop it, ninja chop it, ninja chop it.
Back in, there we go.
- Nice. - Alright here we go,
whoever's new, this will be a four person thing.
Go go go, shove it in. - Ohhhhhh!
- Get it off the side. - I can't, I can't.
I can't, no! - Ahhhh!
- No, no!
- [Together] No!
- No! - It's got to stay in.
- This was the terriblist idea we've ever had.
Alright guys definitely not a brilliant idea
and Devan's idea was to use the funnel as a giant scoop.
And so like we scoop all the liquid in here.
Mason you want to cut it off over there.
- Yeah. - And here we go,
three, two, one, go for it.
And then see if we can get,
ayyyy, we are geniuses!
- Oh, wow.
- Yes! Ah yes!
Oh we're so smart, well Devan's smart.
Alright this might have to be our last scoop bro.
Here we go, go, go, go.
My parents are going to be so upset
when they find out about this table, like so upset.
- You just want to dump this now?
- [Collins] Yeah, let's just give it a shot,
let's go for it.
- Yeah okay alright, nice.
- [Collins] Yeah Mason!
- Oh my gosh.
- [Collins] There we go, that's good,
that's good, that's good.
- [Devan] Alright you got it.
- Alright well there we go.
Now we have the giant DIY stress ball.
How's it going to stay closed now?
Alright guys well there you have it,
this is the giant DIY--
- Uh, you got it on me. - I'm sorry bro.
This is the um (slaps)
the stress ball so. - No!
- This failed so bad. (chuckles)
This is the worst fail I ever had as a DIY.
Now if you guys want so to see me dump all this slime
all over me right now, go check out the video is live
on my Instagram, give it a like, follow my Instagram,
turn on my notifications and comment Fluffy Bunny.
And I will like a whole bunch of pictures
on your profile.
And give this video a thumbs up if you want a whole video
that's just a slime challenge, 'cause if this got wild
you guys know that's gonna be getting crazy.
So yeah just, I'm stressed right now,
I'm trying to use the stress ball.
I'm just going to slap this and then I'll disappear.
So bye.
(slaps)
- [Devan] Bro, can I let go of it now?
Bro where'd you go?
- Ow, this isn't even a dump!