- What's up? It's Collins Key,
and today I'm chillin' here with the one and only
Sam Pottorff.
- Hey, guys. - [Collins] Yeah.
So today we got a challenge for you.
We're going to be doing the Guess that Youtuber Challenge.
We're goin' head-to-head, testing our knowledge right now.
And basically, we're gonna be showin' a photo
of a Youtuber's face, super zoomed-in on one part of it,
and just off that part, we gotta guess who it is.
Whoever can get it first, they win that round.
Whoever wins the majority of those rounds,
they get to tweet something off
of the loser's Twitter account.
- So we get to hack each other.
- Yeah, it's gonna be crazy.
And also, as this challenge is going,
I want you guys, to like, follow along,
guess along with us,
see if you guys can get 'em right.
Give the video a thumbs up, if you guys are ready.
And also, watch 'til the very end
to find out what the tweet is
that the other person hacked off their account.
First one, here we go.
Let's see what it is.
Hayes?
- Oh. - [Collins] Oh, I got it
right off the bat, OK.
- That was good, that was good.
- I saw the eyes, and I'm like, hey, blue eyes squad.
- Yeah. - [Collins] All right, cool.
- Cameron Dallas.
- Oh, you're too quick.
- Matt. - [Collins] Matthew Espinosa.
Yeah, that's Matthew Espinosa.
- Is that? - [Collins] Yeah, that has,
Yeah. OK, cool.
- All right, you got that one.
- All right, let's see the next one.
- Me. That's me.
- That's Sam? Is that you?
(chime) (laughing)
He got his own pic.
I'm looking at it, I'm like, I actually don't know
who that is.
- Thanks.
- Well, no, just off the eyes.
- That is an old picture.
- OK, yeah, with the hair and everything.
- I have no clue.
- Is it?
- Is that Julian Smith?
(chime) - Ohh.
- Yes.
- Bro, legend right there.
- Jenna Marbles.
(chime) - Mmm.
- Ha. - [Collins] Ha.
- Uh. Huh?
Janoskians.
I still can't see.
- Is it Janoskians?
Yeah. - [Sam] Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- I almost said One Direction.
- Yeah, I thought it was, too.
Caspar. Caspar Lee?
Did I get it?
- Dude, you're killin' it.
Yeah, make it really hard.
- Um, that is, there's a dimple.
- I, honestly,
(Jeopardy! Music)
- Is that one of the Harris brothers?
Is that Jack or Finn Harris? No?
- I feel like it, um,
Is it one of the Dolan twins?
- It looks like there's a cheeky little smile goin' on.
(laughing)
- It has that little...
- Maybe look at it the other way.
I don't know.
- No, that's not helping.
It looks like a different body part.
(Collins laughing)
- Is it Crawford?
- Crawford. You did it.
- All right.
- I know. One of us were like...
- So those first ones, they were, I wouldn't say, easy,
but they were on the easier side.
Now, for these next ones, they're gonna get
way more difficult.
- Jack and Jack.
- No. Is it? (chime)
Ah, missed it.
Oh, 's OK.
That's me.
Yeah, OK.
Kian?
- Is it?
Wow. - [Collins] Yes.
- Wow.
- I can't believe I got it, holy cow.
- Wow, that's sad.
- I'm sorry, bro.
- Oh, my, wait,
- Wait, wait, wait.
What is it?
- Fun for Louis. Louis Cole.
(chime)
Yes.
- Whoa. Bro, I give you so much props.
I had no idea on that one.
I had no idea. - [Sam] I love him.
- He has glasses.
- Gingerish eyebrows, right?
- Yeah, a little bit, or could be blond.
- Ah.
- There's really not a lot to go off.
Is it, I don't know.
- I don't want to guess wrong.
That's why I'm like...
- Yeah, no, me, too.
- This is so bad.
- I'm so stumped right now.
You have any idea who it is?
- I'm just going to guess, Tyler Oakley?
(chime)
- Oh my gosh.
We're gonna do a bonus round right now
and we're gonna guess that celebrity,
just for fun, because we love you guys, so yeah.
Let's do it.
You got a lot better at cropping these, I can say that.
Just take a little bit of her eye in the photo.
- The eyes look like they're going outwards.
Is it the girl that was in American Ultra?
- Yeah.
- Kirsten...
- Kristen Stewart, Kristen Stewart?
I got it, I'm sorry I got it.
We'll call it a half point for each on that one.
- Oh, OK.
- Oh, Britney Spears. No, that's Britney Spears.
- Britney Spears.
I always get...
(chime) No, it's Britney Spears.
- OK.
- I always get mixed up with their names.
Is that Pedro?
- Pedro.
(laughing)
- From, uh...
- Oh, oh, David Blaine.
Yeah, OK, gotcha.
- Oh, my gosh.
It looks like Pedro from Napoleon Dynamite.
- Right.
Justin Bieber.
Yeah.
Sorry, I saw the tats.
I was, like, it has to be.
Jaden Smith? - [Sam] Jade Jeshjuh.
5SOS.
- Hmm, nice.
Brown hair. - [Sam] Demi Lovato?
Is that Demi?
(chime)
She looks so different.
I shoulda known that one, I don't know what I was doin'.
Ooh, ah, Mr. T.
Is that Mr. T?
(buzzer)
- Uh, whoo-joo-wa.
- Exactly. Was that anyone huuk-so-howa?
(laughing)
- I know it's not, but Weeknd?
(buzzer)
- No, it's not The Weeknd.
It's, is it Kanye?
(chime)
Oh, my...
- That was a good one.
- I had no idea that was Kanye.
- Wow.
He had bigger lips than I thought.
All right, guys.
So, obviously, Collins won the challenge.
Now he gets to hack my Twitter and tweet off my Twitter.
- I'll be posting in just a moment,
but if you guys enjoyed this video,
give a thumbs up right now,
and also comment down below how many of them
you got right,
or which ones you thought were obvious,
you got right off the bat.
Make sure you guys check out Sam's video,
who did a crazy Truth or Dare video on his channel,
so the link,
you can click his face.
Be sure to follow Sam on all the social medias.
Again, links are in all the description down below,
and without further ado,
boom, there's the tweet.
Oh, it's crazy.
And it's gone.
All right, guys, I will see you again next week.
Bye. (snapping fingers)