- And everything else that comes with the holidays.
Oh my god!
Santa almost died.
That was close.
(upbeat Jingle Bells tune)
What's up guys? It's Collins Key
and welcome to my new holiday video.
One of my favorite things about the holidays
is being able to spend so much time with my family.
So for today's video appearing right here
in front of our awesome Christmas tree
please welcome Devin Key.
- (ninja shouting)
- Hey, whoa, whoa. Ow!
Okay, you're done. Get out of my video.
Yeah, that was fun, okay.
- (ninja shouting)
- Okay, I'm taking this away from you.
Since this is the holidays,
I made my very own holiday challenge,
it's called the Human
Gift Wrapping
Challenge.
It's really fun,
but basically we're each gonna have a minute and half
to wrap each other like a gift.
This is so hard to do an intro on this.
(shattering sound)
- Turn it up,
oh,
yeey.
- (whipping sound)
- Let's get started with the challenge.
- (ninja shouting)
- For the challenge,
since Devin is the guest on my channel Key,
he'll have the honor and he can go first.
Three, two, go.
(speaking in fast forward)
(fast banjo music)
- No, no, no.
- What?
- I know what you're gonna...
Ah man!
(fast forward speaking)
Oh no!
- I think it's been a minute.
Since he's wrapped up and completely...
- Yeah, this is great, this is great.
Great fun, great fun, great fun.
- Completely defenseless,
one bow there, one there, one there, and one there.
- Help, Santa, immediately.
- (Ninja sounds)
- (Screams)
(fast banjo music)
The bonus challenge within the challenge,
how fast can I escape from the wrapping?
Yeah!
- While Devin is hitting him.
- Oh, dude, why?
Ow! This is actually not fun.
Ow.
Okay.
- (Ninja screams)
(wrapping paper crinkling)
- Yay.
- That was round one
of the Human Wrapping Challenge.
Now it's my turn to make him look like a human present.
Three, two, one, go.
- Can I resist at all?
- No, dude, you're supposed to help me.
(fast forward speaking)
(fast banjo music)
(tape pulling sound)
(fast forward speaking and yelling)
- Notice the nice corset right here
to really accentuate his tuckus.
His tuckus is nicely accentuated.
(fast banjo music)
- Woo! Yeah!
- No!
- Yo.
What the?
Ow.
Holy cow,
you're dangerous.
My corset of power is working.
- Ah!
- And (claps), ta-da!
All right, and that is the Human Gift Wrapping Challenge.
And if guys'd love to find Devin and I
underneath your Christmas tree
let us know by liking this video.
And also I want you guys to comment down below,
what was your favorite thing you got for Christmas?
And if this video made you laugh or smile,
be sure to share it with all of your friends.
Devin's social media links are all
in the description down below,
so you should go follow him.
Also don't forget, of course,
subscribe to this channel.
I'll see you guys again next week.
Peace.
(wrapping paper crinkling)
(upbeat Jingle Bells)
That part was so stupid. (laughs)
(wrapping paper crinkling)