(upbeat music)
- So are we like, sure this is the right place?
- I think so, 'cause like basically
everyone figured out that, in the first keyhole
you could see these different wrestling ropes.
And then from there, there was a
profile tag that brought them to
another profile, and then that one
was a whole bunch of different luchador masks.
And then from that profile there
was another hidden tag, and then
it brought them to this pic right here.
Basically, it's a lucha libre fight in Boyle Heights.
- It's okay, I'll protect you.
- Just in case anything happens, this
is my location, avenge my death!
- You'll be fine.
(laughs)
- That's a good one!
- It's after five Collins, boundaries, remember?
- No, I don't know, no I should.
- No, you shouldn't.
- No we should walk.
- Thank you.
Bye.
- Door number one, I think that's an Instagram account.
- It smells like pee.
- You guys, it's a video!
She's probably in here, come on!
- I don't think, okay dude.
- Come on she's probably in here, come on!
- Alright, Jacob, don't leave me, come on!
(cheering)
Is this what you had in mind?
(heavy metal music)
- [Mystery Girl] I used to fight with myself.
Do this, say that, be this person, not that one.
I was putting on a show, a spectacle.
Fighting to hide who I really was.
But, in a fight, someone has to lose.
And when you're fighting yourself, it's always gonna be you.
So I stopped fighting and started living.
You should too, come find me!
You're getting closer!
(groans)
(yells in foreign language)
- What is he saying?
- Light version, I don't think he likes you on your phone.
(shocked yelling)
- I'm sorry, wait, wait, wait, check this out!
(astonished gasps)
(loud cheering)
(upbeat pop music)
- Oh my god, let's leave!
- What happened?
- I just hit on a wrestler in front of his wife!
(laughs)
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
- If you guys need me, I will be in the bathroom,
drowning myself in the toilet, okay?
- [Carla] Okay.
- So, please, move!
- Should we go now?
- No, let's give him a minute.
- Alright.
In the meantime, may I have this dance?
- Dude.
Okay.
(soft upbeat music)
(beep)