- What's up guys?
It's Collins Key, and you're watching
- [All] Magic Monday!
- What's Glozell doing to me?
(Glozell laughing maniacally)
- Hey. - Magic.
- Ever since I posted the very first Magic Mondays,
a bajillion of you have been asking
if I can make stuff float and levitate.
So in fact, you know, what better time to do that
than at DIGIFest with all my YouTube friends
and freak 'em out.
If you guys recognize any of your favorite YouTubers
in this video, be sure to give it a huge thumbs up.
Enjoy.
- [Jay Z] You now rockin' with the best.
- You guys have a bill on you?
- Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yeah, I got it.
- All right.
- Yeah, got some dollar bills.
- Don't lose it.
Don't you dare do anything to that bill.
(Collins drowned out by music)
- This has to do with energy, all right?
You guys know about static electricity, right?
- Yes. - Yeah.
- Check it out, watch.
Have you guys heard of static electricity before?
- Yes. - No.
- He's stealing my money.
- It's all energy, check it out.
- [Man] What is this, static electricity?
- Yeah, static.
Take it, (mumbles)
you put some static electricity into the bill.
This is your bill, right?
- Yeah.
- Here you go, you just rub it on your pants like this.
You get static charge in the bill.
You rub your fingers here like to actually charge.
- Charges battery.
- Charges the bill, yeah.
Oh yeah, it's kind of like charging a battery.
- Put the static into the actual bill itself.
Rebecca, take it, just rub it
on your pant leg for a second.
- [Rebecca] Do it.
- All right, now pass it back.
Check it out.
- It's real, y'all.
- Watch me get the bill to actually
stick to my finger like this. - What?
- Look at this happen.
Like I think it has a flow,
but you actually have to stick to your finger like this.
Take this bill and watch this.
This is gonna be static electricity, you ready?
- Whoa.
- Sticks to my finger, right? - What?
- It's this pure energy right now, watch.
One, two, three.
(people screaming)
- [Woman] What the (bleep)!
This just becomes pure, raw energy on the count
of one, two, three.
- Whoa! - What the (bleep)!
(bleep)
But this is where it becomes magic,
just watch that bill.
We get the energy just right, this is pure energy,
watch, into the bill.
- Oh! - What the (bleep)!
- Oh, Jesus!
Oh, uh-uh.
Oh.
My nipples got hard.
(all laughing)
If you had fun watching those reactions,
please give this video a huge thumbs up.
And if you enjoy this video,
I've got great news because this video
is only part two.
There's a whole 'nother part one,
and if you guys wanna check out part one,
I'm gonna put the video link right on over here.
So be sure to go check out part one.
(imitates air whoosing) Now my face is in the video link.
(imitates air whooshing) And now it's back.
That was it for this week's Magic Monday.
If you guys enjoyed this video,
please give it a huge thumbs up.
Also, don't forget of course,
subscribe to this channel. (claps)
And if there's any YouTuber you want me
to do magic for, put their name in the comments down below.
Once again you guys, I am Collins Key.
Thank you so much for watching this week's Magic Mondays.
Peace.
(snaps)
(light upbeat music)
If you guys enjoyed the reactions in this video,
then you are going to love last week's video.
(Glozell screams)
See that? That's what I'm talking about.
If you wanna check out that video,
I'm gonna put the link right over here.
2013 has been absolutely crazy,
so I made a whole recap video about 2013
(imitates punch thudding)
right around over here,
so be sure you go check out that video.
Bye.
That's the crazy part, watch this.
Pure energy, watch, in one, two,
three. - Whoa!