- What's up, guys?
It's Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
For today's video, I'm showing you guys and teaching you
a brand new lifehack that I figured out
with a quarter and a bit of fire.
Now, if you're under the age of 18, don't try this.
I don't want you getting hurt.
If you're over the age of 18,
just be very careful you don't burn yourself.
That being said, let's jump into this awesome lifehack.
You're gonna take your coin,
and just heat it up just like this.
Just enough and you actually soften the metal of this coin.
So if you soften it enough, you can do this.
Watch, you can take it
(snap)
and actually bite off a piece of the quarter.
And that's not even the craziest part.
(blows)
When this coin gets cool enough, it turns into putty.
Watch.
(blows)
(chuckles)
The piece will reattach itself to the coin.
You guys can spend the money.
If you guys love this and you
want your friends to try it out,
share this video with them right now
and give the video a big thumbs-up.
If you want me to do even more crazy lifehacks like this,
comment down below.
What other random objects should I use
in these lifehack videos?
And make sure you guys are subscribed to this channel
because, if you didn't know, I've got new videos
coming out each and every single Thursday.
For right now, I'm gonna go eat some more quarters.
I'll see you guys again next week.
Bye.