- What's up guys it's Collins Key and for today's video
I'm actually gonna be showing and teaching you
an easy life hack with a dollar bill.
So all you have to do is grab a dollar bill
and follow along, just take your bill,
you're just gonna wanna fold it up just like this
and I guess the easiest way to describe it,
you're just gonna fold it into a little tiny packet.
And now all you have to do with this packet
is just take it and twist it,
and that activates the money hack.
So check this out, now when you unfold this bill,
it's gonna blow your mind.
Actually I figured this out a little while ago,
it's my favorite thing to do, it freaks people out.
Watch.
(snapping)
Done.
Looks kinda crazy right,
now let's make it even crazier, watch.
(snapping)
It's all it takes.
Just like that, I want you to look at this,
there's no tape, there's no glue or anything on this bill.
So if this video blew your mind,
make sure you share it with all of your friends
and give this video
a big thumbs up, if you guys want me to do even more
crazy life hack.
And also comment down below, what other random
object should I do life hacks with,
and make sure you guys are subscribed to this channel
because as you know, there's new videos coming out
each and every single Thursday, I'm Collins Key,
see you guys again soon, bye.
(snapping)