(typewriter keys clacking)
(bell chimes softly)
- What's up guys?
It's Collins Key.
What, you all laughing at me already?
Them hoodlums.
- Not at you, we're laughing with you.
- (laughs sarcastically) Really, though.
So I'm on my super trippy penny board,
and I just got here to the frickin' Queen Mary,
which I just found out this place is haunted,
and she, frickin' Maddie over here, troll maker.
- Sorry, I knew you weren't gonna come,
so I didn't tell you. - She didn't even tell me
this place is haunted.
She was like, "Yeah, it's like this cool ship hotel."
I was expecting like Suite Life On Deck 2.0 on this thing.
(girls talking over each other)
And apparently people die in the boiler room.
Yo, and I've already been dropped off.
My dad, he's long gone so I can't get back to him now.
This is terrible.
Please tell everyone at home.
Why would you do this to a brotha?
- Okay, okay.
- A brotha.
- I knew you weren't gonna come.
- Uh huh.
- Because you hate scary things.
- So I just didn't tell you.
I didn't lie, I just didn't mention the fact that
people have died. - People been dying in there.
I'm actually really uncomfortable with this whole thing.
WorldstarHipHop.
They're on this ledge thing and they're not supposed to be.
There's no one coming.
- [Maddie] Collins, scary.
- What? - Your penny board.
- Girl, if you die. - Give me your penny board.
- No, I'm sorry. - No, no, no.
- This is an intervention.
Girl, if you fall off that edge--
- I'm not gonna fall.
It's extremely wide--
- People die here!
- That's, very good point.
People do die here, so I'm not gonna
give you my penny board. - We're not on the boat yet,
so technically--
- [Collins] Girl, it don't matta.
You finna die.
- Give me the penny board, please.
- [Collins] No.
- Please.
- [Collins] That penny board will not be going to you.
- Someone's gonna come, you need to give it to--
- It don't matta.
Dude, okay, do you think it's gonna be any better
if you're scooting on a penny board across this.
(mumbles) says someone coming.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
- Ninja status.
- So that happened.
- What do you not understand about people die on this boat?
You're gonna be like this,
I'm scootin', I'm scootin',
I'm scootin', something goes down pootin',
I'm over to the side, and I'm like trippin',
and then it's like off the edge.
Off the edge.
What happened?
- I went-- - Yo Madison, straight up.
- If I could just go-- - You hit some oil.
- No, no.
I could just go straight--
- [Collins] This is a ship, they spout oil.
- And I would come back and I would be fine.
- A boiler spirit comes pushing you.
- I would be fine.
I am a perfect combination of stupid and brave.
- But you also told me you're clumsy,
which does not help your case at all.
Why would I give you a means of death?
That's what my penny board represents right there.
It actually kind of looks like a ghost too,
which is kind of weird.
Somehow, she convinced me to frickin' come inside
of this scary place. - Because you love me.
- [Collins] We ran into him.
He's cool. - I am worth
the possibility of ghosts. - Which floor I am on,
by the way?
- [Maddie] You're on my floor.
- I am?
- [Girl In Leopard Print] That's not the cool floor.
- (scoffs) Bro time.
I just got to my room.
My hat looks super swaggy right now.
My room's pretty dope.
Ow.
I keep hitting my head on the ceiling.
Ooh, what does this button do?
Oops.
(girls laughing)
Well, glad we figured that out now.
Did it take off my hat?
Okay.
These goats are tripping with me.
I mean these goat, ghosts.
Ghosts.
- [Maddie] It's three in the morning.
- If you can't tell, it's three in the, yeah,
it's three in the morning. - Nothing's making sense.
- It wasn't that bad, I don't even--
- Were you stuck in your backpack?
- (scoffs) Maybe.
(girls laughing)
Is that even a problem?
Hey guys, like this video if you've ever been stuck
in your backpack, yes, #ThirstyForLikes.
So there's this beautiful view of death.
(girls laughing)
There's probably been someone who lived in this room
and like, died.
- Why are you so obsessed with people dying?
- You're obsessed with your death, Collin.
- Because that's what this boat's all about.
That's its MO.
Look at this.
(electronic music)
This boat was obviously made before people were tall.
Fun fact, did you know that if you're over six foot, two,
you're taller than 94% of the population?
- So you? - That's me.
Watch out, I'm gonna be runnin'.
If you're runnin', get out of my way.
Shoot.
- Collin! - Why would you trip me?
I felt a leg.
- [Girls] No one tripped you.
- Ain't my leg. - Are you kidding me?
I kid you not, there was a leg.
- There was no leg. - There was no leg.
- Was this a motherfreakin' ghost?
- [Maddie] Now it gets Collins,
out of all the people that it could get.
- I made up something cool right now.
Watch this.
- [Maddie] No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- That has to be the coolest thing
I've ever done in my entire life.
I'm like a giant burrito right now.
- [Maddie] Like you're wearing a toga.
- I'm like a Chipotle burrito.
Burrito is going to bed.
Farewell.
- No, no, no. - No, no, no, you have a bed.
- [Girl In Leopard Print] Collins.
- [Maddie] Look at him, he's--
- [Girl In Leopard Print] He did compact himself
into that small group of space.
- [Collins] Now I'm like a frickin' ratchet casedilla.
- [Maddie] Collin.
(Maddie squeals)
(girls laughing)
- Chick, please.
I'm like a Chipotle superhero.
(laughs) So sexy.
Ow, my face.
What's under my bed?
Nothing under my bed.
He's so acrobatic. - [Maddie] Collins!
- I'm good, I'm good.
I think I have like polar bear disorder.
- [Maddie] Bipolar? - Yeah.
- [Maddie] Oh my God.
- Did I mess that up?
- [Girl In Leopard Print] Yeah.
It's the best thing that you've ever said.
- [Maddie] I think I have polar bear disorder.
- [Girl In Leopard Print] I have polar bear disorder.
- I don't like this bed anymore.
- [Maddie] Collins, there's another bed.
- That one's quite sexier.
This is my side bed.
My main bed.
I'ma chill with my side bed for a minute.
- [Girl In Leopard Print] Is this a metaphor for your life?
- [Maddie] Side chicks, main chicks?
- (laughs) I ain't got any chicks.
- Come on. - Who wants me to be a ninja?
- [Maddie] No, this is gonna end so bad.
- Pants, can't do that.
♫ Three, two, one, go
(electronic music)
- All right, so I found this piano
and I'ma try and play it right now.
(piano music)
- [Woman] Sir, you can't play the piano.
- [Collins] Oh, I can't play it? Okay.