- What's up guys it's Collins Key
and welcome to the third day vlog, now for today's video
I'm doing something a magician should never do.
And I've never done this before on my channel
but I know we've got Easter coming up this weekend
so in honor of the holiday weekend,
I'm actually gonna reveal to you guys a magic trick.
What, oh my gosh.
For this piece of magic you're gonna be using the high tech
piece of equipment that they call the silk handkerchief.
Yeah, you take the handkerchief and what you're gonna do
is put the handkerchief into your hand.
And now at this point you're probably thinking to yourself
wait a second what does this magic trick have to do
with Easter.
Well, check it out.
(snaps) Bam.
Just like that.
Egg, what?
I know you guys are probably freaking out right now.
No camera tricks.
Do you guys wanna know how this works?
Check this out.
Hollow egg.
Hit the thumbs up button if you guy's are kind of
blown away by this method.
So literally you stuff the handkerchief
inside the hollow.
Magicians, we like too much time on our hands,
we just make the hollow eggs all the time.
And for this I'm actually gonna teach you guys
step by step exactly what you need to do to perform this
for your friends, your family, and fool them on Easter.
So come on over here Devon.
- What's up guys? - Devon.
This guy's not a magician.
- Yeah, no, I'm not. - Just a regular.
- At all. - He's a Muggle.
Devon's a Muggle. - Yeah, I'm a Muggle.
- So take this, take the hollow egg.
- Okay.
- Take the handkerchief, I have one more hollow egg
right over here and I actually have one more handkerchief.
And I'm gonna take you guys step by step how to do this.
So first step take the egg and you're gonna palm it.
So put it in your hand just like this.
There we go, make sure everyone can see that, got it?
Palm it in your hand, take the handkerchief
give it a nice little flourish.
(laughs)
Just have a magician war with the handkerchieves.
And now you're gonna take this handkerchief
and you're gonna put it into the egg.
Now this is the great part of the magic
because everyone thinks you're just puttin'
this handkerchief into your hand,
when in reality it's going directly into that hollow egg
and you're about to blow their mind in just a second.
So make sure it's all the way in the egg,
nothing sticking out, make sure it's all the way in the egg.
Little magical gesture.
(snaps) Snap.
(snaps)
Then show the egg.
What?
- No way. Now at this point
people, they're gonna freak out,
they're gonna be like what just happened
to the handkerchief?
Why is it an egg?
And the last thing you want to do is turn the egg around,
that's revealing the magic right there.
Everyone's gonna know how it works then.
But unless you're a magician, cause if you're a magician.
I can just go like this (snaps).
And then you actually take that handkerchief
and just kind of.
- What?
Peel it off like a sticker, almost.
There we go.
And actually do you have that bowl for me Devon.
- Yeah.
And this is where you really freak 'em out
cause they think the handkerchief is still inside the egg.
But you go no, check this out.
We take the egg.
- No. - What?
(laughs)
That's a little bit of easy magic for you guys.
- That's crazy.
- No way.
- What? - Oh snap.
Oh, no he didn't.
- Swerve.
- If you guys enjoyed this reveal video
give it a big ole thumbs up
and also share this video with all of your friends.
Comment down below.
What is your favorite Easter candy, bro?
Snapchats and all that stuff is in the subscription
down below so you can just go add the both of us.
- Bye. (snapping)