(upbeat music)
(laughs)
- I'm Leonie.
- I'm Collins.
- I thought you'd given up.
- Yeah, after the art show, I thought
you were messing with me, or maybe this
was some giant, elaborate, prank or something.
(laughs)
- That's not it.
Actually, I can't believe that I pulled it off!
That you're here, it's crazy!
I wanted to give you something.
- What?
- An adventure!
(uplifting music)
I used to be like you, but I was
always so determined not to be normal.
Not to fit in.
I spent half my life chasing this, like,
need to keep trying new things.
To collect experiences!
I spent a year in Rome studying architecture.
Worked as a sous-chef on food truck.
Modeled in New York, and of course magic.
Which is how I found you!
But art, photography, that's what stuck.
It made me realize the only thing
you have, is the moment you're in right now.
A picture isn't real, it's what's
left over from something real that happened.
And people see what they want
when they look at it, it's an illusion.
Just like magic.
- You know, for me, magic is real.
Because, growing up I was always a bit of a loner.
Magic was that one thing that I could do.
And I could connect with these people,
and it was like it was just me and them.
And there was nothing else in the entire world mattered.
I was able to make people feel something.
- The first time I saw you do
magic on TV, you were so honest.
And you cried.
No, no, it was amazing!
I don't think I've ever seen someone
want something so badly.
I'd always imagine.
- What?
- What it would be like to be that
one thing that you want so badly.
- Why now?
- Because I'm leaving LA.
- Wait, what?
- I left you all of those messages,
so you could know me, even just
a little bit, before I asked you.
- Before you asked me what?
- To come with me!
This week is just the beginning of our adventure!
We can go anywhere, do whatever we
want, and just see what happens!
- I can't.
- Collins, this is what I've been trying
to tell you, you can do whatever you want!
- No I can't just leave it all behind!
- Yes, you can, because none of that matters!
The only thing that matters is right here, right now!
- Yeah, but that does matter!
It's my life, magic, my fans, my friends, Jacob and...
(soft music)
- Oh.
- I just, I.
I should probably get going.
- Yeah, get back to your life, I get it.
- What about you, where are you gonna go?
- Oh, probably some other city,
to leave clues for some other guy.
(laughing)
I'm just kidding, I don't know.
I'm not sure yet, but I like it that way.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(ringing)
(laughs)
- There he is!
- Yeah, hey Martin.
- My star clown, my magical clown!
I was just at the studio man, they love it man!
They cannot get enough of you!
- [Collins] I don't want to do the show.
- Wait, what you talking?
- It's just not what I want.
- What do you mean it's not what you want?
You don't know what you want, you're like 12.
- [Martin] Hello?
Are you serious?
No!
(grunts)
- Hey, Jacob!
(uplifting music)