- Squishy!
- Oh my gosh! - Ooh, what!
- When you challenge us to mold squishy foods into candies
and right now we're kicking it off
with the bags of mystery.
Oh my gosh!
Devin choose your mystery squishy.
- I'll take this one.
- Okay, what did you get?
- Whoa, I got popcorn.
- You can't use paper, that's not edible Devin.
- Yeah, this is edible paper, bro.
- Whoa!
Oh my gosh!
- That's really not.
- Ahh.
- It's actually kinda sharp.
- It hurts my lip!
- That's a lot of Airheads.
Lick it and stick it!
- I'm gonna make my entire popcorn container
out of edible paper.
- Dude, this is gonna be so tough.
How do you do this?
- Oops!
- Oh, no!
What are you doing?
(laughing)
You missed the marks so much.
- (coughs) Dude, they're so dry.
The reason I'm doing this is because
these are my binding ingredients.
Oh man.
Ooh that's not good, bro.
Stop!
- Get off my finger, you're not welcome here!
Shmellos!
- These things are like hard to deal with, bro.
I'm like having to smoosh these together
but they're some coating on them so they don't want to.
So they're just sliding around like that.
- You, you almost hit my shmello line.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh yeah!
So now the moment of truth.
I gotta kind of roll this over and then attach the line.
Bam!
Hand inside, shmoosh!
The shmellos!
Squeesh!
Oh yeah, boy!
Haha!
Dude, I'm so excited, it really worked.
- Did it actually work?
- Yes!
- Wow.
- Alright, so, I'm gonna use a Kit Kats as the bottom
of my shmello thing.
I'm gonna place it like that.
Ooh, ooh.
- There is no popcorn container
that is that long and that tall.
- That's why I have scissors!
- Oh man, oh man, oh,
this better not ruin my entire operation.
(screeches)
Oh, yes, yes!
Lots of yeses.
(claps)
- I have the brilliant idea of wrapping this.
Nope.
- Here is where I turn into Devin the artist
because I have to now color in my paper
to make it look red.
- Nice!
- Hahaha!
Sweet!
The lines are getting progressively worse and worse
as I keep going.
- Ahh!
- My thumbs have never gotten a better work out in my life.
- Bam, there we go.
It's a little raggedy but you get the point.
I'm on to the final step.
So it starts off with marshmallows
to kind of like seal it in place.
- Ooh! bro, the cup's almost done.
- Yeah, it's gonna taste so good.
And finally, the yellow Skittles to add
as the buttered popcorn.
Yo, my marshmallows, they may not work.
They may not stay.
- It's busting at the seams!
- Okay, quickly, quickly, quickly.
Ahh!
- No!
(claps)
Yes!
I think I'm gonna win this.
- I thought I had it too it was so close
and then it just.
(dog howls)
- That did not hold at all.
- Well, it, uh, ah.
- Alright it's time.
Bro, what are you doing?
- Well, I'm just helping.
I love marshmallows, I just want to help!
- This is my moment.
- I think you're gonna want to put some of these in there.
- Really, dude?
I know how to do this.
- Now we get to eat these and see how they taste.
Man, this has got paper and marker on it.
So we'll see and you guys comment down below
who won this round.
But, here we go.
Are you ready, Devin?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
(candy clattering)
- Aww.
- Ahh (inaudible).
- Whoa!
(claps)
It's so good.
- This is good, too.
- It's stuck to my teeth though.
- Alright guys, we're on to the next round.
Woo woo.
This is so good man.
- Wha!
- Alright Collins, your turn to pick the squishy.
- A very special technique.
It's called the claw.
One, two.
This one.
And this is how you open it.
Ooh!
My gosh!
Well, it's back!
Ice cream!
Dude! - Bro!
- Squishy ice cream!
Before this guys we actually got some giant
Rice Krispy Treats for the cone.
Right now,
here we, ow!
Watch, we go one, two, three.
(screaming)
- My ear hurts really bad.
- Sorry, bro.
Yeet!
And now, I need to slice and dice
because I gotta create myself.
Woo!
If you didn't know, I get startled and scared really easy
and that's why I do not watch scary movies, ever.
- Oh cool, we got the pink here
and I gotta mold it into a circle.
Alright, first scoop done.
Looking pretty good, right?
- Oh my gosh, this is very difficult.
I think I need more Krispy Treat.
Instead of a cone I have created a ball.
- Okay.
Ah, it's so fluffy.
Mmm.
- Is it good?
- Oh, bro.
- Dude, this stuff feels nice.
So I'm gonna try, to like, put this here.
I think I've ruined the fluffiness of it.
I didn't know you could ruin the fluffiness.
I ruined the fluffiness of it.
Dude, pop this on top like that.
- You know what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna lick my finger
and then, hopefully, it'll stick it to the other one
'cause right now it just, it falls off.
- My finger tastes really good.
- Alright, it's done.
Wait, what's the purpose of that?
Sprinkles!
It's like a cupcake, not ice cream, bro.
- Mine has a little bit of hair on it, dude.
Look at that.
It's like a little, woo!
- So we're gonna be eating these at the end of the video.
So comment down below who won this round.
The next one we're gonna make is gonna be crazy Devin.
- Yeah?
- Select a bag!
- Alright it is a.
whoa!
It's a watermelon, bro!
- Step one we gotta heat up this pot with some water.
As the water's boiling,
right now it's time to chop this watermelon in half.
(knife slices)
- Ooh!
Snap, that actually worked!
We're gonna do a little race.
Whoever carves it out first wins.
(high speed audio)
(cheerful piano music)
I think we're good.
That's it, that's done.
What I don't understand is how I cleared out
so much more watermelon than you did.
The next step is where this whole thing starts to get cool
but first, we gotta finish the clear out, I guess.
(slurps)
Oh my gosh.
That is so good.
Okay, time to add in the water right now, Devin.
- I got my makeshift mitts.
I gotta be very careful.
Make sure no steam.
- Oh my gosh, you splashed it, Devin!
- I'm doing the best I can, bro.
Is that enough?
- You want to do all of it, Devin.
And right over here, guys,
we've got the gelatin.
So, this is what's gonna turn it into the gel.
So, I'm only gonna add a little bit at a time.
Probably way too much.
If I've learned one thing,
it's that I have terrible Jell-O control.
- Jell-O control.
- Oh, gosh, this smells terrible.
Oh, man!
- And the thing is, we don't want any watermelon.
- No.
- So Devin, you're actually gonna pulverize that
and we're gonna add that to the Jell-O
coming up here in a little bit.
So first, oh!
Way too much!
Way way way too much!
And now we continue to mix.
- [Spongebob Narrator]
- I like my job.
This is fun.
- Aright, here we go, the final amount.
Boom!
- Whoa!
Isn't that way too much at one time?
- Devin, I am a master mixer!
- So, weren't you the one to just say
that you have terrible Jell-O control?
(swoosh)
- Believe what you want
Alright, now it is time to add the watermelon flavor.
- Now we gotta break down all the pieces of watermelon.
(magic chimes) Now we got it all
melted down we gotta add back here.
- It's all you, bro, all you.
- Three.
- Better not spill it on me.
Two, I know, one!
- Oh! no, no, no, no!
(slow motion yelling)
Hot!
- I'm so sorry bro!
(beep)
Well, let's just say that did not go according to plan.
- No. - But now,
we got the watermelon in here.
Go for it.
Go for it. - I'm doing it.
I'm going for it, Collins.
- Yo, that thing is really cool.
Next step we gotta pop this thing in the fridge.
We have to wait a little bit.
Right now, let's make it cold.
(magic chimes) - Yo!
That is so good.
- It's watermelon flavored Jell-O, too.
- Alright, here's how the slice works.
You ready? (claps)
(knife slices) Yo, that actually worked!
Holy cow this looks amazing!
- I can't wait to eat this.
- Dude, this is gonna be the most delicious thing
of all time!
Okay, you ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
Wait, first, five second subscribe challenge!
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Alright, ya ready?
Here we go.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done!
- If you can do that, comment down below,
keeper squad, right now.
Let's see how this thing tastes.
Ya ready? - Yeah, I'm ready.
- Cheers! - Alright.
(gushing)
- Whoa!
Dude, next one.
Let's go. - Alright Collins,
your turn to pick your squishy.
- I'm going to do the claw again.
- Aw no.
- Three, two, one.
Ah, the claw is broken.
- Yeah, it must be.
Yeah!
- Okay, let's see what we're gonna do.
- Oh, it's a cactus.
- I was like, what is that?
- It is adorable.
- It's so squishy.
Well guys, this is gonna be a candy, spineless porcupine.
(buzzer)
Cactus.
- I'm sorry, wrong spikey thing.
- Let's go, we're gonna use these.
- You don't need to do it more than once.
(whoosh)
(laughter)
Alright guys, so here we go.
Alright. - Whoa, what are you doing?
- I can't hear you man,
I'm blocking out the haters.
Ow! There's a really weird echo in your ears man.
It like magnifies the sound.
Yo, I remember these!
Dude, they are super sour.
I do not like these.
Listen to this. (clacking)
- You're gonna break the table, bro.
- Shatter a tooth.
Alright so this, the first thing.
Let's see if it'll even fit.
(clack)
- Well, not when you do it like that!
- It's just. (clacking)
- Bro. (clack)
Alright, this is how you do it, Collins.
Gently, and then press.
- Ooh no! (glass shattering)
- I think it broke!
- It literally burst in half.
- So basically you crumble these up
and put them into the cup.
- Or you're cool and have a legit actual little rocks
you can pour into this.
Alright, now we gotta Laffy Taffy.
You gotta make a pink little bow
that looks just like a spiral.
- Or just a mush.
- Ta-da!
It looks like a hat.
What did you do?
- It's like a cowboy hat, perfect.
It's got the googly eyes.
- Alright, I have completed the pebble stage of my journey
and I'm gonna take these macaroons
and kinda stick 'em together.
Aww, I feel like it's gonna fall apart any second.
Alright, got two eyes on there.
It's looking good.
How is it looking?
I realize. (gasping)
- And you mess it up like that - No, my masterpiece.
- Well, I think that I totally won this round.
Like completely.
- Well, yeah, 'cause yours was the only option,
not because it's far superior.
- I don't actually want to eat my cactus because
it is sour and I do not like sour things.
So you get to comment down below who won this round and
we're on to the next one.
(swoosh) So Devin choose
your next mystery squishy cause
we're coming down to the finale.
- This one, it is this!
(bell ring) - Dude, Narwhals
they're, wait, they're what?
- Narwhals.
They're so cute.
- You don't know what a narwhal is?
- I have no idea what a narwhal is.
- Dude and they're so squishy, oh my gosh.
So right now, Devin, the competition heats up.
(squeak)
And time to make an edible narwhal out of candy.
So here we go,
I'm gonna use these blue marshmallows to construct.
- Oh, there's cake here.
Oh no, this is gonna be so messy.
Oh!
- Why are you using?
- Oh, this does not feel good.
That is a terrible idea.
This is bringing back memories from the cupcake.
Challenge. - I know.
Yo, we should do another one of those.
- This doesn't work at all.
Bro, like, what is going on.
- Yo, my narwhals look more like a car right now
than an actual narwhal, but you'll see
how it turns out, this is really good.
- Alright, this may not look like anything
at the moment but trust me.
- That looks like literally nothing to me right now, Devin.
It looks like failure. (claps)
- Alright, time to grab this cotton candy
and I gotta smoosh it.
- That's actually really smart.
- Thank you. - But I still think
I'm gonna win this round due
to my pure engineering ingenuity.
Boom, another narwhal eye, and then you just
gotta add, ya know, a big happy grin.
Uh oh, it like lost its grin.
It's like yeah, grunt.
One part of the mouth just dropped.
Oh, oh, oh, and I almost forgot
the most important part of any narwhal, its horn!
Wait, look at that.
Don't tell me it's disproportionate.
There is my narwhal's horn.
Ya know what?
It needs a final touch to it.
Probably not gonna stay up.
Worked for a second.
- Alright, well, there is it's two eyes.
- It looks like Jabba the Hutt.
- It kinda does (laughs), ooh!
- I want to improve your narwhal.
- You better not mess this up.
Are those eyebrows?
- You have a banana brow.
(laughing) (clapping)
- That's hilarious, nicely done, bro, nicely done.
- I shouldn't, I'm not gonna high five that hand. (laughs)
It's got no mouth, it's like, I'm a narwhal!
- I was just noticing how small the mouth is on here, so.
- Mine's the opposite.
Mine's like mwah!
- And done. (ping)
- I gotta be careful when I eat this one
because there's a lot of toothpicks in it
so you get to comment on it down below, right now,
which narwhal won, and we are on to the finale
and it all comes down to this.
- Alright Collins.
- Here's one.
Okay, great, let's see what we got.
Okay.
A bread!
(buzzer) A sandwich.
So this seems like the sweetest sandwich of all times
but first I gotta squish it and then, yeet!
Ow! (goofy howl) (thud)
Ow, there we go.
Snapped it in half.
It's like a butterfly, like, woo.
So I guess I don't know how we're gonna do this.
I'm gonna make a design, what are you doing?
- I'm making it square!
- Alright we'll get the jelly on there.
Uh oh, this thing is gonna leak off of the side.
- Oh, you're not in time now.
Our table is gonna be stained.
- Peanut butter or should we say caramel on the other side.
Yeah, it doesn't look nearly as thick as peanut butter does.
- So, I guess, ya know, we just get to put blueberries.
- What?
- On there, these are blueberries.
- Ah, okay.
- Nothing like having the earthy taste of some gravel.
- Who wants that?
- Put some narwhals horns.
This sandwich would be amazing to eat,
cause it's literally just straight candy.
- It looks like it would be really difficult and crunchy
and you got all these pokey things.
- Dude, stop hating on me.
Woo, Oh yeah man!
Make a banana sandwich.
- Ooh! - This smells like a banana.
A healthy banana on your sandwich.
Yo, we got tiny little bananas.
- Bro - I'm gonna border them, boom,
around the edges.
- Ooh, gonna use some of these, too, bro.
Oh yeah!
- Nice!
- It's like a spaghetti sandwich.
- Spaghet!
- Alright, next up, I'm gonna add some of these bananas.
Gotta shake them up.
- You don't shake the bananas.
- Yes, you do!
- Ooh, that actually looks really satisfying.
- That looks really cool.
And next I'm gonna add some of these graham crackers.
It is time to put the top on my sandwich.
- But before we do that,
we gotta eat all the other squishy candies that we made
and then we're gonna be eating this sandwich
so comment down below on who won,
but right now let's eat some candy.
So this one right here we got our ice cream.
In my case it's like a bowl with a birds nest
with some eggs.
- Oh I see it, I see it.
- Yup, so here we go. (laughing)
- Nice, I'm not even gonna help you, just let you flounder.
How's the combo?
- Weird.
I think if you don't like weird flavor
'cause they don't taste that good.
It's like the Bean Boozled challenge like man whoo!
- I'm going for mine.
- Oh yeah. - Oh, tastes fabulous.
- Holy cow!
- Wooh, this combo.
- Is it good?
- Mmm.
Bro, this is good.
(laughs)
- So how we're gonna do this, Devin,
I do not wanna have to eat the sour ones.
Gonna do rock paper scissors. - I don't either.
Best out of three has to eat this.
- [Both] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
- Nah! (buzzer)
- [Both] Rock paper scissors, shoot.
(buzzer) - Yeah!
(yelling)
- Three, two, one.
- You can't just eat the Laffy Taffy, no no no!
- Oh, so bad!
(tone)
Ugh!
- Dude, your tongue is getting, like, green.
- Ugh!
- Oh my gosh.
- Yeah, it's pretty sour.
- And can't forget, of course, the rocks.
- I'll take it.
- And now it's time to eat the narwhal.
So I'm gonna eat mine first,
hopefully I don't get a toothpick to the top of the mouth.
(laughs) Got a little bit.
Tastes exactly the way I thought it would taste.
(laughs)
And I guess now I'm just gonna have to pick up
my whole narwhal, except for the bottom half of it.
I do not know. - Wait.
That was, like, his mouth.
He was like nom, nom, nom.
- Yo, yo, we should feed my narwhal.
(shouting)
- He's like a cookie monster narwhal!
I'm so nervous for you.
I don't, what are you doing?
Dude, you're supposed to eat this?
(chuckles)
Dude, careful. - Thank you.
- So I don't even know how I'm gonna pick this up, dude.
I'm gonna scoop it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, the face
is just splitting in, (shouting) oh no!
I'm so sorry.
Oh, alright, here we go!
- Yo! - Oh, (moans) oh.
- You even got cotton candy on there!
Alright, so time to eat these sandwiches!
Let's see if I can get this up.
- It's like a taco, bro.
- Oh, snap, how do I get this up?
- I got it! - Dude!
- Yo. - Bra.
- Oh no!
- Alright, you ready for the bite?
- I'm so ready, dude!
- This is crazy!
- Look at this!
- Three, two, one, go!
All I got was Rice Krispy.
What? - Oh, it's so good!
- Click on subscribe right now!
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one.
- Alright, we love you guys, bye!