- [Collin] We've got real food versus slime food.
(both men shout) Whoa!
- You challenged us to turn real food into slime food.
So right now, we're kicking it off
obviously with cereal.
- Yup, I think I spilled just a little bit.
(both men shout) Glue!
- Ew!
- You just got it everywhere.
- Yo, I think I messed up
I added so much Sta-Flow at once.
- (disgusted sound)
- (shouts) Ah, I just blasted it all over the table!
- (alien music) Mine looks like an alien mucus
(fake sneeze) and then there's this.
- Eww.
Well, I'm gonna add some into yours.
- (shouts) No!
Get your Sta-Flow out my bowl.
(shouts) Oh, dude this is crazy!
- I know, it is really weird.
- (crazy scream)
(blubbering sound)
Whee! (laughs)
Just in case it wasn't obvious
this right here is going to be the milk.
I totally meant to do that.
- My arms are hurting.
- Oh, yeah.
Slime is a Gucci good time.
(rope sound)
Oh yeah, mines perfect.
Dude, it's not even sticking to my hand anymore.
- Really?
- I can go, whee!
That didn't happen.
- Wait, we're connected.
- (shouts) No, get off me!
Stop it!
Why is yours dripping all over me!?
You got it all over the chair!
Bro, are you kidding me!?
- How did I end up with your slime?
- Are you kidding me!?
What is wrong with your slime?
Where did my slime go, what the heck?
Bro, this is game over.
We haven't even made the milk yet.
- My arms are so tired
I have double slime.
- We're gonna take a quick break right now.
Come back, because we gotta clean up, man.
What the heck happened?
This is what happens when you don't make slime for months
you lose your ability, and you ruin everything.
I've got new pants.
We've ruined the chairs.
But right now, we're gonna persevere.
Is it good to go?
- Yeah, it's good to go.
We added some Sta-flow.
- We're gonna split it in half.
- Wait, bro (tearing noise)
- Okay, here we go.
Put it into the bowl, Devin.
- Next up, we add these balls, and these smaller balls.
- Dude, I'm totally gonna win this round
because there's no way you can compete with me on this.
- And, done.
- No you're not.
- Yeah, I'm done
- Oh, all right, cool.
See guys, sometimes the greatness takes a little bit longer
than just mediocre averagness.
- Mediocre averageness?
What are you talking about?
This is a perfect replica, of this.
- Dude, it's actually turning into crunchy slime.
(slapping sound) (laughs)
- Dude, I don't recommend that at all, but go for it.
- It's going inside.
That's enough, I'm gonna break it off there.
Get off my hand.
I'm just gonna squish it around in there.
Oh man, that perfect.
And then, now to get it out
you just tear the bag open like this.
It's pretty genius.
- Thanks. (sinister laugh)
Now it's time to add my milk with infused cereal
so we're gonna swirl it around.
Bad idea, we're just gonna (slapping sound)
All right, now for the main ingredient.
I got a technique for this
it's called, the light shake and shimmy.
I'm gonna squeeze it.
- It looks fine.
- Oh yeah, this is gonna be legit
because now my cereal is going to be unlike your cereal.
You gotta admit bro, this stuff is pretty awesome.
Look at that!
Whoo!
Yo, that looks crazy.
Now you gotta give it the one final technique
I call it, the once around the club.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(rope sound)
- There we go.
See, it's like a fashion statement on my arm.
It's called, the drop and plop.
- [Devin] Intercept.
(sad music)
- I'm sorry man, I just wanted to play with this.
Crunchy slime is so awesome.
Whoa bro, what are you doing?
No, get your fingers out of there.
- I think it's time to call it quits.
I've done just about all I can do with it.
(tada sound)
Now it's time to add the spoon.
You get to comment down below
and let us know who won, round one.
Was it my beautiful cereal, with all the infused goodness
or was it Devin's?
- That looks so awesome.
- Now we have the bowl of slime.
So what we're gonna do Devin, is add a little bit of yours.
- A little bit of it?
- Yep.
(crashing sound)
- Whoa, bro!
What are you doing?
- I gotta sever it with my spoon.
- Bro, why?
- Here's what's gonna happen
we're gonna add a little bit of the real food as well.
- Wait, why?
Bro, that's so gross!
- Because, at the end of this
we're gonna mix together, all the different slimes
all the different foods
and then we're gonna have to eat it
and see what it tastes like.
- Eat it?
- For this round
you challenges us to make a Starbucks frappuccino
out of slime.
(struggling sound) Oh man
my hands are not strong enough for this.
(screams)
- Well, leave some for me bro.
- Then, we got contact solution
because that's how you make the clear slime
if you guys don't remember.
This is gonna act as the strawberry base
to the whole thing.
I'm starting to get a little slime.
(laughs) That would be a funny name for a rapper, Lil slime.
Oh yeah, we're starting to get there.
I need more contact solution.
(screams) It stuck to my arm!
- Why would you do that?
- I'm dripping it!
- No, no, no!
- Now what we're gonna do
is we're gonna add some food coloring into the game
because if it isn't working now
it surely isn't going to work when we add food coloring.
I'll add some to yours.
- (disgusted sounds) It's all over me.
- We're just gonna mix it around.
- That turned real crimson, real quick.
That actually looks-
Whoo, this looks legit
like raspberry or strawberry marmalade.
We got that, now it's time to make my regular slime.
We got some glue.
Now, I'm gonna add the Sta-Flo.
I forgot rule number one.
You're not supposed to add the Sta-Flo too quickly.
Whoopsie.
- All right, this is going great!
- Look how much Sta-Flo I added.
It's a Sta-Flo soup.
- This is still not looking like it's gonna cut it
so I'm gonna make this, some fluffy slime.
- That's so smart.
I need this to look fluffy and nice and frappuccinie.
Instead, it looks like a giant booger.
- Shaving cream.
It's a cloud.
My favorite slime.
- Dude, listen to the sound of this.
It's no longer all stringy and gross.
I've done the impossible.
I've made a full recovery
and I'm doing just dandy.
Now I'm gonna add some acrylic paint.
So first, you gotta karate chop it, to get it open.
- (screams) Bro!
So fluffy!
- That looks so good!
- Wait, how did you get a new bowl?
- (laughs) Magic.
- You smack the slime?
- Yeah, smack it three times.
(magic sound)
(both men scream)
- Now we're gonna dump some of my acrylic paint in here.
Dude, this acrylic paint looks insane.
Oh dude, it got on my fingers!
(sniffing sound)
(disgusted sound)
Holy cow, this stuff smells disgusting.
- [Devin] But, it looks like candy.
- Yeah. (coughing)
- [Devin] This is so cool.
- What happened to my beautiful slime?
My hands are ruined.
Dude, it's ruined my slime.
I think it deconstructed my slime.
- All right, first layer is done.
Next up, adding the fluffy slime.
- (laughs) I just smacked my face.
- I'm overflowing, no!
- This is my moment.
- Whoa, that looks so cool!
- Look at this!
- Ew.
- Too much slime, I gotta cut it off.
(struggling sound)
- I'm gonna do it like this, my final layer.
- I gotta go wash my hands because they're literally pink
and it will contaminate the rest of my drink.
See, if I touch it like that-
- No, no, no!
Dude, why?
- It turns pink, so I gotta go wash my hands.
- It was perfect!
- I actually have a little bit of a different technique
for blasting my whip cream onto my drink, you ready?
Three
two
- No, no, no!
- Wait, first we have a five second subscribe challenge
for you right now.
Can you subscribe to this channel
and turn on the post notifications, in five seconds.
Here we go, you ready?
Five
four
three
two
one
done.
If you could do that
comment down below, Keyper Squad, right now.
Here we go.
Three, two, one!
- Really, that was it?
Whoa, bro!
Chill!
Dude, you're getting it everywhere, it's too much!
- Done, boom!
It's on top!
Whoo, that's fantastic.
Dude, it's like a little dragon.
(dragon sound)
All right, you gotta pop the top.
- Pop the what?
- Pop the top.
It's a goner.
- (laughs)
Really, dude?
- Got it back.
All right, here we go.
Crunch it.
(plopping sound)
- [Devin] I love the sound effects, to be honest.
- Pop the top.
Oh dude, look at that.
This is now my finished product.
I gotta go around the edges, scoop it all up.
Here we go, top it off.
- [Devin] (screams) Whoa!
(slow motion sound)
- I mean, is that not awesome?
Oh my gosh, I've automatically won this round.
You can just comment down below right now
Collin's won the round.
(sinister laugh) I know.
I want to do that again.
That was so much fun.
(high pitch sound)
That's so cool!
Do not vote on what it looks like currently.
You're only voting on the very cool action
of the whipped cream popping out the top
that's all you're able to vote on, with my drink.
- I'm trying not to have the same thing happen to me
that happened to you.
(popping sound)
(both men laugh)
- [Devin] The finishing touch, the straw.
Perfect.
- Off with the top, and in with the hand
and that's how you drink a frappuccino.
Now we're gonna add it to the bowl of slime and food.
So, we added mine in there.
Lets just add the whole cup in there.
And again, at the end
we're going to be eating a combination of slime and food
so stick around for that.
Right now, we are on to the next round.
Egg smashing contest in three, two, one.
(screams) Wait dude, no way bro!
I was totally joking about that.
You guys challenged us to make a slime egg.
First up, we gotta crack our egg.
So, we're recreating this.
Whoever finished their slime first, wins.
This is not about good or bad.
Begin!
(fast forward sound)
It's pretty bubbly, bro.
I don't know what happened.
This is looking pretty-
- You good?
- No.
It looks like a clear liquid glass.
It might not be perfect
but we're going for the fastest round of all time.
Remember Devin, it's all about who makes it first.
Get off my hands!
Boom!
There's two ways to make the yolk.
You can either use the clay
or you can legit, take the yolk from the actual egg.
This is for the winning move.
(suspenseful music)
(plopping noise)
(screams) Yeah!
There you have it Devin, an egg of slime
or a slime of egg.
An egg slime.
All right, so I won this round
but you guys can still comment down below
who you think won.
But, I took home the victory.
You could put a couple egg shells by them
like I just cracked it open.
We gotta take the big ole thing of slime
I'm gonna pop an egg shell in there
and then I'm gonna mix up the yolk
into my slime, to see what happens.
- No.
- Wait, first we got a three second, like challenge.
Can you like this video, in three seconds?
Here we go, you ready?
Three
two
one
done.
- [Devin] That is so gross.
- That looks crazy.
This is now, literally slime mixed with food.
Look at that.
- I feel queasy.
- That's pretty gross.
After this next round
we're gonna be mixing all of this up
and literally eating it.
Don't do it at home.
We're doing it, so you don't have to.
(screams) Pie face challenge!
- (screams) No!
You can't play with my heart like that.
- (laughs) Okay, for this final round
we are making a slime pie.
We're definitely gonna need a lot, a lot of slime
to be able to build the entire pie crust.
Let me leave that there for right now.
Gotta unscrew the top.
(shouts) Yey!
There's always gotta be one in the video.
- Yeah, it took you a long time, I'm really surprised.
- I know, people were probably waiting for it
like, "when's it gonna happen?".
We're gonna add a little bit in.
- Nice, that looks like a lot, too much.
Bro, are you trying to ruin it on purpose?
- No, you just have to evenly proportion it, man.
(overly accentuates) proportion.
- (makes a pronounced P sound)
- What are we, amateur beatboxers?
(makes a beatbox sound)
- I think you're spitting all over everything right now.
- This reminds me of the liquid water bottle
but one that you can not eat.
This is not edible at all.
- I think my slime is officially ruined.
Oh, why?
- It's very thick and resilient.
(stretching sound)
(snapping sound)
- I can't tell if this is a blueberry pie
or a raspberry pie.
I have a great idea, Devin.
I'm gonna put this in the middle, and then close it in here
and see if I can break it.
- No!
- Holy cow, how did that happen?
I legit, did it.
- Okay, okay.
No, it's on my thumb.
- It's like little injections of color.
Whoa, that's super neat.
- It's like a mushroom.
- Some part is super dense purple
and then other parts haven't purpleized at all.
- Purpleized.
- I like that word.
- Oh no, I got it on my pinky!
Mayday, mayday!
No, it's all over my hands!
Gotta go for it.
(screams) Oh, no!
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Oh, no!
It burst on my hands!
Well, there you have-
(screams) This is never gonna come out!
(high pitched screams) I'm gonna go for a second
I gotta go wash my hands, bye.
- Bro, this is looking so cool!
- It looks almost like a galaxy.
I'm gonna use a spoon, so I don't ruin my hands again.
It looks kind of lumpy, chunky and funky, man.
- You take a bunch of this stuff
and you cut little strips of it
and then you lay it over, in this pattern.
So, you make it look like that.
- Dude, you do not use a knife in your hand.
I can't believe I'm the one telling you this
but you do not cut something when it's in your hand.
- Sorry.
- I'm just rolling this thing out, real nice.
Lets get saucy, up in this place.
The first strip.
Oh, it broke!
Dude, that's a metal knife of glass.
(metal scraping glass sound)
I can literally hear that scratching the table, Devin.
There, you have my pie.
It's like a little cobra coming out the top of it.
Well, I'm done.
I've just begun.
As with everything, let the time lapse begin.
(old timey music)
Here it is, the big reveal.
This was suggested by the Instagram Keyper of the week
so shout out to you.
And if you want to be shouted out
as the Instagram Keyper of the week
check the description down below, to find out how.
Right now, the big reveal, you ready?
Three, two, one.
Tada!
Bro, this turned out so good!
You guys get to comment down below, for this final round
who won.
Now it's time to add this to
the ultimate slime food versus real food
and then eat it.
Right now, lets see how they taste.
(both men shout) whoa!
- That's crazy!
Now, lets try it with this.
- What?
- (screams)
- No, what!?
- I shouldn't have done that.
- No.
- Pie in.
- Now we're gonna mix it all up.
(both men shout) Whoa!
- What happened to the Starbucks?
We gotta get that cup out of there.
- Oh, that's so gross.
- This is the craziest combination of stuff, ever!
- Whoo, it smells.
- I smell the Starbucks, and that actually smells delicious.
- It actually kind of looks cool, but it's kind of gross.
- It's all super cold, because the Starbucks was cold.
There's an egg in here too, I forgot about that.
Comment down below.
What are some other real foods
we should make slime versions of.
And comment down below, of course
who won the challenge, overall.
Here we go, time to eat it!
- (shouts) Whoa, whoa, bro, bro, bro, I have to say
I'm smelling this paint and it's really gross
and this is actual slime and glue, and Sta-Flo.
I'm pretty sure this is not good for you, dude.
I don't think we should eat this.
- You know what, you're probably right.
You guys should not eat slime
and I guess I shouldn't either.
I forgot, there's acrylic paint in here
it's all pretty toxic
so just take one last beautiful look at it.
And remember, safety, is of course, the first priority here
so don't eat slime at home.
I guess I won't eat slime either.
It did look pretty tasty
but it's definitely very bad for you.
If you want to see another video, click right over here.
Right now, you have five seconds, to click right over here.
Five
four
three
two
one
done.
Love you guys.
(both men shout) Bye!