- You challenged us to make a whole bunch
of giant candy like this.
Check it out.
Boom, look at that!
- Whoa!
Wait a second, lemme try!
Oh!
- Nah, bro, you kidding me, man?
All right, no more magic.
It's time to make some giant kinder eggs, so let's go.
We have the kinder egg mold, a whole bunch of chocolate--
- Wait, there's mold?
Where's the mold?
- Devan, these are molds, it's how cooking works.
Come on.
- I'm just kidding.
- Time to fill it in, so here we go, ooh!
What is that?
- This is cookie dough that I dyed black
to look like a geode.
There are three parts to the kinder egg.
There's a chocolate outside, the filling,
and then the truffle on the inside.
I'm making the truffle on the inside,
you're making the chocolate exteriors.
- I feel like a chocolatier right now.
Oh!
Dude, I'm like one of the three musketeers
but with chocolatiers, man!
Just a whole bunch of dudes covered in chocolate.
- Oh, dude, since this is gonna be a giant kinder egg,
I'm gonna make a bunch of truffles on the inside.
- Okay.
I'm just trying to get this--
- Are you kidding me, dude?
- Oh, man.
Well, that wiggles a little bit more
than it should right now.
I gotta grab this mold over here,
do a quick little flippity flipadoo.
One, two, three.
(crashing noise)
I kinda bailed mid-way.
So here we go.
So, I'm just gonna take it like this,
just gonna squeeze it down.
What are you doing?
- I'm putting these into the oven
and letting them expand.
- So as your geode truffles are baking,
my egg is gonna be shaking.
We call this the shake and bake.
Wow, that wasn't fun.
Time for me to shake this around.
So here we go, wow.
- Wow, all right then.
- Coat the inside like that, okay!
All right, that's pretty tiring,
so there we go, egg is--
- That hurt?
- Yeah.
Now we just gotta fill in the filling
as well as the little truffle thingys on the inside.
Is yours done cooking yet?
- Not yet.
(elevator music)
And we're done!
- Okay, you didn't need to wake me up like that, man.
I was having a great dream.
- Careful, the oven's open.
- I wake up to such a dangerous world.
- All right, gonna pull these things out of the oven.
Here, thank you for closing the oven for me.
And now, I have these halves.
Having some troubles there?
- I got it.
All right, well my egg is all ready to go.
So now, it's gotta let it--
- Whoa, you're already done?
- Nope, what I meant to say, was it's not ready to go,
and I need to put it off to the side
to let it set in the fridge.
- All right then, well.
- It's my child.
- As you do--
What?
- Nothing.
- As you do that, I'm gonna hollow out
the rest of these, here, and then
fill em up with these nice rocks.
What are you--
- Somehow I forgot the fridge is over here.
- I got a shaker here that also doubles as a hammer, so.
- Yeah, well I got a hook that also--
- Is a hook.
- Doubles as a hook.
- Wait, wait, wait, no, no, no!
I think that's one of those pressure point
things for your back.
- Yeah right, man.
- Yeah, seriously.
(makes painful noise)
Oh, geez.
Here we go.
- Oh my gosh.
I feel like I just got like tasered.
- You've gotten tasered before?
- It was a rough weekend.
Gonna take the bag like this.
(banging noise)
- Got a problem, bro?
You just stopped.
- I feel uncomfortable right now.
- How could you feel uncomfortable?
- Who are you?
You've changed!
You are now me!
And I'm you!
- Yeah!
- This is weird!
Here we go, gonna add in a whole bunch
of sour patch kids right now, in here, like this.
Whoa.
I can't talk over that, man.
- Yes, you can.
- No, I can't.
- And you will.
- I got a whole bunch of sour patch kids here,
so now, I just gotta melt all these
sour patch kids down again.
This is gonna be--
I can't even right now.
This is gonna be the inside filling for my kinder egg.
- [Devan] Look at this, man!
This is looking sweet!
- I melted down all the sour patch kids.
I had to add in some blue food coloring,
'cause it was looking pretty funky.
- I've got half of the geode truffle done,
but now, I have to coat it all in chocolate.
- The next part of my kinder egg,
I'm doing a filling with this
jet-puffed marshmallow right over here.
- Wait, I wonder why they call it jet-puffed?
- Oh, you've never seen it before?
It's this signature look, man.
Here we go, three, two, one.
Boom, look at that jet engine, man!
- Whoa, are you kidding, it's like the arm rocket!
- It's awesome, bro!
- Okay, then.
- And the best part is boom,
look at that, it can fly by itself, man!
- Is it pointing at me?
- Yeah, it's building up a little in the back.
(explosion noise)
No!
- No, no!
What did you do?
- Nothing!
- I have a hole in my chest!
- Well Devan, as you figure that out,
I'm gonna continue making my kinder egg right now.
- Are you kidding me?
You gotta help me out!
The next thing for my mousse sauce
is putting in this cool whip.
- The next part of my kinder egg,
I'm doing a filling with this
jet-puffed marshmallow right over here.
Yeah, we had a very bad experience with this stuff.
- Yeah.
- Time to tear open some pop rocks right now
and just add these in.
Oh, boy, okay there we go.
Dude that sounds so crazy, man.
- Whoa!
- All right, well now time to mix it all up.
- Also coated the inside of these bowls here
with some chocolate, now I'm gonna add this--
What are you doing?
- Hold on.
- What are you doing?
- I gotta inspect it.
- Why?
(sniffing)
- Yep, it's chocolate.
You never know with Devan.
You just never know.
- You kidding?
With me?
Whoa.
Okay, there, yep, yep, yep.
- You wanted us to use this, if you're
not even using a piping bag properly.
(gulp)
I'ma keep mixing this over here.
- Yep, the piping bag doesn't really work.
I'm just adding it in like this.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, but wait!
Oh!
I get it now!
You're doing for the truffle,
you got chocolate on the outside,
chocolate mousse on the inside,
and then you're gonna use these geodes inside that.
- Exactly!
- Holy cow, the whole dish just increased exponentially.
- Got the two domes done,
now it's time to grab the geodes and put em in.
So, there's one right there.
- For my truffle, we've got a whole bunch
of jolly ranchers over here.
That was a quick grab.
Oh!
- That wasn't supposed to open yet.
- Oh, are you kidding me, Devan?
- Oh, man.
- I'm gonna take a whole bunch of jolly ranchers,
place em down over here, create a beautiful pattern,
and turn it into the outer shell of my truffle.
- Nice, well I--
- It'll make a lot of sense.
- Are you done?
- Yeah.
- For the filling of my kinder egg,
I'm making nutella, but better.
- How are you gonna make better than nutella, man?
- I'm gonna home-make it.
- And you think you're really gonna nail
the recipe more than the nutella brand?
- You know, when you say it like that, it sounds unlikely.
- All right, well I'm gonna continue
constructing this absolutely beautiful masterpiece here,
and let's speed it along.
- Yo!
Wait, whoa, I switched places with Devan.
Wait, where'd Devan go?
- Huh, wait, what?
Why am I over here?
- Oh, sorry, I've gotten really rusty at this.
You should probably take back your sack of hazelnuts.
- Hazelnuts.
- I was trying to avoid that, but all right.
I'm gonna take this right here,
and again, I'm gonna use it
as the outer shell of my truffles.
We're gonna flip it over, here we go.
Three, two, one.
(screaming)
okay, there we go.
That's so satisfying!
- Yo, that looks cool!
- Wait 'til you see what I filled the interior with.
It's gonna be saucy.
- Like, is it actual sauce?
- It's not actual sauce, it's just going to be saucy.
- So, sauce.
Got the hazelnuts all blended up,
now just gonna add the chocolate.
- All right, for my truffle, I've got some
peanut butter that I'm gonna pop inside.
It's still got the cover on it, so here we go.
Three, two, one.
- [Devan] Now just gotta blend this stuff.
- Well, we've got everything we need,
so now it is time to fully put our
kinder eggs together and see their gloriousness.
We've got the kinder eggs, and dude, look at this!
This is absolutely massive!
- Dude, they are really heavy too.
- Exactly, so right now, we've got everything
we need to fill it up, but first,
we've got a chocolate layer, and then
a white chocolate layer we've added on top of that.
I've got some candy slime over here,
and as you know, there's going to be a surprise
inside the kinder egg, but right now,
let's put these together.
The giant kinder eggs are all made,
and bro, this is an engineering feat of genius, man!
Like, they are so massive!
- These things are huge.
- But the best part is wait 'til you see
the surprise that's on the inside, man.
Like that's really what takes
this whole thing to another level.
Here is the big reveal, three, two, one!
Tada!
Look at these, bro!
- Dude!
- These turned out to be absolutely insane!
So we're gonna be cracking these things open
and eating them at the end of the video.
You challenged us to make a giant Butterfinger
and Snickers bar, so let's go.
First thing I'm doing is making the inside
of my Butterfinger, so I got a whole bunch
of peanut butter right here.
- And I'm making a peanut for my snickers.
- I'm gonna add my peanut butter in here like this.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(grunting)
That sounded like a pterodactyl.
Wait, wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
- What?
- There's corn syrup?
- Yeah, man!
- You are the worst farmer of all time, Devan.
You couldn't farm a peanut, you don't even know what it is.
- Why would I want--
No, what?
- As you can tell, we got a little bit
of peanut butter over here,
so now, I think I can move this off to the side.
- What?
Just a little bit?
- Yeah, I gotta get pumped real quick, so here we go.
All right, there we go and then--
All right, so there we go!
Three, two, one.
(grunting)
Easy, totally easy!
Whoo, I feel exerted.
The whole thing with the interior of a butter finger
is you gotta make sure that it's super crunchy.
So, got some corn flakes here.
We got some chick-o-sticks.
Whole little tower right over here.
Stay.
I've never even like, heard of these things.
- Oh, they're right here too.
- My stick, no touching my sticks!
Bro!
Devan has butterfingers.
- Watch this.
(crashing noise)
- I'm a little scared.
- I meant to point it at you, but.
- I feel rather uncomfortable right now.
- All right, this thing is heated up,
now it's time to add some baking soda here.
- Here is Helga the hen.
- Whoa, yes!
- Gonna smash up the sticks with Helga the hen.
This is gonna act as the crunchy texture
on the inside of my butterfingers.
- I'm putting this into the mold here.
- That looks so gross.
- Collins?
- What?
- Can you help?
- I finally figured out the perfect mixture,
now I'm gonna pour it into the mold.
- You hold onto that for a second.
No, no, no, no, no.
- What?
Collins!
I don't wanna hold it, it's all you.
- Okay, so here, no, no, no!
We can't just set it--
And we're back to where we started.
- [Devan] Oh, wow, this is really not going in very well.
- [Collins] And that's gonna create a peanut?
- Hopefully.
- All right, here we go, just gonna scoop
out a little bit of peanut butter over here like this.
Oh, yeah, just give a nice little plop down here.
Boom, bigger scoop!
Call me the peanut butter dude!
- Haha, I don't know if I wanna call you
the peanut butter dude anymore.
You're like a pokemon.
They say their name before they do something.
And if you're a pokemon, that means you could be caught!
- You can't catch peanut butter dude.
- Oh you can't, well let's try it out!
Three, two, one!
- Ow!
Holy cow!
I almost wish I was caught,
'cause it probably woulda hurt less.
- Bruh.
- What?
- Can you see how slow this is going?
- Did you just say bruh?
- Bruh.
Oop, I missed.
Completely missed.
I completely missed.
- I mean, it looks kinda cool.
- It kinda looks like a goober.
Right, isn't that a fish, or something like that?
- What?
(stammering)
- It looks like one of those fishes that go.
- Peanut butter man does not seen one of these fish before.
Next up, I gotta melt down
a whole bunch of candy corns for the caramel.
- All right, just gotta let the mold set
and then the peanut is done.
All right, next up, I'm making my nougat.
- To find the illusive candy corn,
I brought along the silly scissors.
- That was a voice crack?
- Nope, that was just me.
- Okay, well, what do they do?
- They cut a hole in the space-time continuum!
So silly!
Time to cut open the fabric of time, you ready?
Three, two, one.
(zapping noise)
Oh!
Snap, yo!
- That looks like you.
- That looks like me.
This is alternate universe me!
- Haha, yeah.
- Where is the candy corn?
- It's been here the whole time?
Just gonna put in this marshmallow fluff here.
- There is one other use, and that is
you can use these to slice off the top
of your recently found candy corn.
- Just what scissors do.
- This is what I call the basketball dunk spike.
Excuse me, I'm going backwards.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one, dunk!
Oh, snap!
That was pretty cool.
We got even more candy corns, and here we go,
gonna add that in like that.
Boom, there we go.
Then we got this one over here.
- Are you making this on the floor, or in that?
- I know you're not really asking this question, Devan.
- I'm not.
- And that hurts.
I've got some dark corn syrup
I'm gonna add into my candy corn.
Is this gonna be the nougat?
- Yes.
- What, whoa!
That looks like--
- [Devan] No!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm gonna get a new one.
- We've got the candy bar molds,
and the first thing I'm doing here
for my butterfingers is the topping.
- And the first thing I'm doing is my nougat.
- This is very heavy.
Three, two, one.
Oh, let's see, okay a little pour.
- [Devan] Look at the rolls, dude!
- [Collins] Dude, that looks beautiful!
Mine's actually looking pretty good as well, man.
All right, so here we go, just gonna pour this down.
- Now it's time to add the peanuts.
- [Collins] Those are the peanuts?
- Yes.
Gonna try to plop it outta here into here.
Yeah!
- [Collins] That looks so cool, man!
- Now it's time to add the caramel.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
We can go at the same time!
We can be bros!
Okay, three, two, one.
Just pour it straight in the center, oh!
That's a lot of peanut butter.
- Dude!
- Time for me to get my hands in here
and kind of mix this up a little bit.
- [Devan] Wait, what?
- I feel like I'm doggy-paddling right now
to get all this stuff in here.
We gotta douse all of this in a lot of lovely chocolate.
But right now, we'll get it all finished up
and then it's time to see how they taste.
All right, the giant candy bars are all done.
I gotta say, I was expecting big,
these are massive, bro!
- These are not any normal candy bars, man.
- Oh, no.
- Holy cow!
- Trying to take a bite of these things
is gonna be next to impossible.
Right now here is the big reveal, three, two--
Wait, a three-second like challenge.
We wanna see you like this video
in three seconds, you ready?
Here we go, three, two, one, done.
Three, two, one.
What's up?
- I messed up.
- Well there's mine, reveal yours!
- Tada!
- There we go.
- You get to comment down below,
which one do you think will taste better,
and we'll be eating them at the end of the video.
- You challenged us to make a giant donut and nerds rope.
So the first thing I'm making for my giant donut
is the round donut-shaped dough.
- Yup, and the first thing I'm making
is the nerd of the nerd rope.
So, to make my nerd, I got a jolly rancher
on the tip of this hot straw.
Just gonna try to blow it up real quick.
- Oh no!
- You broke the faucet!
- I broke the faucet!
- Are you kidding me?
- That's an issue.
- Bro.
- This is an issue.
Yeah, let's just have--
- Bro, are you kidding?
- Haha, whoopsie!
I don't think it's that noticeable.
- Are you kidding?
I'm actually gonna use a mold instead.
That might work out better.
- All right, all I gotta do
is just take these different cakes right here,
like this, just gonna let it go down and--
Devan?
- What?
- I need this space right here.
- Okay.
- Three, two, one, let's see.
Oh, there we go, that's what I'm talking about.
Sweet moves, bro.
Oh boy, yeah, this is--
- And you got it on my arm.
No!
I knew you wouldn't do it.
- My commitment level is weak.
- So, before I do this, I have
to wash my hands, but Collins?
- What?
- I would normally wash my hands right here.
But now, I have to go all the way
over there to wash my hands.
Look what you've done to me, bro.
- I'm sorry.
It was the cakes, man!
- Shame.
- Blame them!
- I'm all the way over here, washing my hands,
and I'm totally separated from the action!
- Yeah, you can't even see how cool
my donut is starting to look, man!
- Actually, I can see it.
- Well, what do you think?
(laughs nervously)
- It's looking good.
- What was that laugh?
- All right, so I've melted down the jolly ranchers,
now I've gotta pour em into the molds.
- While you do that, time for me to move my donut over here!
I tried to talk normal, but that is
a very heavy donut right now.
So, next up I've gotta make some cotton candy
for the toppings on my donut.
All right, here we go, cotton candy machine is turned on.
- [Devan] Just pouring it into the mold here.
- Let's see if this works, here we go.
You ready, three, two, one.
Whoa!
Yo!
- Yes!
- Wait a minute!
This is what I'm talking about!
- [Devan] This is the real stuff, dude!
- Yeah, man!
Look at that sight!
- Calm, calm, calm.
That was too much.
All right, it's gonna just take way too long
to cool this stuff down, so I'm gonna use liquid nitrogen.
- Okay, don't try this at home, by the way.
I think the cotton candy was much cooler,
just saying, just putting that out there.
Can you do this with liquid nitrogen?
Boom!
- It's always the coolest.
Did you get that?
It's really cold.
- It was a joke.
Next, I'm gonna use a little bronca-ya-jus-just--
Bronca-saura-donk, banca-donka-donka-brunkis.
You got it, here we go, three, two, one.
Just gonna pour it in like this, here we go.
- Okay, do I just hold it here?
- Yeah, there we go.
Oh, no, no, gotta catch this!
Yep, keep it going!
- [Devan] Do I spin it?
- Yeah, just keep spinning it.
I think we're reaching the limits
of what the bronky-donkyus can hold.
This will be perfect for the top of my donut.
- This looks like a wand with a spell on the end of it.
- Yeah right, man.
- Abra-cadabra, you shall never do the dab again, bro!
- What?
That's not a real spell.
- Yes, try it.
Uh-huh, I told you, bro.
- Third time's the charm.
- Oh man!
If that's what happened if he tried to dab,
I'd hate to see what happened if he tried to floss.
All right, so now we got these two halves,
it's time to heat these things up and fuse them together.
- Sorry about that, man.
Okay, caught a couple of peeps.
Wait, I wonder if this works with other stuff,
like hot cheetos for instance.
Let's try it, here we go.
Nope, more peeps.
It's infinite peeps.
- All right, so, why are you using these things, Collins?
(crickets chirping)
- That's a good question.
Oh, sorry, to make a topping for my donut.
- This is made now, now it's time to move onto the rope.
- This ain't made, this is wack.
Well right now, it's the moment
I've always been waiting for,
time to yeet 150 chicks at once.
Yeet!
Picked up 15 chicks just like that.
- And I'm just picking up a big tube I made here.
- What did, where?
- This is for my nerd rope, bro.
- No, where did that come from?
- Collins, we aren't playing around.
- Devan, on a real note, where did that come from?
- From the ground, it's been there the whole time.
- I literally didn't see it at all.
(gasps)
(stammers)
Gosh, it's so tough to open, holy cow.
- I thought you were strong.
I thought you could pick up 100 chicks.
- 150.
Whoa, peep slide, bam!
Tilt it!
Look at that, bro!
You just made that peep's day.
- I hate to say it, but this peep is about to be eaten.
You do not wanna give this thing life and a name.
- That's so dark.
- All right, so I'm gonna fill this thing up
with some jello, then let it set.
Three, two, one.
Okay, it's going in.
- I can't see anything.
- All right, there we go, got one.
Hold up, stay there.
- Bumped me.
I don't understand why I'm always being bumped.
- Karma.
Pouring this one in here.
All right, you're gonna let go on the count of three.
Here we go, three.
- No more three, two, ones!
We are banning three, two, ones on the channel!
- Oh wait, but first!
(laughing)
Sweet baby Yoda.
Well, time for me to mash up a whole bunch of peeps!
- Next up, I am making a red nerd
with a red apple, some candy melt here, and some nerds.
- I think these peeps are gonna act
as a lovely texture for the topping of my donut, man.
- Lovely.
Beautiful, glorious.
- It is.
Kinda disturbing, I've got like
a peep's eye just chilling on my hand.
- Hey man, that's a little dark, don't you think?
- I got peep vision now.
- Whoa, wow, okay.
Whoa, getting a little close there, bro.
- So it's basically like a candy apple, man?
- Kind of.
I got a bunch of different flavor profiles, you know?
(spatting noises)
- You shoulda just poured the whole box on it, man.
It's like you break open a box of nerds.
Ooh, missed that.
- Collins, I think the key point is you don't break it!
- There we go.
- Collins!
You're not supposed to break it, you're supposed to open it.
There you go, there you go, there you go.
That was like, nothing.
- Exactly, they must be filled with air.
- It's almost like you smashed it on the counter
and lost everything that was inside.
- I don't know why you would think that, man.
This just in, nerd boxes are filled with 90 percent air,
and only ten percent candy.
- Wait, wait, wait, dude, we don't wanna get sued.
You can't say that.
- Okay, yes.
- You can't say that.
- Just kidding, fake news!
- Exactly.
- Back to you Patricia!
Okay, right now it's time for me to glaze my donut.
- And time for me to finish up my nerds rope.
What are you saying, dude?
(grunting)
- What is that?
I've got the glaze, bro, you gotta chill.
Three, two, one.
- Oh, that's a good coat, man.
- That looks chunky!
- It looks like a smoothie.
Oh no!
It's going down the front of the table, dude!
I just gotta remove this nerds rope.
- Oh my gosh, dude!
- Yes, wait, hold it, hold it!
- This is so dope, bro!
Time to finish things up, and then
we're gonna be eating em.
Giant candies are done, and bro,
that nerds rope is absolutely insane.
- It is massive, bro.
- Like, the nerds are larger than my fist, bro.
- Seriously.
- And this donut, I gotta say,
I think it's 800 pounds, to be honest.
- It's pretty huge.
- I've had a lot of trouble lifting it.
So here is the big reveal.
Three, two--
Oh, wait, five-second subscribe challenge.
We wanna see if you can subscribe to the channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you were able to do that,
comment down below Keyper squad right now,
and let's see how these turned out.
Three, two, one, tada!
Look at these giant candies!
Finally time to eat the giant snickers bar
and the giant butterfingers.
So Devan, which one should we eat first?
This whack, square-looking snickers bar,
or the beautiful, shapely butterfinger?
It's the shape you want.
- All right, let's do yours first.
- Thanks.
- Let's be disappointed, together.
- So, to cut it open, I've got an ax right over here.
- Are you kidding?
- Here's the thing.
If you you ever got a giant candy bar,
do not try this at home.
Just gonna kinda give it like a downward dog.
Here we go, three, two, one.
- Wow.
- Okay.
- [Devan] Dude, yes!
- Holy cow!
- [Devan] That works!
- Boom, boom!
Yeah!
Ax-man, I'm the ax-man!
- I won't, I won't.
- And don't worry, we will not be eating
all of this by ourselves.
We'll be sharing with our friends and family.
Holy cow, this actually looks really, really, wow!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- What, what, what, what, what?
- Use your own fork and grab your own piece of the bar.
- My fork is on the floor.
- Well, it was your decision.
- [Devan] Just gonna grab off.
- So, you're the first one to get
the feeling of the texture.
What does it feel like?
- Yeah, terrible.
- Let's see how it tastes.
Ready, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Whoa.
It tastes like a butterfinger, man!
It can't be that bad.
What, it's that bad?
- It tastes great, but wow, is it crunchy!
- Well, yeah, it's all about that crunch.
So, I think I have a strong chance
of winning this round, but Devan--
- So do I.
- I like that.
- I mean, no.
I'm actually going to undo it from the back here,
and do a nice little reveal.
- Don't worry about me.
Tada!
- [Devan] Yeah!
- [Collins] Look at that!
- Yeah, the back's not so great,
but, you know, the front looks pretty good.
I have no idea how I'm gonna cut through this.
- [Collins] You need a bigger knife.
(elevator music)
Three, two, one.
Oh, oh, it's going!
It's happening, it's happening!
Look at that!
Holy cow!
It's beautiful.
- It looks great.
- I might actually cry.
- Okay, maybe don't cry.
Just gonna pull down here, yes!
Got some of that off.
That's a chunk of chocolate.
- That's like a full chocolate bar, normally.
So, I'm gonna take this little piece of chocolate
over here, I'm gonna be tasteful.
All right, I'm gonna place this down and layer--
(grunting)
- Yes!
I just wanted to do that.
- Holy cow.
(yelling)
- I want the peanut.
- It's definitely wedged deep in the crevasse.
Hey, don't bring that up.
- All right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
Whoa!
- The peanut is too hard.
- Whoa, whoa!
Are you kidding me?
You crushed it, bro!
Creme de la awesome.
Well, as you can tell, my egg
is starting to fall apart, so now
it is time to crack it open.
So, here we go, three, two, one.
We have made it into the egg.
Here it goes, we're moving pieces.
Tada!
- Wow.
- First, take a look at the surprise on the inside.
It's got a balloon in it, here we go.
Oh, it's getting a little bit stuck.
All right, so this is the surprise
that Devan made for me on the inside.
- Yes.
- What is it?
- You can't tell, dude?
- Well, it looks like a little
jet-engine-propelled telephone.
No, no, this is how you handle customer service calls, man.
Hey, so my car phone isn't working, and I'm mad.
- It's a car, Collins, but it's okay.
- I think you should probably grab
like a slab of chocolate first.
Let's try to remove that ball.
It's like a game show.
Remove that ball!
Oh, yep, this is nice.
Scoop-de-doop-doop-Doop
Okay, there we go.
- [Devan] You got it.
- It's been scoopa-dee-doo--
De doop doop doop
Wanna cheers it first?
- Sure.
Three, two, one.
- Whoa.
This thing here--
(evil laugh)
- That tasted like a sandwich with chocolate!
- That was pretty phenomenal, man.
- I agree.
- With the filling on the inside,
combined with peanut butter and jelly,
the chocolate on the outside.
Woohoo!
- All right, let's do this thing.
You ready?
- You want me to help out at all?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Do it with the spoons.
- That's what I'm gonna do.
Three, two, one.
Oh, it's very soft.
- I gotta say, this is a resilient egg, bro.
- It is, man.
I make em good!
- I smack it, I smack it hard!
- Three, two, one.
- Karate chop!
Ow.
- Tada!
- These truffles look pretty delicious, bro.
- Yeah, they look a little dented though.
Honestly might've been your spoon.
- Couldn't have been.
- I think it was.
- I don't think it was.
- What should we serve us first?
- The surprise!
- Wait, it has a rope on it?
- Yeah, well I don't know if it'll get--
It makes sense with the whole thing.
- A pendulum.
You're getting sleepy.
Hold onto this.
- Okay, cool, here we go.
Two things here it's a climbing man.
- Oh!
- He can climb the rope!
See, look at that.
- Look at that!
- Boom!
- He's getting to my hand.
- So right now it's time to taste the delicious kinder egg.
- I think you take one of these massive truffles.
- Don't touch, it's mine.
- What are you doing?
- That's mine.
Okay, so listen.
Oh, that's uncomfortable.
It's like reaching into a pudding.
- Yeah, there you go.
- Ba-bam!
You need to move yours off to the side.
- Move my egg?
What are you doing?
- I help with my foot.
(crashing noise)
Okay, well I'm gonna try right here.
Three, two, one.
Oh!
Look at that!
- Yo!
Yes!
Three, two, one.
Oh!
- No!
- That was close.
- That scared me.
I feel like you're doing something wrong.
- I made these things, bro.
I know what I'm doing, I think.
- I don't think so.
I have it already open.
You hurt your pride more than your fingers.
- [Devan] Yeah!
- [Collins] There you go!
- Look at that, man!
Remember I got those geodes on the inside.
- Oh!
- Yeah!
- Oh, dude, I'm over here looking like a prehistoric dude.
Three, two, one.
Oh!
- [Devan] That looks so cool, man!
- Here we go, brute strength.
Boom!
Why does mine look so much whacker than yours?
- I'm gonna dip it into here a little bit.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one.
This is so good!
Holy cow!
Wow.
Our friends are gonna love this.
- If you were only able to eat
one of these giant kinder eggs,
which one would you wanna eat?
Let us know in the comments down below,
and we're onto the next giant candy.
We've got the giant donut,
and the absolutely insane nerds rope.
Devan, which one should we eat first?
I think let's do yours.
- All right, so here's the thing.
I'm gonna lift it up, you're gonna give it a slice, okay?
- Wait, wait, wait, where, where?
(yells)
- [Collins] Don't try this at home.
I don't know why you would, or how you would.
- Why is it blue, dude?
- You should never cut towards the person.
- This looks gross.
- Forget this, yeah, wow.
- That looks like soggy bread.
- Well, that's kinda actually what is was.
- I'm a little queasy.
- Man up.
Grab a fork.
- Bring it on, brother.
- Clink it.
I want the pink!
I'm gonna take off, here we go, boom.
One of these cotton candy balls.
And then put the peeps on the top.
- You crazy.
- Whoo, it's falling apart!
- Are you ready to go, dude?
You're stalling.
- All right, yep here we go, can't wait.
Three, two--
Wait, if you wanna win a 15 minute video call
with Devan and I, text the word best to 81800 right now.
After the video.
Text the word best to 81800.
You will automatically be entered in to win.
Let's see how this tastes.
Three, two, one.
- Dude, this is so good!
You got a big peep in your mouth.
Way to go, man!
So many different flavors, this thing--
- It just tasted so good, man!
- So good!
- I am over the moon with my creation.
- Wow, now it's time for the main event.
So, Collins, can you move your donut?
- Devan, can you move my donut?
'Cause I can't.
- It's your donut.
- I'm not strong enough.
- I'll give it a shot.
- Lift it all the way up.
Are you actually able to lift this thing?
- I think so.
- Holy cow.
Need more leverage?
- Yes, okay!
- Holy cow!
Dude!
- That was definitely very heavy.
So, I'm just gonna cut a small part
right in the middle here.
- What about me, what do I do?
- I actually cut yours, do you wanna cut mine?
- That would be a pleasure and an absolute honor.
- Man, these knives are really blunt.
- Yep, they are definitely not sharpened.
- You might wanna not cut so fast.
Reveal the toothpicks.
- Check it out, I'm a magician.
It's gone.
- This is the nerds rope here.
- Another toothpick!
- I couldn't make it stick, all right?
And remember, I made a bunch
of different nerds with different flavors.
This was cheese popcorn dipped in--
What are you doing?
- I want that.
- So I'm just gonna break this guy in half.
Wow.
- Ooh, that was good.
- We gotta split this in half.
You know what, I'm just gonna pull it apart.
Just say some words man, fill the time.
- So, Devan's clearly struggling so hard right now.
Your hands have been all over that.
I don't even wanna eat that anymore.
I'ma slice off a new piece for myself.
- Are you kidding?
This is really not easy, bro.
That took you like a solid--
- Oh!
- What, what, what, what, what?
- Little bit of a oopsie.
- [Devan] No!
- That's not rubbing away.
- Let's get into it, man.
Let's eat this thing.
Three, two, one.
(mumbles with mouth full)
- Okay, that one was good.
Very good.
- They're really good.
- I mean it's like, it's a rock.
You choose your life, but all together, good.
- Dude, all of the flavor profiles
in this thing were insane!
- That purple one!
- I know, but seriously, all these were delicious.
- Even the popcorn.
The flavor profiles were definitely on another level.
Don't worry, we won't be eating all this by ourselves.
We're gonna be sharing all of it
with our friends and families.
So, you get to comment down below,
if you had to eat one of these giant candies,
which one would it be?
You wanna see another video, click right over here.
You got five seconds, here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Love you, bye!