- What's up guys?
It's Collins.
Now, Halloween is right around the corner
and if you guys are like me
you probably procrastinate on your costumes.
Today you're in luck because I'm gonna be
doing some last minute Halloween costumes.
To help me out, I have a friend of mine
the beautiful Meg De Angeles.
Hey!
- Welcome.
- Thanks, hi.
- And I decided to turn this into a challenge.
- Woo!
- Here I have a giant pile of clothes,
random costume stuff,
we've even given some categories
like pirates, medieval.
And then in 30 seconds,
using the random pile of clothes
we get to try and make that costume,
super last minute.
Let's get started.
(snaps fingers)
That was (laughs), that was awkward.
Back in black,
that's a Maddie right there,
that's a last minute Halloween costume.
- I think it's like a better base
for all the cool costumes we're gonna be putting on.
- She knows a lot about this.
I'm gonna go with her opinion on it.
The first category is.
- Fairies.
- Go!
(fast forward talking)
I think I have a wand stuck to my butt.
All right, that's time.
- Dang it.
- If you can tell I have the magical fairy wand.
I went with the tutu
because I wanted to be an ultra-masculine fairy.
I'm good, I'm done here.
- He spends his life dressing up as a girl fairy pretty much
but...
Come back from the corner.
- (Laughs)
- Oh a man crying in the corner.
- My fairy friends, Petunia and Patricia.
This is my fairy outfit.
- So I am a fairly of the underworld.
And then this is the gem to get into my fairy caves,
scan it to get in.
- Wow.
- There's only six of them in the whole world.
- Yes, and then-
- That's a lot of backstory for the one gem.
- This is my wand,
I'm like deep and dark
and I'm also a bit hipster
so instead of wands, I go with flowers,
and then I have these sparkling wings on me,
they're just for funzees, they don't even work.
- I think it's pretty apparent who won this one.
I'm like Kanye West with this quilt on right now.
All right guys, so,
and now I'm a dirty fairy. (laughs)
Let us know in the comment
who do you guys think won
this last-minute Halloween costume.
- I mean, it was me but you know.
- We are going to be doing hippies.
One, two, three, go.
(fast forward talking)
I need more suspenders.
- Dude, you're gonna end up looking like a clown.
(fast forward talking)
- Four, three,
- What am I doing here?
- There's nothing! Two!
Oh here! That's just one, okay.
- Dang it, I made a bib.
That was not meant to happen.
- (Laughs)
Like this video if you guys think
that Meg looks beautiful right now
because those glasses are on point.
- So I have this, it looks like a bow
but really it's a hippie band.
The bow represents happiness.
This, you may think it's a bib,
but really it is a very fashionable top.
- Mm.
- And then we have this which is like,
it's more like a cape.
- Oh.
- It's kind of like a cape style.
How about yours?
- The hair, of course, is the most important part
because that's what everyone sees.
I have a little bit of a hair extension over here.
I have these suspenders on,
I don't really know how to put suspenders on,
it's also some nice resistance training
when you're at concerts,
you can get just work your triceps.
I'm a hippie guy so I'm very in touch
with my feminine side
and so I like to wear skirts and dresses
to signify the feminism in all of us.
- You like wearing skirts,
this is the second outfit with a skirt.
- The first one was a tutu. (Laughs)
In the comment down below,
and let us know who won the hippie outfit.
I think you might've taken this one home.
- Oh my god, what is this?
It's like Elmo threw up on my hair.
- On the next category,
we'll see if he chooses another skirt outfit,
but it's gonna be,
okay, you're in for it?
Vampire.
- Cool.
(fast forward speaking)
Oh my god! Vampire teeth.
Clear advantage.
- Oh you got that.
Did you say Claire Danes?
- I said clear... (laughs)
- (Laughs) I was like, "What?"
- I said, "Clear advantage."
(fast forward talking)
- These are, these are, these are,
these are a cross,
I know what these are,
these are the flood gates.
- You're gonna have trouble speaking throughout this one
but that's okay, I'll translate.
- Cool.
So guys.
- He says my outfit sucks.
- (Laughs)
- (Laughs) No, he didn't do it.
- Screw that.
But it is an authentic vampires hat.
I wanna keep it modern and I put on this vest
because it looks like something
that a vampire would wear now to kind of fit in.
These roses actually signify
that I am fourth level warlock vampire
of the seventh degree.
If I just show this rose to people
and they bow down, so.
- Well, I-
- And she's not in my clan.
- I'm (smiles)
- She's like, "I'm not gonna bow down."
- Oh (laughs).
- Thank you.
- This is an eight level warlock clan, you see.
Not to be too mainstream here
but vampires will always have the cape.
If I'm too tired to suck my own blood,
okay, I have my friend Petunia to suck the blood for me.
- I hate losing so bad that every single...
- Collins?
- You have to understand that I literally yet
to win any challenge ever on my channel?
- Oh you tweeted that!
- Let me know on the comment down below
who won this category.
- Or Petunia will come for you.
Hitting this club for thumbs up.
Hit the thumbs up if you don't want Petunia to get you.
- (Hisses)
Like fashion guru tip here,
if you start with maybe like a black t-shirt and leggings,
a lot of costume possibilities are suddenly available.
- Yes. This is an original idea that I had.
If you guys enjoyed this video,
please give the huge thumbs up
and share with your friends.
Comment down below who won this challenge.
It's her.
Get another video on Meg's channel,
she did Divergent tutorial
on how to dress up as Divergent
and we did back flips.
Look anywhere, I'm adding now,
I'm also gonna put the link's in the description.
Subscribe to this channel.
And also subscribe to Meg.
- Thanks.
- All right, see you guys next week.
Peace. (snaps fingers)
- Collins?
Magicians.
- Whoa!