- [Both] Three, two, one... ohh.
- [Devan] That looks so good.
- You challenged us to make Lego characters,
so right now let's go.
For my pancake, I'm going to make the Flash.
- And I'm making Spiderman.
- Start off a little bit differently.
I'm gonna start off with a square body.
Here we go, we're just gonna give his little leg.
Just like that, look at that,
look at that perfect little leg right there, man.
Alright, next up we gotta give him a neck.
I'm gonna give him a little bit of a longer neck
just to, you know, make up for
the fact that his body is so small.
Alright, and there we oops.
And we'll give him his little arms over here.
Next up, I gotta do his lightening belt,
but for some reason I don't have the color yellow.
Oh right, I left it in the kitchen.
So, let me grab that really quick, here we go.
(speed noise)
Alright, got the yellow, perfect.
Ah, no, I need the bigger yellow,
so give me one second, I'll be right back.
We'll place this over here, here we go.
(speed noise)
Alright, I got the bigger yellow.
- What are you doing?
- I'm grabbing the other yellow.
- Where did you just go?
Dude, are my eyes playing tricks on me, or what?
- So, his belt's all like jaggedy lightening type,
so we're gonna go like this. It looks more like a ruffle.
Now we're gonna fill it in with yellow.
Alright we gotta give him his eyeballs next,
so we got eyeball number one over here,
and now the important part, time to give him his red mask.
Here we go, his red mask kinda goes like this,
circles out around the eyes.
My dude apparently looks like Charlie Brown
mixed with Wall-e, man.
- Whoa, he totally does.
- Yeah, this is not as good as I thought it was going to be,
but, at the same time, it's great.
Alright, we're gonna give him a little mouth.
He's gonna be like, "Yeah, what's up?"
He's like (yells).
- He went (yells)
- This is what happens when he's running super fast.
Alright, the most important part,
the lightening bolt on his chest.
Let's do this.
I need a real life example of a lightening bolt,
so time to forge a lightening bolt.
So, let's see, okay.
I think that should be good.
Here we go, let's see, three, two, one.
(yelling)
- Did that even help you at all?
- I actually forgot what it looks like,
so I guess I'll just have to just kind of wing it.
- Seriously?
(upbeat music)
- Alright, now we gotta fill in his neck,
Gotta give him a nice good...
Oh no, it's Hoot-Dini! - Seriously?
- The owl that randomly goes off
which means we need to spin for our wild card.
Three, two, one. You know what, I just really hope
that it doesn't mess up my lightening bolt
because I gotta really make this guy perfect.
- What, salad tong flip?
- No, I got batter hands.
- Ohh.
- Alright, well we got the batter.
I've got some hands, and time to have some batter hands.
Here we go, batter hand number one.
Let's go get the second in.
First up, we're gonna make the lightening bolt on his chest.
He has a circle first that goes around his chest like that.
There we go. Dude, I'm gonna get artistic and creative here.
I'm just gonna drop,
Ah man, that's not gonna work.
And now to finish up, just gotta add the red.
Alright, just gonna finish off the... oh no.
- What happened?
- The batter's like so slippery, man.
It just slipped right out of my hand.
Just gonna do it like, okay.
Nooo! It took off half his lightening bolt.
What if I just use this, just clear
a little path her in the middle.
I'm gonna redo his lightening bolt.
(upbeat music)
- Alright, time to go for the...
Wait, I can't use a spatula to flip it.
- Ohh. - Man.
- You have to use the tongs. What a technique, man.
- Yeah, you can see I embrace the batter hands.
You try to stay away from them.
I'm embracing them.
I think they're actually gonna help out artwork.
Alright, now it's time for the flip.
So, luckily for me, I get to use some spatulas.
- I know, so jealous right now.
- Oh god, my pants.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh my gosh, I did it with finesse.
That's pretty cool.
- You ready for this?
- Yup, I'm totally ready.
- You have to tong it so lightly.
Three, two...
- Wait, five second subscribe challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds.
Are you ready, here we go.
- [Both] Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you could do that, comment down below
'keyper squad' right now.
- Alright, here we go, ready, set, go.
- Be careful.
(yells)
Oh no, but that looks good.
You get to comment down below,
who made a better pancake, and right now,
we're on to the next one.
You challenged us to make Captain America
from Avengers: Endgame, so right now, let's go.
I'm gonna make Captain America's shield first
because it's the most iconic part.
- Dude, I'm doing the same. - A perfect circle.
That's, Devan okay, the second
circle was actually pretty solid.
You wanna take a look at it?
Hey, Devan, look at my circle.
- I'm making an oval.
- That's a pretty good circle, right?
- Yeah, that's really good.
- And in the Marvel movies, his shield is indestructible,
so I wonder if the pancake is
going to be indestructible, as well,
so we're gonna turn this up,
and we're gonna roast it, flip it, and test the pancake,
and then we're gonna continue with the rest of the body.
- Wait, what?
How does that make sense?
- Maybe I have vibranium pancake batter, Devan.
Never thought of that did ya?
- Nope, very unlikely.
- Alright, here we go.
It's a little jiggly.
Doesn't look too indestructible right now. (yells)
- What?
- It's not feeling indestructible.
Three, two, one, oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Let's just flip the (yells)
Okay, together, alright, well maybe
this needs to cook and harden.
(upbeat music)
I'm gonna try to repair the shield.
So, I'm gonna add some extra batter in here.
Hopefully, this will seal the different parts together.
Let's see how strong this pancake shield really is.
Here we go, three, two, one.
(metal clank)
- Ohh what?
That sounded like it hurt.
- Oh, yeah.
(metal clanking)
Ow, that's a strong pancake.
(metal clank)
That's a no for me.
- Oh no, the cap came off.
- Oh that's not good.
- Ohh, he's gonna have a blob arm.
- He has a loaf of bread for a head.
That's just kind of Captain America's deal.
- A baguette.
Dude, I'm not sure how good my shield is looking.
I mean it's not that close to the real one.
What do you think?
- Wait, that's the real Captain America shield?
- Yeah, I mean there's only one.
- No like, that's like the real one?
- Yeah, it's vibranium.
It's indestructible, bro.
- You wanna test it?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
- Alright, here we go, you ready?
- Uh, yeah. - Three, two...
- Whoa. - What?
- You're going a little quick, let me just get it.
Okay, alright, go.
- And you're sure that's the real one?
- Uh, yeah.
- Okay, here we go, three, two, one.
(blasting and yelling)
Whoa.
- Dude.
- That is definitely the real shield.
- Um, yeah it is.
Didn't I tell ya?
(whoosh)
- You were supposed to catch it.
It was coming back to you. - Oh, he has new.
- I'm gonna fill in Captain America's star with red.
Next up, I gotta give him the American torso suspenders.
I don't know, we have like the red and white
across the side.
- We're doing that next.
Now it's time to Captain America the mouth of a hero.
- Doesn't that just look like a mouth?
- It looks like this Devan. The mouth of a hero.
- Yup. - Oh no, I just remembered.
When I flip my pancake, this is gonna become burnt side up.
- Oh no.
- That's horrible.
And now it's time to fill in his hero mouth.
Just gonna put the...
Oh no, Hoot-Dini. - What, really?
- Alright we gotta spin for our wild card,
bro, this is not gonna be good.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Oh, what happened?
- It just popped right off.
Well, it's part of the mystery wheel.
I don't have to get that one, so hopefully
that was not a bad one, so let's see what this is.
- Super acrylic nails?
- What?
- What's the difference between
regular acrylic and super acrylic?
- Alright, I got a bag with batter,
so I don't know really what I do with that, but I...
Oh no - What?
- That means I can't use these containers.
I can only use the bag.
- Oh no.
- I probably like poke holes in it.
Alright, well right now let's go,
- So, this is what super acrylic nails meant.
Wow, I know what acrylic nails are,
but these are definitely super.
- Yeah, and I guess I have to use this bag.
So, I'm gonna have like just poke holes in it
and properly dispense it.
- How do I...
Oh, one already broke off.
How am I gonna pick this up
'cause I can't pick it up like this.
Oh man, oh man.
Oh no, I forgot I have to turn on the thing first.
- Oh yeah, here, oh that's gonna be tough.
(yells)
Be careful, they'll be, how are you gonna turn it on?
Devan's going for like an upside down, like okay.
- I think I got it, I think I got it.
It's the side of the thumb. - As you're doing that,
- Did it turn on? - time to poke my first hole.
- Oh yeah, it's on, it's hot.
It's on, it's on, it's on. Okay, okay.
- I gotta...
- Oh!
- Sorry, I bumped you.
Alright, hole's in.
Just gonna squeeze out.
Oh, this is actually pretty cool, man.
- Oh no.
- I wonder if I can be doing like two holes at once
like dispensing twice as much.
Yes.
- Okay, gotta pick this, gotta get this one, uh huh.
- I'm absolutely crushing it right now.
- Hello, there we go, I think I got it, I think I got it.
Nice and careful, okay, got it here, switch grip.
- Running out of batter quickly.
- Now it's time to fill in the rest of this.
- You gotta squeeze harder, man.
- What, how?
It's not that I'm not trying.
This is gonna ruin my pancake.
I don't like that.
Gonna take on the shoe and the arm at the same time.
- Oh come on.
- Oh boy, I messed this up, I messed this up,
(yelling) I messed it up.
And just like that, it's over.
- Oh, it's gonna take forever.
Bro, this is like a pincher workout, man.
- Pincher workout?
- Just these two fingers pinchin', ahh.
Muscles are starting to feel some fatigue.
- Fatigue. I have an idea, why don't you use
these as little like funnel shoots,
and so you pour the pancake batter
in at the top and let it funnel down.
- See, that sounds like something you would do,
and it wouldn't be effective.
- What?
Alright, here we go, I'm just gonna dispense down here.
- Oh, I gotta support with my other nail, oh.
Dude, it's like one of those cement trucks.
No way, it is actually working.
- Yeah, I kept...
- (shouting) Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, carefully.
- Okay, I'm gonna stop now.
- Oh, you made this so much more difficult.
Now I don't know what to do with this nail, bro.
You compromised it.
- What do you mean compromised it? It looks great.
It's red on the outside, blue on the inside, that's unique.
- Never again. - Well, look at the top.
- Look at, my finger!
- I'm sorry about that. I just wanna help out that...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa no, nope.
Alright, here we go.
Palm technique, and now I have to move onto the pancake.
Wow, that actually works.
- Yeah, that was actually pretty good.
- [Devan] Look at this, it's speedy Devan.
- Speedy Devan.
He's looking kinda blobby right now,
not too muscly I must say.
- [Devan] And done.
- I didn't even think about this,
but how are you gonna flip with those acrylic nails.
- Oh, what?
Alright, it's on and roasting.
- Maybe use your nails to flip it.
- No way, dude.
I'm gonna break off all my nails.
- Alright, here we go, time to flip my Captain America.
- Oh, go for it.
- [Both] Three, two, one... oh.
- [Devan] That is one burnt pancake.
- Yeah, but I mean like it still is recognizable.
- Let me get that bit for ya.
Let me just get that bit there, just gotta scoop it up.
- There we go, okay, perfect. - I got it, there we go.
- I must admit, the shield looks
way better from the other angle.
- Just the palm grip, oh, yup.
Just the palm and a little bit of pinky.
Here we go, coming underneath.
I feel like an eagle flying in for the scoop, you know.
This is actually doing pretty well.
Alright, the flip.
Three, two, one...
- Oh, if you wanna win a 15 minute
video call with Devan and I,
text the word "art" to 81800 right now.
So, pause the video, text the word art to 81800,
and you'll automatically be entered in to win,
and right now, let's see how this looks.
- Alright, ready, set, go.
- [Collins] Oh, that looks so good.
- [Devan] And I lost a pinky in the process.
- How did you make that with the nails, bro.
Oh my gosh.
Alright, you give the comment down below
who won this round, right now, we're onto the next one.
You challenged us to make a dragon from
How to Train Your Dragon, so right now, let's go.
- Alright, I'm starting with the eye, how 'bout you Collins?
- I'm gonna start with the wings.
- Alright.
- So, we got wing number one, and then
we got the other side of the wing.
Bam, and there is the base of my dragon.
That's actually pretty good.
Like that was pretty solid.
- Dude, I feel like you've done that head like three times.
- I always run out of room at the top.
Oh, that's gonna be supper cool.
He's gonna have like awesome little wings.
- I don't have enough room for the top of his horn,
so it's just gonna be a little stump.
- There is actually precise art to adding the
right amount of pancake batter like that.
- Bam, wing number one complete.
- Nicely done.
(upbeat music)
- Now it's time to add some upgrades to my dragon's wings,
so we're just gonna add this...
Oh no, Hoot-Dini.
- Oh, I was on the scales and everything.
- Oh, dude, and you're like pretty early on,
so this could really mess you up right now.
- I know.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- Have we ever gotten something good yet?
- I don't think we have.
- Alright, well let's hope this one changes that pattern,
so let's see what I got.
- (yells) No, dude, I got duct tape.
- Well, I got can't bend elbows.
- Bro, I have like dinosaur dragon arms right now.
- And I have like Frankenstein arms, dude.
- Well, it'll be very interesting to see how
this pancake turns out, and right now,
I need to continue with the designs.
- I don't know.
- So, the first step, I'm gonna pick up this one over here.
- Gonna grab this.
- I got it, and then you gotta kinda go
forward like this, extend the fingers.
- I can't relax any arm.
How is yours going?
- I put the eye in the wrong place, hold up.
- I keep on just dripping everywhere.
- Devan, can I borrow your sleeve?
- My what?
- I need to use your sleeve to wipe up some batter.
- What?
You can't use my sleeve, that's my merch, bro.
- Oh, alright.
(upbeat music)
Alright, we got some paper towel here.
How does yours still look so good
when you can't even bend your elbows?
- To be honest, I don't know.
- [Collins] Alright, here we go, we just gotta dab it up.
- Alright, time to add some scales.
They're going well.
- For a second I thought you meant like scale
like you're gonna try to weigh 'em.
- The what?
Okay, I think I'm done, but now I have to sneeze, oh no.
- Dude, you better cover your mouth, man.
If you don't cover your mouth, there's gonna be a big issue.
- I don't know how.
- What do you mean you don't know how?
- I might need to use your shoulder.
- You can't, dat won't happen.
- Well luckily I don't have to sneeze anymore,
so your shoulder has been spared.
You're welcome.
- Let me return the favor.
- Oh, thank you, okay.
- Hug me brother!
- Oh, okay, alright, here we go.
It's more like a crocodile hug.
What is, what are you doing with your hand?
- Trying to hug something.
- Well, I think I need to turn on the hot plate, sorry.
I'm sorry, did I bump you?
- You did, but I don't complain.
- Okay, hot plate on.
Time to shake up the bottle.
I feel like I'm doing a pretty good job.
Gotta prepare me red.
- Me red.
- This is some risky business.
- Ah, so close.
- Oh, dear.
- Oh, I got it. - Oh, dear.
- [Collins] There we go, a little tongue in the middle
of his mouth, that's perfect.
- Oh, this take max concentration and a lot of arm strength.
- [Collins] For this row of scales,
they're gonna be a little bit unconventional.
- Okay, I'm done with the blue.
Time to go for the eye.
- Perfect.
- Alright, nice.
- You know what, I'm kinda at a loss for what to do next,
so I need some real like dragon inspiration right now.
So, I'm gonna call my pet dragon, Doug.
(whistles)
(dragon flying)
Here he comes, here he comes.
Oh, that was so cool.
- Collins, Collins, Collins, Doug, look at Doug.
- Oh my gosh, Doug!
- Well, I guess we'll continue to roast some pancakes.
Pancake batter work.
Why don't you work?
- Alright, here we go, I'm gonna turn it on now.
Okay, so this is now where I have to be very careful
because I cannot get close to the griddle.
This is super important.
First steps first, I gotta add some more details.
So, this leg over here is gonna be full of detail.
Alright, now we'll give him some waffle wings.
Pew, waffle wing.
- [Devan] Dude, I think I've gotten the hang of this, man.
- Waffle wing.
- I'm gonna do double straight arms.
- Wow.
- Look at that.
Maybe I should not.
- Alright, now I'm just gonna grab the green again
because I need it for...
Oh, I little bit of misfire, here we go.
So, let's get the green on.
It's very difficult to be precise
when your hands are stuck like this.
Little bit there on the tip of the wing, alright perfect.
- Ohh.
- As you can see, without duct tape, with duct tape.
It makes a huge difference.
(upbeat music)
Imagine how all this detail's gonna look.
It's gonna be fantastic. - I'm done!
- Wait you're done?
- Yup, I get to rest my arms now.
- Alright, I gotta try to get the white,
so, I'm gonna use this little spatula to pick it up.
- Nice, it's a spatula not a grabber, Collins, ohh.
- It didn't work.
- You know what, I'll give you my white.
- Oh, thank you, that's very kind.
- There you go.
Oh, okay.
Careful, dude, careful, I got it.
Here's the white. - I don't need the white.
- You don't need the white now?
- I need the yellow.
- Really, I just got you the white.
- Devan, I'm an artist, and I need a yellow.
- Fine, here you go.
Here is your yellow.
- Thank you, alright here we go, same process.
Yup, uh-huh, nice.
Here we go, long shot.
- Dude, it's on max heat.
It's like cooking it right away.
- Alright, I got it, I'll turn it off.
Careful, be careful, and that's it.
I complete my dragon.
Alright, now I'll just let it cook.
Well, I think it's actually almost already cooked.
- Yeah, that's what happens when you're on max heat, bro.
- Devan, can you please hand me that spatula over there.
- Yes, I got you brother.
- Thank you, just put it in my hands, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Do you need another spatula?
- Nope, one's, uh oh, I already prematurely flipped it.
- Ohh, I feel like the flip for you
is gonna be really difficult.
- Here we go, three, two, one.
- (yells) Yes, I got it.
- That's a pretty great dragon.
- I am a master flipper bro.
- Didn't know until today, but, yup,
you definitely passed the exams.
I needed that spatula.
- Oh, sorry, it fell off the table.
I would get it for you, but again, small hands.
- Time to grab my spatulas.
- You got this, Devan.
- Try to get some of it off.
- It doesn't look cooked all the way through.
- Some of it is, but some of it isn't.
- I can only offer moral support
because my arms don't reach that far.
I can wave over here and give you little golf claps.
You got this Devan, you got this, bro.
- Thank you, I actually really appreciate that.
- Hoorah. - [Devan] You ready for this?
- I don't want to say this, Devan, but I don't quite
have confidence you'll be able to do this successfully.
- Really?
- I just need to put it out there.
- Alright, well I have confidence in me, so should you.
- I do now.
- Ready, set...
- That looks so good.
- Go, no!
- Wait is is stuck?
Get your, it's so bad, oh no. I can't even look, oh man.
- There we go, I fixed it, yay.
There it is.
(clapping)
- Ayy, alright.
- You get to comment down below and let us know who made
the best pancake, right now, it's on to the next one.
You challenged us to make Mera from the new Aquaman movie,
so right now, let's go.
I'm starting off by making the crown,
so we have like one peak here. - Hey, same.
Are you copying me?
I'm gonna hide my work.
- [Collins] Here, we got a peak like this.
- [Devan] That's a large crown.
- Now I'm gonna do the head.
Looks kinda like a cowboy right now.
Alright, we'll turn this on,
and then we'll give her some ears.
Next up, we got the eyebrows, and she's got great eyebrows.
Devan, those look pretty great, right?
- Yeah, those are actually really nice.
- Yeah, those are phenomenal eyebrows.
We'll give her two eyeballs.
We'll give her one right there, one over here.
Now, we gotta give her a beautiful smile, look at that.
Look, she's so happy.
Alright, we'll give her a little tongue right here.
Oh, a light gray inside the mouth.
You know, give like depth, and shadows right?
- Shadows and all that great art things.
- The inside of the mouth isn't gray though.
- What should it be?
- It would be a darker red.
- Fortunately, I have a darker red right here.
So, I guess she's gonna have gray molars.
Alright, then we give her a darker red in her mouth.
Oh, wow, Devan you're really good at this.
(thunder)
- Whoa.
(electric buzzing)
Whoa, you okay?
- Yeah, well you know what they say, right?
Luckily, lightening doesn't strike twice.
- Yeah.
Whoa.
The shortest storm ever.
- Now it is time to fill in the golden crown,
so, oh, I have an idea.
Devan, I'm gonna get an advantage on you right now.
I'm going to create an emerald gem in the middle of it.
Well, I just kinda told you what
my advantage would be but there you go.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna add an emerald gem in the middle of it, yes.
- I literally just had that idea.
- Oh, really?
- I think the thing about the gem,
it's very unusual looking, and a ruby in the center.
Alright, now time for the gold crown to be made.
So, we're gonna add the yellow in.
I'm just gonna add in the eyeballs.
Mine's coming along really well right now.
Now for the ears, I see Devan has those small line details,
so I'm gonna try to emulate the same thing.
For the difference, I don't really
know what lines the ear needs.
- Just look at my ears for reference.
Yeah, that is there.
- I saw that, and I'm now and artist.
The thing is she's got red ears
because she recently got embarrassed.
Like something happened, and she got embarrassed,
and so her ears turned red.
And now, the final step, time for the hair.
So, we're gonna fill this in first.
It's time to start roasting my pancake.
(laughs) It looks so good.
Proud of me.
Time to flip my pancake,
and this is gonna be so challenging.
Like this is one of the largest pancakes I've ever made.
- Dude, how are you gonna do this?
- [Both] Three, two, one, oh.
- [Collins] A perfect flip.
- Dude, nice job. - This is pretty phenomenal.
Thank you, man, alright.
- Whoa, that was a weak high five, bro.
- Oh, sorry.
- Alright, it's time to flip mine.
Three, two, one...
- We're doing three second like challenge.
We want to see if you can like this video in three seconds.
You ready, here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one, done.
- Ready, set, go.
- [Both] What?
- I only had a couple hairs fall off.
- [Collins] And only a couple hairs fell off.
- You get to comment down below who made a better Mera.
Right now, we're on to the next one.
You challenged us to make Simba from the Lion King.
I'm gonna start in a very different way.
I'm gonna begin with his ear.
Alright, so the two ears are done.
The thing about his ears is he has
this kinda like lining on the inside, oh.
You've heard of the circle of life.
This is the circle of Simba's ears.
This one over here we'll start with a super curly ear here.
Wait, are you making Simba or Yoda right now.
- No, I'm making Simba, bro. - That looks like Yoda to me.
That's Yoda's ear.
Just gotta add in the color.
(upbeat music)
And now, the most important part.
Time to make his full head, oh, face, face?
There's his face.
Alright, just gonna fill in his hair.
Oh no, Hoot-Dini. That means we gotta spin the
mystery wheel for our wild card.
You ready? - Yup.
- Here we go, three, two, one. - I'm hoping I get red.
I don't know why, I just want red.
Oh, I was so close to red.
- Oh no, what does yours say?
- What, upside down pancake.
- I have to use grabber hands to make the rest.
Like I can't use my hands.
- Nooo, what?
- Alright, got my little grabber hands.
- I can't believe it's turned upside down.
This mouth might look really wack.
- At least you have like regular hands.
I have to use these little grabber things.
- They look like little duck bills.
You know I've actually done exercises like this in art, so.
Yours is almost more interfering
with me than it is with you.
- I gotta scoot over here for one second.
- Really, bro?
- Maybe I just need to get the bigger one, here we go.
Oopsie.
Alright, here we go, gonna bring it over here like this.
Okay, there we go, lift.
- Grab.
- It's so unnecessarily long.
I gotta like scoot my chair back a little bit. (yells)
(upbeat music)
See it shaking, bro, it's just like.
- I see it, I can definitely see.
- Ah, support from the bottom, regrip.
- Whoa.
- I'm gonna put down one of these.
I'm only gonna use one at a time.
Pick it up, squeeze, there we go.
Wait, how are you so good even upside down, man.
Like I can't even figure this out regular way.
- These are actually exercises I've done before.
- What kind of workout has you
doing pancake art upside down?
- No, art exercise, Collins.
- This is so slow.
I don't like it.
I need to get some different claws.
Alright, I got some new grabby hands,
and these might actually be even worse.
There is like no way I can finish my pancake
'cause these grabby hands are all so bad.
I gotta control myself.
Unfortunately, I gotta go back to the big grabby hands.
Alright, here we go, lift, ah, c'mon!
Now I just gotta pick up the gray.
(dripping)
No!
- Oh.
- Oh, there we go, see if I push...
Oh, I broke it.
Gather a little bit up right here,
and then build the circle of the eye.
Alright, last thing I gotta do is just fill it all in.
I actually have quite a sophisticated plan.
We're gonna use a grabber hand thing, grab and grip.
Now I'm gonna lift it up like this and then spin.
Oh, I have a solution.
Gonna take this one here, and use this one
to just hold it in place, and then use this one
to push down and dispense the red, oh man.
- You just messed up his eye.
- [Collins] Yeah, it's ruining kind of a
lots of different parts of it right now.
- Dude, mine is so close to being done.
Please do not mess it up.
(upbeat music)
- Alright, we're gonna push it up over here.
There we go, look at those long shots.
Alright, gotta get out of the way.
You have to get out of the way, excuse me.
- Get on your side. - Let me just finish it.
- I will tickle you if you don't move.
- Okay, I'm moving.
Let's turn it up and let's roast it now.
- Bro, it's so messy.
It looks like a stampede came through.
- Wait, do you feel that?
- Whoa, whoa, what is going on?
- Devan, look out, look out.
(animals stomping)
That was close.
- Uh.
- You're going the wrong way.
Oh no, I just remembered, bro,
I'm gonna have to flip my pancake with the grab hands.
- Oh, that's gonna be so bad.
- Nooo.
Now, it's time to flip with my claw hand.
We reach into the side.
- What if you use the claw to hold a spatula, Collins?
- Alright, we got the spatula.
- [Both] Oh. - Alright, we got the spatula.
- Oh, nice, alright go for it.
- Three, two, one.
- Oh.
- There we go, unconventional flip,
but now it is on the table.
- Dude, it looks like a sunset.
Alright, it's ready to flip.
- [Collins] This looks so good, oh my gosh.
- Ready, set, go.
- [Both] No, no, no!
- [Collins] Rescue it Devan.
- Got it.
- [Collins] That looks so good.
You get to comment down below who won this round,
and right now, we're onto the next one.
- And just for the fun of it,
I actually made some extra pancakes like Godzilla here.
- [Collins] That looks so good.
- I also made Shazam.
- Dude, he looks all buff and everything.
- I know right.
And I made Cuddle Team Leader from Fortnite.
- And so did I.
This is my version of Cuddle Team Leader from Fortnite.
- Looking good, man,
- Exactly, the structure is intact.
See I can hold it by the ears, and it stays up perfect.
Well, the thing is I'm a little bit hungry,
so let me just grab something first, here we go.
- What, no, how do you...
- Oh, I am sorry, oh no.
- My pancake.
- I'm so sorry, man.
I just had to get little food.
- Take your almonds.
- I'm sorry bro.
I trained him really well so check this out.
Doug.
- Hey, Doug.
- Sit.
(crashing)
Pretty cool. - Sit.
- Hey, Doug, wave.
- Hey.
- Doug, speak.
(roars)
- Okay.
- Sorry, takes a little bit of getting used to.
- I think you might have cooked my pancake.
Are you sure you can handle that dragon?
Maybe you should just stick to this one, let go of Doug.
Just handle this dragon.