- What's up? (funky instrumental music)
It's Collins Key and welcome
to the second annual pie eating contest.
I started this last year during Thanksgiving time
and basically, how this contest works is I have
to eat a pie in one minute.
So last year I ate this kind of pie,
which was massive and there was no way
that I could eat it in a minute
and so this year, I've got a slightly smaller pie.
(laughing)
- That gun sucks.
- You blame it on the gun?
So this year I have to eat this pie in the one minute time
and for those of you guys who are wondering
why Devan's here, besides trying to shoot me with nerfball.
Basically, Devan's only job is to make sure
that I don't eat this pie in one minute.
So he's gonna do everything he possibly can
to distract me from eating this.
So we're gonna give this a shot
and whoever loses this is gonna get smack cammed
by the other person with a handful of whipped cream.
So make sure you guys watch until the end to see
how this whole thing turns out and yeah, let's get into it.
Alright, so we have one minute.
Here is the pie.
Devan, (lids clattering)
(laughing) okay, great.
(whipped cream spraying)
We're gonna get a little bit of whip on there first.
(laughing)
That was not smooth at all.
- Three, two, one.
Okay, so you know this round.
(laughing)
- You didn't say begin!
(laughing) - I have to say begin?
- Yeah, go.
- Alright, begin! (bell ringing)
Okay, so this round I'm not even actually worried
because my strategy this year, as opposed to hitting him
in the eye a ton, (slapping)
(yelling)
I'm actually just gonna add a bunch of volume
to his meal, so--
- I'm already halfway done, dude!
(laughing)
- I actually added a ton of grapefruits
and of course, some lifesavers.
So enjoy that. - What?
- And now, to hit him in the face.
(slapping)
- Ow. (squeaking)
- Try another one, oh!
And the socks attack!
(yelling) Oh, snap, get him.
(laughing) (yelling)
There's no way you're gonna do it.
(groaning) (plastic clicking)
Tape those ears around. (laughing)
(video tape fast-forwarding)
Oh! (laughing)
(yelling)
- Well, the competition is over and the results are in
and it looks as though Devan won--
(yelling)
again. - That's what
I'm talking about. - I don't know
how it happened.
I don't know how it happened-- - I do.
- But-- - I'm just a beast
at doing this, man.
I'm really good.
- Okay, ow.
(laughing) (groaning)
It's like on my hair, okay.
It's time I guess for Devan to smack cam me,
so if I can just get out of this stuff.
(groaning)
That actually hurts my hair, hold up.
Oh God, ow.
Dude, why'd you put it like all in my hair?
Okay, hold up.
I've untaped myself--
(yelling) (laughing)
- I missed.
I just have to do it again.
- What was that, bro?
(smacking) (groaning)
(laughing) (smacking)
(whipped cream spraying) - No!
(whipped cream spraying) (spitting)
- That doesn't work.
Not smart. (slapping)
(yelling)
(whipped cream spraying)
- My ear again!
(yelling) (whipped cream spraying)
- No! (slapping)
(laughing) My eye!
(whipped cream spraying) (laughing)
(spitting)
Bro, you're crazy!
Tell if you guys enjoyed this video
and if you guys want a third annual pie eating contest,
let us know by liking this video
and also comment down below,
what is your favorite food to eat on Thanksgiving?
And also share this video with your friends
because as you guys can tell, we did get smack cammed
and we got pretty messy. (laughing)
And this week's Keeper of the Week is Maria,
so congratulations Maria. - Yeah!
- We love you so much and if you want to be the Keeper
of the Week, all you've gotta do is just be super active
on all my-- - Got jacked again!
- Different platforms, liking, commenting, subscribing.
Make sure you have all my notifications on
and you could have a really good chance
of being the featured as Keeper of the Week.
What are you doing?
But yeah, congratulations, Maria, we love you
and everyone go give her a follow right now.
What are you doing? (laughing)
- I don't know.
- That's like tapping my face, okay.
Alright, well that is it for this video.
Make sure you guys go follow Devan
on all of his social media links.
They're gonna be down below-- - Do it down below.
- In the down bar.
- Thank you.
- Really?
No. (laughing)
And yeah, happy Thanksgiving, guys.
Whip cream mic drop.