- What's up, it's Collins Key,
and for this video
I need someone very special to join me.
So everyone please welcome
my brother, Devan.
Hey! - Hey!
- Oh, dude, it's, sorry, I messed that up.
My bad.
Hey! - Hey!
What's up? - What's up guys?
Today, we are going to be doing
the Pie Face Showdown.
The only thing we are missing right now
is a whole bunch of whipped cream,
so let me try this.
Hey! - Hey!
- All right guys.
So we now have the whipped cream
and here is how this challenge is going.
There are seven extremely intense rounds.
And as with every video that we do on this channel,
we are taking things to the next level.
And we're not just gonna be gettin'
hit in the face like just
a little bit of whipped cream
put on this little hand thing
that smacks you in the face.
No.
We are getting hit in the face with a full pie,
but we're missin' the crust,
so give me one second.
(clapping)
Whoa! - Whoa, okay!
- And there is one more twist.
Each round, there is going to be
(burping) a disgusting item
mixed in to the whipped cream pie
that is going to be smashed
on the other person's face
and the loser has to have their mouth open
as the pie goes directly into their face.
Whoever loses the most amount of rounds--
- No.
- They get hit in the face
with the biggest pie of 'em all
that has cocktail of
every nasty ingredient used.
And so you do not wanna lose this challenge.
That goes down at the end of this video.
So make sure you guys stick around for that.
And also give this video a big thumbs up
if you guys wanna see a Pie Face Challenge,
only our entire body
gets smacked with a giant pie.
I wanna make the world's biggest pie
and have a giant Pie Face Challenge.
So if this video gets enough thumbs up
we will do that.
And comment down below
what type of pie should we use if we do that video.
Also, I'm giving away a drone
on my YouTube channel.
All you have to do if you want to win
is just let me know by liking this video.
Comment down below,
what would you name your drone,
and you must be subscribed to this channel
and have my channel post
notifications turned on.
I'm also giving away an iPhone 7 on my Instagram,
a GoPro on my Twitter.
If you want all the rules for those giveaways
it's all down in the description below,
Or just watch that video right over there.
And go follow Devan on his social media.
All of our links are down below.
Without any further ado,
let's jump into it right now.
And this is the Pie Face Showdown.
- Nicely done. - Let's do it.
(bell dings) Round number one.
We are kicking it off with something called
mustard greens. - Ew.
- Which does not look good to have in a.
(sniffing)
Oh. - Oh.
- That's not gonna be good
so I definitely want to win round number one.
Somehow I got the girl cut-out.
- I don't know how that happened.
- Don't know how that happened, Devan?
I just gotta win.
Gotta show that I've got some girl power.
So what we're gonna do right now,
we've got our.
We can cut that out, right? (beep)
So we've got our whipped cream,
hey, hey - Nicely done.
- All right here we go.
We've got the whipped cream.
Gonna put this on there right now.
Oh. What? - What?
Dude, you must have done something wrong.
- Let me try it like this.
Whoa. - Whoa.
(spray can hissing)
- Why is it doing that?
We've gotta go quickly.
All right, here we go.
So put our head in.
Two, one, go.
(game clacking)
- No.
(laughing) (bell dinging)
- I actually got so panicked
during that first round
I forgot which way it needed to go
and so I saw it going that way
and I'm like,
it's going to hit me in the face.
(tape squealing in reverse)
All right, here we go, Devan.
You are going down.
It's time to add this nastiness.
- No. No.
- And bro, you have to keep your mouth open
as this hits your face, remember.
That's part of the rules here. - What?
Oh. - Oh. (evil laugh)
All right here we go, we're just gonna to mix it all around.
Oh, jeez.
- Oh, no!
I think I'm gonna throw up.
- Oh, this is so gross.
Round number one.
Three.
His foot's shaking, you guys can't see,
his foot is shaking on the ground right now.
Two.
One.
(spitting and coughing)
(laughing)
This is gross.
No, get off me.
No.
- I think I might throw up.
Those two tastes just do not go well together.
- All right, and now the first ingredient
goes into the massive pie right here.
- I really hoping you get this.
- The mustard greens-- - I'm hoping you get this.
- Remember, whoever loses the most
has to get hit in the face
with a cocktail of everything.
I'm literally crying right now.
Round number two.
Let's get it. (bell dinging)
Now you know this wouldn't be a Key brothers
challenge without some eggs involved at some point.
So we have some eggs here.
- That's true. - So the next pie is gonna be
whipped cream and eggs.
And we've taken off the faces because, just, no.
- Wait, I want to do this.
- Okay fine, yeah, you kinda get to.
Oh, jeez.
Bro, that last one looked so nasty
so I do not want to lose this at all.
- I don't either, three, two, one, go.
(game clacking)
- No.
No.
- No!
(bell dinging)
Yes!
Yes.
I'm so ready.
(spray can hissing)
Oh.
- [Collins] This is going to be so gross.
So nasty.
- Wait. (egg thuds)
Oh, what?
That's not even part of the challenge.
(laughing)
- What are you doin'?
- It's the anticipation.
Dude, what was that?
- I'm sorry. - Bro.
Uh uh.
- Like, whenever I see eggs
there is just this feeling
that I need to crack it on someone's head.
Ew, it's all yolk-y.
The yolk's on me. (drum and symbol beat)
We are now naming this the jackpot pie.
(slot machine bells)
- So, before I hit him in the face with this pie
I'm going to take a little bit of this
since we don't have enough eggs left and just.
Ew.
- [Collins] It's like eggs that are like, half scrambled.
So we've got some eggs shells as well.
I'm just gonna add that for some flavor.
- Is that gonna hurt if that hits your face?
- Do I have to do this?
It's just such bad-- - It has to be open.
Bro, open.
All right, three, two, one.
- Ow, my nose.
Ow, my nose.
- No, you can not hit me.
I did not hit you with that.
You can not hit me with that. - Okay.
Okay.
All good.
I'm all good.
(saxophone jazz)
(bell dinging) All right guys.
This is round number three and we have.
Oh. - Oh.
- We have a whole sardines.
Like, we have a whole sardines.
I need to win this round.
- I need to win this round.
- I don't want a full sardine goin' in my mouth.
Here we go.
This one, that one's done.
All right, Devan if you could please reposition
it back to the middle.
- All right.
(spray can hissing)
- May the best hand win.
High five.
Psych. Okay, here we go.
Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
(game clacking)
- Oh no, it's too close to me.
No.
No. Yes. - No.
- Yes.
Yes.
Yes. No.
No.
No. - No.
- You have two hands.
(bell dinging)
You had two hands, Devan.
- I used all resources to my ability.
- I don't want a full sardine in my mouth.
(spitting) (spray can hissing)
- This is so nasty.
- I'm so not excited.
- That's a huge one.
I'm already. Dude.
With the sauce?
That was unnecessary.
First he went with the two hands.
Now he put the sauce in there.
Bro.
Bruh.
(gagging) The smell of it.
- This looks bad. - It's quite overpowering.
- This looks really, really bad.
Ready? - No.
- You gotta open up your mouth.
You have to, bro.
That's not open enough.
Bro.
All right.
Three.
Two.
(yelling)
- It burns, it burns my eyes.
(gurgling)
- Okay, let's get paper towel then.
I've got some paper towels. - Rescue.
Rescue my face.
It's actually burning my face.
(yells)
It went to my eyeball.
- I think it's making it worse almost.
- Yeah, it is, I know.
- Oh. - What?
What?
- Oh, it smells. - What?
- I didn't realize how bad it smelled.
You just wafted some my way. - I know how bad it smells.
I didn't do anything.
You did this to me.
Now we are on to round number four.
(bell dinging) Kimchi.
- [Devan] What?
- How do they fit all that kimchi in there?
You can't even put the top back on.
For those guys who don't know,
kimchi is one of the
nastiest ingredients I've ever used in a challenge.
I first discovered it when I did a video with Glozell.
We did a smoothie challenge and it annihilated us.
It's very important that I win this round.
Number one, so that I don't get that dumped on me.
And number two if I don't win this round
I lose the entire challenge right now.
- It is very important that I win this round.
- This is a make it or break it round right now.
Put it on the hands.
(spray can hissing) That's good.
- Okay, ready? - Nope.
- Three, two, one.
(game clacking)
No, no no no no!
You're moving it.
You're moving it. - Yeah.
- You're moving it.
No.
- Yeah! (bell dinging)
Here we go.
- No.
- Yes.
I like this one.
- That's just way too much now.
That's excessive.
- First I'm gonna put a little bit of kimchi into this.
- [Devan] That's perfect.
Oh that's great, nice.
Great, nicely done.
- C'mon kimchi.
Work with me.
Oh. - Oh.
No. - Dude.
I actually would take the sardines over this any day.
- No, I'm glad I didn't get the sardines.
The worst thing about this one
is you know you're gonna get a piece of it in your mouth.
- [Collins] All right, here we go.
- Okay, I might actually throw up this one.
- Mouth has to be open, remember.
- Ah.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
I did get it all in my mouth.
(spitting)
- What do you need?
I have some sardine juice. - No!
Get that away.
Any time I breathe I'm just getting kimchi everywhere.
- You guys, give me a thumbs up
for the fact that we have taken a lot of,
we have taken a beating in this video.
(bell dinging) Round number five.
This is chopped clams in mystery liquid.
One of 'em goes in the, ew.
- Why you gotta do it like that?
- [Collins] It's just chunky.
- [Devan] You're going to get some on me.
Ew. - It smells like decay.
Right now it's a tie game.
Devan.
Let's do this.
All right, here we go.
All right, Devan. - Yeah?
- May the best man win.
We start on the count of tree.
Shrub.
Bush.
Tree.
(game clacking)
- You started early.
You're pushing it my way.
- No.
No!
(bell dinging) - Yeah!
Yes.
- Oh no.
It's just all liquid. - Bro here we go.
Here we go.
- Can you like, not do the liquid?
Maybe just the clams.
Like just need the clams. - Oh, I'm doin'
all of the liquid, bro.
- [Collins] It's the mystery liquid of the clams.
- [Devan] Oh, I gotta do this fast.
This is goin' on your face right away.
All right, bro, you ready? - No.
- You gotta open-- - Just be careful with it.
- Three, two.
He hit my hand.
- Oh, I got your hand?
- Yes.
- Can I get some paper towel?
Ow.
I'm not happy.
And we're on to round number six.
(bell dinging)
For this round we've gotten creative
and taken all the things you would
normally put on a hot dog,
mustard, relish and pickles.
And we'll be putting them in a pie.
This is the most important round of this entire challenge
because if Devan wins it's game over and he gets to
hit me in the face with this pie.
And if I win this round then it goes to the tie-breaker
for round number seven.
And then who knows what's going to happen.
(spray can hissing)
We're going back to the one hand only rule.
- What?
- No more of this two-hands shenanigans, all right.
We're goin' back to the basics of the old school.
- Okay, fine, all right. - One hand.
So place your head down.
All right, here we go, three, two, one, go.
(game clacking)
- No. - Yes!
- No.
- Yes.
Wait, it didn't even get you.
- I know, you were pushing it that way.
(bell dinging) Wait, no.
- I got you. There we go.
- This is actually better than what was about to be on me.
- Here we go.
(spray can hissing)
- That looks really good.
Why don't we just leave it at that
and I'll just kinda - No.
- take these.
No? You sure?
- I'm pretty positive.
- Oh.
- Yeah, that looks pretty gross.
All right, here we go, so we've gotta add some into
the jackpot pie here in the middle.
Oh. - Oh.
- This stuff disgusts me.
- [Devan] Oh, why?
- I'm gonna try to do a long shot with the mustard.
Oops, I can get this, I can get this.
(laughing)
Then we've got the pickles last.
Okay, the smell of it.
- [Devan] There's like, no whipped cream in there, man.
- This one is making me sick just lookin' at it.
Devan, you ready?
- I'm ready, let's just get it over with.
- This thing is just overflowing with goodness right here.
All right, Devan, open your mouth.
I actually apologize in advance for this one
because this is disgusting.
Ready?
Three. Close your eyes.
Make sure your eyes are closed.
- I need to see it comin', man.
- Two. Really?
If this gets in your eyes it's game over.
One.
(spitting)
Dude, don't do that.
- I need a paper towel.
You know what?
It wasn't as bad as I expected it to be.
- I'm not going to get you again, I promise.
You can feel my hands, I have nothing in my hands.
- Just give me a paper towel.
- Okay. (thump)
- Now this is burning my eyes.
Ow, it hurts the eyes.
- Did you get it in your eyes?
- Ow, I opened my eye for like, a second.
(whining)
- Here. - Whoa.
I'm good.
- Dude, your eye is so bloodshot.
- I'm good. (camera snap)
This is it.
(bell dinging) Round number seven.
The round you've all been waiting for.
The tie-breaker.
Whoever loses this is getting a pie
(slot machine bells)
with all the nastiest ingredients
from this entire video
in their face. - I'm so nervous.
- So much on the line right now.
Protocol on this one Devan is of the utmost importance.
Head on the game.
Hands on the button.
This is a free-style round.
You can use two hands.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- You started early.
Now you're pushing it out--
(bell dinging) - No.
Dude, no. - Yes.
Yes. - Dude no.
You distracted me.
- Yes.
- Dude, no.
That was so fast.
- That was, how did I?
- Oh my gosh.
- Like I just want to flip the table right now.
I am so mad. - I am so happy.
(sad music)
A little happy dance. - All right guys.
This whole pie is about to go in my face.
Dude, I can't believe I lost.
I am so upset right now.
This whole nasty pie is about to go in my face.
- All right, here we go. - Wait, wait.
There's one thing I wanted to let you guys know first.
I want to make sure that we can
continue to expand this Keyper family.
Make sure the Keypers from around the world
can enjoy these videos.
So if you guys speak another language
I would really, really appreciate it
if you could translate these closed captions on the video.
There's a link all the way
in the bottom of the description.
So if you click on that.
Translate the video into your language.
You'll also get a credit on my video.
Like, your name in my description
giving you credit for translating and making sure
that Keypers all around the world can enjoy this.
So we can get the Keyper family even bigger.
Show love to people around the world.
- All right, here we go.
- Are we really doin' this?
- Yes we are.
- We're doin' this for real.
- Oh.
- [Collins] No.
Dude, do we-- - [Devan] Oh.
- There's like a whole fish just like, living in it.
- I don't wish this upon anyone.
I feel bad, man.
Here we go. - Mouth open?
- Yep, it's your rule. - Ah.
Okay.
No, I don't want to do it.
Go.
(spitting)
- Oh.