(upbeat music)
(pop music)
(text alert)
- Who is that?
- I don't know.
- Maybe you should check.
(deep sigh)
- Look up.
(text alert)
Back right pocket.
Oh.
- What is that?
(text alert)
- Open door.
- Open the door.
- That was lame, dude.
- Yeah.
- Well, I need to go anywhere but here.
- So why aren't you in Malibu?
- Well, I was.
I'm back now.
I've been thinking a lot about what I said, and I mean it.
I want you to be happy and if I thought Eddie was right
for you then I wouldn't be standing here
but I don't think he is,
and I think,
maybe I could be.
- So your magical pixel girl didn't work out for you
and I'm like what, your consolation prize?
- No, God, it wasn't that at all.
Okay Leone was great.
She was funny, she was cool.
- Then why aren't you with her right now?
- Because...
- She what?
- You're going to say it's lame.
- No I won't.
I promise.
- She wasn't you.
- God, Collins that isn't fair.
You had years to tell me that.
Years.
And now you pick the day I'm moving in with my boyfriend?
- What?
- Yeah, he's been asking, so I decided to give it a shot.
Look, I understand that you haven't really gotten along
with him or even liked him, but he loves me
and he knew what he wanted.
- What?
Okay.
(pop music)
- What's up baby?
- Hey.
- I wanted to show you this.
- What's up?
- Check out this video.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
(laughs)
Okay, I have to go study.
- No.
- I know.
Babe, I have a test tomorrow.
(sighs)
- Yeah don't touch that board, I'm gripping it.
(paper rip)
(pop music)
(record beep)
- What's up guys, it's Collins Key and first of all
I know it's late at night right now
but I just had to post this.
I had to get this off my mind and yeah, I am aware
that things have been really crazy on my Youtube channel
for the last few days and there's one more crazy surprise
that I've got for you guys and I'm doing a meet-up in L.A.
So first of all, even if you don't live in L.A. I still
have you covered because this is going to be live-streamed
on my Youtube channel.
So, it doesn't matter where in the world you live, everyone
can take part in this, but if you are in L.A.
I would love to see you there.
So, I'm going to put all the information
you need to know in the description.
It's happening this weekend.
This weekend.
So again, make sure you guys go check out all those details
and again, we'll be live-streaming it
so I've got you covered.
I just wanted to do this to say thank you because you guys
have been with me throughout this entire process
and just showed me so much love and support throughout
this entire thing and I've had a ton of fun.
You guys were figuring out so many clues and I don't know,
I feel like we got closer throughout this entire process.
For me, even though things didn't go exactly how I thought
they would, but I think what I've learned is that if you're
brave enough to just take risks
and try out new adventures and new experiences,
they don't need to go how you thought
they would and a lot of times they won't, but that's okay.
That's not the point.
The point is you get to learn about yourself,
about who you want to be, and who you want to be with,
and I think--
(knocking)
- Hey.
Cool if I study here?
(pop music)
- Uh so yeah, like I said,
(laughs)
I'd love to see you guys at the meet-up and yeah.
(pop music)