- What's up guys?
It is Collins Key and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now, after my previous sibling tag
with my little brother, Devan,
everyone was like commenting, requesting for him
to be in another video.
So, here he is.
- [Both] Ey!
- Whaddup?
- Oh.
- See how you miss the high-fives.
- Yeah, you always look for the elbow.
(laughing)
- Alright, I'm ready.
- Today, we are going to be doing
the sibling test challenge.
So basically, we've each written down a list of questions
that we should know about each other.
Every question that we get wrong,
the other person gets to throw an egg at us.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- Okay.
♫ Rock, paper, scissors
Darn it!
I go first.
What was my first drawing ever?
- A classical reproduction of a Leonardo DiCaprio painting.
- Nailed it.
It was not. - What was it?
- It was a scribble.
- That's not an actual drawing.
Anyone can say, my first drawing was a scribble.
If it was like a scribble with an intention,
that's a drawing.
What's one specific quality
or attribute I look for in a girl?
- Eyes? - There's two.
I like eyes and I like a girl with a cool smile.
- Okay.
- I like girls with a nice smile.
- What trick could I never do on my scooter?
- Tail whip.
- Darn it!
- Dude these are so easy.
Name one pet peeve of mine.
- Nose hairs.
(laughs)
- Out of nowhere?
When have I ever expressed a disliking or pet peeve-ishness
for nose hairs? - Maybe that was his head.
- Yeah.
What was my favorite to draw when I was eight?
- The booty.
- No.
It was not the booty.
Yoda, in battle.
- Really? - With light sabers that--
- This one's super easy but if I could be an animal,
what animal would I be?
- A squirrel.
What was my first still-life drawing of?
- A naked person.
- Nope. - Dang it.
- That's not a still life--
- He has drawn naked people though.
- That's a life drawing thing.
It's not, it's--
- You've drawn naked people though?
(laughing) - Yes, I have.
- Like he has drawn nude people.
- Alright, so moving on,
it was a still-life.
It was a pear.
- A pear? - What?
- What was the name of my first magic book?
- Mark...
Let me (mumbles)
(laughs)
I can't--
This one's hard.
This one's really hard.
Something complete guide to magic.
- You didn't even get it right.
It's Mark Wilson's Complete Course in Magic.
- Wilson!
(screams) - Dude.
- Who was my favorite Japanese comic book artist?
- Ukazima Mishagawa.
(laughs)
- That wasn't even a real guess.
- Morigato Shugesaya.
Naruto.
Naruto, shuriken.
I don't know, I'll give it one more shot.
Ugize Zimbabwe.
- Okay, no.
When I was 10, it was--
Hold on.
- (laughs) And you don't even know bro, come on.
- Takeshi Obata, I think.
I'm not sure.
- What position do I sleep in?
- On your left side.
- No.
- What?
- Face down, booty up.
And I sleep with my arm like this.
If your arm was like a pillow.
It's like (sighs).
Right now, I could have pulled down my pants
and you guys won't even know it.
- He just did.
- You don't even know though.
He could be lying to yo.
(laughing)
Where was my first Instagram picture taken?
While you're waiting for him to figure it out,
you might as well go check it out.
My Instagram is @CollinsKey , see what my first--
Hey! - Hey, mom.
- Who's that?
Hey mom.
We're over here. - Did you bring food?
- Yeah, did you have food?
- Yeah. - Do you have food?
- What is that?
What's in the paper bag mom? - Food.
- Is that food?
We'll be right back.
Sorry guys had to take a little break
to get a little bit of snackage, you know.
- What game have you always beaten me at?
- Imma go with Battlefront.
- Nope.
It was chess.
- How many times have I injured my fingers?
Like serious injuries.
- Once.
- Nope.
Five times.
- Five times? - Yeah.
When I fractured my pinky,
stung by a bee on my middle finger.
- That's not a serious injury.
- Yes it is.
- That is not.
- I dropped a burning hot pan while pulling out
of the oven on my finger, it burned.
- It's not. - I got--
Yeah, that's a serious in--
For your fingers.
- Dude, I did that to my lip once.
Do you remember that?
I was eating a piece of pizza and (grunts)
and I think the cheese just like, fupam!
And it was like swollen.
- I'm not saying like life threatening--
- Bruh.
Bruh. - Okay.
Oh, I'm gonna sneeze.
(sneezing) - Yeah, turn up the death!
I was trying to do it like the beat drop.
- I slammed my finger in a door.
- Everyone does that!
- I mean, seriously slammed it.
Fine.
- So you only had like two.
(laughs)
- Who was my favorite character in Spiderman?
And it's not the obvious.
- Venom.
(laughs)
- Nope, it's Spiderman.
- That's stupid.
- It's all about perception.
The obvious could be like a villain.
- No it couldn't. - That's like--
- The one obvious person in Spiderman
and that is Spiderman.
- You didn't say the right answers so you got it wrong.
- What was my favorite-- (laughs)
What was my--
(laughs) My god.
What was my fave--
Dude.
What was my favorite event when I did gymnastics?
- The floor!
- No.
High bar.
- What? - Yup.
Like this video right now if you want to see us juggle.
Your juggling is so sporadic.
Oh really?
Like that hurt.
These are like the light--
Ah!
Okay, that actually kind of--
That kinda ow!
That kinda hurt.
Dude 'cause you got me with this fucking--
oh my god.
Hit me with the spikey one.
- Sucker--
(yells)
- Well that is the end of the questions
portion of this video, now it's time to go outside.
And throw them eggs.
And it's the part you've all been waiting for.
Watching Devan and I annihilate each other with eggs.
Give this video a thumbs up
if you're excited to see the craziness.
Let's get it started. - Let's do this.
- Got the eggs.
- Don't throw around my head dude.
- I won't dude.
Ooh! (laughs)
I'm so sorry, dude.
I didn't mean to do that.
Right on the head.
(laughs)
(yells)
(laughing)
(groans) (laughing)
It didn't break.
(laughing)
It didn't even--
Final throw.
I'm going for the booty.
Alright, stand there.
(groans) Oh, I hit the booty!
- That hurts so bad.
You're not breaking this on my head.
(laughing)
- I'm so nervous.
- Oh yeah!
What the heck?
(laughing hysterically)
- That was like way past my head!
Oh my god.
Ow! (laughing)
Ow.
Please hit me.
(groans)
Yeah, you got me.
Oh god.
(groans)
Dude you cannot hit me to save your life.
(groans) (laughing)
Oh my gosh.
- Only two!
- Oh my god.
(groans)
(groans) One egg!
Hey!
Cheater! (Devan screaming)
Yeah, we got all of my hair.
I have like egg hair.
This is crazy.
(groans)
- Oh my god.
Ow!
What was that?
- More!
(groans)
- Ha-Ha, you suck!
What the heck?
- No!
- Dude, you are the worst thrower.
- I hit you several times.
- Ow!
Ow! (laughs)
(laughing)
What the heck? (laughs)
Oh my god.
Ow!
My shoulder!
(groans)
(mumbles) the side of my booty!
Oh, my camera! (laughing)
Yo.
That was my camera, dawg!
Alright, well that was egg throwing madness.
If you guys enjoyed this video--
that was super painful.
Please give it a thumbs up. - That was painful.
- Thumbs up.
To let us know that you actually enjoyed this video.
And also why don't you guys comment down below
what other challenges should I do with Devan?
Also, I'm gonna put all of the social media links
in the description down below.
Be sure to go follow him.
Thank you for watching the Thursday vlog.
Peace.
Oh, he's gone!
This is a big mess to clean up.
Bye!
(EDM music)