What's up, it's Collins Key,
and welcome to my brand new life hack video,
and for this video, to follow along,
all you're gonna need is just a soda can and a quarter,
and I've actually signed my quarter on both sides
so you guys know this is the exact same quarter
throughout my entire life hack.
And what you're going to do,
just start tapping your quarter on your soda can,
you're looking for a soft spot.
Doesn't make sense...
But right there. Yeah, that's it.
So check this out, if I take this quarter right here,
and look at this, we go, one, two, three.
Looks pretty crazy, right?
And check this out, from the outside you can't even tell
that anything's happening, the outside is totally fine.
Even the bottom,
you can't tell that anything just happened on the bottom,
and the top of course is still factory-sealed
but this is where it's crazy.
Because if you take your can and if you shake it,
I don't know if you can hear that, but listen to this.
(can rattling)
Now, I just shook it out
so I don't want to splash you guys at all,
but check this out, if I take, if I open up here,
oh my gosh...
Let's see.
I actually brought along a cup right here,
we'll just dump it out.
(soda pouring into can)
And check this out.
(can rattling)
Look at this.
I want you guys to see, check it out.
You guys can see right there, you guys can see the quarter
with the signature on it.
So, this life hack right now blew your mind.
If you can't wait to try this out,
make you guys share it with your friends right now,
and also give this video a big thumbs up
if you want me to do even more crazy life hacks
like this in the future.
And also, comment down below,
what are some other random objects I should use
in upcoming, future life hack videos?
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel
(laughs) I love you guys so much.
I'll see you guys again soon. Bye.