- What's up, it's Collins Key and today I'm back
for another super-sour challenge
and there's a twist on this one,
but, first, I need someone to help me out,
so, everyone, please welcome my brother, Devin.
Hey! - Hey!
Whoa, this is ginormous!
- Huh?
So, as you guys can tell, we've got some giant candy
here, these are actually lollypops, they're not
maracas, but before we...
Oh, I dropped it, no!
- Why would you do that?
- Ah, it's probably broken.
I've ruined the video before it's even started,
but we have a challenge for you guys,
we want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications
in five seconds, that's all the time you have, here we go,
five, four, three, two, one, done.
If you were able to subscribe and turn
on the channel post notifications in that amount of time,
comment down below, "Keyper Squad," right now,
that way we know that you're like a subscribe ninja,
that's a thing.
Can I have my lollypop back?
Oh my...
Well, now that I'm still alive and I have my lollypop back,
I want to let you guys know that I'm giving away
a drone on YouTube, an iPhone 7 on Instagram,
a GoPro on Twitter,
if you want to enter all these giveaways,
the rest of the rules of the giveaway are all down
in the description below, so be sure to enter
and Devin, I think we're gonna lose our taste buds
for about a month after doing this video,
so if you guys can give it a thumbs up for encouragement
for the fact that we will not be able to taste food
for an entire month, that would really mean a lot.
I'm going to try to explain this challenge as quickly
as I possibly can.
Basically, we have giant candies right here,
one person will close their eyes, the other person
will feed them a candy.
If they guess wrong, they have eat a super sour candy,
but if they guess right, the other person has to eat
a super sour candy and at the very end,
one of us is going to be eating the world's largest
sour candy, so make sure you guys stick around for that,
but right now, without any further ado, let's jump in
and let's get started, clink it.
Oh jeez.
To decide who goes first, we're going to do a very
quick game of rock paper scissors,
so here we go,
Rock paper scissors shoot! - Rock paper scissors shoot!
- Oh man!
So, Devin, you get to choose what candy you want
to use first and here we go.
So Devin's gonna go pick out his candy right now
and I'm realizing, I'm going to be able to hear him
as he's unwrapping it, which I think will kind of
give it away, so I'm going to close my eyes
and I'm gonna put on these headphones,
that way I can't hear anything, here we go,
I'm not using this as a blindfold
I'm just closing my eyes, and this is like the extra
step to make sure I can't do anything,
so, alright there we go,
please don't smack me in the face with a giant lollypop
'cause that would hurt.
- Alright, we have the first one right here,
can't see anything, right, right?
No, okay we good.
- I can't hear you, did you say something?
- What?
Ooh, look at that, that is insane.
Just take a huge bite.
What do you think it is?
- It's chocolate coin!
(talking with mouth full)
- You ate some of his hair.
- So, since Devin lost, I get to choose a sour candy
from the bag of pain.
- Oh, that sounds painful.
- So, we're kicking off with some good stuff,
we're gonna do some Toxic Waste.
- No, that stuff is so bad!
- So, here you go Devin,
oh, it's just a regular sized candy,
alright, well, Devin, you have to take out a handful
of them, not just one, a handful,
this is a huge candy video, you can't go for a little bit!
Our thoughts and prayers are with you
in this difficult time.
- This is so many of them, my mouth is watering already.
(wailing)
- Bro, oh my gosh, dude.
- Woah!
- And on that note, we're moving on to round number two.
- I'd better win this round.
- Alright, Devin, now it is your time for the
headphones of silence.
- I have to say, my taste buds are kind of damaged,
I don't know how I'm gonna do this.
- Yes.
There's one more thing I want to let you guys know
about, Devin, Devin, sorry, bro.
One more thing that Devin doesn't even know about
is that this right here is the necklace of shame,
it is the largest sour candy necklace in the entire world
and what's gonna happen here,
Devin is losing this challenge, so he's gonna put it on.
- What's happening?
- Nothing, just, you're good, just don't even worry
about it and, hey, close your eyes, no cheating,
alright, guys, so this is my item right here,
I don't think he's gonna be able to guess this one,
I don't really even know too much about this item,
so here we go, let's...
What?
I'm very disappointed right now, look at this,
like I thought it was gonna be massive...
- What just happened?
- I just got ripped off, that's what just happened,
I thought it was gonna be a huge one,
this is ridiculous.
- Whoa, what just happened?
- Well, yee!
- A bunch of stuff just hit me.
- I'm so disappointed, guys, alright.
Like tilt your head back.
- Wow, this is tasty.
- Well, yeah, 'cause it's not sour.
- Huh.
Very sweet, bro, I have no idea.
- Well, you had the first part of it,
it's a Sweet Tart, and I thought they were gonna be
massive, but look at this, this is such a ripoff, bro.
It's like a whole bunch of little ones in a big one.
Never judge a book by its cover.
- Wait, do I have to do more sour stuff?
- Yup, sorry, bro.
Alright, here we go, pass me the bag of pain, please.
So, I went kind of hard on the last one,
so this one I'm gonna go a lot easier,
so I'm just gonna go with some of these ones,
the nice little Cry Babies.
- What?
- These ones are, by far, not the worst at all.
Oh, Devin, in case you're wondering what the
necklace is for, basically, whoever loses the most
amount of rounds has to eat the necklace,
and this is like kinda how we keep track of
who's losing this challenge right now,
so you're wearing it.
- Great.
These are so bad!
- Yeah, they're the worst!
- I'm about to cry.
- Yo, there's a literal tear.
He's actually crying right now...
Dude, your tongue, let me see it.
Oh, it looks pretty messed up.
Alright, here we go, round number three, let's go.
- I am really hoping that you mess up on this one
and get it wrong.
- Yup, these are the headphones of silence.
- Alright, here we go.
- Nope, you've gotta stick your tongue out.
- Okay, again.
What, it tastes like a Hatchimal.
- What?
- It like has the texture of a Hatchimal egg.
- How do you know what that tastes like?
- I don't know, it's just kind of like
it's like a surprising taste,
it's a Hatchimal!
Is it a Hatchimal?
It is?
- No, it's a Jawbreaker.
- I thought it was a Hatchimal.
- This is massive.
- No, that's a face-breaker, that will break
your whole face, okay?
Holy cow.
- Now, it's my turn.
Oh, some toxic waste, Smog Balls!
- These are the worst, I hate these.
(talking with mouth full)
- You gotta chew 'em, bro.
Bro, I left mine in for a while.
Dude, your teeth are yellow and green!
Okay, don't actually break your teeth.
(whimpering)
Yes, some retribution!
Bro, that is really bad.
- Are my teeth bad?
- Yes. - What?
- Those are really bad.
- No!
I have to brush my teeth, and we will proceed
on to round number four.
You're still losing the most, so you still got
that nasty necklace on, but, let's do it
Take the headphones of silence.
- I thought you were gonna throw them at me.
- Yo, this thing is huge, oh my gosh, look at it,
it's taller than Devin's head,
I gotta give 'em credit, man, they do not
play around.
Take a bite, take a bite.
Just keep your head still!
- This is familiar.
Wait, bro, is this a Snickers bar?
- Oh no!
- Yeah, did I get it, did I get it?
- You got it.
- Alright, I am so happy right now,
wait, does this mean that you wear the necklace?
- Well, no, we're tied, so like...
- I think you wear the necklace.
You are currently... - No!
- Just hang it over your ears.
Sour Farts candy, what?
- What, no!
- Here you go.
- Just dump it in again?
- Of course. - Alright.
- What does it smell like? - Potent.
Alright, here we go.
(talking with mouth full)
- What, is it that bad?
- Oh yeah! - Really?
Wait, let's see your tongue.
Ha, it's so many different colors, it's crazy.
- Next round, let's go.
Ow, you just kicked me, bro.
- Oh, that smells good.
- Can I smell it?
I just wanna smell it, okay?
Totally stick it in my face.
Can you be gentle, please, Devin?
Can I ask for you to be gentle?
- It's in front, okay, there you go.
- It's a lollypop.
- Yeah.
- Kinda helped when you hit me in the face.
This thing is awesome, by the way.
- I just can't imagine a little kid
eating this whole thing.
- It would take like a decade.
Not only do you get to experience the bag of pain again,
but you are, right now, the current loser.
- No, I forgot about this.
- So, here you go, the necklace of shame,
oops, well I'll just leave it like that.
So, Devin keeps saying that the Warheads are not
bad at all, and, so, if you think they're not
so bad, we're gonna do some Warheads right here.
There you go.
- Oh yeah, doesn't smell bad at all.
- Here you go, and you have to chew these, too,
you made me chew those, like...
I had to chew the Smog Balls.
You gotta chew these, bro.
(talking with mouth full)
- Ow, ow.
- What are you doing!
You said these weren't bad at all, bro,
what are you talking about.
You good?
Alright, well Devin, officially, is about to
quit this challenge and so before he quit,
we're moving on to the next round right now,
let's do it.
I wish that I got this one because these are
delicious, these giant candies are the best,
so Devin doesn't know what I'm talking about.
These are huge.
- I smell something.
Smells like chocolate.
It's a York Peppermint Patty!
- A what?
- It's a York Peppermint Patty, I could taste the mint,
bro, this is delicious, ah, love this.
- Yeah, you got it, yeah.
I want to try it, bro, this looks so good.
- It's like a breath mint and a candy bar mixed together.
- I lost, though.
- Woohoo! - No!
- Not only do you get some sour candy,
you're also getting the necklace back!
- No, you keep it on.
- We're tied. - We're tied.
There's no reason why I should have it on!
There's no reason I should have it on in a tie.
- Ooh, this looks kinda crazy, do this.
Sour Power.
- I don't think this is gonna be that bad,
like I think this will be the best of them all.
- Okay, well if you think that,
I'm adding in these two as well,
so you can take these.
- That's like three candies at once!
- I'll even help you open them, I'm that kind.
- This is going to be literally horrible.
Alright, we're doing this and we have some of these,
these ones, I remember, were horrible,
the Sour Punches, they won't even come out
they're so angry.
Alright, here we go, going with these first.
(moaning)
- Whoa, your breath smells really good.
- No problem at all.
That was delicious. - This is great.
Alright, on to the next one.
- This is the round it all comes down to,
the final round, whoever loses has to eat the
sourest candy necklace in the entire world.
We're tied right now,
so I don't think it's fair, I'm not gonna wear this,
you're not gonna wear this,
we're just gonna hang it back here just like that,
and whoever loses this has to eat that candy necklace.
- Next up, we have this, but it's actually not
gonna be this, it's actually gonna be these Sour Fart
candies.
Okay, Collins, tilt your head up, okay, open your mouth.
- Ow!
Not cool, I'm gonna close my eyes 'cause I wanna win this
fair and square, but bro, not cool.
- Okay, this time, we're actually doing this.
This is five pounds of chocolate.
Alright, open your mouth, Collins.
- Mm, it is a Hershey Bar.
- No, I was so hoping you wouldn't be able to get it!
- Yeah! - Really?
- So, Devin lost the challenge, so you have to eat
the necklace of shame, plus eat whatever's left
in the bag of pain.
So, here we go, Devin, get ready to enjoy all of this,
in the meantime, guys, please give the video
a thumbs up for the fact that this seriously
hurt a lot.
You might want to try this first off.
Here we go, pop one of these in there.
(crying)
- That was instant death!
- And then, also, we've got some a little bit of
Sour Patch Kids, so Devin, here, open up your mouth
right now.
- Wow, this one's terrible.
- And, also, if you guys translate these videos,
you will get credit in the description of these videos,
so make sure you guys do that, that would really mean
a lot, translate these videos into whatever
language you can, right now, here we go,
last thing, open your mouth.
Some Sour Skittles!
But, of course you have to eat your necklace, though,
you gotta eat your necklace,
there, take a bite out of it, there we go,
that's it for this challenge, I love you all so much,
we will see you guys again very soon, bye!