- [Devin] Dry ice smash!
- [Collins] Wait, what? Holy cow, dude!
- [Devin] Look at that!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
- You challenged us to make
three insane superhero gadgets
out of food.
We're making an Infinity Gauntlet,
Captain America's shield,
and the Green Goblin gadget
we're literally throwing off of
our balcony, so let's go!
- [Devin] So this is going to be
the filing for my gadget!
- [Collins] Time to make some spun honey!
I've got some green food coloring
in honey right now.
Going to turn on the contraption over here,
do not try this at home!
For our first edible art piece,
we're making a Green Goblin Gadget from Spider-Man.
Three
- [Both] Two
One!
- [Devin] Should I be, like,
stepping back at all?
- [Collins] Dude!
- [Devin] Yo!
- [Both] Whoa! Oh!
- [Collins] That is so cool, man!
- [Devin] That is amazing!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
- [Collins] This is like Spider-Man's webs right here!
Turn off the machine, and now it's time
for me to get in there with my hands and
collect all the different spun honey right now.
What is that?
[Devin] I got some heavy cream here.
I'm going to put into this bowl.
- [Collins] Here we go.
I'm going to reach in, let's see
how it feels! Oh, my G--owww!
It feels like spider webs!
Oh, I don't like it!
I mean, look at it!
It looks like spider webs!
- [Devin] I know!
- [Collins] Oh, now, man, it's so crazy! Okay!
- [Devin] Okay, now I'm adding some food coloring.
- [Collins] Boom! A bushel of spun honey
right here, man!
- [Devin] Now it's time to add the dry ice
into this mixture here.
- [Collins] Wait, what?
Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait--
- [Devin] Three, two, one
- [Both] Oh!
- [Collins] Look at it bubble, dude!
- [Devin] Yes!
- [Collins] Holy cow?
- [Devin] This is amazing!
This is going to be
the inside of my gadget!
- [Collins] The inside is going to be bubbling?
- [Devin] Yeah, it actually activates it and
it bubble like this.
- [Collins] Now I'm making the first
element of my Tesseract.
So, as you do that,
I've got my ice over here!
Woo-hoo! Whoa!
That was kind of insane.
All right.
I meant to grab it in a normal fashion,
- [Devin] Uh huh.
- [Collins] It didn't go that way.
So here we go. We've got a whole bunch
of ice, here, and there's a cool way
we can pop off the top, Devin.
We're going to use a plunger, here,
and check this out! Here we go, watch!
We go one, two, three
- [Devin] Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
That top's going to blow!
- [Collins] It's a sanitized plunger,
don't you worry!
Instead of just dumping it in,
that'd be too easy, instead we're going to go like this.
A fa la A fa la la la
- [Devin] You're going to break this! What are you doing?
- [Collins] It's a slight dance, Devin!
- [Devin] Put it in like that.
- [Collins] All right, we'll get a
behind the shoulder yeet yeet!
- [Devin] Completely missed. - [Collins] Did I get any in?
- [Devin] Not even one.
- [Collins] I completely missed. All right, here we go.
We'll dump it all in. Bam! Ice bucket number one is in.
- [Devin] All right!
Look at this!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
- [Devin] It's working!
- [Collins] When did that happen, man?
- [Devin] Just now!
As you were dumping all that in there!
All right, my D.I.Y. frozen treat is done,
and now it's time to slice off the top of
my pumpkin in a very cool way!
- [Collins] (karate sound) Not like that.
- [Devin] Even cooler than that.
I've got my power washer here,
I've got the pumpkin secure.
And now, it's time to slice off the top!
- [Collins] Oh, I almost tripped on my way in!
But I am here right now!
- [Devin] Yeah, and tarp the floors.
- [Collins] So, the water power from this
is going to be able to slice off
the top of the pumpkin.
- [Devin] Exactly.
- [Collins] Click over here to vote
if you think water will be able to slice
off the top the pumpkin.
- [Devin] I think it will.
- [Collins] I don't think so, man.
It's water, bro!
- [Devin] All right, here we go!
Three, two, one. No! It's mostly flying back at me!
Oh, yes!
It's gotten more powerful!
Oh!
It's kind of working!
I think this is going to take a while!
Oh, yes!
It worked!
All right!
Now I just have to clean this thing out!
- [Collins] Dude, that was absolutely nuts!
- [Devin] I know, right?
It's my new favorite tool.
Now I'm using a nice method
to gut this thing.
- [Collins] Wait, what is that, Devin?
It looks like a portable windmill!
- [Devin] Exactly!
It might even blow you away. You ready?
(lightning)
Three, two, one
(energy beam)
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Devin] Yep, totally worked.
- [Collins} Yeet!
- [Collins] Well, as you do that, Devin,
here we go.
I've got a couple substances over here.
I've got some Isomalt--
- [Devin] Oh, need some mixing?
- [Collins] NO!
- [Devin] No? No mixing?
- [Collins] No!
- [Devin] I'll make sure not to mix!
- [Collins] Do not try this at home!
It's hot Isomalt!
I'm going to pour into the ice!
It's going to create an insane art piece on the inside!
Three
- [Both] Two
One
- [Collins] You better watch out, Devin,
I'm coming for the art throne!
- [Devin] All right!
- [Collins] So, now, let's see,
I'm just going to pour this around like this.
- [BOTH] Whoa!
- [Collins] It burns through the ice!
- [Devin] Now it's time to gut the inside
of my pumpkin!
- [Collins] I'm getting splattered with pieces
of pumpkin, bro!
- [Devin] Yeah!
- [Collins] Like, there's seeds flying out--
- [Devin] It smells real bad now!
- [Collins] Three, two, one.
And dip it in like this.
- [Both] Ohhhh!
- [Devin] That's so nice!
- [Collins] I wonder if they're going to,
like, intermix and mingle in the middle, man.
It's like a little meet and greet.
A little dating app.
- [Devin] I know, right?
- [Collins] Here we go,
last bit of isomalt in in.
Got a whole bunch of hot water here,
and this is the coolest part.
It is time to get out the isomalt art.
Three
- [Both] Two, one!
- [Collins] Just going to put it in like this.
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Devin] Nice!
- [Collins] Look at it, man!
It's melting the ice
but not the isomalt!
- [Devin] It looks so deliciously blue!
- [Collins] Bam! It is in!
Gonna move this over here!
- [Devin] Whoa! Okay, okay, okay!
- [Collins] Time to pour out some of the
water here, oh my gosh, it got heavy.
You ready? Here we go. Three,
- [Both] Two, one.
- [Collins] I'm just going to lift
it up like this.
All right, here we go.
Oh!
- [Devin] That was close!
- [Collins] Yo! Boom! Look at that!
- [Devin] I just gotta finish gutting
this thing out!
- [Collins] All right, here's the big reveal.
- [Both] Three, two, one. (music)
- [Collins] Yo! - [Devin] Whoa!
- [Collins] Look at that! - [Devin] Whoa!
- [Collins] That's so insane!
- [Devin] That looks absolutely nuts!
- [Collins] Look at these pieces, man!
- [Devin] Good job!
- [Collins] These are art pieces in and of themselves!
Boom! Nailed it!
- [Devin] All right, gotta turn on the helium here.
- [Collins] Wait wait wait wait wait wait what?
- [Devin] I'm making an edible balloon.
- [Collins] What?
- [Devin] What am I waiting for?
- [Collins] When did this happen?
- [Devin] What do you mean?
- [Collins] I just look over, you've got
a dangling green thingy!
- [Devin] Exactly!
- [Collins] All right, I'm going to take this
right here, I'm going to drop it inside my cube.
You're going to be able to blow up
a balloon with that?
- [Devin] Yes.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Devin] Let's see if it works.
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Collins] Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off!
Turn it off, turn it off!
- [Devin] Yes!
Look at that! Look at that! Look at that!
- [Collins] Okay, hold on, here's the real question.
Will it float?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] Oh, my gosh, it's by a string!
- [Devin] Oh!
- [Collins] Oh!
- [Both] Oh!
- [Collins] It's got stuck to the ceiling, though!
It's stuck to the ceiling!
- [Devin] Yes! - [Collins] Oh, my gosh
- [Devin] Dude! - [Both] Yo!
- [Devin] Oh, no, it popped.
All right, well, this is going to be
the inner lining of my gadget.
- [Collins] Thing is, this is going to be a tesseract.
I want some alien abilities coming out of this thing.
My tesseract does not fit in this thing,
so we're going to have to get a little bit creative here.
Kind of bop some edges.
All right, we've got the claws here,
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- and now it's time to bust this thing up!
- No, dude, you need glasses!
Safety glasses
- Safety first, of course.
don't try this at home!
- [Devin] Safety first!
- [Collins] Be very careful there with that!
- Careful, Collins, careful, close your eyes!
There you go, there you go!
- All right, there we go!
- [Devin] We got it! All right! All right!
- [Collins] Perfect, thank you!
- [Devin] All right, all right, I need mine now.
I gotta go, very, very safely.
- [Collins] I'll keep my claws pointed down.
Okay, I'll shuffle this way. All right.
- Where are they?
Oh, here they are.
- [Collins] Can we trade places?
- Yes, yes.
- [Collins] I'm going to shuffle this way again.
It's going to slice off the side, a little wa-chink.
What are you doing?
- [Devin] I'm filling up on the inside
for the inner lining of my gadget.
- [Collins] It doesn't look like
it's working, Devin.
- [Devin] It's not.
- [Collins] Three.
- [Both] Two, one.
- [Collins] Oh! - [Devin] Oh, no!
- [Collins] Yes! And then, I don't want to break too much
of it, but here we go. Let's do three, two one-
(yells)
Woo hoo hoo! Lastly, I've got some
agar agar here, I'm going to add in.
It's going to solidify into a cube,
and look just like the Tesseract.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] I'm just going to pour this in.
- Whoa, okay, all right!
- So, here we go, just going to pour it in,
like this, all the way up to the very,
very tippity top.
Whoa! That was close!
Now I'm going to set this off to the side
to set, and it's time for the next part of
my Goblin Gadget.
All right, next I've got to carefully slice
my watermelon with a shovel.
You know me, I'm very controlled and very precise.
- [Devin] What? - [Both] Three, two, one. Yow!
- [Devin] Whoopsie!
- [Collins] I missed it! Oh my gosh!
All right, we're going to get
a little side hit on here
with three, two, one, yow! Oh!
- [Devin] Well, then!
- [Collins] Here we go,
We have the top here.
We're going to grab some Wolverine claws,
again, do not try this at home!
- [Devin] Check out this awesome pumpkin carving tool!
Look at this!
It's motorized!
- [Collins] Here we go!
- It's getting watermelon juice on my pumpkin!
- [Collins] Bleah! There we go! Nice!
(grunting)
(yells)
Oh, it's heavy like that.
There we go, man.
At least, time for a plunger, man,
this thing's brand new, fully sanitized,
here we go, three, two, one.
Let's see, oh! - [Devin] Whoa!
What are you doing?
- [Collins] I gotta plunge the inside
- -Why? Why, though?
- of it, man, that's how you fully
clean it out, man. Because this is
how you do it, man!
- [Devin] I'm just going to continue back over here.
- [Collins] I think, all in all,
my watermelon's pretty nicely cleared.
Oh, no! I ripped a whole in the side of it!
- [Devin] That's what you're concerned about?
Not the fact that your entire melon is all over our counter?
(popping)
- [Collins] You know, I think we're
going to have to start all over with
a brand new melon and go
a little more carefully like you've done, Devin.
All right, we've got all the elements,
time to put together our Green Goblin Gadget.
I've got my Tesseract here, it's been fully set.
But I gotta say, man, this is a lot more giggly
than I expected it to be.
- [Devin] This stuff looks so delicious!
- [Collins] What is that?
- [Devin] This is my D.I.Y. yogurt.
- [Collins] Oh, so you're going to put that on the inside?
I take my Tesseract, and I've got to
be very quick with this,
I'm going to flip it upside down.
So, oh, my gosh.
Looks like Play-Dough, almost, man.
- [Devin] Exteme concentration going on
over here, all right?
- [Collins] This thing is so much heavier than I expected.
So, here we go, I gotta do this very carefully.
Three, two, one. Wa-boom! - [Devin] Did it work?
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] I'm going to lift it off,
you can hear it, I can hear it coming off.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- -Oh!
- Okay, bam! (screams)
NO!
I don't like you!
This almost ruined it all, man!
- [Devin] Wow!
I have mycelium husk slime, here.
- Wait, wait, wait, let me see if it--
- [Both] Whoa!
- [Devin] I'm starting to add it! Yes!
- [Collins] Holy cow!
All right, so here we go.
So, we got the watermelon,
we're going to place this right here.
We've got to get the Tesseract up
and inside of it, so here we go.
Oh, man, it is,
(groans)
it feels so weird.
All right, let's see.
Let's lift it up like this.
Oh, it's falling apart, falling apart,
here we go, drip it in, drip it in.
(sound effect)
- Oh, no, no, no, no!
- [Devin] You broke the Tesseract, man!
- [Collins] I didn't break it Devin, it all
went according to plan! It just happened to,
we're just going to pick up the pieces
and put them in.
I gotta say, I was hoping it would stay
in a square shape, it didn't.
So, here we go. Spun honey is going to go in,
around the top.
All right, we've got all the elements,
now it's time to compile them.
Put them together, add the finishing touches,
and make these things look incredible.
We've got the finished Goblin Gadgets,
and these things turned out absolutely--
- I know, right?
- Insane, man! I mean, like yours is so cool,
I gotta say Devin was very kind.
He helped me out with a couple different elements of mine.
- Yes.
- So, here is the big reveal. You ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one. Ta-da!
- [Collins] Yes! - [Devin] What?
Dude, I cannot wait to throw these off of a balcony!
- [Collins] So, you get to comment down below
which one is going to look cooler when we throw
it off the top of the balcony and
do the drop test. We'll be doing that
at the end of the video.
Now, we're making Captain America shields
and I'm kicking mine off with a bang.
- [Both] Three, two, one.
- [Collins] It's in!
- [Both] (screaming)
(slow motion screaming)
- [Devin] Wait, how are you catching this?
- (slow motion screaming)
- [Collins] Oh, no!
- Dude!
- I'm trying to-
- What are you doing?
- Here we go, there we go, here we go!
And then we just pour it in.
- What are you doing? Is that it?
- [Collins] All things considered, that went
a lot better than it could've.
- [Devin] Are you kidding?
For the first layer of my Captain America shield.
I'm pouring hot isomalt on this exercise ball.
I've got a super-cool way of painting my shield.
Are you ready for this?
- [Collins] So, you're going to put the paints on?
- [Devin] Yes, I made some edible paint right here.
And then you just put it down, boom!
- Whoa! - Look at that!
- [Collins] That is, like, mesmerizing, man!
- [Devin] I know, right?
I'm going to reinforce my shield with some coconut!
- [Collins] And I've got a giant whisk here
because I am Whisk-Man!
Check it out! Bam!
- [Devin] Nothing's more solid than coconut.
(glass breaking off camera)
- [Collins] Oh! - [Devin] What did you hit?
- [Collins] Nothing!
- What are you doing?
- [Devin] I'm making a coconut blancmange
to reinforce my shield.
- [Collins] Ah, yes, nothing like a little coconut blanc-
- Blancmange.
- Blancwonge--
- I don't even know how to spell it.
- [Collins] All right, well, here we go.
You do that. Time for me to
whisk around my aquafaba right here,
what are you doing?
- [Devin] I bet you're jealous.
- [Collins] Of what?
- My liquid nitrogen.
All right, time to remove my coconuts.
- [Collins] And I'm adding in a whole bunch
of agar agar, and this is going to make mine
really thick.
- [Devin] Look! - [Collins] Holy cow!
What is going on?
- Now is time to smash it!
- Wait, wait, with a hammer!
- What?
All right, here we go--
- [Both] Three, two,
- [Collins] Wait, wait, wait.
Three second like challenge.
We want to see if you can like this video in three seconds.
You ready? Here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one! Done!
Three, two, one! Oh!
- (slow motion) Oh!
- [Devin] Wow!
- [Collins] Look at the inside!
- [Devin] Look at that!
- [Collins] I have never seen a coconut
filled this much, man!
I'm covered in coconut juice!
- [Devin] Serves you right!
- [Collins] It's delicious.
- [Devin] Now that I froze everything
I have to unfreeze it inside this pan.
- [Collins] Dude look at this!
The agar agars coming together.
Man, look at it bro.
- [Devin] Oh I can smell coconut already.
- [Collins] I just had an idea bro
What if we make aquafaba bubbles dude?
All right here we go, just going to pour in
some of the juice right now.
We're going to strain it out, lets see like this.
Check this out and this is what's going to get really crazy.
Gonna open up a tank of helium right now
and its going to infuse all the aquafaba juice.
And who knows what's going to happen next so here we go.
You ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one. - [Collins] Yoooo!
- [Devin] What! Dude!
- [Collins] Oh here's the question though
Because of the bubbles,
- [Devin] Yes!
- [Collins] is there any way of actually making it
float in the air, do you think?
- [Devin] Oh wait, yes! And be very careful
- [Collins] Yeah yeah!
- [Devin] Do not try this at home.
- [Collins] Exactly!
- [Devin] Here we go. Three.
- [Both] Two, one. Yooo!
- Oh, no, no!
- [Collins] Get it off the ceiling. Get it off the ceiling.
Get it off the ceiling. Get it off the ceiling bro!
- [Devin] Try it again. Try it again. Try it again.
- [Collins] Oh my god, it's like dripping all this juice.
Dude it floated up perfectly man.
- [Devin] That was awesome.
- [Collins] Yo, wait, wait, wait, I have an idea bro.
What if I actually just dunk on it?
- [Devin] Three, two, one.
There you go. There you go.
(football crashes)
- [Devin] I think you totally missed.
- [Collins] The way that the bubbles are going, I think it..
I think it worked.
- [Devin] Dude, one of the mic things fell off!
- [Collins] How did that get there?!
All right well we gotta, oh boy that's a
that's gonna be an issue.
This took quite awhile but I made some puffed rice over here
and I made it in the ginger ale that I used earlier.
See there was a purpose for it Devin!
- [Devin] Yeah well, I've been mixing around
this agar agar stuff for a while.
So now it's time to grab the Isomalt.
- [Collins] It's gotta be very carefully done.
- [Devin] Yooo! That looks so incredile.
- [Collins] Very carefully.
- [Devin] So now I need to do this one-handed
cause I got the silver leaf on the bottom.
- [Collins] Do you want me to help you out with this at all?
- [Devin] No, please don't.
- [Collins] I mean, it makes sense.
As you do that, I'm gonna strain out my rice over here.
- [Devin] All right.
- So here we are, just gonna dump it in here like this.
- [Devin] My shield is gonna be extra reinforced now.
- [Collins] All right let's see if you can waffle rice!
Here we go. Gonna add the puff rice in.
(murmurs)
- [Devin] I'm risking it all for this reinforcement.
- [Collins] Yeah, you're really gonna need it man.
Cause if you can get this and your shield will not break
when I punch it with my fist.
- [Devin] Exactly.
- [Collins] Here we go.
Gonna open this up on the count of three.
Three.
- [Both] Two, one. Yooooo!
- [Collins] I've got the aquafabo.
Now it's time to add in a whole bunch of my puffed rice.
Right now it's gonna dry out
and turn into the base of my shield.
- [Devin] We've don't a lot with liquid nitrogen
but we've never filled up a water blaster with it!
- [Collins] A what?!
Hold on.
(screams)
- [Devin] I gotta spray it on my --
- [Collins] All right now!
- [Devin] To get them cold and remember
do not try this at home!
- [Collins] Yes! Don't try this at home.
Oh my gosh!
- [Devin] Three, two, one.
- [Both] Oh!
- [Devin] It didn't work.
- [Collins] Did it go?
- [Devin] No! You can tell it's in here though.
- (mumbles) I lost my balloon, sorry I got it.
- [Devin] Okay!
- [Collins] I lost my balloon.
(screams)
- [Devin] Well, that really did not work.
So I guess I'm gonna have to try something else.
- Can you please hold this in place for me
for a second Devin?
- [Devin] Place them in here. What?
- [Collins] Can you please hold this in place for me
for a second. So here we go.
- [Devin] Yeah sure. Yeah yeah. Oh, oh! Dude! What?!
Are you kidding?!
- [Collins] I'm Sorry.
(chatters)
- [Collins] Can you just grab my balloon for me?
Over here we've got my puff rising aquafaba.
So time to actually add this on to the balloon
and use the balloon--
- [Devin] Here you go. Catch!
- [Collins] Gonna use the balloon as the mold
and the base of my shield.
I think the chunk will actually be able to weigh it down.
All right, so here we go.
Next up, just gonna grab the uh--
(shrieks) No!
- [Devin] What happened?
- Ah! I lost it!
It flipped off and collected a whole bunch of peanuts man.
- [Devin] All right I got it.
- [Collins] Thank you.
- [Devin] Here you go. Here you go.
Sorry.
- [Collins] Holy Cow!
- Next up, we gotta grab some red right over here.
So here we go.
How's yours coming along?
- [Devin] It's coming along pretty good.
It's pretty not blended up at all.
I have to blend this more.
All right the final step is to place down this screen here.
- [Collins] Is that from a screen window, Devin?
Dan's gonna be not happy about that.
- [Devin] My shield is way more important than our window.
Now I'm gonna squeegee it around.
- [Collins] That's not how you use a squeegee man.
I guess that's a creative way of using a squeegee.
- [Devin] It's true. It's not how you traditionally use it.
- [Collins] Time to combine all the elements
and make this into a true edible Captain America Shield
that will blow your mind.
We've got the finished Captain America Shield
- [Devin] Yup!
- [Collins] So here's the big reveal. You ready?
Here we go.
- [Both] Three, two, one. Ta-da!
- [Collins] Look at these things bro!
They turned out so brazy man.
- This is amazing.
- [Collins] So much work it took to get these.
So you get to comment down below whose shield
you think turned out better
and which one is going to taste better.
We spent a long time on these.
We will be trying them at the end of the video.
And stick around to see us throw
the green goblet gadgets off the balcony.
You challenged us to make edible infinity gauntlets
we could actually wear. So right now let's go.
- [Collins] I'm kicking off by making some crunchy honey
with honey and liquid nitrogen.
What are you making Devin?
- [Devin] I'm making Japanese jelly with agar-agar,
stevia, and water.
- That looks like some weird underwater aqua planet.
- [Devin] All right, now it's time to put the jelly
on to the subwoofer.
It's going on the top, dude.
This is how I'm going to mix my color.
- [Collins] All right, so here's the deal.
Gotta kinda move my honey around
just like the liquid nitrogen.
Try to get all parts of it frozen right now. Here we go!
Next up, we're gonna pull out this thingy here.
So here we go.
- [Devin] It's a strainer. That's what it's called.
- [Collins] Let's see if I can hook it on the bottom.
(screams)
- What?!
- [Devin] That is crazy.
- [Collins] Holy Cow!
- Whoa!
- [Collins] Oh! It just fell a part!
- [Devin] That is some crunchy honey.
Now it's time to turn on my speaker.
Three, two, one.
There we go! Oh, oh, oh, oh!
- [Collins] That feels like an alien right there.
Like an alien that would happen in Marvel.
- [Devin] I have to now put on some food coloring.
You might want to step back, so you don't turn purple.
All right?
- [Collins] Okay, yup. I'm going to uh--
- [Devin] Here we go, here we go!
- I don't know where to go!
- [Devin] Here we go!
- [Devin] Three, two, one.
All right, it's doing kinda--
Oh no! It's all over the table.
All right dude. I think it totally worked. Yes!
- [Collins] That's a life hack I never thought I would see.
As you're doing that, I'm just gonna keep
pounding this up into little pieces.
- [Devin] Now it's time to add some blue
right in here like this.
- Whoa! Look at that!
- Oh my gosh!
- [Collins] I'm blown away by this.
- [Devin] Wow!
Now I'm going to add some green in here like this.
- [Collins] It looks kinda like slime.
- [Devin] That stuff flies everywhere.
- [Collins] Yeah it's like projectile man.
Next up, we've got some stones over here.
I'm gonna use these stones to place in the mold
to act as the infinity stone.
Three, two, one.
(screams)
Look at that bro!
So here we go, just place it in the palm of my hand.
- [Devin] Yeah, go, go, go.
- Yes dude. Okay.
Fist bump, Devin.
- [Devin] Wait, wait, no, no, no.
- Fist bump.
- [Devin] Your aim is terrible.
- [Collins] But my fist bumps are great!
- [Both] Three, two, one. No! (explosion)
- [Collins] To get Devin back, it's very easy.
So here's how this works.
I'm just gonna twist the space stone.
It'll make a portal right here and Devin will appear.
So here we are. Three, two, one.
(grunts)
Yo!
- [Devin] You couldn't have made that wider dude?
- I'm sorry bro. It's a space stone. Okay?
- [Devin] The things you do to me on this channel!
- At least you get to see mayo man, right?
- [Devin] I went to like 5 different dimensions.
All right, it's out and there you go!
- [Collins] Wait, so that's gonna be your infinity stones?
- Yeah and you know what's next?
Liquid nitrogen.
- [Collins] Whoa!
- [Devin] All right! Time for some liquid nitrogen.
Okay, pour it right on top!
- [Collins] Like a direct pour on top?
Wait, why you blowing on it?
- [Devin] Cause it's so cool
Cause it's a lot of suds.
- [Devin] Three!
- Holy Cow!
- [Devin] Two.
One.
- Have you started yet?
- [Devin] Now I have. Now I have.
- Oh! It's like a cloud but yet
it's liquid at the same time.
- [Devin] Wow.
- It's so tough to tell where the liquid is.
- [Devin] Definitely do not try this at home.
All right, now it's time to break it up
into the infinity stones.
- [Collins] Oh Man! Here we go.
- [Both] Three.
Two.
- [Collins] Oh! I just had an idea.
What if you pick it up and then you just smash it?
- Oh, yes!
- [Collins] All right let's see this.
- [Devin] Trying to pick it up with these massive gloves.
- I wonder if it's gonna break or not.
Do you need help? Kinda like--
- [Devin] I think I got it. I got it. I got it.
Ready here we go.
- [Both] Three.
Two.
One.
Oh!
(slow motion roar)
- [Devin] I think this kinda beat yours already man.
- [Collins] I don't know!
- [Devin] My infinity gauntlet
I've got the silicon mold right here.
I'm gonna dust it with 24k gold.
Oh, look at this. It's a gold peach.
- [Collins] You're gonna take a dusted peach
and peach fuzz all over it
- Exactly
- [Collins] and place it in there.
Maybe you can use some of your chin peach fuzz.
- That's not there.
- [Collins] I can grow a full beard if I wanted to.
Check this out!
- [Devin] Wow.
- Yeah, I gotta go shave.
- [Devin] All right this peach is good and all
but I'm actually gonna use this feather duster here.
Nothing like 24k gold just flying everywhere.
- It looks like dirt.
Got some blueberries right here.
I'm going to be straining these
into a beautiful, pulpy muusche.
- [Collins] We're gonna take this right now.
We're gonna dump all my blueberries on the inside.
- [Devin] You need some --
- [Collins] No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Some feather dusting. You need some feather dusting.
- [Collins] I feel like I'm in the matrix.
- You don't want 24k gold in yours?
- [Collins] I do not.
Ah, the blueberries are going everywhere.
the blueberries are going everywhere.
Okay there we go.
And now my favorite part. Time to secure the bag.
(comedic drum)
Get it, because if it was money?
- [Collins] Three.
Two.
One.
Just a (mumbles)
a little squeeze like this.
(screams)
- [Collins] Oh! Look at it.
Oh! Oh man. Here we go. Look at that.
Oh, you see it coming through.
- [Devin] Look at this. This is just amazing.
(screams)
- [Collins] Ruined it!
Man, another bag.
- Hey I got another bag too but it's actually secure.
- [Collins] Is this for muffins?
- Disregard what it says on the bag.
- [Collins] I'd actually really enjoy some muffins.
- I don't know how to make muffins.
- [Collins] I want a muffin! If you can't make me a muffin,
Devin I will turn you into a muffin.
All right here we go. Three, two, one. Boom. There we go!
- [Devin] Wait, dude, what? Why am I muffin?
- Because I wanted a muffin Devin.
- [Devin] Am I Gluten free at least?
- Yeah I think you're gluten.
You're definitely a gluten free muffin.
- [Devin] Yes, yes, thank you!
- [Collins] Devin's a free range muffin.
Range around the store freely.
- Oh yeah.
- [Collins] Look at that juice come out.
- [Devin] All right, got some milk now. Time to fill it up.
- Here we go, gonna place some strawberries here
on the inside of my sock.
And this is actually Devin's sock.
Devin only wears yellow socks.
Fun fact that may or may not be true.
- [Collins] Next up, we're gonna take the sock
and do something very gentle with the strawberries.
- Sure.
- [Collins] BAM! Juiced on me.
- O-K, that is terrifying.
Oh man, Okay, All right.
I'm getting behind you.
- [Collins] That is how you juice up some strawberries.
- [Devin] Whisking is done.
Now it's time to fill up my mold.
I got it, I got it, Look at that.
All right, I only have to fill up one half
because I'm gonna use some triphical force
to fill up the other half.
And I'm using a tri-cycle.
- [Collins] I still think--
A tricycle?
- Yes!
- [Collins] That is one wheel of a tricycle's got 3 wheels.
(buzzer)
- Oh yeah, yeah, a unicycle!
- [Collins] You don't know your basic bike wheels.
Our strawberries is stuck in this middle portion
of the sock. So here we go we're gonna go here
It's gonna get like squeezes around.
- [Devin] I'm gonna use some triphical force to coat
the inside of the mold.
- [Collins] But first Devin, you must ride it
to show that you are worthy of using a unicycle.
- Here we go!
- [Collins] Do you even know how to ride a unicycle?
- I do not! I got it!
- [Collins] You got it?
You're like slipping backwards though.
- I'm riding it! Look at this. Amazingness.
- [Collins] I gotta say don't try this at-
(shrieks)
- [Devin] No hands. No hands. Wow.
- Holy Cow! He's riding it. Okay that's enough.
Devin that is enough. Holy Cow!
- I did it! I did it! All right!
- Devin just rode a unicycle for the first time!
- I learned it.
Now I just have to attach this to the unicycle pedal.
- With a carrot. - Not with a carrot.
- You sure? - Put the carrots away.
- I will not. - You don't need them.
(action noises)
- Not only does he do all of his own stunts,
he does his own sound effects.
- Yeet.
- Gotta put it up like this here, looks like this.
- Your unicycle in my face, Devin.
- And then, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- Yoooooo!
- Here we go! - That is crazy!
- And now it's going to coat every side of the mold.
- Time for me to construct the infinity gauntlet
around my hand.
- Whoa.
- We gotta knead the dough.
- I'm making some edible accents for my gauntlet.
Pouring the water in.
Then I have to whisk it super, super quick.
I gotta get it out! I gotta get it out!
- Wait its gonna fall out the bottom though
- Look, look.
- Wait so it's going to turn into noodles then or what?
- Moment of truth.
- Go for it.
- And now you just go right in!
- Oh! Yo!
- Oh! Yes!
- I gotta mold this thing around my hand.
There's a lot of finishing touches we gotta do,
to compile our gloves, put them together but.
- Look at these noodles.
- That's gonna be incredible.
So right now let's finish making the gloves.
We got the finished gauntlets
- Yep.
- and these things look so crazy.
Here we go.
- Three, two, oh wait.
- Five second subscribe challenge.
We want to see if you can subscribe to this channel
and turn on the channel post notifications in five seconds,
you ready? Here we go.
- Five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you could do that comment down below Keyper Squad
right now.
- Three, two, one, ta-dah!
- [Devin] Yes.
- [Collins] Look at how incredible these turned out.
- These are insane.
- Man it took so much work off camera.
You get to comment down below
whose edible gauntlet looks the best.
We'll be trying them at the end of the video.
We've got our edible Green Goblin gadgets
and I cannot wait to take these things
an smash them and break them, see what happens.
- Oh yes.
- But first we need to taste them delicately
to find out which one we like more.
We'll start off with yours.
- All right.
(grunts) - [Collins] It's dangling.
- I'm honestly not excited for this.
- Three, two, one.
(laughing) - Not weird.
- Woo! - Oh ho ho.
- Now it's time for mine so boom.
- Oh, geez.
- Now it's time to find out how this tastes.
Boom, here's my spoonful.
- I'm just gonna dig around in here.
- Three, two, one.
- Woo!
- Dude!
- Oh, oh, oh. (smack)
- Good job.
(smack) - Oh
(smack) - Oh, ow!
(sad music)
- Good job.
- Probably one of the best tasting things we've made
in a very long time.
- You made it.
- You get to comment down below
which one is gonna look cooler when we smash it
on the ground.
We got our edible infinity gauntlets
and now it's time to see which one tastes better.
I think we'll go for yours first.
How would you recommend going about eating yours?
- I think I should pull off some of the fingers here.
I'm going for the red stone.
- I'll take as many of the stones as I possibly can.
- Here we go, infinity knuckles.
- Oh wait, perfect, here we go.
- Three, two one.
- Whoa, woo
(gun noises)
- Whoa, Dude, these are like solid on the outside
and nice and creamy on the inside.
- Wow. So good.
- Very nice.
- I don't know if mines gonna be able to live up to that.
I'll take the ring finger here, oh look at it.
- [Devin] I'll take a nice pinky.
- Three, two, one.
(grunting)
- Wow, that is crunchy.
Very unpleasant experience.
- Yeah I gotta say the stone combined with the cucumber
was definitely very bizarre.
- Yes.
- But you get to comment down below
which one would you like to eat if you had the choice
and right now, we're onto the next one.
Got the edible Captain America shield,
which one do you think is gonna taste better?
- I think mine will, I think it's more unique.
Let's taste yours first then we can taste mine.
- Which part of it do you want to eat first?
- I wanna eat the star and the outer edge.
- [Collins] That's your piece of the star.
- Thank you, appreciate it.
- Three, two, one.
(grunting)
- The star is so brittle.
- Despite the burnt-ness.
- It's actually quite tasty.
Now it's time to try mine after that catastrophe.
- Catastrophe? - Yes.
- I mean hey it was like decent.
How are we going about eating yours, Devin?
- With the chisel.
This is for you, be very careful.
- This just looks like a chunk of ice.
- Gotta get some of this cardboard stuff under here
and there you go.
- Oh man, I don't want to eat some of the cardboard.
- Get a nice chunk.
- Three, two, one.
(grunting)
- Talk about crunchy.
(coughing)
This paper stuff tastes terrible.
- It tasted just like cardboard so.
- [Devin] Yeah neither of these were really a home run.
- You get to comment down below
which one do you think will be able to withstand a punch
and right now we're onto the next one.
- We've got the giant edible Green Goblin gadgets
- Yep (laughing)
and now it's time to throw these things down
on the bullseye.
We're looking for the biggest explosion possible.
Which one should we test out first?
- I think we should test out yours first.
- Devin how about you hop down there right now,
I'm gonna prepare it, the toss (laughing) this is heavy.
- That's a weak toss dude,
last time you chucked it really hard.
- Excuse me I'm preparing, go downstairs.
- All right, all right, sure.
- Prepare to give this thing a big drop.
- Power stance, right just power stance and then drop it.
- Yes, exactly, you're good at the power stance.
- On a scale from one to 10,
how big do you think the impact is going to be?
- Oh geez, I think probably a solid seven.
Mine's going to be way bigger let's face it.
- Yeah but see the thing is Devin,
bigger isn't always better.
Sometimes good things come in small packages.
- Whoa.
- In this case, Green Goblin gadget.
- Here we go.
- Three, two, one.
(yelling)
- [Devin] Oh my gosh.
- [Collins] What did I tell you dude?
Holy cow, I think that was a 10 bro.
- I don't know, yours is so gelatinous,
mine's gonna splatter everywhere.
- I don't know man, so you ready to challenge mine?
- Yeah, I guess we'll find out.
- All right let's switch spots.
- Got my pumpkin Green Goblin gadget
and I'm ready to do the drop dude.
- I don't think you are Devin,
I don't think you understand what it takes
to smash the pumpkin.
- What do you mean? Mine's going to go everywhere.
It's got the dry ice frozen yogurt.
- But what you're forgetting is you have a balloon inside
of your pumpkin.
Balloons ae soft, they float,
it's not gonna hit the ground with any force.
- It's getting dark and mine has glow in the dark slime so.
- Yeah that is kinda cool actually.
- Yeah but on a scale of one to 10,
how far do you think its gonna go?
- I don't know, I feel like it's either gonna be like a two
or an 11.
- What?
- I don't know it's either gonna go everywhere
or it's just gonna hit and not do anything.
- How does a two even make it in there.
- I just don't know if it's gonna be-
- It's gonna be 11 for sure, you ready for this?
- I don't know if you have the ability to
smash the pumpkin, that's all I'm saying.
(laughing)
- So you're stound to my ability?
- I mean slightly. - Here we go.
- Three, two, wait.
- If you want to win a 15 minute video call with Devin and I
text the word super to 81800 right now,
so pause the video, text the word super to 81800,
you'll automatically be entered in to win.
And let's see how this goes.
- Get back for this.
- Three, two, one.
- Oh man, go for it.
(screaming) (laughing)
- Yes.
- [Collins] Oh my gosh.
- That is a Green Goblin gadget right there.
- You know what, I gotta give a round of applause for that,
I did not expect it to go that big bro,
you just cracked the whole thing.
We just launched our brand new Keyper club
and if you become a member you will get exclusive access
to live streams, merch discount codes, custom emojis,
loyalty badges and exclusive content you can't see anywhere
else so click the top link in the description to join.
Only 4.99 a month.