- What's up, it's Collins Key, and
for today's video, I am doing something
that people have warned me my
entire life, I should never do.
Today, I'm gonna be trying coffee for the very
first time, but not just any coffee.
Today I'm trying secret Starbucks menu items,
and to do this, I need my brother to help me out.
Who also has never drank coffee his entire life.
Devan Key.
(snaps)
There we go, what's up bro?
There's no official secret Starbucks menu,
but there are a ton of amazing people online,
who have created their very own
recipes that taste like everything.
From Harry Potter drinks to Girl Scout cookies,
just everything in between, and
they post these recipes online.
Today we're gonna be testing out these items
to see whether or not they actually taste good,
and since Devan and I have never tried
coffee before, give this video a thumbs up
if you guys are excited to see what happens to Devan and I,
because we might just go off the walls crazy.
Please give us a thumbs up for our first
time trying coffee, and make sure you guys go
follow Devan on all of his social media.
- My Snapchat link is there.
- Mine is there.
- All my other links is down below, so let's go.
- Okay, we're gonna go like that,
we'll just start the challenge.
- Let's do it.
- We're kicking things off with a bang,
and this is Nutella, I have no idea how
this is gonna taste, but I'm so excited.
- Let's do it.
All right, I'm ready for this.
(moaning)
- I literally just clapped, and had water on my hands,
and the water clapped into my eyeball.
I got Nutella in my eyeballs, so I can't see too much.
This reminds me of the 100 layers challenge
with Nutella on my face right now.
It's a flashback.
100 layers of hair gel and Nutella!
(screams)
- I thought this one was good.
- Yeah this one taste delicious.
We're off to an amazing start.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, ouch.
This flavor is, Cinnamon Toast Crunch!
- Alright.
- I have no idea how this is going to taste.
So let's give it a shot, this is,
how are we gonna do this?
This is way too intimate, I cant do this.
- Should we take off the top, and then we like?
- Yeah let's do that.
- Hold up, this is gonna be tough.
Yay.
(moaning)
- This one, like, I didn't think these
would actually taste like it at all,
but this one tastes exactly like
a Cinnamon Toast Crunch, like this is.
- Yes, no, I literally.
- Wow!
- I taste the cinnamon, I tasted the toast!
- I tasted the crunch!
So the question I have for you Devan.
- Yeah?
- On a scale of one to 10, one being
the least accurate, 10 being the most
accurate, how accurate is this flavor?
- About a five, I just tasted a lot of toast.
I didn't taste a lot of cinnamon.
- Okay, yeah, you're actually right,
this does get a five.
- Yeah.
Next up, we have Thin Mints.
- Like the Girl Scout Cookies?
- Yeah.
- What?
- And I've never had it in coffee form,
but I have to say, the cookie form, so good.
- Okay, well you get the first sip, honorary first sip.
- Oh it's not coming out, not coming out!
- Is it good?
(moans)
- Really good right?
- See the thing is, I've never actually
had a thin mint in my life.
- Really?
- So I don't know what to compare it to.
- Well I have to say they nailed it, it's really good!
- Okay so I'll go with yours,
thin mints a perfect 10 out of 10.
- It was like blended up thin mints.
It was really good.
- Being a wizard, this one here is
super exciting for me, because this
is a Harry Potter butterbeer flavor.
So, give it a little mix.
- Go for it!
Yeah, let me try it!
- This one is delicious!
- Yeah it was really good!
- This one is my favorite one by far, so far!
- I don't know if butterbeer is.
- What was that?
(babbling)
- I don't know if butterbeer is
supposed to taste like something,
but I mean, taste like how I imagine.
- This one was delicious, they nailed it!
10 out of 10, Dumbledore would be proud!
This one has got to be the most
confusing item on the menu, because
it's called, Blue Drink, but it looks like this.
- It's pink.
- Alright, go for it.
How is it?
(groans)
Tastes like watered down yogurt, or blueberries.
- But like so watered down, that
it's like the smallest amount of yogurt possible.
- Yeah.
(groans)
Oh that was gross.
- But it's called Blue Drink, why?
Negative five for me, negative five.
- Negative 20.
- Whoa!
(laughs)
Okay.
- Next up we have cotton candy!
This is another confusing one, because
it's not pink, or any color at all.
- Well I guess it looks like cotton,
'cause cotton's white, so just like
cotton and candy, not cotton candy.
- It's not what you first think of, you know?
Alright.
- I'm not a big fan of this one,
I think it got, I'll give it like a three.
- I'd say it was pretty close,
I'll give it a five.
- And now we got a banana cream pie.
Not too excited about this one.
(loud exhale)
- It tasted like artificial bananas,
which is probably what it was!
- I don't like it!
So we've just been informed, that
this is actually the only one with
real ingredients, this is the only one
that actually has a banana in it.
- And it tasted fake!
(laughs)
I'd say a zero.
- Yeah it gets a zero.
Zero.
- Yeah, tastes as bad as the blue one.
- Yeah it honestly gets a zero.
Another confusing flavor, we have
the raspberry cheesecake, which
as you expect the color is, brown?
(laughs)
Like, I don't know, why is it brown?
- Hopefully it tastes like it.
I've never had a raspberry cheesecake,
but I'll try to combine the two flavors
in my mind and see what happens.
- Well.
- That did not taste like what you'd expect.
- A raspberry or a cheesecake.
Yeah I'm giving it a zero, there
is nothing more to say on that.
Like I've got the after taste in my mouth
right now, waiting for it to develop
into the raspberry cheesecake, but no.
It just tastes like coffee, so.
Boo.
Yeet!
(laughs)
The most all-american secret item, apple pie.
- Wow you went right in for that!
- Gotta swish it around in your mouth
there for a little bit, just gotta.
- You know what, that one got better as it went on.
At first I didn't like it.
It tastes like apple pie.
- 11 out of ten.
- Really?
- Oh yeah!
- I'd say an eight, tasted kinda artificial.
- Well I'm not expecting a real apple pie to be in there.
- But bro, I mean.
- Like if they put a real apple pie
in here I would be concerned.
- I wouldn't, I'd love that!
- This one was definitely a highlight of this video, so far.
This one is the most anticipated
of the entire video, this is,
the cinnamon roll!
- Nope.
- Doesn't taste like cinnamon roll at all.
- No it doesn't.
Oh, wait!
It has the aftertaste of a cinnamon roll.
So it doesn't taste like a cinnamon roll,
but the aftertaste tastes like what
the aftertaste of a cinnamon roll would taste like.
- No still nothing, this one gets zero.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I'll give it a seven.
- Thumbs up if you love coffee,
and thumbs up if you don't love coffee!
- Yeah!
- Well I want to get both people
to thumbs up the video.
And comment down below what flavor
would you love to see on the secret menu
at Starbucks, it can just be
your favorite food turned into a coffee.
I love you guys so much and I
will see you again very soon, bye!
(snaps)