- To help us with our next presentation, please welcome,
fresh off the Demi Lovato tour, magician Collins Key.
- Yeah!
(audience cheers)
- Hey! What's up? How are you?
- Good!
- So good to see you.
- Good to see you!
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, everything is great, but I just found out back stage
that apparently I put on the wrong shirt.
- How?
- Alright, well dude, this is a live show.
It's not like we can stop it so you can change your shirt.
- I think she said to just take it off.
- There's that option.
(audience cheers)
- Well, you know what?
Tyler, it's all good. Don't worry.
Im a magician, OK?
I got this. I got this.
- Everyone, I want you guys to keep your eyes
right here on my shirt.
I thought it would be kind of fun to use some magic
to introduce these next presenters.
- Yes!
- So, from your choice TV drama,
for the third year in a row, check this out.
Please, help me, everyone
and welcome to the stage the cast of
Pretty Little Liars!
(audience cheers)
- [Tyler] Say hello to Keegan Allen,
- TV star of the summer, Tyler Blackburn,
- And your choice male TV star drama, Ian Harding!
- Yeah!
(audience cheers)
("Rage" by Malibunewman)