- What's up it's Collins Key
and welcome to the Thursday vlog.
Now for today's video I need my partner in crime,
my little brother Devan Key to join me
in this chair right here, so.
I don't know how this is going to happen
but let's try what I always try
and this seems to summon the Devan.
Hey! (laughing)
It worked.
- I was like
I was literally just working on art
and just like appeared here.
You okay dude?
You okay?
- Yeah I was just crying, sorry.
But yeah, seriously I was just working on art,
like in my room.
- It's just like so funny
when I snap and you're always right there.
(laughing)
Like what was Devan doing before this?
Compose ourselves.
Today we are going to be testing out
as seen on TV products.
And this was inspired by the video we did a little while ago
where we test out 99 cent store products.
You guys enjoyed that.
And I guess you guys suggested that we test out
as seen on TV products.
I guess some other YouTubers have done it as well,
so we though hey.
- Let's do it.
- Might as well do it.
So yeah, also I'm doing a big giveaway
on my channel right now,
where I'm actually giving away
an iPhone, GoPro, instax camera.
So if you guys want to win that stuff,
all you got to do is let us know by liking this video
and comment down below what is
your favorite video that I've ever posted.
And of course you must be subscribed to my channel.
I'm also going to put a link
to that video in the description down below
and also right over there.
So you guys can go check it out,
find out all the rules you need to know to enter in.
There's a giveaway on Instagram, on Twitter.
Without any further ado, let's jump
- right into the challenge.
- It's not a challenge actually.
(laughing)
- I'm just so used to doing challenges.
- Yeah so jump into the as seen on TV product testing video.
The first as seen on TV product we are trying out is
jeggings!
So here you go Devan. - No, what?
- Yes. - No, no, no I'm not doing it.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm not doing it.
- What? Dude you have to.
I can't wear jeggings alone.
Come on bro.
I can't do this alone.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Thank you and dude these are with real pockets.
So for this video, I've actually done something
I've never done before and I've actually set up
an as seen on TV product testing area.
So we're going to go to that now,
look very professional, yeah.
- This is not going to be good.
- It's going to be great.
- No.
- We are now in the as seen on TV product studio.
We're about to test this stuff.
We got some jeggings and we're going to put these on now.
Bam and now we're in our jeggings.
- [Devan] These look pretty weird.
- So yeah it's like being in man tights.
What up guys?
Hey chillin' whoa!
- It's really like flexible I can like
(laughing)
- You almost hit me in the face.
Oh you can kick pretty high.
Just be like waboosh.
We're going to see if the jeggings improve our ability
to jump at all, because I don't know.
- What?
- I don't know we'll try it.
Three, two, one.
Okay, show them your (laughing)
We are not skilled in the way of how to wear jeggings yet,
so let's take these off,
and we're going to cut the camera guys.
Next up we've got the Pooch Smooch.
Which is (laughing)
Do like a choreographed dance like
So the Pooch Smooch is eliminate bad breath
for dogs of all sizes.
And since we don't own any dogs,
we're going to be trying these out on
- I thought you were going to say our snake.
I was like that's not right.
(laughing)
- Oh.
- Ah! No!
- It looks gross!
- No!
Ah!
- Let's get it nice and clean guys.
(laughing)
- You got it all over my mouth.
I'm done!
- The Pooch Smooch is not for humans.
Maybe for dogs, but this product is definitely,
definitely a fail in our book.
Next up I bought us some waist trainers.
- Yeah.
- I don't know what these are.
- Wow that is not (laughing)
That is not photoshopped at all.
- According to this it'll give us a thinner waistline.
- Oh my gosh.
- I know these photos are actually
low key kind of terrifying.
- Oh my gosh.
- All right here are the waist trainers.
Let's give this a shot.
- Mine's already been opened.
- I think it goes on backwards like this here
and then close it up like that.
And then what you're going to want to do
is you're going to want to pull these.
Oh my God, I can't do it.
- This can't be good for you.
- No.
Well this is the waist trainers.
Show the profile.
If you want to squeeze your entire body together,
they definitely accomplish that, that's for sure.
For this next
- What?
- I'm mean introduce you to do it.
- No.
- Fine do it.
- For this next one, I'm doing this
and it's called the Vegeta.
(laughing)
- That was the last time you are ever introducing something.
Oh my God.
Well what it's supposed to do is
it's supposed to make perfectly delicious pasta
without the carbs.
Great for gluten free diets.
Turn veggies into healthy spaghetti.
It doesn't sound very realistic at all.
- No.
- But let's give it (laughing)
let's give this product a shot. (laughing)
So for this I brought along an eggplant
and this is the one I grabbed.
- And this one's the one that I grabbed.
- So yeah, I'll give it a shot.
- Whoa!
- Okay, okay.
- It actually kind of works.
Although they're really thin noodles.
- There is no way that thing is going to fit.
It's way too big.
Oh!
Yes!
Never say never guys.
So I would say this is a tentative win.
- If you want eggplant noodles
and I don't know who does.
- And who wants eggplant noodles?
So I guess you really decide for yourself.
(laughing)
This next one here is something that I actually
would have loved to have in my room as a kid growing up
and that is a Hamper Hoops.
So basically it's like a basketball hoop
that you throw your dirty laundry into.
Pump fake dab.
And um yeah.
Oh we didn't just do that.
We're going to look back on that in like six months
and be like what were we doing
- One month.
If that.
- If that so without any further ado
let's go give this a try.
- Kobe.
- Oh!
Ow.
The edge got my thumb.
- You've done played yourself.
- All right I've got the Hamper Hoop
and Devan's going to shoot first so.
- I'm going to shoot some hoops.
- Let's do it. - Let's do it.
- Wo ho, that was so close.
He was so close on that one.
(screaming)
Oh!
All right let's test out the next product.
Next up is the one I've been looking forward to
the very most
and that is the Wubble.
- The what?
- I don't know it's basically a giant balloon thing.
- Wobble baby, wobble baby, wobble.
- You say that in every video
and I always try to cut it out.
It's just so weird. (laughing)
I feel like in every video there's one part
where you're like wob- cut it.
But yeah.
I decided to put you on blast right now.
You didn't even know that.
When I'm like editing a video,
oh like there Devan goes
with his wobble, wobble, wobble baby.
- I only say it in videos.
- You do.
Let's go test it out.
- Let's chest it out.
- What?
Let's chest it out.
First we need to pump.
We need to pump it up.
And let's see we have Vaseline first
which needs to be applied using a q-tip.
I think that should be enough Vaseline.
All right.
- Thrown.
Oh that's awesome.
- Almost hit the camera dude.
(screaming)
- K O.
- My God dude that hurt.
- Look at what's on his face.
- What?
- [Devan] Look at that.
- What happened?
Wait what happened.
- [Devan] Oh man.
- What happened?
- [Devan] That didn't hurt?
- That hurt a lot.
- That was awesome though.
- Yeah that was fun.
- Honestly that was like a ten.
- Except for this.
- Yeah that was...
- That was no fun.
All right cool next product.
- But I would say yeah it was a ten.
- Ten, a perfect ten.
Two slap hands.
- [Devan] Bro.
Just getting my neck in there.
I have one good looking neck.
- All right so that is the (laughing)
This is probably one of the weirdest videos
we've ever done.
But yeah if you guys enjoyed the weirdness and the craziness
of this video let us know by giving it a big thumbs up
and also comment down below what was your favorite
as seen on TV product that we tested.
Also share this video with your friends
if you guys want us to do more videos together in the future
because if you don't share this video
- Why is he doing this?
- If you don't share this video
we'll never do a video again ever.
- Maybe you like that, I don't know.
(laughing)
- Just like all right cool.
And also, oh I'm out of the frame too, shoot.
Also yes, so I love you guys so much.
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel.
Like I said I'm doing a big giveaway here on my channel.
All you gotta do, subscribe to this channel,
give this video a thumbs up,
comment and check out that video about this.
Love you guys so much.
Make sure you guys check out
Devan! Ow! Oh my gosh.
Social media links - Hello, I'm back.
- In the description down below.
He's kind of cool. - Down below.
And yeah, we will see you guys again next week.
Bye Felicias.
- Bye
(laughing)
That was the weirdest video ever.