- What's up guys, it is Collins and as
you guys can tell, today I am outside
I would love to say I just came out here
because it was a lovely day, but
what really happened is I spent like
two hours today trying to light
this one area of my house.
It was not looking right.
I got really frustrated with that,
and I took the camera outside
and I'm like, you know what?
this actually looks amazing right now.
For todays video I thought it would be
kind of fun to do some truths and some dares.
Basically I went on Twitter and
I asked you guys to tweet me
a whole bunch of truths and a whole
bunch of dares, because the last vlog I did,
my brother and I, we chucked eggs at each other
and they really hurt and you guys
seemed to enjoy that, so today I'm
gonna do some more crazy dares.
Let's get to it.
When was the last time you cried?
I don't really know how to answer this
because I am, I guess, like a more
sensitive guy.
It happened a few days, no I think it happened.
♫ About a week ago
Have you ever streaked?
I think I was like a baby I streaked a lot.
I think that's kind of a thing that a lot
of babies do.
Crack a raw egg over your head.
I brought along more than one egg
because let's face it
I can't be basic like that.
Egg number uno
Uggghhhh.
Two
Three.
All right, there you go.
Check it out, I got a mohawk!
What?
Oh yeah.
Next question.
Oh yeah, Chipotle!
I've been rejuvenated.
Thank you for the Chipotle by the way, bro.
Is there a person of interest in your life?
I think I know what you mean
I think I'm pickin' up what you're puttin' down
Sorry, that is a really weird way to phrase it.
By person of interest if you mean like a bae
or a girlfriend, no I don't have a girlfriend.
You know I just dropped my new single
it's me.
I'm single.
Do a backflip
Wait a minute, I gotta keep it real though
How did your parents come up with your name?
My great-grandpa, he was some big-time stock
investor who predicted the Great Depression
and did a lot of cool stuff, so I was named
after him.
If you ever see someone type, like, Colin Keys,
like, be nice, but feel free to correct them.
I was at the mall, I forget where I was,
I was on tour somewhere with Demi, and this girl
runs up to me and she's like, oh my God,
you're Keys Colin!
From the X-Factor!
And I was like, yes!
Who was the last person you texted?
Well, let's take a look here.
Jake Paul, and I said, okay, sounds dope.
Mix a spoonful of ketchup with water and then drink it
You know what, that's just not enough.
I thought maybe I'll use a bigger tablespoon
'cause I think this will work
a little bit better.
I still don't think that's enough.
You know what, this is extreme for an
extreme-dare video.
This is like 80% ketchup.
That looks so disgusting.
(electronic music)
Eww, that is so nasty.
This is so gross.
It smells so bad.
I would literally throw up if I drank a couple more.
Have you ever been rejected?
That fly is crazy.
If you're talking about being rejected by
like a girl, no, but that's only because
I've never really asked a girl out.
I'm kind of shy in that way
Like, I can't just walk up to girls
and be like, Hey, I'm Collins.
You should give me your number.
Let's go on a date.
That's just not me.
I'm finally getting over my awkwardness around girls
I've been rejected by a couple girls,
like nonverbally.
There was this one girl I had a crush on
we were at the movie theater, there was like
eight other dudes and one girl and like
I'm sitting next to her, I was like
oh yeah!
I should probably put my arm around her, right?
I went yawn
and she just went
I'm like yee!
You know, just yeetin' over here
just not even trying to do this yee.
Look at your timeline and retweet the first
thing that you see.
Bam, just did it.
I'll put the screenshot of the tweet
right around over here.
Do you creep on your fans' Twitter and Instagrams?
If you guys tweet me a lot, if you guys
constantly are tagging me in photos
there's a really, really, really good chance
that I've probably visited your profile before.
The moral of the story is, if you guys Tweet me
a lot and tag me in a ton of photos
I creep on your profile.
Yeah.
That's kind of how it works.
Tweet Nick Cannon and call him beautiful.
And, done.
The bromance has been renewed.
Why are you not using Vine anymore?
I'm definitely going to start making
a lot more Vines.
Have you had your first kiss?
Yes, I have had my first kiss
and I'm not gonna say with whom,
and I'm not gonna say when, where,
any details like that.
Yeet.
Which YouTuber do you think would win the Hunger Games?
Jc Kaylen, mainly because of Wishbone.
Scream I'm a sexy pancake in public.
I'm a sexy pancake!
Whoo!
A sexy pancake, dawg!
Let's get a selfie, let's get a selfie!
Hey, hey, selfie!
Woo!
- Hey, I gotta call you back.
I don't know what's going on right now.
- Oh yeah!
Pancakes for the win!
I hate waffles!
Next question, let's move on.
Make this your last dare.
Dare accepted, and that's it for this week's
Thursday vlog, if you guys enjoyed this video
make sure you please give it a huge thumbs-up.
Don't forget, of course, subscribe to this channel.
I want you guys to comment down below and
let me know what other truths or dares should I do?
Add me on Snapchat at CollinsKey.
I'm gonna go disappear and eat some Chipotle.
Bye.
(electronic music)