- What's up?
It's Collins Key, and welcome to the Thursday vlog,
and for today's video,
I'm gonna do something that I haven't done
on this channel in, it's been about a year.
You guys really enjoyed the last one I did,
so today, I'm going to be doing
a brand new Truth or Dare video.
(imitates gun firing)
I had you guys tweet in a whole bunch of truths,
a whole bunch of dares,
and also, you might be featured at the end of this video.
Like, your picture on the screen.
So make sure you guys stick around 'til the very end.
Without further ado, let's jump into these truths and dares.
"Do a standing back flip."
Hopefully, I don't break my neck, but let's give it a shot.
Oh, snap!
That just happened!
"Have you dated a girl before?"
I think it all depends on your definition of dating
because when I was 12, I "dated" a girl,
but most we ever did was, we talked on the phone,
and I hugged her one time, which was pretty serious,
and so, I don't know if that's considered "dating" or not.
"Do you ever wear tank tops?"
Definitely, all the time.
"I've watched you for two years,
and I dare you to do a smack cam."
Under normal circumstances, I would not do a smack cam,
but because you've been supporting me for two years,
I love you, so, smack cam, here we go right now.
Alright guys, smack cam.
Ah!
"Do you have a crush?"
Low key. Right now, I do actually have a crush on someone,
and I don't wanna say who it is,
because it'll make things kinda awkward.
I'm a magician, okay?
I'm good at keeping secrets.
"Put Devan in this video."
Let me see what I can do. (snaps)
- Hello, bye. (snaps) - And there're your dose
of Devan for the video.
"Would you ever date a fan?"
Yeah, absolutely, why not?
So, if you're watching this right now,
me and you, we can be relationship goals. (laughs)
Yeah, next question.
(sneezes loudly)
Jesus Christ, Holy Mary.
"Send an ugly selfie to the last person you texted."
Alright, here we go. (camera shutter clicks)
Alright, I'm sending that to Gabriel from Vine, and send.
"Take three bites of an onion."
Here we go.
(onion crunches) (spits)
(onion crunches) (coughs)
I am done. Done with that onion.
"For you, what is the most beautiful thing about a girl?"
Well, right off the bat, there's a couple things
that stand out to me.
One is when a girl has a really pretty smile.
I'm instantly attracted to her.
When a girl has pretty eyes.
I would say the most beautiful thing is
an amazing personality.
That is the most attractive thing to me.
"Have you ever kissed another YouTuber?"
Nope.
"Shower with your clothes on, or no shirt."
Alright guys, here's the fully clothed shower,
and to make this even more fun,
I'm gonna go on super cold water.
So yeah, let's go.
Yup, there you go, hope you guys are enjoying this.
Yup, this is a great time. So cold.
Alright guys, I gotta take a shower, bye.
"When are you planning on getting married?"
I don't have a set age of like,
at this age I wanna get married,
but it more has to do with the girl.
When I find the right girl,
I think that'll be the right age.
"If you could make up a law, what would it be?"
Law number one, every one must cover their mouth
when they cough or sneeze. (sneezes loudly)
"How much money have you spent on eggs?"
Most I've spent on eggs, for a video, was the GloZell video,
because those ostrich eggs,
they were $50 dollars a piece.
And I had seven or eight of them.
But, if you really look at it,
an ostrich egg is $50 dollars,
cracking it on GloZell's head?
Priceless.
"I dare you to eat a pickle covered in marshmallow fluff
while doing the whip."
Alright, so I've got the pickle
and I've got the marshmallow stuff, so yeah,
I'm just gonna dip it in here like this. I guess here we go.
Ehh! (spits)
So gross. (laughs)
"Tell us some embarrassing moments you've had
trying to impress people."
Honestly, the amount of embarrassing moments I've had
trying to impress people could fill an entire book.
One that happened actually very recently is,
I was on the flight back from Playlist Live DC,
there was a very pretty YouTuber,
she was sitting a row behind me,
and I was sittin' all the way on the window seat,
and I had to get up and use the restroom.
I was like, oh, I'll impress her.
I'll hop up on the seats and walk on the seats
and get up into the aisle,
as opposed to just walking out like a normal person.
And so I jumped up on the seats
and then the cushions on the seats slid out,
so I fell over the row in front of me,
hit this guy in the head,
and everyone laughed, and, oh my gosh.
#TheStruggleIsReal.
"If you could kiss any YouTube girl, who would it be?"
Actually, I wanna get you guys' opinion on this.
So, comment down below what YouTuber you'd ship me with.
You never know, it could actually happen.
"What's your middle name?"
What's my middle name?
It's still Joseph, still Joseph. Swag. (giggles)
So, yeah, my middle name is Joseph. Swag!
"Would you consider your Keypers friends,
or even closer to family?"
You guys are definitely my family, without a doubt.
The Keyper family, when I say the Keyper family,
I really mean that you guys are my family.
You guys are just the most amazing family
I could ever ask for.
"Truth, do you like pickles?"
I guess, yeah, they're okay.
"I dare you to drink a jar of pickle juice."
Awesome. Alright, well let's do it.
So, I could just drink it out of a glass,
and be a normal, boring person,
but brought along this jar, so, cheers.
(spits) Let's try again.
(spits and snorts) Oh, it went up my nose.
Yeah, there's no way. Sorry guys. I tried.
I really tried.
"Use this as your last dare."
And you know what, dare accepted.
And if this video made you laugh or smile,
please give it a thumbs up right now
and share it with all of your friends
and also comment down below.
What is one dare you would love to see me do
in a future, upcoming video?
I'm starting something brand new on the channel.
I wanna do a give back to all of you
because you guys support me and show me so much love,
and so every week I'm gonna be featuring one of you.
I'm gonna be featuring the Keyper Of The Week.
And this one's inspired by my good friend, The Gabbie Show.
You should subscribe to her.
The first ever Keyper Of The Week is...
Beverly. Now, Beverly, I always see you in my notifications.
And every time I see your name,
it puts a big smile on my face,
'cause you're always favoriting, you're always retweeting.
You tag me in the coolest Instagram photos.
You're always sharin' my videos.
Supporting, liking, commenting.
Go follow Beverly right now, show her some love.
And if you wanna be the keyper of the week,
all you have to do is just be super active,
try to get a first favorite, the first retweet,
make sure you guys have my Twitter notifications on,
my Instagram notifications on, YouTube notifications on.
Make sure you guys are likin' my videos,
commenting on my videos, sharing my videos.
The more active you are, the better chance you have
of being featured in one of my videos.
Bye. (snaps)