- What's up, it's Collins Key
and welcome to the third day of vlogging.
As you guys can tell
by all this fan mail here behind me today,
I'm gonna open up your fan mail.
Boom, mind blown.
Bet you had no idea that was coming.
I wanna say a huge thank you first of all
to each and every one of you guys who sent in fan mail
because if you didn't know on Monday, May 9th
it was my birthday.
Eh, turn up, oh, dab.
This is only some of the stuff you guys sent in.
There's a little bit of Christmas stuff I think in here too
from my last fan mail vlog that I didn't quite get to,
so I'll be opening up that today.
Also want to let you guys know
that I'm doing a huge giveaway on my channel this month.
I'm giving away a MacBook.
So if you guys want to win that
all you have to do is let me know
by liking this video, (dinging)
comment down below
what is your favorite video that I've ever posted
here on my channel,
and of course you must be subscribed to the channel.
But without any further ado,
let's jump in and let's find out
what's inside this fan mail.
We'll start off right here with this purple box
and I have a knife to open it up.
So this is from Kaylin,
so let's see if I can do this without cutting myself.
(knife rubbing)
Screw this I'm going back to scissors.
Alright, here we go.
Yo, okay there's this, what are these?
Yo, okay, you know what I know what this is.
This is from when I went out and I visited her.
She was a winner of a one lucky fan visit,
I believe from the StageIt,
and at the hotel that we were at,
it was like a hotel casino place,
they had these mints there.
I went wild at the hotel
and I asked for like, if I could get like 50 of 'em,
and they wouldn't give it to me.
So now, I have a whole bunch of mints.
I believe this is what, oh yeah, this oh my god thank you.
Keyper's squad, what up, hey?
I'm gonna be snackin' on this the whole time.
This next one here is from Hannah,
and I have to say A-plus job.
The design is killer and now let's find out what's inside.
So I need my scissors. (box crunching)
(surprised grunting)
I almost just cut my pants open.
So let's see what we got here.
We have a squishy ball, which is a smiley face.
It's like emoji almost.
Check it out, it's like a stress reliever ball.
It's like... (grunting)
that's actually really hard.
Is this like for forearm strength or something?
'Cause like wow, I'm really having trouble with that.
Okay, yo straight up right now,
I'm about to take this to the next level.
I'm gonna see if I can take this ball,
bounce it off the wall and land it in this box.
Can I get a no way?
That's what I thought.
Alright, here we go.
Oh, did you guys see the oh, I got it in there!
We have a bear right here.
Bam.
Yo, it's like the Keyper bear, it's got a little key,
it's got some wings on it.
That's pretty legit.
And let's see, we have a, this looks like a transformer.
It has a disc shooting thingy.
And I like this thing, alright cool.
I might hit Devon with this later so, shh.
Yo, okay this is Bazooka bubble gum,
and I literally have never had Bazooka bubble gum
in my entire life.
Now that it's my birthday,
I'm about to enjoy some Bazooka bubble gum
for the very first time.
We'll go with one, two, three.
My jaw is kind of hurtin' a little bit,
these are really difficult to chew.
This is piece number four.
Piece number five.
Wow, piece number six.
Piece number seven.
Piece number eight.
Piece number nine.
And last, but certainly not least,
we have piece number ten.
I'm gonna need subtitles.
This is a lot of bubble gum.
I'm gonna try to blow a bubble right now,
so let's try this, okay.
Three, two, one.
(gum thumping)
Cool, we've also got this lovely cinnamon candle.
Let's take a breath.
(inhaling deeply)
Oh, that's pretty spicy, yeah.
Also got an assortment of candy,
so yeah, thank you so much Hannah.
And now let's move on to the next one.
This is by far the shiniest one I've received
and this one here is from Jasmine.
So, we're gonna open this up. (tearing)
Yo, this is so cool.
Not only do we have this picture,
but we also have this picture right here.
So yeah, thank you so much Jasmine.
Like I love these, these are really pretty.
Oh, and then can't forget that there's actually a ton of,
is this either just one long cord,
or is this, yo, this like, yo ho ho ho!
Alright we talking now.
Whoo!
I think it's kind of like a scarf,
like you kind of take it like this
and you just kind of give it a flick over your neck.
How's it look guys?
Rapper, two chains, what it is boy.
Boom.
Alright, so let's see what inside this one.
We've got some wrapping paper.
Thank you, yay!
Bam!
Bam! (laughing)
Collins Key, we got a nice key, so thank you Carla.
Next we got a Webkinz, bringing it back,
and this one is a little frog I believe.
But it's like a pink Valentine's Day lookin' frog,
so I'll use this as a clip on my necklace.
Bam!
That's what you call bling right there kids.
Better get it right.
Then we have also again just have an assortment of candy.
We have gum right here, don't choke.
I'm not sure what that means.
I'm gonna try to blow a bubble right now,
three, two, one. (gum thumping)
You should be in the psychic business
because that is pretty incredible.
So we have this, we've got some Fruit Snacks right here.
We've also got Strawberry Twizzlers.
This is a lot of candy.
Can't let my family know that I have this,
otherwise it'll all be gone by like morning.
So yeah, thank you so much Carla, I love it.
This next one here is from Catherine,
and this actually from Singapore,
so I'm really excited to find out what's inside.
Alright, let's see we'll open this up.
(paper tearing)
Ooh!
Another package.
Hey we found, are you eating a cookie?
- Yeah. - Where are they?
- Huh? - Did mom make 'em?
- Yeah. - What?
Okay. - Yup.
- Let's see what we got inside, we have...
- Ooh.
- Batman!
- It's like a pencil or a pen case I think.
- Yes, awesome. - That's cool.
- Yo, I think this one was like,
yeah this is one of those iPhone lenses.
- Oh, wait, what? - Yes!
- No way!
- Yo, the game has been changed.
Even though it's my birthday,
I'm gonna be kind and I'm gonna give this to you.
(excited yelling)
Devon's birthday was actually last month, so yeah...
- Yeah
- happy birthday bro, thanks for being in the video.
- Thank you, happy birthday too.
- Absolutely, I like Devon's hair.
(laughing)
- And I'm out.
- Okay, so this is from Urban Outfitters.
So either, Urban Outfitters is legit
and sending me something
or you guys are even more legit and sending me something.
So let's see if I can.
Ingeniousness. (box tearing)
Bam!
Boxes don't matter to me.
Paper, yay!
Fisheye phone, yo!
Yeah it's like a gold fisheye lens.
So the only name I'm seeing on here is Cassie.
So yeah, Cassie!
Thank you so much, 'cause this is freaking awesome!
So yeah, thank you!
You guys, straight up,
my gram is about to be popping off to another level now.
So yeah, you all better watch out.
Next we are going for the envelope
with the macaroni and cheese duct tape.
That's definitely a new one.
So let's see what we got in here.
You guys got me some legit, I believe this is tape.
But it says like bam, we have donuts
and then we also have mustaches.
So you guys just gave me some of the most legit tape
I have ever seen in my entire life.
And I've gotta say it's pretty fitting,
when you have macaroni and cheese duct tape
on your envelope.
This next one here is coming from Australia,
and there's no name on the outside,
so hopefully I'll find the name on the inside.
Shout out, (paper tearing)
for the little tear thing right there.
Yo!
This is huge, this is a,
okay I've never even heard of a Violet Crumble,
but maybe it's like an Australian thing.
But yeah, this is pretty legit.
We also got some other candy in here.
(deep inhaling)
Lifesavers.
A Wagon Wheel.
Yeah we definitely, I don't think we have these in America.
And then we also have Caramel Koala right here.
So that's definitely Australian right there.
This is super awesome,
so Amy thank you so much
for all of this really cool Australian candy.
This next one here is a rather small package
but you must not judge a package by it's size.
We're gonna see what's inside this one here.
Let's see, we open this up.
Not exactly sure what this is.
This is a Carolina pepper, world's hottest pepper.
Please take a bite on camera.
And there's nothing else.
Just like a couple oil stains.
(heavy sighing)
Alright Ryan, you challenged me, so here we go.
If I die, Ryan this is on you,
because I don't do well with spicy things.
So let's see, I'm gonna use a tissue,
'cause I don't even want it to get on my fingers.
Let's see.
Oh, that's a big one.
Alright guys, here we go.
Three.
Two.
One.
(dramatic orchestra music)
Y'all must think I am crazy,
if you really think that I'm gonna be eating one,
no I am not eating a pepper.
No, I am not eating the world's hottest pepper.
Guys, I wanna live.
I am sorry Ryan, challenge is not accepted.
I will literally die if I ate one of those peppers.
So yeah, let's go to the next one.
And this on here is from Jessica.
Alright, so let's find out what's inside.
And you know what, this one here is also from Singapore.
So yo, shout out to Singapore,
you guys are representin' so far.
So let's see.
What are these?
We got some potato chips.
Barbecue flour, Jack 'N Jill.
So that must be like a Singapore brand,
'cause I have not heard of Jack 'N Jills.
So we've got Jack 'N Jill.
It looks like we've got
a whole bunch of candy from Singapore.
Sesame Street, is that Sesame Street.
Wait, wait, wait, hold up.
'cause I think that this is Cookie Monster.
Is this Cookie Monster?
No, it's just monster.
It looks literally like Cookie Monster
and he's selling a cookie, but it's not Cookie Monster.
What?
You got Yeppies.
You got a Hello Kitty on the side of this,
so I know Hello Kitty.
We got the Tinker lollipop.
Yeah, we also got some other candy as well.
See, actually you know what,
I was thinking for another video,
I might taste some candy
from somewhere else around the world.
So let me know if you guys want me to do that
by liking this video and comment down below
what part of the world should I taste candy from.
This one's got leopard print on it
so it kind of caught my attention.
And I'm not sure where this is from,
I'm not sure who it's from.
I'm sure we'll find out inside.
But, yeah let's do it.
Alright, so we got some newspapers.
I'm like, low-key more excited about the fact
that these newspapers are in another language,
and I don't even know what's inside of here yet.
So let's see.
Alright we have a little card here.
So hopefully we can use our detective skills
and find out who this is from.
So this whole thing here is from Marin,
and this is awesome.
This actually from Norway.
So let's see what we got inside.
Alright so the first candy here is called Smash
and it's salty and air crispy, corn cones,
covered in milk chocolate.
That's tongue twister.
Yo, this is huge!
This chocolate bar is bigger than my head.
This is quite a lot of candy from Norway.
So you know, I think the time is coming very shortly
where I'm gonna be taste testing a lot of candies
from all around the world, so stay tuned for that.
This package here is from Rhiannon.
So let's find out what is inside.
That was a solid scissor slice right there.
Yo, straight up, this is super legit.
It's like a box.
This appears to be handmade,
like the paint has literally even dried this thing together.
So let's see if I can, carefully get it open.
Yo, I've been seeking for the right prom date,
will you go to prom with me?
This is, I gotta admit, this is pretty legit right here.
This next on here is from Sienna,
and the envelope or whatever
is like around the actual package itself
is a little bit confusing to me.
Yeah I can't get this open on my own.
Okay, scissor time, let's do it.
Oh my god, Sienna, there's a picture of her right there.
I don't know if you guys can see it,
but like, she's like, the picture just flew off.
Alright perfect, let's find out what's inside the box.
First of all Sienna got me covered with some blue shades.
Eh, stunna'!
And then we also got, let's see, a magic carpet I believe.
It looks like a little magic carpet,
like a little magic rug.
And then we've also of course got a dope deck of cards.
Y'all ready for this.
Oh snap, that did not just happen.
Yo, straight up, this is so legit.
Sienna got me an Etch-A-Sketch.
If y'all remember what Etch-A-Sketch's are.
Oh my god, this used to be my jam, my childhood jam.
Oh my god.
Get funky with it, oh, oh, oh!
Thank you so much Sienna.
Alright this one here is from Niley,
and I gotta say, overall, pound for pound,
that's quite a bit of decoration just for one envelope.
So thank you.
Yo, this is crazy!
There's like a whole bunch of mini cards, eh!
Mini cards for days!
Alright yo, check it out, right here,
we got one, two, three.
Oh snap, that did not just happen!
This one here is from Alyssa, and I gotta say,
(paper rattling)
there's definitely something like shakeable inside of this,
so let's see what it is.
Yo, this is awesome, can you guys see it?
This is so crazy, thank you so much.
And now to find out, (box rattling)
what's shakin'?
Alright let's see.
So first of all we got some Silly String.
Don't tell Devon.
And then we have a Glow Stick.
Heck yes!
And then we've also got Nerds,
which I've never actually had Nerds before.
I've heard from multiple people though,
that Nerds are like the best candy so let's see.
Take a little handful,
not too much, keep it tasteful.
(agreeable grunt) Yeah, these are actually, yeah, wow,
these are rather tasty, yeah.
Thank you so much Alyssa.
Alright this one here is from Alexa so,
that was supposed to be a very dramatic tear
but that did not work at all.
So yeah let's find out what's in..
(laughing)
I'm terrible at opening up this stuff
so I'm just gonna kind of magician time,
cover up the rip that may or may not
have been created in the paper.
And these are awesome, these are really cool.
Thank you so much.
We're going up to the next one right now
and this here doesn't have a name on the outside.
But we are about to find out who it's...
I can not open this stuff at all.
It's a shirt.
I think it says something.
I never got my acceptance letter for Hogwarts,
so I'm leaving the Shire and becoming a Jedi.
Yo, this is straight up, okay, yeah I'm,
this is new favorite shirt right here.
I'm definitely gonna be wearing this shirt.
Thank you so much,
and there is no name like anywhere to be found,
so if you sent me this, you know who you are
and thank you so very much.
So this here says,
"Will you please put this in your Youtube video."
And you know what, I've gotta obey,
so this one here, this is goin' in the Youtube video,
so let's see.
Opening up here.
Yo, this is awesome,
it's literally my face on playing cards.
Alright guys, we are getting down to the last few right now.
So next, I think I'm gonna hit it with this box over here,
'cause it's pretty colorful, and yeah let's do it.
I challenge like all of you guys
to like send like boxes of just stuff, like I love it.
So yeah, thank you guys.
I gotta say, even through the mail
the presentation on this is on point
'cause there's like this little chocolate
just sitting right on top.
So I don't know if you could have planned that any better.
Alright so we've got a few more chocolates
and we are unrolling this thing.
This is a, I don't know if you guys can see,
this is a lot of bubble wrap.
Alright, so let's see, this like Webkinz squirrel,
this is kind of like the epitome of having a Webkinz.
So yeah, this is my new best friend right here.
Thank you so much, Samantha.
This guy's like super cute.
You know what, I might even like low-key log him in
and like just be playing on Webkinz.
You guys never know.
Alright, so again this one doesn't have a name
on the outside,
hopefully there's a name here on the inside.
Whoa, okay!
Good job, 'cause whoever sent me this,
you scared me really bad just now.
Like I literally freaked out.
Well this is from Sadie, I believe she lives in London,
and yeah, she sent me this is super cool.
She sent me some like London coins as well.
This one here kind of looks like a penny,
but it has the Queen's face on there.
I'm gonna try to spend these in America
and just kind of like see what happens.
I'll probably do it on my SnapChat.
So, if you guys wanna see that
you might as well add my SnapChat.
My name is CollinsKey.
But yeah,
you guys can also use the scan code right over there.
Thank you so much Sadie.
We got a whole bunch of mustaches.
Yes!
Alright cool, and let's see.
We've also got some money glasses.
This is for whenever you guys go to like a family gathering
and people are like, "Oh, so how much money do you make?"
Just take these glasses, put 'em on,
and then just walk away.
This is pretty awesome right here.
Thank you very much Kaylyn.
Alright we are now down to the last two.
So we got this huge box, it says fragile,
please handle with care.
So I will not spin the box around.
Alright, so to start off with, there is bubble wrap.
Oh there's another layer of bubble wrap.
There's actually a lot of bubble wrap.
This is heavy!
Yo, we got all the goodies.
We first, we got a rock, some Silly String,
classic Coca-Cola bottle, another rock.
Maybe it's like a coaster.
Yo, and then last but not least, check it out,
it's like an outline of me, but like on this legit canvas.
This is so cool.
Thank you so much Simon.
Hey guys, this thing is massive.
So I really have no idea what's inside,
but yeah, right now my head barely like fits above it.
Let's find out what is inside.
I'm really having, if you guys can tell this thing is huge.
Yo!
(box crashing)
It says, "Stop,
"must have Devon with you while opening this."
Hey Devon!
Devon's back! - Hey!
- Okay, so let's see here.
Yo! - What?
- I think on the count of three we'll do the reveal,
you ready?
- [Both] Three, two, one, boom, whoa!
- What, that is so sick!
- Dude!
Yo these are so awesome!
So this is from Mara.
This is absolutely insane.
- What!
- Thank you so much
Mara for this! - Yeah, thank you very much.
- And if you guys enjoy this video
let me know by giving it a big thumbs up
and also comment down below.
What was the craziest thing you think I got
in this entire video?
Make sure you guys subscribe to this channel,
there are new videos coming out
each and every single Thursday.
Thank you Devon for being here.
- Yeah of course.
Happy birthday by the way.
- Thank you very much, I appreciate it.
- Yeah.
- And also I wanna let you guys know one more thing,
and I'm super excited,
but this year I'm apart of AT&T Hello Lab.
So basically I've got like a brand new show
that's gonna be coming out here on my Youtube channel.
I can't tell you guys - No way.
- what it is.
Like I gotta be super secret with it.
But in the meantime I've been binge-watching a ton
of the other Hello Labber's shows.
One of whom is Grace Helbig and it is freaking awesome.
She has a show called Writing with Grace
and it is absolutely crazy.
It's a love story, but there's flying cats and dogs,
there's a crazy group chat,
and I believe there's no gravity as well.
Like the whole thing is just completely out of control.
(laughing)
So this week I challenge you guys
and maybe even challenge myself
to write a chapter for Grace's novella.
And the best part of this
is that Grace is gonna be reading her novella
onstage at VidCon.
So make sure you guys check out her videos.
You guys can binge watch on it as well,
and also make sure you guys go write that chapter.
In the meantime, I will see you guys again, next Thursday.
I love you all so much, thank you!
- [Devon] Yeah!
- For all of this incredible, incredible birthday fan mail.
You guys are simply the best, love you so much,
see you again soon, bye.
(snapping)