- What's up, it's Collins Key and for today's video
I have absolutely no idea what I'm doing
but join me and meet my little brother,
or should I say, Elsa.
Hey, there we go.
- Why?
- Today, Devan and I, we are doing
the Disney Princess Challenge.
Basically, there are five different Disney princesses
that we have created unique, original challenges for.
We're going to be going through these
and whoever wins the most amount of these challenges,
they get to have the loser go run through
a public shopping place--
- What?
- In one of these costumes.
- No!
- There's a lot of incentive to win this challenge.
Give us the thumbs-up if you guys love Disney princesses.
Also want to let you guys know, Devan and I
are doing a live stream today at 4 PM Pacific Standard time
so if you guys wanna join us there,
I'll put the free download link for live meet
in the description below.
I'm also doing huge back-to-school giveaway right now,
I'm giving away a Macbook computer on YouTube
and an iPhone six on Instagram.
If you guys wanna win the YouTube prize, all you gotta do
is let us know by liking this video,
comment down below what' your favorite video
that I've ever posted on this channel.
You must be subscribed to the channel.
For the iPhone Instagram giveaway,
I'm gonna put all the information down in the description
below so be sure to go check that out
to win an iPhone 6s, follow Devan on all
the social media links.
- Yep, my Snapchat link is right there.
- Boom.
- His Snapchat link is there,
all my other Instagram and Twitters down below,
so go check it out.
- In my Snapchat before, I was doing like
pull-ups in this dress,
doing like some Olympic gymnastics routines.
Make sure you guys add us on Snapchat
so you don't miss any of the fun shenanigans
that is always going on--
- It's just a bunch of behind-the-scenes footage,
so go check it out.
- Right now, without any further ado, let's get in,
and this is round #1 of the Disney princess challenge.
Dab dab, lets do this.
(yelling)
For round #1, it is battle of the Belles,
and for this challenge we have to carry
three books on our head and balance them
and go to that wall over there without dropping them.
Now if you drop your books, it's automatic disqualification.
- I'm good.
I'm good--
- Which will not be good.
I didn't mean that, that hit you.
- Bro, I had that.
- My hair looks like a soccer mom by the way, guys.
Alright, cool.
Just lost my hair.
Me and my hair (???).
- I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
- No no no wait, it's tickling my armpit.
- That doesn't count, it doesn't count.
Alright I got it, oh that doesn't count,
that doesn't count, I got this.
- This isn't fair, bro.
- I got this, I got it, it doesn't count.
There we go.
- No!
- This is great, you know, I'm not holding it at all.
See, I'm not holding it.
- I got automatic disqualification.
That didn't go according to plan.
- Make sure you read your books, kids.
- Joking, alright.
Well I lost my hair, I lost my books,
and from what Devan said, I didn't see him at all,
but he says he didn't cheat so he won fair and square.
- I didn't cheat at all, we're good.
- I lose round one.
Alright round two, let's get it.
- Let's do it.
- This is the Little Mermaid challenge.
As you guys know, the Little Mermaid loves
collecting human items.
For this, we are going to be using forks.
Devan, do you have a fork?
- This is my fork.
I don't think this is quite fair,
because you have a much bigger fork than I do.
- I think this is great.
- For this, we're gonna do rock, paper, scissors
to see who gets the bigger fork.
Put your fork down.
Ready, rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
I win!
I get the big fork.
Three, two, one, go.
That's my fork!
Okay, whoever gets all his rope on their fork first wins.
I win, I win, I win.
Good game.
- I won!
- No no no no no no no fam, I won that round.
- I won this one.
- After watching the instant replay,
it does appear as though Devan did get his fork in the air
before I did, so Devan did--
- I did?
- Yeah, so you take the win this one.
- Yeah!
- Yay!
I just messed up our yard, bro.
This is the Snow White challenge.
For this, we have a whole bunch of poison apples
and it's whoever can eat the most poison apples
in 30 seconds, I know it kinda goes against the whole story
but whatever.
Alright, three, two, one, go.
- Oh no.
I'm sorry.
What?
(timer ringing)
- Don't know how I fit one and quarter apples
in my mouth but
I win so we Gucci.
Don't you hate it when your headphones get tangled?
This that relatable moments here.
Whoever can untangle their headphones first,
they win this challenge, so go.
- Okay.
- Alright well I'm going for this kind of like
grab everything technique.
- I don't have a technique so I'm just going.
- Getting so close, getting so close, yeah.
Now just the two little headphones, what are you doing fam?
Get it together.
Bro, I'm like a tangle person right now.
- Mine got more tangled.
- Yes there we go, one is free.
One is free, there we go, mine are like, rubbery.
Oh no, you're getting so close, no no no no no.
- I'm getting closer.
- Does blowing on it help?
Okay come on, I'm so close.
Look at this, there's like a knot at the end.
- I'm so close.
- Yes!
Alright cool, now I can finally listen to
all my Disney tracks in peace.
- I can listen too, actually.
♫ Let it go let it go ♫
- I'm done.
- That didn't work.
Alright cool, next round let's go.
Round #5, the tie-breaker round.
This is the Else frozen challenge.
We have some Slurpees right here in some Frozen cups
and whoever can drink the full Slurpee first,
the full thing, without getting a brain freeze, wins,
so light up your cup.
- Is that possible?
I got it.
- Wait wait, I can't gett.
- Did you get it?
- Think I broke it.
Well I broke mine so I guess cheers.
- Cheers.
- Here we go.
Ow, I have such a bad brain freeze.
- I can't do it, I'm only halfway through.
- And there you have it.
Alright guys, that is the Disney princess challenge.
We are about to now have Devan run through the grove
dressed up as Disney princess.
- I forgot I had to do that!
No!
- Should have drank it a little bit faster, bro.
- No!
- Give the video a thumbs-up if you guys love
the Disney princesses and also give this video
a thumbs-up if you guys want us to do
a part two to this video, comment down below
who's your favorite Disney princess of all time.
Make sure you guys go follow us but right now
I think we're gonna go out to the Grove and Devan--
- I'm not happy about this.
- Let's do it.
♫ Let it go
♫ Can't hold it back anymore ♫
(laughing)
- This was absolutely terrible.