- You challenged us to mix Flaming Hot Cheetos with milk.
Oh, this does not look good!
This is such a weird food combination.
- Ugh; are you ready?
- Three, two, one.
(loud chewing)
(moaning)
I thought the milk was supposed to make it not spicy.
It's still spicy.
- Why would anyone do this?
That tastes so, ugh.
- You guys challenged us to a whole bunch
of crazy weird food combinations that people
actually seemed to love and so today, we are going to be
trying all of them, right now, let's go.
Time to find out what the next food combination is,
here we go, three, two--
- Oh wait I think we're forgetting something I think we're--
- Oh yeah yeah yeah, sorry, at the end of this,
we're mixing all the foods together
into the weirdest food combination of all time.
So this is the bowl of doom, we're going to
leave it over to the side.
- Alright now that we got that out of the way,
three, two, one, oh, wait what?
Doritos, marshmallows and nacho cheese.
- Oh my gosh.
- Alright, that looks good. - I think that's enough right?
- Oh, I have an idea!
- Ooh, what?
- I think we should dip the marshmallows in the cheese.
- But first, we juggle.
Oh no! - That's not even juggling.
- I completely failed, hey.
- Four ball juggling fam, yeah that's lit.
Back to three balls.
- Distractions.
- Suh dude.
Alright I'm ready, going to dip it in,
wait, stop stop stop.
- That actually looks pretty cool.
- I'm just gonna just plop it in.
- [Devon] Nice.
- So let's do this, actually I think
we should just pop the marshmallows on here because
we've got to melt them as well.
- [Devon] And now we're going to drizzle.
The final step; I have no idea
how this is going to taste though.
(ragtime music)
- [Boy] Dude this actually looks amazing!
It smells phenomenal.
- Oh it smells 10 times better than this other Cheeto thing.
- Like the chips mix with the marshmallows
and then the nacho cheese, heavenly bro.
- Oh, oh oh oh, cheers.
- This is gonna be so good bro.
Wait wait wait wait wait but first
we got a challenge, I want to see can you subscribe
to the channel turn on the channel post notifications
and give this video a thumbs up in seven seconds,
here we go, are you ready for this,
seven, six, five, four, three, two, one, done.
- If you can do that comment down below Keyper squad,
right now. - I can't wait any longer.
- Let's go for it.
Mmm, oh my gosh.
- Wow.
- This may be my new favorite meal of all time,
like I thought this would be disgusting
but all the flavors actually came together perfectly.
- Ended up all over my face and I just
didn't care because it was a second meal, just, you know.
- So whoever came up with this, shouts out to you
because I would've never put this together.
- [Devon] Alright here we go.
- Just going to spoon it in, ew.
Alright here we go,
three, two, one.
- What, what, grapes and ranch?
People like this?
- Grapes?
Want to crack them open? - Sure.
- Oh dude this is cool I can like spin the top off, pew.
- Sounds like you broke something.
Here is your bushel of grapes.
- Is it called a bushel?
- I don't know.
- [Boy] Alright, just kind of dump them in?
- [Devon] Yeah.
Alright, my turn.
- Ew.
- Alright here we go.
- This is not how you're supposed to do this.
Three, two, one.
- Eugh, mm.
- I can't I can't I can't I can't.
Uh uh, uh uh, no no no no.
Dude wait hold on I've got an idea,
we have to mix them all together,
so let's do this, put all the grapes
in the Ziploc bag right now and then
we're going to dump all the ranch in here.
- Wait what?
You better not pop it bro, you better not pop it.
- This looks disgusting dude. - Oh, I'm not ready
to add this in here.
- Alright so you have to open it up bro,
I don't want to smell what this smells like.
- How does it smell?
- Mm, just ranch.
Eugh, oh my gosh.
- Hmm, I wonder what's under here?
- Now this was actually suggested by the Instagram
Keyper of the week, if you want to be shouted out
as the Instagram Keyper of the week, check
the description down below to find out how
but right now I guess we're going to find out
what you suggested, three, two, one.
Bread and peanut butter and pickles.
- Wait what?
- Like a sandwich?
Oops.
- I think we should do something where
we each make our own sandwiches and see
who can make the best sandwich possible.
- This is some thick peanut butter bro.
Woah.
I know that Devon has a master plan strategy
going on, I don't but I'm going to try to beat him anyway,
so there we go, boom, you've been peanut buttered.
- [Devon] Now I'm making a skyscraper sandwich.
- What? - Yep.
- Ah, stop dripping your pickle juice on me.
I could leave it like this which is kind of basic,
but I think simplicity might be the goal in this one.
- Maybe.
(air horns)
What, what, you're never going to be able to get that--
- Yep yep yep haters gonna hate Devon,
and then for the win, pickle mania, yeah boy, woo.
It's been pickle-ified.
I got to make an X with it, it's like,
this is the X Games of pickle sandwiches.
Alright there we go, bam, masterpiece completed.
Now the moment has come to taste the sandwiches.
- Alright mine's going to be pretty easy to eat.
- [Boy] You taking a bite out of it already?
- Mm, this is actually really good.
- Mine's like real heavy bro,
oh it's dripping pickle juice.
I don't know how I can make this work.
- Enough stalling.
- I can't, I can't do it.
My mouth is stuck.
- Too much peanut butter?
- Way too much peanut butter.
- Really?
- Oh my gosh it just fell apart, okay quickly, put it,
okay boom, there we go.
- I'm going to take another bite,
this is actually really good.
- Add your sandwich to it.
(groans)
Let's see what you got in store for us this time,
three two one.
Honey Nut Cheerios and what, cream cheese?
- Is that right?
- That's a thing?
As you guys know I'm the best at opening cereal
because you got to make sure when you open it
that you can reuse it next time.
- Uh huh?
- The family loves me.
- Wait what?
- Yeet, yeet yeet.
- Bro I wanna pour it, I wanna pour this.
- Okay fine and we want to let you guys know
that every single Saturday at one PM Pacific
Standard Time, we're doing a whole bunch of crazy
challenges, DIYs, experiment, live on Live.Me,
and we're partnering with Live.Me all summer long,
so every single Saturday we're doing it,
the free download link, it is down in the description below
that way you can come join us and also,
comment down below and let me know what should we do
on these live streams because whatever you want us to do,
that's what we do, like literally anything,
so right now Devon do we have it going?
- We got it going.
- We just going to stick a spoonful in,
just kind of carry the lot out.
Three two one.
(loud crunching)
I actually like it a lot, 10 out of 10.
- It tastes like popcorn, this tastes like popcorn.
- You're so right.
Going to put a big, um.
That's looking pretty gross man.
Alright here we go three, two, one.
I love Oreos, and I love orange juice.
- Bro you can't eat the filling,
dude we have to dunk it first.
- Okay hold on wait wait, if I.
- No way what, seriously?
- We good, okay wait, can I dunk it?
- Dude go for it.
- Alright let's go, alright I want to try it, here we go.
- And he can actually eat it, what?
I got to try this.
Mmhmm, that's so good.
I wonder what could be under here?
- Can I take a guess?
- Sure.
- It's a banana.
Let's find out.
Eh it's Pringles, and some, Nutella on chips?
Game changing bro.
- Nailed it.
Alright, I'm going to try these Pringles,
you try the Ruffles.
Ah, no, I hate it when that happens; why?
- [Boy] Your Pringles are just way too thin for this.
- Oh no it's breaking again, okay.
I got half a chip and a lot of Nutella.
- Three, two, one.
Yo.
- I think I've found my true love.
- This is the greatest thing I have ever experienced, ever.
- The crunch of the chip, mm, mixed with the creaminess
of the Nutella.
- Mm we're adding this weird food combination with pleasure.
First some chips.
- Then some Pringles which are chips I guess.
- [Boy] And then last but not least, some Nutella.
- [Devon] It's not, there we go, ugh, that was a mess.
- This is the final weird food combination before we try
the world's weirdest food combination.
- Not excited. - Who knows, it might
be delicious, three, two, one.
Doritos. - Hey Mountain Dew!
(fizzing)
- Alright there we go, alright cool
so then I guess just dump it in here?
Yeah just go for it, alright, here we go, dump it in.
I can feel like, oh, this feels so weird, second bottle.
Ooh.
It makes like, it makes all the chips look
like regular chips because it takes off
whatever the Dorito coating is on them.
- Eugh!
- Oh it smells toxic guys.
I guess we kind of crunch it up a bit.
(overlapping talking)
Alright here we go.
- Don't pop--
- What?
- I thought I saw the bag pop.
- [Boy] You got to crunch the top of it a little bit more.
Ugh, oh, oh that looks so gross.
- [Devon] Splash guards splash guards splash guards.
- [Boy] Oh no it's about to get chunky, ugh.
- I'm sorry but that does not look good.
- There's no way this can be good.
- No. - No way.
Are you ready to take a bite of it?
- Yeah.
- If you want to be featured in the next video
comment down below and let us know what are some gross
foods we should combine together or what are your
favorite weird food combinations but right now.
Let's try this.
- It dripped on me.
- Three, two, one, oh I can't, there we go, one.
Oh, I can't do it bro.
- Not good.
Did you, did you just spit back in there?
- [Boy] So here we go, going to dump the Doritos now in,
ugh, not looking forward to this.
No that's enough, that's enough.
The Cheetos turned into pudding, literally bro.
- [Devon] They're so soggy.
- And the grapes with the, ugh.
- Oh I forgot about the grapes.
- Eugh, I don't want to do this anymore.
- [Devon] Dude I completely forgot about the grapes.
- Oh man the cream cheese and the cheerios.
The worst is the bottom feels like a flippin' sponge.
I got a full bushel of grapes, Devon.
Ready?
- Yeah I'm so ready.
- Alright Devon the moment of truth, you're going
to go first, go for it, alright, three, two, one.
Oh my gosh, if you guys want to see us battle
and see who can make the best pancakes
click right here and if you want to see the gummy food
versus real food challenge click right over here,
and now it's time for my bite, is it good?
- I almost threw up.
Ugh.
- Oh my God, mine tastes awesome dude.
- Dude I literally almost threw up.
- Mine was really good, alright goodbye.
- Bye.