- Hi guys, it's Collins Key.
Welcome to the Thursday vlog.
I just got my wisdom teeth removed
and it's feeling really weird right now
but I love you guys, enjoy this week's video.
Give it a thumbs up for encouragement.
Oh my god, I love Ratchet.
(whines)
I love my viewers, you guys mean the world to me.
- Swing around, yeah.
All right, go ahead and sit down.
- (sighs) Feels really nice.
- All right.
- The Jurassic Park ride.
Haha, bird, go away.
- No, that's a lizard. (laughs)
- Oh. Hello lizard.
- He's probably gonna feel loopy for the rest of the day.
- Whoa, this is weird.
- [Cameraman] How do you feel?
- Uh, everything, it makes a lot more sense
but not really.
I wanna work out right now,
but they said I wasn't allowed to.
I want to lift this whole car up.
- [Cameraman] Lift it up?
- Yes, with my muscles.
- [Mom] What kind of muscles?
- All of them.
The majority of them, at least.
Whoa, you can't do that to me, mom.
I'd be very sensitive right now.
(growls)
- [Man] Are you singing a song?
- No, I'm exercising my upper neck muscles.
(mumbles)
- [Mom] No, put it on your face.
- Oh, oh, okay. (sighs)
- [Mom] Keep the swelling down.
- Oh, why didn't you tell me earlier?
Why was she walking like that?
She was just walking in the middle of the sidewalk.
- [Mom] Perfect, no, no, not so much.
Collin, stand up, sit up.
(laughs)
Collin, sit up.
(laughs and snorts)
Sit up. - I can't.
- I know, but you gotta stay focused.
- Whoa.
They put me like on this table
and I was on the table and they were like
"hey" and I was like "hey!"
and then they like had this needle
and they took the needle and they put it in my arm.
And I was like (screams)
and I was like chill, I was relaxed.
I think I'm gonna start drooling.
Cause I literally can't swallow.
I can't swallow anything.
Why?
- [Mom] We're gonna get you a Jamba Juice
but you can't use a straw.
- Yeah, I love Jamba Juice!
(sighs)
(incoherent noises)
- [Man] What's your favorite video game?
What about Battlefront?
(yells)
Yeah?
- Can you figure out how to get in that chair?
Okay, good.
- I made it!
- Move your legs over.
Oops, nope nope nope.
(laughs)
You gotta sit up a little bit.
This is the hardest part, this is hard.
Okay, see if you can, there you go.
- I did it!
- [Man] Are you excited for Jamba Juice?
- Uh-Huh!
Feed me.
(coughs)
- You can close your mouth to swallow.
- I really can't feel this part of my face.
- I know, is it numb all the way up to here?
- No, no, no, yeah.
Don't touch me, don't touch me mom.
Amateur.
Why do you guys support me?
You guys are freaking awesome!
- More jello cups?
- I get to eat jello?
- Yeah, or I can get you sorbet later.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Oh my god, that's awesome!
- Yeah, I know.
- I'm so happy.
(slurping and giggling)
Shh, I'm stealing her tissues.
I didn't touch your tissues, mom.
jello! Yeah!
- That's good, that's good, okay, glad you're excited.
(laughs)
Okay, slow down, slow down.
Wait, stay there!
Where are you going?
Oh, you're gonna go get the, you can.
You can feed yourself.
- One small bite for man,
one giant bite for mankind. (slurps)
(laughs)
(chokes)
(yells)
- You can have your jello cup back.
- Yeah!
If you guys enjoyed this video,
give it a big thumbs up for a little bit of encouragement.
Comment down below what was the funniest part
of me being awesome?
Subscribe to my channel because I do awesomer
videos than this a lot.
I love you all so much.
I will see you next Thursday.
Until then. (yells)
And now I'm gonna get up, and keep filming.
- What are you doing?
- I filmed the outtro to the Thursday vlog.
- Oh good for you.
- Yeah, I did a really good job.
- All right, I'm here like a dinosaur, ha ha.
Okay, let's go.