- Let's go!
- Wait, no, no, no, no, no! (Devan screaming)
No, no!
Bro come on, are you kidding me?
We are doing an
extreme Coke and Mentos video.
We're starting off, we got a whole bunch of Coke here,
a whole bunch of Mentos.
We've also got some Wubbles.
We're gonna be starting off the smallest Wubble first,
filling it all the way up with Coca Cola,
and from there adding a ton of Mentos
and just watching it go crazy, we're gonna go for
a medium sized one and last but not least
a full-sized Wubble filled with a ton of Coca-Cola,
a ton of Mentos, to see what happens.
But before we get into it, we've got a challenge for you.
We want to see if you guys can subscribe
to this channel and turn on the channel post
notifications in five seconds, here we go.
- [Devon And Collins] Five, four, three, two, one.
- Done.
If you can do that, comment down below
Keyper Squad right now.
And at the very end of this, this super Wubble
is exploding in someone's face.
So make sure you guys stick around for that,
but right now let's get into this video.
Yee!
No I'm joking, I'm joking, I'm joking.
Yee! (bottles clatter)
- Why, dude, why?
- It was impulse.
Oh, we're off to a great start.
No fail so far.
We're gonna be starting off
a little bit smaller with a balloon,
so Devon, if you wanna pop those open right now
and just so you guys know, if you wanna try this at home,
it takes seven Mentos in one two-liter thing of Coca-Cola.
I think it's Diet Coca-Cola that you wanna use.
And as Devon demonstrated,
yes, it will go crazy and it will go everywhere.
(growling)
You're gonna be filling up one of the balloons.
Should we go with the two-liter?
I think we should, like, some of the little one.
- Yeah, let's do a little one.
Yeah, let's do a little one.
(somber music)
- Also, like, throughout this video, ha!
Oh.
Ha!
Oh, man.
I had this beautiful image in my mind of like
it was going like whoo, and like go flying out
and me catching it and it'd be like ah!
But it didn't work.
Here we go, so what's gonna happen,
we're gonna dump this in first.
- All right, you got it? - Yeah, okay.
Let's see here.
Oh no!
- No! - Oh, no!
- No!
- I'm so sad it got shaken up
before we could even put it in.
- Wait, but is that gonna counteract the effects?
Does it do that?
Is that a thing?
I don't know if that's a thing.
- I don't think so, all right, here we go.
- I guess we'll find out. - We're gonna dump it in.
It's not working.
- Maybe we have to stretch it.
- Yeah, yeah, stretch it, Devon, that's good.
Okay, here we go.
What, another one?
How did, did I shake this?
I probably, oh, I tried to throw 'em.
That like shook 'em all up.
- Oh that's right. - That was not a good idea.
Ha, ha, ha! (buzzer)
All right, you ready?
- Yeah, I guess.
(upbeat music)
- Ha!
Oh, I thought.
You spilled it.
How does it? - I don't know.
- Huh?
All right, let me see, oh, I know what I need to do.
You need to actually stretch the balloon out first.
- Oh.
(balloon hissing)
- You can get rid of that one, bro.
- What do I do with it? (laughs)
- I don't know.
(air horn honks)
Drink it.
- All right.
(ballon hissing)
(balloon hissing)
I'm really concerned right now.
(balloon sputtering)
- Whoa!
- No! - No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Not in the rose bushes! - Bushes!
We got it, fam! (laughs)
That was close.
All right, Devon's gonna be opening up that.
We got two more Coca-Colas,
gonna do like a quick little like open.
Yah!
(bell dinging)
All right, here we go.
You ready? - I think so.
All right, I got it.
- This one here should go better now
because it's all stretched out
so let's give it a shot.
(upbeat music)
No, I don't think that it--
- I think it is going better.
- It's better, but like it's not best yet.
If you know what I mean-- - 'Cause nothing's.
Oh, wait, hold on.
- Oh, it's not even filled up yet.
- It's like a heart. - Oh, okay it's working.
I'm gonna grab it like this and just kind of
stretch it out.
- It better not break.
- So we're gonna add a little bit more Coca-Cola.
(upbeat music)
- That works a lot better for sure.
- Yep, see if we stretch it out, absorb it.
Oh!
Dude, it's drinking it!
It's like empty on the top.
Dude, check this out! - No!
- Come here, look at this!
It's actually like taking it, dude.
'Cause see if I like stretch out the balloon,
it like opens up space
and it takes more of it.
All right, Devon, remove it on the count of three.
You ready?
One, two, three.
- Got it.
Got on me.
- Perfect, so now we have our first balloon
and now it's time to add the Mentos
so Devon, if you wanna get that prepared.
This thing just like sags, bro. (laughs)
- Wait, hit it on the table.
(balloon thuds)
(laughter)
- It's like a giant earlobe bro.
Hilarious, fam!
Here we go, I have an idea. (bell dings)
You have to remove the finger.
(ballon snaps)
- What, what, what?
- Ow.
- What are you doing, bro?
- I have an idea!
- Let me do this.
Let me do this. - This is ingenuity.
- No, no, stop. (laughs)
- So I've been given the Mentos duty.
Oh, I have an idea.
Dude, I got it, I got it, I got it.
- I don't think there's any way to open it.
- I know what we're doing.
- What are we doing?
You're letting it go.
What are you doing?
- Just let go! - No!
- Be a man!
(growling)
Okay, there we go, hold onto this.
- Okay.
- We're gonna stick the tube in the top of this.
- And then just like let it all kind of fall in.
All right, here we go.
Three, two, one, add 'em in, add 'em in.
Dump 'em, dump 'em, dump 'em, dump 'em!
- No, we lost one!
We have a casualty.
- I mean, we're improvising, guys.
We're gonna give this a shot.
- Want me to turn it upside down.
- Here, three, two, one, here, upside down.
- [Devon] Whoa!
What?
- Shake it up!
(screams)
(laughter)
(screaming) - Round two!
- Let's go!
(high-pitched wailing)
So for this one, we have to utilize
the funnel technique right here
which basically, you stick a funnel inside of
the medium sized Wubble.
While he is doing that, I've got something
I've always wanted to try, which is putting Mentos
in my mouth and then filling it up with Coca-Cola.
So as you do that, I'm gonna try this.
- What? - I don't know.
We'll see what happens. - All right.
(upbeat music)
- Ah, this is delicious.
I love this.
Oh, my, (gags)
(laughter)
- I can smell it from here.
- Three.
Two.
- I'm putting this down.
I wanna watch this.
- One.
(soda hissing) (laughter)
(Collins spits)
(Devon laughs)
(soda hissing)
Dude, my mouth straight up feels so fresh right now.
Like, so fresh, bro.
It's like the North Pole is in my mouth at the moment, bro.
Like, I'm just breathing icicles, like ah!
All right, guys, I want to try this one more time.
Take it to the next level
and this time I'm gonna like tilt my head upwards
as I put the Coca-Cola in my mouth
and maybe just like, I don't know, shoots in the sky
like a giant volcano of awesomeness.
Here we go.
Ow! (laughter)
It popped out onto my eyeball.
Oh!
(yells)
(laughter)
(soda hissing)
(spits)
(coughing)
It went in my nose!
It burns!
It burns a lot!
Well, I guess that was everything
I wanted it to be and more, so.
- Splash guard.
- I'm sorry, Devon, I'm so soaked at this point,
it doesn't really matter.
(Devon laughs)
All right, perfect.
There we go, yay!
All right, let's go for the next one.
- Yo, this thing is gonna break.
It's burping, what?
(Collins laughs) (burping)
Why is it burping?
- I feel like Salt Bae.
Oh!
(laughter)
Yay, alright, let's go for the next one.
Oops.
- Whoa, bro.
There's little bubbles in the Wubble.
This is insane.
Wait, look at this!
I think it's having some weird reaction to the Coke.
- [Collins] Oh my gosh!
- [Devon] Look at that.
- That's enough Coca-Cola.
Yay, yay, yay, yay!
So right now (laughs) next
we are gonna be moving on. - That rose bush is gone.
(Collins laughs)
- We are moving on to the Mentos.
I literally got it in my eye again.
We're gonna fill up one of these Mentos bags
with a whole bunch of Mentos
and then dump it in here and see
what kind of crazy reaction happens.
(Devon mumbles) This is gonna be crazy.
- It's gonna be insane.
- Here we go, three, two, one, you ready?
(Mentos plopping into Coke)
- Oh!
(crickets chirping)
(hand slapping Wubble)
Oh!
(laughter)
Bro! - Ow!
- What the heck?
- I've got an idea.
Actually, you know what I think would be really fun?
We're gonna do one more of the smaller ones first
and we're gonna see if we can do a good all like
roundhouse kick on it
and see if we can break it midair right now.
We're gonna fast forward and go right to the kick
so let's do this right now.
All right, guys, this is Devon's payback.
- All right. - Here we go.
- Here we go.
(Wubble explodes) (Devon and Collins exclaim)
(Wubble explodes)
(growling)
Look, my foot is like completely soaked.
(Collins laughs)
- All right, you guys, here we go.
We are onto the main event, the massive Wubble.
- No, no, no!
- But right now--
- No, no, no, no, no, no! (laughs)
No!
I literally already got soaked!
(Collins laughs)
- Let's get to it!
Yay!
(laughter)
- No!
(Collins laughs)
- Let's do it.
(Collins exclaims)
You little booger!
No!
No, no!
(Devon giggles)
(clock ticking)
- Yo, this thing is huge.
- Huge! - Huge.
All right, guys.
I'm about to pull the craziest prank on Collins right now.
He just went inside to get a whole bunch more Mentos.
Little does he know when he comes back,
I got a surprise for him.
- [Collins] Oh, got all these Mentos, all right, cool.
- Yo, what's up?
- Here we go.
So we got, all right guys,
so we got a whole bunch more Mentos.
We also have a giant bowl of Mentos right now.
We're about to add it to the giant Wubble.
So here's the game plan.
I'm gonna hold it and then you dump all the Mentos in.
All right?
All right here we go.
We got it open, you ready for this, Devon?
- Better close your eyes.
Better close your eyes.
- All right here we go, three, two.
Oh no, no, no. (Devon exclaiming)
Oh my god!
- Bro, this is crazy!
(upbeat music)
- It worked, it worked! - Dude, look at it!
- It worked, it worked! - Look at it, look at it!
- Huh?
- Whoa! (laughs) - Oh my god, no!
No, dude, you, it was this stuff?
(Devon laughs and exclaims)
No, dude I am getting you back right now.
No, oh my god!
- Oh my god! (Wubble slaps Devon)
(growling)
(heavy slap)
That so backfired.
What?
No!
(items clatter)
- Well that's the video, guys.
Love you all so much.
You guys wanna see. - Woohoo!
- I love you all so much.
I'm cold.
I'll see you on the inside. (screams)
No!
Bye!
(bell dings)
(upbeat music)
Hey! - Let's go!
- What?
(Mentos plops into soda)
Oh. - Wait, wait.
- Dude, dude, dude, dude. - Well that was lame.
- Dude, that was so weird. - Yay!