- Welcome back. - What's up?
Yeah, or that, okay. (Gabbie laughs)
What's up, it's Collins Key and welcome
to my brand new video and today I'm here
with the beautiful Gabbie Show,
Aye, turn up.
- Woah, woah.
- So yeah, welcome to my channel.
- Yay. - Good to have you.
We have been meaning to do a video together
for it's been like since the Demi tour right?
- Yeah.
- It's been a long time. - Wait, look how much
tanner I am than you.
- Okay, I tried tanning today.
Okay, I tried tanning today. - Did you?
- Yeah, I got burned.
And today, we're about to do a little battle.
We're having a challenge, we're going head-to-head.
We're gonna go a Viner versus YouTuber.
We each prepared a list of questions,
we're gonna go through them one by one
and whoever answers the majority of the questions right,
that person gets to hack the other's Twitter
at the end of this video.
So yeah, make sure you guys stick around
until the very end to find out what the crazy hack is
and give this video a big thumbs up if you're excited
to see this crazy trivia.
So yeah, without further ado, let's get started.
- I have some really good questions for you.
Just so you know, I'm gonna win.
- Uh oh, uh oh.
Guests get to go first on the channel,
that's how it works.
- With me when it's my channel, I just do whatever I want.
(laughs loudly)
- Well, I have to show a little bit of chivalry here, okay.
- What did crack kid get hit in the head with?
- A basketball.
(Gabbie scoffs)
I love that Vine. (Gabbie laughs)
Yas!
- Yah!
- I hope you have a shovel girl question in there.
- I don't. - Like what color
was her shirt or something.
- All right, well point Collins.
- Aye, turn up, you got the S.
- Well, of course.
- You have no idea how many people
mess with the S. - Really?
- Oh, yeah.
So before hoverboards, what did every YouTuber
ride around on?
That's not like regular scooters, right?
Okay, is it? - No. (laughs loudly)
- This was before I was popular. (Collins laughs)
You're killing me, Smalls.
Is it a scooter of some type? - No.
- It's not a scooter? - No, it's a Penny board.
- What the heck is Penny board?
- A Penny board, they're like little mini skateboards.
I think it started with like
all the British YouTubers, like they all
got Penny boards. - I've never heard
that in my life.
- Comment down below and name some YouTubers
that you guys know for sure rode Penny boards 24/7.
Okay, now it's your turn.
- So zero for me.
- Yep.
- Dang it.
Finish this sentence.
- Uh oh.
- If you want a french fry.
- Oh yeah, eat a french fry.
If you want a burger, eat a burger.
(laughs loudly)
What is the most disliked video on YouTube?
- Your board, I'm just kidding.
(laughs loudly)
I don't know any of these.
You were like, "Oh, give me some easy ones
"that I can answer."
- No, I wanted hard ones,
I wanted hard ones. - Most disliked video?
You told me you wanted easy ones.
- No, I want some hard ones.
- Oh, you're a cheater mcgeeter.
- No, what is this?
Oh my god, I grabbed it. - It's a Finn doll. (laughs)
- I'm like what is poking in my back.
- It's Finn the Human.
- Think about it, it needs a lot of views
on this video to get a lot--
- Justin Bieber.
- Which one?
- Is it Baby?
- Yeah.
- Baby has the most dislikes? - Yeah, the most disliked
video on YouTube, which is sad.
- Is it the most liked video on YouTube as well?
- I don't think so.
I don't know. - Baby, little Baby.
- I know.
It's pretty sad.
- Who has the most loops on Vine?
- Oh, I think I know this one.
Is it Lele Pons?
(Gabbie groans) Yeah, did I get it?
I'm acing this so far. - You Googled, I'm asking
the obvious questions. - No, I did not, I promise.
I did not. - This is my fault.
I did this.
- So every year YouTube does a video
where they recap what happened that year.
What is this video called?
- Oh my god, stop.
That's a really good one.
I don't know, I'm not even gonna try.
I can't even try. - You can't even try?
- It's like one of those things that you click it
and you know what it is,
but like I never remember. - Yeah, it's YouTube Rewind.
- Why was I gonna say that, or I was gonna say Replay?
♫ Shawty's like a melody in my head
♫ That I can't keep out
♫ Got me singing like
♫ Na na na na everyday
♫ Got my mind (mumbles) replay
- Yeah!
We started off strong and then it dipped
and then we got right back into it.
That was good.
- Don't drop what?
- That thun thun thun.
- (sighs) Too easy.
- You can go for another one, that one was easy.
- Okay, that was dumb.
We're not gonna count that, that was just a bonus round.
- Yeah, a really quick bonus.
- How do you block out the haters?
- With the spoons over your eyes.
- (sighs) Collins. - And you're like,
"Mmm, blocking out the haters."
What was the first YouTube video ever posted?
- Wait, I know this. (Collins laughs)
Now watch me whip. (laughs)
- Okay, do you wanna know what the answer is?
- Yeah.
- The answer is Me at the zoo.
- Okay, I did not know that. - It was like some dude
at the zoo with an elephant and he was like,
"Aye, it's an elephant."
And it was just kinda like, "What?"
- And that's what he uploaded?
That's like Vine now. - That was the very first.
(laughs loudly)
- Who on Vine hates sauces?
- Okay, this is so hard.
- This is a hard one, but not if you know Vine,
if you know it.
- Can I have like
a little hint? - Sauces!
- Sauces!
- Who do you think videos it?
- I have no idea.
- Look at all these sauces!
- Sauces!
- I actually thought I knew Vine, I've never--
- Are you pretending to not know to make
me feel better? - No, I actually have no idea
who this is.
- Um, Marcus Johns.
He had like a whole series about like,
"Look at all these sauces."
- Sauces!
- I got a point finally.
- What is the type of video where YouTubers talk
about their life story?
- Draw my life.
- Yes, that's it, yep.
(exclaims loudly)
(laughs)
- Who was the first Viner to hit a million?
- Was it Nash?
- No.
Oh my god, no.
Not even close.
- Okay, I don't know.
Was it like Marcus Johns?
- Marcus was the one, yeah.
- Okay, here's a quick one.
How old is YouTube?
- I know this for 100% fact.
It is, pause, wait.
15?
- 15 years?
- No. - No, they're 10 years old.
2005.
- I swear to god I knew that because that was the year
I started dating my first boyfriend
and in my head that was 15 years ago,
but I knew it was 2005 so give me that point.
I need it, come on.
- Okay fine, I don't know what just happened,
but you get a point right now. - I knew it was the year.
Who is the prettiest girl on Vine?
- Oh, this one's so easy.
It is the Gabbie Show, hands down. (Gabbie laughs)
Of course, of course.
Like I'm blushing sitting next to her right now.
- I thought you were gonna go, "Oh my god,
"that's so obvious, it's Lele Pons."
- No, I would actually say you, of course, yeah.
- Awe. - Because you're gorgeous.
- Who was known as the Squirrel Whisperer?
- Oh my god, I think I know what these are,
but I'm not.
Oh, Jerome, is it Jerome?
- Come on, he's the Squirrel Whisperer.
- I had no idea, but I remembered one selfie he took
on like Twitter with a squirrel and I love squirrels
so I was so jealous that he somehow talked to a squirrel,
like could make it
take a selfie. - Whatever.
- So this is the final question.
Name one hidden Easter egg in the YouTube website.
- Can I Google it?
- No. (Gabbie laughs)
That's so cheating, what?
- See, this is how small my capacity
for irrelevant information is.
- Irrelevant? - Like it's in and I enjoy it
and it's great and it's gone.
Like the Easter egg--
- Easter eggs are freaking awesome, they're like
my favorite things. - They're awesome,
but do you need to keep them in your mind?
- Absolutely for moments like this
when your challenging me.
♫ For a moment like this
- What is it?
- Well, there's a couple.
Like one is Use the Force, Luke.
If you type in like Harlem Shake, then all the videos
do the Harlem Shake and just cool stuff like that.
- I didn't know about any of those.
I just want to see one of them.
Oh my god, I'm so excited I'm gonna die.
(Harlem Shake music)
Oh my god.
(Gabbie laughs)
I love it.
- Stop it.
- Oh wait, okay.
I don't know how to make it stop,
there's no pause button, oh god.
Wow. (Collins laughs)
A tornado flew around my-- - No, a potato.
See? - A potato, dang it.
- Vine reference, I just made a Vine reference.
- [Viner] A potato flew around my room before you came.
- Clearly you won, Collins.
- Yeah, so that was kind of a landslide, but you were
a great sport about it. - A landslide?
- You were a great sport about it.
- Rude.
- Stick around to see what the tweet is
that I'm about to hack her with.
I'm gonna post it in just a little bit,
but for right now make sure you guys give this video
a big thumbs up and also comment down below
how many of these questions did you know
and also what's some other random trivia
about Vine or YouTube that you think
we have no idea. - I need schooling,
I need schooling.
- Make sure you guys check out the Gabbie Show
on her channel because we just did a video over there
where we did a Halloween What's in my Mouth? Challenge.
- It's really gross.
- I don't even know what happened there. (Gabbie laughs)
You guys just have to go watch the video right now
because things got crazy.
Now, it's time to announce the keeper of the week
and this was actually inspired by this girl right here,
the Gabbie Show, because she has a showstopper of the week,
but my keeper of the week is Stephanie Keeper
and you are on Instagram, you are always going so hard,
I see you all the time and I want to say a big shout-out
to all my super active Instagram accounts
because you guys make me smile so much
like whenever I go to tag photos,
you guys are always posting the coolest edits ever.
So shout-out to all of you.
And I'm gonna feature more of the Instagram fan accounts
in upcoming videos so if you guys want
to be the keeper of the week, all you have to do
is just be super active on Instagram, on Twitter,
on YouTube sharing my videos, liking, commenting.
Basically the more active you are,
the better chance that you have of being
the keeper of the week, but again,
congratulations, Stephanie, I love you.
- And here is the tweet is that Collins decided
to share with all of my followers.
- Cheese.
Boom, and now it's gone, but if you guys
want to see more fun tweets that we do,
you guys should follow us on Twitter.
I'm just saying her at name is right there,
mine is right here.
Bye. (snaps fingers)
- Collins, where'd you go?
- Aye. (Gabbie screams)
Do the Harlem Shake.