Всем приве-е-ет, с вами Брайн!
Добро пожаловать в Five Nights at Freddy's 4. Ваа-а.
Но сразу говорю для этой игры нужны хорошие наушники
Эмм!
О вот кажется у меня есть кое что для этого дела.
Ну что-же ставим громкость на максимум и вперёд.
Новая играаа!
Так! Ну что это за смех был.
5 дней до вечеринки
О господи!
Он выглядит очень очень очень очень очень МИЛО!
Чооо!
И он с нами разговаривает О ГОСПОДИ!
Он говорит
Так тут у нас мини-игра,и она мне уже не нравиться
Потому-что меня пугает этот медведь который следит за мной глазами
Я хочу выйти,Давай!Стучись в эту чёртову дверь
Чего тебе надо Завтра другой день
На этом конец мини игры
и начинается
Ночь 1 да
кликни сюда что бы подбежать к двери
ОГО
Ого это уже не плохо
СЛУШАЙ ВНИМАТЕЛЬНО ЕСЛИ ТЫ УСЛЫШИШЬ ДЫХАНИЕ ТО СРАЗУ ЖЕ ЗАКРЫВАЙ ДВЕРЬ
And also we have a cupboard certainly not out of any vylazit muzzle
but you would not be scared if you are bi night went to the closet and saw something like
CHO!
So there was no one
Lord, this is a game already keeps me stress though it has only just begun
So
TTTTTTTT
nobody here
HECK
all on the darker it's not like I do not like
Breathing're here.
So I once again run up in the fucking door but no one, and I expect there to howl that something terrible
and howl worst thing is to expect that the worst when there is no wa
CHOOOOOO!
so by the way we're oooh God is that Cho was it was
Now you need to check this door because there may also be those fucking eyes
I heard the breath you heard breathing
No, of course we're SUCH BLIND IDIOT !!!!
XYX he left
breathing, oooo I slishal breath God is so terrible stress
XYX
so you need to turn
AAAA Lord, who are you
Wrap
I fuck you out of my bed
АААААААААААААААА
OH MY GOD
ААААААААА
It was so unexpected that I put in my pants
Well now everything curtain pancake
I do not want to put up with it enough to endure it
pancake and scho these sounds and so no strain, no bi put here Normal Música example
Hmmm!
YO ahaha
There's someone in the kitchen climbs
MAMA IS YOU
For 4 o'clock in the morning, and so far nobody to me, AAAAAA went out from the court
Uraaa we passed the first night, only the first principles for the second time is not bad
What would be some sort of mini game
four days before the party.
You know he's hiding again
So this tells us that as I understand it bear
so well, that I look at the door there is now, and now we can get out of the room yes
Again, this fucking BEAR!
Cho and Mangla Mangla you doing here?
God I'm so sorry to look at this person is not on it and on it
m yes but of course now it's here on the telly to watch AAAAA ahah
what the hell fucking foxy damn what he was doing
So, Fun with Plushtrap, fun to use the ctrl Plushtrap for flashlight and there was something to write about something that would keep the cho
OH MY GOD
He looks so scary as much as I fear and do not have to look
He's RAN
What kind of report time
So I'm not going to explode ??)
What I do not understand this shit ,, light lumiere whether to arrange
TOO BAD.
I do not cope for a task well, because I do not actually know what to do was
Night 2 Well
Shoot, and who blinks
AAAAALLLL!
Only the second night began what the hell
Ohrenet it is much more difficult than the previous part of this game
Well try s new, and by the way just noticed the snail with eyes phones with eyes.
Who looks at the lamps, which look at the robot, and the robot looks at the fan, and the fan
You cho FOOL!
So, I go ka check the door and I have not tested them
so does anyone
Oh there she was
Damn I Slizhov what the steps to my mime
EYES AGAIN WHAT IS HELL
This door ka Now I moved all the recovered his fucking eyes
I'll go better check
ААААААА!
What the hell, it is necessary to close the door, went out from the court foxy what you doing here
so I go ka so far from the court because I feel zade fucking Bears
flashing something, it probably means someone close, or that this is a bear put me nous
Oh God, he opened his mouth
This little sweet
so there is not anyone
and there is not one
and here
АААААА
HERE THEY ARE
foxy
Oh God when more than 6 hours of the night come on, let's not much left, I can feel it
and put me bear
yeeeeee
second night the first time, at least the first night the second time and the second night of the first
and the second from the first
Well 3 days before the party left
aha mini game, and neither uzhli without you about and who is it again Freddy s we talking just now in the kind of portrait
very strange
near the exit so if you run you'll be able to get out, that is for us who wants to run.
hurry output close to God foot quickly from someone only
Oh God too postural, in a hurry to find somebody who could help you you know what happens if you can not run the type of God
there inside oh just noticed that the inside of the baby's eyes bear
I Slizhov for you lalaalalala
so so for no damn he caught me
again, tomorrow is another day
Cho you tired of this day
Fun with Plushtrap
Use a flashlight that stop at around Plushtrap on X
This way it's a mark that is to shine a lantern when it is on it but no later, or earlier
because it can attack
He sits as butane Well brought my money
ok I again did not work ha
The main thing that went on to 3 night hmmm
huh I can shoot those huge headphones very loud headphones
Well I hope you like this video if so to put my finger top and subscribe to my RSS feed
also if you want to continue this game that would proshol rest of the night also put a finger top and write comments
Well, that's all you had to Brian emergency meeting until pff