- Hi sisters, James Charles here,
and welcome back to my YouTube channel.
Oh my gosh, it feels so weird to be sitting here
in the studio on camera recording this video for you guys,
but I am so beyond excited because it is about time,
and I am ready to come back and work so hard,
and to see all of you sisters. (squeals)
Okay, okay, okay.
I have a lot of thoughts, and I want to gather them
in this intro pretty quickly,
because this is gonna be a bit of a long video.
For those of you guys who do not know,
I basically just took a much-needed month-long break
from filming YouTube videos, and also from social media.
I've obviously been posting here and there,
kind of easing my way back into everything,
but it's been a very, very crazy month.
I've worked on a lot of fun things.
Let's be real, when I said that I was taking a social media
break, I kind of just meant from being so in it.
The past three years, I have been like literally addicted
to filming videos and checking my social media,
and it was so much fun, but it got to a point where it was
incredibly, incredibly toxic for me and my mental health,
and after everything that just went on on social media,
I just kind of needed some time to detox, slow it down.
Of course, still do what I absolutely love,
which is just handling business,
playing with makeup, and seeing my friends,
but just do it on like a little bit of a lower scale.
I'm really, really excited to say that after the last month
I've done a lot of growing and thinking.
I'm now able to leave my phone in another room,
and walk out and like enjoy life.
Which sounds so stupid, but like,
for me, that's like major, major progress.
I'm in a better state than I was mental-health wise.
I am just so blessed to have the same amazing friends
that I have around me, and it's been a really,
really incredible and eye-opening last month.
I'm very, very excited to tell you guys about it.
Obviously you guys know it is June, it is Pride month,
where all my fellow LGBTQ+ members get to thrive.
Literally my favorite time of the entire year.
One of the days I was playing with makeup,
I recreated a look by @chloefitzmua.
She did this like really cool rainbow dripping eye,
and it was so insane, it was so beautiful.
When I posted a story of it on my Instagram,
I got thousands and thousands of tweets and comments
asking me to film a tutorial on this Pride makeup look,
which is exactly what we're gonna
be doing in this video today.
We're gonna be playing with makeup and just doing
a little bit of a chit-chat, getting ready with me.
I have not filmed one in like literally over a year now,
which is is so crazy, but I'm so excited to just chill,
play with makeup, talk to you guys, fill you in
on what's been going on in my life for the past month,
and just talk about the future,
which I am so beyond excited for.
So if you guys want to see how I created
this look right here, keep on watching.
(upbeat uplifting music) (harmonizing)
All right you guys, let's just get started and get glam.
Usually when I do these type of makeup looks,
I start with my base already done.
So I'm just gonna kind of like,
go through it kind of quickly
with this little chit-chat get ready with me,
because the eye look took me a long, long, long time,
but it turned out so freaking bomb.
So I'm so excited to show you guys how I created it today.
I'm just starting off with my Tatcha Water Cream.
My skin has been disgusting recently.
It's really rude, like beyond homophobic.
In Pride Month too, how dare it.
I've been really taking extra care of my skincare recently.
Trying my best to get it kind of back to normal.
I digress, we're gonna be using very
full coverage foundation today, as always.
Next I'm gonna grab the Tatcha Silk Canvas as well,
and just put this on my nose and my porous regions,
just to kind of smooth everything out.
Next I'm gonna grab a little bit of the Dragun Beauty,
I think it's the Skin Perfecting Potion,
and I'm just going to color correct my beard region.
I have been getting laser hair removal,
which has been absolutely amazing, because I hate shaving.
It is my least favorite thing in the entire world.
I think I'm only on like my fifth or sixth session,
and it usually takes like 10
before it actually like stops growing back for awhile.
So we're still gonna color correct,
and get these gray tones out of this beard,
because I do not want it showing through.
For foundation as always, I'm just gonna
grab my Too Faced Born This Way,
and I'm gonna mix together the shades Nude and Golden.
I got spray-tanned last week, but it's already kind of like
basically gone, so I'm not exactly sure
where my skin tone is gonna end up being.
Oh, that's actually like a good match.
I'd like to thank not only God, but also Jesus
for this incredible foundation today.
While I'm blending this out, I thought it would be
kind of fun to just like tell you a little bit
about what's been going on for the past few weeks.
I've been posting little stories here and there
to kind of keep you guys posted,
but it is so weird for me to not be like literally
posting everything I'm doing at all times of the day.
I turned 20.
Which is so gross, disgusting.
I've been really not looking forward
to my 20th birthday to be honest.
I'm not really sure why, I just
really, really liked being 19.
It was by far the best year of my entire life thus far.
Obviously knock on wood, I have many more to come.
It was just really dope, and also, I feel like
a lot of my audience is very, very young as well.
So I feel like now that I'm 20, I'm like old,
and nobody can relate to me anymore.
Like, is this stupid, I don't know.
Then next year, it's like 21 when I'm like
an official adult, and then like can drink,
which literally does not even matter, because you guys know
that I don't do any of those things anyway.
I don't know, I feel like I'm getting old,
and I don't want to get old. (laughs)
Anyway, for my 20th birthday, my best friends and I
all celebrated together, and it was a day
that I will literally never forget, I had so much fun.
We took a boat ride over to Catalina Island,
which is basically just like a,
it's like a mini paradise honestly, off the coast
of California, and it was so, so, so beautiful.
We wanted to just spend a day on the boat
all together, swimming and relaxing
and listening to music and just having fun.
We were supposed to go parasailing too,
which I was so excited to do.
I've literally, that's like on my bucket list.
I want to go parasailing so freaking badly.
It just sounds like it would be so much fun,
but the weather was really windy,
so we weren't able to do that, which sucked,
but instead we got to have a really, really
nice lunch on the water, which was so delicious.
I think I got fish and chips,
and then we got to rent a golf cart,
and we got to drive around the entire island,
which was so much fun okay.
For those of you guys who have been following me
for a very, very long time, about two years ago,
you guys know my best friend Laura,
we went to, I think the US Virgin Islands
with Benefit Cosmetics, which was probably the best trip
that I've ever been on in my entire life.
It brought back memories, because when we were on the island
we got to ride around in golf carts.
Laura and I one night accidentally
drove the golf cart off of the cliff.
So yeah, that happened.
I don't really have anything else to say, but I don't
want to talk about it, dark memories, we were fine.
So getting the chance to ride together
on a golf cart again was exciting,
but also literally mortifying for everybody involved.
We split into two different groups,
and we got to ride around the entire island,
which was such an incredible experience.
(group cheering) (engines roaring)
We got to sight-see and see the village,
and also go to the top of the mountain
and see literally the most beautiful views ever.
Also too, on the way down the mountain,
it was around I think like two or three o'clock,
so all of the kids were getting out of school,
and we passed one group of kids on the way down,
and one girl turned and was like,
"Oh my god, that's James Charles."
And within seconds, we literally had the entire like school
running after our golf cart, which was probably the most
crazy experience ever in the entire world, it was so fun.
So we got back, we returned the golf carts.
I think we went to get Starbucks
and a little bit of ice cream,
then we went to the beach to take a little bit of a nap
and just kind of rest and get everything together.
In the middle of my nap, Drew woke me up,
and as soon as I got up, I looked at the edge of the beach,
and literally like 100 different school kids
were all lined up, and started singing Happy Birthday to me.
- [Group] Dear James, happy birthday to you.
- Oh my god, thank you guys. (cheering)
Thank you all.
And I literally started bawling, it was so cute,
and it just made my day so, so, so magical.
I literally could not stop smiling, oh my gosh.
Just the act that all them took the time to find us
and sing to me, just made my birthday so, so, so special
and I got to take photos with every single one of them,
and they were all so sweet.
- [Group] Hi, sisters!
- It was just a really cool and heartwarming experience
to get kind of a little glimpse into their world, of like
the island life, because it's so different than my world,
even though we're literally like right next to each other.
So that was so much fun.
If you're watching this, and you were on Catalina Island,
I love you, thank you for being
the absolute sweetest and making my entire birthday.
I'm actually loving how my skin is looking right now,
despite the fact that it is beyond dry
and literally crusting off.
Somehow it looks smooth, I'm happy.
I'm gonna move on and set my face in place
using a mixture of setting powders.
I think a really long time ago I did a video
about mixing all of my setting powders together,
and it literally made my skin look so good.
I was on set for a photo shoot and music video yesterday
for over 12 hours, and by the end of it,
my makeup still looked like I just put it on.
I'm not kidding, that has never happened to me before
with no retouches, and I feel like, I don't know,
but it could be the powder.
I'm obsessed with this mixture, and I'm never gonna
let myself go back to just one setting powder ever again,
because I need to lock this in.
Aside from my birthday, one thing that I've been
working on a lot over the past month has been music,
which I'm so, so excited about.
There was one night that my friends and I
were having a sleepover, and I ended up staying up
until like five or six in the morning.
I don't know why, we literally just could not go to sleep,
and when I woke up the next morning, I opened my laptop
to start replying to business emails
because it was a Monday, and I realized
that we had stayed up until five or six in the morning
working on an acapella arrangement of the national anthem.
I still to this day, like don't really remember working
on it, but I posted it on my stories and on my Twitter
because it was hilarious and absolutely awful.
(off-tune electronic singing)
And so many people were like, "Oh my God,
"you should actually try to record this
"and make it sound really, really good."
So that is exactly what I did.
I invited my friends Zoe and Gabe over, who you guys know
from the acapella group I was in, Flashback,
and we literally just spent the entire day
singing the national anthem and celebrating America,
which was so much fun, and by the end of it,
oh my god, I was so, so, so pumped.
I posted a video of it on my Instagram.
♪ That our flag was still there ♪
(group harmonizing)
- And so many of you guys were being so supportive,
which I was just so excited about.
Actually, my good friend Austin McBroom of the ACE Family,
invited us to sing the national anthem
at the ACE Family basketball game at the end of the month,
which I am so beyond pumped for.
Also really nervous because it's like,
literally the hardest song in the entire world to sing,
but I think it'll go really, really well, fingers crossed.
It was so funny too, because
when the poster for the game first went up,
it just said, "National Anthem: James Charles."
Then everybody started freaking out.
I don't blame you, but I'm promising you right now
I will never try to sing the national anthem alone.
I am well aware of the fact
that it would sound absolutely awful.
I don't have the range for it, I need my fellow
two harmonizers to make the arrangement amazing,
but I'm really, really excited for the event,
and hopefully you guys will tune in.
Alongside of the national anthem, I also got to go to
a music studio for a very, very exciting project,
which you guys will be seeing very, very soon.
If you remember at the beginning of the year
I went to Nashville, Tennessee and met the Cimorelli girls
for the very first time, and still to this day,
probably one of the best weeks of my entire life.
Love them the absolute most.
We did three videos together actually,
a harmonizing challenge on their channel,
and then a Demi Lovato medley, and then on my channel
we did our cover of Never Enough,
which is probably my favorite video of all time,
and also one of my most-viewed videos of all time,
which is so crazy that you guys loved it that much.
It means the absolute world.
After being in a group chat together and talking
almost every single day for six months
and not seeing each other, we were getting deprived,
so the Cimorelli girls flew into LA and we got to
spend the week together, which was so, so, so much fun.
(exclaims loudly)
They were filming a ton of different videos,
working super hard, as always, but we definitely made time
to just chill and hang out together,
and of course create some really amazing music,
which I am so pumped for you guys to see.
These videos may, maybe even be better than the first ones.
I don't know, I don't want to put it into the universe.
I'm gonna let you guys decide obviously when they come out,
but they are so good, and I am so excited
for you guys to see them.
Just singing with the Cimorelli girls
and being around them is just like literally
one of my favorite things in the entire world.
They are all just the most amazing and kind people,
and they are exactly what I needed during this break
just to kind of raise my spirits.
And I am so glad and so excited for you guys
to see the videos that we have coming very, very soon.
Now that my contour's all done, I'm just going to
bake my face using that same mix of setting powders.
Then we're going to move on to (pops tongue) the eyebrows.
A lot of times I skip my brows in my videos just because
it's kind of the same process over and over again, but,
but I'm gonna include it today because
I have a fun little new technique that I want to try out.
So I'm gonna grab my Anastasia Brow Wiz, just like always,
in Medium Brown, first and start sketching them in.
I'm gonna try my best to talk during this brow portion.
So if these turn out absolutely disgusting
like 2016 James Charles' brows, it's not my fault (laughs).
So like I was saying in the beginning of the video,
I was really, really excited to actually have
a little bit of time off this month because I got to use
a lot of it to play with makeup.
Now obviously makeup is my job,
and I literally love doing what I do,
I would not change it for the entire world,
but sometimes when I'm filming or just going to events,
it starts to get a little bit less fun because
I don't get to be as creative as I normally want to be.
So because I had nothing to do, I got to really sit down
and literally do whatever look I wanted to do,
which you guys obviously saw on my Snapchat.
I did a drag look, and we did like a whole fun little
photo shoot in my bed with my team, which was so much fun.
I'm gonna insert a little bit of vlog footage right here
if you guys want to see some of that, because it was crazy.
(camera flash whining) (shutter clicking)
- Merci. - That's a man!
That is a man, (laughs) that is a whole entire man.
(woman laughing) Oh lord Jesus
in heaven above. (shutter clicking)
Oof. (laughing)
Oh, that one's kind of, oh, the nipple's showing.
Aside from doing my own makeup though,
one thing that I have been dying to do for the past
honestly several months now, has been get my makeup done
by a few different makeup artists that I love the work of.
I've just been wanting to get my makeup done, and then
look at the finished result and just like analyze it.
Look at things that I love, look at things
that I don't love as much on my face.
Spoiler alert, all of the artists absolutely killed it.
I worked with my good friend Eros,
my friend Arielle Espana, and then also Glam Tech Steven T,
and I looked so freaking beautiful.
It was just really, really fun to work with some new
artists, see my face in a way that I don't see it every day,
and also pick up a lot of new techniques as well.
You guys know that I have kind of fallen into the trap
of using the same products and techniques
a lot. (laughs)
But I feel like I learned a lot,
and I'm really excited to implement them into my routine,
because I feel like that's what being an artist
is really all about at the end of the day, and try them
on for you guys, which we're gonna do (snaps) right now.
Now that my brows are all filled in, and I like
the shape that they are kind of going in right now,
before I go in and cut it with concealer,
I'm gonna grab the Anastasia Dipbrow Gel.
Now if you guys remember a few videos ago,
I talked about the new Dipbrow Gel kind of in depth.
It is a new product to the Anastasia Brow line.
I'm obsessed with it, it's basically
a mix of Dipbrow and eyebrow
gel, duh, hence the name Dipbrow Gel.
It's a very, very full-coverage brow gel.
When I was getting glammed by my good friend Arielle Espana,
she actually used this color, which is blonde, okay,
obviously I'm not a blonde,
but to set the brow hairs in place after,
and it really, really lightened them up
and kind of gave them this like gray effect,
and I was obsessed with it looked.
I thought it looked so cool, it was a very, very
different look for me, and I want to try it out today.
So I'm gonna grab Dipbrow Gel in the shade Blonde,
and I'm gonna go in and just kind of
brush this through the hairs right in the front.
Then kind of like fade it in,
and this is gonna kind of give us that like Instagram
ombre brow type of look, look at that.
Oh, that's good, that looks so good, oh my god.
I love that, I love this technique.
Thank you Arielle for showing this to me.
Thank you Anastasia for creating
a really, really bomb product.
See this is why I love working with new artists,
because you never know what techniques you're gonna pick up
and how you could change your routine.
I definitely want to keep doing this,
because this looks really, really good and fresh.
Okay, I'm gonna do the other brow off-camera quickly,
cut them with concealer, and I'll be
right back to start off the eyes.
All right you guys, we are back,
and both eyebrows are on and slayed.
Now it is time to move on to the eye looks,
where we are recreating this like dripping Pride look
inspired by @chloefitzmua.
For this tutorial today, I'm gonna be grabbing the brand-new
Morphe 25L palette, I know shocking,
not the James Charles palette, we're probably
still gonna grab one at some point later on.
But this is the brand-new 25L Live in Color palette,
and this is part of Morphe's Pride collection.
It is a beautiful rainbow palette obviously, and aside from
the white and black, none of the shades in here
are dupes of the colors in my palette.
They're completely unique and different.
Both beautiful rainbows, and I am
so excited to play with it today.
They also launched a Pride brush set as well,
which I'm going to dip into.
If you guys want to check this out, here's the catch though,
you can't use code James.
Now shocking, I know you've heard me say this
literally a million times, but I'm really, really excited
because with Morphe's Pride collection,
they actually announced that they would be donating
100% of the net proceeds to The Trevor Project.
The Trevor Project, in case you have not heard of it
or don't know, is a charity that deals with anti-bullying
and suicide prevention and awareness
here in the LGBTQ+ community,
and the work that they have done is absolutely amazing,
and obviously you guys know
I love Morphe and work super closely with them.
So this partnership, I truly feel like
is like a match made in heaven, and I am just
so excited and so proud of Morphe for doing this.
Literally they're making zero dollars on this campaign.
Everything is going to help the community.
Check it out if you guys want to, it's really, really
amazing, and your money is going to an amazing cause.
To start off my eyes today, I'm gonna grab the brand-new
Anastasia Beverly Hills Eye Primer.
This actually launched at the same time as their
summer collection and the collab with Alyssa Edwards,
which I from so excited to check out as well.
Definitely let me know if you guys want
to see a video using the Alyssa palette.
I freaking love her, but for now
I'm just going to take a flat brush, this is the M166,
and I pat a little bit of this primer onto my eyelid
so the shadows have something to stick to.
I'm first gonna grab my M431, this is just the pencil brush
that is available in my brush set,
and dip into the bright red shade, which is called Life.
And tapping off the excess, I'm going to pop this
right in my inner corner to start off that rainbow ombre.
Next we got the same brush, I'm just going to wipe off
the excess on the edge of my hand, and then dip
into the bright orange shade, which is called Pride,
and I'm gonna put that right next to the red.
I'm just really taking my time in packing those colors
on there, and slowly kind of blending as I go.
Blending together matte bright shades
is one of the hardest techniques to do in makeup,
and it really does take a little bit of patience, so.
Got to make sure we get that nice ombre blend.
Next with another pencil brush, I'm just gonna
grab the shade Sunlight, which is the bright yellow,
and pop that next to the orange.
Oh wow, that is a bomb yellow.
Next with another pencil brush, I'm gonna grab
the shade Nature in the bottom of the palette,
it is the bright lime green, and put this next to Sunlight.
For the blue shade, I'm just gonna grab an M124
and dip into the shade of Playground from my palette,
just because the 25L doesn't have a matte blue in it.
I'm just tapping this in to kind of form that outer V shape.
Going back on a little bit of Nature
to blend those two together.
Gonna grab a little bit of Truth and Love Wins
mixed together to create a neutral purple shade,
and use this to kind of sketch out the outer point.
Now I'm just gonna go back in with the same colors
that we used before just to kind of
finesse a little bit of this blending in here.
Okay so now we're gonna move on
to the concealer little drips and creating that 3D effect.
So I'm gonna grab my Tarte Shape Tape,
and this is in the shade Light Medium Honey,
which is the same color that I used to cut my eyebrow,
and a tiny liner brush, gonna dip into that concealer
on the back of my hand, and super, super carefully
and slowly I'm gonna start drawing in my little drips.
All the drips should kind of follow this general shape,
which is basically just like a line down, and then
a kind of dot at the end to simulate the paint drip.
You all know what a drip looks like, just follow me.
You want to keep dipping back into your concealer as well
because when you go over these colors, the concealer
is going to mix with the pigment underneath on the brush,
and you don't want the paint drips to look like
light green, or light blue,
or light whatever color you're over.
You want them to look like that nude concealer color,
so don't be afraid to use a lot.
While this concealer is still wet,
I'm gonna grab the tiniest little packing brush I can find.
This is the E39, and dip it into the shade Canvas
from my palette, which is the like light bone-color shade,
it's pretty close in color to the color of my concealer,
and I'm just gonna start patting this over top
to set that concealer in place.
Okay, so now we need to add the shadows and highlights
to the eye look, so it actually looks
three-dimensional and it looks like it's dripping.
This is where it gets fun, or a lot less fun
if you have no patience. (laughs)
I'm gonna grab an E35 brush,
this is just a super, super tiny flat brush,
and I'm gonna use a mixture of the 25L
and my palette just to grab some darker shades.
I'm first gonna grab Boutique on this brush,
which is just a dark maroon red,
and a little bit of Benny as well,
and very, very carefully I'm going to use this color
right up against those lines that we created
with the concealer to form shadows.
Okay I'm not using this brush, that was a bad idea.
I'm actually using the M250-0 inside,
which is a liner brush.
If you make any mistakes along the way,
just grab you a tiny little dab of concealer
and you can easily fix it up.
Next I'm gonna grab a little bit of 10% Off,
which is just a deep burnt orange shade,
and use this to shade right underneath the Pride color.
Next I'm gonna grab a little bit of Tea,
and use this to shade the yellow.
Next I'm gonna grab a little bit of Daddy,
which is the deep green color,
and use this to create the shadow in Nature.
Then a little bit of NYC and Parade mixed together
to shade in that Teal region.
Spooky and Cola for the blue section,
and then Spooky and Escape for the purple finally.
Once your shadows are all done,
it is time to add the last step, which is highlights.
To add in the highlights, all I'm gonna do is grab
a tiny little bit of white concealer on the back of my hand,
and that same exact liner brush.
I'm gonna add in tiny little reflections
on the bottom right edges of all of the bubbles,
and you just want to keep in mind
that all the reflections should be on the same side.
You can also add in tiny little highlights
to any of the like, little droops,
just so it looks a little bit more real.
Yes, guide my way. (clicks tongue)
That was disgusting, that was gross.
I regret that, I'm sorry.
So that is pretty much the whole
drip technique, all complete.
Like I said, obsessed with how this looks.
I'm now gonna move on to the lower lash line,
but first I want to grab a tiny little brush,
and I'm going to highlight my brow bone using this
bright gold shade in the 25L palette called Stonewall.
Now we're gonna do the lower lash line.
Just gonna grab those same colors going back in the rainbow,
so first gonna do Playground.
Connecting that up to the little wing that we created.
Then Nature, then Sunlight, then Pride,
then last but not least, just a tiny
little bit of Life on the inner corner.
With that same brush from before,
we're gonna grab a little bit more Stonewall and just
put that right in the inner corner over top of Life.
That's like too bright, okay hold on, let me grab
a little bit of Literally from my palette instead,
which is a little bit more of a muted color,
and layer that over top.
Never thought I'd be saying a highlight would be too bright,
but I guess there's a first (chuckles) for everything.
All right you guys, and that is one eye all complete.
Definitely a lot of steps involved with this look,
but not too complicated if you have a little bit of patience
and a very, very steady hand.
I'm gonna go ahead and do the other eye off-camera quickly,
and try my best to kind of match her,
or at least get relatively close.
Obviously the drips don't have to be perfectly symmetrical,
and I'll be right back to finish off the rest of the look.
All right you guys, we are back with the other eye done.
I just popped on mascara and false lashes.
These are the Lilly Lashes in the style So Extra Miami.
Literally my favorite pair of all time right now.
They out beat Miami by like, kind of a lot.
I like how dramatic they are,
and you guys can use code JAMES for 15% off
your purchase if you want to check them out.
I already went ahead and wiped off my bake,
so I'm gonna give my face a quick spritz
of the Morphe Prep & Set setting spray.
Then I'm going to grab the 25L palette once again actually,
and dipping into that Stonewall shade once again,
I'm gonna use this to highlight and see how this looks, ooh.
Oh my god, that is so pretty.
Wow, I really like how that looks.
Little bit above the eyebrow bone, as always.
Then I'm gonna use that color to highlight my nose bridge.
Now that that highlight is all placed on there,
I'm just gonna grab that same exact brush
and dip into Literally from my palette,
and use this to blend together the blush and highlight.
This is literally my favorite trick to do.
It looks so oh my god, it looks so pretty.
So actually in real life as well,
you can really see that pink shift to the highlight and,
oh my god like, yeah.
Since the eyes are very, very intense on this look,
I definitely don't want to take the attention away
from this area, so I'm just gonna apply a nude lip,
and use my favorite combo the
ColourPop iluvsarahii lip liner in Curvii.
Then just adding a tiny little bit of gloss in the center.
Then last, but finally not least,
finishing off this look with a spritz
of the brand-new Anastasia Dewy Set Setting Spray.
♪ Why do I need to be good all the time ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ I'm wrapped around his finger but he is mine ♪
♪ Don't care what they say too late anyway ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Why do I need to be good all the time ♪
- All right sisters, and I think that is this
dripping, rainbow, Pride Month makeup tutorial all complete.
I am literally obsessed with how this look turned out.
Oh my gosh, I am so glad
that you guys asked me to film this.
Literally the first time that I posted it on my Snapchat,
I started getting comments right away,
and I was so annoyed, because I'm like,
"Oh my god, I just spent six hours on this,
"why did I not think to film it?"
But I'm so glad that I got to sit down and play with makeup
and do this look again today.
Thank you once again to @chloefitzmua
for inspiring this look.
All you sisters, make sure to go check her out
and show her some love and support.
I'm sure she would really, really appreciate it,
and she's the genius behind this
original concept and this Pride makeup look.
I really hope you guys enjoyed this video today as well.
I really don't film chit-chat
get ready with me's kind of ever either.
Honestly I've always been a little bit scared to do them,
because I feel like we do so many crazy things
on this channel, that people don't even care
about these type of videos anymore,
but I really hope that you guys enjoyed this video.
I definitely had a lot of fun sitting down today,
talking to you guys one-on-one,
giving you a little bit of a life update,
but most importantly, taking some time
and doing what I love doing the most,
and why you guys are all here on this channel,
which is playing with makeup.
So, I loved filming this today,
and I really hope you guys liked it, too.
If you did, please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below, and show your love and support.
It would mean so, so, so much to me.
Also leave me a comment and let me know
what type of videos you guys want to see
now that I am back here on YouTube filming once again.
I am so pumped to get back to work.
The last month has been a much-needed mental break,
but I'm also going crazy.
You guys know I'm a workaholic, and a sister is ready
to get back to work, and I hope you guys are excited.
If you have not already, make sure to click
that big gray Subscribe button down below,
and come join at this sisterhood.
I would love to have you in the family,
and also click that bell icon so you get a notification
every time I upload a brand-new video.
If you'd like to follow me on my makeup journey,
you can follow me on Instagram and Twitter,
they're both just jamescharles.
My Snapchat for more behind-the-scenes type stuff
is jamescharless, with an extra s after Charles.
One last quick thing before we end off today's video,
I've been getting a lot of questions about Sisters Apparel,
so I thought I'd give you guys a super quick update.
We did have to switch our merchandise partners, but we have
a new company that I am very, very excited to be working
with, and we should be up and running very, very soon.
Obviously I will keep you guys posted.
We did have a summer collection planned for the middle
of May that has a ton of items that I am so pumped for.
The Sister Slides that I showed you guys months ago,
that I've been getting so many questions about,
literally like to this day, Sister Slides is like one of
the most searched terms on the Sisters Apparel website,
and they're not even out yet.
We have water bottles as well,
perfect for the summertime or working out.
Also Sisters swimwear too, swim trunks,
and a one-piece bathing suit, they are so beyond cute.
Then for June, Pride Month, we had our
Rainbow Artistry Collection coming back as well
with a few new added pieces
that I am so pumped to show you guys.
With everything that has gone on,
we did have to push both launches backwards,
so the first thing that will come out
will be the summer collection,
and then after will be the Pride collection,
even though it's not Pride Month.
One thing that I do want to tell you guys is that
I was planning on donating a huge chunk
of the Pride Month proceeds to The Trevor Project,
just like Morphe did with their Pride collection.
When it does launch, I will still be donating
a huge chunk of the proceeds to The Trevor Project.
Just obviously, a little bit later on.
Since however, the donation wasn't able to be made right
now, I do want to do something special for Pride Month,
so I've decided to donate all proceeds from this video
on AdSense directly to The Trevor Project,
so we'll add those together, and I will keep you guys posted
with how much we were able to raise for the foundation
when the Pride Month collection launches later, so.
Lots of fun things.
All right you guys, this has been a very,
very long video to film, but I had so much fun,
and I really hope you guys did as well.
I love you so, so, so much, Happy Pride,
and I will see you on the next one, bye, Sisters!
♪ Why do I need to be good all the time ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ I'm wrapped around his finger but he is mine ♪
♪ Don't care what they say too late anyway ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Why do I need to be good all the ♪