- [James] Hi sisters James Charles here and
welcome back to my YouTube channel.
Jumping right into today's brand new video, I am very
very excited but also nervous for this video.
This is something that I wanted to film
for a very very long time now
and that is how I used to do my makeup
versus how I do it now.
This trend has already been going around for a
pretty long time now so this is
definitely not an original idea.
A few years ago people were doing
the how I do my makeup in high school versus now
challenge which was so much fun to look back at everybody's
transformations and even I did a video a
few months ago where he reacted to and
recreated my first ever makeup tutorial
and even though I've only been in the
beauty community doing makeup for about
three years now I will definitely say
that my makeup has changed so, so, so much
hopefully for the better,
I mean I literally used to have Sharpie eyebrows
that took up half my freaking forehead
and a man bun that was a literal rat's
nest on the top of my head.
In the past three years I will confidently say that
I've definitely upped my style, makeup tips,
techniques and products that I used so
for today that I thought it'd be so much fun
to split my face right in half and do
a little beauty battle with myself basically,
when you literally don't have
anybody left to collab with
and do one half of my face how I used to do my makeup
with all the old techniques and products and
the other half of my face how I do it today,
see the comparison, see how everything has changed
and hopefully you guys will pick up some tips and techniques
of what not to do along the way.
So without further ado let's take a trip down
memory lane and jump right in.
(upbeat music)
I just scrolled down my Instagram for several minutes.
Literally I have PTSD from looking at some of these
disgusting photos but I came across this look that
was posted on May 14, 2016 and it is captioned tangerine.
I feel like for the old half my face, this is a really good
look to do today that encompasses kind of all the techniques
that I used to use and now don't use for obvious reasons.
That has gotta be the harshest contour
I've ever seen in my entire life.
My eyebrows taking up half my forehead.
I will say and pat myself on the back a little bit too,
through scrolling down through all these repulsive looks,
the one thing that I was never horrible at was eyeshadow.
Everything else has been majorly improved
but I was always a pretty decent
at eyeshadow and it was always been my favorite part
of the makeup routine so definitely
just a super simple glam eyeshadow look.
My winged eyeliner is going straight out.
I don't even think I have a lash on.
My nose is not even close to contour and my lips are lined
normally and this was before I had anything done to them
so you get the picture.
I think this is the perfect look
to recreate today and even though it is pretty simple,
I think there's going to be some very dramatic changes
from one side to the other and hopefully I'll be
able to show you guys a lot of really
helpful tips and techniques so let's jump right in.
So the first step of a makeup routine
is of course always skin prep.
Now on the old side, I'm just gonna go right
into the Benefit Porefessional primer, no moisturizer,
nothing beforehand.
I literally used to be obsessed with this stuff.
I would use the most of it.
This primer for me is one of the main reasons
that started my conspiracy theory that primers do
absolutely nothing because this primer actually hurt my skin
more than it actually helped which I'll get into when
it comes to the nose in a little bit.
Now on the newer side of my face I'm going
to first grab the Tatcha Water Cream.
This is my all-time favorite moisturizer
and a good moisturizer is super important for me
before I put on any makeup to make sure my skin
stays hydrated and healthy all throughout the day
and is able to breathe underneath eight ounces of product.
Obviously as you can see I'm having a very intense
breakout on this side of my face right now.
I'm not exactly sure why.
I've been traveling a lot recently and I've been
of course taking extra precaution to
make sure my skin stays healthy
but we're not gonna be taking this into
consideration when it comes to the final judgment later on.
Thanks.
Although I don't always prime now,
when I do skincare is of course my number one priority
and that means I usually go the Tatcha Silk Canvas Primer
which I feel like is also very very fitting today
because just like the Porefessional,
this one is obviously meant to it fill in everything
and make it very, very even so hopefully
we're going to flatten out these pimples
that we have going on.
So normally next I would jump right into foundation,
but on the old makeup side
we actually have a few more steps to do
before that so I'm gonna let the primer
sit on the new side and right now we're
going to go in and a color correct using
the LA Girl Pro concealer in the shade Literal Orange.
So I obviously am a man and I do have a 5 o'clock shadow
that is really, really inconvenient.
I am getting laser hair removal all over my face to
get rid of it because I absolutely hate it
but now I just use a full coverage
foundation and a lot of concealer to
cover it up to kind of eliminate using
87 different products on my face but
back then it was not the case,
so I'm gonna put this basically everywhere that hair grows.
I was apparently convinced that I was doing drag every time
I put my makeup on.
I'm just gonna blend that in using my Beauty Blender.
This next step I cannot believe I ever actually did,
but if you scroll back to one of my first
YouTube videos, it isn't most definitely there.
When I first started to makeup I had a major, major issue
where every time I would do my foundation
they would always completely slip off my nose
and leave little holes and cracks and look disgusting
whenever I tried to nose contour.
I was so convinced it was the oils in my nose
that I was literally just sweating
all day long
but I later found out once I was educated
that it was actually the Porefessional primer
not really working together with a foundation that I always
used and that is why.
That is also why I stopped using it this combination
but at one point I did finally find a trick to
fix that and I taught you guys in my
videos if anybody remembers from
literally day one and that was using a
Mac Paint Pot and literally putting a
huge layer of that on my nose before I
actually put any foundation on and the
logic was that if the foundation slipped off
when I tried to contour,
there would be another extremely thick layer underneath.
Absolutely ridiculous.
I really could not tell you why try new primer
or try new foundation never crossed my mind
like a normal human being
but this trick did do the trick for a pretty long time.
I'm gonna keep my Paint Pot out because
we're gonna be using it later on on the new side
when it comes to eyeshadow
but it is now time to move in to foundation.
For foundation on the old side
I'm gonna grab the Make Up For Ever Ultra HD stick
in the shade Y325.
Now if you've been along since day one
you would know that this was literally
my ride-or-die Holy Grail.
I still to this day I really like this foundation and
the formula to it a lot if you guys saw
my finding my perfect foundation shade video
from a few weeks ago this was literally one
of my top contenders and so many of the comments
said you guys really, really liked this color on me
but when I moved to LA it was just a little bit too dry
for my skin and I've obviously moved on to Born This Way,
which is what I'm gonna put on the other side of my face.
I'm gonna start by blending this in using
my Morphe M439 brush.
Use code James for 10% off.
That has never changed.
I can already tell that this color
is way, way, way too yellow for me.
I would always just blend the foundation right
over the color corrector as well and then always
be really upset and confused when I would
get hate comments telling me that I looked orange.
Should've listened.
Now on the newer side of my face,
I'm gonna be using the Too Faced Born This Way foundation
and for today's look I'm gonna mix together
the shade of pearl and natural beige.
The Born This Way foundation is a little bit
more medium coverage but can be buildable
and I like this formula a lot better
because it's more hydrating
and keeps my skin looking healthy
throughout the day as opposed to cakey
and I'm just blending this and using the
brand new Jeffrey Star X Morphe
contour and highlight sponge.
(beep)
Of course my camera stopped recording for a few seconds.
Sorry you guys I am back.
Would it really be a James Charles
video without a technical difficulty?
No.
Next I was obviously going to be concealer
getting right back into things.
I went in on the old side with the LA Girl Pro concealer
in the shade of porcelain, literally the lightest shade
that they have.
I actually have nothing bad to say about this concealer.
The formula is really, really bomb and it's only $6 as well.
I just wanted to move on and try out different formulas.
So on the new side, I use the Too Faced
Born This Way concealer in the shade vanilla.
I'm just gonna blend this in using a Beauty Blender.
I want to move on to the next side pretty quickly
because no matter on what foundation and concealer
and primer I'm using on my face if I don't work fast
I get very, very creasy and crusty pretty quickly.
So I'm gonna grab the Coty Airspun powder on the old side.
Obviously you guys know this powder has been with me
since day one.
I love this one.
This treated me very, very well when I was living back
in New York but this is also the powder that
created Flashback Mary
and definitely made me look very very cakey
because I was using way too much of it
but that's the whole point of learning
and improving as an artist.
So I'm just gonna grab a powder puff and dip right in,
pack this into place.
I can't believe that I used to literally do this.
On the other side of my face,
I'm gonna grab the Laura Mercier translucent setting powder
and I'm going to use my beauty sponge to
melt this into the skin.
Just for you know
slightly lighter coverage look,
I really really like using my same damp
beauty sponge to push in the powder to the skin.
I'm not really sure when I made this change
but I am so glad that I did because
I feel like this just does so much better of a job
to still set everything in place so it doesn't slip
around during the day but it just looks
so much more natural when you're up close
you don't get that same kind of
gross cakey and dry texture that you can
sometimes get using a powder puff.
I just feel like it really holds up a whole lot better.
Then I'm gonna grab a tiny little bit of extra powder
on a fluffy brush and just go over everything to
make sure everything is nice and set in place
and that I didn't miss any areas.
Now that both halves of my face are set in place,
the next step of my routine is of course going to be
to contour and chisel everything out,
add some dimension, but before I do that on the new
side I want to go ahead and give myself
a quick spritz of the Morphe Prep and Set
setting spray just to kind of melt everything together
and this is not something that I used to do before so
I'm going to keep my palette up here to separate it.
(wind chimes)
I don't know if you can fully see it on camera
but looking in the mirror this side of my skin is
definitely just looking a little bit more radiant,
you can kind of see the skin popping through,
which I really, really like whereas this side is
still really beautiful, it's super just
full coverage and very, very matte so
really just depends on the type of look you're going for.
Now for contouring the one palette that I used to use every
single day was the Kat Von D shade and light palette
and not gonna lie, it had a really, really bomb formula
and I loved it for a long time but unfortunately
I no longer have it in my collection and I
refuse to go buy it and support her so
I'm just gonna use the Anastasia contour kit
and just go a little bit more heavy-handed than usual.
Gonna grab my Morphe M405 brush and dip right there
into the middle shade and just go right in there.
I used to be obsessed with going in at the absolute
most with contour and I'm really not even sure why.
My cheekbones and jawline are already
pretty defined to begin with.
I really just wanted that like chiseled
jaw line moment which really didn't even look that good.
It honestly just looked ridiculous but
we're just gonna recreate it today
for the sake of the video.
I'm gonna use even more to contour out my forehead.
I mean this honestly has not really changed that much
because I'm definitely still insecure about the sides of it
but I am a lot better at making it look softer
and blended while still bringing it down a little bit.
Now you're probably thinking all right James that looks
crazy, let's move on to the other side and trust me
I'm thinking the same thing but 2016 James was not
because one thing that I loved to do was after my
contour was already laid down I would take
a smaller fluffy brush and dip into an
even darker contour shade and just get you know
a little bit on there and just go right into
the absolute hollow of my cheek bone
and just put down a little bit more.
Okay now that was maybe a little bit much.
It never really looked that bad.
Now going into that same exact M405 brush.
Well not the same exact one but same type,
you get the point and dipping into the same color,
I'm gonna go in and contour the other side but just go
a little bit lighter.
Holding this brush right between my side burn and ear
and just lightly blending this downwards
in circular motions, keeping it very, very light
and soft pulling just a little bit
onto at the top of my forehead
and still underneath the jawline as well
and then just gonna grab an M527 brush
and dip into this shade next door
which is a little bit more bronzy, caramel type of color
and I'm gonna use this to go lightly over top of that
contour color just to kind of blend together
the natural skin tone and the contour
without making it look too harsh.
I'm gonna quickly apply a little bit of
the MAC blush in the shade Peaches
on my Morphe E4 brush.
You guys know this blush is my all-time favorite
but I'm only gonna put this on the new side
because I literally hated blush
when I first started doing makeup and never wore it.
I really did not know what I was missing
because this looks so pretty and youthful but oh well,
you live and you learn I guess.
And now we get to move on to one of the most
important parts of my makeup routine
which is my nose contour.
Now if you've been following me since day one,
I'm sorry first and foremost because my
nose used to look so bad in all my Instagram photos
because I did not know how to contour and even when I was
learning how to contour it was still
a really really rough process.
At first I could not figure out
how to do the illusion, so it just looked bad.
Then I'd learned how to do it.
Then I learned how to Photoshop and FaceTune
so it looked so fake to the point where I couldn't even
breathe and now several years later I am finally at
a place where I'm confident with my nose
and how it photographs in photos.
I stopped erasing the entire thing in editing apps
but I definitely still do contour quite a bit
so I'm gonna grab my contouring brush and dip into the same
exact contouring palette firstly on the old side,
I'm just gonna grab that same contour color
and a lot of it too and I'm just gonna go
right in on the actual edge of my nose.
Oh my god this is triggering.
I'm blending that shape right upwards.
Oh wow, this hurts.
This hurts a lot.
Now if you really like the way that your nose looks
in makeup naturally of course
this step doesn't really matter
but for me personally I prefer my nose to look
a lot more narrow so I'm gonna grab the
same exact contour color once again but
instead of putting it on the absolute
edge of my nose and going around the bulb
which just makes it look really, really wide,
I'm gonna kind of focus this color on the top of the nose
bridge and pretend that the bulb tip isn't there,
just go right over it, kind of straightening it out,
which gives the illusion of
a more pinched and straight nose.
Just gonna do it another quick spritz of setting spray
before I move on to baking which is the next step.
- [Man] You're kidding.
- [Woman] That's kind of- - [James] Wow.
(laughs)
- [James] Are you kidding me?
Let's try that again, a little bit of urban decay this time.
Then just going in with some more Coty Airspun powder
and a powder puff to bake.
I used to put the setting powder here and just go
straight down and then I'm bringing it
all the way up to the back of my head,
I have no idea why and then right on the center of
the forehead and then just using the
Laura Mercier on the other side,
I'm gonna bring this powder all the way up
to the side of my nose to snatch it and
create that illusion and then just keeping it focused
right underneath my eyeball in this little triangular area.
I am very excited to tell you guys that
for the brow portion of today's video I
am actually partnering with Anastasia Beverly Hills,
that's right, to show you guys their brand new dip brow gel
and how I like to use it and also how I wouldn't
necessarily recommend using it.
If you've been around since day one you probably
remember the James Charles block brick Sharpie eyebrows.
Now at the time I loved them,
a few people on Instagram loved them
but for the most part they were disgusting
and everybody made fun of them all the time
including the Queen herself,
Anastasia Beverly Hills who tried to get
me to tweeze them all off and I literally
looked at her face and said absolutely not.
Can you say ego?
They had no arch to them whatsoever.
In fact, they almost looked like
I was frowning half the time.
They literally took up half of my forehead in thickness
and they also had no dimension either.
They were all just one color up straight like dark
brown almost black all the way through.
Three years later after a whole lot of bullying,
hate comments, tweezing and practice,
I am finally at a place where I really really
love my brows so let's compare the old to the new.
Starting off I'm gonna grab my Anastasia dip brow
in the shade dark brown and my Anastasia
number 7B brush and I'm just going to dip in to the palette
right here and I'm going to grab quite a lot.
I usually like to take the spoolie first
and go upwards just to kind of get the shape of the brow
but I'm actually going to use the spoolie
and brush them this way to actually kind of have a flatten
them out since I've definitely tweezed
an arch into eyebrows over the past few years
and I'm just gonna go right in
starting at the front of my brow
which I never recommend doing any more
and just drawing a line.
This really used to happen every single day
and then at the very last second straight down.
(screams)
Oh no.
I'm grabbing a little bit more
on the same little angled brush.
I'm just going to sketch in the tail of my eyebrow,
going out the top,
straight down and then using whatever is left
which is apparently a lot.
Just gonna brush that right in.
Can't believe I'm doing this right now.
Ah oh my god.
That used to be on my face every day and I
never thought there was anything wrong with it.
As if that was enough I'm next under
grab the brand new Anastasia dip brow gel
and I'm gonna layer that right over the top.
Now listen I'm actually really excited to tell you guys
about this product today because it's really, really dope.
This is a super, super pigmented, full coverage,
waterproof new brow gel but it can also be used
like dip brow to actually sketch in hairs
and actually add hairs in place.
I've personally been loving using this on myself
before I even draw anything in
and also on my friends that don't have as many brows hairs
because it does such a good job of kind of
sketching it in and still making it look
like a natural look but like I said this
is very, very pigmented so if you were
going for this block eyebrow which I would not recommend,
you could really just go right in
and push that product right in there
for the original James Charles Sharpie eyebrow look.
Gonna grab a little bit more of the LA girl Pro concealer
and I'm just gonna squeeze that onto at the
back of my hand
and then just grabbing a Morphe M410 brush.
Just gonna clean that up a little bit.
Now moving on to the now side of my face,
thank God, I'm gonna grab the Anastasia brow
in the shade medium brown to start this off.
Using the spoolie, I'm just going to a brush all the hairs
upwards and then going right in, I'm going to lightly
start in the middle of my brow drawing
just tiny little hairlike strokes at the bottom
just to create a little bit of dimension.
Then just following the natural shape of my actual
brow bone and going above that going to
bring that line upwards creating an arch
which is flattering for human faces
and then when I get to the tail,
I'm just going to pull that line straight out
as opposed to straight down.
Going back in with the spoolie each time as well
to make sure that nothing ever gets too intense or dark.
Then I'm just going to fill in the tail.
I'm gonna clean this brow up in a second
but I'm pretty happy with the shape so far.
I'm next going to go back into the brand new
once again Anastasia dip brow gel
but this time I'm gonna use the color soft brown
which is lighter than my natural brow colors.
Like I said this product is very full coverage,
so for someone like me who likes a defined brow
but doesn't want to look like this,
I like to use a lighter shade and go in
super, super lightly and use this brow gel
to still lock everything in place
while adding a little bit of extra color
but not a whole lot.
What's super cool about the dip brow gel as well
is that it does of course set down and lock your
hairs in place but the drying time is a
little bit slower so I'm actually going
to take another clean brow brush.
This is the number 12 and just go right in and
use the excess dip brow gel that is in the hairs,
use this to lightly blend the product forward
into the front of the brow and then using that same brush
just making tiny little upwards flicks to
mimic the appearance of real hairs
in areas that are a little bit more sparse.
Now the new dip brow gel is smudge proof
so it is definitely not going anywhere
but I do want to go ahead and clean it up just a little bit
so I'm going to grab the Born This Way concealer
one more time and then just a rounded concealer brush
and I'm just gonna go right in and
really make sure it is super clean.
All right sisters and those are both eyebrows all complete.
Go ahead take your screenshots.
I've handled the bullying once, I can do it again.
Let's just be thankful that there's been quite an
improvement over the last three years.
Here of course we have the original
James Charles sharpie brick eyebrows
and on the side we have the new and
improved sister snatch brow both created
using the brand new Anastasia dip brow gel.
It'll keep your brows waterproof, smudge proof
and looking absolutely fantastic all day long.
If you guys want to check this out, it is launching online
at AnastasiaBeverlyHills.com and in stores on March 7th
and it is only retailing for $18
and I totally would recommend.
That took plenty long enough and I never
want to experience that again
so I'm gonna move right on to the next step
of my routine which is of course going to
be the eyeshadow.
Now for eyeshadow primer, once again for the third time in
this video I'm gonna go to the LA Girl Pro concealer
in the shade of porcelain and I'm just gonna go right in
and paint this on the lid.
This is what I used to do in every single one of my makeup
looks and then I'm just going to blend this in
and I'm gonna set that base in place using some more
Coty Airspun powder on a dense packing brush
and then for the other side I'm gonna grab
my Mac Paint Pot once again for a slightly different use
this time and I'm just going to lay down a generous layer of
this right over top of my eyelid and I am not going
to set this one with any translucent setting powder.
Alright you guys so to create this warm tone smoky eye
that I had on in the original photo, I'm of course gonna
grab the James Charles X Morphe iconic palette
and I'm going to basically use all of the shades
in the middle row but this video is already getting
very, very long so I'm gonna do the eye
portion off-camera.
Like I said earlier the only one thing that I didn't have
that much trouble with was eyeshadow.
Of course I've improved my techniques and
gotten better at blending but regardless
I've done so many different videos on
eyeshadow techniques so I'm gonna cut quickly,
still use the techniques that I would have used
then versus now and I'll come back and show you guys
the finished look and move on to the next step.
All right sisters we're back and I just
completed the eye shadow on both eyes off-camera quickly.
As you can see the looks are a little bit different because
I wanted to recreate the look exactly on this eye.
It is just a little warm tone
half cut crease moment and it looked
like it was a matte shade on the lid and
on this side, I did kind of like a
modernized version if I was to do a warm tone
half-cut crease, this is kind of what I think of,
just kind of orange and brownie tones
pulled out into a nice little wing
and then a metallic glitter right on the lid,
kind of messily placed just so it reflects in the light
and looks so incredibly stunning
but regardless I think both eyes with different styles
and techniques still look really, really beautiful.
That being said, the next step of both of these eye looks
is a winged liner.
Although drawing a winged liner has never
really changed for me, I definitely did learn a lot
about where I like to place my wing.
Probably the worst part of having a thick eyebrows
aside from the hate comments was the lack of
eye shadow space that it actually gave me
to work with and at the time I obviously
didn't know this but when your eyebrows
taking up half of your eye region and
then are just straight downwards,
it really cuts off a lot of this outside
area that I would now like to use for
blending really big eye shadow looks.
So when it came to drawing winged
eyeliner when I first started,
I really did not have a lot of room to do it,
so the one mistake that I made all the time
was drawing my wings straight out just like that.
Now don't get me wrong drawing your wing
straight out can be a really, really helpful technique.
In fact, for my sisters that have hooded eyes,
it is the absolute best way to draw on a wing eyeliner
and make sure that it is actually seen
but for me as someone who doesn't have hooded eyes,
drawing your wing straight out could actually
tend to drive the eye downwards and especially
with a brow that doesn't have any arch
it's really not helping.
Over on this side, I'm going to pull the wing liner
much more upwards in the same shape that
I drew my eye shadow in.
Just like the eye shadow it is two completely
different techniques and styles.
I do honestly think that they both look really, really good.
This wing turned out better than I honestly anticipated
but I definitely still prefer a wing that is
much more pulled up.
I just think it really makes the eye
look so much more snatch and gives it life
whereas this eye just kind of looks a little bit
more dead and basic in my opinion.
Moving right along, I'm gonna give both sides of
my lashes a nice curl and then going to
apply a heavy coat of the Benefit Roller Lash mascara
on the old side and then on the newer side
I'm gonna add a light coat of the Mac Extended Play mascara.
Now as for lashes, I'm zooming in on this photo
and it looks like I don't have any on.
I'm not exactly sure but I do naturally have
pretty long and thick eyelashes to begin with
so I honestly might not have been wearing them
considering when I first started doing makeup
I literally could not put on lashes
without gluing my eyes shut so I guess I'm gonna be skipping
that on this side of my face today
but on this side I'm gonna pop on the Lilly Lashes
Miami So Extra.
Use code James chains for 15% off your purchase.
Alright guys those are both eyes all complete
looking beautiful, looking fabulous on both sides, kind of.
We're going to go ahead and dust off the bake
because this powder has been sitting on my face
for literally like too long now so let's do that.
It is now time to get our glow on and what is so crazy
is that we're actually going to be using
the same product on both sides of my
face and that is the Anastasia Beverly Hills
So Hollywood Illuminator.
This is literally the first highlighter that
I ever bought and I have stuck with it since day one.
I love this color.
It works so well on my skin tone.
I still reach for it every single time I do my makeup.
Clearly as you can see she's seen better days,
but she's still working good as new.
A lot of you guys know when it comes to applying a
highlighter or metallic shadow using a tiny little bit
of setting spray can really make a color pop.
Now when I used to apply highlighter
a very very long time ago I would do
what you're not supposed to do which is
basically drench the brush first,
this is a Morphe M501, and then dip into the pan.
Well this does apply a very very blinding and metallic glow,
this can negatively affect the formula in the pan
because you're basically adding a
setting spray and water to the mixture
where it was not intended to be.
Also when you apply highlighter wet,
it can look really really beautiful but it can
also look super streaky.
This might not look that bad on camera but in person
this looks absolutely ridiculous.
I know everybody loves a good glow and trust me
so do I but it just is not flattering.
I also used to shoot my Instagram photos
in a basement using only a ring light
so I used to have a major problem actually
getting my highlight to reflect for some reason
and I think that's probably why I went so ham
on the setting spray and highlighter before
but regardless let's go in and highlight the other side
and make it look nice and pretty the way I do it now.
This time around I'm gonna grab my setting spray
but instead of spraying my brush first
I'm gonna actually give my
face a good up little spritz.
Once again to kind of melt all the
powders together but also to give us some wetness
for the highlighter to stick to
and I'm going to be using the M504 brush this time
which is a little bit smaller than the M501
I'm gonna dip into the once again So Hollywood illuminator
getting quite a lot on there and I'm just gonna apply this
right on the top of the cheekbone
keeping it most intense right here
and then just using any excess that's left on the brush
to blend it out.
Much prettier in my opinion.
And then I'm just gonna grab a little bit of Face
from my palette and add that right on top.
Oh that just looks so pretty
and the little of sparkle glitter.
Grabbing a little bit more Face on that same brush,
I'm just gonna tap it off so there's not a whole lot
of product on there and I'm gonna pop a little bit
right above my brow bone for subtle little highlight here
and then also a little bit on the top of the chin as well.
My nose highlight has never changed,
just grabbing the M431 and a little bit more face on the end
of that brush, I'm just gonna draw a straight line
right down the center and then a tiny little dot
at the tip for my little explanation point.
Alright you guys, with our highlighter being on and glowing
to the Gods we can go ahead and move on
to our last step which is going to be the lips.
So for both sides of the lips today,
I'm going to using the Ofra liquid lipstick
in the shade Venice.
This is another one of those products that I've
been using a since day one and literally
have not find a better version of.
I really, really like the formula of the Ofra liquid lips.
Now since this photo was taken a few years ago,
a full disclosure I have had my lips done.
That was a personal choice by me.
It has been well over a year since I actually did them
though so they are definitely going way, way down
but they are still nowhere near as small
as they were in this picture so
I'm just gonna go ahead and apply this lipstick
to the old make up side and I'm not going to over line
literally in the slightest bit and then on the newer
side I'm gonna go just slightly outside
of my lip line for a more voluminous look
and we are finally finishing off of both sides
with a little bit of sister setting spray
to lock it all in place.
(windchimes)
(upbeat music)
All right sisters, then I think that is my
how I did my makeup then versus now look all complete.
Oh my gosh you guys it was so much fun
taking a trip down memory lane and reminiscing
all the old products, tips and techniques that I used
to use a few years ago.
It's only been three short years but I am so proud of
the progress that I've made from this to this.
I do think both sides still look beautiful in their own way
but I can also happily admit that three years ago,
I came to the beauty industry with a whole lot of passion
but also a whole lot of ego as well.
I truly thought I was the best, the best
that I could not get any better but boy was I wrong.
Practice really really does make perfect
and I am so grateful for every single one you guys out there
who saw potential stuck by me and also left
constructive criticism and that goes for all
my artist friends out there as well.
Thank you guys for always teaching me new tips and
techniques that I get to integrate into my routine
and just overall thank you for inspiring me and
being really cool friends.
I had so much fun doing this video today and seeing
how my style has changed and what's even
so crazy is that I'm probably gonna look back
at this video in five years and be like
ew this looks absolutely disgusting but
regardless I hope that all of you
sisters will still be here in the long run
and we can look back and laugh together
and I cannot wait to see where
the makeup industry takes us both.
If you enjoyed today's brand new video please
don't forget to give it a big thumbs up
down below and show your sister support and love.
It really means so, so, so much to me and
really helps me out and also click that big red subscribe
button down below and come during the sisterhood.
We are over 14 million sister strong
and I'd love to have you join the family and don't
forget to click that Bell icon so you
get a notification every time I upload a brand new video.
If you'd like to follow me on my makeup journey,
you can follow me on Instagram and Twitter.
They're both just James Charles
and my Snapchat for more behind the scenes type stuff
is JamesCharless with an extra S after Charles.
This video's sister shoutout goes to sister Sarabeth.
Thank you so much love for always following and supporting.
You know I love you literally so so so much
and if you like to be the next videos sister shout out
don't forget to always retweet video links
when they go live on Twitter and also
turn on my YouTube post notifications.
Alright you guys thank you so much for watching
this video today.
Here's to another amazing three years of make up progress.
I love you so much and I will see you in the next one.
Bye.
(upbeat music)