James Charles: Previously on "Instant Influencer"...
Hi, sisters. James Charles here,
and today I have something extra special for you.
We started this competition with six artists.
- Hi, James! - Hi.
- There's been drama...  - Oh, you're so beautiful!
I was going for that wig.
Whatever. I'm still gonna beat him.
The sauce. I can't.
- ...and struggles.  - Paint is not the move.
Gabriel: Ten seconds on the clock. I still don't have my wig on.
Some have had triumphant wins...
The winner of today's Compact Challenge is Ashley.
Congratulations.
We're doing a drag show tonight.
You're extraterrestrial look was out of this world.
Two challenges in a row, baby.
...and some have missed the mark.
I'm sorry. I need to breathe before I cry.
She looks like a windburned Mrs. Claus.
But in the end...
The judges and I have decided
that your look was the weakest
and we have to send you home.
...only one
can become an Instant Influencer.
Good morning, artists.
- All: Good morning. - We have to talk.
So, last night, I got a chance to look back
at the footage from last week's episode
and I saw what you guys did.
You all look really confused. You know what you did.
I honestly feel like you all owe me an apology.
And scene.
Oh, my God.
- Really got me, James. - Jesus Christ!
( groans )
The blood went away from my extremities.
I don't know what was happening.
It was a hot mess,
but he deserves an Oscar for that.
James: Take this from me, because I've had to deal with this.
As an influencer, when you grow a following,
you will either say or do something that people
might not like and might not agree with,
and eventually you might have to apologize.
So, for today's Compact Challenge,
you guys will be filming your very own apology videos.
Oh, my God.
On each of your workstations, you will open up a compact,
and I have randomly assigned each one of you a minor scandal.
Okay.
You guys are going to have 15 minutes
to run anywhere you want on set
and to film a one-minute, no editing, apology video.
I like this.
All right, artists. Your time...
( voice breaking ) ...starts...
( loudly ) ...now!
Ha-ha! Good luck!
You can't have a great complexion
because I'm not supposed to be wearing makeup in this.
"Overdoing click bait titles to get views"? What?
"Missed your own meet and greet." I look like I just got beat up.
"Caught over-editing your photos."
"Filming second apology video to say sorry
for putting ads in the first one."
Whew.
- The things I do. - ( laughs )
I can say a million times
I'm not in this for the money.
Hey, dreamers.
I'm sorry that I misled you guys.
I want you guys to continue
to be honest with me in the future.
I just really want to apologize and I want to change.
( sobbing )
I love you guys all so much.
Please just remember that.
It's one take.
I'm gonna sit down and pick which one
I think is the best.
Allowing those ads to run, that decision that I made,
has shown you guys nothing
but that I am greedy and in this for the money.
Time! Time! Time is up.
Oh, shit.
James: Okay, bring me the phones, everybody.
Let's see what we got.
All right, you guys. Well, I know this challenge
was very short and very stressful,
but filming an apology video is not fun,
and sometimes you do have to address things in a timely manner.
All right, let's jump in.
Hey, Dreamers.
I wanted to apologize
for not coming to my meet and greet.
I've been through a scandal in the past couple days...
- The lash. - The lash!
The thumbnail was like somebody getting their wig snatched off,
and you guys were really upset
that that clip wasn't in the actual video.
My nose looks so much thinner than it does in real life,
and I-- it's because I have a Squidward nose.
I had a family emergency,
and it just was too heavy on my heart for me to come.
I'm, like, actually feeling it.
I know, I know.
Allowing those ads to run in my previous video
is absolutely unacceptable. At this point, all I can do--
James on video: Time! Time.
You're like, "No!"
- You can see my heart drop. - James: Yeah.
All right, you guys, well, I am so proud of all of you
for taking these scandals head on.
Hopefully, this will not be training for the future,
but if it is, now you know exactly what to do.
I'm pretty sure that you would all make it out of these uncancelled and alive.
So, congratulations to you guys.
But two of you guys really impressed me today.
Gabriel, your honesty and your message really came across,
and I felt like I was literally watching your apology.
"I'll be at the next meet and greet ready to take a selfie together."
And also Benny. You prepared so well for this challenge.
Ruining your makeup takes a lot of dedication,
and you really took it to the next level,
and I'm really looking forward to seeing
what your future photos will look like.
Congratulations, Benny.
you are the winner of today's Compact Challenge.
- Yay! - Which means you are going to  get a major advantage
in today's elimination challenge.
I won the advantage! I can't believe this.
My strategy was be crazy and to make James laugh.
Oh, my gosh. I have a win.
After today's Compact Challenge,
you guys are probably starting to feel like
- official beauty  influencers, huh? - Yes.
Good, but I want to take it one step further.
In today's elimination challenge,
we're gonna be focusing on one of the most important things
of being an influencer-- collaborations.
Both: Hi, sisters.
I'm gonna turn you into a sister skeleton.
Okay, let's do it.
( gasps, laughs )
Collab videos are super important because two influencers
get to come together to share ideas,
stories, and also their audiences.
And, if done well, it should pay off for both people.
It may seem like collab videos are super easy
and just two friends hanging out and filming a video,
but there is so much more that goes into it.
You need to pick a unique concept
that will grab the viewers' attention
while allowing both personalities to shine.
To help you artists out with today's challenge,
I want to invite in some of my friends.
- Hey, guys. - ( screaming )
- Hola, hola.  - Hi!
- James: Hello, hello. - Hi!
- Hi, guys. - Hello, you guys.
Thank you all so much for joining me today.
As I'm sure you guys know, but just to remind you,
we have Nikita Dragun, trans icon.
Da baddest, Bretman Rock.
Hi, guys.
- The Latina, Louie. - ( clicks tongue )
And also advocate for inclusivity, Nyma Tang.
Hi.
As I'm sure you guys have guessed,
you guys will be filming collaboration videos
with our influencers here today.
And, Benny, as the winner of today's compact challenge,
your advantage, you get your first pick of who you want to film with,
and then you also get to assign your fellow artists to their influencer.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. - Choose very wisely.
These guest collaborators are huge,
and I know who I'm gonna pick.
Benny, who do you want to film your collab with?
- I choose Bretman. - ( gasps ) Oh, my God.
Benny and Bretty!
I've been watching him for years.
Who do you want to pair up next?
Okay, I think I'm gonna go...
- Gabriel with Nyma. - Hi.
James: Okay. Come on down.
- Hi. - Nikita with Ashley.
- Okay. - Hi.
We have the same shoes, so--
- Oh! - Ashley: Watch out!
And then finally that leaves Louie with Kailin.
- Come here. - We have the same jacket.
Yes. Oh, my God, yes.
Now that you guys are all paired up,
artists, you are going to have three hours
to film and edit a collaboration video
with your influencers.
They'll be three to five minutes long,
and remember to keep them fun, unique,
and most importantly, very, very entertaining.
Remember, this is the last challenge
before the finals next week.
$50,000 is on the line.
And while we're on the topic of collaboration,
of course, a collaboration with me, yours truly.
So remember to blend, but don't blend in.
- ( gasps ) - Three hours until upload time.
Your time starts now.
- Okay, where are we going? - Let's go.
Let's go, Benny.
Like, literally I've been following you since 2014.
And, um, I just decided to get into makeup because of you and James.
- Oh, my God, that's so sweet. - And that's why I picked you.
Okay, so what are you vibing? Like, tell me everything.
Honestly, like, I feel like we have this really common
- just, like, bad bitch vibe. - Yeah.
And as I've been in this competition, they've kind of been like,
"You don't seem vulnerable,"
like, that I don't really show my emotions.
So what I think we should do
is really get down to the core of why we are the way we are.
- Yeah. - Like, my followers beg me  for teen mom stories.
I think it would be so interesting to, like, get to know you on that level.
- To really open up and... - Yes, I want to open up  to you, Nikita.
- ...almost take it off. - I want to open up to you.
- I want to take it off for you, Nikita. - Stop!
Do you want to say "Hola, perras"?
Or I always say "estupidas"  as my intro a lot.
- Ooh, that might be better. - Like, "Hey, estupidas."
Yes, let's do that instead.
By my favorite snack.
Kailin: I'm gonna do a makeup application
inspired by his favorite snack,
which is a huge part of his channel.
But above all else, I really want personality
to show and shine throughout this video.
I'm so used to doing longer videos, so if you think this
can fit three to five-- what's your goal?
- Five minutes.  I think five minutes. - Five minutes?
- What was your zodiac? - I'm an Aries.
I was thinking of maybe doing-- like painting you as your zodiac.
The reason why I wanted to do something with her zodiac
is because it's trending all over YouTube.
- Um, so, flames. - Yeah, I--
Yeah, let's go.
The plan of the video is to do a five-minute makeup challenge
that's really funny
and me and Bretman together is gonna be hilarious.
- We got this. Me, too. - I'm so happy that I got you.
- ( both laugh ) - That was so good!
- Hit record. - Okay, come closer to me.
You know James is gonna be so particular with that shot.
Three, two, one, start!
Ah! Okay. One, two...
Foundation, foundation, foundation.
Girl, it's not coming out.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God!
- We're not doing makeup today. - What?
We're going to be taking it off.
Okay, so, we're gonna start with lashes.
- Stop. Okay. - Yeah.
- I'm scared a little bit. - Why are you scared?
Wait, do you want me to soak these off or just pull?
- Yeah, pull 'em off. - You want to pull?
Ah! Ah!
Tell me a little bit about her. Who is she?
Honestly, I have had so much responsibility in my life.
I was a mom when I was 16, girl.
Like, when you're pregnant in high school, that's not easy.
Stop. How was that?
- It was horrible.  It was horrible. - What?
I was, like, a whore to everybody.
( both click tongue ) Hey, estupidas.
Welcome back to my channel. It's your girl Kailin,
and today I am with Louie. Louie's Life.
- The baddest perra.  - Yes, the baddest perra.
God, your lashes look incredible.
Wow, I look like a gremlin next to you.
No, you don't. Well, what got you into makeup?
What got me into makeup was I was an artist on paper.
- She's an artist. - Yeah.
I feel like I'm doing a bad job
'cause I feel like I'm not engaging with the camera.
This is, like, my actual, like, first collab.
I've never done this. I'm trying to think of talking points,
'cause this seemed like a great idea.
What do you think we're lacking?
Or what do you think could be better?
I think my editing will save me,
but I just think that I need to talk a little bit more.
Okay, let's do the outro.
- Bye, love y'all. - Bye, bitch.
Mwah! Bye, bitch. Aah!
That was really good.
Wow, everyone is still filming.
Yeah, I have two hours to edit. You know what? It's gonna look good.
That's another thing, too. I feel like a lot of people
want bad bitches to, like, fight each other.
Honestly. And it's like, there's room for everyone, girl.
There is. Okay, so should we do outro?
Thank you for doing my makeup. This is literally, like,
out of my comfort zone, but I love it.
My God, Benny, we're the first ones back!
We have an hour and 50 minutes.
- Let's go edit. - Let's go. Okay.
- You think you got it? - Um, I sure hope so.
Oh, my gosh. Gabriel.
What did I need?
If he's not back in, like, 10 minutes, that's not good,
because editing takes a long time.
( British accent ) We haven't got much time.
( normal voice ) Hi, baby.
Oh, you found some crystals, too?
Diamonds are a girl's best friend.
- Yes. - Diamonds are a girl's  best friend.
I love the diamonds.
You're so patient. I really appreciate that.
I just want to make sure we have time to edit,
- 'cause I'm scared. - I think we will.
Nikita: The challenge for this one is going to be
finding the balance of being vulnerable, funny, entertaining.
If it's not punchy, if it's not every single second is something,
then someone's gonna click off.
This is such a dope experience, 'cause I'm literally--
- Oh, my God. Stop. Thank you. - I'm learning so much.
Try to press that and cover the F-word.
( horse whickering )
I love it. I love it.
Okay, let's add some transitions.
We could even record it. I feel like it'd be funny.
Oh, my God, you're right. Wait, wait, wait.
- Do I need a lot  of transitions? - No, you don't.
- Do you know how much  footage you have? - We have an hour.
- Oh, shit. - I work slow.  That's my weakness.
I would focus more on conversations and comedy than so much makeup.
- 'Cause I'm not sure  what your focus is. - Yeah, I agree.
And I think you adding the dancing is gonna really show,
okay, they definitely did a collab, because it's what I do on my channel.
And then this is your channel, so it's like...
Right now I'm in rush mode.
Okay, I'm kind of thinking we should cut out all the food.
Our only option right now is just to start cutting footage left and right.
We're just hoping that what we're cutting
is not ruining this video.
You-- you-- you know more than I do.
- That was so stressful. - ( chuckles )
The most intricate eye look ever.
- Right. - I can barely film a normal  video in under three hours.
There is a lot to edit,
so we'll do this as good as we can.
You're about to see me, like, be so frantic.
- How much time do we have left? - 26 minutes.
It right now seems very jumpy.
There's just a lot. I'm stressing out.
I really did want to have the talking points in it.
But at this point, I think it should just, like...
- Makeup it? - Make it, like, a time lapse.
Right. Then you can go in and pick the specific audio
talking points that we had
and you can put that in behind the time lapse.
- I think I got this. - You got this.
( muttering )
Artists and influencers, you have five minutes left.
Five minutes!
God, I'm nervous.
Let me make sure it looks good.
I'm so scatterbrained that this is gonna, like--
I know it's gonna mess up somehow.
Not to put pressure, but there's two minutes left.
- Whoa, whoa.  What the heck? - What happened?
- Wait. Why did it do that? - Why did it do what?
- Oh, my God.  I deleted the footage. - Which footage?
Oh, my God, are we done? I can't...
Wait. Save it, yes. Oh, my God, save.
- Am I gonna hit save? - Save! Press save!
- We have... - 58 seconds.
- 56, 55. - No, stop. Press save.  You're making me, like...
It won't-- how do I click it?
- Click it. - It won't go.
( squeals )
Yeah, take that out.
You have to stop. If you don't save it now, you will not get anything.
Five, four, three, two, one!
Time's up! Hands up! No more touching.
I'm, like, genuinely terrified.
Yay!
Benny, we did it.
- Export. - 1080 HP.
Put it on Public. Trending. Hashtag.
Your videos better be done and ready for the fans to enjoy.
I am so excited to watch,
and I will see you in the judging room.
James: Hello, artists, and welcome back.
I want to introduce our guest judges.
Joining me as usual is Norvina, makeup icon and legend.
And we also have a very, very special guest,
one of my closest friends, Nicole Faulkner,
also known as Lipstick Nick.
She's the Director of Global Artistry for Morphe
and she's the founder of Pout Beauty Bar.
I cannot believe Lipstick Nick is here,
and I'm so excited to see what she has to say about our videos,
but I'm also really nervous
because I don't know what my video looks like.
Just like I told you guys earlier,
collaborations are a huge part of being a beauty influencer.
It's all about working together, creating unique content,
and sharing each other's audiences.
Remember, you guys, next week is the finale,
and after tonight's elimination,
only three artists will be left.
We have a lot of videos to watch,
so Bretman and Benny, we're gonna start
with your guys' collaboration.
The rest of you can take a seat.
All right, you guys, let's go ahead and check out
your title and thumbnail. Oh, my God.
"Iconic 5 Minute Makeup Challenge." Would you click or skip?
There's something really funny about it. I would totally click.
- Absolutely click. - In terms of the title,
personally I'm bored of the word "iconic."
I feel like it's, like, very overused.
- I guess. - Give me some excitement.  Give me some enthusiasm.
All right, let's check out this collaboration video.
Both: Hey, bitch!
It's your girl Benny Sarah. Welcome back to my channel.
( screams ) Or whatever. It's me, Bretman Rock.
Miss Benny, can I just ask you,
why are you not wearing makeup right now?
Well, we're going to be doing the five-minute makeup challenge.
Shut the-- ( horse whickers )
I did all of this in two hours
and you're telling me I only have five minutes to redo all this?
I have a date after this.
- Start! - Aah!
Oh, shit! Oh, my God.
And we blendin', bitch. And we blendin', bitch.
And we blendin', bitch. Out of time, bitch.
29, 28, 27...
Hurry up, bitch.
- Eleven... - Ten, nine...
- Oh, my God. - Four, three, two, one.
- Oh. - ( horse whinnies )
Okay, guys. Thank you so much, Bretman, for being in this video.
- And we both look... - A mess.
- ...very interesting. - But I had so much fun.
That's it for this video. So, bitch, be you.
Always be you. And stand out!
- All right. - Yes!
All right, you guys, Well, this video was definitely very fun and fast-paced,
which personally I definitely like to watch.
But maybe with, like, a little bit less of, like,
the profanity and, like, bitches and stuff like that.
Norvina, what do you think?
I really liked watching you guys.
You guys were high energy.
You could tell you were having fun.
James: Nicole, what did you think?
I felt like throughout the whole video,
you were kind of cut off,
so just try to keep that in mind.
Like, center yourself.
And I also would've loved instead of you screaming out
how many seconds were left, maybe you could've put a clock on there
because that's when you're gonna say funny stuff.
That's good quality content
that you guys could have had banter in those 30 seconds.
- Yeah. - Benny, you won today's  Compact Challenge.
What was your strategy in picking Bretman
and then also assigning the influencers?
I picked Bretman for me because as I started in makeup in 2015, um,
you and Bretman were the only beauty boys I really watched,
and that really inspired me to do makeup.
And for everyone else, I was just trying to, like,
pair who I thought would work together.
Yeah, so it was definitely like a positive--
- Yes. - This is a competition, though.
Well, thank you guys so much for sharing your video with us. Great job.
All right, Ashley and Nikita, you guys are up next.
All right, you guys, let's check out your title and thumbnail of your video.
Ooh.
"I Can't Believe I'm Talking About This."
Okay, I would instantly click this.
- Same, same. - Of course.
Well, let's jump right into your video.
Hey, guys. Today we have a very special guest--
- Miss Nikita Dragun. - Oh, my God, hey.
Ashley: We're gonna jump into something a little bit different.
We're going to be taking it off.
Oh, girl, I can do that. Hold up.
Nik-- Nikita! No, no, no, no.
Nikita, I want you to take my makeup off, and I take off yours.
Just this baddie who's always been
trying to find, like, her confidence throughout life,
especially through my journey of, like, being a mom really young.
- Wait, what? - Yeah, girl. I'm a mom.
Now he's old enough to where he cheers me on and supports me.
I'm sorry. I'm having an emotional moment as I'm trying to take this off.
I'm like... ( squeals )
Nikita, you're really similar to me in so many ways
even though we're such different people.
I have this kind of bad bitch mentality.
It's because that's, like, my almost, like, alter ego.
And I just felt like I needed to have, like, a defense mechanism.
When you're pregnant in high school, that's not easy.
Nikita, you've been amazing.
Thanks for getting vulnerable with me, girl.
Thanks for letting me take it off without having to take it off
because I would've charged extra.
Thanks for watching this video, and I will see you guys next time.
- Oh, my gosh. - That was so good.
I don't know you, but you're a baddie, you know what I mean?
You guys wore the same damn stripper shoes today.
It's amazing. And that can be intimidating to a lot of people,
so I love that I got to see, like, your vulnerable side,
and that makes you like a girl's girl to me,
both of you, so I really connected with that.
There was one part where Nikita started opening up about some real shit,
and then you, like, randomly jumped
and started talking about yourself again, and your pregnancy.
And I was like, "Oh, okay. We're going back to you."
I think it was just an editing flaw,
but overall I think it was a really cool concept, so...
Wow, that means a lot. Thank you.
Nicole made a really good point about, like,
I'm sure you let her finish in person,
but on the video, we didn't see it.
- It looks a little... - That is something
that as a content creator is so frustrating,
because there have been so many videos that I have posted
where I've gotten thousands of hate comments,
"Oh, my God. Why did he say this?"
Or, "He should've let this person talk more."
And this is for everybody as well.
Think about what the viewer's gonna watch
and how the organization might affect that experience.
Understand. Thank you.
But, Ashley, it was really awesome to finally...
- I knew it. - ...finally see you open up  and be vulnerable.
I love your guys' concept of de-glamming and getting vulnerable together.
I wish you would've explained why when you take your makeup off
it's like showing your true authentic self.
You kind of just jumped right in without a proper explanation.
Then all of the sudden, we're just getting lashes ripped off.
- Right. - It was amazing  hearing your story.
First time I've heard that story.
That's the first time I've shared it.
I'm sure there's a lot of young moms out there
that are watching and going like, "Tell me how you do it.
How are you taking care of your son and then also filming videos
and collaborating with brands? How do you do this?"
- I wanted to know more. - Get more into it.
- Absolutely. - Understand.
All right, Nikita and Ashley, thank you guys so much.
You can take a seat.
All right, Gabriel and Nyma, come on down.
Ooh. "My Zodiac Chooses My High Fashion Look."
- Oh, James is gonna love that. - I would click this because
I have a new interest in zodiac because of Norvina, actually,
and a lot of people are very interested in it.
I mean, I would click it 'cause of the makeup.
It's striking. This red eye shadow's beautiful.
- Let's jump in. - Lovely.
Nyma Tang. How are you guys doing?
- So, I'm so happy  to have you on my channel. - Thank you for having me.
Thank you for letting me do this with you.
I'm excited to see what you can do.
So, as you can see, I already started her lip.
Her being an Aries, she is a fire sign,
so that's what is inspiring this look today.
This is where it gets ugly.
( no audio )
Thank you so much for watching.
- I love you all. - Bye!
I thought the makeup was gorgeous.
She looks stunning.
I think one important thing that I want to add
for you, Gabriel, is you really have to
set your intention on what it means
to be an influencer for you
because that is how you should approach the project.
And I would love for you
to just collect yourself a little bit
and have a plan in the future.
Nyma is such a-- such a stunning canvas to work on,
and I really, really like the look you created on her.
Unfortunately, there was technical problems.
I would've loved an introduction into the video.
There was, actually. It was cut off.
There was a lot of footage.
I really tried to edit as much as I could,
but it didn't work out.
Your artistry is insane,
but for a video like this that's gonna live long,
it's way more about personality than anything,
especially in a collab video.
Thank you so much.
Gabriel: I'm really satisfied with my artistry,
but I'm feeling really not good.
All right, Louie and Kailin.
Ooh! "Hang With Me And Louie's Life: It's A Party."
- Very cute. - Okay, before we even  watch the video,
would you guys click it or skip it?
- Norvina: I would click it. - James: You would click it?
- Yes. - I would click it  because of the makeup.
But I personally like more of a, like--
a title where I know what I'm about to watch.
- It just seems like a hangout. - Yeah.
Okay, let's jump in to the video.
Both: Hey, estupidas.
Welcome back to my channel. It's your girl Kailin,
and today I'm with Louie. Louie's Life.
- The baddest perra.  - Yes, the baddest perra   in all the land.
We're just gonna have a good time. That's what's gonna happen.
We're gonna cheese me out. We're gonna do some makeup.
- It's gonna be a blast. - Yeah, it is.
We're doing a little Red Hot moment. You down with that?
- Little Red Hot moment. - Inspired by his videos,
- and kind of  his favorite snack. - My favorite snack.
If you guys want to see his favorite snack,
you're gonna have to go to his channel,
because that's what this is all about.
- ( speaks Spanish ) - Yes, get over there.
So, I wanna, like, know more about, like, your start,
- and how you got into it. - Okay.
'Cause you've been doing this for a while, right?
For a minute. I started doing YouTube, like, five years ago.
So this would not be a Louie's Life video
if we did not take a moment to dance.
Mmm! I'm gonna show you the jean grabber.
So this is the girl who is always dancing-- yes!
You know her. Do a little turn.
Oh, yeah. Thank you so much for being in my video
and hanging with me on my channel.
- It was so much fun  to have you. - Thank you.
- Until next time. - Both: Mwah! Bye, beauties!
So beautiful. I literally can't. You're stunning.
So, what do you want me to do for the B-roll?
I'm gonna zoom in.
Do you want it more-- do you like it more zoomed in?
Whatever works for you.
Whatever. I'm gonna laugh at it.
- ( applause ) - Yay!
- Norvina? - I loved the opening.
I thought you guys had such great chemistry.
That being said, I felt like I was watching a makeup artist
just doing makeup on her client and engaging with a client
that has an incredible personality.
So I was just watching Louie,
but I felt like you kind of faded into the background.
- Yeah. - So something to, you know,
think about for next time.
I am also Hispanic and I am a jean grabber, so--
- She knows! - Okay, I relate.  I can relate.
So, I loved that, and I know that it is hard
to work and kind of turn your head,
but I would've liked to see you turn your face
a little more to the camera.
- Yes. - Norvina: Absolutely.
Your vibe together was really positive.
It seemed like I was just hanging out with two friends.
That's what you want a collab video to feel like.
Obviously, there were some cut issues in the end.
Kailin, you struggle a lot with time management.
There were a few times where the video just jumped from one topic to another.
When I went on my cutting spree, I cut out those prompts,
and then I accidentally cut out those endings and...
James: But it's really about picking a concept
that you know you can execute in that time period.
Well, thank you both so much. You can go ahead and take a seat.
Kailin: I know I could've done better,
and for me to have made it this close to the finale,
I'm just annoyed at myself.
Artists, amazing job today.
Your collab videos were so entertaining to watch.
This has been incredible.
I want to say a major, major thank you to Nyma,
Nikita, Bretman, and Louie for joining us today.
I love you guys all so much.
You all killed it, and thank you for bringing
your personalities and also your knowledge to these influencers.
We judges have definitely a whole lot of thinking to do.
You guys can head on off, and we'll see you in a little bit.
- All right. Good luck, guys. - Thank you, guys.
Oh, my God.
Beyond drained.
So, this is a really, really important decision,
because obviously what we decide right now
- is who makes it  to the finale. - Yeah.
- Right. - Well, let's talk about Benny.
Bretman was, like, such a big support for me.
- Confidence boost. - But I just am scared  because you never know.
This video was super fun, but it feels like
- he's putting on a persona. - Yeah.
I enjoyed watching theirs the most out of everyone.
- Really? - Yeah, and I felt like Benny  really held his own.
Let's talk about Nikita and Ashley.
I started getting teary,
and I was pinching my freaking thumb.
And I was like, "Stop it."
Any time I talk about my son, that's, like, a trigger.
This was a very, like,
female empowerment type of video
and I felt very inspired.
So I really connected with that whole thing.
This was my favorite one of the day.
But she never connected
the removing the makeup and the vulnerable...
- Yeah. - ...which could've made it  so much stronger.
- Two seconds. - Should've been clear, yeah.
Shall we talk about the elephant in the room?
The overthinker in me was like, "Add more. This is not enough."
But I really regret it.
I should've taken that time to go and edit.
From what I've seen today, at least,
I don't know anyone else's level of artistry,
but he looks, like, crazy good.
He's insanely talented when it comes to artistry.
But we have just not gotten to know who Gabriel is as an influencer.
- Right. - Okay, let's move on  to our final video,
Kailin and Louie.
I just feel like she started amazing.
And then it just kind of-- I was like, "Kailin, where are you going?"
Yeah. I did like that she got up and danced.
Like, I felt like there was funny moments.
And if there was more,
I wish she would've kept that stuff in.
Although the editing was not great,
it made me want to watch more of them.
All right, well, it definitely seems like
we have our decision made up
about who is moving on to the finale.
- We do. - We do.
Norvina, thank you for joining us tonight.
- Thank you, James. - I love you and I will  see you next week.
And, Nicole, thank you so much for bringing
your knowledge and artistry to the competition
and I really appreciate your time.
- I love you. - Love you more!
- Thanks for having me. - ( sighs )
- ( line ringing ) - Hi, everyone.
- Hi, James. - Hi, James.
I wanted to give you all some news together this time.
All right.
Some of your collab videos today really clicked,
but some of them made me want to click away.
Oh. Is he gonna come back on?
James: Ashley, Benny,
and Kailin...
congratulations,
the three of you have made it to the finale.
Please come join me back in the work room.
Nice.
- Yes. - Oh, my God.
I made it.
I came into this not feeling like I deserved
to even make it through night one.
And for me to have made it to the finale,
like, I'm really grateful.
( knock on door )
Hi, Gabriel.
I think you know why I'm here.
Unfortunately, out of the collab videos today,
- the others really shined... - Of course.
...and yours was the weakest video
and I have to send you home.
I want to make sure you know I am so proud of you.
Technical difficulties and time management
are real issues that happen all the time.
Been there, done that, and I believe in you so much
to be able to learn and grow from this.
You are such an incredible makeup artist,
and the detail work in your looks literally blows my mind.
Like, there's so much that I want to learn from you.
This experience taught me what my life is about
and what I want to do with it,
because coming from a background where I didn't have much,
sometimes I can be hard on myself,
but I really made myself proud.
We got to know you as an artist,
but we want to know who is the influencer
underneath the influential artist?
'Cause he's there, and we want to see him
and I'm so excited to watch you grow even more.
- Thank you. - Before we go ahead  and send you home,
- I want to sign off  together, okay? - Okay.
All right, you guys, thank you so much for watching
"Instant Influencer" episode three.
I am joined by the beautiful,
the incredibly talented Gabriel Dreams.
You guys, make sure you go check out his work.
He is so incredible. Where can they find you?
It's Gabriel Dreams on all social media.
Both: Bye, Dreamers.
- We are the final three! - Yeah!
I'm really excited and thrilled
because I just can't believe it's all happening.
I put a lot of work and effort into this competition,
so, yeah, I'm definitely ready for this.
- Hello, my three finalists! - Oh, my gosh!
- Hi, James. - How are you guys  feeling right now?
- So, so happy.  I am so ecstatic. - So happy.
Ashley: Relieved and more nervous, actually, if that makes sense.
Now it's setting in and it's really, really getting real.
Next week is the finale.
I want you guys to get ready to think big.
That is your only hint that I'm giving you for the finale challenge.
- Wow. - I'm very proud  of the three of you.
Go home, get some rest,
and I'll see you very, very soon.
- Bye, James. Thank you! - Thank you so much.
I wonder what the challenge is gonna be?
- "Think big"? - "Think big."
- What does that even mean? - "Think big."
Thank you so much for watching this episode of "Instant Influencer."
If you enjoyed it, please don't forget
to give it a big thumb's up down below
to show the show your love and support.
Also click that subscribe button,
and finally click that bell icon,
so you get a notification every time
I upload a brand-new episode.
If you liked any of the looks that you saw today
and you're feeling inspired and you want to recreate them,
make sure you tag me, tag the show,
and finally #InstantInfluencer,
because I'll be reposting some of my favorites.
See you next week.