[music]
Hi, sisters! James Charles here.
Last year I started the search to find
the next beauty influencer.
You guys auditioned
and we flew out the best of the best
to compete in Los Angeles, California...
- Hello, you guys! - Hi!
...for fifty thousand dollars.
Oh my god!
I'll test their artistry,
camera presence,
and potential to be
a beauty superstar.
There'll be a few special guests.
You guys are hot too.
Sometimes we love people even though they're messy.
How do we fire her if she's already on set?
Remember to blend,
but don't blend in.
Go!
- Just go big. - Or go home.
What the ****?
Three...two...one! We're done!
I have no idea what this looks like.
I honestly feel like you all
- owe me an apology. - [crying]
Some missed the challenge a little bit.
I want to fight both of you right now.
- There'll be a ton of surprises. - [screams]
But only one can become
an Instant Influencer.
[music]
Cut. Period.