♪ I got you under my skin, yeah ♪
♪ You are a bad, bad thing ♪
♪ Care about no ones ♪
♪ But you under your skin, yeah ♪
- Hi sisters, James Charles here
and welcome back to my YouTube channel.
Now if you'll notice,
we are not exactly in our normal filming location.
I am currently at my front door
and that is because for today's brand new video
we are doing the one thing you guys have been requesting
for a literal months,
and that is the finished house tour.
Now if you guys have not yet seen my video
from Tuesday, make sure to click right up here
because I teamed up with literally one of my favorite
YouTubers of all time, Mr. Kate,
and we decorated my entire house.
Now in case you missed it, I moved into a beautiful big
house about four months ago now
and my life has changed so much for the better.
Myself, my little brother, my friends
and my family are all able to come over here,
relax, get some work done, and just feel so at home
and I literally am so beyond excited
to finally have it fully decorated
and looking so incredibly beautiful.
And this home would definitely not be possible
if not for you guys.
So like I promised at the end of last video,
welcome to my finished house tour.
(uplifting music)
- [Drew] Wait twist around, let's make sure
your foundation matches, for a real one.
- Does it? - [Drew] Yeah it looks good.
I just wanted to make sure. - Okay.
- [Drew] 'Cause this is where you got caught last time.
- That's so true.
So walking into the front door of the sister sanctuary,
we have a big open kind of like formal foyer
which I really, really love.
You can basically open the front door
and see all the way out to the back yard
which is like probably my favorite part of the entire house.
Obviously we're gonna walk all the way through it,
but I just love the open floor plan,
it makes everything feel so connected.
On the first wall of the house, we put a beautiful
huge kinda circle mirror.
So when you walk in, you can check yourself,
make sure you look beautiful.
Or if you're heading out for the day,
you can quickly pop right back into the mirror
and see if you still look sister snatched,
which of course, we do.
It is my job.
But as you can see in the background of this mirror
is the first room of the house,
the first thing that you see when you walk in.
And it is this beautiful formal living room
that was actually completely style by Mr. Kate and Joey.
This was like the surprise room that they do
for their little series, Oh My God We're Coming Over!
Favorite series literally in the entire world
here on YouTube.
But, they basically locked off this entire room
and decided to sister style it for me.
When I first moved in it and started decorating the house,
this was literally the only room that I had
absolutely no idea what to do with it.
I know I kinda wanted it to be like a formal living space
for when you first walk in,
'cause I feel like that's how a lot of houses are I guess.
But I wanted to give it to the hands
of Kate and Joey who I absolutely trusted,
and I trusted them for the right reason
because this room literally looks so beyond beautiful.
I feel like it is the perfect entry way
into the sister sanctuary.
So if you guys wanna check out the full transformation,
make sure you go check out the video on their channel.
I'm gonna link it down below, I absolutely love them.
But if we do a quick little walk through,
we have a beautiful little chaise lounge
right here to just take your shoes off
and relax after a long day of work.
We also have a little table with a sister safety pin.
Because the earing that I always wear
I thought that was such a cute little detail.
We have a fireplace to keep warm because it does get
a little chilly here in the California nights.
This beautiful piece of artwork that Kate and I did together
is a little DIY project.
And of course this beautiful, brand new, shiny black
baby grand piano.
Oh my god you guys, I am absolutely obsessed with this.
This was actually gifted to me in secrecy
by Linda Morphe, the founder of Morphe.
As you guys know I did my palette with them
and this just means literally the entire world to me.
As you guys know I do have such a huge passion for music
and playing the piano.
I of course have the one upstairs as well
which we'll get into later.
But working with the Morphe team on my palette collaboration
has been literally like a dream come true
and I'm so grateful to every single one of them
and the fact that they wanted to go out of their way
to buy me such a beautiful and timeless gift
that I can play every single day,
like means the entire world to me.
Now that's pretty much the formal living room all complete.
Like I said, if you guys want full details,
head over to Mr. Kate's channel.
But if we move onto the next room now,
we have the dining room (laughs),
which I'm so beyond excited to actually have in this house.
Obviously the center of this room is this huge table
that we got from Ikea.
I really, really like this table because it's so large
and big and can fit so many people.
When we first moved in,
I really thought I was gonna keep this
because of the fact that the color of this wood
is so similar to the color of the wood floors,
but Mr. Kate suggested that we get a really cute carpet
to kind of separate the two
and I really, really like how it turned out.
We also got a farmhouse style dining chair set
from Living Spaces which I really, really like
how it pulled it all together
and of course, a black bench over there as well.
For some more sister seating if we have a lot of people
to kind od squeeze in.
I honestly cannot remember where this light is from
but I do know that it way cuter
than the one that was there before,
so I'm very, very excited on this little switch out.
I think it really brought the whole room together,
again kind of continues the whole
modern contemporary farmhouse vibe that we have going on.
So that is pretty much the dining room,
where all of our family dinners happen.
Like I said, so excited to finally have a space
to all just enjoy and relax and eat really delicious food.
Moving onto the next room.
As you might see, we have this really large
open entrance area, which I absolutely love.
The ceilings of this house are so high up
and because of the fact that we have these
railings and balcony up here,
I can sing for real and it echoes around the house.
One of my favorite past times when I'm not working
all day long (laughs).
So we if we actually take a little bit of a step backwards,
this is what is called a mudroom,
which is apparently not that common
in California houses for some reason.
The house that I grew up in upstate New York
with my Mom and Dad and brother, obviously,
didn't have an entire room dedicated to being a mudroom,
where we just left our shoes and coats and jackets
and for some reason, just having this here
still very, very nostalgic
and it's like a piece of home back here.
I don't know why, this area's just like kind of
weirdly special to me,
even though we literally just take our shoes off here,
but it's the first thing you see
when you're coming from the garage and that's the mudroom.
And then next door to the mudroom
is the sisters office.
Now, this is definitely like the one room of the house
that is still a little bit under construction,
'cause recently my manager just quit his firm
and now works for me full-time only,
which is really fun, really fresh.
We get so much work done
and I am so blessed to have him in my life.
We just hired an incredible new assistant as well
and also, my editor is in the process
of moving out here to L.A. very, very soon,
so we can work even hard on my videos
and get them done faster,
which is going to be such a huge weight
off of mine and his shoulders.
So, we tried to make the office look as cute as we could
for the sake of this video,
but it's probably going to be changing
a lot within the next few weeks.
I will of course update you guys on Snapchat
and as well, I kind of want to do a
behind the scenes production type video later on.
So of course, if that video goes up,
you will see the finished office
with my editor kind of walking you guys through it.
But regardless, here we are. So the first thing you see
when you walk right into this room
is this huge sister neon sign,
which is probably blown out on camera,
I'll make sure to inset a little overlay
so you can see actually how good it is.
But I am absolutely obsessed with this.
Obviously you guys know that sisters is like my entire brand
and this is the logo that we have
on all the sisters apparel pieces,
which is my clothing line.
And because the fact that these windows
are facing away from the sun,
there's not a lot of natural light in this room at all,
and the last thing that I want
is everybody to be working in here kind of dull and dreary
and like falling asleep during the day.
So this is a beautiful light source
to kind of brighten the mood.
Along these two walls,
we just have a cute little L shaped desk
to sit and get work done.
I custom made this out of different Ikea pieces.
Of course, we have the iconic ALEX drawers
that literally every single beauty guru
and their mother has in their house.
They really are so convenient to use
and also these two table tops with the legs below as well.
Above the iMac, we have these two floating shelves,
which Mr.Kate also picked up from Ikea.
I really like how these look in the room
and it's just a really cool way
to just kind of store a few extra pieces and storage items.
I keep some important files and different stuff
in these boxes and we also have some cool achievements here
like my People's Choice Award and the Shorty Award as well,
which by the way, a really good plug here,
a perfect promo opportunity,
we're actually nominated for
YouTuber of the Year in the Shorty Awards this year,
which is so incredibly cool.
Last year we did win Breakout YouTuber of the Year,
which is already such a huge honor,
but I think we did this when we had
two or three million subscribers.
Now we're at a good and fresh 14 million.
So I feel like YouTuber of the Year
is such an incredible and huge honor.
If you guys want to vote for me,
it would mean so, so, so much.
You can vote every single day and I'll leave the link
in the description box down below.
You guys continue to surprise me every single day
and how much love and support you've given me.
And we're one of the fastest growing families
literally on the entire platform,
so I feel like we've got this in the bag.
So if you guys want to go vote,
vote for me for YouTuber of the Year at the Shorty Awards.
And also vote for my best friend, Drew,
Lone Fox in the house and home category.
You're welcome for that.
(laughing)
Final touches of the room,
we do have these black rolling chairs
for my film editor to sit at.
But we also have these super cute little
kind of hairpin stools as well.
Just so we can kind of sister spin around
for a real one in here
and a lot of the meetings we do have are held in this room,
so it's really good to have extra seating area
in case you have extra guests, for my lawyer
or my assistant or somebody joining us.
And then finally, last but not least,
on this wall, we have this TV screen
that is live broadcasting our calendar.
I've been wanting to do this for a very, very long time.
I'm someone who lives my entire life by my calendar.
I have to know what is going on at all times of the day.
Super good to be able to walk right into the office
and look at the screen and see what's going on,
what I need to do, what time I need to wake up,
who I need to be on the phone with,
and what is going on later on in the day,
that I need to get ready for.
And last but not least, as we head out of the office,
we have a poster with my favorite quote in the entire world,
work smarter, not harder.
A quote to live by sisters.
Here is the wine cellar which unfortunately
is still not filled up.
You guys so I am a sober sister and do not drink.
I really want to fill this with Mexican coke bottles
because they're so cute and so vintage
and I also have a little bit of severe addiction to them.
But I cannot find a bottle that is actually big enough
that doesn't fall through these things.
If you have any suggestions, please let a sister know
because this is looking very empty and sad.
Regardless, let's move into the kitchen and living room.
Even though I personally do not do any cooking,
well I guess we do do a little bit of baking.
The kitchen is probably the room we spend the most time in
in this entire house and I love, love, love my kitchen.
Not a whole lot has changed since the empty house video
but I do love how we decorated it.
We just have a cute little vase, a lantern,
and a little plant and table,
and also a very conveniently opened issue of Vogue Australia
thank you to my assistant for doing that (laughs).
There's me.
We have this huge black planter behind the sink
we three different plants in it.
There is a huge beautiful bay window
that leads out into the backyard.
So this is a really cool way to kind of separate
the outside from the in with still like a living element,
if that makes sense?
I just really like it.
We have this huge Viking professional fridge
and I though I would show you guys
since we are pretty much a fully sister stocked right now.
Love it, as you can tell, lots of a Red Bull,
I need a whole lot of energy while I am working all day long
and not getting any sleep.
Gatorade for Ian, lots of coke for the addiction.
Fiji water so you can stay nice and hydrated,
salsa, syrup for waffles in the morning,
lots of fruit, lots of apple slices,
eggs, and my bits and bobs.
So once we've prepared our breakfast foods in the morning,
we head over to the breakfast nook,
which is right over here.
It's a simple round table that I got from Ikea
and just four of the iconic white IMS chairs.
I really like these chairs for some reason.
I got them because literally every single
interior designer ever uses these on Pinterest boards
that I was following when I wanted to
decorate my first apartment,
I just kept them ever since.
Did I just do a chair review?
4.5 out of 5, would recommend.
I have a little tray on the table from CB2
and also this plant I got from HomeGoods.
Mr. Kate and I just replaced the old light that was here
with this insanely gorgeous super black pendant light.
It was gross and white and crusty before
and I think this just ties together
the space so incredibly well, I just love how it looks.
Behind the breakfast window,
there is this huge bay window that leads out
to the backyard area, which I'll get to in a second.
Mr. Kate and I decided to add some curtains to the area
just to kind of add a more homey and comfortable vibe
when you're eating breakfast.
But I love how this window lets so much natural light in
and like I said, when you walk in the front door,
you can literally see through the entire rest of the house.
I feel like it just brings the whole house together.
And last but finally not least,
on the wall, we just have some typography posters
that I custom made in photoshop
and got printed over at Staples.
We have this, good and fresh,
for when you're eating your breakfast foods
and it's just so good and fresh
and then also this one from Andy Warhol
at Morderna Museet in Sweden, I like boring things.
Flowing right from the breakfast nook and outside,
we have the living room,
which is once again, similar to the kitchen.
Me and my family spend a whole lot of time in
and this is by far one of my favorite rooms
of the entire house.
I am obsessed with how this room came out.
I think it just pulled together so, so, so well.
Obviously the biggest piece of this room
is the huge L shaped sofa.
This is literally the most comfortable couch
in the entire world
and I've gotten so many questions asking what this couch is
and it is actually not the cloud couch,
which is like the couch that every single person ever buys.
They're literally $20,000
which is the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard
in my entire life.
This one I actually got from Living Spaces
and it is the same exact thing,
but it was a fifth of the price
and it was actually being discontinued
which leaves me to believe that
they may have been getting sued for copying.
Not my problem, it is now here and we get to enjoy it.
On the couch, we just have some
different textures of pillows
from Target, HomeGoods, Ikea, CB2 as well.
And then in the middle, we have this gorgeous coffee table
that I am obsessed with.
Before we actually redecorated,
there was a clear acrylic one here,
which I really liked too,
but we ended up moving it upstairs
because the fact the couch is so big,
we really needed a bit of a bigger coffee table
to kind of anchor the whole room together.
That was Mr. Kate's suggestion
and I literally agree and I am so obsessed with this
concrete and glass asymmetrical moment
that we have going on.
On top of the table is just a few
different coffee table books.
We have Chanel, Louis Vuitton,
and also the new Balenciaga collection as well,
and just a super simple vase with fake plants in it
because I can't keep a real plant alive to save my life.
Below the coffee table and couch,
we have a good and fresh Jute rug
that Kate actually picked out.
Now, if you guys remember in Tuesday's video,
we were actually having a little bit of a dilemma
when it came to this rug.
When the installation was first starting,
I was really, really scared because it had been
raining all week in L.A. and this carpet was looking
very, very yellow, which is my biggest design no no.
I hate tan, I hate yellow,
but Kate convinced me to just wait it out
and see how it all looked in the end.
And now that the natural daylight
is kind of floating in here
and illuminating the room,
I actually really, really like how the colors
of this rug turned out
and I think it adds a beautiful texture to the room.
Should have listened to her from the beginning,
but it does go to show that the design process
is never perfect and sometimes you have to wait
until the end to see the full picture.
Speaking of pictures as well,
we also have three prints here on this wall.
We have another Andy Warhol one right there,
another typography one that says good things take time
on the right and then in the middle
is this huge photograph that I actually took
when I was on my trip to South Africa last year.
This is an iPhone photo that we got printed
on canvas and framed and I just think it looks so sunny
and it's a really nice break as well
from the typography that you guys see
going on a lot in the house.
Behind me on this wall, we have of course,
the entertainment wall.
There's a huge TV that we got from Costco
right here on the wall.
I'm not even sure how many inches that is,
oh, I love that sentence.
Under the TV, we have a few different decor pieces,
some books, and also some and Xbox controllers
for gaming during the day.
Then we have two black massive
shelving units on either side.
I was very, very skeptical about these
shelving units when I first kind of moved in here
because I feel like they are very, very dark,
but we just finished decorating them
and putting all these different pieces on there
from CB2, HomeGoods, Target, Ikea as well,
and I really, really like how the shelves
ended up looking fully styled.
We tried to pick a lot of bright items
such as different white decors pieces
and also plants as well,
to brighten everything up from the black
and I'm obsessed with how the styling looks.
And last but finally not least,
we have this massive love sack right here,
that we just sit and chill on
and I threw a blanket and pillow over top.
And I think that's pretty much the living room all complete.
That is pretty much where we spend
most of our time during the day.
Let's head upstairs and I'll show you guys
where we spend most of our time at night.
Now we start heading upstairs,
all the light comes shining in
and the lighting should look really good
and beautiful and fresh.
This is literally some of my favorite areas
of the entire house because of how bright it is
and how alive this whole area feels.
When you first get to the top of the landing,
this is the first wall that you see
and I just decided to put two more typography photos up here
we have this one saying be yourself
and this one, once again from Andy Warhol,
saying all is pretty.
Me.
Along this entire wall is just more shelving units,
just like the downstairs.
I wasn't exactly sure what to do with these
but we did decide to turn this awkward height
little shelves into kind of benches
which I think is so, so, so cute
and they're really comfortable.
We just got some sheep skin rugs from Ikea
and some more pillows from CB2 and Target
and then this little area right here
is where I get to take all my selfies during the day
because if you come this way, right here,
oh sun's right there.
It's a little bit early still to be taking
my golden hour selfies,
but at this angle, so good.
If we just keep walking this way,
we have this cute little desk area right here.
Once again, more decor pieces.
We have the original
James Charles 100,000 subscribers plaque.
So cool how far we've come
and we'll be getting to that in one quick second.
And I've just this little desk area
that we filled with some
different color pencils and Sharpies,
of course, some sister scissors
if we're getting any crafting or work done.
And usually my assistant will just leave
his laptop right here during the day.
This first door right here is the guest room
for friends and family,
where different people will stay.
I am obsessed with this room.
Just like how Mr. Kate did my front little living room,
my best friend Drew actually did the same thing
but in this guest room.
Over on his channel, Lone Fox Home,
I think he did an incredible job styling it.
So if you guys want to see how we turned
a tiny, little, drab room into
such a fabulous guest room, I'll leave the link down in
the description box down below as well.
But I'll give you guys a quick little overview.
We have a massive California king sized bed right here,
smack dab in the middle,
and we decided to go for a kind of more darker gray sheet
just because kind of all the bedding in the house
is so white and bright.
So we thought this would be a really good contrasting piece
and I really like how Drew actually styled it.
We just have some more dark gray
and different textured pillows.
This braided one is from CB2,
this one's from Target,
and I think these ones are just from HomeGoods.
This adorable hanging mirror is actually a DIY project
that Drew made out of an old belt
and an Ikea tray over on his channel.
I love how this looks above the bed.
It is so frickin' dope.
Next to the bed, we just have those side tables from Ikea
and then over here, we just have this kind of
strangely shaped shelf from Living Spaces.
I really was not convinced on this one
when Drew first showed it to me,
but I think in the room with everything styled
and on top of it, it looks so good.
And last but finally not least,
we have this huge Ikea mirror right here.
I'm obsessed with these,
I think it was like the STAVE mirror, it was called.
And it's just large so you can take your OOTDs,
check your outfit, check your makeup before you head out
and that is the guest room all complete.
Now heading out of the guest room,
we're going to head into probably my favorite room
of the entire house.
It's where I get all my work done, the sister studio.
But quickly before we head into there,
I do want to show you guys something
that I am very, very proud of. As you may or may not know,
us YouTubers, when we hit certain subscriber milestones,
we get these things called plaques from YouTube.
This was one of my biggest achievements
and I was so excited to get this
in the mail for the first time,
but it has been about two years now
since we had a 100,000 subscribers
and the family has grown just a little bit at least,
to a good and fresh about 14 million,
which I cannot thank you guys enough for.
I am so blessed to have you guys watching and supporting me
and I kind of wanted to showcase that in the house
in a very, very special way.
So after 100,000, the next big milestone
you get a plaque for is one million
and it came with this little gold pipe on right here.
But it was actually a dark gray background,
so I decided to get this all reframed
so it's nice and bright and white.
Very matching with the whole aesthetic.
But after the 1 million plaque comes the 10 million plaque
and that is proudly displayed right here.
I had an amazing and lovely dinner
with a few of the YouTube executives a few weeks ago
and they actually gifted this to me live in person,
which was such a cool and honorary moment.
But when you get the 10 million plaque,
it actually just comes like this, it's like a trophy.
But I thought it'd be really cool to get it framed
in the same exact shadow box
that I was doing the one million in,
so now they are matching and looking so cute
right next to each other on the wall
and it's quite the glow up.
Speaking of the sisterhood growing
and a little bit of a glow up,
if we head this way around the corner,
we get to the best room of the entire house,
the sister studio.
And if you're wondering, this door right here
leads to Ian's room.
It is not exactly aesthetically pleasing
to this whole video,
so I'm sure he'll do a room tour at some other point.
You can watch his video for that,
but this door right here leads to
the sister studio, come on in.
As soon as I got confirmation that I moving into this house,
this room was literally the first project that I worked on
because I have always dreamt of having a room
where I can get everything done,
have friends and guests over and film comfortably.
A room where my manager, assistant, videographer,
editor, writer can all be in
and it won't feel cramped
and this room is exactly that. In the middle of this room,
we have this brand new white dining table actually
which is my new filming desk.
As you guys remember, in my old one I had
a tiny little Ikea desk which was so inconvenient
to film in front of.
You have no idea.
All my stuff would always fly off of it
and it was impossible to film collabs in front of.
So I'm so glad that I have a massive space
to spread all of my makeup out on,
so I can just concentrate on the filming production process.
I keep a mirror on my table,
a charger for my second phone that I take my selfies with
and then I just keep my brushes displayed on here
as well for easy access.
The James Charles X Morphe palette is also
always here as well because it really
the only palette I ever reach for.
Also, the iconic sisters fan is here too
because when you're filming in front of bright lights,
it definitely does get very, very hot.
Behind me, I just have this white hanging backdrop roll.
This one's from the brand, Seamless.
You guys know my YouTube backgrounds are always white.
I don't know why, it's just very aesthetically pleasing.
This bench right here, I believe, is from All Modern
and it's really, really comfortable,
but we did order a different bench from the brand, Article,
it was just on back order, so it's not yet here.
When the new bench does come in,
I'm actually gonna put this bench
below the two typography posters in the hallway.
Apparently there's a chair here.
Right now I'm really not sure why.
Over on this wall,
we have the iconic sisters bench that was custom made
for me by my best friend Ethan Dolan.
He got this for my Christmas gift
and I'm so grateful for it.
It is so comfortable and chic.
It is a beautiful black cushion bench
with a sisters cut out in the front
and it does have LED lights inside as well,
so the sisters is glowing which is so cool.
Right here, I just have my brand new pro photo D2 light
and also this beauty dish right here.
I got this for myself as a Christmas gift this year
and I am so beyond excited because I feel like
my video quality is like the best it can possibly be,
but my photography game definitely has a long way to go
and I'm very, very excited to learn and use
literally the best equipment.
So that is chilling right here
until I kind of wheel it out to wherever I'm taking photos.
There's a simple bathroom right here
that my guests or I can use the bathroom while filming
or of course when I do in the sink as well.
I got these two super amazing black directors chairs
from Amazon so my assistant or manager or writer
or myself can sit back here and feel very, very professional
like we're in an actual sister studio.
And then speaking of sister studios,
is this beautiful, insanely large acrylic sign
that Mr. Kate and I actually got from
Sign Makers here in L.A.
They custom laser cut all of this together
after I designed it on photoshop
and I just think it turned out so, so dope.
I think it is such a cool piece
to kind of anchor the whole room together
and remind everybody where they are.
They're in the sister studios.
Now moving onto this wall, my makeup studio
would not exactly be a makeup studio without makeup in it
and that's what is inside these double closets right here.
Hallelujah.
This is pretty much where I keep all the makeup products
that I use for my videos.
They're all organized into little
clear shoe acrylic organizers.
I got this technique from Desi Perkins,
Down here, I just keep pretty much all the excess stuff.
I definitely like to keep the boxes
of all the different equipment stuff that I buy
just in case something is not working or if something breaks
I can read through the manual and figure out why
and how to fix it.
Here I just keep the Morphe X James Charles PR box
just to remind myself of what
an incredible collection we've created.
I usually keep extra cameras right up here
but I'm filming on my extra camera today.
It would normally be right here.
And then at the very, very top,
I just keep all of my beautiful wigs,
so I can pick one out and just look stunning and beautiful
if I'm doing a drag look
or just taking a fun Instagram picture
or hanging out with friends.
Last but not least, probably the most important part
of the sister studios,
what makes everything happen
is the different camera equipment that I have
and that is pretty much all right here
in the center of the room.
Now you may have noticed,
pretty much the entire room is filled with this like
strange metal cage and all these poles
going around the ceiling
and what this is for is basically so I can hang
all my different equipment pieces from the ceiling.
And what that does is basically open up the entire room
so people can actually walk around
and not have these ugly stands literally
taking up the entire floor space.
Now, I do really, really want to do a video
documenting the behind the scenes process
of what actually takes to make a YouTube video.
Everything from just thinking of a simple idea,
turning into a full on concept,
actually sitting down and filming the video,
and then fully editing and getting ready to post.
If that's something you guys would be interested in,
please let me know.
I think it could be so cool
and if I was to do that video,
I would kind of like to do a full equipment tour.
I've shown the different equipment and stuff that I have
on Snapchat a few times now
and it seemed like a lot of you guys
are very, very interested in that.
So please let me know.
But to summarize here,
we have basically a diffusion sheet
that makes the light very, very soft.
I just got this brand new light panel
that hangs from the ceiling
and it's literally the brightest thing
in the entire world.
We have my massive camera and lens right here,
they sit on my tripod to get the perfect angle.
My microphone is wired right here,
so I can make sure to turn it on
and never lose the audio
like has happened several times at this point
and to make sure of that,
we also have a pair of headphones
that sit right here as well,
so we can hear and make sure that it is on.
Once the camera is on and rolling,
I have this monitor right here
so anybody watching behind the scenes
can see exactly what is going on.
And then we also have one last monitor
that is in the front,
so I'm sitting behind the camera filming the video,
I get to see exactly what you guys are seeing.
Hi sisters, James Charles here
and welcome back to my YouTube channel.
So yeah you guys, that is pretty much
the sister studio all complete.
Like I said, let me know if you guys want
anymore in depth studio tour of all the equipment that I use
and the behind the scenes process
of making a youtube video.
I bet that would be so much fun
and I would love to show you guys
what it actually looks like
and how much work goes into it
and also just let me nerd self come out
and talk about the different equipment and technology.
Let me know in the comments down below.
But without further ado,
let's head into the last and best room
of the entire house, the master bedroom.
Before we walk in, we have literally my favorite
thing that I own in the entire world.
And that is my family photo.
I did go ahead and post it on Instagram,
so you may have already seen this picture
and everybody inside of it.
But basically when I had my
Morphe X James Charles launch party,
it was my first time ever having my California family
and my actual like birth family,
my Mom and my Dad that you guys have all met
in the room at the same time
and I hired my favorite photographer, Brandon Lundby,
who did all my campaign images,
to take a family photo.
Actually getting everybody to stand still
and smile for this photo
was probably one of the most difficult things
I've ever done in my entire life,
but we did do it and literally one shot
out of the entire ones that we took
and it is beautiful and it is framed
and I get to look at this every single night
before I go to bed and just say I love you
to all the most important people in my entire life.
Every time I look at this photo, I start tearing up.
It just means a lot that it is right here.
Moving on, we have two double doors right here
that lead to the master bedroom.
Now, as soon as you walk into the room,
there are two doors on the left and right
and that is where my closets are.
It is supposed to be like a his and hers type of closet
but it's just a sister and sister closet
because it's literally just me living here.
But this is pretty much the closet where I keep
all of my like more kind of nice pieces.
Moving over across the hall,
this is more like ath-leisure type of closet.
It's just like everyday type of pieces.
I have all my hoodies on top, organized by color.
The white stuff is here, gray, black, black,
and then the occasional few color pieces
that I do happen to own, are up here.
I have all my different t-shirts on the bottom row
and then I like to keep my sister apparel stuff right here
for super easy access. So walking out of the closet,
we get to the actually master bedroom,
which is literally my favorite area in the entire house.
I could not imagine this coming out literally any better
and I am so blessed and lucky
that I get to go to sleep here every single night.
As you guys saw in Tuesday's video,
before this kind of whole house restoration
started with Mr. Kate,
the only thing that I had in this room
were a mattress and also a leather poof
from my old closet in downtown.
So it was definitely time for a full room makeover
and I filled this up to actually feel like a master suite.
So I got this bed from Gets Laid Beds in the UK.
I love the name, unfortunately hasn't happened yet,
but who knows, maybe 2019 is my year, probably not.
This quilt, my best friend Drew actually made
by sewing together a bunch of different textured patterns
which I love how it turned out.
I think it looks so frickin' cute.
And once again, we just have a ton of
different textures on the pillows.
This one was a DIY project as well,
this one was from CB2, and this one HomeGoods, HomeGoods.
This is the bed and it's literally so comfortable
and I love waking up here every single morning.
It just feels so bright and lively
and I'm actually excited to start my day,
which is rare I feel like for a lot of people.
If we roll off the bed this way,
did you love that little action that just happened?
We have the sisters piano,
gifted to me by one of my best friends, Grayson Dolan,
just like Ethan's bench in the beauty room,
Grayson got this for me for our Christmas video
and it's probably my favorite gift
that I ever received from anybody.
I started bawling crying when he revealed it to me.
Obviously the twins have a very, very special place
in my heart and the fact that they went out of their way
to do this stuff was literally was just like insane.
I have this proudly displayed in my master bedroom,
so I can now play piano on both floors of the house
and serenade any boy that I may have over.
Although, that would maybe scare them off.
Coming over this way, speaking of having boys
and other friends over,
in the middle of the bedroom is this beautiful living space
which I'm so excited about because obviously
I did not really know what to put in here
because there was literally just a poof in here before.
But since there as so much space,
Mr. Kate and Joey suggested that we should make it into a
kind of like formal living room in the bedroom
and I love how it turned out.
Oh my god, I feel like this just looks like so, so good.
The couch, the side table, both of these chairs,
and the acrylic coffee table that was once downstairs,
were all from CB2
and I love that this area all came together.
Now there is so much space for all my friends and I
to sit down and chill watching TV,
by the fire, keeping it nice and warm.
Also speaking of fire,
we have these super cute fire and fireplace tools
and also this little log rack,
even though this fireplace is 100% electric
and we can't even open it up anyway.
But it's for the aesthetic purposes of it all.
And last but finally not least,
we have this shelving unit once again,
similar to the ones downstairs.
It's all black so we tried to pick some more
lighter pieces and lots of different textures and shades
to kind of bring it all together.
I'm not really sure why,
but I feel like this shelf is like my favorite one
of the entire house.
Walk over this way,
we have another huge selfie mirror.
Same exact one that was in the guest room.
Same purpose, taking cute little OOTD pics
and I love how this whole background
of the bedroom and sitting area looks,
especially with the light in the upper corner.
You're just gonna check your makeup,
make sure you still look flawless and good and fresh,
and we've looked better,
we looked better in the guest room, but it's okay.
We're just gonna forget about it and move on
and hope that the youtube quality saves us.
That is pretty much all of the master bedroom all complete
and last but not least,
heading into the master bathroom,
where I get to sister shower.
Basically this entire back wall is all a mirror
which I really, really like.
There is so much space to get ready in here.
I could be brushing my teeth,
my friends could be getting ready and doing their hair
all along this countertop space which is so convenient.
I keep all of my toothbrushes and hair supplies
and different skincare stuff all right here on a little tray
and all these drawers are just
filled with personal care items
which you definitely don't need to see.
The master bathtub is right here where I get to sit
and just take my bath and kind of relax.
I don't actually think I've taken a single bath
in this house yet,
but it is on my bucket list and I do have some
bath bombs at the ready for a nice and relaxing night.
And of course, we do have a major shower here as well,
which is literally the best thing in the entire world.
Oh my god, you could fit 100 people in here,
not like there's ever gonna be anyone in here with me,
unfortunately, but it is so fun.
We have a regular shower head
and also the rain shower as well which is so fun
for a full showering experience, if you will, I guess.
The acoustics in here are pretty good and fresh
so there's lots of concerts going on in the shower as well.
Can you see the rainbow?
Love that. - It's so cool.
- Is it right there? - Yeah, just a little reminder
that you are in fact gay.
- I think they know.
(laughing)
Alright you guys, that is pretty much
the master bathroom all complete.
Which means the master bedroom is all complete
and which basically means,
I think we're pretty much done with my house tour.
Oh my god.
Well, I really, really hope you guys enjoy this video
and like all the decor and stuff that we came up with.
I have never been happier in my entire life.
It is truly the best feeling in the entire world
to have a beautiful, fully decorated house
that I get to wake up in every single morning,
that I get to get work done in,
and that I get to invite friends and family over
to create memories every single day
and this would not be possible if it were not for you guys,
so thank you so much.
Well you guys, I really, really hope you enjoyed
my finished house tour video.
I am very, very proud of myself for actually getting it done
and not waiting until literally the week before
I move out in a few years.
So I really, really hope you enjoyed
and if you did, please don't forget to give it
a big thumbs up down below.
It means so, so, so much to me
and also as well, please don't forget
to click that subscribe button if you haven't already.
Come join the sisterhood, we're over 14 million.
Sister Shauna and I would absolutely love
to have you join the family.
And if you'd like to follow me on my makeup journey,
you can follow me on instagram and Twitter,
they're both just jamescharles.
My Snapchat for more behind the scenes type stuff
is jamescharless with an extra S after Charles.
This video's sister shout out goes to sister Maya.
Thank you so much love for always following and supporting.
I love you literally so, so, so much
and if you'd like to be the next video's sister shout out,
don't forget to always retweet the video links,
they go live on Twitter
and also turn on my youtube post notifications.
Alright you guys, thank you so much
for watching this video today, I love you so much
and I will see you in the next one, bye.
♪ I've got you under my skin ♪
♪ You are a bad, bad man ♪
♪ Care about no one else ♪
♪ but you under your skin ♪
♪ If this is sad, sad man ♪
♪ Don't have no one else ♪