- Hi sisters!
James Charles here and welcome back to my YouTube channel.
As many of you guys know, yesterday was February 14th,
meaning we celebrated Valentine's Day,
which is probably my least favorite holiday of all time.
I've been single for about 19 years now and at this point,
I'm really having trouble figuring out why.
I like to think I'm pretty good looking,
I'm funny every once in awhile,
have a beautiful house, steady income, lovely family,
lots of Instagram followers, that's a fun plus too.
I can really only think of one issue
that may get in the way and that's that
I'm a boy and all the boys that I'm
interested in are straight,
but that can't be it, right?
After a lot of thought,
I finally decided okay James, you need help.
It's been long enough.
I decided to reach out to cupid
and as you can see from the three arrows
lodged into my head right now,
he was really out there trying for me yesterday,
but unfortunately I think the arrows
may have missed the boys because
I woke up today and I'm still single.
Not gonna lie, at first I was really, really sad about it.
I've wanted a boyfriend for so long now.
I've been trying really hard and it hasn't been working out.
I imagine the cute dates and taking them out to dinner
and driving around and taking cute Instagram photos with.
(man sighs)
But then my mood started to change and
I really had to take a step back and think.
Why am I gonna spend the entire day being sad
when I could be happy instead?
I know my prince charming will come
one day if I'm patient, maybe.
Even if another boy doesn't love me back right now,
at least I know that I love me and that's all that matters.
I decided to spend my day on myself
doing what I love the absolute most, playing with makeup,
and this is the look that I came up with.
Without further ado,
if you wanna see how I created this
anti Valentine's Day makeup look, keep on watching.
(upbeat music)
Alright you guys, let's just jump right into
this pretty in depth tutorial.
We're gonna be focusing mostly on the eyes,
what's going on underneath the glitter,
and also the arrows that we're going to
sister stab into my head for a real one.
As you can see, I'm starting off with my base already done.
I just went ahead off camera and used
my normal products like always, but for my brows,
I did use something a little bit different
that I get to tell you guys about today
and that is, drum roll please,
the brand new Anastasia Dip Brow Gel.
I am very, very honored that Anastasia asked me
to be the first beauty guru to reveal this to you guys.
It is basically exactly what you would think,
a hybrid between Dip Brow and brow gel.
It is an insanely pigmented, super full coverage,
waterproof, and smudge-proof brow gel.
It comes just like this and this has
literally been my newest staple addition to my brow routine.
I'm obsessed with this.
I'm not gonna go too much more in depth
because Anastasia's gonna be talking about it
a lot in the next few weeks.
If you guys wanna see how I fully use it,
make sure to check out my video next Friday,
but I just wanted to give you guys
a little sneak peek of it now.
Here it is and get ready for this
to literally take over the brow world.
Now that being said, my face is done,
my brows are locked in place,
and let's move right along to the eyeshadow
portion of this look.
I'm just gonna go ahead and zoom you guys right in
to my face so you guys can get all the
details for the eye portions.
I don't really do tutorials very often, but whenever I do,
you guys always ask me to zoom in
so you can actually see what's going on.
Hopefully this is good.
Welcome to my face.
It's very crusted and pimply right now,
but we're gonna make it work.
Starting off this look today,
I'm just gonna grab my MAC Paint Pot in the shade Painterly
and apply a generous coat of this to my eyelid.
I'm just gonna blend this all over the lid,
acting as our eye base slash primer.
I'm not going to set this in with any powder.
Grabbing the James Charles x Morphe palette
and an M456 brush, use code JAMES for 10% off your purchase,
I'm gonna dip right into the shade Boutique with this brush
and use this color to start stamping
that cut crease shape into my lid.
Just going to focus and push this color
right above my natural crease because
we are going to cut it a little bit later on,
but I just wanted to lay down the darkest shade first
and then we're going to blend upwards.
Once we get to this outer corner,
I'm just going to feather it out and pull it up
in the shape of a wing.
I'm next gonna grab a little bit of a bigger fluffy brush,
the is the M433, and dip into the shade Love That
in the palette and use that to buff out Boutique.
I'm basically just stamping this color on there
and then using very, very tiny and light circular motions,
just lightly diffusing it upwards.
Make sure that there are no harsh lines or edges.
Grabbing a different M433,
I'm gonna dip into the shade Skip in the bottom corner.
This is the bright neon pink.
I'm gonna use that color to buff out Love That.
I'm not liking how this is looking.
Maybe if I grab a little bit of You're Kidding
and put this overtop?
This eyeshadow look so far is turning out
like every single relationship I've ever had,
a major failure.
That's looking a wee bit better.
Now that we have the crease all laid out
and kind of blended,
I'm gonna grab a little bit of the
Tarte Shape Tape concealer and just
put in on the back of my hand.
Using a flat top brush, I'm just going to cut the crease.
Just going to stamp this brush
right above my natural crease.
Then we're just going to carve out the line.
Wow, that is a cute crease if I ever did see one.
♪ Thank God something went right ♪
♪ I'd like to thank not only God ♪
♪ But also Jesus ♪
♪ And cupid ♪
♪ Just kidding, he's a little bitch ♪
Once the lid is all cut and the
concealer has dried down a little bit,
I'm gonna grab an M124 brush and
dip into the shade Pinkity Drinkity in my palette
and I'm going to use this color to set in the lid.
Then to cut that crease even further
and just add a little pop of something,
I'm gonna grab the Urban Decay Heavy Metal glitter liner.
This one is in the shade Grind.
It's a light pink almost holographic glitter in here
and we're just going to use this and
line right in this crease area, following that cut.
You're gonna wanna take a deep breath
and go very slow while you do this.
Be patient because if you mess us this line,
it's gonna look so crusted and dusted and wonky.
You also will definitely have to do
multiple layers on this liner because
if you want it to look good, you have to do a lot of layers.
If you do make any mistakes with the liner,
just fan your eyeball until everything dries
and then very, very carefully you can
scrape it off using a pair of tweezers.
That's for eyeliner.
You could do just a black wing if that's all you have,
but I feel like to go along with the pink
and monochrome type look that we have going on,
I wanna do a kind of muted cranberry type of color.
I'm gonna grab two different Kylie liquid lipsticks.
We have a bright pink, just a bright red,
and then also a black gel liner
and kind of mix together a little concoction
to get a muted maroon.
I'm gonna grab my Anastasia number 12 brush,
it's just an angled brush,
and dip right into this and use this color
to draw my winged liner.
That is pretty much the upper lid all complete.
It was a little bit of a journey to get here,
but in the end,
I think this cut crease turned out really, really bomb.
Let's go ahead and move on to the lower lash line.
Using the same colors and brushes from before,
I'm gonna grab my M456 and dip into
a little bit of Love That and Boutique
and buff that right up along the lower lash line.
Just placing it right in there and
making sure to connect that up with the outer wing as well.
With my M433, gonna dip into Skip.
I'm gonna pull this shadow down pretty far as well
and really buff it out.
We are gonna be putting on glitter
and I wanna make sure that there's
kind of a color behind it.
Be careful of any staining.
Before I move on to any glitter,
I'm gonna grab a little bit of the
Jeffree Star liquid lipstick in the shade Drug Lord
and a tiny little detail brush,
this is the Morphe M170-4 brush,
and using a tiny little bit of this on the back of my hand,
I'm going to use this to cut out my inner corner
and also line my waterline.
I'm just gonna set that white in place
using a little bit more of Pinkity Drinkity.
Using a pencil brush, I'm gonna grab the shade Literally
and I'm going to use this color to highlight.
I'm just gonna place this color right over my brow bone
and then right in that inner corner as well.
Then with another tiny detail brush,
I'm gonna dip into the shade Sister,
which is a metallic kind of rose gold color,
and I'm going to give that a quick little
spritz of Prep and Set and then
apply that shade right overtop of Literally.
Wow, look at that.
Now I wanna go in and add little glitter,
little glitter heart tears to this look.
If you guys remember a few months ago,
I did my recreating my follower's makeup looks video.
I did that rainbow cloud eye,
one of my favorite looks literally of all time.
I had little glitter tears dripping down from it.
I'm basically gonna do the same exact thing on this eye,
but all in a monochromatic pink.
I'm first just gonna dust off any
translucent powder that I have sitting and
baking on my face.
To draw in the little glitter tears,
I'm just gonna grab a tiny liner brush.
This one I literally still have in my
brush set from when I did my art supplies video
over a year ago now.
These ones are so good because they are so detailed.
Then just dipping into a little bit more of Love That.
(makeup product falls)
Oops.
I'm basically just gonna scribble these in down my cheek.
When I'm drawing these in,
I'm using a super, super light hand,
but then adding more pressure in certain areas
just so the color for one, isn't all even throughout
and this is gonna give it kind of that
watercolor actual teardrop type of effect.
Then on top, I'm basically just going to
randomly apply an assortment of loose glitters.
These ones are from In Your Dreams Cosmetics I believe.
This one is from Violet Voss and
then I also have these chunky glitters
that I got I think from Michael's.
They have tiny little pink heart glitters in here,
which is perfect and I'm gonna glue these on the tears
as if I'm crying hearts.
Starting with the tiny little hearts,
I'm just gonna use lash glue to dab them on.
If you have any really ridiculous pimples,
this is a great way to cover it right up.
Alright sisters, and I think that is one eye
of this anti Valentine's Day look all complete.
I love how this little glitter crying tears
cute crease turned out,
but that did take me quite a little bit of time.
Sorry for not talking very much.
I'm gonna quickly go off camera
and do the other eye and be right as close as I can get,
pop on a pair of lashes,
and I'll be right back to finish off the rest of the look
and get into some sister special effects
with cupid's arrows.
Alright sisters, we are back.
The eyes are looking relatively symmetrical right now
and I also popped on a pair of Lily Lashes
Miami So Extras on the eye.
I think the eyes turned out so beautiful,
but now it is time to move on to the rest of the face.
Next up of course is going to be the highlighter.
We have to get our glow on,
which I'm now realizing I probably should've done
before adding in the glitter tears
considering it's gonna overlap a little bit,
but it wouldn't be a James Charles
video without some poor planning.
Let's do it.
I'm gonna grab the Morphe Prep and Set setting spray
and give my face a quick little spritz
just so the highlighter has something to stick to.
Then grabbing my Morphe M501 brush,
I'm just gonna dip right into the shade Literally
from my palette and lay this down as
kind of a blush mixer pre-highlighter color.
Then using a JH30 brush,
I'm just gonna grab a little bit of a mixture of Face
and also a tiny bit of Sister for a more
pink rose gold iridescent glow,
give it a quick little spritz of Prep and Set
and then just go right in overtop for a blinding glow.
If I can't attract the boys myself,
maybe this highlighter will help.
Not with jokes like that, oh my God.
Little bit above the brow bone as always.
Then...(man screeches) down the center of my nose.
You guys, I don't know how my nose contour
looks this good right now and it's
probably never gonna look like this again
so let's say a silent prayer and cherish this moment
as we highlight using a pencil brush.
This is the M431 and a little bit more of Face.
Now we get to move on to the lips.
For the lip, I do wanna stick with a nude color.
I know, kind of boring.
Of course you could do a maroon
or a darker color to match the liner,
but since we have so much going on
and we're gonna add more in a few minutes,
I do think a nude will be a good option.
Before I do that though,
I am gonna grab the Kylie liquid lipstick
that we used beforehand for that bright pink,
this is Say It No More, and use this to just line the lips
so when we add the nude overtop,
it'll be a very pinky nude as opposed to
a more peachy nude.
Honestly, it doesn't even look that bad, that pink,
but that's...a little much for me I think.
That was a rhyme!
♪ It doesn't even look that bad, that pink ♪
♪ But that's a little bit much for me I think ♪
(man laughs)
On top of that,
I'm gonna add the Ofra liquid lipstick
in the shade Sao Paolo.
You guys know this is my all time favorite nude.
You can use code JAMES for 30% off.
I'm just gonna layer this overtop to like I said,
create a more nudey color out of this bright pink.
Then finally, just a little bit of Drug Lord
right in the middle for a nice highlight.
Alright sisters, that is pretty much this
Valentine's Day look all complete.
I'm now realizing that it would've been a lot smarter
to add the glitter tears in the next step
along with the arrows to go from a
Valentine's Day wearable actually pretty look
to a more non-wearable anti Valentine's Day look,
but guess who didn't think of that?
Me, so I guess this is your wearable
Valentine's Day look for today.
You could totally stop here.
Even with the glitter tears,
I think this look did turn out very, very beautiful,
but if are like me and you've been
single for a very, very long time, 19 years to be exact,
and you do not like this holiday anymore,
keep on watching and let's add some special effects
to make this an anti Valentine's Day look.
Jumping right in before we even get to the makeup portion,
I'm gonna teach you guys how to make
the arrows super quickly.
Love being a cute little DIY channel.
What you're going to need is red construction paper,
I just got this from literally the dollar store,
a pair of sister scissors, some super glue,
and then also a pair of chopsticks
from the last time that you ordered Chinese food.
Basically what I'm gonna do is start by
folding my construction paper right in half
and then just using my pair of scissors,
I'm gonna cut out a...parallelogram, geometry, out of this.
Is that what it's called?
A parallelogram, four sides, definitely parallelogram.
If you open it up, you have the bottom of an arrow.
Wow, I am such a queen of DIYs!
LaurDIY is shaking!
Then I'm just gonna cut this shape right in half
again on the fold.
Now we have two and then we're just gonna
repeat that step one more time.
Now cut it in half.
Now I'm just gonna take my pair of chopsticks
and rip them right in half just like that
and then carefully, I'm just going to put a
tiny little bit of glue on the edge of this chopstick
and I'm going to stick on the bottoms of the arrow.
Perfect.
While this dries, I have a roll of toilet paper
sitting right here that we're gonna use later on,
but I'm just going to stick this right in here
and let it chill.
Just repeat the same exact process two more times
for two more arrows.
We are back and all three arrows are complete.
I took my shirt off so we can do some
(audience cheering) special effects stuff.
Unfortunately, that's gonna be all of the
shirt taking off that I'm gonna be doing this time of year.
(audience laughs)
These Valentine's Day jokes are getting so old already.
Oh my God.
We get it, I'm single forever.
Okay, moving on.
I'm just gonna take a really insanely
sharp pair of scissors.
Please be careful and use your parent's permission
if you for some reason are recreating this look.
I'm basically just going to cut this here.
Okay.
Next I'm gonna grab a little bit of the
Ben Nye Nose and Scar Wax.
Just gonna grab one of the brushes
that I have laying out here and
grab a little chunk just like that.
Basically, what I'm going to do is
form this around the bottom of the arrow that we just cut
so one, I don't stab myself with wooden shards,
but I'm also going to flatten the bottom edge just like that
and kind of pinch it out so therefore
when we stick the arrow to the skin,
it actually has a surface to glue to
as opposed to just flopping down.
Once the piece is all set and has a flat bottom,
I'm just going to set this arrow off to the side
and let that scar wax dry out a little bit.
Now we're gonna get started on the arrow holes.
If you've been subscribed for awhile,
you may have seen me do a few different
special effects things before.
I did the mermaid video, I did the melting skull video,
and I also did the video with the
twins and Emma for Halloween.
My knowledge when it comes to special effects
is really not that great at all and just saying
that I really wanna learn a lot more about,
but those few things have allowed me
to achieve basically every look
that I've tried so far so we're good.
What I'm gonna start off with is a
little bit of Ben Nye liquid latex.
Just gonna pour a little bit of it
into the bottom of the cap.
Then just grabbing an old, dirty sponge
that I was about to throw out anyway,
I'm just gonna dip it right into the cap.
I'm just going to dab this on right where
I'm gonna place the first arrow hole.
Quickly before it dries,
I'm gonna grab a little bit of toilet paper just like this
and basically rip a circular shard kind of, just like that,
and I'm just gonna stick it right overtop of that area,
flatten it down using my hand.
Then just grabbing a little bit more liquid latex,
I'm going to go right in and just
press that right in and go over those edges.
Then we're just going to let this dry.
While that dries, I'm just gonna start prepping the
second arrow hole over here,
and then a hole right down here too.
(high pitched ding)
To lock those in place,
I'm just gonna use a little bit of
translucent setting powder to make sure
that none of the latex is still sticking.
Then just using a small concealer brush
and a little bit of foundation of the back of my hand,
I'm going to quickly repaint over those areas
to disguise the latex.
Now that the new skin is pretty much
as disguised as we're gonna be able to get it,
we get to do the fun and also dangerous part
so please be careful.
I'm gonna grab a tiny little pair of eyelash scissors
and I'm basically going to cut a small hole in the skin
right in the middle of where the toilet paper is.
Once you get through,
you just kind of snip around a little bit
and take some of the excess off to kind of form a hole.
That is pretty much exactly what you're going for.
It looks really, really gross, I know,
but we're gonna fill it up.
Now I'm going to grab the arrow.
Then grabbing a little bit of Spirit Gum,
this stuff is basically liquid adhesive.
It is what a lot of drag queens use to glue down their wigs.
Just gonna put a little bit of this
inside of the hole on my skin.
You actually activate this glue by tapping it,
so I'm just gonna kind of jiggle my finger in there
a little bit just so it gets kind of tacky.
Then I'm also gonna put a generous layer of that
on the bottom of the scar wax that we put on earlier
and I'm going to tap that as well until it gets tacky.
Once it's looking pretty good,
I'm basically just going to take this arrow
and carefully maneuver it right into the hole
and then stick it to my forehead.
This is not going well.
(man sighs)
Instead, we're going to figure this out.
I can superglue this to the thing,
but do you think that'll stick it to my head?
I don't care.
Let's go.
This is so not safe.
That's okay, don't do this at home.
Please stay, please stay, please stay.
Yas!
I am the queen of special effects, just let everybody know.
Before this literally falls off my head,
I have two different types of blood,
the liquid Ben Nye Stage Blood and
the not liquid Ben Nye Thick Blood.
I'm gonna use a mixture of both of these
to make it look like this is bleeding.
I'm just going to dab this around for the puncture wound.
This is also going to help hide
the seams of the liquid latex too.
I'm gonna put some kind of going up
the base of the arrow as well because
if this were to actually fly into my head,
there would definitely be some sister splatter.
That is dark.
Gonna use my hand to tap out any excess
and to kind of fade it in.
Then I'm just going to use some Thick Blood
and this is going to go right inside of the hole.
This step is so gross and actually makes it look real.
The tendons are really just flying out for a real one.
That is one arrow all complete.
Oh my God you guys,
I cannot believe how freaking real and crazy this looks.
I'm gonna now do the other two quickly and carefully
before this one flies off and I'll be
right back with the finished look.
(upbeat electronic music)
Alright sisters, several hours, lots of liquid latex,
and lots of superglue later,
that is this anti Valentine's Day look all complete.
Unfortunately for me, I am still very much single,
which means cupid's arrows did not hit
any boys for me yesterday,
but I think he may have missed and hit me twice
because I am literally in love with
how this makeup look turned out today
and I really, really hope you guys enjoyed this video.
If you celebrated Valentine's Day yesterday
with a significant other, it must be nice, cannot relate,
but hope you guys had a really fun and fresh time,
wishing you the absolute best,
or if you were like me and you are sister single,
I still hope you had a really fun time yesterday.
While having a boyfriend or girlfriend
does lowkey kind of sound pretty fun and fresh,
don't rush it.
The right person will come when you least expect it
and you guys will live happily ever after.
All that matters at the end of the day
is that you love yourself and hey,
you also got me, sister James here, loving you as well.
All that being said, if you guys enjoyed today's video
and you like how this anti Valentine's Day
makeup look turned out,
please don't forget to give it a big thumbs up down below
and show you love and support.
It really means so much to me and it helps me out a lot.
Also, if you have not already,
don't forget to click that big red
subscribe button down below and come join the sisterhood.
We are 14 million sister strong and I'd
love to have you join the family.
Also, make sure you click the bell icon
so you can get a notification every time
I upload a brand new video.
If you'd like to follow me on my makeup journey,
you can follow me on Instagram and Twitter,
they're both just James Charles,
and my Snapchat for more behind the scenes type stuff,
the place where you'll probably find out
if I ever do get a boyfriend first,
is James Charles with an extra S after Charles.
This video's sister shout out goes to sister snacks.
Thank you so much love for always following and supporting.
You know I love you so, so, so much,
and if you at home would like to be
the next video's sister shout out,
don't forget to always retweet
when something goes live on Twitter
and also turn on my YouTube post notifications.
Alright you guys, thank you so much for
watching this video today.
I love you so much and I will see you in the next one.
Bye!
(upbeat electronic music)