welcome back gamers sixty men compete
for six men yeah I did not read that
right sixteen women compete for six men
this should be interesting
I love reacting to these let's just go
hey
aim the game for the fame everybody just
on my name steady hands always no track
never going back always being best you
know got my man
he's got the math gamers damn he had a
lot of girls by the way Jesus okay so
the concept of days come on you all do
the average dating app has three times
more men than women Society did you know
that 3 percent of men have 100% of the
sex something to think about the science
is there but what happened if we was the
opposite oh my god wait a minute wait
wait wait 16 6 math be like bra humble
to be continued you're not important so
dry lonely flesh these have some in so
betas am i right lonely single pathetic
if you don't have at least 20 girls
basking in your glory as you wake up
everything I don't know why I'm saying
all this sorry
[Music]
okay
so now the girls pink I'm suggesting in
a good essay to you I've ever said my
name is Marcus I'm doing part-time
school and then part-time work why they
say these are some tough contenders what
are you doing don't work at the
part-time describe yourself you need to
impress all these groups of women work
part-time
what makes you stand out out of millions
billions of boys hmm try a little bit
I'm a name Kaitlyn I'm working full-time
and it's amazing yeah my name what are
you doing
ramen while I'm in there say can you say
something interesting like my hobby is
just spreading misinformation on the
Internet
one of my hobbies is blowing up power
plants and not getting caught say
something I just wore a ah no I'm from
Queens New York and I produce a model
I'm Wesley there you do not model
you're way too short not that there's
anything wrong that's just an industry
standard graduated from UCSB my name is
Jalen I'm music producer rapper okay let
me guess
Jalen's gonna get all the puss well we
already know from the beginning or
alright so now they got a pic I really I
really hope the water that will not get
anyone you know why am i laughing at
that that's horrible
come on oh god now nervous
oh it's all spelled this is what I said
1% oh the guys gets all the women that's
how it works
welcome to my guild wait who's lonely I
feel bad
oh wait okay there's one this is one I'm
Rebecca Rebecca yeah I'm from New York
I'm from Brooklyn I hear the New York
accent once I hear that I'm like okay I
want to connect with that person yeah
here because it's we got to stay
together you gotta stay together how do
you feel having a long line of girls
nervous I'm 18 yeah yeah sure my brother
Kalin he doesn't look that bad come on
why didn't I want to pick him seriously
if you can like lick your elbow it could
actually save you from elimination
outsmarted you got up smarted actually
grew up playing lacrosse yeah I played
lacrosse awesome oh sweet okay do you
still play I played at UCSB okay so we
shouldn't probably ever really cross
together I mean that'd be pretty fun
what see this guy's operating at like
500 ping or something what's his problem
what do they always have to have one guy
just completely stone out what's your
guy's deepest darkest secrets what's
your deepest darkest secret see I like
that all the girls from life separates
is like I'm favorite color what's your
favorite kind of water deepest darkest
secret this is good this is what guys
knows how to do they know how to dig
deep that's deep I do sorry but ah geez
what a big one I saw over there I go to
school by them television PR I'm
surrounded by creatives
yeah I just love being creative you know
absolutely and maybe that's just the New
York in us have you ever heard anyone
say hate being created that's gonna hate
creativity it's just a way this is a
waste of time really I just like mundane
tasks and people not asking me questions
we were to describe you as a shy
introvert she's about to explode if he
says gamer next she's gonna rock it off
come on say it gamer game eye drops yeah
okay hey okay
aim the game for the fame yeah everybody
just on my name Oh steady hands always
no track never going back always being
best you know got the man he's got the
map unlike Jubilees sixteen six men
three times uh uh that doesn't matter
oh yeah when I need to piss piss yeah
whip up my dick dick
it goes play splash my flesh please
sometimes also tickles oh do you think I
could get Wellman like that not that I
want one but like come on I'll be honest
that was a good freestyle
it's hard oh okay I'm sorry guys my
birthday's coming up
any plans no not right now my ref is
coming after you got any plans no why do
I hate this guy I'm just Joe I don't
hate him favorite dance move for every
chance one
oh this guy got six women smooth wait
who I inspired you to be a rapper
it was Lincoln Park Chester no way try
so hard got so far oh my gosh nice I'm
sorry can you tell me what that tattoo
is about though we go what do you call
yourself like I just stick in any way
make music yeah I like different stuff
like what thanks buddy how would you
describe yourself artistically like
music uh I would say music oh it's
almost like a nice
he said music how you describe yourself
artistically like music or something Oh
music oh my god
I love how you guys have to fight to the
death right now I love the contrast from
last episode color fight to death I'm
gonna be real with you guys if I did
this which I would never do because why
man Queen - yeah Queen yeah I don't care
for Commerce then you would decide who
you want to pick right away come on this
is way too short of a time to really get
to know one you just go from vibe and
appearance they're just pretending it's
hard come on it's not hard if you're a
guy let me know if you think the same no
way now I'm speaking for all guys if
your woman let me know if you're
surprised by that how about that
[Music]
you ask too many questions I'm sorry you
see executive decisions all the girls
from last episode oh my god I don't know
how to do this too many questions
go environment see you know that he
eliminated the right one just based on
night I love you though it's a little
difficult sometimes but yeah I just keep
pressing on it's only because you're
taller that's smooth cuz she's not even
taller that man it's not that it's not
like I'll stay in the goats can you eat
sushi like all the time I can you see I
had sushi ate sushi every single day
that's issues messages yesterday he's
definitely gonna pick her because anyone
that you can eat sushi with is a winner
[Music]
what nice meeting you too it's always
the talking oh we still talk with still
dark
[Music]
it was pretty like natural conversation
and have a lot in common so it was fun
yeah yeah yeah
again not a sip but I fell for why I'm
in here I really truly do it's odd but I
guess it's fun I had a good time you're
the creepy one
you're the creepy one this guy looks
like a toddler enter his body and he's
just very confused like arms what I do
with him
I'm interested yeah I think yeah have
you done dad I'm actually down - yeah
she seems smart so like I could learn a
lot from her
that was great I love these this is a
guy with the creepiest personality that
girl literally dropped the beat for him
and he eliminated her right after fair
fair sum to me if you support beautify
wow you guys are early huh him well it
was six men mister sub to support
beautify alright so you messed up - yeah
it was literally I wouldn't say hardest
because I'm a guy guys aren't hot to me
alright I can say that you're a
good-looking and I agree I produce and
modeled
if you got meaning these videos just
read the comments they can you let it go
on a day with people like this it's an
awkward and it's probably painful to be
alone in a room with me I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna pretend like that's not
the fact but at least this is really
what I've been competing against
throughout these years which I I'm don't
care anymore obviously all right guys if
you enjoyed this episode it's much like
let me know if you own more of these I
love to make them and check out Jubilee
$5 every merch goes to Ocean Foundation
support waters workers are important
splish Splash splish you know I mean
splits fresh fish taking their pace hit
oh you know what big peepees do they
play PewDiePie
pixal ings of course pixel ings is a
creature collecting game I'm the primary
shareholder over a Brazilian players
have downloaded and it's got a perfect
score it's safe to say it's the most
popular game of all time
PewDiePie pixel aims it's awesome deal
with it
build with it
[Music]