memes loader intro leave your entry
close I haven't showered since 2018
you mean 2019 no Dolan take a freaking
shower that's so gross I smell it from
here
it was think you think II piped showered
since the last decade
you mean the decade from 2010 to 2020 no
2018 first meme Uganda knuckles 2019
first meme mafia City 2020 first me
World War 3 I can't wait to get my
drafting letter banking news sign me up
for that my man man born in four 20 1969
wants to change his first name as nice
the World War three memes really lost
their meaning quite quickly didn't they
suddenly they were just not as important
anymore happy new years from Asia
imagine still being in the last decade
this post was made by Asia game good one
Asia good one me accidentally steps on
toy pig my dog so you have chosen
playtime time to play yes haha banette
we have fun now when World War three is
trending and you realize we are all 19
year olds now I'm in danger oh god what
happened to my audience
I need the 9 year olds back I need the 9
year olds back so I can keep making
videos and have an audience that watches
damn please don't get drafted please go
to the doctor and say you got
tuberculosis or something dude come on
man come on you gotta keep watching
bus drivers when they see each other
pilots when they see each other
is it because is that a pee pee joke I
understand when you're laughing at World
War three memes and start to wonder why
the Sun is coming out at 9:00 p.m. I was
a little too dark for me get it because
it isn't dark at all it's quite light
that's bright the humor so far has just
been amazing 20/20 here but you realize
that 17 2018-2019 20 had a massive
plague outbreak I'm beginning to see a
pattern here
that
not sure I like what is the patent what
there's a pattern people talking about
World War three happening me just waking
up god how old are these two days and
it's already irrelevant Jesus PT PI it's
really messed up when people pressure
you into having a baby
also PewDiePie Frick yeah I don't know
how I walked into that meme good job
Felix when ready goes from talking about
the Australia fires to the plague and
World War three all within the first 72
hours of the decade oh no it's all
falling apart you know war is bad and
all and it's bad for the economy in
general right but it's good for the meme
economy you know at least we'll get epic
memes you know at least we can get more
pickle Rick missile Rick's and stuff
like that that'd be epic
all the Zoomers will be fortnight
dancing kapa World War 3 I don't flash
player shutting down plague Australia on
fire my depression a terrible 2020 let's
get it let's make this the worst year
ever guys starting the decade off
correctly or if you got two seconds in
you only get one chance on this I can't
believe that made me laugh
Shrek funny is the equivalent of
fortnight bad I swear
Shrek funny check from me right Shrek is
funny it's ironic I'm being ironic shrek
is funny it's not funny but I'm being
double double ironic so that makes what
does that make shrink petition for peers
to review the World War three means so
that it dives in the war never happens
alright guys I got you on this one don't
worry I already killed a new guy memes
not gonna lie
each baby pewdiepie I would master Yoda
you stay away from my child which is me
the child of me that is me follow your
dreams
I'll follow your dreams this meme has
cinnamon toast kin energy all over it
girls hitting puberty I hate my periods
voice I think puberty where is this
brother
good meme I'm on the bus and this guy is
so fine
but he has an iPhone 6 and you're on a
bus for poor people ride on buses poor
small peepee small peepee I don't care
this big paper cup where I find big
babies change my mind
I'm Punk so Hamish rebel I'm Asian so I
much like math I dye my hair so bling
blong I am a youtuber so I must be
sponsored by red shadow legend accept me
I have integrity guys I will not know
rate shadow ladies if you're watching go
away shush shush
go away I will not sink too steep level
stooped level of patheticness I don't
want your money I can't be bought oh
Jesus Christ please the delivery guys
when there's even order at 11:59 so they
don't have to hear the I ordered last a
kid it's like one of those jokes do you
feel like you have to say I'm not gonna
lie I made a decade joke but it was it
was a lot of levels of irony behind it
and they've timing was completely off as
well I did it before so I didn't even
make sense
Mojang previously stated they didn't
want to create sky dimension until they
could make the nether more interesting
now there are they coming Mojang hives
creator of aether mom finally we can
smoke the clouds finally maybe find like
in viscid IKEA tower up in sky oh my god
a decade of PewDiePie tribute is this
one of those where it's okay oh wow oh
oh wow it's a little annoying because
you know it's just like an overlay it's
not the picture itself you know what I
mean it's not like they found picture
that outline this right there's no all
right I mean big people you sure yeah
yeah big peepee joins the army to pay
for college
hey at least if you die I don't have to
pay back your debt the four horsemen of
whom hmm
listen send us out to World War three
we'll take care of it quite quickly
University student in Hong Kong now
using trebuchet to retaliate against the
police what's what I've been saying this
is huge PP energy cuz trebuchet are like
a birthright to people and I'm so glad
they're yours utilizing it well done
Hong Kong I respect you well done big PP
trebuchet when in doubt trebuchet that's
what I've always said don't know what to
say to you a girl during a date
trebuchet
what no trebuchet you don't understand
Trebuchet she's he's speaking French
he's so cultured wow he must have a big
peepee and then you get laid instantly
trust me guys trust me on this one
Carson whoops I'm waiting for the day
World War three happens and people start
making memes of it big peepee here's a
mural on wall in my town down in
Australia god damn that's a big peepee
that slush sucks guarantee you petition
to change the up down vote icons pee pee
or smoke pee pee smell pee pee all I
said was I beat the Enderdragon
with no armor on oh that's big peepee
that's big peepee when you buy eight
Wi-Fi routers to make a meme because
it's cheaper than buying editing
software stocks okay Felix
he just had eight of his friends changed
the name of hot spots reddit me knowing
none of us redditors have hate shrek
funny shrek buddy everyone all right
fine you get PP uh when you hear that
your husband decided the size of the
peepee of random stranger and in it
confused ravioli noises might say gets
big peepee hey wait what
Australians be like 11:59 that's awful
I couldn't possibly give this a big
peepee I'll give a small peepee whoops
misclicked all men are pigs women are
equal to men
I will initiate self-destruct Wow women
just got owned
epically that's a big peepee for women
world's last male northern white rhino
dice oh ah that's so sad small peepee
that's so sane there it is the guy on
the Left got number two the guy on the
right didn't even make the list y'all
see the problem you'll see the problem
disgusting me planning what to say if I
ever saw Felix me when I see Felix there
you go it actually happened twice
already
I know I know I'm supposed to say
something I don't know what it is but
related si from now on I'm not gonna
repeat myself what it is okay I'm just
gonna be like password it's more creepy
go away but can I have a ship small Fifi
go away what is the male equivalent of
brick this I'll just be a stripper the
military yeah pretty much see you guys
at World War two
big VP when you make a joke in class and
your crush laughed the loudest the best
thing that can happen to a potato
potatoes would be like I'm not sure if I
understand this joke I'm gonna go with
small people in this one because I don't
get it
are you saying that you're a potato this
one is amazing field leagues after
beating entered agnus 69 Jack after
beating Andrew Dragon 69 noise my fellow
19 year olds Australia has been on fire
for almost three months spread awareness
no way that many what's a hot it's not
funny don't laugh at it
what's a hot why would you write hi
there it's not funny the last video of
the decade will be happy wheels so
prepare yourself well that was a
freaking light well I did it okay I'm
sorry was late
damn that's sick and you guys complain
there's not fanart look at that that's
amazing very nice oh whoa
I can zoom in instant very large dick I
got to meet baby pie today super cool
and really nice guy and he passed the
test
laughs related to science that's how we
knew did you pass phrase yes yes it did
Felix slowly starting to lose his legs
90 oh my god that's so sad look a
totally slow ass I was actually winning
that race as you can tell here because
there's no one ahead of me
no one except the person taking the
photo but they weren't damn it
baby Yoda baby Groot baby sonic baby
Felix PewDiePie pp PI damn I really look
like I can slay some you know what I
mean I look like I'm not pushing around
what youtubers should I fight to the
death
meet me on the sky block at dawn audio
jaxa we both have 69 power level my god
for truly a match Poots the person who
made this has big peepee Rhino redditor
well actually it's a girl did I start it
that's a great episode big peepee me
dying in World War 3 the guy that killed
meat starts doing four do they have for
tonight Iran I think this is an
important thing before I go mom do they
have Ford 19 Iran can we just settle it
in like one big battle or yeah
said do we have to commit killing right
when you realize pewds is taken break
when World War three is happening and
beginning if a denier that I'm not so
sure I like oh good I'll be in Japan
when it happens guys don't worry god
damn it maybe this time japan will win
if your pangas Sebald i'll be fighting
on their side
you're a crush talks to you she wants to
show you a meme she opens reddit
it's your meme damn that's how you know
you straight about to get some action
like that's just
instead pee pee dip how effort is
rewarded I hope it's a fact even if you
can't draw your meme still gets up votes
because it's fan hard and that's a fact
been drawing my jersey essence last year
what a journey and that's a fact
oh that's opposed to be me oh my god I
couldn't even tell because it was so
well drawn that it was too
photorealistic I thought I was looking
in a mirror that's big peepee oh my god
they made it for the meme and it looks
so bad I mean you'd still get a big
peepee I'm not gonna lie it looks even
worse than the video I'm not saying it
looks good I'm just saying that I think
it would look even uglier if you painted
it gold big P big potential right here
Oh God
maybe oh that makes me want to try it
robell three should be fought on
minecraft server so nobody's alright
yes let's just Hunger Games it out guys
come on we don't have to kill each other
hey son I found the picture of your
grandpa hey damnit small peepee I don't
like this don't make fun of me
World War three here we come new USA
military uniforms damn this is gonna be
the new area 51 meme I feel like that's
the energy I'm getting here you know it
feels really bad to joke about this but
also it's so good for the meme economy
so I kind of
me winning fake arguments in the shower
the shampoo bottles big peepee oh I just
jog every once in a while I do CrossFit
I lift competitively beard said I have a
big peepee big peepee you now you have
double peepee how big does that make it
peepee huh there's news about World War
three and you have a brother he's only
nine he watches PewDiePie is actually 19
oh god no you're 9 now again I changed
it back don't worry guys if you're
watching this you're 9 years old all you
got to do is smash like on the video and
share it with a friend and they will
also turn 9 so you don't have to get
drafted don't worry you're safe upload
this image to instantly have girlfriend
all right maybe large I'm not that type
of girl 10 minute later next meme Wow me
when I maybe when I see how I hired the
bear bear all the games on that lid
spotted in Toronto I'm probably a little
late but still pretty nice to them yeah
it's so nice and I didn't see it
I can't believe it I'm so it's still
really cool Thank You G fuel check out G
fuel guys
enter the code PT pilot treat yourself
I've seen this and it's really funny
so my keyboard broke I can't type are
without copy pasting it now I'm using
the dreadful ear language to replace the
broken key of my that's really funny
guys I made an our bench so we don't
shoot each other I'm just here for the
memes okay alright YouTube
okay we're cool let's go no one the
camera angling anime when a character is
about to go insane that's great
yeah they love that angle don't they
there's a picture of young piers right
before he lost his legs in a shark
attack oh my god that makes perfect
sense because I remember when we did
that they were like there's a ton of
sharks out there so don't fall in the
water and I was like oh no maybe you
know I mean this is cannon huge I don't
want to play with you anymore
minecraft this those episode takes so
long to make and I don't feel like I had
no time because I'm so busy with other
things
so I'm sorry starting from nothing you
made us laugh every step of the way
helped people throughout the hardest
time and we have you through the hardest
time just by your mistakes
here you are happy that everything you
beautify for the best decade and cheers
to the next one oh thank you guys big
peepee well done
Walt I'm not pewdiepie but my name guy
Oh oh my god came here for Felix that's
so adorable look at them why can't I
move
I can't scroll down to Edgar but my it
looks a few thank you mom an email
youtuber is that pewdiepie is that the
pewdiepie you're talking about love Y
paper review PP is it time for a new
name I think it might be time from now
on we call it people review when
PewDiePie sees a bad name you have lost
your PP privilege that's correct that's
how that works me relax we're gonna have
this all right I'm gonna end it there
hope you guys enjoy this episode
subscribe and I see you gamers on the
battlefield
[Music]
you are entering a new era where you
shall craft the hope
the hour of fart smells and poop grades
is coming
marzia Edgar and buttons need you
the timer you will face but crawlers is
all about when you are seated on the
porcelain throne where T is the game to
play
I'm not supposed to have my opinion
about that but the prices
you