what's up gamers do you like video games
what but you never play bring it for
review III 2019 Xbox Playstation look at
placing they have theirs yet Sony is an
attending III 2019 oh okay well that
saves me some time Jesus let's start off
with Bethesda
[Applause]
we've a game there is no game without
the players really it all comes down to
you you keep us in check you keep us in
check it's basically code for yeah we
made some shitty games and through all
of it you're always there with us you
are definitely not afraid to tell us how
you feel
[Music]
what did fall I'm 76 get in rating again
two points oh my god brah
you'll feedback sometimes challenges us
but it forces us to be always
challenging ourselves this whole
conference to me just sounded like we're
we're still friends right
sorry about that really bad game with it
but we're still cool right like we're
our friends here showcase get off the
stage we won time you guys know Todd
Howard was in the Chess Club who's
laughing now yes I was in the Chess Club
we have had an incredibly exciting year
Bethesda Game Studios given some of that
excitement impressed you're still here I
love him yeah all the bad games are
totally fine as long as start Howard
makes a joke about it
see that's the face you make when you
have a game rated 2.7 actually over the
last year we've had over 60 million
players in our games Wow ever they have
over 60 million play how can we say
something good about this situation
oh god anything oh we have this many
players but did they have fun we have a
lots of players the score Fred buzzwords
mean like everything is great everything
is good we have lots of players what's
that only 41% of them like the game but
there were so many of them a type of
game we've never done before had a lot
of difficulties at launch we had a lot
of difficulties at lunch oh really
you don't say could we edit out copies
oh my god oh I guess we can't
Oh time that is amazing oh my what
happened a lot of well-deserved
criticisms yeah your game man not good
team kept working on it
and you kept playing it well maybe if
you stopped releasing unfinished games
Todd but the development team were
working on it and they were they should
have just done it from the beginning
Todd you're making me angry Todd and
then in comes these two guys I don't
know they just said a couple of things
and one guy had an awkward laugh before
[Applause]
it's kind of cute but speaking of cute I
asked myself this question every time I
go to the office
just kidding defecating just eating we
are very excited let's take a look
meeting it thank you okay about the game
and then for some reason the yang
started just amping up I don't know who
this guy is I don't know why people are
so excited
Thanks thank you everyone
wow thank you and gaming the Elder
Scrolls online has dragons dragons of
the world of Tamriel what happens next
check out elsewhere the latest shackles
new players
yeah well a necromancer everyone say
yeah everyone saying they had a paid
audience they're clearly just trolling
like for then keep an eye out for a
dungeon DLC adventure called scale
breaker which you'll see in August
nobody Bethesda III crowd some more
awkward laughs anyone you would like
some okay here we go
you think I'm gonna talk about the games
really no one cares this is like we're
talking about commercials then they
brought out the I think the most swedish
person they could find after liberating
America from the Nazi scum in
Wolfenstein to the new Colossus hello
everyone we don't all talk like that all
right
after killing all the Nazi scum in this
video game it there this year we take
you back to Europe with two new
Wolfenstein games we take you back to
your why is it funny it's not even funny
even more evil Nazis to kill Wow God
that was beautiful
out of thousands of people in the
audience they're like okay that girl
show her in the center now never seen
someone so enthusiastic you know that's
a girlfriend being dragged into this
just kidding all these people they don't
have girlfriends because they're gamers
brofist if you're a gamer too and then
finally we get to the doom stuff that's
the good stuff that's right that's the
game this whole time I mean like come on
dude
you know it's innovation and creativity
is in our DNA and a very large neck
Jesus Christ look at that thing my god
sorry and all of these advances work as
a big net come on all right moving on we
got EA EA was so goddamn painful to
watch it's four hours
give you give me the hot babes let's get
it goin yeah yeah we're talking about
Star Wars they're making a Star Wars
game it's Star Wars
it's a Star Wars game please keep it go
and they're making a Star Wars game wow
that's so cool
so the added Greg get Greg I know his
name is Greg instead of that guy from
last year I guess they listened to
feedback so you know I gotta appreciate
that EA the guy from last year I mean
come on why didn't you rehire him I
don't understand
bring back III 2018 guy come on it's
like they picked up they don't know the
cringe right they're like all right how
can we reduce the cringe please I don't
like you everybody's anxious to see what
this 15 minutes is going to be listen we
have more maps so let's deliver a brand
new one to you this is Alison dead yeah
without the cream sisters boring I don't
care the fight no yeah you were supposed
to deliver I'm so disappointed
we can't wait to let me play it
yeah hahaha that's the true excitement
yeah come on this is why you need to
hire the Ubisoft people she just want to
see if skate 4 is happening or not I get
it on the same where we skateboard of
course we're gonna come to a play we've
got a booth out there look at the guy in
the backcountry to play it you know
doesn't matter what we think it only
matters what the players think they're
the ones playing the game so if they
love it great and if they don't they'll
tell us the feedback and we'll do our
best to address it well thank you Ben
get back to work I want everybody right
now this is serious
okay there's a serious your hands
together because joining us here on the
stage here in just a moment is one of
the best wide receivers on the planet
from the Pittsburgh Steelers from the
University of Southern California a
hardcore mad and fan ladies and
gentlemen all the way in the back give
it up for juju Smith juju us the juju of
course wow that's so sick I brought a
couple of codes here for juju we're
gonna give juju some codes as well we're
also gonna be sharing on social channels
check that out juju dispenser there he
goes
handing out those coats I don't know
that you're gonna get those back that's
kind of the point of giving them out
sorry okay okay we're gonna kick to
somebody else for this announcement oh
yeah here's Joey Graceffa producer and
content creator youtuber I love this
they learned from last year we need a
youtuber for this make a pretty recorded
goddammit then yeah yeah what up guys
thank you for having me EA and Need for
Speed payback if you guys didn't know HP
payback I'm but um yeah it's great game
and I'm so excited to announce this
upcoming partnership with one of my
favorite games so this summer the Sims
is actually partnering with the UM this
is why I'm proud to be a gamer this is
to me what gaming is all about where's
his [ __ ] gaming channel did this
become his gaming channel bring back
shirtless Joey Graceffa gaming please
welcome back everyone to another episode
of sim stem anya so in the then we have
Xbox Xbox it's such a weird cult around
Xbox I really don't get it
like these people in the crack
go in Oh boo boo gaben yeah bruh bruh
like overall it was a pretty boring
conference there's not much to say about
it I didn't really want letting to send
a bird about anything oh my god it's
Keanu Reeves yay oh my god huh Keanu is
the best I love him so much
oh my god the screams please Jesus stop
oh my god that was actually me I was
there that would actually be me if I'm
in Canada but the best part of course
let me tell you was this the feeling of
of being there of walking the streets of
the future is really going to be
breathtaking did he just say embrace
thank you
then my booty came out he's welcome
there's nothing really to say about it
but his name is Matt booty so I thought
it was worth it
head of Xbox game studios Matt
Taha his name is bode September 10th oh
wow
Gears of War Farm that's so awesome oh
my even bothered then came in hello I'm
French and I don't know what to do with
my hands
hello everyone yes we've got your back
new content free updates and many
surprises inspired by our community and
i was III pretty much in a nutshell 2019
it's pretty disappointing I feel like
they've learned it's it's year they're
learning how to avoid the cringe what
started off is something so beautiful
it's now just become a stale corporate
marketing event that's in the chat boys
this might be the last one my name
appeared pie and brofist what you never
played super simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
convinced yet okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]