him and he said and everybody
around because he ain't got nobody
to listen to listen to listen
i'm a blue bubbly baba
pull up
all right no one's here but i'm gonna
talk anyway i gotta i finally got like
the
elgato hd pro it's the thing you used to
record uh
game console capture with i had it
forever
and i just was so scared because it was
like oh you have to install it into your
computer
what can you hear me by the way
that'd be [ __ ] awkward if i have to
tell this story this is funny because
like you literally just
i was so scared because the idea of
putting something
by myself and my computer was so was so
much more difficult
in my head than it was in real life it
so when i did it it was like
changing the head of a vacuum cleaner
like it was so easy and i felt so stupid
for putting it off usually
computer related stuff is always more
difficult than you think it is
but this time it was the opposite so i
was like what the [ __ ]
this is funny now i can play on my
computer
with the playstation which is really
nice
is there music though or am i missing
out
i'm not sure i don't understand like
maybe i need to share the live stream
yeah that's it
members only or
out
yeah [ __ ] why is no one coming to my
stream
okay here we go people are coming what's
up
danny fighter
how are you this blessed morning
excellent no one cares danny fi i'm
kidding sorry
you're the only one here i shouldn't be
roasting you
oh e lsd what's up gamer oh
sorry i did an oopsy
you saw it from the discord server why
aren't
why aren't people seeing it anywhere
else
this uh very confusing for me
you saw it on youtube how many people
are in here there's gonna be like two
people in here
no worries no worries
what's up gamers early gamers
i feel like people can't get access to
it
youtube is doing some weird algorithm
[ __ ] here
there's no way
this is no way
all right maybe i'll just post it on the
discord then cause i i think youtube is
it's like oh this is a hidden thing we
shouldn't share it
but i still want my members to see it
obviously
yeah but it i i get that you guys got
the notification but two people getting
their notification makes no [ __ ]
sense
you're not special i mean you are sorry
all right two people two people stream
[ __ ] it why not you know what
great i don't care how many people are
watching
is the game too loud or something just
let me know
oh nice i can actually hear the game now
i've been playing it
without hearing anything
i think i will replay this game
honestly
[Music]
um
are you talking about lsd now or
meditation
or meditation through lsd
whatever gets you off
i'm not into drugs this is a play on
my full name oh well that's someone else
whatever gets your eye off and eats soy
alchemy
yeah i know i know
certain type of drugs can help you reach
some sort of
ego association which makes you it
changes you as a person but i'd rather
if i wanted to reach some sort of
conclusion about myself and my ego i
want to reach that on my own and not
help through drugs because
i want to be able to return to that
place on my own
if i ever get there not
relying on drugs to get there
go sit under a freezing waterfall until
you realize well i guess that's
what i'm gonna have to do isn't it i
wouldn't mind
it's a journey there isn't it i'll get
there
uh i want to upgrade some stuff real
quick
how's the is it is the game play too
loud or too low
oh no
i like when you really practice your
mindfulness you can sometimes feel your
blood moving through your body i know
what you mean actually
that's a good idea i was a good minute i
didn't practice i'm
trying to really feel your body because
it takes you out of your mind to do that
uh do i want to upgrade this no
motokuyo
[Music]
i think i'm really close
yeah we're almost maxed it out so i
might as well go for that first
all right let's do a main quest because
everyone wanted it last time
maybe i shouldn't do many questions
since no one's really watching right now
what do you guys reckon it feels a bit
like
because people really want to see them i
might as well wait
am i going to play ballarant again
honestly valerian seem pretty
fun i can see myself getting into it
i'm not proponent of drugs but some
things give you a glimpses into another
side of your consciousness
sounds like you are a proponent of drugs
my dude no shame
do what you want to do i don't care
damn this looks pretty
i love the clear what blue sky this
makes me uh miss winter
isn't that crazy
it takes into a state of mind that when
you try to recreate
that sober assume it's not the same
well yeah that's drugs for you
all that white hurts my eyes ah put on
dark mode quick
my eyes start burning out
let's [ __ ] these guys up
i got [ __ ]
so [ __ ] cool
ready
they're really strong
[Music]
one enemy actually takes time
float
this is like far cry japan yeah
i think with most drugs your body
becomes desensitized to the enhancement
to your constitution but mindfulness to
the effects
become more by now yeah i mean i guess
another word of mindfulness in this
scenario for me is like
i'm very much against it but i'm also
open to the idea that i
have never tried it so i can't really
judge it but i i just know it's not
i know it's something i don't want to do
oh we got a mythic quest here i didn't
realize
let's go for it then
thank you jay appreciate it
do i usually talk about drugs in these
streams no i don't think so
it just was brought up
[Laughter]
foreign
alcohol is a drug
nicotine is a drug
is
blue
[Music]
uh
i like the song is playing it's popping
there's hardly anyone in this stream i
don't don't understand why
thanks for being pierced floor gang out
thank you matthew
it is very chill though so i'll take it
it's a lot easier to stream and there's
only a couple people
guess we got to climb this mountain [ __ ]
yeah i'm into it
which mountain though i can't even see
it it's so semrina
oh [ __ ]
so oh i see so you have to it's an
element of gameplay
i don't realize
if you can [ __ ] off mr dog because i
clearly need to hurry the [ __ ] up
oh it's taking damage now
oh my god it's right there
here we go
that's kind of fun
unexpected but yeah
i wish i could sit in the game
like dark souls style
why is my camera inverted well i'm so
glad you asked
because you see the gameplay is here so
it makes sense
that i'm like looking at the gameplay
nice attention to detail
do you understand let's see how my hair
looks like a [ __ ]
ball thank you
ah yes yeah
okay so we need to find the next flame
pretty quick
otherwise we are toast or the opposite
of toast i should say
all right here we go ascend mount
joe i don't have time for dogs
oh god
i'm sorry doggy dog
where am i supposed to go clearly here
if there was a dog here but i
oh i see it i see it
when i learned that word the first time
i always thought it was samus
it helps oh you're dead
[ __ ] i'm gonna die oh i'm stuck
i can't uh
well i'm dead where do i go up
can i jump back at least
no i can't right
where do i go up oh there
oh my god it's i can make it easy
the [ __ ] i can't believe i almost died
there cringe
i'll become a white walker soon
i haven't seen game of thrones or read
it
but i understood the reference that's
epic
i can sit a little bit i guess
i can sit a little bit
i don't really have time for dogs
[ __ ] i was hoping there would be a
grappling hook place there and i just
went for it
guess not zero deaths cringe
well this is going great
it said it's so hard to see
i don't know where to go
maybe i'm supposed to go up on the side
here
no
oh there it is yeah
come on just go can't really see
there we go
nailed it what's up samurai
nice we can upgrade our sword now how
you doing mame
frost coast my body a final suit of
armor buried in silver
that was beautiful we're almost there
cool quest
i'm not sure why the stream is not
alerting everyone
but uh it's a very chill chill group of
people
i think we're less than a hundred
this looks a lot easier than the other
ones because i keep getting lost
otherwise
i know i know bro i know
uh now where the [ __ ] do i go from here
excuse me
where it must be over here
yeah there it is
oh this is a close call dude
we made it
squishy
nice
is our cool picture to be taken here
this is what it really looks like
if anything i just want like
i want like uh
this with the audio and uh
that's cool an animation like a
recording of it and then have that
animated like a
maybe use wallpaper engine or something
that'd be [ __ ] cool
that looks cool too much
too much looks good on its own
let me actually try and get a better
pose
oh i love how you can see the ocean
really struggling here
i feel like this would look better
without me
um
there we go that's what i wanted
yeah it feels like a loading screen
isn't it
can you record video clips
what is happening
[ __ ] i guess i can't record it off my
elgato i'll just record it directly
congrats on getting on the top of kevin
kaise
thank you thank you i might make this
into a wallpaper on my computer
hey fitz i just want to thank you for
being like a father to me i'm autistic
so i had a lot of troubles growing up
but you have always been a great role
model
and you inspired me to better myself
every day thank you may
that's so nice infinity
don't push yourself too hard
i don't know what sounded patronizing
but i feel like i do that with my son
it's always good to improve yourself is
what i mean but
all right one more
that's pretty comfy too
i like that one
legit we saw sunset yesterday
and i was like dude that would look way
better on ghost of sushima
oh no now that ruined it go away dual
shock
peaceful stream you may rest here
while going to the next video welcome
guys
all right i think i got it that should
be enough for a loop i'll try that out
and i'll share it on if you guys have
wallpaper engine
it might be cool let me try and color
grade it so it fits my computer a little
better actually
yeah more blue would look better on my
computer let me do it again
you guys use wallpaper engine
it's pretty cool you can get like
animated
um backgrounds and [ __ ] i'll show you
mine
got the rain it's comfy got the blue
theme
nice i like it
feels good man i got this theme for
windows as well
i make sure i don't show anything weird
though
yeah windows looks different
it's kind of cool it's got a different
like
big like it
important things you know things that
truly matter
all right back to the gameplay
where did the gameplay go oh god what
have i done
oh i removed wrong [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] video capture device
oh god what did i do there we go
there we go we're back
it reset the audio though is it too loud
now or is it okay
when you can't tell your gameplay from
your wallpaper
it's a problem
it's hard to tell this is win well i'm
sorry
all right let's keep should we keep
playing the game
should we try that all right
we got to be hurry hurry here we go
hurry here guys that's english right
at least it's obvious where to go now oh
god i spoke too soon
this is a weird universe repeats just a
small streamer
yeah right alternate small streamer
pewdiepie universe
uh
and we're hot and it's how
okay i guess we go here
someone else uh died there that's pretty
cringe
i think we're going down here aren't we
yeah doesn't look as cold as before
there's a thing there
oh god i'm supposed to swing somewhere
that was a tricky one
is there any nihongo bros in the chat
why did they add kai at the end i never
i've never heard
sleep comes drawing near deeper i begin
to sink cold and slow step
sheesh
did i just i just run past it to go
back no i didn't do that right
am i that dumb it felt like i walked in
circles there
i am lost
yeah uh excuse me where do i go though
didn't i just go here oh god i'm going
in circles
[ __ ] it i'm going for it huh
it's a [ __ ] bear
kumasan i don't have time for you
get the [ __ ] up
[Applause]
someone built a [ __ ] dojo here
what a legend
foreign
nice this is so cool
i love that it's so japanese to build
places in pharah
locations a friend of mine told me about
a ramen place that's like
built on top of a mountain so you have
to walk all the way just to get it
it's like at the most obscure spot ever
but it's still
popular
i'm sure the ramen isn't that good but
it's like the journey to get there
all right we're gonna fight this guy why
why
aren't this awkward i'm not getting a
prompt
well glitchy i guess
what is happening i want to fight you
he said find a rock
i guess i wasn't paying attention this
is awkward
teach me
here we go i don't have any resolve
i used all of it i should have killed
the bear
in before frostbite
oh god
well that's a little harder
this is going to be tough i don't have
any resolve in this battle
all right
[Music]
i
is
i didn't see the prompt i was so focused
on the combat i did not see the text in
front of me
[ __ ]
[Music]
you fight with no honor
you didn't study the blade deeply
oh [ __ ] oh [ __ ] that's cheating
[Music]
he's letting me fight him that would
have been a lot easier
come on
[Music]
okay so hold to switch ghost weapons
where the flame oh okay so it's two
charges
that's really useful
i kind of want to check out this guy's
dojo a little bit
so like any [ __ ] up here you know you
know i'm saying
i love the the duels i wish they made a
whole game around it
it's like the most fun part
right and then have multiplayer aspect
to it kind of like for
honor if they made a second one skip all
the
cut scenes and [ __ ] i don't give a [ __ ]
have it more focus on the duels have
multiplayer options kind of like
bloodborne
that'd be so [ __ ] cool
that would that that went well this is
the back end
hopefully there's a cool little
view from point i expect it a bit more
oh i like the red in the sky
and every skype
what should we go for
i really like when you can't see
anything
have you guys played rage shadow legends
wow i'm glad i'm
i'm glad i'm in the chat i don't i don't
like it
oh that just goes down all the way
a musician it was crazy i almost freaked
my ass off but i found you
i mean him
dude this guy knows how to play
purity of war new mask huh
the fire of war is fury cannot be
contained
uh we got ourself a new mask check it
out
i do quite like the one we have
haunted dreams worn by those who have
seen
death that's pretty [ __ ] badass
kinda want that
is that the one
mask is really cool too
nasty that's cool
that looks cool
there it is it doesn't match it's just
kind of ugly
i think i like that one
which one is more aesthetic because
that's really what i give a [ __ ] about
i think this is the most aesthetic one
it doesn't look good in this light
though [ __ ]
the pain of being a man
they all look terrible in this light
what the [ __ ]
can someone change the light please it's
almost like the game lets you alright
haunted dreams it is
[Music]
red goes better yeah
let's try it see how it looks like nope
that looks [ __ ] terrible
that's the one let's go with that i
don't [ __ ] care anymore
we can upgrade our sword that's what we
can do right now
get the n95 mask [ __ ]
i didn't think of that
also i remember pete saying i didn't buy
the digital
deluxe version of this game what would i
do with it
okay yeah now i regret it maybe
it just i don't know they're just trying
to squeeze extra money out of you i'm
not down with actually
boom
pewds growing as a channel yeah thank
you
we upgraded everything yes
yes where's the the boyers over there
where's the armor
any gifts i shall accept guardians
scowl for someone aiming to disassociate
from
physical pleasures and striving for
minimus valley why are you building a
clothing brain
uh good question
it's step by step process i would say
it's also fun
i feel like if i cut i like i know what
i need to do to get there
but if i i know if i do it all at once
it's not a good idea
and it's also harder when some some
stuff are tied into your business
so it's like bigger decisions to make
but yeah i think i think especially not
tsuki per se
because we're more environmental
uh conscious but like the merchant that
i sell
is obviously not good for the
environment and i do feel kind of
strange about that
where is the armor like it
it is fast fashion and um i'm
technically against it
there's also problems because if i don't
sell it people will be like where is it
where is it i would not hear the end of
it
and i i don't know i guess there has to
be a way and
the problem is actually if i sell merch
for a higher price because that's what
it would cost
to produce like more i got on a
different tangent here that's not what
you asked but
um people would complain
because the prices wouldn't be higher oh
yeah step by step
i want to upgrade the ghost armor
what the [ __ ] are you doing get out of
my shot i'm trying to look at myself
are there any cool arm uh
like clothing options
i can't see anything
what should we do next
how long have i been streaming should i
open up the floodgates
it's a has been an hour all right well
it's been fun
chilling with you y'all it's time to
open up the floodgates
all right i'll be right back i'm gonna
get a drink
oh
okay
um
what's up [ __ ]
um that's all good dirty i'm already
aware of
other ship that i don't like about
myself that i want to change
but i'm working to get there
how y'all doing [ __ ]
i'm eating a shitty pear doesn't taste
anything
what the [ __ ] is this why is it shitty
i've been waiting like five days to eat
it and it's still not good
gotta be right man
i ate all the other fruit
my mom works for unicef big thank you
for the donation you're the best
is unicef connected with save the
children
i should probably know that
hmm that part was good
delicious
are you guys enjoying watching me eat a
pair because i'm enjoying myself
tony back with the daily simple what up
man
did you guys not get the mem memo jesus
is so early i've been streaming for an
hour for members only but there was like
50 people in there
i'm so confused like now there's clearly
way more members
so clearly not everyone got them like
the notification
you didn't see it yeah [ __ ] i gotta ask
youtube what the [ __ ]
feet licks about to shop some painters
feet licks don't call me that [ __ ]
name
[ __ ] youtube
it was kind of fun though we were
literally you could actually talk to the
guy
no offense guy it's a lot harder this
way
i guess you can see it later i mean i'm
walking in the wrong direction
it looks so appealing over here
we need a question where we climbed the
mountain
and got the fire sword it's pretty cool
where am i going
it's on my right left
i posted it on the discord because i
noticed no one was getting it
but um
i low volume or is the game
um
how's that
i love you big pp move to japan last
year if you ever get a chance to go to
sushima i highly recommend it much love
oh cool appears new floor game over here
just want to say i love your
videos bought one of the g fuel from the
provo hey
that's right stinky no members i'm just
kidding
members got a special offer on the new g
fuel cups that's epic
join member now
hopefully finish the game how long is it
left
cringe if you don't have the g-fuel
shaker like
who would not have it
how else are you gonna drink g-fuel
i thought we just did i don't want to
speak to you again it's boring let me
kill people
is my phone ringing
give me one second
you
sorry gamers
golden retribution
there's no other cool armor
i wasn't muted oh no that's embarrassing
oh that's nice the emperor's tears
[ __ ] yeah jin's voice actor the same as
zoros
the one from one piece yeah i heard that
i guess i gotta get into one piece man
i like that it's still going you know
which one is cooler
the island's keeper
oh red is pretty dope
oh i like that i like the red
ah
let's see how this looks oh that's
pretty
cool i like the red i'm going with the
red [ __ ]
i should play a simulation game and
learn how to fly a plane
yeah i'm kind of down that sounds fun
there was a secret illuminati chat in
the first hour stream maybe
all right sounds fun damien
[Music]
ring ring hey felix can you please stop
collecting my socks
i understand the sentiment but i'm
getting a bit creeped out all the best
pokemane
[ __ ] it's almost 6 a.m where i live but
hey floor gang time
[ __ ] yeah yeah it's a weird time to be
streaming
i am aware all right
i'm i'm gonna google i gotta google
how to get rid of this [ __ ] bow
because it's too
ugly i hate it oh
oh oh
i had an upgrade that looks amazing
yeah yeah nice
oh [ __ ] yeah oh [ __ ] yeah we look cool
now
yeah you don't [ __ ] with us
oh hell yeah
yes if only jurgen was alive everything
would be perfect
oh yes
we get the [ __ ] jurgen
ammo leicester been a fan says day one
thank you mo
oh i knew
there was something wrong with it and i
was like what is it
oh got it
[Laughter]
sometimes sometimes i get people that
are uh
like special so like
i don't want to be rude and then oh god
it's just someone trolling
[Laughter]
good one
hey it's your boy mike hunt
my child molesters a big fan man
have you heard of my dad joe
damn they hate me huh
bring it ow don't bring it
well this is going
terrible [ __ ]
stream is always starting in midnight
hawaii
yeah i know i hope when i i'm in japan
i can stream in an actual good time for
people
because this is like the worst sign well
that went great
uh zero thefts right yeah thank you
hey felix uh
much love from long time fan i owe you
so much for all these years
entertainment from 2011
to now just want to say thank you thank
you right back
yes is that a cool screen shot
i wish there were more fights like at
cool places
what the [ __ ] how
[Music]
[ __ ]
float
tier three merge is i'm i don't
it was done so long ago i'm so sorry
it's taking so long
and i would like to say it isn't my
fault
but i think it probably is my fault
please say hi to my child melissa
hello melissa how are you doing long
time fine here shout out to bertabo the
greatest unfinished masterpiece of all
time
thank you
the problem is i i can't i keep moving
houses and then they send me the merch
so i can improve it
but i keep missing it so it's just
taking a lot extra time for no
good reason
have ever watched xserbia your videos
and philosophy are great
remind me a lot of him i don't i haven't
watched now i recognize the name though
[Music]
can i come in uh oh okay i guess not
sorry sorry sorry
overwhelming forces when you go to japan
do you think you will
do more collabs with anime man yeah for
sure
all right this sounds like a challenge
to me
oh what are you aiming at
oh
i think i got him one more
right in the taters
uh they're calling for backup please do
you think swedish or english
i think in it depends what the context
of what i'm thinking of
come out come out let's play
ah the [ __ ]
who did they
who's doing that [ __ ] stop
what the [ __ ] just happened did the game
just automatically kill me because
that's
what that felt like
i am going there i don't care
i don't care what it takes
what the [ __ ] is it that far
are you serious
look they're just is the game memeing me
like they're just shooting me from
nowhere
yeah yeah the game was like you can't go
here
i can't get in this is a problem with me
someone tells me i can't do something
have you watched god of high school or
taro god yet no but i'm watching prison
school and it's hilarious
i guess the point is that i was gonna
break in
like a different way huh all right
seems hard to keep up with donations
while playing the game bootleg excuse me
uh wait who's the bootleg
there's no way i can be he's younger
come on
yes
[Music]
ow don't do that
god damn that's a lot of them
calm down folks
i'm gonna have to go all out just once
oh this fire sword
no i can't die now i can't turn out i
don't want to die now oh god
oh he shot his [ __ ] friend
[Applause]
[ __ ]
catch
jesus christ i made it out alive
of course
[Music]
can you not do that attack oh my god
three times really
there it is [ __ ] the game is dark
thank you steven
are your thoughts on tax lane don't know
who it is don't care
guess i got my combat that i wanted
jesus
oh that's you
why is everyone so shocked about that
what did i just say i'm sorry i take it
back
you think joe rogan is tuned in on this
shivering
at the amount of donations
i believe so
who's dax playing
literally
literally who is that
tax flame more like dex got no fame
because i don't oh that's a bear
sorry bear you have to die
is that the one items is it the ice
cream man oh i saw that
never mind i know who it is that was
great
we need more smoothie game show some of
the game show contestants
yeah i never saw him back in the day i i
thought i knew like all the og
youtubers [ __ ] but that's like one
generation above me
so i don't really have any like oh my
god it's him it's more like oh that's
interesting i guess
but it was a good video
i'm just looking for loot and stuff
sorry i know it's boring
i want to upgrade my armors you see guys
so i can look cool in the game
looking cooling game is the most
important part of the game
poor bear he was finally free
gonna play cyberpunk when it's released
yes of course i am
it will never be released however
i just predicted the future all right
where am i supposed to go
all right guys i'm ready
i never used to poison thank you
forgetting about it
where are they where the [ __ ] are they
i'm not watching more avatar because i
just got the video copyrighted and it
was more annoying
to deal with than it is to enjoy
watching it
what's happening
can you talk to him did the game did he
just glitch out
there we go
[Music]
foreign
wait for the [ __ ] patrol to approach
all right i can wait
weird question have you listened to ben
ply's music
he's it's possible i just don't i don't
remember the name of a lot of
artists that i listen to
hey that's my move
whoa they both died at the same time
what the [ __ ]
was that a scripted event
er howdy sir howdy harley quinn
lethal mode too easy
investigate the fight at toyotaro
damn what a lady
where do i survey 30 meters from here
can i say bruh bruh
bruh you betray the bra brah
have to go now great stream csdn
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
am i surveying yet then
foreign
[Music]
oh god oh god oh [ __ ] rick what have we
done
oh i don't [ __ ] with the flame sword
i changed my mind guys
oh
[Music]
that's even the answer a little bit
[Applause]
yes
that was [ __ ] dope
dude that was sick i love that
where are they oh there's more
well nailed it
this is too intense
yes oh
i'm finally using heavenly strike guys
it's amazing why did no one tell me
about it
fear me
[ __ ] i i may have used it in a bad
timing whatever it was cool
[Music]
why would you say that what's wrong with
you
what's overrated about it
huh how dare you disrespect
mount fujisan uh love what you do
thank you sweden shout out to my balls
reaching okay
let's keep playing
i was 14 when i found your channel i'm
23 now hey mike's worth awesome your
content is matured of all this i grew up
can't thank you enough
for everything over the years thank you
right back man
appreciate you wolves at gates
yeah the straw hats are gone
we obliterated those scum traitor scum
floor gang is overrated why would you
say
that wow now you're just being mean
for no reason
i can upgrade the ghost armor but it
looks so ugly the sakai armor is the
best
hippies anyhow spending cash i don't
have but i was furloughed due to covet
i'm three months late on rent and
without help soon i'm homeless
any help or ideas
aren't there government subs things to
help people
i'm sorry i don't know i'll refund your
donation
uh sorry about that i don't know what to
say
maybe start by don't donating to
streamers that's just sorry
sorry i don't need to be sarcastic about
your situation all the best
hey pigs just want to let you know you
make me smile well thank you
yeah plea please don't donate money to
me if you don't have
the money to to spare
it's mainly just for a way to for people
to leave a message it's not really about
the money either
um now i got distracted what am i doing
i go back here
we oh man we have a lot more to liberate
in this [ __ ]
pewdiepie i'm spending my money on your
flare gang stream please do not make
this a waste of money
the money will go to
me figuring how to [ __ ] get to japan
that's the goal
it's so complicated
uh all right let's go back and we can
upgrade
nothing yeah why would we get back
upgrade the ghost armor and get the
black dye on it
all right fine you win
this is the coolest armor
i'm not interested this is a sidequest
it is it's a side quest isn't it what do
we get mongol commander armor
hey all right all right
all right speak with the man in
yogaku where is he
where's the man
thank you
[Music]
is it better
did you guys hear that
that [ __ ]
sushi rolls god damn thank you sushi
rose
not subaba's wrath
you get so much stuff in this game
there's so much unlockables it's insane
how does that look like ooh
[Music]
i like our stuff
i wish the game let you like uh have
set outfits i don't know maybe you can
do it but like if i have a certain armor
i want to put
on certain charms as well and this is
too much effort
to do that
yes yes scratch on my belt laid out
that was it
oh
he went up again
ah [ __ ]
oh that dog slayer man
can't see anything
ah [ __ ]
come get some
yes
[Music]
get fluted
pewds can you change stances is that a
thing yeah but they were all swords
people
there's no point in changing stance in
case you're new in the game yeah
stone is water shield windest spear
moon is big people it's epic
but if you're trying to be sarcastic
then you make no sense so
oh there's another quest here wait
obtain mongol armor pieces is that the
same thing
kill general dog shin my man's got a
dog shin what the [ __ ]
good job pierce very nice thank you
this
it just hit me i uh i was roasting
excuse me a little bit before but
he seemed like a good dude like i have
no i don't have
anything bad against him a bit random it
just hit me randomly i was like
i don't want him to think i don't like
him or some [ __ ]
hello well that's a good start what the
[ __ ] just hit me
this is a cool place for maybe a photo
[ __ ] i got poison
oh it's only two people [ __ ]
[Music]
oh we got more
maybe this will be a good photo
jesus
[Applause]
[Music]
that was my move
yes
[ __ ] see i miss it once and
ruin
[Music]
flute float why can't i flute
this is so unfair
let me play my [ __ ] flute
uh would i consider participating in the
minecraft championship which is hosted
by
nox crew and uh nah
sorry no not interesting
but thank you for asking
i'm sure it's better than minecraft
mondays at least
i'm sure
i was torn between 100 mil and the glow
in the dark ended up getting the glow in
the dark
a gloss in the dark [ __ ] you made the
right choice my friend
ah he tricked me
i can't block behind me i forgot
can you say ben is an epic gamer i
wanted to be my friend again oh ben what
the [ __ ]
could you see that i blocked that but it
didn't count oh [ __ ] then nice
show me
this is a lot more pleasant
is this a cool screenshot
nah
that's why i found this already
you know you got to get a flute after
this playthrough you're right sierra
you're absolutely right
thank you fox
oh that's pretty ah ah there's a bear
yeah again run
[Music]
yeah again no
i can't all right all right it's too
cute i can't do it
ah [ __ ] oh [ __ ] up [ __ ] i changed my
mind
all right all right
ah [ __ ] not my leg [ __ ] up
you fight with no honor
ah god
stop doing that
i'm petting the fox over here there you
go you're a good you're a good [ __ ]
don't don't mind this giant matroc city
oh god oh done we're back god damn it
god
this ends now
heavenly strike the bear
oh my what the [ __ ] i play song in your
honor mr mayor
pewds just watched two to three videos
and got addicted to your channel
if there's been a best gamer award you
seriously would have won it and you
deserve it thank you
i don't win awards anymore because i'm
too controversial so people pretend i
don't exist
it's more convenient that way
arrow upgrade okay epic i don't want
awards anyway
legit don't want him
uh my friends don't believe me can you
tell them how much of an epic gamer i am
my name is kyla thailand epic gamer
number one i've been saying it my whole
life
imagine being a ronin and you suddenly
hear flute noises
oh god no
run
[ __ ] the stand up
anyone else
oh my god oh my god
uh
i always
i'm almost dead i'm almost dead
uh can we uh can we can we talk about
this
no i heavenly strike failed me
the [ __ ] i was so ready for it just get
paid so i'm spending the wealth it's
three i'm here in cali
thank you for staying up with me that
was not epic
it's so hard when you're playing the
spear and the shield at the same time
sorry chica i disappointed you
pewdiepie has died zero times in this
game oh nice thank you nightbot
nightboy knows what the [ __ ] up
all right now i can redeem the
redemption
sup [ __ ]
bring it dogs
is that all you got dogs
pathetic
[Music]
i feel like here's uh he's in here
hello
it's so fast
it's so fast i can't do it
dodge this [ __ ]
dudes you make my dates better to top it
off can i get a brofist
hell yeah thank you sir joe
see how i nailed that
all right we're done here who's oh
there's a bunch of people in here
bingo
so proud of far have you been so far
so proud of how far you come watching
since 2011. thank you kyla 2014. i read
that wrong
hello
yeah nailed it all right surely now
they're all dead
oh yeah now you need my help
my name is alan and been watching since
amnesia hell yeah
i guess everyone's from cali now rescue
the hostages what the [ __ ] where
there's more in this village bonus kill
enemy
with a long ball for sure i'll do that
do i get a longer period to dodge with
the wind stands if they have a spear
i want to try it that theory is correct
because man was it [ __ ] short
uh die i need you to actually die though
thank you that's one
[Music]
you didn't see me here
i don't want to kill you
so good against these guys
did i forget about the main quest god
dammit
yeah i feel like that was the reason
there's no way it's that difficult to
parry those
i think i was in the wrong stance
are we dead over here my dude
they saw me
one more
there's five hostages [ __ ]
where
[Music]
yeah why don't i see any enemies
they're all ins they're all inside
let's blow them up
boom boom
ah you made it out alive
let's not fail this question what what
the [ __ ] just happened
oh he's gonna he's gonna kill a hostage
i'm gonna fail
is the officers
yeah i failed [ __ ] come on that would
have been so
fun guess this game hates fun huh
i'll spam them more next time
oh that resets my longbow challenge god
damn it all right
i've been asking to take over a pub as
landlord so this may be my last live
stream for a lot well all the best and
good luck
[Music]
oh we're here now
can i just help this is that a giant
whale whoa
did you guys see that last time
the [ __ ]
holy moly
this is some legend of zelda [ __ ]
you know when you go inside the mouth
[Music]
wow
so damn
they were making candles out of the
whale oil and [ __ ] like that that had so
many uses
back in the day i guess there's a lot of
meat too [ __ ]
boy be packing dude literally
[Music]
all right let's blow these [ __ ]
to smith the [ __ ]
[Music]
[ __ ]
well that's one quick way to do it ow
and then i burnt myself
can you stop
god that's annoying why is there an
arrow guy there
who uses arrows inside [ __ ] cringe
dude
vader
who's next someone else in here my oh
there's
slippy vicky has to see his brain
functionality and it's a dude
wait what don't say that
um
let me turn off a little bit it's so
bright i can't see the game
i haven't been able to sleep but happy
to catch this stream yeah
i put people to sleep over here good
night brayden
hey felix i'm an 89 year old used to be
harassed by my client spend
during the battle b series but i never
stopped supporting you and never will
you ignored my last super chat sorry if
i missed it thank you for being a bro
uh i don't ignore them just to be clear
get the [ __ ] out of my [ __ ] face
don't ever want to see your goddamn all
right so now we have to do the bonus
thing
i wanted uh all right so the last one is
where this where
where is the last one
where are they keeping you
is that him
or is it up there it must be up there
i'm moving today what and walk waking up
with the livestream made me feel a lot
less anxious that's great
i'm sure you'll do great just remember
it will take a lot more time than you
think it will
so just take your time with it
sorry if that made him more anxious
i feel like that's what makes me anxious
when i move because you're always like
all right
it won't be that bad oh it will be bad
it's better to know
and you're prepared it's not yeah that's
historic principle
assume assume the worst uh sorry about
the early method
he's not a doodoo head there you go
nikolas
it wasn't a dude ahead i just wanna
all right so i have to kill you with a
heavy arrow
i don't think he died he did okay one
more
why you so fat why you so bad
homie just chilling down there i can't
feel bad you know
where's the ladder
where is the ladder i guess i don't need
it
one more please tell me there is one
more
oh there is isn't it
[Applause]
what a [ __ ] tank respected
does that not count are you serious that
does not count
it is the longbow
foreign
again
nice get the flute
oh next time they're alive i should play
the flute and then kill them
that'd be [ __ ] cool yes
do i have to kill the dogs to save this
man
i'm so lost
oh my god thank you
thank you thank you
guess we have to kill the dogs
let me try first can i let you free oh
you can nice
thank you top of the morning
no problem no problem
oh we got another piece guess i didn't
get my side quest
have you watched any kurosawa films i
haven't
i really want to watch son
i've watched what is it called the
classic
[Music]
oh samurai
what is it called biggest i like my
between wanting to
watch your stream and not wanting to
spoil it for myself
huge fan from sydney thank you travis
sorry about that bro
jurgen looking smooth look at you there
we go
that's more normal let's get this
[ __ ] armor come on
liberated [ __ ]
this is the other piece of armor no is
the other piece of [ __ ] armor
i gotta kill general dog [ __ ] over here
what the [ __ ]
did i get the armor no
where's the quest
oh it got updated now i see all right
hold options for detail
fit for the con son of a guard
open the cars
okay
[Music]
are you winning son absolutely
dude once i'm in japan i'll be ultra
winning
right now i'm kind of winning but
i i'm not like do super duper winning
you know what i mean
i just got it change a couple things
be a little bit more epic then i'll be
in japan
streaming epically
no more controversy no more drama
but enough to keep me challenged and
stimulated
that'll be epic
is it possible you just dance right get
your again
so [ __ ] cool
don't interrupt the way of the flame
all right here we go oh can i change
stains at least god [ __ ] damn
there it is
the bar is so tiny too it's so hard to
see it
i click i click it's so hard
i feel like it's better to just look at
the attack instead of the bar
yeah i think that's what i should do
oh by the way we have some upgrades i
forgot about that
sorry my dudes
i don't want any of them they'll suck
uh yes sure
come here [ __ ] try k
can say armor [ __ ] now this is coolest
armor
so i installed the elgato hd60 pro
which is like this thing that goes
inside your computer and now i can
actually hear the game while i play and
it's
so nice the soundtrack the audio
everything is amazing
i fight with army yeah i strike you from
horse
you dare poison me
i [ __ ] block you
there it is you're there
[Applause]
[Music]
nailed it nailed it
get fluted [ __ ]
get loaded [ __ ] you'll be
streaming in full samurai
armor when you get to japan right of
course
i'll play this game first game i'll
stream
oh sorry zoe i didn't see your super
chat it was it was a long message and
then
something happened have you seen me
known me and my messages you helped me
get through my mother's death inspired
me to start editing i love editing
pewdiepie videos especially with marcy
i'll make my day to watch that's cool
thank you sorry about your mom hey pewds
i want to thank you for keeping it real
you get this often but really help me
claw my way out some really dark times
hang in there captain thank you for
watching appreciate y'all
you just had to ruin my flow
and for this you will die
i saw a bird come on bird show me the
way bird
what you got bird
all right bird all right i guess that's
one way to do it
i'm not interested anymore bird
[Music]
they always come in and ruin the [ __ ]
fun
[Applause]
oh that would have been cool
[Music]
you want to run little boy
i play the flute
enjoy the tunes
nice
you did not study the flute deeply
hey kids since becoming a member my
herpes is really cleared up
i'm so glad i'm glad i could help you
with that one
[Music]
chief
this game is really freaking pretty bro
i know
i love it could play forever
don't need real life
an mmo like this imagine that'd be sick
oh god is this place down the hill oh
no mr dog shin we got a way to go
this could be a cool screenshot
of cool
is it
is it cool
hey felix first time doing this so i
feel kind of anxious i want to say thank
you for posting
your video very well thank you we might
say it was so wholesome
i don't have to thank me for that but
thank you for watching irani that's
great
i'm glad you guys liked it yeah it's one
of those words like
uh you don't want to seem like you're
just trying to milk your wedding
at least that's not what we wanted to do
um
but we also want to have a memory that
we can share and it's fun
i wish jargon didn't look so awkward but
what if we sit on you
trying to get the right post hey felix
thank you so much for your support with
yemen
it means the entire world to me some
since 2011 and just turned 21 a few days
ago congrats on all the success much
love for
from your yemeni fan base how nice thank
you very much
i'm glad to support it youtube bird
wrote
nothing but donated 200 australian jesus
christ uh
thank you thank you very much very kind
of you
i'm just out here trying to get the
right screenshot and jurgen number
five won't [ __ ] do it there it is
hey hey hey see i hate this one
look up there we go
uh video clip what the [ __ ]
why don't tell me
hold up let me record this so i can make
a little maybe we can have a better
worse weather or something
yes okay i'm recording this so
i can make a wallpaper out of it
i'm so excited to do this once i'm done
we did a couple already
i'll share them in the members chat if i
managed to do it
and it's a wallpaper engine i'll
probably try and do it at least
i don't know if the quality is good or
not it's only 1080p but
we got some really cool ones
oh come on that's even prettier god damn
it all right
i'll record a couple seconds
should i put some particles in it well
that [ __ ] up the bitrate doesn't it
not bitrate but uh you know what i mean
let's see how particle look like maybe
if it's snowing or something
can you do that i don't think you can
oh that looks good
uh nice
doesn't look good
does that make it better i don't think
it does
youtuber uh you're not leaving any
messages
and you're donating so much are you okay
if you donate one more with no message
i'll refund it because then i
i'm suspecting foul play
that's kind of cool because that looks
like snow let's go with that
what's up furious dog sorry i i can't
read all of them that's why if they're
less sometimes i don't read them
after this jump off the cliff for epic
gamer moment
all right i want to try another weather
really quick
i quite like it like this
ah that looks [ __ ] aesthetic dude
that looks sick thank you yeah
now
maybe we should get something more comfy
hey pigs hey felix been a fan since
2013.
thank you caitlyn i just wanted to thank
you for everything og brofist from the
king
that that's a lot of caitlyn's watching
you're like the fourth caitlyn
the youtuber stop it i'm not reading
anymore stop it
stop it
wow
i think if we color grade this a little
blue
it could actually be quite epic
is that comfy
let's not come face it
whoa
so
this is important
there it is
boom boom
boom you don't like the red
no taste
they say
all right let me just stop not bad oh
that's how the game looks like okay cool
is there a ski lift down there or
something
let's climb with the jurgen all the way
he can do it
come on [ __ ] jump
jump jump [ __ ] come on
come on come on it's like edgar when he
wants to jump down the bed come on
you're a coward and a scoundrel and you
will never be a true samurai
don't look at me like that oh you're so
cute i'm so sorry
can i jump down from here even who
thinks i'm gonna die if i jump from here
place your bats
all right
it worked
tactical tactical death
slaughter the enemy leader i will study
him
i will study him deeply for extra points
should we do a indiana jones entry
[Music]
that's not fair
i think i'm what that oh i didn't heal
my poison
i got confused what was happening fine
let's redo that again or else the reason
i am it's gotta be epic
it's gotta be epic we gotta kill mr dog
shin
what the oh
all right uh second try
here we go [ __ ]
oh [ __ ] i didn't um
i'm sorry guys i'm just sorry
all right now we get a chance to redo
this part right
i can't reach him
[Music]
up
come on no heavy armor
i were talking look this guy's alive we
can do it now
oh he doesn't let me play the flute god
damn it it would be funny
all right you're gonna get your own
fascia now [ __ ]
[Music]
stray she must
you're too short
[Music]
sad
oh
nice that's what i'm [ __ ] talking
about
yes
anyone else didn't think so
[ __ ]
ready
uh
fear me cowards study the flute
weak
he sounded like jontron what the [ __ ]
jontron mongol confirmed
oh my god it's so these are them
yeah okay
that went well
nailed it zero that's totally guys
their move sets are so difficult
did it easy i gotta end this stream in
five minutes
because food is ready
food time but i wanted the armor
but ma'am i wanted um i'm sorry
what food she's italian what do you
think pasta
or pizza
i am joking much amazing [ __ ]
i'm so lucky
well we got a banner
that's something
weather is a bit rough here up there in
the mountain
i just want to eat meatballs every day
every single day but i can't
and it's not fair
banner is mine your banner
is mine your banner is mine
who's playing that music it's beautiful
how we doing in here boy
what the [ __ ] this village is so big
all right let's do it
nice
now this is something worth photo mode
that's gonna be my new background
didn't really capture its beauty but
now that's so big pp all right guys i'm
gonna end the stream there
thanks for watching hey pewds love all
the good you've done my friend
namita is an indian 19 year old who's
giving exams
to be an epic floor gang pediatrician
epic would go insane with a shout out
shout out to
rohit's friend namita epic good luck
all the best have a great [ __ ] day
have a great [ __ ] night
have a great [ __ ] everything remember
to enjoy yourself
life is short every day count and all
that [ __ ]
see you guys next time
adios see you gamers
i'm gonna eat feels good man