right on time [ __ ]
guess who's here right on time [ __ ]
surprise i'm right on time
bet you're surprised right now
i'm not late i'm early [ __ ]
how dare you
guys i have a confession to make
i have to make an apology
here on the live stream
it's happening
i'm so sorry
about the fact that i have to
drink this
not evenly mixed protein drink and with
some of it stuck on the ceiling
goddamn ceiling gang i'm gonna
as apology i am going to chug the whole
thing
in one giant
gulp who's ready
with your guys support i can
do it
okay here we go who's with me
who's excited can we do it
come on
no i can't do it i don't have enough
i don't have enough support for my
audience
my audience don't believe in me enough
what's that they're beginning to believe
they're believing i can do it okay here
i go guys
ah
thank you to my audience i could believe
in myself
thank you school45
where's my [ __ ] phone i need to turn
on the lights
now what i i wanted to say
the [ __ ] i lost connection there for a
sec
that's weird
i keep losing internet what the [ __ ] is
happening
it goes from excellent to [ __ ] in a
second
wi-fi be like bye bye
have you listened to logic's new album i
don't listen to simps
no i don't the [ __ ] kind of question is
that
logic more like making no senseic that's
what he should call himself yeah i
said it because everyone's too afraid to
say it
i bet if he came in chat right now hey i
signed with twitch can i
collab with i'd be like bro go watch it
go watch rick and morty and shut the
[ __ ] up
[ __ ] i'd say that to his face no
regrets
why don't you
don't you go suck on a
lard and make your face all
buttery and disgusting that's what i
would say
i would say logic more like can you just
go away
that's what i would say any other
question
have you heard bill delphine's news song
velda do i listen to sims
i thought we were through this i don't
listen to james
i thought we were through this
okay okay
all right how you how y'all
[ __ ] doing
[Music]
huh
hey pigs my birthday was yesterday
thanks for making another year filled
with awesome
yeah yeah yeah yeah
did it go down again
the [ __ ] is happening
this is my discord maybe
i mean my uh dropbox maybe my dropbox is
like
auto syncing it likes to do that
sinking and that could be it
sending lot from japan any plants are
coming back open up your country
it's closed for everyone open it
now thank you
i'm sending data
so it might be youtube that's the simp
today
why am i online on skype
that [ __ ] gotta log into discord i don't
remember my discord login
who's ready to have some fun today
someone said small pp wi-fi
are you ready to have some fun
hypershade dick 11
let me hear you say it live hypersedex11
the [ __ ] is wrong with me
i just want a snooze that's all i want
i don't feel anything i just want one
so bad that's all i want
but there i am
yes feel great is it working
the stream working who knows who cares
i'll just keep doing this
time to change internet provider
yeah it's not like that takes two years
in uk
but yeah sure i'll just switch i'll just
switch i'll call him right now hey
give me the internet cool that'll be two
years no problem
but we'll pretend that it will take one
week
legit it took me two years i'm not even
joking to get this one installed
i think i think it was my dropbox it
should work fine [ __ ] dropbox
likes to be in the background a little
simp in the background
we hit 106 mil
you know what time it is
if you wanna be free you gotta listen to
me
i hit subs 106
in your fantasy
i'm gonna do it
do you think oh yeah
oh yeah if i did this on twitch
i'd be banned right away youtube
this is okay
what am i doing don't ask i'm hitting my
peepee
i'm beating my peepee you got problem
with this see
huh you got the problem with me beating
my pippy
oh cause i'm a guy oh
oh i'm not allowed to do it because i'm
a dude
oh is it because i have a pp i'm not
allowed to do it
oh so that's why
oh oh i see
ken can you call me i'm waiting for ken
by the way in case anyone's wondering
we'll play a game well i'll play ghosted
tsushima in a bit
but i will play with king
scat man's world i want to play that
song it's been a while
sashimi
i don't prefer i'm more of a i'm more of
a scat man john
kind of guy
can you guys hear this wait wait wait
wait i realized my microphone is
decent [ __ ] there's one that was all
out of
that was all out of rhythm wasn't it
yeah [ __ ] let me
beep okay sorry let's do that again
i need to stop i'm sorry is anyone
watching oh okay
cool i'm a few uh
hours away from asking my girlfriend to
marry me
oh my god good luck bro if she says no
that just means you're not a sim so it's
all good tense
what the [ __ ] does that mean
that cured i think i think i'm cured i
felt so [ __ ] a second ago
i just had to play the tambourine all
the endorphins
and peepee beating yeah
came back to me melatonin bit like bruh
feel good now
remember that kids you ever feel bad
just put on scat man
you'll feel all better
[Music]
sweet you got snooze withdrawal just
play the tambourine man
you feel dead inside just play skatman's
world
the [ __ ] is this guy doing hello
should i just play ghost with sushi man
ken is not coming
i'm a skip man who's a scared man
oh well well well where where where
where
what kawaii is is
yeah i played scat man now i feel good
man thank you for asking though
okay jesus what's happening
oh wait i started steam what the [ __ ]
did you try this pogo stuck game out
yeah i'm i'm uh launching it
me too i'm just looking this guy with a
stick looking at me yelling
is ken too high am i too high
are you too high
people say hey lower ken's voice he
sounds like a
alcoholic uncle
[Laughter]
no they're being nice i'm kidding why
does every game we ever play is like the
loudest thing in the world when you turn
around
because [ __ ] game developers
are like hey
i made this song i'm gonna play it on
maximum when they start the game
yeah [ __ ]
ken has a chocolatey voice today
chocolaty
i just woke up voice i'm like
that old man flame yeah that phlegm that
sits there in the back of your throat
i got it then when you're 70 it's gonna
be like
a fine whiskey that's just been sitting
there oh god
and it's gonna have to be removed with
the chopsticks
oh like a straw like suck it out or a
straw yeah
okay i don't know if i can talk have you
been watching that uh
that school anime prison school yeah
how do you know did i tell you about it
yeah of course you told me about okay
okay i've been telling everybody about
it because i love it it's so funny
it's good yeah and it's also got those
moments of
you're like probably if you're watching
with mars you gotta look at it'd be like
uh
no marsha is into does it do it
yeah it's just a big fetish anime but
it's still good
happy saturday papa pizza and uncle ken
well well well
it's good right how many episodes did
you see
i've watched all of it i forgot i
watched it [ __ ] until like i actually
saw on
mars his um instagram he had like a
picture of the guy with the ears like
the big dude
oh yeah legend yeah
legend
yeah the part where uh for those of you
don't know
it's an and it's actually well animated
but i didn't want to watch it because
i just heard it was edgy which is like
the japanese term for a little perverted
but not
no no yeah no actual nudity but i think
prison
school really like pushes it as far as
it can go with it
uh but it's actually very [ __ ] funny
it makes me laugh
a lot out loud
especially the part where
um in the first
in the first episode where the the
the girls torture the guys and make them
like spit on their face
and and uh
makes the the girl makes him lick his
boot and then the guy interrupts him be
like you don't have to sing
come on don't do this this is too far
and then they get pissed off for
stopping her
i wanted her what is wrong with you
[Laughter]
so good okay
um maybe we should wait maybe we should
connect before i show the gameplay this
time so i don't
reveal my [ __ ]
yeah okay
again yeah or
have to apologize for people spamming
you yeah
we're not friends
okay it's making a noise in your ear
when i meet myself
no okay good
good good
yay
that's it yeah i'm almost finished with
the
stein nogueto
it's all right it's pretty good
doo doo doo
you're almost done with it yeah i'm
episode 21 i think
oh yeah you're real close they made a
they made another series it's like
alternate timeline but it's not as good
so i wouldn't recommend wasting your
time i probably won't do it then
yeah i'm watching i'm gonna watch
magical mystery girls or whatever the
[ __ ] you recommended me
oh yeah like it's i get why you like
watch the couple then you're like what
the [ __ ]
but uh i just watched one episode oh
yeah it gets better as it goes
now not that it's gonna blow your socks
i'm not trying to over hype it or
anything but it'll just be better than
the first episode
okay
what does chat think have you seen it
what was it called game
um magical game magical mystery game
madoka magical girls or whatever
it's got a got a long name
look at these weaves i just i i i
invited you are you in it
uh oh i guess full screen again to see
if you invited me let me see
yeah it says invite sent now you're
always off alone how about now this
show up now that messed this from me i'm
trying to see here
there we go can move this
play game okay did that work
yeah wait it says one two out of four
just
oh wait i can't start okay okay cool uh
all right i guess i can show you guys
oh wait can i just change my settings
really quick yeah yeah yeah do whatever
you gotta do i don't know what the heck
is going on
what the hell we can change our dudes we
got we gotta make a gas look the
[ __ ] is happening oh god this is someone
alright i wanna change the size uh
even hear the game and i clicked into it
there we go we can customize our dudes
oh my god change the [ __ ] thing
you try to change i got it one second
this is very annoying what up girl
i crashed cool nice game
all right you want to change the
resolution i changed the whole
doesn't quit you had just the magic
which had the whole game nice me
what the [ __ ]
okay attempt number two i just wanted to
put it in window mode
it's too much to handle i guess yeah
actually that's a good
call see display borderless
anger what are you looking for
what do you get maker how do you make
our guys look good um
wardrobe wait what
you make your guy look good i try and
get the game to play
thank you yeah you do the work i'm just
gonna play around with stuff over here
okay all right
did you do it yep
okay so map one rage with your friends
yeah that sounds fun
very nice then i have to invite you
that's right maybe i picked the wrong
option then
loot with your friends or skate with
your friends
co-op run yeah i host and i
invite okay i invited you all right
uh we're almost there stream patience is
key
it's the one you just said what time is
it yeah okay
okay i think i'm in sweet uh
all right nice it's working
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
hey hey look we're we're as bald as you
are in real life
me i'm a ball
i got some music playing out of me okay
so what the [ __ ] is this game i only see
streamers play it and i don't understand
i don't know this sucks this sucks bro
you can standing how do you do it i hit
it with my pogo stick like i bounced
into the wall and bounced off of it
well i did it too yeah but i think it's
the uh the ones that aren't
diamond or whatever like the ones that
we're on whoa
sweet like a square okay that makes
sense
how am i so good
[ __ ] i'm so bad alright here we go
no stop adding me i'm
french we're not friends [ __ ] up oh my
god here they go why can't they just
but then i learned their lesson already
there's a meme now
i can't get up the first place
there we go oh god there oh okay i can
do super jump i didn't know that no one
told me
go up go up yes
there it is all right got it i guess i'm
all alone i'll just
hang out up here by myself how can i be
good like you
years of practice i've been on pogo
sticks ever since i was born i came out
the womb with a pogo stick
that's disgusting bro stop god
why does he never stop walking it's so
annoying
he's in a pogo stick he can't you can't
stop [ __ ] you're right that actually
makes a lot of sense
okay
i'm a slow learner that's all i oh i got
it
are you playing with the mouse and
keyboard yes oh
i can't play the controller oh well that
explains it doesn't it
gotta use your tools man but she got a
controller landing right right there
beside you come on you got this
shut the [ __ ] up you piece of [ __ ] we're
not friends ken
yes i did
[ __ ] off with your cowboy [ __ ] you bald
son of a [ __ ] yeah my money
my money ow oh you're dead
i'll kill it oh wait we can't i can't
hurt i don't think
okay we kill it we can you just gotta do
the special jump
that right there is normal i don't know
how we get out of here
oh i killed it no
yay did we do it did we do it what
happened
we did it yay whoa i got a laser
i'm just having some deja vu for some
reason maybe whoa maybe you've shown
this game to you before
whoa yeah yeah they hit the other button
to shoot
a little gold dot by your heads how many
shots you got
did you show this game to me years ago
no i did not i have not played this
before
chat have i played this before i feel
like you showed it to me at some point
now
i'm having some weird deja vu uh
who have you been cheating with me on
huh
murphy player you play with multiplayer
you play with multiplayer but yeah
everyone's saying no
no i haven't talked to mark in years
i'll get in here what is this lois it's
a teleporter
you have to break it like this with your
soul
okay it's got to recharge okay here we
go
what the [ __ ] i died what how
can you hear my gap no but you're just
going
you're looking forward to get you like
baby baby mario yoshi's island you're a
bubble come back
nah i'm good come back
good okay just get me here
reload your pogo stick oh there you are
yeah yeah just get up here bruh
yeah bruh all right and then yeah yeah
and get here
and then i'm trying to save you that
here
get up here yeah get up here
oh yeah we did it you did it i guess you
forgot to use heavenly strike or
something like that that's probably
addition
yeah i have no honor my diamond
you can have it thanks bree
i don't even want it
these [ __ ] slidy ass [ __ ] you know
what i'm saying
you know all about yeah i know what
you're saying bro i know what you're
saying
bro whoa ah
[ __ ]
[Music]
i see what you meant with your character
speaking before
so if you jump and use the shoot button
you'll make it up there a lot easier
oh for [ __ ] sake why you know tell me
huh yeah i did tell you
i tell you this come on
yes
oh he's dead this is so sad i'm a bubble
boy
i'm a bubble bar living in the west side
yeah you're safe my friend bro you're
safe come here
come here [ __ ] say come here
i save you
yeah right so we're like jay all right i
guess
we're done oh we're going in level
level two how many levels we played uh
not enough
yeah my diamond no no
having this strike
you have oh my
god why did you make it in ghost of
tsushima i'm on act two now
how about you i beat it the other day oh
[ __ ] nerd
yeah i played it more than you though
it's all good
how much you stream jesus christ
i thought i was playing at a line i
don't know like five hours a day i guess
oh damn yeah that'll do it
games man yeah i get it i got no light
while i do have a life
it's hard to do youtube have a family
and do all that stuff and play video
games
he some somehow he managed to do it how
does he do it
he has a wife he has kids and he plays
video games
and dentist hates him how does he do it
literally has no time to lay around and
do nothing
[ __ ] how do you get there
is there like how do you do the big jump
we've been doing yeah
just right a lot of people don't know
how to do it
do you a lot of people just don't know
[Music]
we gotta break these we gotta break
these my dude
these don't this don't break bro nah
they break
yep jump off the wall here we go you
just gotta it's gotta
you do wanna i oh yeah oh yeah i got it
i got it i got i got it
a lot uh all right so all right
all right [ __ ] off it's so annoying
stop jumping for one second please oh
you do a flip okay
wait what yeah you flip you get the big
jump
what you jump into a flip in the air
and then you land and you get the big
jump
no that doesn't work and now i died
that's exactly what i'm doing saved my
life
saving my life
you just gotta land there on the side my
dude
oh i was so close i was so close
all right all right little guy i keep
jumping in the hole
you do it
[Music]
[ __ ] damn it
all right all right [ __ ] piece of
[ __ ]
no right from the side over here
don't you tactical advantage on me
you need me my name oh your mama is a
pogo pole how could you
yeah i said oh okay listen
you're scared of me say it yes i
scared her no i was up and then i [ __ ]
up
there it is touch the wall
try not to touch wall have you tried it
[ __ ] dude
this is getting painful yeah it's like
jesus just
there it is there it is
there it is here it is
my fingertips are sweating ken i don't
know
if that's supposed to ah [ __ ] it
all right so you jump here you jump
there and you jump here
you jump here you do this and you jump
uh [ __ ] yeah there is okay i got oh [ __ ]
oh my god there it is there it is i did
it
i did it did you do it yeah just kill
yourself
okay just kill yourself
you think there's a spike right here
[Music]
come to me my child
i did it look mom
shut up shut up chat shut the [ __ ] up
look what happens here they are like
they think they're so
smart they're like oh look what this you
do
all right we're alive we didn't shoot
that [ __ ]
can we kill that bug i bet you we did it
like oh never if there was an
average and who did it faster i bet you
we did it quicker than anyone's ever
done hell yeah yeah duh yeah the best
obviously
okay i can't i can't get out of this
place
oh you can shoot twice the controller is
a mistake you can shoot twice now
nah i think you got to power up that's
not only she once
what the heck's the point of this
there's nothing here
oh maybe go this way
it's really hard
i can't don't think i can
do that
i can't even get up to the bit where you
make the hard jump
oh nice okay
okay ken got it oh okay
now
[Applause]
i'll feel all the way down all the way
okay okay i got it i got it i got it
okay
it's okay we're on level i don't know
all right we did it
we did it feels good man what punishment
heck yeah
easy peasy feels good man feels good to
be a pro gamer
yeah i know i mean
some people not pro gamer cringe
so cringy i'm pogo gamer you know what
i'm saying
that's why i tell chat all the time it's
like look i'm a pro gamer i'm literally
getting paid to be bad this game
yeah what do you do heavenly mr heavenly
strike
you just have any strike you have to use
it felix oh i'm sorry did i make it far
in the game without it okay cool
i used that move like three times the
whole time i played the game
like your resolve is a little more
important than just like getting one
unblockable hit that doesn't kill
anybody
autumn are we supposed to break those
uh just the ones that don't make x's you
know what i mean i don't know what to do
with the teleporter thing
that you're talking about yeah there's
nothing down here
here we go easy
can you imagine some streamers like cr
uh rage over this game cringe
[Laughter]
unbelievable um oh they're asking we
gotta go have we get up there
oh that's easy you do one of these oh
there's nothing up there is there oh
that's easy my dude you do one of these
oh i'm sorry i gotta just kill like
did you get up there oh i killed one of
them did i get up there i'm sorry am i
up there
is that the question thank you lembos no
yeah yeah
[Music]
don't you just love it
[Laughter]
people play this game for more than 30
minutes
whoa invincible oh is that what it is
i got a key can we let other people join
in maybe
does anyone else have this game no it
only see four people never mind i don't
want to play with two other guys
that are bald yeah that's weird
i got a keyboard oh my god it's so
annoying like in
at least happy wheel if your head makes
it up you can like pull yourself
over i'm saying it now
happy wheels have better controls in
this game i
said it and i don't give a [ __ ]
oh we got some air here sweet
i like that sound effect keep doing it
feels wonderful in your ears i found the
lock
it's on the line oh i got the key it's a
downer
down yeah over here i'll save your life
don't worry
nice okay you got it how do you put it
how do you insert this
i don't know how to use this key
help
me above it oh no could that be it no
because there's a thing there
is there what about that purple thing
you break the squares above it
damn it
oh you have to jump from here
yes
ah why did i click god damn it well
there's nowhere to go up here
seriously yeah uh it's evening
i feel like these teleporters do
something all right
oh i'm getting good i'm getting good ken
i'm getting control of the controls
i'm get i understand the matrix
wow amazing i understand the pogo stick
oh i got something a dna thing what does
that do oh
yeah it took me to the teleporter i
dropped the key no i died never mind
what
what happened i died
i got the dna thing and i jumped into
the teleporter here and it killed me
maybe these are bad blocks
you got the key now try it if you can do
it maybe i'm the alpha and you're the
beta
and i okay i can't do it
should we play rocket league instead
this is lame yeah
okay so still get my refund on this game
yeah [ __ ] this hey developer if you made
this game
i'm just making it i'm just going to say
we were mildly amused
for 20 minutes you did it
i'm just it's kind of like a youtube
party game i guess yeah i'm sure
a bunch of people and everybody scream
at each other yeah yeah it was our fault
honestly i feel bad
for not having fun
whoops oopsie let's see
another any other good game oh we didn't
make a cobblestone generator that's why
what do you mean other good game we're
playing rocket league
let me ask it's a great game i still
haven't played since last time
that we played it off stream all right
uh it's going free to play now
it's pretty cool that was a weird sense
structure i did there with
that i don't know what you said yeah
it's going they're doing free to play on
rocket league
oh yeah so finally some noobs
yeah right crush yeah i don't know if
they've done it yet
uh paul marsh we gotta make a
cobblestone generator oh we'll do that
in rocket league
huge ass yeah thank you we'll milk it
for three maybe four episodes
it'll be the best thing ever
generator and nothing else that's it
go block
oh man
yeah they need it i'm sure someone
modded you can mod make modern maps on
rocket league
someone's bound to have made a
are you there cobblestone generator
you're not there anymore what the [ __ ]
happened
i guess i'm all alone
that's weird did my headphones change or
something
yeah they did so it's my problem
testimute it now i hear you can you say
something
weird hello can stream hear me
yeah but you can't hear ken
weird it's probably a discourse setting
that up
[ __ ] ass [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
lasagna testified it
nothing's working i think discord just
needed
needed restarted
you can hear me right
stream streamer dudes who's watching
there's nothing better to do on a
saturday are you
everything's frozen up what the [ __ ] is
happening
uh okay play some speedrunners
god am i laggy or what what is happening
strange and no
beast master 64 more like beast fail
epically
see you on the phone
strange
am i choppy i'm choppy as hell aren't i
the [ __ ] happening
you hear me hello
give me a sec
what it doesn't let me change
the [ __ ]
what is happening oh there we go
testing no
i don't get it why is the simplest thing
so [ __ ] complicated
test the way all right yeah that works
and then i'll put testing
testing it's literally because i plugged
in my
this that's all that [ __ ] everything
up it's like oh you want to change
every sound settings now oh i see it's
my computer's fault but
i don't get it i really don't understand
why i have like 50 audio output
oh it's happening this is the test of
stoicism i'm about to lose it
i'm [ __ ] so pissed off
nothing works [ __ ] fantastic
is it the new windows update like what's
happening
i can't even hit the [ __ ] start
button without it lagging
is it working
all right you guys are still here that's
good
[Music]
fixed awake can't deal with minor
inconvenience it's just i
don't know this movement things should
be easy and it's become so [ __ ]
complicated and i don't understand the
reason why
bill gates needs to come in here and
apologize that's all i ask
i don't think it's that much but that
would at least make me feel like
okay i guess it's okay
i'm gonna play whitney houston for a
second
okay i can hear it
nope
i'm gonna play whitney houston again
okay it's working
all right i don't see a single reason
why it shouldn't work
now
all right works great hello oh you
what did you figure it out i don't know
what's going on
i was messing hey just restart your
computer man
every time
whatever just read your chat everyone's
like oh my god
there's so many i don't know he's gonna
tell us not to uh we're not renting
again
oh my god i can't hear ken is it because
we're not a call oh my god play ghost of
sashima
all right play with jack yeah call you
all right
yeah tell them actually no i hate you
i'm lagging again it's the [ __ ] it's
the
rocket league doing it i'm lagging my
computer
i think so because as soon as i start it
oh man that's nuts what are your uh let
me think
it's probably my obs settings let's go
say
f6 like what are your you have them set
to like
really half or like the
uh what do you call them the presets how
about you think
before you open your [ __ ] mouth how
about that
no i just think what i thought i'm sorry
what is it uh which obs
do you use just regular obs or the
streamlabs obs
obvious studio okay
okay look at my options down i got a
different one see as soon as i quit it
works fine
yeah but i've streamed i've streamed
rocket league many times on this
computer yeah well
it's because like the newer versions
come in quality preset
do you know what i'm talking about yeah
is do you have it set to like higher
than
just normal you can also just control
delete and you know look at your
processor and see if it's like
a gpu or anything's being overloaded
[Music]
and then you can figure out the problem
from there i'm sorry for yelling before
i feel bad now go menacing
song but at me i don't give a [ __ ] okay
i'm used to it he's always like this
channel
uh what is in my output settings
um should be like under output and
streaming and then uh
i i use a different obs so i can't tell
exactly where it is but
it should be under like a preset like
quality or uh
fast very fast
slow it depends on what the process it's
some quality right now
some quality did you control delete to
see if anything was like having trouble
look at your uh whatever the [ __ ] it's
called
you look task manager and uh your
processors
and performance and like crap
not responding not responding
your task manager's not responding do
you have a windows update because i had
one before we started
yeah you do have a windows update
it's using fifty percent of my cpu
sixteen percent memory
what about your gpu
50 50. did you say you have a windows
update
yeah well that's actually
honestly probably what it is
[ __ ]
i don't know why but windows updates are
like dick your whole computer
up when you try to stream [ __ ]
those god damn
let me try one thing okay um
i think it it could just be what my
encoder is
yeah as well as the next question let's
go ask you use your gpu or your
cpu to encode all right i'm gonna stop
the stream one second don't go anywhere
crazy my stream's still on okay what are
you implying i say crazy [ __ ] cause i
you know i don't you know i never say
anything
i was playing the [ __ ]
i use um the nv enc encoder
me too you use it as well
i think that was the issue yeah i mean
if you turn your stream off you might as
well just windows update uh
it's probably
so much yes like how many tabs you got
open
[Laughter]
don't ask those questions okay
all right youtubers we have at least 50
tabs open with potential videos in the
future that we're going to do
all right all right it seems to be
working fine now i think i just needed
to restart obs
uh if you like left it open and not
close it in a while no
it just stopped working for some reason
i don't know why
yes one thing all right well good
nothing nothing made you wrong then
i guess not boom
boom baby
yeah all your little people that left
your stream came over here to see what's
going on oh yeah
yeah i lost half my [ __ ] audience
come back [ __ ]
come back friends come on friends
we have we're celebrating your birthday
over here
yeah it's your birthday
i admitted you oh okay
you know how it is thing got those
alerts turned on see where you hit
damn you invite me so many times okay
let me click on it jesus
nice hat [ __ ] i'm back at gold
now
[ __ ] cringe look at look at you over
here like
trying to look good with your car i'm
trying you mean i
did you mean i do look [ __ ] good is
that what you're trying to say
i spent 50 quiddie okay and i look
goddamn goody
it was worth every penny oh my god what
button doesn't what i don't remember now
buttons boost b all right can you cover
the first goal
just making sure i got my settings
these are flying all over the place man
i'm scared just make sure they don't
score
okay good all right i'm back
yeah well make sure they don't score
oh god that's the wrong way what are you
doing
i try to interrupt it nice shot
nice shot you did it go again nice i got
it
all right go in the middle go for it ah
[ __ ]
come on kane
don't think so [ __ ] get a kid
don't think some [ __ ]
i'm kind of lagging not gonna lie like
yeah it's kind of wonky
i don't have any boost i can pretend
jump nice
oh my god
let me change my setting
what's laggy everything everything
your stream looks smooth though
okay come on [ __ ] you call yourself a
rocket league
gamer no yeah
me
[Laughter]
you said you got to me why is it heading
to our goal
they they're the ones that hit it they
knock me out of the way i'm sorry
[ __ ] off man i don't have any boost i'm
just pretending i know what i'm doing
don't think so [ __ ] nice nice
ah yes
oh god i'm getting bruce i [ __ ] this
i'm done damn it too soon
what'd you do is anyone hitting night
oh god
[ __ ] you
they're stealing all my boots ah crap i
did a backflip looking like a dumbass
oh god go in
it's in it's in it's in no
god damn come on cam
come on okay oops
oh god
uh all right
go for it play it up all the way
[ __ ] they hit it
nice
blew me up dick
come on we got a score [ __ ] i'm in such
an awkward position here
go for it hit it one more time sideways
okay never mind he was there he blew me
up
go for it nice
nice
we gotta score all right i'm gonna try
yeah you get it
i'm in bad position yeah
nice uh oh okay
see yeah i'm lagging dude that's super
weird
there's a delay in my controls [ __ ]
it's so weird god if this guy would stop
blowing me up
non-stop that'd be great
i tried
oh no oh
one minute come on we could scar yeah
boost
nice pass
great pass come on kane
get the boost all right go
for it you got it thought i could
damn it damn i don't know why i'm it's
like
performance i'll go everything perform
i'm blaming lag oh god it looks ugly now
[ __ ] the game looks bad
[Applause]
we'll do this go for it
oh my god no oops
almost shot it in i was like oh god
it looks like a different game right now
all right here we go
the guy blew me up for like the eighth
time this game jesus are you [ __ ]
serious
thank you it worked out
[Laughter]
doesn't count doesn't count
i lag
and i'm a noob yeah that's right
god damn it looks ugly i guess all the
quality
i can't stand how ugly it looks
turn up render quality it's so weird
like i can stream this game on my
[ __ ] laptop and it doesn't lag so it
shouldn't like
streaming it from here sounds weird
cause peter played on now is a monster
well it's a lot better than a laptop at
least
yeah exactly it doesn't really make
sense
let's try this
look at that ping look at that eight
ping you have
ain't bad man we're not friends you're
blocked
julian black you blot
blood you're all blocked simps
go watch pokeman [ __ ]
all right come on ken come on
let's practice i passed the ball
i passed the ball trying to get people
talking them in to give me their twitch
prom
free money uh yeah get my pre twitch
prime over here uh alright youtube
you can't have it it's mine you get
access to um
[Laughter]
ad free viewing right uh you get access
to
uh the friendship club where we're all
friends
uh super special friendship club over
here wow oh god
oh nailed it i nearly can i hit that
right on as i wanted it
oh my god ken what the [ __ ] was that are
you staring at the ball or are you going
to hit the ball
look at this guy he was right actually
can i
change my name uh uh big dick club
that's where we are everyone here a huge
dick
it's a big pp club you can't use a big
dude sorry big people
hey what you want you wanna you
you wanna add free content or you want a
huge penis you all tell me
what you prefer these guys are pretty
try harder
but can you defend the goal then
i don't know have you tried that where
are you where are you then
all right all right we gotta take turn
who takes the goal
okay i'll sit back here no no you i need
you to get the goal
hit the lap all right get that ball yeah
and i'll get the bounce now you back up
a little bit
all right now you you get this ball
should have been there man you should
have been there man
oh look at that one
all right go for that that's a need to
go
nice good job
what if i don't miss that that was like
the slowest lob ever
you got it i'm proud of you well done
yay all right you go for it
okay go for it again i hang back
oh oh it's tempting to get those go for
it
go for it
i'm gonna try and play it up never mind
any boost i just realized
there comes oh god it bounced
the [ __ ] was that
what a bounce back up dude
i need you here i'm here
go for that nice okay try and play it up
in the middle
just hit it one more time never mind
oh [ __ ]
i got this oh he didn't hit it he faked
me out
that was good nice say dude well done
all right go for it go for it
nice one more time one more time go for
it go go go go
[ __ ] i didn't hit it right
uh okay this is epic no boost
oh [ __ ] so lucky come on
come on
what's up old glen dog
you got it yeah
all right we got the way here
don't think so [ __ ]
play it up [ __ ]
uh yeah i definitely
go for it i'll go further
i've got a [ __ ] bounce [ __ ]
go go go go nice
are you gonna hit that oh he is no
no go for it
good aim i hit with my tires you know
bruh i tried
calculated calculated
calculated oh epic games wants to
install itself thank you epic games
what the [ __ ] yo dude
hey by the way i see you playing other
games you want to you want to play
fortnite bro sorry i hit that
i don't mean intrude bro but yeah but
like have you thought about it right now
calculated
pick up the wall can we score a goal can
can we do that
no nice
thank you
that's what you get [ __ ]
come on man
pass it to me where you at
[Laughter]
oh he's got a youtube channel this is so
embarrassing
that's so cute oh come on let's go again
how the [ __ ] are we getting the same
points
i don't know we um i feel like
positioning i'm learning i just still
gotta be able to hit it
hey you're blocked hey and your penis is
the smallest one i've ever seen
yeah urinal cake the [ __ ] is wrong with
you
been watching since i was 12 i am now
20. i mean 19.
thanks for all the good times
it's complicated it's complicated it's
complicated bruh
what are they doing go for it going to
make some noise
nice nice maybe not the nicest
i don't know what the best way to hit
things i don't know if you like jump and
like
hit it there you go either one of us
would have got that that was easy hell
yeah
hell yeah do you like jumping like boost
flip into it to hit it harder or i don't
know
jump lean back boost
bean bag booze okay
like that see how i did that perfectly
nice shot you saved my ass go for it
again go for it again play it in the
middle
nice
i'm going for it [ __ ] i should not have
but i wanted
nice nice
they're not going for i go first
ah i was so close
oh no whoops oops oops
is your birthday today mom
yeah no months of september yeah chad
said it's your birthday
no they just can't believe we're playing
games together it must have been your
birthday or something
it's my birthday oh my god that's all i
wanted for my birthday to play games
pewdiepie
i get to do what all these little fan
boys and girls will never get to do
it must be my birthday
no it's just a saturday for me guys
oh nice i'm playing one more time come
on [ __ ] yeah i came to suit i'm sorry i
thought he would hit it
[ __ ]
it's funny that you tried
i appreciate the effort oh i bounced off
the wall there
god damn
get it
that was a [ __ ] slow-mo lock on
target that [ __ ] is going in i don't
give a [ __ ]
there are some ain't no beats that no
nothing
what
what you just know are you going for
that
nice call cool i can hear your little
stink and the answer is
35 months never oh i'm one of my buddies
that plays this game a lot in the chat
and he's making fun of me he's like
you're [ __ ]
shut up good good
good
you down what did you get it i didn't
have time to go around i had to go there
and i hope he hit the corner but he'd
[ __ ] it perfectly he went right over you
what do you mean
oh you're complaining you're actually
complaining at me mr
zero all right i'm sorry okay
no no it's all right play see how you
get that ball
good shot
[ __ ] for everything i do is
going to be hardly judged
you [ __ ] go for the ball ken hit the
ball
i got it thank you
this [ __ ] is on the ball every
time i hate him
it's not my birthday it may might as
well be giving me all the subs please my
birthday
that's when you hit the reverse button
[ __ ] it then
shut up you haven't realized i left like
five minutes ago
i'm still doing it i don't care
i'm going to do it he's doing it big
this guy he's probably better than me
anyway
why are you leaving me like this why why
you rage quit because um
listen up i know it's your birthday i
know it's all good
but i think if i don't play ghost with
sushi my least
everyone's going to start crying very
soon
over that game i guess so
doubt it look what you did chad
i was having a good birthday
[Laughter]
and then you guys start bitching and
whining nonstop like you always do
look what you did now can't nobody have
anything nice because of twitch chat
that's our
youtube channel excuse me same thing at
this point
should i call it rocket league stream
still you call what
uh rocket league stream sale hey might
as well
i don't i don't think you're chatting
there's a difference
don't come here and diss my audience
i'll have you know their iq are
extremely high
yeah i'll have you know i bet you in an
iq test
they would get over 80.
i'm 88. yeah
yeah i bet you feel bad now
[Laughter]
oh i still gotta refund that game uh it
wasn't
pogo's stuck yeah
it's a good game i like that so i got to
chapter two with the ghost of shishima
yeah i gotta continue did you get the uh
did you get that armory you get in the
second
no i didn't search the g well there's
one mission
like one of those blue missions you get
from the storytellers you get some armor
yeah pretty good armor you gotta you
gotta do a bunch of 1v1 combats
but it's pretty epic oh that's my fourth
play but the armor is good
do you remember what it was called uh
the giga
say that again ghost uh
armor what's it called
how do you fight do you use like a bunch
of the ghost weapons oh it's the
gosaku's armor
i used uh the
armor
oh you like the bow mm-hmm oh yeah i
went for the bow armor right away
nice get that extra slow motion yeah
yeah
um all right well enjoy it
i'm gonna go play something else i guess
have a great birthday man and again
happy birthday dude
i hope you enjoyed playing with
pewdiepie
this make a wish foundation made this
happen thank you
all right i'll talk to you later i'll
see but
all right i'm gonna get a quick snack
i'm starving dude
and then we'll play yeah
foreign
you
all right let's read donations yeah
this is your wonderful authentic and
hilarious you can't get me through my
darkest time
and now that i'm 100 better and employed
i can finally get back stay amazing
amelia thank you so much
thank you tony apparently i missed your
old message
but you're full of cash what a simp
dick though i'll say that much
oh man what is flavor is this peanut
butter pretty good
i'm getting stronger pushed a new record
today
even though i felt like [ __ ] had a
headache i was like whoa
feels good man
youtube here are two pewds thank you for
everything you do really helpful
i'm happy to be here man
i'm still fairly weak
but it feels good when you hit a new
weight
floor game man 20 muscle increase
how many push-ups can you get
i don't know probably a hundred
something like that
should we do a challenge or if i buy and
go satoshima i have to do push-ups
so i start at 10 then i have to do 20
and so on here i go for the big d
shout out just trying to return the
favor everything you've done thank you
so much tony
69.99 rainbow
color
i can probably not do a hundred no way i
can do a hundred
what the [ __ ] am i saying that's so many
i'll probably do sixty yeah i can do 60
million
did you say hi to my bro benship hero
i run dude we'll do 69 then
prove it
well it's easier to just say that i can
do it
let me prove it
thanks for making my mom laugh a ton
from
from tlc that's great man been playing
tsushima along with you have been loving
it
what can i say before gang hell yeah
all right help me set the rules then
damien already moved to japan
yeah time zone will be a lot better i
look forward to that
why do i eat like a cat shut the [ __ ] up
it's covered protection
so i don't have to touch it it's called
smart
one death there's 10 push-ups that's
easy
okay
bring it around
20 we'll start with 10 and if it's too
easy i'll do
20.
okay
just sun is still moving on to some
ebola gotta get those mental gains as
well
uh excuse me ebola was a fascist so
therefore
cringe bro
i'm charging it it's connected to this
thing
that's so annoying
i haven't read it yet but he feels like
the author if i recommend everyone's
gonna go
oh my god alt-right pewdiepie confirm
alright is this working
i'm drinking jack's coffee top of the
morning
couldn't be bothered to make a g fuel
do you like this by the way i'm playing
in like high contrast mode it looks nice
all right let's go and do the quest
final sim super chat me just a quick
question if you
got an update about the upgrade uh i
have no idea i need to talk to youtube
i'm sorry man
it's annoying what a guy
okay
foreign
you can never have too much contrast
shut up
again they took your nails
[Music]
i'm playing on this mode
unusual
the [ __ ] is our quest now
right
oh
so this is the new area it looks really
cool
i love it come on here again
[Music]
100 just kill people from a distance
i'm like nah man i don't wanna go close
i kill him from distance thank you
this feels good technique
what the should there be a big red there
huh
that's kind of cool
up
oh we got him over here minor range
charm
that might be good
what should we do let's just go there
let's see what we can find man
act 2 yeah oops i meant to do that
screenshot time i've already taken a
bunch
[Music]
i took a bunch of cool ones actually
let me show you
got this one pretty cool
i really like this one sorry no this one
pretty cool
[Music]
this one's pretty cool too
pretty nice
[Music]
i just can't stop taking screenshots
i'm addicted to taking screenshots
yeah i got that farmstead
damn so much [ __ ] on the map
see i don't care about taking photos but
uh
taking photos and goes through hell yeah
that's cool photos in real life
no thank you what the [ __ ] breaks dude
but i have to take photo now oh because
tsushima
yes yes yes yes yes yes
logan paul be like i have to take photo
of this
good joke this will never not be funny
[Music]
let's see if i can remember how to play
with a different controller now
some buttons don't work on it
i think i can't use that
hello
oh he's got a shotgun
it's not fair my controller doesn't work
all right [ __ ] it
why did i do this
i can't use the controller properly it
doesn't count
it doesn't count
you see me if i do it yeah you see in
the mirror
there's no space
i realized i was just supposed to do 10
but i did 20. doesn't matter
so quick
that's the only time that's gonna happen
the only time
god damn controller cut me man
we'll add five each time for the mean
because then i actually don't re i
really do
all right we're okay
whoa he [ __ ] floated
that was cool
i like that
oh why is that bamboo there it's so out
of the
everything that looks so good
keep
you
yeah i felt nothing in my arms that was
a wasted workout
[ __ ] if only i knew how to do better
[Music]
posture
oh my god
it's kind of curious how it looks
can't see it
wasn't too bad straight back
plus you can't even see me
the [ __ ] was the problem
oh what's happening
let's follow up
show me the way cannot stop picking up
flowers
i'm addicted
where am i almost there
what is this no save for later
then i'll do it now thank you
i just gotta sit let's do mythic
is
[Music]
foreign
and say the n word because everyone is
equally shocked
i'm sorry guys i am so sorry
well first of all
okay
is it good now
unbreakable
thank you john
this must have been like a important
quest to do
there's no way they would have put this
right here
a hundred eight hundred meters
kind of want to take a screenshot here
this air is pretty cool
i do want to get a new armor though
the temptations
we got a fox then where
there you are banked
show me
oh cute
oh god i looked away two seconds there
he is
come on banked i need more resolve
there it is nice thank you bang
let's pay our respects for bank
[Music]
can i pet him i've done it before but i
think he went away
there you are let's pet little bang
there you go who's a good boy ah shame
he's like floating
it would have been a cool picture
it's bait
oh he's so cute and now he dies
can't use the bow the button is broken
on my this controller
i wish you could do a meditative pose
instead of the flute where's bank uh
where's jurgen
there you go
just sitting down here could have been a
cool photo
are these bad ones are good ones
they're bad ones
arrow anymore
i see you faking out
mongol eagles what
[Music]
so much cooler without the bars
feels more immersive makes it a little
trickier too
i don't know when they're gonna break
their stance basically
all right we're on our way not a lot of
money but love your videos a lot thank
you
very epic
change your armor if you can't use the
bow that's actually a good point
um i guess roman
this one is clearly the coolest one
i love the look of this game so
apparently
uh the creator is the ones that made
infamous and that was the first game
that really had photo mode
it's cool how that becomes a thing
i don't like taking photos in in real
life but i take them in video games
oh jesus christ
yogurt whoopsie dude
he's dead
i look like tambourine boss from dark
souls
tambourine i meant trombone
satori but he's on
oh what is this
cool wow
yes
are we dueling can we do a lingerling
[Music]
i have the same outfit
oh no i'm gonna die oh it's push-up time
[ __ ] oh what have i done
okay i gotta do it i gotta i gotta do
this first try let's go
[Music]
okay
that's not good oh that's bad
nice
i [ __ ] blocked that that's ridiculous
[ __ ] i died well
i tried all right all right tell me what
i'm doing so god damn wrong then i gotta
squeeze my glutes more i saw someone
said other than that i am pretty
clueless
oh god that does not count come on
is this good am i doing it correct
is that good
am i doing it right now
yeah is this how i do it
one two
i can't do it it's impossible
i tried guys i really try
i'm doing great i'm finally the perfect
form i ever achieved
real i it's annoying because like
everyone is telling me
all i'm doing is wrong but i don't know
what the [ __ ]
to change uh
hello are you reading these are we just
sending money i read it i read it john
what the [ __ ]
were you smoking perfection all right
i'll just do what i did and
squeeze my glutes and people can cringe
all they want
i'll do i'll do 10 because i'm probably
gonna die
was that better felt better
felt more on my back okay
all right i feel like i get to die now
on purpose and it doesn't count because
i started off with low health oh wait
you can't see the gameplay so you don't
know what's happening anyway
cool i definitely didn't die there [ __ ]
[Music]
foreign
no i died [ __ ] i thought i had him
just tighten your traps see i don't even
know what that is
i google traps and it's not muscles
you're not supposed to feel your back
great i made my shoulder blades
keep your shoulders from branding
tighten your core how do you know
it's not tighten
[Music]
straighten up shoulders hide away
straightening them up
i guess everything is [ __ ]
i do crunches instead
straighten your back but it was straight
[Music]
too low
tighten your pee pee shoulders back
not arched i see i don't
understand how to reply that
[Music]
slice my peepee
look forward while doing i'll try that
then
[Music]
at least i can see in the mirror
tighten your bumps
now this is gameplay alright in full
screen [ __ ] too bad
i'm sure i'm gonna die really quickly
again
this guy is really tough
all right
doesn't help my [ __ ] chair is in the
way
all right
yes i did it all wrong got it all right
come on no it doesn't hold up it does
not count
i need a fair start at least
post your from now on you have to post
your physique otherwise
shut the [ __ ] up
don't flare your elbows what does that
mean speak english
i mean i don't speak english oh elbow
closer to your body
all right let's try that
alright here we go
um
it's not going great
i blocked that what the [ __ ]
elbows what's my elbows these right
how do i keep them closer to my body
i keep elbow closer to my body i squeeze
my glutes
i don't arch and i look forward
is that it just a lesson for me to learn
how to do push-ups apparently
i didn't did not change my camera again
[Music]
it's better so apparently i've been
arching my
elbows too much didn't know that was a
big problem
those who are good just keep your back
flat
okay we're learning gamers we're
adapting
it's very hot in here i gotta beat this
boss
i don't think my armor is good enough
can i pause
working why not
that does not count my controller didn't
work come on
see how [ __ ] fast i died
so what's a good gear against this guy
because i actually wanna
doesn't does the hat not actually do
anything
what's up
and then i died because i got hit twice
i had full health too
all right
all right so traps
elbows aren't straight
okay 10 is fine
it's not a problem
this is a bit annoying come on
which is the point
[ __ ]
[ __ ] i die so quick it's unbelievable
we're doing this
[Laughter]
good form okay
okay
come on
oh god that's bad oh god again
okay
nice no
come on we're so close
no i couldn't block that one it was
unblockable
god damn it i thought no we were so
close
oh you couldn't see me because it was me
i was so close [ __ ]
okay
all right you get to see this one
apparently
god that was so close
come on
oh
[Music]
[ __ ] come on
come on
no
we're close
no i didn't block it i didn't block it
close so close
[ __ ] i will do it i will do it if the
last thing i [ __ ] do
come on
oh my god i'm dead terrible around
foreign
plano health
no again i'm so close
honey hello
i don't care my form is good or not i'm
just trying to get it done okay great
[Music]
focus i can do this
can't block that first attack god dammit
block that [ __ ] thing
uh
oh
yes got him not even a problem
no more push-ups
good fight he put up a good fight but
that was easy
that was [ __ ] easy
he may have had it at the first half not
gonna lie but we [ __ ] did it
dips let's go elbow close rain try to
hold your core so you don't let your
stomach drop for a lift evidence is that
this is way too much
information just tell me one simple as
if you're talking to a toddler
if you're gonna instruct me how to do
[ __ ] please
when you do your traps up and then you
know whatever i'm like okay
all right got it all right sorry i'm
sorry i know you guys are trying to help
but so many [ __ ] eletus as well i
can't
you're doing everything wrong don't even
try
[Music]
reflect on uncertainty
i should have bowed
i guess i'll do that
we're doing haiku this looks beautiful
[Music]
100 muscle increase we're playing
goes to sushima i feel like
[Music]
face down no face was supposed to be up
i read comments saying
it's beautiful definitely do a photo
here
can i sit
the problem of having big pippy you
can't do proper push-ups
ninety percent of people correcting you
can't do twenty percent
oh man
let's do a better time
so to use heavenly strike do i have to
hold it down i think i
used it a couple of times but it didn't
really
do you like it
[Music]
too much red yeah
let's do another
it's just that time of day i think
even that looks great
[Music]
all right
i can use bow and arrow here at least
the [ __ ] is happening with it
no more taco hat this is so sad
the moogie prefecture
apparently this is mongol territory what
the [ __ ] oh god i don't want to die
you're gonna run
oh god i'm almost dead get the [ __ ] out
i'm done i'm done i'm out i'm out i
don't want to die i don't want to die
[Music]
no [ __ ] i died god [ __ ] damn it
[ __ ] arrow guy came out of nowhere
and the hostages were killed oh i didn't
die
i don't want to do it anymore
[ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
should my center of gravity be like at
my chest
like yeah that would make sense
like where should i focus my weight
i didn't mean to run in here come on man
all right let's do this chill
love this area very cool
[Music]
where is everyone kill enemies without
healing
i get bonus points if i do that
let's do it
if i get seven of them without healing
okay i can definitely do that
hmm
haha i did it sweet
the hostages are fine look at that
oh yeah i'm wearing the wrong armor for
this
[Music]
this one looks
yeah i feel that
[Music]
all right two more
someone said focus on your bicep now i'm
confused
internet make no sense nothing new here
all right
here's for winning duel and greatly
improved form keep
up dang huang thank you thank you very
much
feels good man new member of floor game
welcome kaleos
epic
where are the hostages he's just sitting
there it's like i'm not leaving
oh here we go
does he see me no
there's a ton of people there as well
are you serious
[Music]
oh my god
at least i didn't die hey phil is
watching your videos for about seven
years just want to simply say thank you
for all the good times and laughs
hell yeah thanks for being here man i
appreciate you
let's never do that what i just did
again
stealth gang
[Music]
you didn't see me but here i am
maze master dick dick
you're dead
who am i missing here could you buy much
love from toronto hell yeah
love toronto cool place i like
why does that not kill them
seriously that was a headshot cut and
clean
but i shot them in the head do i need i
guess i gotta upgrade my
bow now
[ __ ] what a fam all right i guess i
can't do that
[Music]
could it be that i'm not wearing my
armor anymore
[Music]
maybe
here let me just do this so we get sarah
that
nevermind
whoops at least i didn't die
drop and give me a 10 maggot i'm not
doing it
i gotta die
let's be more careful i guess
don't have enough patience to do
stealthing properly i'm sorry
thanks india thank you thanks for
being great background noise as i
deliver all these amazon packages
how's the tambourine delivery business
going
is it thriving as per usual
i think they saw me
maybe not
oh my god
[Music]
yes
oh i did it what a mess
feels good man
it's too what who's left
he doesn't want to be saved apparently
hostage equals 10 crunches
this is how i play games apparently i
[ __ ] up [ __ ] it all up and somehow it
saves it okay
i got arrows what the [ __ ] is he doing
you want me to die what the [ __ ] albin
one guy fell in the water
oh what the hell that guy's calling us
can i save him now
oh now you want my help
have a snickers bro just take a snack
bro
brush your sims we're saving here
unbelievable
all right
you didn't see me but here i am
it's quite a lot of them aren't there
submerged
seriously they didn't see me that's
hilarious
oh [ __ ]
uh 30 minutes maybe yeah is that okay
are you hungry
damn it i didn't realize he was gonna
see the dead body at least i didn't die
[ __ ] doesn't count if the hostage died
oh man i want to fail all right let's go
this way
[Music]
or poor lad
they don't see anything oh no
i don't want to die though kill the
hunter kill the hostage
oh no the hostage died
man do i suck at [ __ ] hostage quests
we simp for charity epic yeah it's
important please
i guess i'll go around everything what
if i just shoot him with a bow
[ __ ] oh i'm out of arrows okay that's
not working
um
shame on you it's so boring sneaking
i hate it i can't i hate it let me just
fight
when stan's kick is this okay
uh
do you
i had no idea he was there that is so
lucky
all right here we go
why does it look like a coat hanger
oh they make noise is that it
some explosives
[Music]
just go for it [ __ ] it
dude
[Music]
no push-ups [ __ ] you
no
a key of
[Music]
damn that looks so pretty the only thing
that looks a bit awkward are the
characters themselves
almost wish this was like first person
hero to chima
damn that looks good
amazing still alive [ __ ]
[Music]
guess i have to upgrade all of them
before i i mean unlock before i upgrade
so we're doing the mythic quest right
yeah
we have a long way to go all the way
there
can we fast track anywhere
nope
hey facebook defenses 2017 appreciate
your content in the work you
put into it happy birthday to ken come
ladies gotta say this game is great i
want to visit japan one day take care
bro
hell yeah i'm so happy for kendall and
his birthday
got a long road ahead of him boy
i kind of want to push him in damn
screenshot time question mark
damn
holy [ __ ] dude
so pretty i'm trying to
i want to get the thunder
we get this camp for fast travel
so low on everything okay i have arrows
someone saw me
oh
[Music]
where's it going
mhm
whoa
[Music]
you [ __ ] shield [ __ ]
[Applause]
guess who didn't expect the leader for
the 500th [ __ ] time
[Music]
they're so strong
did it
no push-ups i studied deeply
[ __ ]
nice that was sweet dude
no more mongols sorry
mongols guess you're not so
epic after all
go here again
that are not defeated
stream went down what happened
why did the stream go down
it's so crazy
[Music]
anyway
taking your sweet time bruh
wrong horse stream crashed stream fresh
[Music]
dude there's so many of them
it's so strong
oh
[ __ ] stun me as well
[ __ ]
my face get all red
come on
good start
[ __ ] damnit
they didn't even die just did it because
i wanted to
[Music]
[ __ ] you
of course
[Music]
okay
tell me my form is wrong shut the [ __ ]
up
i didn't even die
maybe that maybe the punishment is not
hard enough
maybe that's the issue you get
so cut if you don't do this bit right
oh my god that was so the [ __ ] is the
deer doing here
see now i start off with full everything
oh you're definitely dead
fitter
come on [ __ ]
[Music]
[ __ ] did not mean to do that
oh my god
[Music]
a little tricky not gonna lie
remember i alluded this before yes
[Music]
nice
i have nothing but my skill
left i'm out of here [ __ ] this
[Music]
[ __ ] this give me something
arrow nah i'll take it
[Music]
yes
it's all good part of the plan
[Music]
oh i have nice
the [ __ ] is going on with my armor
easy that was too easy i think
screenshot time
the land of the rising sun
quite like all of them
my taco had too good man
we got all the birds in the back there
that's kind of cool
what's your favorite pokemon i'm so glad
you asked
bulbasaur
[ __ ] bulbasaur up in this
[ __ ]
pretty nice screenshot i'll send it
later for
the epicness
this game is so i can with
so much confidence say that this is the
superior game
over the last two months you just get
first i thought like well last of us
looks really good but like
no this game looks so much better i
think last of us has more details
like facial expression and that kind of
stuff is is where last of us wins but
anything else man this game is so much
better
what do you want ain't got time
i ain't got time for this vision
he sings the n word but i can't do that
so i say [ __ ]
i know i'm kind of a hero i'm kind of
like the greatest person alive
are these mongols
hey guys what's up
what's your favorite digimon akuma
always thank you for asking
this is mongol territory nah no problem
guys let's do this ow
stop it i don't have anything i don't
think i'm ready for this
overwhelming
i don't think so
okay maybe this on that note i'll do my
final
push-up actually let's save real quick
final push-up all right tell me
everything wrong with my form
go all out
did i say i think so
is food ready what does it say i can't
read show more
olive oil on one olive oil
where is it where is the olive oil i
don't know
uh check under the laundry i think under
the laundry or where the garbage is
oh i'm getting really tired
ah
am i swallowed yet
i think you did yes it worked
oh
zebra meat
sorry
thanks for watching this live stream
it's been my pleasure
that was 5 000 push-ups in case you join
in the medal
we out here we're simping left and right
20 percent muscle increase
all right thanks for joining us
appreciate it as always
all love good fun horrible
so see you soon
bye bye