good
morning
too early to earn a little stream right
it's too [ __ ] early what the hell am
i doing
oh god good morning
hey look who's three minutes early to
the live stream
what's good [ __ ]
hey socrates thank you for joining floor
game
epic
i saw people mad in yesterday's video
being like
how dare you gatekeep philosophy [ __ ] i
was roasting everyone sub right
just because i made fun of assassin's
creed for having shortcuts in it
[ __ ] how dare you keep my gatekeeping
[ __ ]
anything left no
it's 8 30 for me thank you for asking
i know i'm eating apple it's pretty
cringe
i'm cringing every bite
who eats an apple
how many calories is in an apple
52 cringe
oh i'm cringing so hard
i wish i was eating another fruit
my life was hard like that life is just
tough man
how are you guys doing on this blessed
morning what are your plans for today
so carter's saying you can't be a
philosopher if you have a bad memory hit
me in the fields
really he said that yeah they were such
elitist
all of them plato stalkers they
they're like the most if anyone would be
a gatekeeper be [ __ ] them
pits i give you my permission to use my
band's music
you're right it is a bit quiet here but
i don't feel like it
thank you anyway
apple gang apple game what's up
oh yeah this stream is sponsored by that
i have a sponsored ad read to do today
you guys want to hear i think we'll save
it as a highlight
i won't read it yet thank you rope palm
nick thank you very much
26 000 people watching pewdiepie eating
apple
this is epic
i got 26 000 people no cam and i'm
eating
apple it's whatever
people say they only watch my stream for
my body
yeah well i'm eating an apple what do
you got to say about that one
how is doggy doing
for those who don't know we have a
hedgehog he stinks he smells
even if we clean him he's a smelly boy
i'm working out next to his cage and i
get the whiff of his shits
in inside me while i'm trying to like
breathe heavily i'm not a fan
i'm tired of his [ __ ] literally
fedex how do i get a hold of you to do
some sponsorship dead serious
i have a business email check it out
nice photo match that took of you today
thank you damon
it was funny people got so mad that i
wasn't wearing a mask
when there's no one around what's the
point of a mess
i'm a big i've always i don't know
maybe i haven't always spoken about it
yeah i think i have
and then people got mad at me so i
deleted it but i was like yeah everyone
should wear a mask i literally said this
in like february or march
that's what we need to do and people got
so angry like this is so irresponsible
felix delete this i'm like
all right guess i'm not getting into
this
and then there's one photo of me outdoor
where i'm not wearing a mask
where's his back just [ __ ] up karen's
goddamn
this is the content i sub for i hope you
enjoyed yourself
healthy peers epic thank you miss gear
i'm not healthy this day i ran out of my
breakfast i had to eat myself breakfast
not epic when will i play too very
similar
every day
i also remember people criticizing
the wearing of masks in the in like uh
early like i bought maps the first thing
i did
because i'm like this shit's about to
hit japan because it was happening in
japan
uh when i was there i was in japan when
it was happening
and then uh people started criticizing
masks like mask
isn't going to do anything the
microorganisms
are going to penetrate the mask surface
anyway
so i am an intellectual will not be
wearing
or will not be conforming to this mask
suicidal pressure
now they're like look at me in my mask
hey guys
be responsible
i remember i remember what you said
what do you think of ksi's new music
video i haven't seen it
i'm sorry ksi i haven't seen it
sorry i'm almost done with this apple i
hate when people eat
just wanted to say i've been watching
since your allies in wonderland to the
moon let's play
thank you for your integrity and
entertaining persona keep doing what you
do floor gang sim kang hell yeah thank
you kiki
epic
i want to learn to meditate why should i
start learning
just breathe bruh just close your eyes
and breathe
yes i wanted to tweet this but i don't
tweet anymore but i was like
mask who wears a [ __ ] mask betas just
hold your breath
[ __ ]
sierra oscar bravo said that mask
stopped breathing problem solved 400 iq
look at all these baiters wearing masks
just don't breathe [ __ ]
cringe you breathe in public
what up it's the biggest sim back in the
chat potato ward fighter 666 epic
fine felix you win how much do i have to
donate for you to give me my band a
shout out
nothing i'll look up what it was called
and then i'll shout you out
three hours later there you are
now
shout out to pyrograph
band pyrograph everyone there we go
tier three merch is so [ __ ] close i
don't know why it's taking so long i'm
really sorry
it was done like three weeks ago i'm not
even kidding
hey man just want to say you brought me
up from a lot the low points in my life
i've never been able to appreciate
you because i've been a kid
what but i have a job now so here's
money nice
this is a great business deal for me
like i get all the kids
invested i'm like mcdonald's with a
happy meal
right i trick all the kids in be like
look what a happy place is this and then
you're done you're hooked for life now
you understand i i'm so ingrained in
your childhood
so give me all your money here's what
i'm saying thank you
honest question though because i get so
many people saying like oh
you help me with low points and but like
what did i do
i don't i appreciate it but like what i
do
i didn't do nothing and i'm not saying
that's to be humble it's like
i want to understand
i don't get it i'm not special guys
sorry fire alarm is going off
i think it's supposed to be today they
doing the
testing i'm going to bed peers wish me
good luck good luck on your sleep my
dude
excuse me j j
beaches
what why thank you for 100 jesus christ
should i stop super chat this is getting
ridiculous
coral gecko art thank you for the laugh
thank you for your gecko arm
oh my god they're doing fire alarm tests
can you hear it i forgot my neighbor
told me and i forgot
have you watched
yes i have a [ __ ] i read the manga
before you even knew what it was
so don't ever talk to me about dora
hedorah because i'm a
anime gatekeeper
yeah i loved it so good do you ever find
it weird that so many people watch you
while you stream
right if this if it was 39 000 people
like looking around me and i i'm like
what the [ __ ]
i'm just hurting at a banana go do
something else
that's probably why i am not good at
streaming i keep forgetting i have an
audience
i should probably do something
interesting right
whippery i simply appears damn hong kong
dallas thank you
hopefully this fire alarm testing
doesn't go on
felix please say my name joshua la three
i'm i'm sure i said that right
banana gang help you help you banana
king
people's low life they think nothing is
going the way it's supposed to
but in that time
your video has been a constant factor so
it's
how it helped me also others too i guess
all right
so this is like because it's a daily
thing you have something daily to enjoy
is that it
that's nice i'm glad i can be there for
you guys
with my hey guys let's watch reddit now
hello
what do i think of kill bill haven't
seen it in like
six years
pierce doesn't tolerate simping even if
it's for him
i will not do that [ __ ] i don't want
fire alarms
at 8 40. come on guys
don't do fire alarms at 8 40 don't be
that guy
i know you warned me and i forgot about
it
should we play some video game
yeah yeah let's play video game
we're almost done with act 2.
dude
thank you rob
yeah got a 1971 copy of sun and steel
dude that's rare my dude
how much did that cost
good luck in your band johnny i'll
probably shake it out after maybe i
don't know
yeah i feel like that book uh that
mishima novel was already rare
but then i mentioned it i figured the
prices must have gone up a lot
because i struggled to get my copy i
actually asked the fan to send me one
all right we're breaking free we're
soaring
[Music]
kids do i stick with college courses
oh my god these live questions while i'm
trying to climb a ladder
in a video game
my friend wants me to take or do i go
with what i want to do radiology
i don't i don't know this i need to know
more
obviously i'm going to say go for with
what you want to do but i need to know
your
situation more my dude i don't know what
your circumstances are
for me it's your philosophy videos that
makes me feel joy and peace can you
shout out my bro sam cohen he wrote a
song called vultures
shout out to sam cohen
can i play game now yes
[ __ ] out oh god all right i'm not
reading the message whoever wrote me on
my phone
sorry my phone fell
[Music]
epic
i'm attracted to the girls and the gays
can you hear the the coach
did i get seen
[Music]
my best friend used to watch your videos
all the time and then when she passed
away watching your videos was something
i look forward to
oh i'm sorry to hear that ashley damn
you paid 250 for your coffee you have
sounded still i knew it
it's a cool thing though that there was
originally not a book actually it was
published in a magazine
it's a strange one it's a really [ __ ]
weird book
oh man um
what's the train i thought why are you
eating c ceiling fruits like
apple banana i recommend floor flutes
like a melon
cucumber [ __ ] you're right my dude
i [ __ ] up
yeah you enjoying that fire alarm in the
background i am just imagine how much i
am enjoying it
[Music]
i'm a 29 year old engineer bro quick
question how is
baby made use the super chat to buy
yourself a proper weight set bro
yeah i i will once i get a better space
i probably will get but thank you dirty
shirley i'll use the money wisely
where are the stables
everyone left i can just jump down right
oh no
no don't kill the horse for [ __ ] sake
stop
killing the horse [ __ ]
no yeah again no i can't do this
[Music]
no
if jurgen dies i'm uninstalling i'm sick
of this
god [ __ ] damn it
hi to ben and nate from hunter
yes
[Music]
i don't understand why they have to test
it so many times
i never heard of kingdom of cartoons
nope
no y'all out no
no
[Music]
this is not happening
this is not happening no
[Music]
the [ __ ] no
he's looking at me
[Music]
all right well that was ghost of
tsushima i hope you guys enjoyed that
let's play
i think that does it for me
hope you guys had fun that was fun until
the end a shitty ending but
yeah i can't complain too much
thank you for watching
cool why do they always have to do it
every time every time there's a pet
we're gonna kill it aren't you sad now
can i just enjoy having a pet without it
just being ripped apart
every [ __ ] time every time every time
every game you love this
you love this little thing well it's
dead now
how do you feel now do you don't feel
good now do you
come on
they made me name it the
is there is act 3 any good is there any
point
this [ __ ] annoys me just so much
is it worth it
his body just disappeared
dude
without being seen okay
if only i had like a horse to help me
guide me through it
that was like really good itself like
maybe named
shadow or something cool like that that
could be cool
you need uh what's going on
should i come is that a yes
okay right back
did you guys see anyone come in here did
it show on the screen
fi it was my turn to check the fire
alarm
so a guy came in here
i don't know if he saw him
all right i'll read the last super chats
i appreciate you guys but it's a bit
distracting and i just want to play for
a bit
hey peers you're one of my heroes thank
you very much
uh will you tell me if my new song could
be jake paul yeah it will
definitely don't even have to look
have you read myth of cypheus yeah and
the stranger
by albert camus uh i have not
maybe i should check it out fire alarm
go
yeah we're playing minecraft right now
it's whatever it's not a big deal it's a
pretty cool game
oh god i think he's gone
you didn't see me but here i am
sorry i got a little bored i hate
stealth [ __ ] it's so
lame it's lame i do
you guys like stealth whenever this
there's stuff
i feel like you can only do self if you
build a game around stealth
if it's just a side mission i'm like
[ __ ] this this is boring
i ain't doing it you know what i'm
saying don't bother
that's like if tetris was like all right
now we're gonna add in
um an fps where you do trick shots
like now this doesn't really goddamn it
still mad about you again not gonna lie
i'm tired of pretending i'm okay with it
how many years i've died now
how many timelines do i have to sit
through
with jurgen after jurgen just going
bye-bye
i don't know who sees me i honestly
don't even [ __ ] there we go
i did it my expert rolling skills paid
off
at last
[Music]
four
that's too many
so two in minecraft one in last of us
one it goes to tsushima
could i swim in the ocean where's my
objective it doesn't tell me
there's this way
[Music]
someone sees me apparently
can't see this because i'm fast
oh i have to go up there
can't wait for the next game where you
get to name your horse and then the
horse dies in
i reached the tree i did it mom
at least someone didn't hit him with a
golf club
you're right at least he died with some
honor
that's a good point i'm gonna keep it
really chief you're probably gonna hear
from peta
[ __ ] god damn it
what are they gonna do tweet about it
[ __ ] peter can't do [ __ ]
whoa what's happening wait
i died how
the [ __ ] i didn't die that was there
that's that does not that does not count
i don't know what the hell that was
uh yeah epic
where do i go here
investigate the area i'm doing it that
[ __ ] flames
i'm not even touching them great
playthrough so far i agree
check out here
more dead people
i see you dead people you're not you're
good though don't care
he saw me
there we go
ah [ __ ] i just got here again
i'm supposed to walk not bad
i think i'm supposed to go this way
[ __ ] they got i got milk
this is not epic
maybe the water would like heal me you
know what i mean
let's go splish [ __ ]
whoa
i'm not going to the bridge
i thought the game was supposed to teach
me
i agree you could i agree
keep dying
you're not supposed to go that way okay
sorry game i guess i chose the wrong way
wait i was supposed to go that way
what is happening is the game i think
the game froze
oh
oh what oh it's fine okay all right cool
wait so they killed me right before i
entered the bridge
and then they were like actually you
need to go to the bridge again and die
just a little further ahead
nice i'm just angry at this game at this
point
they [ __ ] kill you again
the rules i don't care if i was enjoying
it
can't horses get plot armor
can't peter do you something useful and
just like ban
game developers from killing animals
that's a cheap plot device
who would do such a thing
oh look we got a shitty yet again now
[ __ ] yet again
so what is i can't hear so what is act
three about
me i wanna i'm alright
what are my expectations to be am i
cured now yeah what is happening
uh we're going back to the stables
they want to remind you don't they hey
here's the horse oh wait never mind it's
another one
those [ __ ] this is not okay
ah [ __ ] took the what i want i guess
i'll get
oh my god i get this
insomnia gang right on your head that's
the only people watching this
33 000 people with insomnia
[Music]
with me
it's a little slower
so now we're at the north part of the
map so there's still a lot less then
it's a fire alarm
it's really annoying
the thing they do in the uk
there you go
this alarm is relentless
[Music]
i like that there's a snow area
it will make all the blood splatter
really cool oh i just sound like a
sociopath what the [ __ ]
survey the frozen i just want to kill
can i just kill them
i don't want to survey
[Music]
haha you thought you could fool me
i don't think so [ __ ]
um
screenshot yes
here it is i knew my white armor would
look cool in the snow
but this is not a pretty location is it
we'll get another shot like this at some
point
but i really want to get this shot
it's too much
maybe another angle yeah see from this
angle looks way cooler
but then the flowers are coming
all right we'll get it next time mission
failed well what the [ __ ]
slave [ __ ]
[Music]
you're uh [ __ ] i don't know
hi guys what's
[Music]
lethal gang
all i want to do is kill kill kill
we walk into joel and abby
[Laughter]
what the [ __ ] we're going to this cabin
the [ __ ] dude
is that a [ __ ] golf club
you're free i'm your savior here you go
joel
you're welcome japanese joel i saved
your life
now your game will not be so shitty and
you could make it
a third one in the series
alternate timeline japanese the last of
us
has been saved we couldn't
we couldn't save jurgen but at least we
could save the franchise
is it my
that's kind of fancy
it says i can upgrade this no it's just
going to breathe
it looks the same upgrade that's so
boring
what about the gosaku armor
that's it boring
i'm helping you sleep that's not a
compliment
but thank you i'm glad upgrade ghost
armor terrifies enemies and look
goes uh dope all right i was thinking
about it like does it look cool
um then i thought nah i probably doesn't
look cool
if it scares people that's always cool
hey guys
signal fireworks okay
matthew thank you very much
yeah the game is really cool i just wish
they didn't [ __ ] kill my horse
you can shoot them while they are in the
air shoot what birds
am i dumb
i think i'm dumb guys
there must be oh that's the essence it's
like mulan
have you seen that movie have you seen
oh
come here [ __ ]
[Music]
you're about to go boom
whoa whoa hey you almost hit me [ __ ]
crazy
that hurt
push it out
[Music]
got him ah they didn't fall
they just made a hole we just made a
hole for this host matthew lane finn mob
stand up
what the [ __ ] matthew finn mob
fire alarm is still going strong it's
been an hour
whatever
this might be like a cool screenshot
if i can zoom out a bit more i guess
again
so pretty
[Music]
i would look forward to cyberpunk if it
would ever come out
the [ __ ] are you doing
[Music]
oh he got me oh
ow ow ow that actually hurts
something happening over here
what's happening
don't ever
damn that did a lot of damage [ __ ]
don't look away kids i didn't die i
swear please
i'm sorry oh there i died actually
i want the guard outfit yeah they look
[ __ ] cooler than mine
that's impossible i cannot look
i should have been
yeah yes put in the air i've been
poisoned
god these guys
you can get a guard outfit oh [ __ ] yeah
sorry i gotta look out for my homies
there i feel a little bad i didn't do
that
let's go for another plan of attack you
know what i'm saying
stealth gang
slippery waterfall game
and then we do
[Music]
stop poisoning me
no damn
one shot kill on those [ __ ]
[ __ ]
you get pushed you get pushed man
can we do a stand-off
[ __ ] every time he hits me with that
[ __ ] thing
thank you for the streams i'm losing my
mind now the alarm is getting really
[ __ ] annoying
god damn
all right let's do a standoff classic
they don't want to do a stand-up that's
fine
[Music]
maybe that will help
stop poisoning me no
let's get the arrow oh [ __ ]
this is really [ __ ] hard
oh
[Music]
no
stop shooting me
[ __ ]
yoona you [ __ ] hey pit's been really
rough lately i've been cheerful for you
and your vids cheer me up
flexing keep on flexing my man god
[ __ ] damn it
god damn it it's so thought it's fine i
got this easy game
what you want to do a lot of people
don't know this
this is part of the plan you want to hit
this [ __ ]
riding that [ __ ] eye
oh you survived that am i am i supposed
to think believe that you survived
[Music]
will you [ __ ] died
there we go
[Music]
[ __ ]
oh
[ __ ] you now six seconds left
yoona yuna i don't have time to babysit
you yuna
all right part of the plan guys watch
this
i'm going to sneak this time
all the way no one's going to find me
what you want to do this is actually
part of the plan you go here
you click here a lot of people don't
know this you go here
uh and you go here
and you go here and then
we stealth king kia kill self kill this
guy
whoa
fear me [ __ ] oh
[ __ ] this is how i should have done it
[ __ ] yeah
and now explosive arrows
into this guy's [ __ ] face
oh my god the arrow guys i'm going for
you everything
and i die
he was targeting the hostage and then
out of nowhere
i'm going to slam it with the shield
all right guys this is all part of the
plan uh what you want to do is you want
to die
at that point and you want to keep doing
this
and then you want to keep going here and
then you want to be in
oh my god yeah in the way
[Music]
hey you're scared you should be scared
i'll shoot you in the arrow you also get
it
hey you like arrows so much don't you
marry one
no i don't think so [ __ ]
[Music]
you're not so big now are you [ __ ]
you're like a little
[ __ ] ball a ball of [ __ ]
you go easy easy
cannot stress how easy that was
that fire alarm works yeah for sure
yeah i think it works guys i think it's
a fire alarm it works i
don't know i have this idea don't worry
johnny don't worry
all the best
all right you're free or whatever
live a life you're live a life and be
free
dude they're not even tired they're
they're just [ __ ] chilling
this guy doesn't even give a [ __ ]
[ __ ] do you know how many knives i had
to waste for that battle
keep hiccuping
[ __ ] where are the hostages
oh i had to pick this one
up
i didn't even float time hello pierce
big fan brofist dj ac3 very epic thank
you for the breakfast i will take it
and now i'll play my [ __ ] flute there
that's right right up
suck it suck my flute now this
is a photo mode
pov you are the end of the flute
that's my favorite one so far get fluted
[ __ ]
shave beard for good luck pigs no no i'm
not sure
new wallpaper right there
flute gang official wallpaper right
there
why isn't your longbow white as well i
haven't unlocked any skins for my long
while it is a bit annoying i agree
ended a facetime call with my girlfriend
to watch the stream you made the right
choice matt damon
welcome back to like to hear we don't
have any sims around here am i right
gamers
am i right or what
damn whoa how do we get so much
we maxed out all the stances
yeah shave your taint though good night
beach
what trying to pronounce my last name
agaronin
agaronin wasn't even hard come on
so this is our new city
wow
this is a stereo statue of jurgen
he's so beautiful
where's the statue there was a real one
let's fake
where's the swords uh person i can never
find them i don't understand why they
don't just mark them
right am i crazy i'm probably crazy
oh we can upgrade longbow hell yeah here
we go here's the boy here
don't mind if i grab your [ __ ]
a lot better draw speed
i don't know man
give me both vanity gear look i don't
have anything else
oh the longbow we can change
yeah let's cover that door
what do you guys think can we
any dice for the golden retribution
doesn't even look good
ugly
i'll buy the red one just well it's guy
because i think it's
let's change the
oh i had noble crane whatever that is
that actually looks better god damn it
oh my god i already had a bunch
yes cool
hello puppy what's up dallas
i kind of want to just check around the
area i don't want to do quests right
away
what do you guys want to do
i just [ __ ] around a bit
whoops see can we
get you're getting a little longer
just a little longer man that's all i
wanted
is that too much to [ __ ] ask uh
let's go to izumi village
oh we got a armor thing here
what do we get whoa
what is that
do i have to unlock that
there it is nice
that's the one right
way to copy
quest blows mr round senpai hell yeah
yeah they're quite i don't know i just
like the open world aspects i think
that's my favorite part of the game
it's my favorite part of the game it's
just when i get to go flip flop
can i get like 15 i need it for a thing
sorry bro
you're 15 or mine
i don't like the purple thing i wish it
was red
bring stefano to complete your quest
stephanos dead
they're all dead
sorry about your house bro i go here now
i'm back hello i'm just looking if you
have like anything
it looks like you're quite poor though
it looks like you're very poor actually
this is kind of cringe bro
why is this house so big and have
nothing in it there we go
kalista just posted an emote thank you
watch me land on the horse
told you
told you bro
eyes michael i just want to say hello
what's up michael
uh oh oh oh
hey careful
jurgen would never do that
illegal
hate the horse could i at least got a
white horse
to match my armor wait was that a bird
you guys see that
oh we got a gang of games
what up gang
don't think so
ah he got me [ __ ] i couldn't see and
i'm dead for [ __ ] sake are you serious
i can sell the iron
once i'm done upgrading what do i do
with that then
i think i'll change back to hard i think
it's for more fun
there's the bird let's follow you
bird is struggling
there we go
what do you want to show me bird
oh skeleton vengeance
oh sick
sick sicker
are these bad guys
how does that feel when your horse
no not that one
yeah be afraid
percy
say iron one more time what
i know
you know what i don't need the horse
i'll just walk
now how you always say legend you're not
much of a fan of ghost armor also cried
when my horse died i don't know by you
love you always legend sorry i can't
read
thank you elephant x that's a disgusting
name i regret reading that
okay i think i'm always i think i've
almost upgraded everything i just need
um
one more upgrade on there oh god that's
gonna take a while though
[ __ ]
i don't need horse i don't need anyone
i walk
it's to honor jurgen my man
if his japan gang arrow mongol gang
cringe
agreed [ __ ] how do i get down
maybe if i had like a horse or something
oh look there is one how convenient
all right [ __ ] jump jurgen would jump
he wouldn't even yeah that's right [ __ ]
oh he actually did ah weak leg weak leg
jurgen would never stutter weak [ __ ]
horse
is not a walking simulator
hello where is everyone
you mongol can i kill you oh sorry
you seem cool bye-bye
god everyone's poor here
everyone's super poor this place poor
this thing stinks
there's no mongols
this is mongol territory but no one's
here
[Music]
let's keep exploring i guess and
fast travel there
hmm
edition prepared to sing back at me
nice yeah i saw this for coming to me
very nice i like it
i don't need you bird i can find it
myself
midnight hanabi
i don't like it
i think this is the coolest armor
how does it feel to die
oh i [ __ ] hit the bird i'm sorry
sorry bird
oh my god i'm i'm i feel terrible
this is awful i can't believe this
happened
sponsor eagle now what have i done
[Music]
rest
cringe ass horse
all right there's something over there
with the wind guys
everyone say something about how
sponsory how much sponsor eagle meant
for you
oh actually that's a perfect segue for
me to do my sponsor read
okay guys sponsor eagle may have died
but he didn't die for vayne what's this
he delivered one final message
this is crazy
he says nordvpn
pewdiepie there's a limited time offer
ending soon this is what he said
verbatim
last chance to get 70 off
a three year plan which means you pay
for 36 months this is his final message
guys don't make fun of this
he wrote this knowing he was going to
die
plus viewers can use your code
my code pewdiepie
to get one extra month of nordvpn for
free
check out nordvpn.com pewdiepie enter
code pewdiepie
take control of your internet experience
today with nordvpn
thank you sponsor eagle this is the last
chance
again 70 off that's a lot of percentages
and just imagine that sponsor
eagle died for this
yeah thanks guys uh rest in peace uh
sponsor eagle
and uh hopefully he'll be reincarnated
uh as a as a falcon
or maybe as an ikea bird wow thank you
sponsor eagle we will never forget those
were touching words
i don't know about you but uh that
really spoke to me
i ain't gonna stand you the [ __ ]
anywhere [ __ ]
i don't care about killing dogs at this
point because you killed my love
i cannot [ __ ] block those
there we go
this guy takes such a [ __ ] beating
jesus
can you block please for the love of god
i'm looking at the archer in the back
and that's why i
like get confused
let go little pupper
don't think so don't
ow you poisoned me
oh you can't see bye bye [ __ ] why am i
such a boomer
uh kill everyone uh flute
[Laughter]
[ __ ] i'm so idiot i cringe
[ __ ] no i did the thing
i did the thing guys [ __ ]
i guess i have to do some i have to tell
an embarrassing story
about myself one time
i uh
i i don't know i don't do embarrassing
things i'm perfect i'm
absolute chad in every situation never
done anything cringy in my life
okay so don't ask
hey
uh what
oh you're dead
[Music]
[ __ ]
struggling a little bit
[Music]
they're [ __ ] armor things
there it is
[Music]
god you are so annoying
i did not [ __ ] die at the last guy
are you serious
what a joke sponsor eagle died for
nothing
i feel nothing killing this fluffy
little [ __ ]
[Music]
i'm getting you all you will all paste
taste i mean not chase
[Music]
easy [ __ ]
yeah call your little frenzies
got him no not
from the kill cool
oh
[Music]
all right now we're talking now we're
talking
that's how it's done look at the size of
my dick
[ __ ] yeah you saw that you're getting
fake here again you did nothing you just
watched
hate you i hate you very good
fake year again
to my core you make me sick
unbelievable let's get older
the deers are fighting with the mongols
can't believe it
can't trust anyone these days
i just can't
give me all you lose give me a loot
give me all the loot then you get the
fluke when i'm gone
when i'm gone
[ __ ] you get the food
doing good do a mythic quest to get the
flaming sword
i don't have it yet my dude my wish
[Music]
guess we keep riding through the night
it'd be cool if
if we had like
it'd be cool if we had like a black
horse named
shadow because then we could ride
through the night and like do a bunch of
oh uh oh no
i don't like it if you continue to live
farther in the story you get to pick
another horse really
i feel like you're lying to me and i
don't trust you
i don't trust you i'm sorry i can't let
my emotions
be swayed like that i do i ain't doing
it
this is like minecraft snow biome it's a
lot like minecraft actually
i see a bird let's follow
my insides are hollow
thought of here again dead tough to
swallow
so sad
what do we get
[Music]
azure dragon yeah
there has to be something there right
you guys doing today good morning all
early stream today feels good man kick
off the day with the stream with the
pewdiepie you know i'm saying yeah
yeah there's a road
yeah words are cringed
this feels very swedish am i the only
one getting reminiscence
riding with your horse through the snow
just me fair enough
why is it so shadowy
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa that's a cool
place let's go there
it's the mission after the one you're on
is might even be the one here on yoona
wants to take you somewhere and she says
but let's to get
you a new horse um oh well morin sent
them not to do it then
you can't just replace [ __ ] after
[ __ ]
just like women it still works
if you've replaced horse after horse
then maybe you're a [ __ ]
have you thought of that maybe you're
the problem
you're fire in flames yeah
when will you be returning to some
nautica probably never because i
finished the game and i'm done with it
i beat it 100 did y'all forget this i'm
so confused
you all got memory lost say something
i thought i was too
damn they really make you go the long
way huh [ __ ]
ah i just have to guess it felt
yeah i'm missing the fire alarm now it's
too quiet
whoa this is disorienting
yeah this reminds me when i was rock
climbing in sweden wearing a samurai
armor
yes pretty much the same thing
whoa i thought i died
jesus close call but not today
because we got the grappling hood
yeah feels pretty badass not gonna lie
yeah i knew i would make it didn't even
hesitate
it's pretty dope climbing there
all right we made it better we're worth
it
no there's another one all right
i can make it oh no
no no
oh god oh god
okay we're here
what the [ __ ]
i don't know how i didn't see that
wait a minute
am i supposed to be here
oh i am
oh god
this is some hardcore hardcore parkour
yeah
wait a minute oh i see it this might be
a cool screenshot if i can nail it
i don't think i nailed it
here i go here i go
it just looks kind of awkward
it looks like a flying reindeer
superhero rain there man
yeah why is there not been a superhero
rain
hmm
all right we made it
are you going to watch avatar why don't
we watch an episode today
to get you people to [ __ ]
i'll watch an episode all right
let's watch an episode after undone
you guys down for that charm of kami of
the sky
where is it what was it called
comedy of the sky
was this the one
help me help me
all right let's go with that
now you ruined the shot you basically
just came in and ruined the shot
[Music]
can you get away from there
that's not the right one
i just wanted to know which one it was
charm of negan
why do they name them differently
yeah that's the one okay cool seems
pretty good
can't find a good horse these days no
matter much how much you pay these fools
ooh gear upgrade
i think you would love the game oxenfree
i think i almost played it at one point
it's too many games
give me your loot
sorry bro do it i don't get anything
from these right like why do i kill them
sorry i don't know why i did that
what is santa claus in this game
no no way
no hell yeah
he's in the lighthouse over here
this is a cool shot
or is it
i don't know
this era just not look as pretty why the
dolphin you killed brook though
i don't know i feel terrible
whoa that's cool
sun came out
[Music]
flowers are too busy
don't jump off now boy
i'm out of i'm out of creativity hey i
got nothing
i'm sorry i tried to make cool photos
for you guys
but i can't
i know there's always something in the
lighthouse so check it out
hey oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
i collected those banners so i could get
a new saddle for here again but jurgen
is dead so i don't know why i'm excited
yeah look new saddle available cool
thanks guys
genie baby big pp you can't call
yourself big peepee genie baby what the
[ __ ]
don't do that
nice
that's pretty
shout out to casey from jimmy
all right
yeah they often feel has a nice touch
too
there's snow
i like the stillness
it's quite pretty too honestly
i like the crashing of the waves
oh i like this
you can animate this that look [ __ ]
sick dude
how that is a wallpaper have that
looping
[ __ ] i clicked the wrong button
wow
sorry guys i got very preoccupied
no
wish i could have
see the feet aren't like i'm sorry
i'm sorry i don't really i forgot what i
was doing
jesus christ my bad
i can jump from here just roll before
see
totally
i told you it's fine bro hey look found
stuff because of it
the nightmare also has very good game
yeah i played it it's on my channel
thank you for the recommendation
unidentified location really
but i'm right here my dude
oh there's a bamboo nice
sweet uh
oh god what an awkward pattern
nice
yes see that you're getting fake here
again that's how we do it in this
[ __ ] [ __ ]
bamboo master [ __ ]
[Music]
where should we go next here
i don't know why it feels more immersive
to just
ride around that's when i'm into the
game the most
i can kind of make my own story of what
i'm doing
that is the real question
[ __ ]
yes
[Applause]
oh my god i miss thank you
no i missed
get fluted [ __ ] i'm the flute
samurai
oh this is a cool shot
sorry i'll stop i'll stop
[Music]
stop i'm sorry
i like the horse but he ain't no jargon
i don't trust him
probably a russian spy or something
see they give you locations and then
you're like all right new adventures
let's go fake here again
i feel like oh they don't let you go
back
that's interesting
we missed the location there
i missed an hour and suddenly jurgen is
gone guys should we tell him
should we tell him the great tragedy of
dark plague is the wise
whatever the [ __ ] name is
oh no these people are in trouble i'll
help you
what the [ __ ] is wrong with you i was
helping
don't ever come near me and fake your
again again
don't ever where is that over there
it's a tree it looks so out of place
what the sheep was gone all along whoa
what was that
jorgen five what a great name
yeah i share the screenshot it's in the
member chat
uh on an imager
i have a whole folder
mongol filthy mongol territory is there
anyone up here
welcome chit fan first day as a member
[Music]
yeah
can't get pewdiepie cherry it's in back
order minus one is in measurement my
lack of reclining
chair features are 100 my pp and muscle
growth stagnant
what will i do yeah our regular chair
will do for now don't worry
it's okay we all been there they're
wearing a mask that's why i keep
forgetting
well that could have gone oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] you shield gang
yeah eat [ __ ] [ __ ]
yeah now who's blowing me up it's very
annoying
[ __ ] oh god horsey no stop killing the
horses
oh [ __ ] i dodged
oh this is pretty hardcore
i will not do i need this oh god
this was like a lump a lot more than a
[Music]
bargain
just gonna pick up some loot guys
yes
is that all you got i'm the flu
king [ __ ] you got nothing
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm [ __ ] sorry
i'm [ __ ] sorry
[Music]
oh i'm coming for you why
now i get to kill
they're all dead god damn it
well it was fun while it lasted
i enjoyed it for what it was
flute gang well right i can't it flute
on the bridge
that's racist
why can't they float on the bridge the
[ __ ] that's my privilege
as an american
ah can i have us horse instead
yep it's possible to have a section of
discord that is exclusive to people that
have the purified chair
yes i love that idea that's hilarious
chair cat the council of jab will gather
and discuss important business in their
chairs
great idea
it needs to be verified though
we have a yearly um
yearly meeting finally caught you live
we've been watching since 2011. i love
watching you grow dude
you should be so proud of before you
come thank you rinpoche remind me
rinpy rampive senpai
okay we liberated it we liberated the
city
yes yes this is
i don't know about you guys but i have
to pee very badly
so if you have to pee as well hold it
just a little longer because we're gonna
do a classic
pewdiepie p at the same time
where we go and we pee at the same time
liquids will leave our body at the same
time
do you understand do you understand how
important that is you know how special
that is
to pee at the same time oh i missed my
[ __ ]
it's going to be epic
just like that hold your goddamn peepee
just like jurgen hold his and think
about that
i think let that sink in for a minute
all right what do we
damn we have a lot to explore you can
can you do this by the way i keep
forgetting
so we can track resolve
now the wind will blow us to resolve
give us that result
wait to replay the game so i can pick a
different horse and select kaga later on
nice
hey pitts just letting you know that you
are amazing we both
have big peeps oh that's great hey pitch
just got 100 million chairs the most
comfy ever
hell yeah your butt will thank you
welcome welcome all the members have fun
at the beach whoever said he's going to
the beach
great i forgot today it's actually a
really hot day in
uk tomorrow's gonna be hot too
just don't go to bed
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
get [ __ ] fluted [ __ ] don't
ever don't ever come at me again
[Music]
i enjoy this so much more than the main
quests
i wish to do the storytelling without
cutscenes
they could have done it with that i
don't know if it would have been better
but i would have preferred it
[Music]
you tell the story through gameplay i
think it's so much more fun
you can have some cutscenes but like not
many
i've been watching you since 400k have
been a super lurker damn something
annoying and fangirling about you
at pax a few years back that's fine when
you show the pit
the people who's behind you in canon
line
that's cool apparently i met you uh
and now an exclusive section for discord
and the chair is in
backing order i'm writing wait what
phil i can't make sense out of that
message going to be completely real we
achieved
kill general
freeze and balls gang
it's the game yeah they have nature and
and
and uh open world in such cool ways it'd
be cooler if they just told
i feel like cutscenes have become a
replacement of
storytelling and it's lame it's just
lame
i don't like it it should be an addition
remember when cutscenes were something
like whoa what the [ __ ]
there's a cutscene holy [ __ ] this is so
cool
like diablo and warcraft and all those
games there's a [ __ ] cutscene you get
a cutscene at the end
oh that's so epic
that was like oh great because all right
cool
back in my day cutscenes used to be
cool but now they're not cool
goddammit
oh he shot his friend
[Music]
i love that spray
yes oh we got the shadow
uh fry thing where are they
boom yes
anyone else [ __ ] there's no one else
i wasted it
can i please use it on this game
[Music]
yeah you're right i should do a
screenshot in the middle so battle
that'd be sick
try and do it on those those are cool
because you split the [ __ ] half
how the [ __ ] did i do that that was so
[Music]
cool
of course he finishes with that
aah
[Applause]
uh
this is [ __ ] tough dude
yes oh that's [ __ ] badass i wish the
background was cooler
holy [ __ ] what a [ __ ] blood fest
ah it doesn't look good
someone's calling me and i don't care
all right perfect time i actually
pee i'll be right back guys
good morning okay
so
how we all going in here [ __ ]
why are you typing peeping
what's going on
hmm so juicy
me and my manager sees that watch you
all the time and always make pewdiepie
references at work epic what's the
pewdiepie reference
we're running what music do i listen to
man christian psalms
there's some juicy ass [ __ ]
apple [ __ ]
i was gonna get an um i know this is
really interesting
but i was actually going to get a pair
and then i thought it's not quite ripe
yet
so i took the apple and i don't regret
it
here goes my daily symphony again jokes
aside i really love how the membership
turned
us into a close community again hell
yeah i'm more than happy to support it
keep the good work loved you he loves
you right back tony
if the members stay around what it is
now
then in 10 months
we should have gathered 1 million for
charity that's the goal i want to reach
i think that could be so cool
high pitched long time fan rewatching
playthroughs like mad father and missile
[ __ ] all right give me a recommendation
like another game like that because i
really want to play another game like
that
so
how's your peepee
do you ever think about how you change
your generation for the batter no i
think about how i made it worse
that's what i did
this is really loud in the mic i'm so
sorry
i'm almost done
almost my apple almost died
i missed your twitch board from pubg
you mean the sound board alejandro
by the way thank you very much 100 jesus
very generous
oh my god should i bring back
i thought it was kind of annoying it was
kind of funny though
the shadow
would you ever consider doing a pity
pewdiepie community stream like having
big names in discord do a stream event
host a rocket league tournament yeah it
could be fun
well like how the blood comes out
how are these particles
quite like that you can't run but you
can't hide dog
because i love your q a videos
if i have a question for our fans uh do
i have a question for my fans
um
i'm sure i do
question for my bro okay
are you boy or a girl
or rather not say i guess it's the third
option in this
day and age
let him donate some [ __ ]
yeah uh you beer considering
what morning livestream my morning poop
what the [ __ ]
all right see this is why i don't have
any questions for you
for you guys because i get comments like
those
kill an enemy with a smoke bomb oh [ __ ]
i didn't do that
doesn't matter what your gender is as
long as you're pee pee huge
good point all right
do you eat your vegetables that's what i
want to know
please honestly
yeah sorry that was an apple burp that's
disgusting
good good you passed the test so far
i almost died look it's jacksepticeye
spanner i knew they put him in here
that's on about the edge i [ __ ] knew
it i knew it's jacksepticeye
why is the reason that you're watching
this live stream
when you could be doing anything else
stupid question you're watching the
greatest gamer on the planet
killing killing it the airless the
realest
gorillas and pillars and propellers and
gorillas to illus
and then i illustrate pillars i'm the
gamer though the
painting of the can't nobody stop me
saying
i'm the [ __ ] a grain and
main ain't and i got maine
and i'm on my maintenance i go insane in
and i go
no complaining because i got spray
sprays
spraying and then
dude that was sick that was [ __ ]
awesome dude
hey face i got the pewdiepie cherry hell
yeah i decided to trust your advocacy
i'm very thankful
i'm very thankful that you decided to
trust your ass in my hands i wait
wait that sounded wrong i'm rushing
doesn't sorry ha ha
do you guys think shane is guilty all
these war crimes you guys because people
are saying he's an actual pedophile i'm
like
i don't i don't like that i don't think
he is
i think he just makes a lot of edgy 2011
jokes
i think there's a clear difference there
but
i watched some of youtube that were that
was like i'm not going to say that he's
a pedophile
but i'm gonna keep showing you these
clips to make him seem like it as much
as possible
but i won't say it so he doesn't sue me
of course
where the [ __ ] is this last one
where is he
i would kill him with a small phone
this is very bad
[Music]
i love that move is so [ __ ] smooth
oh that's when i want to take the
screenshot
[Music]
uh hippie it's been a time for about
three years always wanted to see you
play red dead redemption really
i heard that wasn't that good of a
video
like it's like all these little kids
forgot
i guess they didn't live through it like
everyone was trying to be edgy as [ __ ]
on the internet
around that time that was like the point
i was trying to
shock humor yeah it's cringy looking
back but that's the landscape of it
i think some stuff he did was like
extremely inappropriate
and went too far but like to build this
case just because he made all this joke
to make some assumption of a label this
is [ __ ] up
why can't i find this last one sorry i
put a stupid question i felt guilty
so i'm just donating to say sorry eat
your mom that's all right i don't
even remember you're all good
i'm not playing red dead redemption not
happening i'm not interested
i'm sure it's a good game but life's too
short and
i'm not playing
it looks like a cutscene [ __ ]
party and i i i'm done with it
i killed an enemy with smoke bomb what
the [ __ ]
god damn it
should i get out of here
here we go this is oh cool
nice an actual battle it's been a while
[Music]
you killed my father
oh yeah will you kill my dogs
you kill my horse i'll never forgive
the japanese
oh [ __ ]
should i do water
can't get past his defenses
the [ __ ] all right
i died [ __ ]
[ __ ] come on i can do this
that's easy
look away one second guys uh not uh
i dare you to play on lethal mode lethal
mode is easier
than hardware
[Music]
is
dude
[Music]
i got a squat ah [ __ ] i'm tired
i gotta check my did i drop my iphone
why is he bowing
i feel like this is a cool screenshot
but i
don't understand
piece of mongol armor
what
his arm is right there that's what he
was doing
did i just progress a mainland quest
without trying
is that what's happening
hey whoa what's up
jesus hold up one second guys
hold up hold up hold up
[ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
no he didn't down the strike and i
couldn't see it
[ __ ] battalion out of nowhere
what just happened
i mean you shitty horse
cool new alright
uh i didn't diet tactically respawn
i would have wasted too much uh stuff
there
learn the [ __ ] difference
understand do you understand
it's 3am yeah it's gotta be late for you
guys go to sleep or some [ __ ] i don't
know
how do i get there maybe there's a way
around it
yeah it is isn't it
next time you're at the lighthouse
taking a photo
make a leap and capture a photo before
you fall alright that's a good idea
yeah let's do that
am i gonna have to swim across
[ __ ] that's gotta be cool
i've been thinking uh i know this is
kind of cringe but i've been taking
uh cold showers lately i've been trying
because i read it in this book about
buddhists that would meditate
under freezing cold waterfall and they
would talk about how
horrible it was but eventually they got
used to it so i wanted to try and
get comfortable with the freezing cold
shower but
it's more i realize that i do these
things that i'm like look around on
youtube
and it's like this whole sub-genre of
people doing these kind of things and
i'm like [ __ ]
am i just going through a mid-life
crisis is this what's happening
i don't feel like i am but then i look
at all these other people
i'm like god damn it
[Music]
can't i just live in this time where i
can go to waterfalls
instead i have to take cold showers and
be cringed
not epic glory days are over
the time for men rest in peace
now we just get to simulate it through
video games
so we have that
you ever decide to go back to minecraft
should try an ftb
in infinity evolved mod what is that is
that good
i keep hearing people suggest mods but
i've never been impressed by it
[Music]
all right apparently everyone takes cold
showers in the chat what the [ __ ] is
wrong with you guys
are we all simultaneously mid life
crisis
[Music]
oh that was cool
he's not dead
i take showers that will burn me nice
run your flesh off epic
show me the way little bird
this is good for the environment
yeah true
oh my god this is great
oh yeah i was gonna make another video
on the pole guy from tlc
there were so many more cl apparently
they got robbed with machetes in them
someone said i'm like what the [ __ ] did
i miss
the hustle
this is not the right way
hot showers give you instant six-pack
the hotter the water the more effective
it is
what is there science behind that my
dude
[Music]
even when it's small
you're dead my dude
oh sorry horse
[ __ ] i'm sorry
how's it going in here my dude
[Music]
why would i pre-order a game that i can
buy
regardless when it's out pre-ordering
games
is for sims i'm just gonna go ahead and
say it
that did not explode
god damn it i'm getting kind of annoyed
that's better
jesus
that's all i wanted
don't care i don't care
hello
i have the biggest people of all i don't
think so i've seen
no wait i haven't but i am seen mine
nice we're getting there
all right we need one more i guess
i don't know
can i fast travel
hey p is watching since i was 10 just
turned 20.
i've been wanting your merch but don't
ship to south africa i'm sorry about
that i don't know why
would you ever play skyrim no
already played it a little bit long ago
i'm sorry
maybe if it comes out on
um
let's try to make a joke and then it's
like oh wait it has already come out on
everything
god damn it
i do
oh sorry boys
[Music]
fear me mortals
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
[ __ ] didn't look cool i want a
picture god damn it
i've been watching you since i was born
damn sleepy chance see that's
the kind of dedication i want i want an
army
watching no one else
that's really the goal here
you were 13 when you started watching
you guys are way too young to watch me
you understand that
way too young did you not hear me swore
did your parents not say no you can't
watch this
i have not seen demon slayer no i have
none
if you're pregnant right now
put like a microphone through the belly
over the live stream
sorry this is weird i'm just making a
joke
teach them young charm of fire doctrine
nice i wanted that
you were 37 when you started watching
what the [ __ ] how old are you now
a hundred
[Music]
that's pretty dope though not gonna lie
we're following the wind of resolve
jump here again fake here again sorry
come on [ __ ] come on [ __ ] jump
damn jurgen mountain going out here what
the hell
yeah nice
how long am i going to stream i don't uh
what time is it until 12
probably until lunchtime
how long guy how long do you guys want
me tell me
we're about to run in some trouble
big fan from taiwan thank you
[Music]
no more [ __ ] spearing smearing
why is the eagle here i don't want to
hit it
hold up i want to learn how to do the
techniques
so hold then tap or i can do
hold and tap tap all right let's do that
oh
it's not that good
so [ __ ] strong
uh can you show your face
should i just maybe use a shield
technique
oh i should use a shield stance that
explains it you're free my dude
wrong stance my bad guys my bad i
thought this was a big guy
yeah i should
nice jacket is it gucci i love it
been here hey pewds 48 years old 19 year
old
been watching since we'll see journals
so can't introduce me to your content
no way thanks wall street journal keep
doing what you do
hell yeah thank you wall street journal
since i was watching uh steins gate
about time travel uh anatomy about time
travel and
all the characters get this one move
where they're like okay if i can change
one thing what it would be and i was
thinking back like
yeah that time was pretty stressful but
i would not take it back and i know it
sounds really like
yeah i don't regret anything i've done
in the past because it's made me who i
am today but it really put me through an
experience that
uh made me grow so much so much
you wouldn't believe like you wouldn't
get it as a normal person living a
comfortable life someone's saying i'm
really
i'm happy i went through that experience
i wouldn't be the same person for that
so i guess it's the cringy quote i
promise but uh
[ __ ]
temple is so weird
let's check for upgrades
yeah i love the slow attack so good
the dog's gotta go
so do you
[Music]
that was pretty cool that was pretty
dope
[Music]
sorry doggos
i feel terrible hey man thanks for being
you i feel like i learned a lot
about life from you thanks for being a
good role model thank you zach
keeping you mate
you're updated what does that mean
updated
revelated
all right looks like we can climb here
is my previous stream not available
it should be
i'll check on it after
oops
something nearby it is available and
what the [ __ ] you smoking man
stop smoking
what's up here damn that was cool
we can do a photo with it follow up
damn this place looks cold
i feel cold just looking at this area
found it bamboo time
well that looks so cool
wait what
oh [ __ ] i hit x instead sorry
come on boom boom boom boom
boom boom boom
too slow
[ __ ] i hit one wrong
nice i'm here just for you to say my
name
mike peepee
i'm not giving you the satisfaction
[ __ ]
i'm not doing it mike pp is your name
that's such a silly name
what a silly name you have there mr mike
peepee
that's hilarious your mom must be a
comedian
just got down watching house i don't
know if there any other horror movies
you recommend
doing that during the grudge series
really good
the tv show watch that
recommend it tell me
are there no foxes in this area foreign
[Music]
dudes i showed all my friends the shout
out they can't believe it thank you
pierce you're the best hugely
nice i'm glad it made
your day a little epic air air
yeah you have a fast today if you're
jewish
epic
how's it going so
that was the fox then right there
is one
i know you're a fan of evangelion would
you like to see
an anime an op animation with you in it
kind of like g fuel sponsor i mean i i
guess that's kind of where we were going
with the g-pro sponsor
there is possibility would you ever go
on the joe rogan podcast check today's
video guys that should answer it
all right foxy show me
show me the way this is the way
i know jurgen is [ __ ] crazy
holy [ __ ] this version of jurgen needs
to calm down
i can't seem to get the right shot
i don't know i don't like it that much
i like them
that looks so [ __ ] terrifying
[Music]
getting hungry i could
feel my little minifest
i'm hungry i'm tired i love you honey
last of us two is a better game how can
you say that with this straight face
how dare you
would you would be better with
screenshots if you didn't diss the
photography subreddit
sorry photography subreddit
i [ __ ] up man i don't know what
thank you adore pdp
so
can you please wish rob one a happy
birthday
happy birthday rob one have a great
from hannah hope your birthday is
very empty
say what you want about the japanese but
man they cannot build [ __ ] temples
without
getting them obstructed somehow
they just can't do it man
yeah that's cool i ain't hating
oh i have a question for you guys since
you asked before if i had question for
fans
what's something that you dislike that
everyone seem to like
thanks for inspiring me to play games
nice
some games are fun i kind of fell off
games for a while too
star wars taylor swift tick tock my hero
academia
nice uh fortnite
boring storyline same what
alcohol okay quantum theory
i just can't stop talking about quantum
theory guys
anime [ __ ] off how can you not like
anime
that's too broad that's like saying you
don't like movies
there's got to be some anime you can
like
i will not accept anime unless you see a
specific enemy
all right don't ever piss me off like
that again
i had my 29th birthday recently happy
birthday shamus
couldn't see your family oh that sucks
still like a great time spending day
with girlfriend watching your streams oh
that's awesome shammus
thank you for watching happy birthday
disney movies hmm
please elaborate on the joe roger thing
no that's today's video
that was the point so no way i can go
further away it's quite annoying
i feel like this will look prettier like
without me
uh simple and clean
you don't like lord of the rings can you
not
how can you not like how can you not
like lord of the rings
i needed an elaboration on that one
chief
is there any music that you are
interesting that you would recommend
not really i'm sorry
definitely that's good check them out i
don't know
lord of the rings is too long
myself doesn't like lord of the rings
either
i don't get it
just don't get it man
you've never seen lord of the rings
what the hell
is
i swear you guys i worry
i worry about you
you haven't either seen then go watch it
if you want a game that's amazing
screenplay hellblade
send a second fight also lord of the
rings
[Music]
it's more than big peep
at least read the books at least
please do yourself a favor
i'm gonna die here aren't they
i never watch or read harry potter quite
proud of this achievement
honestly that's that's like one you can
live without
i don't think it has that much
importance i know people love it and i
understand why but lord of the rings is
different
like you can talk there's no important
value out of harry potter let's get real
here
i don't like lord of the rings because
it's long and i don't like the genre
do you realize you're watching a live
stream we've been live for hours
where you literally could have watched
the whole trilogy while i'm sitting here
in my ass
explain yourself
you're going to need a better one than
that
uh uh uh
not really a fan of fantasy dude it's a
movie that
transcends the genres you don't have to
like fantasy to like
lord of the rings
next
everything is boring i said it then what
is exciting
for you guys [ __ ]
so i just killed their dog for no reason
get [ __ ]
so
[ __ ] i liked it more before
yeah it's like insanely over
if you clean that clean this up
fill in his sword it could be really
[Music]
cool
whoa jesus what a violent dog murder
[Music]
sorry
should i do a main mission i guess it's
been a while
i don't i don't like them
so much more fun this chill right around
right down the coast
this is gorgeous
[Music]
i want to take a screenshot you can't do
it
when are we gonna get some more
philosophy it would be very interesting
to hear your take on solar system marcus
aurelius tanaka epic dudes
yeah i know
i know thank you
no i'm an idiot
oh pretty
i like
he's saying my car from bethany what's
up sam's girlfriend bethany
what's cracking on them
i love this game it's so pretty
we killed them whoa did you see that
deer what the [ __ ]
[Applause]
i ain't falling for your tricks
now
it's too much bladder
that's not gonna do anything ugh
hmm
it had to be done it had to be done i'm
sorry
god i'm getting really tired guys
i'm sorry yellow this move she's best
friends yeah
kevin yeah i did it
kill an enemy using perfect parrot all
right let's do make this the last
mission
let's let's go perfectly
oh avatar i forgot all right let's watch
avatar yeah
let's do this and then avatar
homie doggy just be chilling
oh
my dog i saw you killing other dogs oh
no
i'm so sorry
sorry doggo
i'll make an apology video for your dog
don't make your dogs unsubscribe just
for that that's not fair
i've done a lot of good things for dogs
[Music]
ow
uh
okay we did it all right let's have a
tart time
let me just upgrade my techniques
my ghost [ __ ]
who's excited for avatar
we're just excited for a copyright
all right
what is your favorite lord of the rings
what is your favorite block in minecraft
well you see little timmy uh
third one probably my favorite first one
or the third one second
they're all good they're all [ __ ]
good what kind of question is that
avatar last airbender
episode one
we were flapping in the in the game
and then ever