hello friends
hello besties what's going on
[ __ ]
sorry i'm late sorry
i'm so sad
so sorry
i'm just turning on the lights
how about not screaming in our ears for
how's that start with that
how are you ah too bright don't like it
i don't know how these [ __ ] streamers
sit day in the night with
lights in their eyes it hurt it hurt my
eyes
so are we good oh right see this
forgot about that very cool where does
it look coolest
deadshot tambourine this is very it's
mirrored so it's awkward
there we go did you guys get yours
which number did you get
you guys complain about bright mode and
dark mode try sitting with
these lights in your eyes hello guys i'm
blind and then you go in like a dark
place in a video game what's up uh
what the [ __ ] was your name
uh deborah good name
well done hey pilch
hi from india me and my brother have
been huge fans for the last six years
shout out to ronak and makul verma
uh oh can you hear me so
i'm getting warning messages i'm not
sure what that's about
my mic is very loud yeah
is that better
bing bong
warning stream is [ __ ] loud
yes yes yes yes
i wonder why does it change if i do this
i don't think it should but let's try it
bing bong as i do sound check
bang ba i just realized i'm live you can
hear it
hi pewds can you say pink leaf pig lee
yeah i read every single comment all
right some people let's do this line and
close spaces
slashing my to call it better you see
ccst my voice can't hear bing bong
bing bong what stream can don't shout xd
bing bong hey hey
bing bong dong dong gamer moment
question mark potatoes bing bong stop ha
ha ha ha ha ha
great i always do a sound check in
swedish too
just to beat it
dispute it it's the only swedish i ever
taught brad throughout the years just to
beat it
what's up [ __ ] we're
[ __ ] streaming in the beat
i want to play the goddamn game what do
you guys want to do today should we
finish goes to tsushima
i think we're pretty close we can go in
go hard finish that [ __ ] boom and then
i'll do all the collectibles
on my spare time because i love it so
much
and then we can move on uh hello ignore
my name but hey yeah
all right ignoring your name hell yeah
pierce have you ever considered joining
the sem squad
uh no for [ __ ] sake what the hell epic
epic prince why why even ask
we're getting so many members now that
members mode is becoming uh
spam this is out of control
we need an apology bro i already [ __ ]
apologized
what do you want from me
i can't just keep apologizing that's not
happening
i'm not apologizing screw you guys
yeah you got nothing
donating until you notice god damn it
i've no
i noticed all the donations what are you
talking about gina
gina the splena i will
buy on ebay okay finally catching the
stream been watching since early days
amnesia
thank you alexandra good times
we need to play some more early day
amnesia
i feel like it's been a fan for seven
years i've just gotten my first official
play from freelancing
congratulations i want to donate to
charity
and help out oh my god
should i just make super chat charity
this is coming i don't know why some
people get it wrong will you
i mean thank you i'll be funny i don't
know will you ever do a meet and greet
if you want of course if you ever do a
meet and greet here in america
uh i have question mark what the [ __ ]
i was 10 minutes late drop the apology
act
um
i want to finish goes to sushma i think
uh i can't believe that you actually
replied
thank you thank you
now i'm just lost what do you guys want
from me
i got no i get no feedback
all i get is noise
you know what i'm saying you know i'm
saying [ __ ]
see what this is it's a goddamn video
game have you heard of that
so we're trying out something new here
today okay
we're doing streaming it's something
that the kids are into
where you play a video game live now
when i first heard about this i thought
cringe
no one's ever gonna watch that and i was
right
why the [ __ ] would you oh yeah it's
glitched here super annoying
this this quest is glitch for me i can't
can't do anything about it
yeah all right but we're finishing this
goddamn game
we're doing main quest only mother
yeah let's go can you guys hear it
because i can't
streaming that's cringe
they patched it bro i know i can't be
bothered downloading the patch what am i
a [ __ ]
patcher do i look like a guy that
downloads the patch
nah you tell me [ __ ] now get it right
the first time go to sushima
we're gonna get a 10 out of 10. now you
get a 10 out of 10 but
a little less respect from me
all right let me let me pull up so i can
hear the [ __ ]
the game as well i like hearing game all
right now i can hear the game
all right sweet home alabama
you may notice a little difference you
may notice little difference
that's right that's right all right
all right
i got the black knight what's up damien
bring in my
oh nice uh huh
you gotta teach your question how to
hold this liquor man you laughed you
lose this week
oh my god you keep asking i'm doing it
i'm doing it now back to the point i got
the black armor
looks cool right [ __ ] looks cool as
[ __ ]
nisakara been watching you for a long
time
always make me laugh thank you nishikara
rohan
got a new job lobby pierce see this is
uh my theory is correct
uh you just got to get all the kids when
they're young and then they'll donate
their
first paycheck to you this is working
i'm like mcdonald's
of happy wheels thank you i'm joking by
the way i really appreciate it um
it's [ __ ] dope isn't it
uh i also so my half bow doesn't look as
good as my long bow because the long bar
has the little
fluffy bit at the end uh i really like
those tangly little
bits at the end of the sword and they're
red on top
but i wish the tangly bits were red
because now it looks a bit
scattered you know what i mean kind of
cringe
not gonna lie because i give you money
can you go big screen face cam and point
at the camera yeah
or it's your boy bearcat i can do i can
do it without clicking because i can't
be bothered
it's your boy bearcat there you go
you're welcome
thank you bearcat what the [ __ ] oh yo
bearcat small peepee hey pigs do you
drink coffee in the morning dude i'm so
glad you asked that while i was talking
about armor in a video game
because i don't i don't drink coffee
because i eat
salted caramel porridge in the morning
and
coffee just doesn't go well with it even
though i do like coffee
so i hope we're clear on on this coffee
issue over here
is my consensus is i drink coffee and i
would like to but i do like salted
caramel porridge
more than i like so we're clear
are there any confusion if you guys have
questions
just like uh hit me up in the dms
actually just ask saib about the coffee
and he'll tell you
now what's more important about
my coffee drinking is which sword will
look
cooler with my armor this one
no this one no this one
no no no no
i thought maybe that would that's kind
of aesthetic
no oh
let's try that and it's called bish i
like that
have i ever been to sweden no sounds
like a terrible place
i'll never go to there's such foul lands
okay i think we got a new replacement
i think we got a new winner
yeah this is it i like how i went we
need to finish this game
and this is what i'm obsessing over
listen this is important you don't
understand it
oh that one's [ __ ] nasty oh and it's
got the
red dangly [ __ ] it's got the red dangly
bits i'm telling you
i wish i could get a oh i think that's
it i think that's it it's got the red
dangling bits
yeah what do you guys think
all right yeah i think that's it i think
that's what we're going for
all right uh main quest main quests got
it
i do want to get the armor though which
one is that it's not this one right
what am i missing for the arm request
all right
oh it's thundering sewed up
we got to get the con armor
sorry i was trying to study okay let's
do it
no one no one tell joe rogan that we're
alive right now
he's gonna crunch so hard please
please please please the mask isn't
shown in the
cut scenes mr omcharen cringe
i cringe at you on that's right i can
cringe back at you guys
epic
do i have to do this
i cringe at stealth quests whoever
invented stealth genre
i cringe at you i cringe at all of you
you were wrong
okay it's not fun all right where's the
fit the con this is the quest i want to
do and i can't track it now because
we're busy in the
main all right fine we'll have to do
this
all right i'll change armor to the ghost
armor even
how i play this i don't care if it's
better
game sound is too soft really
try this
did you get a haircut or are you balding
thank you hannah what a
nice question
hold up hold up hold up hannah hannah
do you see this hairline this is the
perfect hairline
okay yes it's a little thinner on the
side that's normal
that happens to everyone shut the [ __ ]
up hannah
small peepee i'm not insecure about it
he's balding oh god oh no
bald oh no
what have i done nice hairline hairline
of a god see there you go
some people get it it's because it's
this angle all right if i cared about
how i looked i would go like this i
would sit like this this is my good
angle
hey guys all right let me just play this
video game over here i don't
but i have to stand the comments like
hannah coming by i'm playing a game here
and i'm trying to play a video game here
we're not talking about my hairline
right now
we're no one no one brought it up
no one
i cringe at you you don't creatured me
hello i meant i got my first paycheck
from freelancing
see here's a nice person i plan to
donate most of it oh yes i'm dumb small
pp anyway
say hello they send love to martial
edgar and maya too see wasn't that so
was that so hard thank you
i thought i proved my hairline epic by
shaving my head
but i guess that's not enough
your fantasies can never be quenched
that was cringe but i was also imitating
cringe just to be clear
leaving for recruit training thank you
come back with 20 muscle increase
can you imagine being a scout and then
just like always keeping your back open
if i was a scout i'd have my back
covered at all times
boom sexy sexy
sexy
they really laid this out all out for
isn't it
oh could this be cool no i make a stupid
face don't i
i think you're in denial by your hair
i think you are dumb have you thought
i think you have a bad perspective on
life
i think you're wrong [ __ ] i can't be
bothered
could have been cool yeah yeah yeah i
like the soundtrack
can we kill
think they saw me well the quest failed
yeah i wasn't supposed to be seen my bad
i guess i'm not as stealthy as my
hairline huh
see i can make jokes i can make the joke
you can't
all right let's try that again
that's gotta feel bad i have a whole
[ __ ] sword through your body
you know me
man search for meeting was a great book
thanks for recommending why did you like
that
it's an important book
i think i can double kill these i have
the ability and i don't know how i do it
but i want to try
yeah did it
cool i never done that i missed the
funnel dog also could you give my friend
donald montana shout there you go donald
montana i hope you're watching hope
you're having a great life
thank you scott then i'm gonna have to
read quickly now because uh
game play and [ __ ] you know i mean
all the best yeah i said your name right
thank you very much
rg knows what's up all right where the
[ __ ] am i going
let's just say cell
oh i'm supposed to sneak in the lion's
house but we're so close
i think they saw me i'm in
i mean boys yes yes yes
in case you're just clicked on the live
stream i'm a new upcoming streamer
uh i've done the comedy in my spare time
for a couple years and then i dabbled
into music
uh i've done tv shows i've done all
kinds of crazy things
and now i have decided to become a pro
ghost to teach my player
so please become a member and we'll just
have like fun we'll just have fun and
chill we'll talk about nice
supporting body positive messages
about how everyone has perfect
hair lines and there's nothing wrong
with that and all this stuff like that
it's just positivity all around so
please come remember
uh zero death so far is my death count
uh we're doing a little it's a little
fun little thing we do
investigate the barrels the barrows
god damn it i [ __ ] up the quest
because i wasn't reading i thought i was
just letting it
all right i guess i invested to get
there barrows
goddamn barrels see uh for those who
are new that's an old joke from [ __ ]
years ago
all right
i know what's with all these barrels
all right we invent all right bros we we
investigated the barrels
now we just gotta reach the top of the
lighthouse bros
follow me bros yeah
all right climbing climbing climbing
bros ah more barrels
stinky barrels filled with poison ah
don't like the barrels okay we got out
away from the barrels
waves are okay i don't like barrows i
miss
out last period slo that ain't from
outlast
morgan get that [ __ ] out of here
that's bad reese yeah
okay bros we managed to do that quest so
far without
stupid barrels i made a gold stephanos
statue holding a barrel in creative
world minecraft epic
proud of you all right looks like we're
going to survey this area for more
barrels brows
okay i thought it was a barrel for a
second it was just a button
trapped inside my body trying to get out
save me save me guys
i'm trapped help me the barrel strapped
me inside this
boomer's body
this receding hairline boom her body
help me browse
he thinks he's still 20 years old it's
really cringey
what is he streaming someone said he's
gonna
sign up
that sounds exciting
i'll check it out later
i don't like the quests this game is so
much more fun when you're just riding
around doing stuff
that's when i have the most fun with it
at least like what did we just do
like that wasn't fun i didn't enjoy it
but i love the game i love how it feels
i love his looks
i love everything they captured with it
but the come on like
what was that i don't give a [ __ ] i know
that's my fault
by the way lost my family oh sorry to
hear that part
damn
gosh yes it's thrown out of the way all
right favorite game of the last five
years
i can't go from one comment like that to
another i don't know how to respond
i'm just sorry there that man favorite
game of the last five years
this one i'm probably under there i
don't know
last five years
uh two things any news about the shout
outs at the end of the video
coming very soon it's been the on the
back of mine we're working on it
and uh i don't know why the [ __ ]
merch isn't out yet i don't understand
why people can't just get it done
just get it done just put them up just
put them up
just put them up
um
just be patient it'll probably within a
week
oh i got a new gift
let's get the armor
i did a lot of side quests on this game
as well and
they are not good at all
the main quests are okay but
man it's so much more looking at that
i just want to look at that i want to
look at things and go ha look so pretty
your hairline and my grandpa go way back
nice one
man again also will you and marcia ever
visit australia once that virus is gone
uh my partner would love to meet you
both or watch your videos for years oh
thank you
um this is so far
if australia decides to come a little
closer then yeah i would definitely
consider it
should we kill some people it's been a
while
whoa what a sound
i don't understand all right here we go
nice camera angle
you run away from me bob
i don't have
i i played this game for hours and i
still don't understand when exactly i'm
supposed to parry
like after i see it or after he hits it
here let me show this now no it doesn't
work
now okay what was the difference
is it right as it takes
try again now
now
it's too slow that one i noticed i was
too sick but a lot of times i just like
i don't
get it there it is
confusing
you want some help buddy look he's
wearing a banana he's
trying to cover his hairline cringe
how low are we talking oh it's pretty
low uh if the mic starts sounding
like a robot just tell me all right
bro you're balding that's cringe bro
i kind of want to play sakura after this
game well i officially broke
but to be honest just feel like i had to
send this damn
please don't donate if you're broke me
and
this channel go way back
when i was we child of six
how far we come bros wait you watch this
channel when you were six years old is
that weird
tell me
do you have any product or beer all in
your beard
uh i don't [ __ ] with beard oil
i think uh that's uh like essential oil
you don't need that [ __ ]
i don't believe it sure it smells nice
what does he do what does it do to my
beard that it doesn't already do
beard
like 20 bucks i ain't gonna pay 20 bucks
for beard oil for oil for my beard
essential oils work okay bro sure
if they were so essential they wouldn't
be needed to be coal essential
ever think about that
it makes it softer i don't need my beard
is soft like a pillow i don't need to
make it softer
moist my beard up with a bunch of [ __ ]
no
hey pewter's got to go to work have fun
at work ryan
have a great day everyone i'll be back
i'll be here once you're back
you're [ __ ] dead bruh
that's not fair he has armor
that was clean dude
that was pretty clean
nice you're welcome
zach why thank you very much
what are we talking about beardo being
cringed
maybe it isn't i don't know i just don't
i don't really need it
it's like a conditioner what does it
really do
i don't believe it
if i have conditioner my hair alone okay
all right all right
okay cringe oil that's what you call it
on some real didn't you used to be
blonde when you started youtube
did your hair naturally change over time
uh
well if you want
it's complicated okay uh
my no one believes me when i say it but
my hair goes blonde
if i stay in the sun everyone thinks i
just have highlights or i'm trying to
pretend like it doesn't
and if you watch my first videos i'm
also very bronzed
or um yeah
like jenna marbles music video level of
bronze
because i was always out in the ocean
and [ __ ] like that
quick little funny edgy joke there haha
um
so yeah it just goes blonde i can still
do it if i do it now
but i just spent all my days inside now
like a real man just might ever tell you
to shave
she thinks it's a little long
i think she's a little wrong
you know i'm saying
this looks like some nice little cabins
mine goes red in the sun yeah mine does
too i have a little bit of
um soulless dna in me
i'm not shaving this time i'm gonna let
it grow to the floor
all right watch this
no what the [ __ ] how i'm
[ __ ] i'm almost i'm dying of poison
oh [ __ ] it tastes really bad i have to
kill something really quick [ __ ] i'm
gonna die
i'm gonna ah poison now i have zero
deaths
this is impossible
oh he died oh i did it i did it
oh i almost died for you in your shitty
hairline god damn it
this is not fair that was so
embarrassing
could have died dude we've been playing
48 hours and i haven't died and that was
so oh he's oh you're still oh yeah
how does that feel
that was [ __ ] clutch apparently
there's a little dog alive still
hello doggy goodbye doggy the last of us
how dare you make me kill dog
bye bye you're gone wait what the [ __ ]
is left
someone isn't dead this is hurting my uh
i see
you [ __ ] bye
epic
yeah yes love it or hate it
you're looking at people see
a lever action why jay are you on drugs
what the [ __ ] are you talking about
thank you though
i'm a [ __ ] you then
clutch king yeah baby
yeah but you told me not to do it oh
there's a dog
okay guys look away from the stream
okay guys look back on stream just shave
edgar and paste on head problem solved
that's actually helpful thank you
finally someone being helpful just
killed the con
all right can i help you now dude big
fan since barrel days hell yeah
battle still they still going though
scam angle
nice sorry i gotta change my uh
battery on these i'll just be one sec
i also got to put on the old ring
because i forgot about it before and
it's not weird it happens that's not the
reason
uh
that's not the reason i
stopped
it's [ __ ] good what's good what's the
problem
legit yeah could it be fuller yes
uh oh hold up i'm gonna change the
battery once
bing bong we're back in action
um
does it bother me no no it doesn't
hey
not one bit and you know why
because in real life you saw me and you
comment about my hairline
[ __ ] i smash you
that will actually dampen
what you say ah i wouldn't say that my
faith
but you're hiding you're hiding because
you're spraying
see i eat protein
twenty percent muscle and cream what
happened like i never
i'm legit addicted to these these are so
[ __ ] good
why have i gone 30 years in my life and
not eating salted caramel before
if god was a flavor it's salted caramel
so good
oh
is mcdonald's better than sweden italy
or japan or uk
bottom uk for sure it's [ __ ]
maybe it's gotten worse over the year i
don't know
next up italy it's not bad but
it's not great but not terrible either
sweden it's all right
holy [ __ ] is so good
i said this before right but
i ordered something at mcdonald's in
japan and um
sorry really chewy my bad
afterwards the lady came out looking
really distraught and be like
sorry i'm like oh great maybe they
didn't have the order or something
she's like you have to wait two minutes
i'm like
yeah that's that's fine i can wait two
minutes
it was so funny
i'm so used to like sorry we messed up
your order or
sorry something went wrong you'll have
to wait it's like sorry i have to wait
two minutes
we're so sorry it's okay
hey if it's been watching sentence
around the time you and marcia first
met love seeing you and your humor
evolve
as mine did over the years that's cool
man thank you just bought
some 100 ml gang merch thank you
teammate i like that merch it's cool
oh i have an epic rant for you guys um
and i'm curious what your thoughts on
this is because it bothers me a lot
and it's the how long it takes to eat
out if you go to a lunch place in uk
or anywhere in europe i would say for
that matter
you have to wait so long
like it almost makes me not want to go
out and eat because it do
you just have to wait so long whereas in
japan i know cringe japan is great
and it gets old to hear it but it's so
fast it's so fast
and you just you just want your food i
just want my food i just want my food
i don't want to wait for my food i want
my food right away i sit down
i don't want to wait more than it takes
for my chair to cook a meal
that's the criteria
where the [ __ ] is his mongol armor piece
rescue hostages assassinate an enemy
from above
i gotta do that
it's just because we went to a sushi
place and we were there for i swear
almost an
hour and in japan
i mean it's uncomparable this service
incomparable whatever the english is not
to mention the fact that you don't have
to wait so long
i don't i don't understand why why does
it take so long
did he hurt him
out
we got any cool pictures from us i feel
like i saw manny but i was too late to
all right let me see what you guys
thought about it
so she's worth the wait here
chick-fil-a's got his son well that's a
franchise i'm just mentioning like
any restaurant you go to the uk you
still have to wait a pretty long time
the food is good so it's worth it so we
still go but
it seems like i was like okay why don't
why don't someone create a restaurant
um with the same principle here in uk
but it seems like people just don't mind
waiting like they go out to eat to just
sit down and
that's part of it simp grind is still
going have a good
thank you tony appreciate it
i sound like a karen why because i want
my food fast
like every person ever
hey look at leg though god damn that's
some photo mode moment right there
i cannot find this [ __ ] mongol [ __ ]
maybe it comes from the oh it comes from
the leader once we're done with this
quest isn't it
thoughts on slow walking person their
worst
they're the worst they're the worst
thing worse
slopes slow-moving people i can get
around slow-moving people at airports
needs to be uh escorted out like they
need to be treated like terrorists
because they are and i'm tired of
pretending that they're not where is
this guy
oh nice
you're in an airport you can't walk slow
you have to go to the side otherwise
i know the rules be conscious around the
people around you
there are more people in the world
you're a terrorist get away
worse i'm so glad you brought that up
if you're a slow-moving people person at
an airport
i don't care how good of a person you
are or how big of a fan
you will be treated like terrorists that
you are
mental terrorists
the escalator stand on side thing is a
bit controversial though
now that's really interesting because if
everyone just
stood next to each other at the
escalator it would actually go quicker
as opposed to
uh have the people standing on the side
so in some ways i find it a bit annoying
this rule that you have to stand on the
side
especially when it's really busy because
it would actually go quicker if everyone
just stood next to each other
because there's more space being filled
but i digress whatever it's called
english i don't speak it
alright we got another piece sweet
ew who even goes into public yeah
i know that's not a carrot you guys
don't know what a cairn is if you think
that's a karen cringe
you guys are cringed now i cringe in you
speak with apprentice what am i doing
here
that's so far
noise
anyone i don't agree with is a karen
apparently yeah
no making society better chad that's
what that's called
people that decorate their houses really
ugly too
terrorist you're done
you're done you're out anyone else it's
not a karen that's making society better
chad chad society mean that's what that
is
what else annoys me people's ass cracks
if i see your ass crack you're done
i want to see that [ __ ] you're out snip
snip peepee snip you get you get
escorted out
choke hold whatever you do it i don't i
don't hurt people
clearly i'll pay people to hurt you
though
uh this is if i'm a dictator basically
if you're a ass crack grad scene in
public
two guys will or girls we're a
progressive uh nation of course
we'll come out and uh
what am i talking about they'll pull
if you mess up the people get smaller
yeah i'm making this up as i go but i
actually it actually makes a lot of
sense now that
it's coming out of my mouth i actually
oh i got the armor hey
just a wee bit i don't like it that much
maybe if we change color on it i'll go
to the
uh black color merchants
what else annoys me um
bad design yeah bad design in general
really pisses me off i talked about this
many times before
but yeah designers that uh either focus
too much on design
and too little on utility or too much on
utility
and totally a little on design uh
ppsnipped it's gone
we're an aesthetic based society we
value art
not art because artists cringe obviously
but aesthetic looking
uh things i would i don't know how to
phrase that really but you know what i
mean
uh
yeah let's try the white dye first
like people dressed really ugly yeah
people get snipped
if you dress bad is that you're done
it's more about how you interact with
the world that's why art is cringe
because
art doesn't help the world
so you want to slowly castrate people to
keep them in line
yeah what do we do with about the women
i never thought about this
i didn't really
oh come on they don't give you an armor
die for
for this one seriously
what about the black armor i think it's
here somewhere
you're an artist for a living
so you can't dye this armor
i hate it it's so ugly yeah i mean
oh
should i buy this while i'm here
that was cool too if i get a good hat to
it
that looks pretty good too but i don't
want it
uh what in the world did you just try
and say captain because i can't read
that
even that looks cool
okay let's upgrade the armor then i've
been saving it for a long time
so i should have a lot of upgrades
available
yeah seven jesus
alright what else bothers me if perfect
utopia that i
created
loud noises in general so that's a
boomer
yeah you're not allowed to have certain
decibels
over different things right
uh motorcycles you get the full
castration
what the [ __ ] is that mask
this is swordsman armor is inside
but i'm loud yeah yeah now now i am but
not in my new society
my new utopian
so what does this do major increase
health reduces all damage by major
amount disguises you while out of combat
massively reducing mongol detection
speed
this is a really good armor
i just hate how it looks
um i don't want to wear it
let's upgrade the ghost armor
that was pretty cool actually
max
can we not upgrade the mongol armor
interesting you can't do it
resolve gain ghost deal 50 more damage
strike an enemy with ghost weapon causes
the enemy to deal
no that's not good
i don't like him i feel like i should
upgrade this
one
look at me what the [ __ ] am i wearing
soccer's armor is the best looking facts
excuse me what the
[ __ ] am i wearing
whoa it's a monkey mask
that looks kind of cool
oh i like them golden one
all right let's check out the ghost
armor
which one is the ghost summer
that was kind of cool
that was kind of cool too
wow
i like that let's do that
look guys i'm nina
it is maxed out
so my phone keeps going on
clearly i ran past her what the [ __ ]
you can get a trophy for dressing up
like sly cooper
because they made that game no no
play-free bird what is that
species
i have to upgrade ghost one more really
no i did it
i definitely upgraded it really did i
[ __ ] up
lorena bobbitt times i don't know what
that means
i forgot the color too you're right [ __ ]
i'm an idiot
[ __ ] oh god damn it
people who don't use turning signals
yeah yeah they get a peeper snip thank
you for adding that
i forgot about that
oh you're right i didn't upgrade it
yeah the ghost ghost one looks better
can i talk to you really quick
great now i can't upgrade [ __ ] sake
yeah that looks way cooler
where the [ __ ] did she go
there you are what the hell stop running
i missed a rocket launcher damn
whoops all right now we get to pick one
i'm picking the white one
uh because uh should i pick the white
one or the black one
no you're not even black cringe why
white horse yeah they said entire
journey last time as well but they
[ __ ] lied
i know this is really annoying and uh i
don't care
i don't care
i don't care i don't care
that was really cool which mask should i
wear with this
i think it looks so [ __ ] cool
and then what we do now that we have
jurgen he can wear this
see that's aesthetic
is
i swear i spent half the game going
through customization
it's just a little bit i think that one
fits better
i gotta ride all that way [ __ ] that
ultra
you need the ghost armor for this
mission god
no come on white psychiatry
physique aesthetic
white knight simp yeah sure
wait this is not where we're going
what's cooler than white knight why
can't i get on my [ __ ] horse
a useless horse
you're gonna have trouble because it's a
stealth mission excuse me
that one sells better than me
can i have my horse back
this is the most annoying mission in the
game super style really
uh looking forward to it i'm going to
zoom call jack
black on thursday about my bet hey well
tell him i said hi
i am not going in the right direction am
i cringe
here we go
i also cannot kill anyone no
whoa here we go
stay safe stay strong stay floor gang
you said it well stetson
well done
use arms and charms armor and charms
yeah
if it's that annoying i'm definitely
doing that
yuri
all right this is a good chance for me
to prove to you guys once and for all i
am really good
at stealth missions watch me do this
everyone said it's really difficult
watch me do it on the first try
[ __ ]
okay
watch me do it on the first try
what's happening
without the ghost armor dun
i'm actually i'm actually i won't say
i'm happy
jurgen died but i'm happy i have the
white horse because i actually wanted
the white horse
to match me so i'm it's not it's not
that i'm happy it's more like
uh conflicting emotions jurgen number
six is uh
i'm happy with the argument number six
but i'm still sad
that yoga number five died stealth zero
shut up
you haven't even started yet
okay where do i go
what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] dude
can i oh i can jump okay
oh close
uh will i do more collabs with
jacksepticeye well i
am jacksepticeye so that'd be kind of
cringe if i didn't
have you ever seen us in the same room
together i don't think so
hope that answers your question bro all
right
it's good i'm wearing the white armor
it's like extra stealth if you wear
white because you can't see white in the
dark
if i attack the guards it will chrome a
monster they think i am not
all right i guess i can't kill them that
means i can't use the wind charm either
there because they have a poison on them
because i upgraded them new technique
available
all right all right all right
have i finally done it no we have these
i didn't see them
otherwise we're almost maxed out
see i wish i could just have it selected
right
you can make a quick change
it's a bit of a flaw in the game to be
honest
because now i have to change these as
well
oh wait i don't have to have that
oh my god we're sort of the stealth ones
i don't know
where are they there
my god
there we go he's ready
what does one have to do to become a
moderator nothing
just be really sexy
huge pp as well
all right this is very easy so far not
gonna lie kind of cringe
obviously they want us to swim at this
part
all i do is swim swim swim no matter
what
oh my god you guys struggled on this ben
yikes
uh let's have the wind chimes ready
beard says everything hell yeah classic
classic videos we watched
some of those last time it was fun i
wish i knew where i was going
that way yes
uh i suppose i have to go
there
i don't know
oh we were here before what the [ __ ] why
are we back
no more milk huh
what oh but i oh
uh stealth hundred thank you
no
are you serious
wait a minute wait a minute
where am i now
why is the wind telling me to go out
oh my god he teleported me
yeah i would love to play dark souls i
love dark souls my favorite game [ __ ] i
[ __ ] that up
don't fall down the waterfall
i just got platinum on this game 20
minutes ago
hell yeah i don't know what that means i
think i was supposed to jump here
i have this i have this thought
nice
so we're literally going the same way as
last time this is so easy
we got smoking sarah that's so far feels
good as well
i don't mean to rub it in that but you
guys are probably not very good at video
games
i don't want to make you guys feel bad
or anything but uh i'm probably
a little better than you man
i i would probably cringe really hard if
i watched you guys play a video game
it would be tough for me to backseat
game because uh
i would just feel bad the whole way
through
i'm being you yeah you see how annoying
that is
you understand now
okay where
all right should i go in here you can't
see me he can't see me i might miss him
i'm a shadow in the night
i am a shadow in the night
and night oh yeah we already stopped
here i forgot about it
where's the ladders around the corners
you think they up their security after
what happened last time you know what i
mean
because you're a huge inspiration so i
made my own jaws cars
hopefully oh cool hell yeah
dope
all right we gotta get in his private
quarters this time
oh man we're going in there that's kind
of cool
this could actually be fun how about
that
okay so they fixed a lot of their
security flaws from last time huh
yes we have to prove
we fight with honor
uh can i get up there how does it look
like
they can't see me i'm invisible
you didn't see me but here i am
ghostmaster64
i've got all the achievements in every
single video game ever made
sonic the hedgehog's favorite foot is
chili dogs
really thank you ma miss salty giggles
i'm glad you told me that
play flute they will fall asleep
[ __ ] they don't let you that's funny
you can't play fluid on a stealth
mission how am i gonna make them fall
asleep
oh gosh uh do you think you'd ever do
engineering again when you're old
random chinese dude bro have you not
seen my minecraft red
redstone engineering videos
that's some top level engineering not
getting any better
oh [ __ ] he almost saw me
can't see me i'm invisible
you didn't see me but here i am [ __ ]
they definitely see me
where am i supposed to go
is there not a ladder oh it's right
there
foreign
good
you have night go all the way to the top
all right all right all right
am i just walking in circles now [ __ ]
you didn't see me you didn't see me but
here i
am laddermaster64 i assume i had need to
enter in this
assume i have to enter here
now's my chance to get up there my dude
there's a guy right there
you didn't see me uh excuse me guys
don't detect me but uh have you guys
seen the
have you seen the ladder oh it's right
here i found the ladder guys thank you
don't worry about it keep
not detecting me thank you
i grabbed that loot and run and then
they need to get the
my pee pee grow forever
it's my birthday i woke up to watching
your livestream happy birthday armani
hell yeah yeah hell yeah happy birthday
man
dude my birthday hasn't been in so long
it's like everyone's birthday all the
time when it's my birthday you know what
i'm saying
what do you do what do i do
all right we're going up
should i go in there i feel like i
should oh there's a ladder
flip flop
yes yes yes yes yes going to the top
yes yes yes yes should i stream on my
birthday
then everyone have to uh birthday say
happy birthday
that is my turn oh yeah happy birthday
armani boom that was a lot of
good [ __ ] right there [ __ ]
all right i'm at the top now what oh
almost see me you didn't see
me but here i am almost on top master
64.
can i go in the ladder please
go below yeah i figured but
leave the message where they can see it
must be here right
oh yeah it's ken's birthday today
mr b's birthday
it's also my birthday today so it's
whatever
no wait my it's not my birthday sorry i
forgot
it could be if i
was born in a different day it would
have been my birthday
it's also jacksepticeye's birthday and
your mom's birthday so
remember remember that that'd be awkward
forget your mom's birthday
yes all right looks like i did the
the thing that was so difficult
uh was that so hard
i see what you mean though i'm not
trying to roast you guys all the time
like you guys always wish me uh i do
hate stealth quests uh it would have
been
normal for me to not like that
all right speak to you now where is she
unison
it's jaws cause again your fans are
amazing they just gave me 15 subs
that's so sweet you guys are so nice
all right back to aesthetic gear
sucker yeah
yes lovely lady looking at me
and oh my bad see it looks so good
yes i keep forgetting where it is it's
here
oh god i have so many uh
that's pretty good let me try that one
second
that's pretty good i need that and then
the last one will be
that's pretty dope all right we're good
thanks for waiting shrek has big pits
why they're my reading chat
because you were half away across the
map jesus
is there any video game is there like a
database of video game characters
birthdays
so
so today is
uh oh god there's a lot of birthday
august eight
oh my god there's so many anime
characters birthday today
i gotta show this
what the [ __ ]
all right i i don't recognize any of
these
how do they know
oh there's the attack on titan guy's
birthday at least i know him
but look dude who are
oh that one girl in naruto chocho
akimichi nice good to know
uh quinn the snake's birthday is today
that's pretty wait
it's not august 8th um wait what am i
saying it's august 2nd
oopsie sorry guys oh rio's birthday
nice uh jeremiah
orange birthday that's pretty cool
i guess what i'm saying is you guys
aren't very special
okay here we go someone made a [ __ ]
tumblr post
august 2nd
no way big titties
epic
okay yamato
i i don't know who he is and i watched
it
all right well i guess you live and you
learn you know what i mean is it tyga's
birthday today
from toradora no where
no you [ __ ] lie
you got me all excited
god damn god damn you guys
speak with your allies and i'm good
we heading out boys
is this the last quest i think this
might be the last
different tiger
out on netflix now if you guys never saw
that anime it's it's
pretty damn good i recommend it
where is [ __ ] unit
it's jojo it's a dog birthday no it
isn't
that chocolate or coffee chewing gum
eating some of them
does it not let me do the mongol armor
still
ugly
foreign
title about people needs to beat master
women's smasher
it's iggy's birthday today no it isn't
it isn't i would have seen it
i'll let you cry that episode with paul
nareth
so good where is she
i just want to go god
am i blind
i'm wearing the wrong mask and no one
told me
so pretty
this is annoying the [ __ ] out of me
are they in the building
nice one bradley very nice
i guess i'll talk to them
oh yeah it's science birthing make sure
you say
thank you
am i blind jesus how did i not see her i
as the wind was blowing through what are
you doing here
why why are you here
can't you just be at the same spot
come on that's a that's a simple move i
ain't doing that [ __ ]
i'm a samurai not a simple right yeah
that's right paulo
degree
i watched prison school episode
11 yesterday if you've seen it it's the
funniest
[ __ ] and i reacted to it before it's
this part where
how do i explain it the ma the guy has
to explain
even though he's a boob guy he prefers
boobs he has to explain why he prefers
butts over boobs
uh to the principle of the school
because the principal of the school
is a butt man and they're about to get
expelled so he has to prove that he's a
butt man
because any butt man the man that likes
butts can't be bad
so he goes through this epic rant it's
so funny
why butts are better because of
evolution
because we used to walk on four legs so
we would look up on
butts they are the source of everything
good
it's so funny and it gets so worked up
talking about why butts are superior
that
the principal just starts hugging him
it's okay
i used that scene to convince my wife to
watch it wow
all right here we go epic video games
this should be epic this is the end so
let's get into this [ __ ]
whoa
well i [ __ ] up
you [ __ ]
damn she's a badass
i was trying to be moonstone
general
why won't you die
oh this is cool we're all going together
i like that
nice
okay where are they
oh
i can never learn
not ishikawa
gotta have my bro bro get up bro stop
sleeping
he said manga that's so cool
yes oh that was cool [ __ ] i should
nice
i hope there's more fighting [ __ ] yeah
this is so epic
hey games what are they doing what are
they doing
that's right we are saved
even though i would probably puke the
[ __ ] out all over it
i don't know samurai
it is not the way
oh god it's one of these [ __ ] all right
i guess i don't go
where the [ __ ] am i going
i know my body is nowhere
that almost ended in a cringe here we go
this way
sarah that's gotta keep it gotta keep it
so far
you know what's really tempting to use
here
these
i think i'm not supposed to fight right
now i'm just supposed to
go up high
thank you ray ray breathing is something
i never actually thought about that but
yeah needing oxygen
you're technically in need of someone
else when real chads are completely
independent
so i have to agree with you on that one
chief
uh is this not high enough i need to go
higher
can i fight my way there because that's
more fun
dammit
do it again do it
there you [ __ ]
how
what up
oh i've always wanted to get that one
it's not a cool background
maybe we changed
it's a bad angle i should get it another
time
kind of like art huh
you know i was joking come on you know i
was joking
you must have known
guess time of day doesn't make much
difference here
cool
imagine getting stabbed cringed nice
poor dude has been impaled for half a
minute
whoa that's it
ah we got big boy
how does it feel to be a big boy huh
oh you big boy
oh you're not so big now are you big boy
uh why would you why would you donate
that ander
what's wrong with you
man you guys are confusing
i was was a worn car and i forgot what
my mission
anders lying all right fair enough it's
still annoying
i like if it's true or not i still find
it annoying
sorry i know maybe you didn't mean bad
but don't
don't just don't do that no spoilers
come on even if you're joking
whoa whoa i didn't know i could do that
[ __ ] that was cool
whoa
did he just say finland
oh you [ __ ] [ __ ]
i don't have flame [ __ ] well catch it
go to sleep [ __ ] that was sweet
[ __ ]
almost died [ __ ]
i slice [ __ ]
who's doing that
where are you no fascia for you man
ass over titties ray ray
nice thank you sweden is not cringe yeah
you're right it is
it's time
damn he's got a drink out of that big
ass bowl i want a big ass bowl
bonjour
don't put this on me push-up time
i don't squeeze the balls why would you
do that
oh ow
ow
let's go let's do this i'm pumped
oh god it got right into it uh which is
saying
i guess wind stains all right uh
okay that's that's oh god
okay i almost died i think i did die i
could spend three results to come back
hey what's up
she says jesus
what is he jesus [ __ ]
uh don't kill me please i'm swedish
sweden is cringe swedish
swedish oh wow
uh all right i guess i'll have to learn
the movement
i think i need to change my charms as
well
what the [ __ ] is his move set
he just does whatever he wants
this is not gonna work uh deal bonus
damage yeah that might be good
what's better here
that for sure
can i i don't need
guess that it's not even gold then
maybe that
that's pretty good yeah
uh mongol armor
go in moon stains all right let's try it
oh my god yeah i can hit him
that was cool
no moon sounds was definitely
the right sense
definitely a lot easier come on
let's go
how do i dodge the last one
how do i dodge that
not better
jump to just oh i can jump
some say i can't jump i think i just
have to jump you're right
i've never done that all right fine
thank you
oh jump in there
that's not good
that's the jump
who took damage there me or him
is
i gotta i gotta block more because that
increases my resolve and i start up with
so little
that's the jump one i should know that
by now
let's try a flurry
come on
jump [ __ ]
he does not care about your flurry yeah
i should stop doing it it doesn't work
it's so cool
oh nice
not too bad
did i just
i blocked i blocked oh god
give me a little bit more resolve and i
can do this
that's the jump one [ __ ]
jesus
now
oh ah
my eyes
my eyes my precious eyes
i can't use canis let me
he's cheating
do i have to redo the hole no oh i
didn't have them selected here we go
slice and bites all right gotta stop him
uh actually i get result points if i
stab you
there we go i get result points you see
oh
i need to charge my results oh no more
fast shot dude
i don't [ __ ] think so my dude
no fascia no far shot
no for sure oh yeah no one gonna flush
off
yeah oh he's got a
[ __ ] god was it that big before [ __ ]
that's it
finish here this will be easy
uh let's do it cool
shoot him in the foot
works every time
my dude is nasty [ __ ] yeah
where you going where you going oh it's
gone it's gone
where you going mr khan
you fight with no honor [ __ ]
[ __ ] get grease [ __ ]
you fight with zero deaths
i am the one the way i don't don't need
the hey face man
how's your face now face man
you want to flash on me no one can flash
that that box
ow
jesus all right it's getting a little
bitsy in here
okay
jesus don't hurt me swedish
the [ __ ]
all right you're hurting my feelings all
of you
oh sorry about that thank you
whoa big boy
jesus
show me your face
guess not he's shy
oh that's a con i didn't realize
whoa ah sick
can you not do that
who's the fascia guy huh are you the guy
that yells fascia
stop it
who's yelling fascia there will be no
fascists
there will be no fascists
all right where's the khan
wait for his sword to go out
does he not go out
that's gotta hurt a little bit
that's gotta hurt
i know you hurting man i know you
hurting
oh
boy we did it too
easy oh that looks [ __ ] nice
oh i wish i could snapshot that [ __ ]
photo time
damn that was cool
[ __ ] yeah let's go
nice nice nice nice nice
we died zero times we did it guys
get fluted mr khan as soon as i get the
option to play the flute i'm playing the
flute dude
nice
game of the year game of the decade
i felt my muscles increase as i played
it
there's more what else is that i would
kill it
oh oh yeah we got a simple
no i don't need it anymore my name is
khan and i don't know how i feel you're
killing khan sorry colin
you have a cool name though
there's suit
another boss no
i went all out just this once
we gotta find our uncle is that it no
what is it
what is it don't spoil it but what is it
temple all right what do we got
no spoilers no spoilers
awkward
jargon returns
abby comes out
foreign
that
nice felt good to take that one off
oh we're almost
maxed out so what's next
we did that all right kaze
we got some gifts
key jeans blood that sounds cool
what does it look like so apparently
there's something else to the game
i don't like that oh that's kind of dope
should be
whoa what the [ __ ] what what quest is
left
i did it what are you smoking are you
guys trolling me
check out my village uh where's that
again it's soft isn't it yeah
yeah okay oh
oh
i've got a flute [ __ ]
we fluted a lot of people on this
journey
but this flute most of all goes out to
my man
shadow jurgen
he was like a father to me
the gods are not angry are not happy
about the loss of jurgen
sup tonight
we have our final quest ahead what will
happen
will there be another boss fight we
don't know
this thunder's weather seems appropriate
for our last little bit
oh geez
how are they still people like this land
i'm too strong for you batus
let me check this box ah [ __ ] what the
hell
let me check this box
cool uh
where are we going i don't know about it
no one
this way
hey oh okay it is defining it is the
last boss
are you winning pills yeah we're almost
at the end of the game dad
i think a red armor will be good for
this fight
i think that would look cool
yes
they have to bow usually something
happens if there's a sign in your bow
yeah they got fishes
what's up fishes
they like my song don't they
this is not the doc
i'll do a screenshot during the battle
if there is one
so emma wait on the dock for your uncle
excuse me where is the dock
it's here it's over here
oh i have to press to win okay
oh i am playing oh
all right i think this might be a really
cool screenshot i'm going to record this
you think you're an artist feels cringe
i'm contributing to society
you understand
i wish he was still moving during this
part
because that would have been a cool
screenshot i almost like this without
him
just like nature oh this is pretty
i quite like this
this looks good and without me like a
screen saver or some [ __ ]
no filter just nature at its rawest form
i posted a wallpaper engine uh
once i did people like them they're in
the members only chat though
all right let's try to get with
oh this filter
yeah i think that's enough filters
i forgot to take a screenshot great
no filter challenge oh
no
gin
better than the last of us you [ __ ]
back
foreign
damn
here we go last bit wow it looks so
pretty
[ __ ] and it's not even upgraded
damn this looks good if only i could
have my red armor
is that too much to ask
ah look at that tree dude
so we're not fighting i thought for sure
we were gonna fight
what's the point of this
foreign
where is this
okay i won't be reading donations now i
want to just focus on the game thank you
i can't yeah i do kind of want to go
back and look at the tree again i'm not
going to lie
i'm regretting a little bit
glad we got to do that a quick time
event
social
is it who's gonna become the ghost is he
trying to
pretend i'm confused
foreign
is this guy for real
um
are we back at the tree
thank god
damn damn
damn the game looking good though
i love this i wish the story was more
so like you can feel it
i'm full screening this i don't even
read the chat and [ __ ]
foreign
ah
damn this is good
foreign
here we go oh
the pressure playing on hard mode is
difficult
can you imagine the tension
how you almost feel in your gut
having to fight against someone like you
don't want to
sure
so i'm actually going to record this
because that looks [ __ ] nice
and then i can loop that and have as a
background
just give me 10 seconds sorry i'm
actually
ruining this moment by making a
wallpaper yes
just run away you don't understand
honor cringe just run away
so
oh god damn it that looks so good too
must not make wallpaper must not make
more paper
the time has come
hey
foreign
why he gotta go against his uncle like
that
yeti
this is so dope
nice
i actually do get to do the fight or not
oh wait i get to do the fight
what you don't understand is i'm too
strong
i studied the blade with you son
what the [ __ ] i blocked all of those
what happened there all right guess this
will
take a little while i would be cool to
do it on the first try
there it is
i try to do that
um
oh come on yes
uh
you were like a father to me
the warrior's death
more your staff obviously
always that would just you that would
disgrace him so badly otherwise
to let him live is to die anyway
he's okay
it looks like i picked the choice that
no one wants you guys don't you guys
don't understand
my tails
damn
he was all about honor it was all his
whole character was about it
it totally fit
i didn't understand why that was even a
choice
and it was also his way to finally obey
honor which is what he wanted his son to
do anyway i know he wasn't his son
so he makes sense it's a sweet ending if
you think about it
sucker punch well done
i would not spare him if i played it ten
times more
that was the good ending i'm serious
beautiful i actually really really like
that ending a lie
even though i i wasn't on board with
this story a lot of times
that was an incredible ending so good
i love that i wish there was more of
that
you made the right choice especially in
their culture right yeah
totally fit
i don't doubt a second it's noisy great
game that's so much fun
i'm actually going to keep playing it
because i want to get all the
unlockables and [ __ ]
i'll probably 100 it just because i
think it's so pretty and i just enjoy
playing it i've been playing a ton of it
on my own
doing side quests and just looking at
shrines and [ __ ] it's so fun
it's a long time ago since i enjoyed a
game like that
uh i loved it i could could it
definitely could have been better uh
there's a lot of things to improve but i
that makes me excited if they do a
sequel like
so cool
i'll probably give an eight and a half
almost a nine
very close to a nine eight point nine
it goes eight out of ten but game of the
year anyway yeah i can see that
you get a better house if you spare him
yeah well you get a worse ending if you
spam
uh thanks to everyone for watching and
uh being here it's so fun doing these
uh live let's plays i love it
back to gaming we're bringing back to
the roots
the way i saw it killing him was a
contradiction to dean's character
yeah i i thought about that too but i
saw it as he's doing what
his uncle wanted him to do all along
he's fulfilling that wish
when one of them have to die
he's going with what he wanted all along
which is to follow the way of honor
even if it wasn't a samurai anymore it
was a one last
decision to do it for him which is a
tough decision to make
but it's the one he wanted so i think it
was a
beautiful ending that's great
there's another scene after the credits
i'll wait
if you replay in slow-mo you can catch
us we've gassing shut up
i'm not like ellie all right i'm not
just gonna let him go in the end
all right
well done i don't know how they made a
game so pretty
i don't know how they did it it's so
good
it's crazy how just a game looking nice
makes you want to play it i've never
i mean obviously there's a ton of pretty
game that i liked playing but
just graphically it it was a while ago
you're like whoa
i love this i want to be part of this
world i don't even care if it's just
running around doing [ __ ] i'll actually
really like that
thank you name i'm glad you agreed we
don't always have to agree on the
choices but
i feel strong about it what i did
and i know i mean last of us last of us
yeah uh
if i if someone asked me like which game
do you recommend this one or the last of
us um
there's no doubt this is a game you can
have so much more fun with
last it was just dreary and annoying
like comparing it to this my god
why was it so like uh maybe last of us
came out in a bad timing or something
that man
looking back at that just gives me like
makes me angry makes me sad
it's too much man
not much of a gamer and i completely
skipped this generation of consoles but
this place
was truly a pleasure to watch thank you
so much gt i'm glad you enjoyed it
that's great
props to
naughty dog for making a bad game so we
could make i'm just kidding i'm joking
that's rude last of us wasn't two wasn't
bad it was just wasn't the game
anyone wanted
what's next
i want to play dark souls or sakura
or maybe even god of war since i never
actually finished it but
we'll see
dark souls 3 in case i didn't say that
i might do a poll and we'll see which
one of those three gets more votes
yeah i remember when i started playing
god of war i was so excited to play it
i don't know why i was so like i guess i
was really busy at the time i was
in japan at the time it just didn't feel
right for me to start a
let's play i like the soundtrack it's
nice
now if i can stream it it's more fun
to share i enjoy this so much more
personally i enjoy playing games like
this more as a let's play formula
your playthrough games were equally epic
hell yeah
it was fun to play last of us i had some
great moments
i think last of us probably wins in a
lot a lot of the details
of the design of the graphics
like fingers and that kind of stuff look
way more like
that's kind of stuff i kind of miss on
this i want the fingers guys
all right i'll do a vote witcher 3 i'll
add that to the list
because i always wanted to play that as
well here we go there's one more scene
one last screenshot well played man
comfy viewing yeah it was
it's a comfy game i'm wearing the white
uh ghost armor
aesthetic i like it
yeah you better be sorry
i'll do a poll right after cause then i
feel like i get answered
the house is really shitty i'm not gonna
lie
uh
do the poll before end the stream can i
do that
uh is there any point it's like oh here
we go i hit the map and what the [ __ ]
whoa what the [ __ ]
yeah i know there's a couple left
do i have to do that now or
why is it telling me so dramatically
i never discovered that what the [ __ ]
go inside the house oh god why did i do
that
damn the ghost armor is white looks
[ __ ] cool
why did i make it black uh where's my
village [ __ ] this is my house
there's an easter egg in the house
oh god where's my house
uh
see
the barn shut up all right i think
that's it
i'm gonna do a save there and uh
the game is over all right i'll do a
poll now i'll do a poll and you guys can
vote
all right i'll do
i won't do just members on this poll
i'll do for everyone so everyone can
vote
um all right okay
just finished ghost of tsushima
thanks to everyone for watching
was really fun uh
go ahead and vote
place your vote for the next
game we stream ow
floor gang
big pp 20
for life for life
for life ooh
all right option one should be dark
souls three
option two should be sakiro
option four three is god of war
uh and then i'd witcher just because i'm
curious i don't think that will get a
lot of vote but
all right three two one post
go
god i love the white armor it looks so
cool
all right let's see the pulse let's see
the results
god of war by far
damn
all right well from what i can tell so
far
whoa ow
god of war is winning by a lot
the pole is under community oh god he's
gonna
god you're useless you're good number
five was way better i should get you
neutered
oh all right god of war hype gang
i swear to [ __ ] god can you stop
i guess this is the after hours
sorry bear i need your
uh skin thank you
let's liberate the rest because
i'm the [ __ ] best hest
let's do a ghost style
assassin is m enemies from above without
being seen
i think they saw me
it's the ghost [ __ ]
here
nice
liberated
next one use ghost stance there's a
ghost sense
what sorry doggie
if there's norse mythology in god of war
that might be really fun
too i read a little bit about it it is
interesting there are some really good
philosophy from the time as well
we weren't all booga booga back then you
know what i'm saying
is this liberated boosh
next one
that's the god of war is all about cool
i have it literally ready i could start
it now
i think i have it i'm not sure though
oh god i forgot our useless you can
smear guinness
uh
i i would start it now but it makes it
confusing because um
the the parts of the videos like this
will be the end of ghost of tsushima and
the beginning of god of war if i do that
that that's just very confusing for
people to find it i think
you get a light lion cloth armor if you
get all the hot springs here
what is that because i have uh i think i
almost have all the hot springs
uh two more should i do that is that
worth it
ain't got time for your sims
kill an enemy with a smoke bomb
that's a sticky bomb
hello
sorry dog i know you didn't do anything
bad but
all right all right now you're really
pissed me off
how did he hit me
that's what i'm talking about
far shot somewhere else [ __ ]
all right another place liberated
love the white armor on this so cool
we only had two more places left to
liberate
you get half naked in if you go to all
the hustle
you get to be half naked what what does
that mean
what does that mean though let's do that
really quick
because i'm very very intrigued
maxed out everything feels good man
oh man we're missing a lot of crickets i
didn't realize
all right so the next one is over here
somewhere
you get nude armor what
all right i'm going for the nude arm of
my my dudes
for show [ __ ] show
for show
what are the poll results right now
you get a sick mask too all right i'm
into it
where am i 48
god of war i'm glad you guys are really
excited about a game then that's pretty
unanimous
that should be cool
so
you feel the coldness of this
ah
i'm not getting it this looks better
like this come on
just this looks better
should i play the game and shut the [ __ ]
up because i can do it i can definitely
do this
i mean i okay i see the hot the spring
don't i yeah it's right there
dude my nipples gotta be so cold
i can reflect on my uncle
he did deserve a warrior's dad
all right prepare to be naked
i did the right thing god damn it all
right whoever's still in the stream you
guys are oh geez
appreciate you guys
cuz we're technically done with the game
this is kind of awkward
real jeeps i mean all right so the next
one is
this way
all right it's further than i thought
god damn it
i guess you guys really just want to see
uh
him naked right that's the real reason
i turned up the ac and now i feel the
immersion a bit too much
god damn it's cool freezing my ass off
all right let's just one more
yes i'm here for sexy half naked gin yes
yes yes yes
oh i see it you see it don't you
i'm gonna 100 this
i might do one more stream where i get
the last bits
if i want to but who knows
before i got to war then i know
everyone's one wants to move on probably
i played god of war 3 so i have some
knowledge of the universe and all that
and i've read a lot
of all about the stories
and a half naked armor
our health is max [ __ ]
huh so this means we have seen jen's ass
technically
18 times feels good man
so how do i get it then did you guys
troll me
a true samurai needs no clothes
jin sakai after too much sake
where is it nice
this is when the game becomes dark souls
and you play online and you play against
uh is there anyone a mask for it as well
no i assume there is what's the most
appropriate
mask for this
monkey
we got the best armor in the game guys
dude i want some of these masks
no mask dude look at this mask look at
this mask and tell me no mask
kobe mask bet you know
the sexier you are the better armor the
less armor you need
those those are the rules of every video
game come
let's on these [ __ ]
we have to go around the mountain
gandalf
oh you want to show me something
sorry ladies i know it's a little cold
but
shogun storm
hey hey hey don't run away coward it's
cold
feelings for way you didn't kill your
uncle you would have gotten the red
variation
of the of the sack i
armor say i already have the red version
of it
do you mean the red animation of the
ghost
yeah you're gonna snake it all the time
it's only fair that i'm naked too
this is the best armor of the game
i said it before i was playing around
with my head i'm like it would be cool
if this game had online multiplayer
and focus more on the duels because the
parts that i enjoyed the most
was by far the samurai duels
maybe it would have been a bit much if
there's too many of them but and then
having that implemented as an online
multiplayer
kind of like dark souls do i think that
could be really fun
i want this game but more dark soul like
basically
like open world aspect is really cool
damn this armor is [ __ ]
oh my god this armor
ow [ __ ] out i'm the ghost
he brutally murders a dog
now it's time for the real screenshot
the [ __ ] you say to my mama
hey there's a horse here no one's
talking about that
i call that stumbling from horse
yes that was [ __ ] beautiful
ow
i threw it on the dog
sorry dog
thank you for finally dying
i feel so bad
now that's the screenshot
fear the monkey get fluted
what happened to this game
let's go oh he's still alive
oh the thunder at the same time did we
get it no
the lightning is liberating
is liberated [ __ ]
armor op can i upgrade it i didn't even
that didn't even strike me
can i upgrade it nope
all right we have something on the way
we might as well check it out what's up
with the armor what do you mean what's
up with this
greatest armor
whoa what's happening over there
what the [ __ ]
it's a siege weapon they got trapeze
now my dudes you got trebuchet can i
come
bro you shot your friend
how monkey don't like fire
stop shooting your friend
monkey burn
i [ __ ] dodged
all right all right all right all right
enough you know go to sleep
i'm almost dead this cannot be happening
thank you
no look away look away look away look
away look away
ah how did i die here out of all pla
i guess the armor isn't that good
heavenly naked strike i should have done
it god damn it
stop that he [ __ ] burned my underwear
off
that's right i'll have redemption
ow well that's a problem what's he doing
nasty monkey go sickle mode
bro you just shot your friend bro
monkey go sycomo
you don't [ __ ] with the monkey that was
a lot easier
the [ __ ] i died because it was too cold
you're right
monkey go boom monkey go boom boom
monkey please go boom boom monkey
what the [ __ ] i just burned it down i
didn't get to go boom boom
monkey no boom boom
boom john whoa my feet d
uh i i guess i'll play the flu
this is for all the fallen trebuchets
out there
what what location am i looking oh
there's a fox nest
or den nest yes right they crack from
eggs
hopefully i'm still worthy
i love how peaceful it is
so i get a if i do all the fox once i
get something as well
sorry i know i know it's a good meme
uh but i love this game because i love
how it looks like
so beautiful
ow
wait i didn't look at the fox i just
decided i was going to jump down oh
there it is i can see it
yeah i get a die for completing
everything what die is i
this is important i need to know
is that cool
oh that quick one really
i'm still naked under the armor that's
right
more charm power
sweet
talk to ishikawa to get the tomoy fox
mask is that cool
what color is it
hmm
oh [ __ ] i wasn't looking ah [ __ ] the
bridge
wolf mask from completing fox then looks
cooler it says i have so many [ __ ]
there's so many [ __ ] ends
oh god there's artifacts as well can i
track them
like how would i i think i'll just go
for max and these
i only have five left okay i quite done
a lot then
it's faster to travel from the city i
can't travel to that one
stop ready filled with wonder
and nature
is that i heard a fox did you guys hear
the fox
i definitely heard a fox
am i crazy
was it the horse maybe
they really nailed exploration in this
game
love it i am happy
happy happy
i feel good and [ __ ]
oh now i got the parrots down see
see i don't i guess i'll never learn
there it is
oh all right all right getting there
never mind
get sliced [ __ ]
you're welcome hey peter saw the paul
wondering if you're familiar with
uh yeah i finished god of war 3. like 10
years ago
maybe i watched a quick recap video so i
remember but
that was an epic game i actually
remember uh
that was right before i started youtube
and i bought a playstation with whatever
money i had
and i bought two games uh
i bought heavy rain and i bought god of
war and i got to say
i liked heavy rain more at the time but
i'm excited for uh god of war the new
one i know they try to do more story in
this
this one it's just crazy looking back on
on
that time and i i'm so lucky to
be able to stream for you guys i'm very
happy i'm able to do it
i i think for the first time in a long
time
things just feel good i'm just happy
about it so
thank you guys let's follow a little
foxy first
i
just feel grateful for so many things in
life right now
i got no complaints no complaints
could be in japan but you know
uh they're attacking me while i'm trying
to follow this
excuse me uh jurgen you don't have to
follow
what's wrong with you
whoa [ __ ] left dude
wow so pretty screenshot
time you know it is you know what it is
you know what it is
it's screenshot
let me play the flu goddammit
honestly this looks better without me i
feel like
i can't be bothered i've done so many
i've done so many oh god i'm dead
look away kids
look away kids i came this far
to die like this
all right let's get in this is the last
this is the last camp to liberate
toshima
very epic all right you're dead you're
dead
you're dead
you almost shot a deer
boom
that's a lot of them and i have no
weapons or upgrades all right i'll do
this
she says
oh
this is so [ __ ] tough
nice
oh my god i'm dying
i can kill that dog
i need to kill the dog the dog is my
salvation
sorry
beach bus beach bus
why aren't i got nowhere ghost stuff
left
okay okay
okay that's not good
all right he's invulnerable
there's a lot of them we're gonna have
to be creative
get roof [ __ ]
jesus
oh god
ah
[ __ ]
wow
nice
this is a quite the battle jesus [ __ ]
that's the last one
sexy sexy sexy
liberated from all the heated
alright we have four more
three more hike
a couple more bennett is the most all
right i'll do that at my own time i
don't have to watch that
thank you i'll end the stream here thank
you for
joining this epic adventure
i had so much fun it was very fun
i'm gonna go have some dinner and then i
will study the blade deeply
in my own spare time i'll come back
stronger i'm so glad i played it on hard
it made it so much more challenging too
it's a good call
um thanks for being here appreciate you
uh mr beast is live streaming right now
if you guys want to check him out
tell him i sent tell him i sent you
and see you guys next time