you thought 5,000 episodes wasn't enough
say it with me blows yeah we're back
baby for another hundred episodes of
happy wheels we're starting a news I'm a
disability I'm just gonna play once you
guys just couldn't have enough could you
your fantasies could never be quenched
well here I am
ah the sweet sound of happy wheels it
just brings back over memory anyway are
you ready
[Music]
I missed you happy wheels let's freakin
do this so let's go by anytime and sort
by rating harpoon Dodge I'm glad to see
they're innovating cuz I never played on
our own harpoon Dodge - oh ok we're
starting with harpoon dodge - Oh easy
three two one go easy that one's easy I
did it I did it my god I'm so scared
it's just oh god this is actually Oh God
not it Mike
I'm still alive I'm still alive it's
fine I'm choking myself oh that does not
look good
it's okay guys I'm a little rusty
but I'll be I'll do it I'll do it I'll
do it I'll control shift ejector I
checked alright so you want to go as
flat as possible
oh you want to go dolphin that's all I
know
that's all I remember Oh see this
dolphin I'm actually having fun playing
happy wheels
oh god it's hard it's fun that's my head
well we got a metal penis everyone is
happy wheels gonna become like minecraft
or people people just start playing it
under ironically again I think I know
what I need to do I think I know what I
need to do no worries I don't alright so
you want to make sure that that's it oh
damn it I am so terrible oh I'll take it
I'll take it I'll take it
I may have lost my foot but I'm still
alive no seal boom oh yeah yeah I'm
still alive god damn it oh oh oh that's
just gonna hurt oh my god stay
Oh awesome
Oh Oh see Elmo there it is oh damn I'm
good once you get going this is easy oh
that's easy the classic easy bring it
happy wheels I got use of experience
yes alright we're dropping down now I
don't know why my foot is coming with me
see you later foot live a good life
nothing
[Music]
have they finally added checkpoints no
thanks for playing it I hope you liked
it have a nice day have a nice day have
a nice day everyone harpoon Dodge one of
course of course cannot have enough of
this
easy whoa oh do one where I have to jump
I have the poco oh no I'm still alive
I'm still alive I'm still alive I'm
still alive I'm still alive
I want a ship it kind of bends up a bit
and then control dodges okay that's good
to know it went through my knees all
right they I think they got my knees I
don't know what to tell you guys guess
it's still coming
did it bottle flip nunny bottle flip oh
my god we're very proud newb uh what all
right whatever I'm a sniper guys
this is it oh this is it visiting this
is it create the meme face one oh hell
yeah meme face click language I already
failed clearly clearly memes are only in
Spanish Spanish that's right
as click a key see allocate este muy
bien muy bien
sorry boy here we go I'll do the serial
me my love that means so much
alright what's next are the eyes okay uh
oh yeah
Feliz release oh so kawaii
[Applause]
burger burger I can't wait to see what
my troll face is gonna cara cara condo I
mean it's impressive what people did
this hairless its there is to me sorry
to interrupt this video just want to
give a big shout to my boys el gato
the elgato hd60 s to be specific with
this beautiful baby I can record videos
in the top quality that I have and no I
don't need the camera I mean the
gameplay footage Thank You Maya she's on
my son if only al gato did cameras then
I would have such great quality but
until then check out the HD 60s if you
can record any form of gameplay mobile
phone anything you can plug into your
computer almost think you guys got a
prize right rub swag I nod rub swag all
right here we go
rub drink first fries zero - lets
breaking through this rope swing baby
tell you yeah there we go
[Music]
yeah I'm still alive I'm still alive
oh yeah let's go grab grab grab grab
can I still grab with my handicapped arm
that is the question ah by arm it's been
a play oh there it is
perfection so how do I go here with that
guy still alive baby oh we hit it we hit
a quitting and then now we drop it drop
it bear oh no no no no oh god oh god oh
god
hey stripey baby oh god what's gonna
happen Hey pixel on my god it's
minecraft oh my god is ma am I supposed
to go here okay I'll go
Super Mario is this guy making me all
the maps no one else is making this
nothing like winning in fetal position
Oh ultimate glass break I can still do
it son help me adjust my spine son
that's not my spot all the comedy has
definitely increase it's funny because
now it's ironic
get up dad all right
[Music]
okay ejected dad always just the top dog
why am I even playing this in garbage my
time for its we - number one most
subscribed everyone yeah we made it I
can fry to eat well oh well that was
happy wheels hopefully everyone is happy
as happy wheels
brofist on 100 mil baby see you guys
tomorrow bye
also check out merge the
discreet what super simulators becoming
relevant no no don't leave
no please sponsor eagle please do
something
yes
this game is still relevant
dear me
[Music]