welcome back to Minecraft part for
gaming week I was mining my house okay I
was building this thing and I'm placing
a stairs and I see this guy who is that
what the Frick are you go away
hello get off my property I have a gun
maybe he's a friend I don't want to be
racist hello
he killed the fish hello hello I'm
talking to you
oh jeez you're creepy Oh God scary Felix
okay dude we can be friends hey you want
melon do you like this oh look at this
he liked it what are you doing with that
block hey hey put that block down put
that block that goddamn it put it down
put it down put it down put it down
where do you go away God there's enemies
everywhere I have to kill them all right
do I kill ender men you just farted
hey melon take it oh Jesus what that was
so scary
you better not steal my stop dude
we're cool it's all good just like
nothing happened all right you just all
right
I'll stick to what I'm doing you stick
to what you're doing and no more melon
from now on they're all dust city of
some people okay so basically I built
this indoor pool it's pretty sweet it
leads up at dark and I'm like building
the house just making it nice making it
cool it's gonna like you know do your
thing it's gonna I'm gonna live here
actually there's one thing I mean wanted
to do cuz when when I started playing
Minecraft the the bed was automatically
red that's how I remember minecraft but
now they have dying stuff so I think if
I do this and this it's a red bed now I
feel at home now I can sleep at night
there it is that's what I remember no
that takes me back you wake up to
burning zombies that's what I like
that's what I like to see I haven't
finished this because I want to fish so
we I want to have I want to have actual
fishes in my house I want like the stars
and this night and everything to be epic
know I only have one string god damnit
what drops strings two spiders drop
strings
I'm sorry mr. spy there you have to die
yes ha ha
Oh also by the way oh yeah don't jump on
the crotch everyone lost their mind
lysippos oh I am learning as I'm going
okay no I'm not a Minecraft veteran yet
we're going for the ender dragon snaggin
what was i doing I already forgot yes a
fishing rod that's what we're doing I
know how to make it in by hand but just
so you guys learn I'm making a fishing
rod then of course we need a boat right
both time both time sorry Jurgen you
can't come with me
what's the grass not growing all right
doesn't matter it's both time damn I'm
fast oh yeah oh yeah that's what I'm
talking dude that's a fish right there
that's a fish right there
here we go bros here we go come on come
on grab it come on grab it come on you
want it don't need a bait on the fish
don't laugh at me you're again I'm
trying here do I need a bait for it I
probably need a bait for it could I
actually just capture him with my bucket
this is how we fish in Sweden with
buckets come here man come here man
come here come here come here come here
come here
tactical fishing haters said it wasn't
possible but I got a bucket of fish now
you go in there oh my god I got a bucket
of what where he got again my friend we
gotta get him a friend Bros technically
you're supposed to row a boat backwards
so this game isn't that historically
accurate after all okay
all right we're going scuba diving can
you make scuba diving equipment in this
what the hell just happened
god I'm God I'm God it's scary down
there no I'm not scared of everything in
Minecraft okay you know what let's just
make a bunch of buckets I don't have
time for this it's bucket making time
smash like if you're excited for bucket
making time that's what I thought that's
what I thought all right we're making
but that's what I thought that's what I
thought all right we're making buckets I
got a bucket full of bucket full of
sunshine
[Music]
Jesus Christ
what is happening or you can drown in
Minecraft that's so unrealistic
commit god damn why can the fishes
breathe underwater then huh
explain that liberals let's try and find
more exotic fishes you are Oh God
everything is scary in this game come
back here
god damn they're too fast squeezies come
on all right you're too ugly yesterday
I'm sorry those are the Minecraft rules
don't look at me I don't make it up your
ugly you die you're coming with me in
the bucket right now I don't come in the
bucket all right in the boat then fine
no I want my turtle in my house can we
drown the people Oh kitty kitty you're
going in the bucket get it you're going
in the bucket you have no saying kitty
your dog in the bucket
you're going in the bucket come here you
snake god damn it so disrespectful
what's happening hello how's he doing
dude you got so much bread bro yes you
know mine do you go I'll sleep in his
house have you been looking at me the
whole night well sorry I thought it was
my house what I can make dyed pants what
leather okay six leather I'll be right
back
cartography table all right well this
pool idea is very underwhelming why are
they old there is it the draft in the
water all right it's cow murdering time
Peter I have to do it I have to get
emerald I have to get dyed pants all
right you gonna die
you didn't even drop leather you're
useless they're escaping they're
escaping they were escaping the camp no
they're all this gay Bank what the god
damn it you are you and you're dead
you're dead you're just dead that's what
happened no one escapes my camp all
right one gets to live because he's good
you escape you die that's the rules well
you're all there you suck dude
I will now we can get an epic pants at
least now we can get the Gucci pants hey
come on did I tell you to stop you the
Gucci pants guy there you are
six I need six are you crazy
oh my god dude let's let's bounce uragan
these people are trying to swindle us
alright well this works out because I
actually wanted to just ride out and
murder people I haven't really explored
the area although oh wait actually I
forgot I want to make a comp s can you
make a compass I remember making a
compound even back in my day I don't
want to get lost I don't want to lose my
epic house
boom boom boom and then in the middle
there's my compact alright we're going
out on an adventure
[Music]
oh it tells you where the house is
oh that's so nice stop stop resisting
stop resisting we got six okay no more
killing
we only reap what we sow that is not how
that expression marks okay well I feel a
lot more confident just riding off
seeing what we're gonna find you know
I'm saying like who knows what we're
gonna find like a little hole that's
pretty cool actually I do need coal hold
on hold up once a your again again yeah
again where is here again
where's here again again it's getting
dark yeah again when you're again he
must be here somewhere
Oh God hello have you seen her again
Oh God big one help me I looked away one
second and then he was gone
have you seen Jurgen oh my god he must
have fallen down the hole or something
he must be so scared oh god no I was
hoping he maybe he ran back home scared
chicken oh so happy oh I'll never leave
you again here again whoa Jesus almost
fell down there my god it's dangerous
this game
whoa what a mountain well what is that
the shipwreck what is that all right
you're gonna stay here gonna make sure
it's safe
what kind of wood is this
is that a treasure chest
oh my god minecraft
oh my crack paper
hey you're again god dammit why does he
keep like stay yet Oh God not this again
I left him here oh I hear him you snake
where are you sir way to get a whistle
to get your horse to again oh my god I
look so pimp I have less armor but I
look cool so it's okay why do I hear him
but not see him what what the hell is
this have you kidnapped Jurgen hey what
the hell are you you tried to kill me
I'll kill you it's a crossbow you should
wait too slow bro
cool it's getting dark again the Jurgen
is nowhere to be found hey look more
enemy flowers I know I hear them here
they are not here explain my oh my god
what the hell are you wearing what is
this
they must have captured your again give
them back to me
Jurgen are you in here there again I
hear you I hear you you seen the trees
or some [ __ ] oh my
why do I feel like I'm going crazy where
this yard again the thing is I hear you
the ghost of Jurgen is haunting me I
swear to God it was my only friend now I
can't find him I looked away two seconds
and then he was just gone just like that
[Music]
where oh my God where were it do keep
disappearing it oh alright we have him
back I looked all night literally all
night I don't know what you were doing
and I'm not even gonna ask going back
home here again what the hell is that
got a donkey gonna come with me donkey
you want someone weak are you kidding me
are you kidding me are you kidding me
are you kidding me yeah yeah