good morning gamers it's another
beautiful day in Minecraft in today's a
very special day isn't that right Sven
that's right hey both cow
play the music okay keep playing both
cow for many years me and Sven have
built together this structure it's a
structure that symbolizes the power of
friendship the power of love and the
power of perseverance I introduce to you
the giant meatball that's right take it
in take it in and soul its glory that
was finally peace on earth
isn't that right chicken crap what her
sheep died for this you know he died to
make this possible without water sheep
there would be no giant meatball why did
I build a giant meatball you might ask
for water sheep this meatball represents
everything that water sheep believed in
friendship loyalty trust and all those
good things that he stood by what if
what the Sheep was here alive today I
know he would be proud no one loved the
meatballs more than more the Sheep he
was like a father to me it was like the
son that I never had and I loved him I
may have shown it in weird ways when I
may have not always been the nicest and
you know I'll admit I may not always
been perfect for my god the meatball
and I'm so proud to call myself an
America I don't name them stop jumping
in boats men please I know you're
excited but I haven't even shown look at
the press cow over there I haven't even
shown you guys the best bit so I've been
messing around with redstone I've spent
a lot of time with the Redstone and I
god I hope it works
sorry Sven you can't ride this it might
break you just gotta hit this and then
voila baby
it's as glorious on the inside as it is
on the outside
Italian leather exterior all handcrafted
by one Scandinavian Swede
it's took a lot of time I'm not gonna
lie I think the elevator took more time
for me to build I thought okay cool I'll
build an elevator
that'll be epic not it's not epic I mean
it's it's super fun like I love writing
it I want it the idea was to have
something go all the way all the way to
the top like the very top and I'm like
no I'm tired of farming piston steel
material
I'm tired of the circuits always messing
up and I don't understand why but it
works for it works pretty well I'm like
it's really fun to write it the thing is
like spent stop teleporting you scare me
what if Sven rides it oh my god I never
thought he's probably too short I think
he's too short
yeah sorry it's fine you're too short ha
ha let's try it the thing is I know you
can build elevators probably way smarter
I guarantee you that I just wanted to
try it out myself I know you I could
probably do it easier so well if I had
the sticky pistons I don't have sticky I
don't have slime I let me see Qiao I
don't I'm stinky poopoo all right I'm
not going near this place when it's dark
too many creepers have blown up my
circuits too many times for me to leave
it around a dark alright it ain't it
ain't happening alright but let me show
you seriously I had so much fun building
the elevator like AI know it's janky and
whatever but I didn't realize the red
Sun was so fun to just mess around with
okay so I want our son to ride it fan
coming here I wanna see if it works I'll
be so happy yeah sometimes sometimes he
breaks sometimes it breaks it's fine
it's member ru hello
he's like stuck in the elevator fan see
oh there you are
okay hey can you come down here it's a
ball inside of a ball what else do you
want baby
alright come on let's do this thing
crawl inside the fence he teleports
alright so follow me I'm just gonna put
the leash on you spend because you're
being a little difficult
yeah this is gonna be a problem all
right fine I'll make a special to put it
for you thread thread you're being very
difficult don't be shy it's gonna break
the whole thing then please please
please go go
no no no I know you don't like tight
spaces anymore after what happened in 86
come on gee believer never have kids
thank you thank you friend is gonna go
for a ride
listen I know you're scared of elevators
it's fine trust me are you sitting all
right here we go
three two one you can sign so basically
the way it works is it's a staircase
it's a glorified stair trace one signal
goes to the upper ones one signal goes
to the pusher ones and there one taken
delay and then I don't know it just took
me a lot of time to figure out how
redstone works isn't that right then and
a lot of wool first thing you stone and
I think like the circus would still
connect and I didn't understand why and
then I saw the people use of wool so I'm
like okay I guess I'll use wool and then
these added delay even if you don't add
a delay to them which added in another
mystery to the problem but basically
yeah it goes one two three four sad
where is he there you are he's fine eat
something
wait what happened here does it double
sip is that even possible
wait where's the next step pushes here
versus here pushes here it pushes you up
there
[Music]
it still works apparently okay cool I
didn't know that was possible
let me try what
oh my god it skips a step that's genius
I don't even know what I built so yeah I
it's so satisfying I love the sound
that's why it gets stuck sometimes my
god I was planning to put carpet all
around here maybe like put a floor here
you could have a really big floor right
and then I thought it could be cool
maybe can you do like catapults and
stuff because then like if I have Jurgen
here and we head out an adventure we can
catapult out there into the water these
are just ideas I have I want to build
Sven I want to build it's so fun to
build I love my craft oh yeah you're
gonna scan I forgot I lost Jurgen I've
looked everywhere Sven today we bring
back Yuri and he has to be out somewhere
he wouldn't just excuse me excuse me
what the cow you are good for one
purpose and one purpose only actually -
playing music and your delicious shoes
thank you oh that's right we're right
haha my crap just keeps on surprising I
didn't know you could do this why can
you do this
me and both cow forever and ever
going Nick's adventure and drinking his
juice damn that was beautiful thanks
both cow you're the best okay I really
miss water sheep I'm not gonna lie I'm
not over water sheep I'm not over Jurgen
being lost I'm not over anything I'm
honestly hurt I'm confused and you know
depression shows its way in many forms
and I chose to build a giant meatballs
other people do other things okay but
now that meatball is built I still feel
the pain it's still there let me see if
I can find something else like a
substitute right I need to make this
right hello there Frank do you know what
if she rang I'll tell you all about it
it was the best wait it was like a
father to me how did you know they
whichever lava now don't want you to get
hurt I got it cool you just ruined my
life okay never mind you are the lucky
new water sheep it's an honor and a
privilege where's the Bell here we go oh
my god the meatball appears before IKEA
Tower my god it's so beautiful I was
thinking about putting a Swedish flag on
top I just got really tired of farming
it looks kind of like a Death Star or
something cool I'm glad this van is
taken care of oh my god I know you were
evil he's talking to spider evil chicken
black my God how can you do this chicken
ah Who am I kidding it's not the same
smell it's not the same it doesn't feel
as good as when what the Sheep did it
you don't squeal in pain like what the
she it's not the same it will never be
the same what we had was special all
right there's two water cows now because
I'm too annoyed that Sven keeps entering
Oh
sorry since worry what are you doing you
get to live so apparently you can build
like a dispenser or something like that
I want to try that wait I think I have
one oh yeah it's right here
see I thought dispenser was like a
garbage bin or something clearly not the
case I have a lover yeah this is all I
need
so if I place dispenser how does
dispensers work there we go and then I
put like so I can
what are you doing how did you escape
don't look so innocent oh gosh you
people like there you go stay there so I
just put a lever on it oh my god you'll
never be water shaped egg come on come
on participate right you'll never be
water what what threaten don't go
near him right he's evil that's right I
see it in his eyes tell me what water
she pays oh my god how does he do that
Oh what
[Applause]
you will never be water she died it just
becomes more of them what don't go there
ah you all went there guys this is a
restricted area you can't
well aren't you adorable fine alright
enough playing around we got actual
stuff to do it is 3:00 a.m. we are here
to summon back water she minecraft
spirits and gods not can you hear us we
want water sheep back and you're going
to of course
I will ring this bell three times we
bring sacrifices on the third ring I
expect water ships returned one what
that you guys hear the door from the
nether portal water shape water shape
you're not water she he's not coming
back is he
[Music]
stop it guys
he will never come back spend I'm going
to bed and don't even try and console me
okay guys I think it's time we realized
what the ship is gone forever
we need to build a memorial it's the
least thing I can do this is for what
get out of wait can you not
there it is you know I may I may have
been partially responsible for what
happened to water sheep I may have done
I'm not perfect by any means but I still
love him that's right we have gathered
here today to say goodbye before to she
now stop thank you now continue spending
well that was it basically rest in peace
water she rest in peace
may your rule forever be soaked in water
okay so then we may have lost water
sheep there's two people that we can
still retrieve sven uragan two and
boneyard again are still out there
we're gonna get them gosh darn it now we
need to make water drinking potion and
underwater scene potion or pufferfish
I'm sorry it's to save them their phone
I'm sorry
sorry then we have to make potion of
night vision so we can see golden carrot
my god
it better be worth it let's extend it as
well this done I'm bringing my lucky
pufferfish on the way you'll guide the
way to thin their bone come on son hurry
the boats bank there we go
like so we're gonna get a backspin don't
worry Oh God we're going near that place
no don't worry then close your eyes
close your eyes it's fine
oh you look away that's right look away
nothing bad over there well that's a
shipwreck here what kind of wood is this
whoa I never seen this this is young
jungle it's jungle we never been too
young go okay but I haven't been here or
someone else probably wore their sheep -
we have so many places left to explore
in this game a thousand part series
spend a thousand perfect it's getting
party great so I think it was yeah
Jurgen was over there and we swam from
this island to here so it must have
happened somewhere here between you oh
my god is gonna be difficult
okay stay and stay and hold the boats
vent and I will look for I will drink
this this gives me underwater drinking
and fairness whoa forget how awesome
whoa okay now we actually am well it's
actually easier maybe I'll be insane
okay this is good bone yard again is
white here isn't it
bone yard again where are you we missed
you bone Jurgen are you out there well I
saw something white dude I'm scanning
guys honestly I know this is Dora the
explora but help me if you spot did you
guys see that am I crazy
if you spot him you got sitala bro I
swear I saw something in between sky
freakin eel things right because I went
here tonight
where are you doing there bone alone I'm
pulling out my coordinates so you guys
can tell me what coordinate if you see
him alone it's impossible I'm just gonna
scan over this area this is where I lost
him no no it's so dark
mission failed Sven we'll get him next
time
puffer fish you did nothing explain
yourself
Oh God come back I'm just kidding I was
kidding
Oh God Buffy I'm sorry oh I'm sorry you
don't look too good puffer oh my god oh
my god you're gay I have wheat for you
he doesn't want it
[Music]
why are you here you just wanted to walk
oh my god how did you get here I tried
to find Dinnerbone then I find real
Jurgen epic oh my god yes the series is
same the boys are back in town the boys
are back in town gosh darn it why did
you leave me I was so scared you're
again number two
oh I'm literally lost on the way back
home it's alright been here before
No thank God we made it back oh my gosh
they're so beautiful
I'm teary-eyed I'm so happy we'll find
in their bone next time Jurgen I have to
show you the giant have you you haven't
seen me complete oh my gosh you
disappeared while I was building it oh
you stay there please alright what the
cow played a song
it's the song of uragan and friendship
listen to this year ago they have the
bass though yeah
Georgians back in town baby that's what
I'm talking about
for those of you don't know we have new
merch check out the represent that comes
identify and support the uragan and
Spence here we have Spaniard versus
rifle counts good luck next time
thanks for watching another episode next
time we're gonna find at the ender
portal see you then bye bye what you
never played to / simulator you know
it's fun right I'm not supposed to give
my opinion but give it a try and then
you can tell me if it's good or not not
convinced yet okay I'll cut you a deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price