you know oh my God he's still tough oh
my god he's flying out there again good
morning gamers welcome back to another
episode of Minecraft I know
surprise look at IKEA power in all its
glory so beautiful
[Music]
we are nearing the end game we beat the
weather last battle I've cleaned up a
little bit but next up is the
Enderdragon baby the final boss of
Minecraft
after that we go get a bunch of cool
stuff as well so it's time for us to
prepare for that our next step is to
increase our village make more bad bad I
have this genius contraption right so
there's a little hole here in the class
and then you put a boat here and then
eventually we'll catch a baby that's
right I don't catch all your children
Riptide I think Riptide is pretty good
Riptide what is Riptide 32 what do you
think I'm made of money I think that's
another thing I can put in my Trident it
means I can use the Trident as a means
of transportation yes please spend where
is my purse I need it now give me my
purse I don't think I have any money
left
no I'm poor again oh god I'm gonna have
to trade with people far far away
okay give me my stuff I have an insane
amount of pumpkin okay so then what do
you do with all the cats daddy's coming
so you gotta go business trip dami if I
can use it I love the trainin we got to
travel far in the south maybe I should
kidnap these people in the South
actually IKEA bird did I see IKEA bird
or am I crazy
I can't apart you can't ah alright fine
you're coming with me IKEA bird how did
you sneak with me how did you do this
stop low-key kind of cute though Oh Oh
fine
one thing I want to do at some point
let's try and collect every monster in
the game
because apparently you can put you can
put any monster in the game in a boat
we're gonna put the ender dragon in the
boat get in the boat I think you can
actually put the wither in a boat as
well that's gonna be the next oh god I
can't board is gone
let's art gold with this playthrough put
every creature in a book so this is one
of the first and biggest villagers I
ever traded with and this is where I
make my stinks this is where I are on my
bread and butter
are you having refilled all right it's
been days my god no
he went into a cactus here bird
[Music]
Oh No
IKEA bird get in boo boo you're coming
with me if anyone has an objection feel
free to call the cops why I can't Oh was
I talking to you
they bye to your friends Mike here bird
was like father to me I love him like my
mother everything was going so well
till the Fire Nation just get in the
boat it's not that hard
what is this place the Netherlands why
are we riding in a boat don't ask stupid
questions
No
it was like a father to me the way he
would trade me melons for a discount I
felt truly like I belonged
he was irreplaceable there will never be
another man like Hey wakey-wakey
get in the boat get in no listen
get in the boat or I'm gonna shove this
bed somewhere you're not gonna like it
thank you what happened to your friend
nothing special
hey no hard feelings right trust me this
is 100% safe I've done this before go to
the boat you think I'm ready
my neighbor's gonna just just press it
just trust me so do you think that guy
is good still gonna trade me a riptide
about three hours I know you can plate
wet damn we're fast you can place eyes
and then that's a really fast way to
actually transporting another with ice
and a boat so apparently you can take
one of the farmers and place him in your
automatic farm and he will replant the
seeds I don't know if that's true or not
but I mean if that's the case that's
right that means I get free labor uh
don't worry about the new guy guys don't
worry about him don't don't even look at
it how much do you want to bet he
doesn't have riptide anymore no baby
come on guys okay he still has replied
so that's okay yeah he's like whoa guys
guys it's raining potatoes this is crazy
don't worry man I'm just preparing your
little a little new adventure all right
enjoy your new home and job 20 well what
in the world oh my god it's raining yes
this is perfect and even real what are
you doing in my house
guess this against the rules to kick you
out all right you can stay just like be
nice how does this work
oh my god Oh spen did you see that wait
what oh my god that's awesome let me get
away whoa
this seems very dangerous I don't know
why anyone would do this no oh my god
you what Allah ah all my friends
look what a great job he did I'm flying
away I'm out of this to disguise and
beyond I'm gonna find uragan again I'm
gonna find that kea bird oh my god
it's snowing up no are you kidding me ah
this is the worst episode of all time I
have a sign bed and I'm not afraid to
use it if anyone come near me
what are you guys even yes finally
haha woohoo
yeah the circle of life continues little
child follow me little child now we
place another boat trap we refill the
food and more baby will come what what
are you doing here
haha alright let's put some more
potatoes and carrots
he's the electrician he's just making
sure it's all running thanks thanks mr.
peepee really appreciate it
guys just like food raining from ceiling
does anyone know where that comes from
this is so strange
suddenly my pants feel like they are hot
9 - look he grew up curse of vanishing
ok you guys are just getting greedy now
yes that's what I like to see
alright gamers I am back they're all
farmers now come on you're my destined
new farmer we're gonna have a great time
together I'm so glad no one is going to
escape my prison unless I willingly
escort them out okay don't look don't
talk to him don't talk to him spend a
look at him he's bad man very bad man
look who doesn't have a job huh well we
will sort that out for you buddy don't
worry about it
just follow me in here yes yes
oh you're lonely okay I give friend I'm
very generous man people don't
understand you know actually I think you
should be alone for no reason whatsoever
despite the fact that I don't like you
and I don't like your bold fit where is
your face there it is okay
well that's all I got a safe that's all
the reasons I need let's replace my oh
look who's already started huh from the
boat hey what a loser what a nerd
hopefully this won't get overrun by
zombies I have protected at this time
let me see oh if you like the boat so
much why don't you why don't you try
this so basically he will work for me
and I will sell him his own crops
now that stinks so whatever hijab he
does for me I will sell it back to him
how did you escape get back in chamber
that's right shame on you so the idea is
to just expand the whole the whole way
like infinite I want to have as many as
possible keep making bet back
yeah and eventually will have it will
have infinite Bibby Wallach you're not
supposed to be a shepherd you're not
even supposed to be come out of here get
away from him you don't love him that's
right you're supposed to be a farmer ah
ha ha looks like we caught the big one
boys how did you even get there
into the cell why do I enjoy this so
much
why does making villagers go into this I
don't know what Hey look at him I don't
know why I liked any other they're all
brothers and sisters even more they're
our family of pain they're our family of
so look who decided to become farmer huh
okay all right
look like anyone's opinion can just
change huh what is he doing give me back
my money that's my money
damn alright yeah that's right give me
all your money okay one disappeared
that's so crazy it's time to finish up a
tower of llama wives Tower of llama the
most ambitious project I have there we
go Thanks
just stay there thanks bro see you in
forever
there you go
should we make a tower of cat maybe wake
up feeding time he's like no I want to
sleep oh god oh god we have to eat this
the first time we get to eat that
relatable moment when you're dragged out
of bed because carrots are raining from
the sky all right come on guys make more
baby okay so I like my house I really do
but I think it's what do you think your
again I think it's time we update it
it's looking a bit small in comparison
to everything else we have around this
and I want to make it like a traditional
Swedish house I think that could be
really fun as well but to build we must
first destroy man this feels weird this
house has been here longer than almost
anything in this playthrough that feels
this feels so strange
oh my god it's so sad analyst away I
didn't expect to be feeling feels so I
had this house for so long
Hey look who caught a couple babies huh
yeah oh no it's just your kids oh don't
worry I'll take good care no Charlie's
gaping get their boats child you're
coming with me
don't think so child look at this that's
the one thing that's been with us in
number one tree of life wait why do I
hear a tiny one oh my gosh
why does everyone make him pay I didn't
ask for this congratulations guys
damn I'm rich now oh it's all working so
well look at that things are going well
for once in an episode not really
actually but oh look he's teaching his
child to be as worthless as his father
come on all right
I don't really have the materials to to
build a house I want to build so it's I
gamers last episode I blame peepee
poo-poo oh my god he's hiding from me
now what spawn zone and why did I just
spend 15 pounds on it last episode I
said pee pee poop who was healing then
with her pigs healing him
are you kidding me the pigment healed
him
you guys healed him but I was wrong they
actually started us a great decoy and I
feel like the only honorable thing to do
from my mistake my miscalculation is to
make a memorial for all the pee pee poop
was out there that fought all the brave
people poo poos that fought and died so
we could defeat the wither that's why I
want to build a quick little memorial it
won't be anything fancy but something to
represent each torch represents one
peepee poo-poo this is actually one of
the first things I ever build in
Minecraft I was like hey gorgeous it
looks pretty cool I'll just place a
bunch of them down it's surreal to do
this like 10 years later just but for
all the wrong reasons why people
[Music]
oh my gosh I can just right-click
why hasn't no one told me
[Music]
there it is like a beautiful
whoa that actually looks though and I
missed a spine
okay gamers as a final ending for this
episode I want to do something with
Jorgen we're gonna write out so I don't
know if this works but someone made it
I'll put his imprint in the description
so that if you put down a diamond block
and a nether stall named Petey pie which
of course I just happen to have on me
and then throw a sword on it
it should create a pewdiepie boss throw
them as a star and then a sword did I
not do it oh it worked
oh my god it's cherry pie it's berry pie
in Minecraft but wait
I am PewDiePie Oh God
pizza pie has a lot of health don't hurt
me Petey pie please oh no it it how is
this even possible so I'm playing on the
easiest difficulty No
oh my god it's still tough oh my god
he's flying out you're it again no I
don't want to hurt you yard again don't
hurt me
I need to drink milk
oh wait I'm fine no no I love your yard
gate don't do this to me y'all guys stop
fighting we can be together I love you
please don't make me do this back off
peopIe oh my god
I'm going for hardcore DPS oh this is so
Oh back off sweat back up find water
through these I don't want to hurt you
you're the only one that I haven't
killed no we're gonna look so evil it's
evil Sven
stop stop sled oh my god the knock-back
oh what is he doing oh my god oh
god what else couldn't read if I
possibly have up oh my god of course
it's what that she hey wait what they
should follow me all my loved ones are
back but they're fighting against me
there you go you're in what they're now
what their sheep damn he's fast
oh my god stop it berry pie Oh stops
water sward
stop it pit if I get it
oh my god
ten out of ten yes headphones where do I
put them getting up with them on my head
how do I use the chair oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my chair how do I put
on there oh my god and I can change
music that is so cool wait let me get
the chair bag Bob's orbit gone
what oh my god I can ride their chair
what yeah Bob's one Oh big for Baba BIP
Bop Elbe River deeper deeper deeper BIP
Bop our trip
papow oh alright gamers ha ha ha
look at me Sven we're gonna beat the
ender dragon in this chair thank you so
much
mech Macke Stein for creating this
that's amazing
hope you guys enjoy this episode if you
did smash like subscribe check out the
merch of course to support the series oh
my god it go fast oh my god it can't do
this okay alright that's it see you guys
bye