heyyo good morning gamers it's minecraft
day yeah my favorite day i love
minecraft i am legit addicted to this
game i am having so much look at this
look at my form it's epic and look at my
oh my god I feel like this probably goes
against some rules and regulations all
right who's hungry
who's hungry there you go there you go
have it all eat as much as you can
now the reason I did this is because we
actually need to start murdering them
because we're going I got em alright I'm
just gonna kill I'm sorry
PETA look away ah I need your meat I'm
sorry they're escaping stop them oh god
what am I done
[Music]
okay all right the children gets to what
are you doing in my boat okay that's
awesome you guys can stay in the boat
that's oh you're friends with uragan you
can stay why do I even have a farm this
is to look at all the children you
wouldn't kill a child Felix no I
wouldn't oh my god all right okay it's
Oh
tourniquet yelling I'm sorry sorry sorry
sorry all right the kids gets to live
I'm that gracious but I do need their
meat because today we are going on epic
adventure that's right everyone
we had these treasure maps and we're
gonna go and find where it is it looks
like it's probably pretty goddamn far
epic that is the cutest thing I have
ever seen in my entire life
oh yeah I made some improvement to the
house as well
got this new carpet got this new
terrorist it's pretty epic it's whatever
I and these bad guys attacked me so I
put their banner on our epic Tree of
Life okay Jurgen has to stay on this
adventure actually maybe I should bring
him oh god it's too scary so we are the
tiny dot on the map that's so far there
is this one mirror oh look it it is it
changing it is changing oh god this is
so complicated dude all right we'll get
Jurgen for this one all right you're
again let's ride so we have to ride this
direction question mark hey yah Reagan's
friend hello Jurgen is friend this is
epic Oh God we're gonna need a boat
aren't we oh maybe not so all the people
in this village disappeared it I don't
know why it's not like I was trying to
blow up their house or anything but
turtley still here hello turtle and
stone person is still here hello stone
person so now wait this is now we're
going south how'd it go in on the map
surely this should be the way or is it
this way okay wait so we need to go west
we need to go this way
ah gee belieber god dammit
yeah it's this way no it's not yeah okay
this way I don't know how this works
okay I've never done this I'm a gamer
it's old gamer intuition that's all I
got
I haven't shown everything I've been
doing I've been playing offline for
hours and hours and I'm so hooked on my
crap but I haven't done any adventure so
I'm excited now to go on epic okay this
is working I think now we're just going
up again aren't we
what about this way I think we might
have to get a boat I don't like this
will you be a good boy Jurgen we're
gonna we're gonna do it like this they
oh god stay you're how did I not bring a
shovel to a goddamn treasure hunt map
hunting thing this is what I get for
forgetting everything Jurgen stop
wandering off my guide I've already lost
your brother now down the hole you go
just be a good boy and stay in the hole
here I have a flower don't look at me
like that I'm sorry I have to that's
right well there's another City day
there's another city
all right Jer again don't worry I know
what I'm doing oh yeah ah my boat
where'd my Boca anyone no I feel bad for
uragan hey maybe we can trade with these
people
maybe this city is less lousy than the
other one the city is being under attack
alright then I won't go then okay so now
it would make sense that we just need to
go in this direction at least if you ask
me is it possible that the treasure just
underwater I think that might be a yes
there's what there's light under the
water it's a Santa Claus I can't see I
don't have my glasses oh my god there's
so many cities whoa the map the map is
appearing these days with the ship in
the sand question mark okay let's
remember where we parked our boat
so treasure maps I think I need dark
wood I remember why I need a dark wood
but I think I do
nothing's gonna stop me from getting
this treasure oh god I think it's by the
city well that's perfect I'll just place
torches so I can remember how it's sand
zombies and so aventure deep in the
night this is just like a love thing am
i right my glasses are practically
flying wow what's that okay we need to
cross the street see ya okay oh damn I
swim faster underwater okay we're going
we're getting close gamers what what is
that that's my other nether portal what
that's crazy
what hey he's got a golden arm art stop
stop stupid baby I I will kill a child I
don't care god these ones so what Wow a
rich boy hypebeast okay are i gamers
we're gonna find this treasure if it's
the last thing I'll ever do so I see my
direction right where I'm facing it's
kind hearted this is faced away from it
and this is face towards it let's see
how my orientation skills will pan out
that's what I wanted to do okay should
be somewhere yeah no problem right how
in the gods are am I gonna find this
game a wig yeah yeah Oh looks like Sun
is almost up gamers oh that's me
Wednesday me week is over gave me week
for life oh alright so I need a lot of
dirt oh look at me I got arrows inside
me I need a lot of darts so we can make
an air bubble thing God what if we find
Gucci pains in the treasure that would
be so awesome how do you make an air
listen I don't have time for both people
[Music]
go back to the swamp shrek oh and the
music kicks in at the perfect time and
you're having an epic adventure looking
for minecraft okay so I don't know if
this is the most effective way to do it
knowing myself most no no it is why is
there no scuba equipment in Minecraft
they had nine years to add it my way
what an irony to dig up treasure map we
have to build
that's called a paradox my minecraft
children it actually makes it easier
with sand cuz then I can just drop them
drop them faster minecraft I ain't got
time not I feel like this is the time
where in my audience this is cringing at
me like what is he doing it
listen I don't know okay I'm not
pretending that I know all I do know is
like subscribe for more epic minecraft
okay come on
straight down here should do it okay
let's go gamers hopefully we don't drown
so how do I know how deep it goes
oh I'm drowning I'm drowning I'm
drowning gamers if I didn't could if I
didn't oh god I'm opposite drowning can
I assume in at least smelly must be here
somewhere
maybe just dig deeper question mark my
name is Jeff like where is it
where is it god dammit Jurgen is waiting
for me he's gonna be so pissed dude
maybe I can make an airlock underneath
the water and I will make it easier for
me to just mine
alright dolphin I don't have time for
you my being pranked is it a thing maybe
it's like has to be surface level and
I'm just digging super deep it's harder
to find these math and diamonds okay I
give up I'm starting to think there was
no treasure oh my god but at least we
had fine I'll get them at the llamas are
gone
alright well at least we can explore
what we were gonna do last episode whoa
it's like a pyramid that's awesome can I
go what in the world is that this place
makes zero sense whoa look at these this
time no trash okay here we go
gamers no stepping on traps ok gamer
learned from my mistakes
diamonds oh my god man I run horse armor
your again is gonna be so happy
oh my craft
oh this is better than any treasure the
trip was worth it after all
Oh God Felix maybe you shouldn't be
greedy you literally cannot carry
anything else
okay gamers let's go what if we uragan
starve to death in the hole oh please
please be in the hole please be in oh my
god you're in the hole you're gay yeah
[Music]
did you have a good time I dude I got a
carrot eat the carrot how do I give him
the carrot all right cool
well anyway I have a present for you oh
my god oh my god you look so good your
game you don't mind if I have the carrot
do you thank you what up cows oh my god
what am I gonna do about you I didn't
realize they would get so many alright
I'm making a diamond pickaxe coz we're
gonna go on epic gaming has been [ __ ]
it's crazy how much time you can spend
in this game seriously alright I'm
working on the powered rails guys please
don't judge me so I'm gonna get some
more nether I forgot what it's called
we need to mine more of these which is
always the most fun ever all right we
have obsidian so I want to see what it's
like if you head out in the other
direction because I have leather I have
epic stuff to trade with the villagers
can I kill that thing I don't have an
arrow all right time to make a bridge
[Music]
whoa what is that what is that it like a
frog is it dangerous
hello let me be your friend it's so cute
oh god it's coming towards me safe
distance safe distance I'm gonna kill it
it is decided you're again you will not
believe this sorry you can't commit this
in hundred percent safe I've never done
this okay we're gonna kill the giant
frog thing maybe he just wants to hug me
I'm not gonna faint
yeah hello where'd he go I wanted to
kill it well we'll look at that it whoa
it's so big oh there it is
alright ok alright ok it's a battle of
the battle begins I can't shoot ah this
is bad it's alright I brought don't
panic I brought water buckets it doesn't
work I brought plenty of food I'm ready
maiya you may have done the upper hand
mister quick scope quick scope quick
scope Oh
hit them that was easy dude easy mode
you see that pig alright I'm gonna find
that demon frog now have I mind those I
think I have what are those [ __ ] ass
oh it's over oh it's over not like this
hmm
no yard again you will not believe what
just happened
[Music]
you be quiet
oh god I hit my sheep I've sunk in soul
yeah I lost everything that's epic gamer
rage quit I'm so sick of dying this is
for Jurgen ah ah you can run but you
can't hide it
I'd feel bad if Jurgen wasn't dead that
needs to be suffering in this world so
apparently one block in in the nether
realm is eight blocks in the other round
so if I walk like this I open up
opportunity now hopefully all my stuff
isn't gone I count on maybe some of my
stuff maybe just not all of my stuff
trying to have a PMA over here okay back
to level 4 s oh my god oh yes oh I got
my job okay guys banks oh my god alright
you know what I had a feeling so many of
you have to say it told me that you can
enter a code like a text and then you
won't lose your stuff if you die but I
feel like that beats the purpose alright
we're doing it survival I'm a pro player
okay another thing I read is apparently
if I mine those then I can breathe on
the water
question mark it's the hottest day in UK
I have two lights headed on my face so
the green screen will work why am i
torturing myself okay another thing you
guys told me was to bring up the
brightness oh my god that is so much
nicer see I listened to you guys to buy
do you tell me to do all these awful
things instead we had a trust and that
trust is broken forever
whoa what is this
Cirie's saying fifi feast did I just try
to mine with a melon oh my god you can
I'm mining with a melon brush I keep
mellow meaning
alright let's build our little portal
over here one two this will literally be
the furthest we've ever gone I'm
actually kind of scared plus we're
really low down Oh dog what's gonna
happen dude look how long it's taking
all right gamers I am all gamed out
smash like subscribe for more minecraft
and I see you guys next episode well you
never played super simulator
you know it's fun right I'm not supposed
to give my opinion but give it a try and
then you can tell me if it's good or not
not convinced yet okay I'll cut you a
deal
the game is available for free and
that's a great price
[Music]